(A summer day with the sun
beating down on your head)
I used to practice a lot
on the fourth floor.
This is where I waited.
(The Comedian Association office
located in SBS open hall)
Hey, hurry up and come.
(This place is the cradle
of a lot of comedy shows.)
(Jae Suk in 2002)
(From senior to young comedians,)
(they could do all the comedy skits
they wanted here.)
(Se Chan from 13 years ago)
Turtle and red-crowned crane
(In this place
full of comedians' happy memories,)
(they will have
a general meeting of comedians.)
Gosh, this place is...
Oh, hello.
Hello.
(Stay quiet.)
- Stay quiet.
- Yes, Jae Suk.
Suk Jin, come here.
Come here.
- What?
- I'm Term One.
- I know.
- You're my junior.
- I am, but...
- Why do you think we're here?
- You know we are...
- Today...
- Stay quiet.
- You're my senior,
but you're younger than me.
- What?
- You're younger than me.
But we're here as comedians.
- What's so funny?
- Hello, Suk Jin.
- Why are you laughing?
- We weren't in the same company.
- You're not supposed to laugh now.
- Excuse me.
- I'm sorry.
- I'm teaching him a lesson.
- Don't laugh.
- I'm sorry.
- Wait.
- What?
You're not supposed
to tighten discipline...
among your juniors like that.
- You're tightening discipline.
- What did I do?
- Don't talk back to your senior.
- You stay out of this.
You're not supposed to treat
your senior like that.
What? I'm just trying to get along
with my seniors and juniors.
Anyway, I'll try hard.
Try hard for what? You don't
even know what we're doing.
Since I'm Term Two...
- That's what I was going to say.
- Okay.
Where's our colleague?
- Who?
- Our colleague?
Se Chan's colleague.
Who's Se Chan's colleague?
- Let's call the rookies first.
- Okay.
- Do we have rookie comedians?
- Yes.
We're having rookies today.
- Those guys...
- Are they my juniors?
- I need to teach them a lesson.
- I should...
Suk Jin, I'll give them
a good scolding.
- You should.
- Hey, hurry and come.
He's worked hard for a long time
as the youngest one here.
- I know. Thank you.
- Hey.
- Come running.
- Hurry up and come.
- They're coming.
- Those punks.
- They are so...
- Why aren't they coming?
(Why aren't they coming?)
- I'm sorry.
- But...
- You stay out of this.
- Jae Suk.
As far as I know,
when you worked as a comedian,
you really hated
the seniority system.
I'm the one who got rid of it.
- It's not...
- But I have no choice today.
It's not like you got rid of it.
You just avoided your seniors.
- That's right.
- So you were ditched.
- You were ditched.
- Are you laughing?
Why are you being like this to me?
You're treating me like that
because I'm Term Three.
Hey, will you stay quiet?
Don't pull out his longevity hair.
It's not a longevity hair.
- Don't pull it out.
- I don't have a longevity hair.
Gosh, that's ridiculous.
I should teach the rookies a lesson.
- Hey.
- Hurry up.
- Hey, you chicklings.
- Hurry and come.
You rookies, come running.
Come right here, you rookies.
You punks.
- Hello.
- Come here.
- Hey.
- Are we rookies?
(Term 4: Kim Jong Kook,
Haha, Song Ji Hyo, Jeon So Min)
Hello.
(Disciplined)
You don't have to be so polite.
- Hello.
- Take off your mask.
- Hey, take off your mask. Gosh.
- Hey.
- Okay.
- Hey, take off your mask.
- Hello.
I'm taking off the mask.
We have a term breaker here.
- Hey, stand up.
- Gosh, So Min.
(Hey, stand up.)
- Hey, stand up.
- Gosh, So Min.
- Hey.
- That's not what we do.
This isn't a place like that.
My goodness.
Hey, what happened to your nose?
That's because of the mask.
- It's the mask.
- That's not what we do now.
All right.
- As you can see...
- What are we doing today?
They are the new members
of the Comedian Association.
Do you know
why you're wearing yellow?
- Because we're rookies.
- Exactly.
Make sure you don't ruin
the mood of the meeting today.
(Smiling like a chick)
- Hey.
- I want you to try your best.
- Okay.
- You stay out of this.
(You stay out of this.)
(A punch in the stomach)
Don't meddle in.
- Don't step up.
- Stay out of this.
- Hang on.
- I said, don't meddle in.
This is what we should do.
- Se Chan.
- Do you have a problem?
- You should get a penalty.
- Why did you...
- He looks into your eyes.
- You make eye contact with me?
Can't I?
- Are you good at fighting?
- Yes, I am.
My gosh.
We don't have a good fighter here.
- Really?
- Yes. We rarely fight.
Hey, when it comes to fighting...
What did you do before
becoming a comedienne?
I worked at a cafe.
I heard that
you had a boyfriend before.
But you're not seeing anyone, right?
Yes. Oh, right.
And I heard you devoted yourself
to taking care of your boyfriend.
That's not true. I've never
had a boyfriend before.
- My gosh.
- Excuse me,
but you don't have to do this.
- That's... She has bad habits.
- You shouldn't...
- That's a bad habit.
- She learned weird stuff.
And I've never had
a girlfriend before.
- Why?
- That's enough.
I'll punch you in the stomach.
- Stay quiet.
- You can punch him when I hold him.
All right, So Min.
What did you do before?
I studied abroad.
(I studied abroad.)
- Hey.
- Again?
You should stop saying
that you studied abroad.
- Where did you study?
- To be a comedian...
What did you do before? Gosh.
You look so cute in the picture.
- Pardon?
- You look really cute.
This is from Yeong Ja's bus.
That's a long time ago.
- When was that?
- Only top stars can get on the bus.
("Yeong Ja's Golden Days",
November, 1995)
(He was only 19.)
With your eyes open wide.
(Straining his eyes)
Open them wide. Start.
(He had cute snake eyes
25 years ago.)
(Sending a message to his mom)
Send a message to your classmates.
Say your school and class. Start.
(My classmates from Grade 12,
Class 9 of Shinsung High School!)
(I'm on TV.
I said I would be on TV.)
(Jong Kook was on Yeong Ja's bus
at the age of 19.)
Isn't he Term One's senior?
- That was a long time ago.
- Yeong Ja's bus.
Have you been on Yeong Ja's bus?
No.
Only top stars could join the show.
- Is it "That's it. All right?"
- Yes.
- Well...
- My gosh.
Only top stars could
join the show back then.
- Did you really do that?
- I did it in this very building.
- You look really cute.
- "That's it. All right."
- I look cute, don't I?
So what did you do before?
I was a bully.
- A bully?
- I was released two days ago.
I was released two days ago.
Don't feel small.
- It's not like that.
- I'll take care of him.
- What did you say?
- Go ahead and deal with him.
I'm not going. He should come to me.
Why would I go to him?
- Wait.
- What?
You two can go outside
together for a while.
You can go.
- No.
- Go ahead.
- Just go.
- Okay. I'll go with him.
- Bye.
- See you.
Hang on.
- I don't have to go.
- Okay.
- Let's just go.
- Jong Kook.
- Yes?
- Take him to Seoul for sightseeing.
That's a good idea.
I'll take you to Seoul.
In 1, 2, and 3.
(He feels dizzy
after the sightseeing.)
All right. Let him
go sightseeing to Seoul.
- He just went sightseeing in Seoul.
- Okay.
It's so convenient
to have him around.
You can go sightseeing
to Seoul right away.
- All right, guys.
- Yes.
So we just met the members
from Term Four.
And you have a colleague
who's from Term Three.
- I called him.
- Your colleague.
- I have a colleague.
- Where is he?
Love your colleague and love your
country. Come on out, my friend!
- Love your colleague.
- His colleague?
- Hello.
- Hey, Yong Jin.
He's Term Three. He's my colleague.
They are our seniors.
(He's Se Chan's best friend
from Term 3.)
(He made his debut on "People
Looking for a Laugh" in 2005.)
(He spent his youth
in this open hall with Se Chan.)
(He looks like a tiring
and demanding senior.)
He brought coffee for the seniors.
This is for the seniors.
Hey, you should watch and learn.
He walks with a swagger though.
What is this? I want something weak.
- This is weak.
- This is a multigrain shake.
There's nothing for us.
- I'll have a multigrain shake.
- I want a multigrain shake.
- Do you have anything for us?
- Is she our junior?
- Yes, she is.
- She's...
- Excuse me.
Don't you see us here?
Is he our junior?
- He used to be a bully.
- I see.
They are our seniors.
You have big shoulders.
I like them.
He was a bully.
Is the picture someone else
with the same name?
I see. It looks good.
- Let's have a seat.
- Okay.
- Let's sit.
- Everyone's here.
I'll sit here.
Okay. Sit there.
I haven't been here for a long time.
It's been ten years.
(Staring)
What are you looking at?
(He forgot about his character.)
Suk Jin.
If you keep doing that, we will
have to treat you the same way.
You can't talk to me like that.
The situation is...
- The cameras are still on.
- They are on.
We were taking a break.
- Did he talk down to you again?
- Yes.
(Shaking his head)
Hey.
Hey, you...
Pardon?
You stay out of this. Hey.
- Yes?
- He's not good at skits.
You keep looking into my eyes.
- Where am I supposed to look at?
- Yong Jin is...
- Avoid my eyes.
- Avoid?
I've been here only for
a few minutes,
but I can tell
who the weakest one is here.
It's so obvious.
(He's done identifying
the weakest one here.)
- You know who's weak here.
- I do. You don't have to tell me.
Hey, I guess you don't know it well.
I can barely feel his touch.
He's so weak.
He's like a cat.
- What happened to your face?
- What?
You have black powder on your cheek.
Where do we have black powder here?
You got it when you took
Suk Jin to Seoul for sightseeing.
- You look like Rambo.
- Where is it?
- It's on your cheek.
- My gosh.
(The black powder
on Jong Kook's cheek is from...)
He looks like Rambo.
(He was taking his senior
to Seoul for sightseeing.)
(And he got the powder
on his cheek.)
(He was sitting there for a while
with the black powder on.)
Where is it?
I thought he was injured.
This is hilarious.
- It's so funny.
- I can't believe this.
I like your black powder joke.
Your black powder joke
is really funny.
- Excuse me, Suk Jin.
- What?
What term are you in
for black powder?
I'm from Term One.
- Term One?
- Yes.
I guess Myung Soo is his colleague.
- Myung Soo is my colleague.
- He's from Term One.
- That's funny.
- All right then.
What do we do now?
Will you open the safe behind you?
This one?
(There's a safe
for the association membership fee.)
(Jae Suk from Term 1
opens the safe.)
Do you know the code, Jae Suk?
It's open.
- Why?
- What?
There's a mission card.
(There's no money
but a message in the safe.)
"My dear fellow comedians."
"I need some quick cash,
so I'm taking..."
"the association membership fee
of 4,000 dollars."
"I'll spend the money
on good causes."
"Special term comedian,
Lee Kwang Soo?"
(Special Term Comedian,
Lee Kwang Soo)
"Special term comedian,
Lee Kwang Soo?"
It was Kwang Soo.
(Did Kwang Soo take the membership
fee of 4,000 dollars?)
He did it again.
He took the money.
He took 4,000 dollars?
- There's news.
- The news is on.
(There's breaking news delivered
to the Comedian Association.)
This is news that's just come in.
There was a robbery in the office...
of the Unofficial
Comedian Association...
where Yoo Jae Suk is the president.
What?
(There was a robbery!)
The amount stolen is...
four thousand dollars, which is for
the rent of the Association office.
On the basis of the evidence,
the police say...
the 2m-tall comedian...
Lee Kwang Soo is the suspect.
(Suspect Lee Kwang Soo)
- Lee Kwang Soo is the suspect.
- My goodness.
- It's been a while.
- Did Kwang Soo leave our show?
The police checked
the CCTV footage...
and found out that Lee Kwang Soo
stole the money in the safe.
(Did Kwang Soo
take 4,000 dollars...)
It turns out he bought
seven expensive gifts...
including a shirt, a bag,
and speakers.
So that's how
he bought all the gifts?
(Now the truth behind
the expensive gifts is revealed.)
He's a jerk!
That's how he got us the gifts.
(The gifts were too expensive
for a stingy guy like him.)
(And there's another message
in the safe.)
"Reminder."
"Your association has defaulted in
paying the rent of 4,000 dollars."
"We'd like you to pay the rent
by 4 p.m. today."
"If you fail to pay it off,
under the terms of the contract,"
"two of the comedians will
have to pay the balance."
"July 6, 2021, Creditor SBS."
"Debtor the Unofficial
Comedian Association."
Gosh, what is this?
All right.
As you just saw
the reminder and news,
you were supposed to pay
the rent of this office yesterday.
But you failed to pay it...
because Kwang Soo stole your
membership fee of 4,000 dollars.
- Oh no.
- What do we do?
But according to Article 3 Clause 47
of the Comedian Association Rules,
the members should be divided
into Team Senior and Team Junior...
and pay half of the rent each.
If the two teams
pay 2,000 dollars each...
by four o'clock today,
all the comedians won't
get a penalty.
But if only one of the teams
manages to pay,
one member of the team that failed
to pay will get a penalty.
If both teams fail to pay,
one member
from each team will get a penalty.
I don't think we can pay it today.
I'll tell you
how to collect the money.
After a mission, the winning team
and the losing team...
will choose a debit card.
Each card has
different amounts of money,
and the cards for the winning team
have more money in them.
You will go...
to the ATM with a card you picked.
Once you complete the mission,
you can withdraw the money.
(They can withdraw money
if they complete their mission.)
Let's try the first withdrawal then.
(It's time
for the first withdrawal.)
According to
the Comedian Association Rules,
for the first withdrawal,
seniors will be the winning team,
and juniors will be the losing team.
- And now you will choose a card.
- Okay.
- The winning team gets ten cards,
and the losing team
gets eight cards.
(10 cards for the winning team
and 8 cards for the losing team)
There are cards that have 100
to 800 dollars for the losing team.
And for the winning team, there are
cards with 100 to 1,000 dollars.
We can pick 800 dollars.
And...
we need leaders for each team.
These two seniors
will be the leaders first.
And you can pick two leaders here.
The leaders will pick a card each,
and they will scratch the back
of their cards to see the amount.
(They will scratch the card
to see the amount.)
But it's not that...
you get the amount right away.
- You see the ATMs here.
- Right.
You will go to the ATMs...
and answer quizzes there.
- Quizzes?
- Then you can get the amount...
(They should answer a quiz
to get the amount on the card.)
(Quiz?)
on the card.
- That means we won't get the money.
- My gosh.
- What is Yong Jin like?
- What do you think of Yong Jin?
He's no different
from the Empty Heads.
- That's not true.
- But...
he reads a lot.
- I read a lot.
- He does read a lot.
But he doesn't have good knowledge.
I know things like the four
precious things of the study.
Do you know the four
precious things of the study?
I do.
- What are the four precious things?
- I know the word, "treacherous".
- Do you know "treacherous"?
- Yes.
I know a lot of idioms.
And I'm conversant
with the stock market.
Can you spell umbrella?
U.
- Go ahead.
- You watched the episode.
- U, B...
- U?
- U and B?
B comes after U?
I mean it has a U and a B.
- What comes after U?
- Don't ask me.
Suk Jin, you don't have to do this.
Just tell me what comes after the U.
- It also has an R in it.
- Okay.
- So what comes after the U?
- Why are you being like this?
Tell me what the next letter is.
Hang on.
- Suk Jin.
- My gosh.
- What?
- Stand up.
- What did I do?
- Hang on.
- The juniors are watching.
- When we're with others...
Why do you try to humiliate
your junior around others?
- Is it my fault?
- Is an umbrella that important?
- Hey, is it my bad?
- Hey, Jong Kook.
- Did you work out?
- Yes.
Please help Seok Sam...
- run up the stairs.
- Come on out.
- No.
- This is...
what my senior asked me.
Hey.
It's been "Three Meals for Jae Suk"
for the past few weeks.
(What the members hate the most...)
(is the combination
of Yoo Jae Suk and Kim Jong Kook.)
(He's Lord Yoo's guard
who stands up for his tyranny.)
"Three Meals for Jae Suk"
never ends.
(Lord Yoo and Servant Kim
show up every week.)
- Did you meet Jong Kook in private?
- No, I didn't.
Why would I meet him?
How could he...
Keep running.
- Why is an umbrella so important?
- My point.
U-M...
B-R-E-L-L-A.
- Hey.
- Umbrella.
- She knows it.
- Look at Se Chan.
Your boyfriend seems happy.
(Shush!)
(She encourages false rumors.)
(She wants everyone to know
about her secret relationship.)
Strict discipline.
(The march ends.)
- Strict discipline.
- Well done.
(Seok Sam is back after the
running with the drill instructor.)
- Thank you.
- My pleasure.
Well done.
"Three Meals for Jae Suk"
never ends.
When is it going to end?
How many seasons are there?
- Pull yourself together.
- Okay. It was my bad.
- We should respect each other.
- It's B that comes after U.
- Yes.
- Have a seat.
So we have two seniors here.
Who will go first in this team?
Ji Hyo goes first.
Will the person who picks a card
answer the question?
Yes, she will.
But you all will have to
do it at least once.
- Just decide who goes first.
- You should mix them well.
When I made my wish yesterday,
I didn't say how many times.
(So Min got her wish granted
in the last episode.)
(Tell me the answers to quizzes and
make it look like I got it myself.)
So Min, you shouldn't
use your wish for this.
My wish is too good
to use for this though.
- You think?
- You should give it a try.
Just use it.
She wants to use it
for one-on-one games.
It's too good for this, So Min.
What is this thing?
- What?
- Oh, it's sigma.
All of a sudden...
Why are you saying that
all of a sudden?
They sometimes have
the same problems.
Can we pick a card first?
Pick a card,
and go to the ATM with it.
There will be a quiz.
We have to answer the quiz
to get the money.
If you answer the quiz, we will
give you the amount of money.
But, if you fail,
you can try again. You can enter
the code up to three times.
It's possible.
But the amount will be halved.
(If they give a wrong answer,
the amount will be halved.)
We have to keep trying.
So you have two extra chances.
That means we should pick
a card with big money.
It will be great
if we pick 100 dollars, right?
Then you can get
at least 25 dollars.
- Exactly.
- That's right.
Now, I want the two leaders
of each team to pick a card...
and scratch the back.
Can I give it to another member?
No, you can't.
- Who should do it? So Min?
- So Min.
- So Min and Ji Hyo will do it?
- Ji Hyo, will you do it?
Should I pick first?
What do you say?
- You go first, Jong Kook.
- Go ahead, Jong Kook.
I'll pick one in the middle row.
I choose this.
- Let's check.
- Good. I thought of choosing that.
- Really?
- Yes, I picked it at first.
- Start from the corner.
- I got 300 dollars.
- Not bad.
- Gosh.
- Let me check.
- Okay.
- I got 300 dollars.
- Not bad.
(So Min obtained a 100 dollar card.)
How much? 100 dollars?
- That's a shame.
- You got the lowest amount?
- If it's a 100 dollar card...
- Oh, my. It's 1,000 dollars!
- One thousand dollars?
- It's 1,000 dollars.
- See? I said I had a good feeling.
(They're making such a fuss.)
- It's 1,000 dollars.
- No, it's 100 dollars.
(One hundred dollars)
- One hundred dollars?
- See?
- Is 100 dollars the lowest amount?
- One hundred dollars...
- Gosh. Out of all these cards...
- I said I had a good feeling.
- You should do better than that.
- I got a 300 dollar card.
- Oh, yes. I got 800 dollars.
- That's great.
- Oh, my.
- That's so great.
- See? I told you.
- The lowest is 100 dollars.
Why did you pick a 100 dollar card
out of all these cards?
Jong Kook, how did you pick that
There will be a new set of cards
in each round.
- Oh, really?
- I see.
- Okay.
- Oh, gosh.
Then can we go now?
All four of you
picked a card, right?
You must put this on
since you all get the same question.
- We all receive the same question?
- Although it's only 100 dollars...
Oh, it's not that?
I really should get it right.
Could it be very difficult?
Jong Kook, you've got this.
Get the right answer no matter what
even if you fail in three attempts.
I trust you, Jae Suk.
Gosh, I'm nervous.
Okay.
How does this work?
(To withdraw cash,
insert your card into the machine.)
"To withdraw cash..." I get it.
Here we go.
- Oh, here. Should I put it in here?
- You shouldn't just put it in.
(He put in the 100 dollar card
that he just obtained.)
(To withdraw cash,
insert your card into the machine.)
(To withdraw the balance,
solve the following quiz.)
(Write the meaning of the following
Gyeongsang Province dialect.)
("I'll kickya witma foot.")
Goodness. What's this?
(The 1st question)
Oh, gosh.
This isn't an easy question.
(All the quizzes are related
to Korean and foreign languages.)
(Jae Suk, 300 dollars, So Min, 100,
Suk Jin, 100, Jong Kook, 800)
- Oh, no. What should I do?
- What's with this notepad?
(Jae Suk, 300 dollars, So Min, 100,
Suk Jin, 100, Jong Kook, 800)
(Translate the following
dialect expression.)
(Since they have never heard
the expression before,)
(they're thinking hard
to figure it out.)
("I'll kickya witma foot"?)
"Remove one cue card..."
(Jae Suk starts writing the answer
after thinking hard.)
- Oh, should I remove this?
- This?
Does it come out once I remove it?
- That's right.
- Does it come out right away?
(I will kick you with my foot.)
Is it not the right answer?
(Correct.
You will receive 300 dollars.)
Okay!
Oh, I think...
(Jae Suk withdrew 300 dollars.)
(Jae Suk succeeded in the 1st try
and got all 300 dollars.)
Wait. It's confusing.
What... What should I do?
(Correct.
You will receive 800 dollars.)
Oh, my. Hold on a second.
(Jong Kook also succeeded
and got 800 dollars!)
(The Term 1 senior member returned
with 300 dollars.)
- I knew it. That's Term One.
- Did you succeed?
Of course.
(Elated and proud)
- Okay!
- Did you get the right answer?
All right! I knew you'd succeed.
He's good at everything
that's related to kicking.
Okay!
- Good job. You got 800 dollars?
- You see...
- Yes, I got 800 dollars.
- Nice.
- Great job.
- Okay.
He's close friends with gangsters
from Gyeongsang Province, you know.
I'm going to kick you with my foot.
(Meanwhile, in the bank...)
(Big Nose is struggling.)
(He wrote down something.)
(I'll kick you with my shoes off.)
(I will kill you.)
(Incorrect. Try the next question.)
Is it incorrect?
(Suk Jin: 100 dollars,
So Min: 100 dollars)
(Half has been deducted.)
I think...
Next question.
(He failed to get the lowest amount
and even lost half of it.)
(Write the accurate name
of the object in the picture.)
What's this?
Oh, that... It's confusing.
(Kelp noodle)
The two of them are solving
the second question.
What's the question?
- Is it shredded radish?
- No, it's not radish.
The thing that you see
at a sashimi restaurant.
- Kelt noodle.
- No, it's not kelt noodle.
- It's kelf noodle.
- Jellyfish?
- No.
- Gosh.
- Is it correct?
(Kelt noodel)
(She even misspelled "noodle.")
- This is what So Min wrote.
- Isn't this correct?
(Empty Head's incorrect answer makes
everyone laugh at her.)
I'm worried about So Min.
I give up. I have no idea.
(Suk Jin: 50 dollars)
I give up.
I'll try the next question.
(Write the accurate English title
of "Running Man.")
"Write
the accurate English title..."
(Write the accurate English title
of "Running Man.")
(The easiest question that shows
how they look down on the cast.)
All right.
I know the answer.
(Following the confident Suk Jin,
So Min also wrote the right answer.)
- Okay! Did you get it right?
- Okay.
- You know...
- Good job. I knew it.
Did you come back out
after spelling "Running Man?"
- Running Man!
- I was even confused...
whether there should be
1 or 2 Ns in "running".
To tell you the truth.
(So Min reacted
just as the staff expected.)
- They're so mean.
- That's the intention of the staff.
- You tried to make me look stupid.
- No, we didn't.
As a result, Jong Kook and Jae Suk
with the most seniority...
- in their teams succeeded at once.
- I'm relieved.
- Great.
- I knew it.
Jong Kook got 800 dollars,
and Jae Suk got 300 dollars.
- We won.
- Hey...
- Did you pick an 800 dollar card?
- Yes, I did.
He picked an 800 dollar card.
Both So Min and Suk Jin succeeded
on the third level...
and gained 25 dollars.
That's good.
- She succeeded.
- Great job.
The preliminary round is over.
We'll begin the first mission now.
What's this?
What's going on?
What's this? I guess
we'll be pouring water on one other.
I think it's flour.
It is flour?
- Is it not water?
- Oh, it's flour.
(Gourd bowls and flour are
essential props for comedians.)
Everyone, gather around!
- Term Two!
- Gather around!
(The Term 1 senior member gathered
his junior members.)
- We should bend over backward.
- What's going on?
- Take your hand out of your pocket.
- Stand straight!
Take your hand out of your pocket.
(He gets most excited
when he scolds his junior comedian.)
You can put your bags down
for a while.
- Okay.
- Yes.
We're all so obedient.
We all listen to him.
- Yes, sir.
- Got it.
- You don't have to do it to me.
- Yes, we should, sir.
This is the difference
between a director and cast members.
The seniority among us
doesn't matter.
Sir, why don't we eat together
sometime?
The first mission where you can
show off your slapstick skills is...
Flour Marionette.
"Marionette?"
Three of the team members hold
a gourd bowl.
One of them sits on the chair.
Another sits on the floor,
and the last one lies down
with the bowl on the belly.
- I see.
- On the belly?
The remaining member of the team
will move flour to the bowls...
with both of the arms
tied to those ropes.
It sounds simple.
The total weight of the flour
in the bowls will decide the winner.
The flour in the farthest bowl
will be tripled,
and the flour
in the second farthest bowl...
will be doubled.
(The farther the bowl with flour is,
the better chance they have to win.)
However, the opponent team members
will sit on both sides...
and pull ropes that are
tied to the wrists.
- Of course, it wouldn't be easy.
- We should pull it hard.
We won't be able to move ahead.
Oh, no. We won't be able to put
any flour in our bowls.
We can win this.
There will be two rounds,
and the team with more flour
will win.
You have to decide
which team will go first.
They'll go first.
- Junior comedians always go first.
- They're juniors.
- Am I right, sir?
- Why? Sir.
- All right.
- Why is that?
We'll go first.
- Pardon?
- You're awesome, sir!
- He's taking the lead as always.
- Why should we go first?
- As their senior comedians.
- Exactly. We'll go first.
- Let's decide the positions.
- Okay.
The flour that the lying one has
will be tripled, sir.
- Really?
- Yes, that's the best spot.
- Then he should take the position.
- Then...
- As your junior comedians, we'll...
- Right.
- Then you guys lie down.
- Pardon me?
- You two lie down.
- But only one of us...
- No.
- You two lie down.
We'll lie down
as your senior comedians.
- My, he's so cool.
- Of course.
- Sir, you're awesome!
- Indeed.
Sir, you're so cool.
- You're respected for a reason.
- Gosh, seriously.
Why would you keep making
your juniors do the hard work?
- That's not my intention.
- Then why...
- They should be in that position.
- Are you willing to get floured?
Then you'll get...
both black and white powder
on your hair.
- Black and white powder?
- Hey.
- You'll get white powder too?
- You'll look like Cruella.
- Hey, don't be cheeky.
- He'll look like Cruella.
- That's okay.
- Understood?
He's okay. He and I served
in the same military unit.
- I adore him.
- We served in the same unit.
- Yes, we served in the ROK Navy.
- Suk Jin.
- We both served in the ROK Navy.
- Yes? Why?
- We're not in the military.
- We served in the same unit.
- That doesn't matter here.
- This won't work. Jong Kook.
- Come with me.
- Show him the stairs.
- Let's go.
- Why won't you listen to me?
- Come on.
- Let's go.
- Hey.
- Start with your left foot.
- Okay.
How many more times will we do
"Three Meals for Jae Suk?"
- Strict discipline.
- Good. I like this.
- Shouldn't three times be enough?
- He should get it together now.
- But he doesn't seem to do so.
- Why? He's so stubborn.
- What is wrong with him?
- Strict discipline.
(Seok jin came back looking pale
after getting disciplined.)
Okay. Good.
- Strict discipline.
- Look at his face.
- He's improved.
- Stop. In 1, 2.
- Stop.
(He does well now.)
- I'm back, sir.
- Good job.
- Thank you, sir.
- He can do it well now.
- I will get floured.
- He pulled himself together.
- It worked.
- Suk Jin, you take that position.
- Yes, sir.
- You take the lying position.
- The weight will be tripled.
I feel heavy responsibility, sir.
How about I sit here instead?
- Then you sit here.
- Here? Can I?
- I'll take this position.
- Okay.
- Shall I scoop and move flour?
- Yes, you do that.
- Yong Jin, you sit here.
- Do I sit here?
- Hey, Se Chan.
- Yes?
- Overcome it.
- Yes, I'll overcome it.
Especially when So Min pulls it,
you should...
The tether between you and me
(The tether between you and me)
(She's simply excited
about being tethered to him.)
- This is the sound inside of us
- My gosh.
The one on this side clearly looks
like a rope.
Then why does the other one look
like a metal chain?
- It looks scary.
- Right?
- Yes, it looks like a metal chain.
- I can see that.
Isn't Jong Kook pulling too much?
Hey, stop.
I'm holding the rope
just as the rule allows.
- I never go against any rules.
- I know.
- Get ready, everyone.
- Let's do this.
- Let's say a chant.
- Should I lower the bowl?
Yes, please lower it for me.
- Suk Jin.
- Yes?
- Shout a chant.
- Put it over your head.
When I say, "We win",
you say, "no matter what".
- Gosh, you.
- Where's your sense of humor?
- Suk Jin.
- You don't like it?
- That chant is so lame.
- I'll come up with something else.
That's not cool in this era.
"We win no matter what"?
That's what people hate the most
these days.
- Then what?
- JRS!
- What does JRS stand for?
(No one has heard
the chant "JRS" before.)
Just like a robot and steel!
(Just like a robot and steel!)
(What?)
That's funny.
Just like a robot!
- What's that?
- Just like steel!
Let's be as strong as a robot
and steel!
- Understood?
- Understood, sir!
- Yes, sir!
- Say "JRS"!
- Let's go with "JRS".
- JRS!
- That's a funny chant.
- My, that's so funny.
- That's our team chant.
- JRS!
- Just like a robot and steel.
And steel.
(They finished getting ready
with the JRS mindset.)
- We can do this.
- Be strong.
- Got it?
- I'll be strong, sir.
- Understood, everyone?
- Yes, sir!
- We're ready.
- Let's go!
Ready.
(They begin the 100-second mission
with a mindset of steel.)
(He's ready to be strong enough
to scoop flour.)
(No extra points,
double score, triple score)
(Jong Kook and So Min started
pulling Se Chan's arms.)
Throw it now.
- Oh, my gosh.
- Throw it.
- Throw it now.
- Oh, my gosh.
(It's not easy to put the flour
in the bowl.)
Come on. Throw it.
(Covered with flour)
- Hey, throw it.
- I'll focus on my left arm.
You have no other way.
Just throw it as hard as you can.
- I'll focus on my left arm.
- Hey, throw it.
- Hey!
- Se Chan!
Hey! JRS! Remember it!
What is Jong Kook doing?
Just like a robot!
It's not against the rule.
Put it in the bowl here.
It's a shame that I have to wait
to watch this on TV.
Put it in this bowl.
Throw it!
- Hey!
- Gosh. Darn it.
(The white powder festival)
Throw it.
(Unlike what he expected,
Jae Suk is covered with flour.)
- Throw it.
- Jae Suk.
- JRS!
- Just like a robot!
- Just like a robot and steel!
Just like a robot!
(Time's up.)
- Gosh. That was so hard.
- I got a lot in my bowl.
- Gosh.
- All right. Time's up.
(The team collected quite a lot
with the JRS mindset.)
- We got more than we expected.
- Indeed.
Exactly.
- Please pour it into this bowl.
- I got some in my bowl.
- I got some too.
- That's right.
- We'll weigh it separately.
- Let's weigh Jae Suk's first.
- We got some despite that.
- It was really hard.
It was no joke.
Pour it all.
True. Suk Jin got flour
only on his nose.
Let me take a look.
(The player from Team Junior is
Jong Kook, an athletic comedian.)
- My goodness.
- Don't pull it yet.
I tried pulling it,
but he wouldn't even budge.
- Are you doing a chest workout?
- Yes.
This is nice. Hold it tightly.
Still, Jong Kook,
I'm a young, healthy man.
I know.
(The young, healthy man is
playing with the rope frivolously.)
Could the rope snap?
No, it won't snap.
(Acting up)
(He disappeared.)
(An urgent meeting
has been arranged.)
Come on, Jong Kook.
You should've given me a heads-up.
What was that? Enough is enough.
- "Enough is enough."
- Oh, boy.
Don't go overboard.
- Were you dragged all the way here?
- That was scary.
You should at least give me
a heads-up.
It's amazing that he can be dragged
that far.
- We'll begin now.
- Yes.
- Here we go.
- Ready.
- Don't hold there. That's good.
- Hold it.
Get set. You shouldn't hold that.
Don't let him scoop any flour.
(The young, healthy man and Mr. JRS
will fight against Jong Kook.)
- That's good.
- Don't cross the red line.
(The fitness YouTuber grits
his teeth and stands up.)
(He started pouring flour
into the bowl.)
No, wait. Pull it when he stands up.
That's good.
(The healthy man interferes
Jong Kook.)
I'm a healthy man just like you.
Here we go.
(I'm a healthy man just like you.
Here we go.)
- Great. Keep going.
- Here we go.
(Mr. JRS is trying his best too.)
- That's good.
- Great. Let's do this.
(Shouting)
- Jong Kook can't scoop any.
- That's right.
He can't scoop any flour.
- He can't seem to do it.
- Gosh, you.
(Gosh, you.)
(Jong Kook began showing off
his strength.)
- Hurry up and go back.
- No.
(Jong Kook began showing off
his strength.)
Pull it.
(They succeeded in irritating
Jong Kook.)
(Jae Suk and Yong Jin are
shouting.)
- He can't scoop any.
- Hurry up!
- Jong Kook can't do it.
- He can't do it.
He can't do it.
(Mr. JRS got so excited.)
Stop him.
- Stop him.
- Don't come here.
(The 2nd urgent meeting)
(The young, healthy man was
dragged helplessly again.)
Where are you? Hurry up!
(Time is passing by
even at this moment.)
Hey, don't...
Jong Kook, Ji Hyo got no flour
in her bowl.
- Jong Kook, where are you?
- Pull it.
(The healthy man and Mr. JRS are
keeping him from moving.)
Pull it. Don't let him
scoop any flour.
Are you exercising?
- Okay!
- What?
- What was that?
- It was our first try.
(So Min and Ji Hyo's bowls
are empty.)
- I think it was...
- I can't believe this.
- What's this? My bowl is empty.
- Gosh, seriously.
That was funny.
Haha, you can pour it.
- I have too little.
- You tripled my score, right?
- Yes.
- Only Haha got flour in his bowl.
So Min's bowl is almost empty.
I mean... Our bowls are empty.
So Min has no flour.
We should've looked
just as they did.
Now...
- I'll announce the result.
- Okay.
Team Junior collected more flour,
but Team Senior won
since they got more extra points.
(Team Senior won
with the tripled score.)
- I knew it.
- We're senior comedians.
Right. The person in the front...
- I guess...
- How did this happen?
I think they got more flour
in the farthest bowl.
It was fun to see Jong Kook's arm
moving as I pulled the rope.
- Right?
- As the person pulling the rope.
- It was fun to see him move.
- It feels good.
I could see that he got flustered.
I got so excited.
- It feels good.
- I defeated only one arm.
- Then why am I so excited?
- It's fun.
It's funny.
- We'll begin the final round.
- Okay.
Come here.
- Suk Jin, will you scoop flour?
- Yes.
- The strong Suk Jin will do it.
- Really?
- We're leading the game, you know.
- I see.
- Suk Jin will do it?
- The strong Suk Jin will do it.
- Yong Jin, cover your head.
- I'm okay.
(So Min gave him a bowl.)
Hey, come over here.
- Why?
- Look at this.
(There's a hole in the bowl.)
- Hey... My gosh.
- Why?
- Are you kidding?
- What is it?
I can see through the hole.
(Earlier on)
(She put a hole in their bowls
without letting them know.)
(Then she gave the bowls to them
playing innocent.)
(But she got caught right away.)
Are you kidding?
- Hey...
- That's too visible.
- Did you think I'd be fooled?
- Come on.
Do you think we're stupid?
- Hey, do you think we're stupid?
- My gosh. Frog.
Bring me another bowl, Frog.
(Shouting)
(The veteran comedian is
psyching himself up.)
That's great. Keep going, Suk Jin,
the strong man.
- He looks so weak.
- He looks like a grandpa, right?
He looks cute.
- That's enough.
- I'll hold it like this and...
(He's wasting his energy
to make himself look cool.)
This reminds me of quartering
in a period drama.
- Show us what you've got, Suk Jin.
- Let's do this.
The strong Suk Jin!
Let's begin. Ready.
Put the flour in here.
It'll be tripled.
(Their 100 seconds started.)
It's not so easy to put flour
in the front bowl.
(It's important to aim to put flour
in Yong Jin's bowl.)
(The strong Suk Jin
grits his teeth.)
That's good.
(He's shouting loudly, but...)
Go, Suk Jin.
He's just shouting.
- The strong Suk Jin.
- Go, Suk Jin!
- Go, Suk Jin.
- The strong Suk Jin.
- The strong Suk Jin!
- Suk Jin!
- Come on. Cheer up, Suk Jin.
- The strong Suk Jin!
- Go, Suk Jin.
- Your bowls are almost empty.
Come on, Suk Jin.
The strong Suk Jin is
moving to the right.
- He's mine!
- No, he's mine!
(They're fighting over Big Nose.)
I like him more than you do.
- He's mine.
- Suk Jin.
- Come on. What are you doing?
- He's mine.
Suk Jin is so adorable.
You know, I can even make
eye contact with him.
He lets them drag him around.
- Please!
- The strong Suk Jin!
What are you doing, Suk Jin?
Gosh, seriously. What was that?
He looked like a zombie tied up
in a zombie movie.
(He's exhausted
after getting covered in flour.)
- Gosh, the strong Suk Jin.
- You try it.
It's just impossible.
This is the final round.
It's Team Junior's turn.
Let So Min pour the flour.
So Min, you do it.
- Me?
- Aren't you strong?
- No, Ji Hyo should do it.
- Yes, I really am strong.
She's Suk Jin's rival.
Exactly. You should do it.
I'll show you that I can do
better than my rival did.
Oh, really?
- It's hard to put it in there.
- True.
It requires much more energy.
- Gosh, Jae Suk.
- Why?
- How could you put a hole in it?
What's this? How are we supposed
to play the game with this?
Hang on. This is too much.
Come on, Jae Suk.
- I understand that you're anxious,
- Is it a mask or what?
but we can't use this.
Why did you...
- What is this?
- Hey...
Play jokes like this
when you're at home.
- Gosh, seriously.
- We can see your face through it.
I mean we can't use it. Seriously.
You should've at least
done it quietly.
- I mean...
- Come on.
Call me Super So Min.
- Go, Super So Min.
- That's good.
You'll win if you just collect
as much as you did earlier.
- Okay.
- That's good to know.
Right. We got so little flour.
First, try to put some
in Haha's bowl in the beginning.
- She won't put any in the bowls.
- Me?
- You're wrong.
- I know.
Ready.
(Here goes Super So Min.)
I knew it.
(They can turn the game around
if they collect as much as before.)
Call me Super So Min.
Okay.
(Fluttering)
(Swaying)
- So Min.
- Super So Min.
The game has begun.
(So Min, the game has begun.)
So Min.
(She won't be pouring flour
any time soon.)
Super So Min!
(Fluttering)
(Giggling)
Super...
- Super...
- You should put it into the bowl.
- You should, but you can't do it.
(You should, but you can't do it.)
- You can't do it.
- You should put it into the bowl.
Super So Min!
- How foolish.
(The crazy coachman)
- What an idiot.
- An idiot.
(Suk Jin gets his energy back
and pulls again.)
So Min!
Super...
Super So Min!
I bet you can't do it.
You can't do it.
Hey, wait!
(She obtains the bucket.)
(Wild horse So Min
looks to tip the bucket instead.)
You can't do it.
(The crazy horseman
keeps tugging at the reins.)
You won't be able to do that either.
Stop trying.
That's impossible to do.
You won't be able to do that either.
(Super So Min now causes mayhem.)
Hey, that's cheating!
- You can't do that.
- I can't?
So Min going crazy
is absolutely hilarious.
You've already cheated.
Super...
So Min!
- So Min.
- Super...
Super!
- Super!
Super So Min!
- So Min...
- Do you even know how to spell it?
(Do you even know
how to spell "super?")
It's S, U, P, E, R.
(He attacks her with her weakness.)
That's how you spell "super."
So Min's mad.
She's...
(She takes it out
on those watching instead.)
She's causing mayhem again!
She's going wild.
- She's going wild.
- So Min...
(Flour bombs!)
Suk Jin, don't!
- Suk Jin, don't!
- Pull it.
(The bucket is used as a helmet
to block the flour.)
As if that's possible.
(While the relentless Super So Min
attacks them with flour...)
- I lost our grip at the end.
- Yes, near the end.
I have some in mine though.
They made me so angry.
- Especially Yong Jin, right?
- Yes.
You fool.
The spelling of "super?"
(What hurt the most
was him asking her the spelling.)
Do you know how to spell it?
- I can't believe it.
- It's harder than it looks, right?
It's nearly impossible.
If you think about it,
we did a good job against Jong Kook.
Yes, you did.
All right.
We have the flour you collected.
(The result)
(Did Suk Jin put up a good fight?)
(Or did So Min
turn the tables around.)
However, the winner is Team Senior.
(Team Senior wins the game.)
- Nice!
- All right!
- Go, seniors!
- I knew it.
It's okay.
Just do well in the picking stage.
It's all about picking
the right card.
The two who didn't play
will pick the cards.
- So Se Chan and...
- Really?
- Here you go.
- Pick the one with 1,000 dollars.
Here are the options
for Team Junior.
(Team Senior: 100 to 1,000 dollars,
Team Junior: 100 to 800 dollars)
(Yong Jin and Se Chan
will represent Team Senior.)
Let me see.
- I think I chose a good one.
- It's 1,000 dollars.
- It's 900 dollars.
- Okay!
- Nice.
- It's 900 dollars.
- I have 400.
- Okay.
- That's good enough.
We can just win both.
Okay!
Look. Ji Hyo picked the card
with 800 dollars.
- Nice, Ji Hyo.
- Is it 100 dollars again?
- It's 100 dollars.
- Why is it always the same?
But even though Ji Hyo
has the card with 800 dollars,
if you divide that by three...
- It's still good enough.
- Come on.
She still managed
to pick 800 dollars though.
- I can do it, you know.
- Nice.
- Nicely done.
- Of course.
Those who picked the cards
will head to the ATM machine.
Head inside.
(They enter the bank
with the cards they chose.)
(Yong Jin picked the card
with the largest amount.)
How do we do this?
- Does the card go in here?
- How...
- Does it go in here?
- Let me see.
- I got this.
- Let's do this.
We can do this.
(The first question is revealed.)
(Chairman Yoo Jae Suk's birthday
is August 14, 1972.)
(Write all the numbers
in Chinese characters.)
How can one know all these?
You've got to be kidding me.
(Write all the numbers
in Chinese characters.)
- It's...
- One...
- How do you write eight?
- Ten.
- I know what 8 is.
- This is 4.
- No one will be able to do it.
- This is eight.
- There's no way.
- This is nine.
Maybe Yong Jin could step up.
We'll get to see
how smart Yong Jin is.
(Out of all of them,
Yong Jin seems most reliable.)
What's the character for eight?
(Why is he writing down
the year 1800?)
(Does he think this is 7?)
(He boldly designs
a new numbering system.)
(He ends it with a question mark.)
I'm going crazy over here.
Please...
(He thinks he only doesn't know 4,
but even the first number is wrong.)
- One last number...
- Why can't I remember it?
These days, Ji Hyo...
Well, she's been receiving lessons.
She's been studying up
on calendars too.
I have a feeling
she'll know these numbers.
This is killing me.
In Chinese characters?
(She manages until number 4.)
So Min would know this.
How am I supposed to know this?
(One, two, three, four...)
I don't know what seven is.
Eight.
Hold on a second.
(Instead of 5, she wrote "won.")
(She suddenly changes it to pi.)
Hold on a second.
I can't remember the numbers!
- Me neither.
- Same here.
This is driving me crazy.
Eight.
I don't know what 7, 8, and 9 are.
- No way!
- I don't know.
I just don't know.
(Incorrect. Try the next question.)
(Ji Hyo: 800 dollars to 400 dollars)
(He's trying to figure out
the same question.)
I can't remember what nine is!
This shouldn't air on TV!
(It's another episode
his son shouldn't watch.)
- I don't know the answer.
- This can't air on TV!
(Thump)
- Please!
- I don't know.
I think I got the most right though.
(After long consideration,
Haha puts up his answer sheet.)
(Year 1972)
(Haha: 100 dollars)
(Incorrect. Try the next question.)
I give up.
Next!
(Se Chan gives up too.)
Is this 5? Maybe it's 6.
Seven?
- I give up!
- It's seven.
- Unbelievable.
- What's eight?
What do I do?
It's too hard.
- What's the second question?
- Did anyone get it?
(All of them move on
with the amount now cut in half.)
- "I'm new to the world."
- "To the world."
"I cry a lot."
"Please give me milk."
"Everyone smiles at me."
- "Please give me milk."
- "Everyone smiles at me."
- What now?
- I cry a lot.
- It wants milk.
- I know what it is.
- It's a baby.
- Here.
I know what it is. It's a baby.
A baby.
(What am I? Answer: Baby)
Could they not know this?
(Answer the question in English.)
(Thinking)
"I'm new to the world."
I don't know what this is.
What do I do?
It's too hard.
Are you kidding me?
(A cow?)
(Incorrect. Try the next question.)
Why? Just give me one more chance.
- This...
- I don't know the answer.
(The other Empty Head
has the same question.)
- Please...
- Unbelievable.
My son will see this, you know.
(The spelling is based on
how the vowel sounds.)
(Incorrect. Try the next question.)
My son will see this, you know.
How can one know this? Next!
This is bad.
(This consonant is written as giyok.
How do you write this next one?)
(Thankfully, he doesn't hesitate...)
(when it comes to a quiz
on the Korean alphabet.)
(This consonant is written as giyok.
How do you write this next one?)
(Incorrect: The answer is tieut.
You can no longer withdraw money.)
This shouldn't air on TV!
This can't air on TV!
- I don't know the answer.
- This can't air on TV!
(Only yelling resonates
around this gruesome scene.)
Please!
This is bad.
- My son will see this, you know.
- This can't air on TV!
- I don't know the answer.
- No!
- Darn it.
- This is bad.
My son will see this, you know.
(He's desperate.)
This can't air on TV!
(This can't air on TV!)
No!
- Gosh.
- I feel for you.
- You...
- Please head back inside.
- Your son Dream...
- Oh, no.
My son will see this.
What do I do?
I'll probably do the worst today.
Come to think of it,
I get how this can be upsetting.
Yong Jin, how did you do?
Me?
- Did you get any right?
- No.
Gosh, Haha...
- Unbelievable.
- You're an Empty Head too.
He's an Empty Head.
Darn it.
- Let me see.
- I almost had it though.
(The original Empty Head
comes back out empty-handed.)
I couldn't guess any one of them.
- You two...
- A cowboy?
Did someone write "cow?"
- Seriously?
- Was it you?
What did you write as the answer?
How do you spell "cow?"
With an A or an O?
It's O. What did you write?
Cow with an A.
I thought it meant...
that you were milking something
in a new world.
- I thought it was milking too.
- Still...
It's why I came up
with a part-time worker.
This is super annoying.
Are you kidding me?
Milk? A baby?
(Incorrect. Try the next question.)
(Ji Hyo: 400 dollars to 200 dollars)
"I cry a lot."
"Please give me milk."
Please give me milk, right?
(Surprisingly enough,
he gets it right.)
A baby.
(That is correct.
50 dollars will be withdrawn.)
I don't know what the answer is.
(Haha: 50 dollars)
(Haha manages to withdraw money
in just two questions.)
- Still...
- Why?
- You got the second question?
- He studied in Germany.
- You answered "baby" correctly?
- Yes.
- Wasn't that an easy one?
- I'm surprised.
They thought of cows.
- Cows?
- Because of the milk.
I thought it was a cowboy.
(Ji Hyo tries to answer
the last Korean alphabet question.)
(Incorrect: You no longer have
a chance to withdraw the money.)
Why is her hair all messed up?
Did you not get any of them right?
I got all of them wrong.
A dog?
What's the answer to that one?
- You guys are killing me.
- A dog?
Out of those that competed,
only Haha managed to win the money.
Really?
- You guys are hilarious.
- I thought it could be a baby too.
This is why
you're on the smarter side.
You really didn't know it?
Seriously?
We're too ashamed
to look you in the eye.
You two are unbelievable.
Now that it's over,
- you'll clean up and head to eat.
- Sure thing.
- I'm sure you're all hungry.
- We are.
Before you eat though,
you'll play another game.
You'll be playing
for instant cash...
in this game of
Colorful Slurping Noodles.
Slurping noodles?
On the white t-shirt you'll wear...
will be circles that indicate...
the addition
or subtraction of points.
Next, you'll have jjajangmyeon
with a blindfold on.
As you slurp in the noodles,
try getting jjajangmyeon...
in that area. We'll give you money
depending on the number of spots.
That sounds fun.
The more jjajangmyeon you get,
the more money you get.
Four areas will get you 100 dollars,
and 2 areas will take your money.
Your team members will draw
the areas to earn 100 dollars.
The other team will draw the areas
where your money will be taken.
Put on the blindfold
as you have jjajangmyeon.
We'll combine the number of areas
where you got jjajangmyeon on...
and give money to your team.
That sounds fun.
Who's going to eat it?
We can't shake the noodles.
We need to slurp the noodles.
You can't shake the noodles.
Jae Suk is good
at slurping noodles.
I'm good at getting food
on my shirt.
Each team can pick an area
to write "double",
and if you get jjajangmyeon in
that area, you'll get twice as much.
- Okay.
- Who is going first?
- Yong Jin will go first.
- I'll go.
- Let's go!
- Let's go, Yong Jin!
- Let's have So Min go first.
- Okay, she can go first.
(So Min versus Yong Jin)
When we were playing a game earlier,
these two were really annoying...
during So Min's turn.
- I guess we were a bit...
- You were really annoying.
But it was fun to watch.
We need to make fun of So Min.
They teased her after a long time.
Last time, So Min shook with anger.
I'll keep teasing you.
You can't bear it, can you?
We'll keep going.
That tone though...
How annoying!
The thing about noodles...
The sauce gets on your shirt.
Put on the blindfold.
But the noodles are long,
so they hit your shirt too.
They'd hit somewhere around here.
- Over here. They'd hit the shirt.
- I think this area will get a lot.
Hold on. The area under the mic.
The noodles are short. If they
were long, then they'd hit here.
They're short, so we should draw
an area around here.
That's right. Let's leave no space
for the red circles.
- Exactly.
- Draw them in the center.
All right. If you're done,
hand the shirt to the other team.
- Use the red marker...
- I think So Min won't drop it.
You're so sneaky.
There you go.
(This will be counted as
minus 200 dollars.)
The circles cannot overlap.
Let's eat now.
(Yong Jin of Team Senior
goes first.)
You saw it, right? Keep your head up
and slurp the noodles.
- All right!
- Slurp the noodles.
I'll slurp the noodles.
Chinese food!
That's the spirit!
There you go.
Okay.
- That's great!
- Ready.
- You should eat without thinking.
- They picked the good spots.
They picked excellent spots.
We'll win for sure.
Let's go.
(How will it turn out?)
Let's go!
- They need to be longer.
- That's not strong enough!
- Come on.
- You're eating it too neatly.
- Come on!
Bring back the energy you had
when you were...
on "People Looking for a Laugh".
(As soon as he hears
"People Looking for a Laugh",)
(he gets jjajangmyeon
on the 100-dollar area.)
- This is like "Comedy Big League"!
- You're doing great!
- That's great.
- Keep going!
- We got one.
- Make the noodles long.
Eating the noodles is not important!
- That's not good!
- Slurp more!
- We got one.
- Hey!
Eating the noodles is not important!
- Just slurp the noodles.
- Slurp more!
- That's good.
- There you go.
- Come on, what's that?
- Shake them. That's it.
- Shake them.
- Come on!
- What are you doing?
- Yes!
(He got it on minus 100 dollars.)
- That's it.
- Shake them.
Come on.
- What are you doing?
- Yes!
- Hey!
- No!
Well done!
- Gosh.
- Gosh, Yong Jin.
Keep going!
It's even.
- This is...
- Shake the noodles!
We drew the circles
in the wrong spots.
There's so much on the red circles.
All right!
He got so much jjajangmyeon
on the red circles.
We should've drawn one here.
My gosh, he got so much
on the red circles.
- What a mess.
- All right.
He got it on only one red circle.
- They got 2.
- He got 2 black circles.
There's more on the right side.
We got one on this circle.
- Where?
- We'll get 100 dollars.
(There's a tiny spot here.)
- Please take a look at it.
- Be honest.
- Over here. Be honest.
There's a spot here, right?
(She wipes it off with her finger.)
No, there's nothing here.
- There's nothing.
- Don't erase it off!
- Why would you erase it?
- There's nothing!
You got 300 dollars
and 2 minus 100 dollars.
- Yes.
- We'll give you 100 dollars.
It's not bad.
So Min is good at this kind of game.
Let's see how well you slurp
the noodles.
I'm not so good
at slurping the noodles,
but I'm good at spilling food.
I've been doing it for 36 years.
She always spills food.
I'm not even kidding.
I always spill food.
(Will she be able to eat
in a messy way in front of them?)
All right. Let's start.
- You can do it.
- So Min, many people are watching.
- All right!
- Let's do this.
You need to sit up straight.
- It's the first round.
- Ready.
- Let's do it.
- Enjoy it little by little.
(Team Senior drew their circles
on top.)
(Slurping the noodles starts.)
- Let's go!
- That's it.
That's a lot of noodles.
(She grabs a lot at once.)
- Hurry up.
- Don't eat neatly!
There you go.
(She's at risk already.)
(The seniors find it entertaining.)
Slurp them.
You're so cute
eating the noodles like that.
That's it.
(She tilts her head more
as they find her cute.)
Who eats jjajangmyeon in braids?
How can you eat it
while tilting your head?
No, don't tilt it to that side.
Tilt it to the other side.
- It's not even close.
- Hey.
- Why are you lowering your head?
Since when did you start
eating neatly?
Make it messy!
It's more difficult
than you thought, isn't it?
No!
(She gives up on using chopsticks.)
- No, you can't use your hand.
- You can't use your hand.
- Just eat it normally.
- Slurp them in.
That's it.
(Shaking)
My gosh. You must be
on a blind date.
It's too close to the red circles.
Is there a guy
you want to look nice to?
So Min...
- There's a spot here.
- That was incredible.
- There's one here.
- No, there's nothing.
There's nothing.
- It's not in that area.
- The noodles touched the area.
- No, it's not in that area.
- It's not in that area.
No. Look at this.
It's not in that area.
- There's a spot in that area.
- It's not in the area.
- I swear, it's not in the area.
Come take a look.
Pick the next players.
Ji Hyo will go next.
I'll go next.
- Let me see yours.
- It's risky to draw it there.
- No, it's fine.
- Let me see yours.
- It's risky to draw one here.
- Let's draw one here.
Jae Suk is good
at slurping the noodles.
Are Jae Suk's front teeth
crooked to the right side?
Then we should draw a circle
on the right.
- Yes, it's this side.
- It's under here.
(They draw all their circles
on the right.)
His teeth... Wait, they're crooked
to the left side!
Suk Jin, they're crooked
to the left side.
We should've drawn the circles
on the left.
- It's okay. It doesn't matter.
- It doesn't matter.
With teeth like his,
we can draw circles on his shorts.
Also...
Can we draw them on your socks?
Hey!
I think it'll splatter to his socks.
We're done drawing them.
- We're done!
- Please exchange the shirts.
(They're done marking
the 100-dollar area.)
- Give it to me.
- You can mark...
- Collect it.
- Here comes our ace.
- Let's not cheat.
- All right.
The master of slurping noodles.
All right. He'll make use
of his crooked teeth.
His favorite dish is jjajangmyeon.
Can I draw a circle here?
I think it'll splatter up to here.
What if it splatters up to here?
The crooked teeth.
- All right.
- You can do it!
- Ready.
- You don't have to grab a lot.
Of course.
(The master looks relaxed.)
- His shirt...
- Jjajangmyeon was delicious.
All right. There you go. That's it!
Yes!
(What happened?)
- There you go!
(He already lost 300 dollars.)
- Strike!
- All right!
(He leaks lots of noodles
on the left side.)
(It was the left side.)
- What are you doing?
- That's it.
- Make them longer.
- We knew his teeth were crooked.
I told you the noodles
will sway to the left side.
- The left side?
- His teeth are crooked.
- I told you! It's the left side!
- It should've been the left side!
You didn't know?
The noodles follow
the shape of his teeth.
(Fascinated)
He got it. It's going great.
- All right. Good job.
- Good job.
- Good job!
- That's too much.
He's just getting them on his shirt.
Don't put the noodles on your shirt.
He's incredible.
How is he eating it like that?
He's being too obvious.
- The noodles stopped there.
- I'm sorry,
but isn't he done?
How can he spill so well?
He's...
(He's excited after getting
jjajangmyeon all over his shirt.)
Even my daughter doesn't spill
like he does.
Five, four, three,
- two,
- He's done with the noodles.
- One.
- He finished the noodles.
There aren't enough noodles.
- There's more on the left side.
- He was like a two-year-old.
Oh, it was here.
You did well.
It's a total mess.
- You got some on the red ones.
- He got it on all circles.
He got it on all four circles.
You're getting 200 dollars.
- Yes!
- Nice!
- Well done.
- Nice.
Keep going!
- Could you...
- Lift your head! That's it!
Could you give her
some pickled radish?
You should shake your head.
You shouldn't eat it like that.
You're eating it too neatly!
- Don't you know what slurping is?
- You're trying to avoid it.
- She spat it out.
- That wasn't slurping.
She got a spot on one circle.
- You're getting 100 dollars.
- All right!
You are tied.
The team that picks
a longer noodle will win.
- All right.
- Sounds good.
We'll have Suk Jin pick it.
Okay.
- Then let's have So Min go.
- So Min, you should pick it.
- No, Ji Hyo will go.
- So Min loses to him all the time.
What do we get if we win?
If you win, you'll get a chance
to withdraw 1,000 dollars.
Look at Suk Jin.
Let's do this.
His name is so cute.
- I'll destroy you.
- Sure.
- Should I go first?
What if it gets cut in the midway?
- Then you're done.
- Then that will be it.
I'll mix the noodles first.
- Come on.
- No, just pick one right away.
- You can't mix them.
- Once you mix them, you're done.
Just grab one.
- It's okay if it gets cut.
- He grabbed one.
- That's it. Stay still.
- You're done.
He grabbed one.
- That's it. Stay still.
- You're done.
(He grabbed the shortest noodle.)
What's wrong with you?
- What was that, Suk Jin?
- Ji Hyo, pick a good one.
- Ji Hyo, get a good one.
- What was that?
Why did you pick that?
- What's wrong with this?
- He's done.
- It got cut in the middle.
- All right!
- Yes!
(Pulling it out)
- We won.
- Suk Jin!
- All right.
- What was that, Suk Jin?
This was...
- Ji Hyo is indeed amazing.
- This one is long though.
Why did you pick that?
- This is fun. She's good.
- How would I know?
Thanks to Ji Hyo,
Team Junior takes the win.
We need to withdraw
1,000 dollars this time.
- Please pick one.
- All right. This is our chance.
- We need to pick a good one.
- Who's going from our team?
Us two.
(Se Chan and Yong Jin
are withdrawing the money again.)
- But...
- Trust us this time.
- You can trust us.
- You can do it.
- Trust us.
- Which one should I pick?
(The two Empty Heads
are full of confidence.)
You can pick one.
We got 400 dollars and 700 dollars.
(Team Junior got a chance to
withdraw 400 and 700 dollars.)
- Good job.
- You guys are really good.
- I got 400 dollars.
- Why are you guys so good?
- I got 200 dollars.
- He got 200 dollars.
(Team Senior can withdraw
400 and 200 dollars.)
It's okay. Our team is going great.
Ji Hyo, you never know.
- You can do it.
- I can do it.
Jae Suk, I'll go and play it.
- Okay, let's go!
- Let's go!
- Yong Jin.
- Okay. Don't worry.
(Yang Se Chan, 400 dollars)
Here I go.
(He enters the bank
with headphones on.)
(Lee Yong Jin, 200 dollars)
(Jeon So Min, 400 dollars)
Let's play this.
Hello.
(The first ATM quiz
that the Empty Heads will play)
After removing one cue card,
you'll be given a question to solve.
I can do this!
All right!
("Beautiful" and "Tomorrow"
are the words...)
(that Americans misspell the most.)
(Please write the correct spellings
of the two words.)
- How can I...
- I have no idea!
Not many people know
the correct spellings of these!
I have no idea.
I don't think any of the members
know the correct spellings.
Oh, no.
(Se Chan wrote down
his answer confidently.)
(As expected, it's wrong.)
This is so frustrating!
(He lets out his anger at the ATM
out of embarrassment.)
Let's see.
This is so upsetting!
(Yong Jin is really upset.)
This is...
It'd be faster to rob the bank
with a mask on!
This is so upsetting.
If they push me like this,
I won't comply.
Do I have to write both?
Can I just guess one?
(Incorrect. Try the next question.)
- It's wrong, isn't it?
- I give up!
(Ji Hyo is thinking carefully.)
(We can see how hard
she's been thinking.)
What could it be?
There's an "I" in it.
(She can't recall the spelling
of "beautiful".)
This is really upsetting.
(It's wrong.)
I have no idea.
I give up. I'll try this one.
(So Min tries for an answer
after thinking hard.)
Do I have to write both?
Can I just guess one?
(Even So Min got it wrong.)
- It's wrong, isn't it?
- I give up!
- I don't want to do it.
- I don't think this will work.
- I won't go for this next time.
- How come?
- I have no idea.
- This is...
(All of them failed to get
the correct answer.)
Yong Jin, you don't look so good.
I have an upset stomach
after having jjajangmyeon.
(Current Amount of Team Money,
Team Senior, Team Junior)
What is this?
Isn't it something scary?
It's something scary, isn't it?
Is this "Let's Go, Dream Team"?
The set itself is the highlight
of today.
- They put a lot of effort into it.
- Right.
I guess we need to push
the other and stand on top of that.
- How do we play it?
- Let's say you're there.
If someone approaches,
you should punch him...
- and make him pass out.
- I can punch them?
You know how comedians
are all talented.
- That's right.
- So this time,
we'll see how well
they can use their bodies.
- I'm good at that.
- The last mission...
is Let's Fly, Tarzan.
We're flying?
Each team will take turns
to attack and defend.
The members of Team Defense can
stand on the column of their choice.
If one of you falls
while trying to get on it,
then he or she will be eliminated.
After Team Defense
takes their places,
the members of Team Offense will
take their places on the columns.
The team that dominates
more columns wins.
(The team that dominates
more columns wins.)
Sir, I have a question.
Can we get in the way of the member
who's flying by?
- You can do that.
- Of course, that's what it's about.
If you fall while trying to attack,
then you'll be eliminated.
Even if we take a place
on the column, Jong Kook...
- He'll attack us.
- "Hey!"
(He'll turn this game
into a super-strength performance.)
When the director confirmed
that we can kick our opponent,
Jong Kook quietly nodded.
(He nodded when the director
gave them his permission.)
- He nodded. He's so scary.
- Team Defense...
can push off the members
who attack them.
I think we should jump off
with Jong Kook.
So our balance and core muscles
are important in this game.
- "Balance and core muscles"?
- "Balance"?
Do you know how you spell that?
You keep... There's a "B", right?
(There's a "B", right?)
- There's an "A" too.
- You used up all your knowledge.
I'm sure there's a spelling
of it on your shoes.
It's on my shoes.
Do you want to go for it?
What do you say?
You'll read it off your shoes?
That's not allowed.
- Bring it on.
- It's an open-book quiz.
Bring it on.
Let's fight.
"Let's fight"?
- I'm confident.
- I love fighting too.
You'll play each round
attacking and defending.
We'll give the team money
according to the number...
of members that survived.
Good. Let's do this.
- Yes, let's do this.
- They have So Min and Ji Hyo.
It's disadvantageous for us
since we have two women.
- Let's do this.
- Let's play it.
- Okay.
- I should grab somewhere higher.
I should grab somewhere higher.
- I'm ready.
- Go for it.
- That was fast.
- But this is...
It's hard to land on the column.
- You'll do a run-up from behind?
- Right?
I should grab around here?
I got this.
- We must go that far.
- Is this how it's done?
For the female members,
you can step on the third line.
- Over here?
- Yes.
Okay.
- Let me give it a try.
- Ji Hyo, try it from here.
Ji Hyo, you should
stretch out your arms.
Grab as high as you can.
There you go.
You should swing just like this.
Let's go. 1, 2...
Hey. You brat.
What are you doing?
You were supposed to jump from here.
Why would you jump to this column?
She's a true comedienne.
- She's a comedienne indeed.
- That was funny.
She fooled everyone.
You fooled us, didn't you?
So Min, you should grab over here.
- Here?
- Then jump off from there.
Ready, go. You should jump.
- That won't work.
- That's it.
Hey.
(The frog fell just like that.)
- You told me to grab there.
- So Min.
So Min, how could you grab there
just because I told you to?
(Senior Yang teases Junior Jeon.)
Ji Hyo, try it again.
- Suk Jin, give it a try.
- No, thanks.
Why not?
- Why would I?
- You should practice.
- Why would I waste my strength?
- Let's do this!
- Get ready.
- Team Defense will go first.
Will you give it a try now?
- Let's do it.
- He just did.
- You did it?
- Yes.
- You need to come here.
- I'll go there.
Se Chan, you need to come here.
We need to stay together.
Otherwise, Jong Kook will kick me.
- They could fall together.
- Of course.
I'll hold you.
- You should hold me.
- Okay.
Why am I getting nervous?
- Let's go, JRS!
- JRS!
- Just like a robot...
- and steel.
- Just like steel. Be strong.
(He sets off
after getting encouraged.)
There you go, Se Chan.
- You need to grab me.
- I did.
- I did grab you.
- My stomach muscle...
almost got torn.
- Nice. You got me.
- I got you.
It's way better to be with someone
than to be alone.
It's way better.
We can't fight
against Jong Kook alone.
I meant that it's better for me.
Since there are two of you...
- Oh, you meant for you?
- Yes, it's better for me.
(Taking aim at his target)
Wait. We should land
on these two columns, right?
- Or should I join you?
- No, go to the other one.
- Tell me.
- Go to the other column.
- We should defend.
- The crane wing strategy.
But I think it'll be hard
to land on that column.
- Just hurry up and jump.
- It looks hard.
- How is it hard?
- It's easy!
The rope is too straight.
- Just jump already.
- It's okay.
- They made it all doable.
- No, it's not prepared for it.
- Yes, it is!
- Just go!
- I said, it's difficult.
- If you decide that you can do it,
then you can go.
You should try it.
Try going to that column.
- It's difficult.
- Should I go first?
Or do you want me to go first?
Should I go to that one?
- What's wrong with him?
- What are you doing?
You told me to try it.
- I told you it's easy to go there.
- This is driving me crazy.
Hey, Yong Jin.
- Is this your show or something?
- I'll go first.
- What are you doing?
Landing there is difficult.
- You need to be determined.
- Just go.
You need to do a run-up from behind.
- Go.
- There you go.
- Nice.
- That's it.
(He's in danger.)
You need to go back.
(You need to go back.)
- My gosh.
- This isn't right.
- Suk Jin is out.
- What's wrong with him?
- This is driving me crazy!
- How annoying!
- This is...
- Suk Jin!
Suk Jin.
I told you it's way easier
to land there.
That's not true.
It's easier to land there.
- How is it easier to land here?
- I'm telling you, it's easier.
If Jae Suk didn't grab me,
I'd have fallen.
It'd be easy if someone grabs you.
- Move out of the way.
- Can't I stand here?
You're eliminated.
(Suk Jin is separated from others.)
Which one should I land on?
- This one.
- Just pick one.
I can defend against Ji Hyo
and So Min from there.
That's a good idea.
I think that'd be better.
He looks like Tarzan.
That's good. You're going to use
only one hand?
- No, I'm getting prepared.
- You'll fall for sure.
(If you jump off too hard,
you'll fall.)
If you jump off too hard,
you'll fall.
(Grunting)
- What are you doing?
- Oh, gosh.
(He flies in the air.)
He hasn't fallen yet.
(After taking a trip around,)
(he falls.)
What was that?
Look at him.
(This is the slapstick comedy
of a comedian.)
- That was awesome.
- What was that?
- He's good.
- Hey!
- He stepped on both.
You practically traveled
all over the nation.
- My gosh, you're good.
- It is difficult.
- It's difficult.
- I told you it's difficult.
- What was that?
- This is difficult.
- How is this difficult?
- Because the two of them...
- It's not easy!
I'll go there next time then.
It's difficult.
- My gosh, that was terrible.
- It's Team Offense's turn.
- You can go.
- It's not easy.
- Try it. It's really not easy.
- If one person falls with them,
and if one manages to land
on a column, we'll win.
That's right.
Is it okay if we move
to the other column?
- Yes, you can.
- Then I'll go there.
- Okay. Give it a try.
- Okay.
I thought it'd be easy.
(Se Chan moves to the other column
to avoid Jong Kook.)
- What was that?
- I think I could go there too.
I think you can just kick them.
I'll fly and kick both of them.
(I'll fly and kick both of them.)
I'll kick both of them.
I'll jump off from here,
fly, and kick them.
That'd be fun.
It's like billiards.
- Should I stay here?
- No, move to that column.
You should shoot him
with a high speed camera.
(Team Senior chose
the less dangerous option.)
- Okay. I got this.
- He's pretty nimble.
(We'll be done for
if we don't stop Jong Kook.)
We'll be done for
if we don't stop Jong Kook.
He looks so determined.
Look at his face.
(Roaring)
I'd fall on my own if I were you.
- I'm glad I'm on his team.
- Look how he's clenching his teeth.
Here I go.
(And these two need to stop him.)
I should go back when he jumps off.
(Roaring)
(Here he comes!)
(Kicking)
There you go!
(Killing two birds with one stone)
(After destroying them,)
(he relaxedly lands on a column.)
(Impressed)
(A cruel fairy tale,
"Protein Tarzan")
He actually kicked us.
He kicked us for real!
What's wrong with that?
- We won, right?
- Hey.
He actually kicked
the inside of my thigh.
- I mean...
- Team Junior won,
but they can get more money
if more members get on the columns.
- It hurts.
- He's right.
He actually kicked us.
I think it's better to go first.
You actually kicked us?
- Good job. All right.
- Good job!
- I'll try it again.
- Our team is good at this.
- Team Junior wins the first round.
- Yes!
And you'll get the team money
for the three members who survived.
- They'll start first, right?
- Yes, it's their turn.
This time, Team Junior
will defend first.
Should I go first or not?
You should.
We can definitely defend
against them.
- Jong Kook is...
- Shall we start?
I shouldn't join Jong Kook
on that column, should I?
(I hope he falls!)
I hope he falls!
- There.
- That was smooth.
How did he do that?
I know. He must be really strong.
(Ji Hyo goes next.)
- I don't think stepping on it...
- There you go. Good job.
- She is good.
- She is really good.
Is it better to stand alone?
- Of course.
- I can reach this far.
- Okay.
- Okay. That's good.
- Where do I go?
- Well...
- As for you...
- Come here.
Come here.
I don't think
anyone would come here.
Make space for me.
I will make space for you.
Be careful.
Don't swing too hard.
You will bump into her.
- Be careful.
- You don't need to swing hard.
- Swing hard.
- There you go.
- You don't need to swing hard.
- Swing hard.
- There you go.
- Look at that.
(Hanging)
It's over.
(At that moment)
You need to get up there.
- Grab him.
- There you go.
(Got him.)
There you go. Grab him.
Grab him. There you go.
- You did it.
- Good job.
- So Min grabbed him.
Thank goodness.
(He managed to survive
thanks to So Min's help.)
Hold on to me until the end.
All right. Bring it on.
(All right. Bring it on.)
- Suk Jin.
- What?
(It's time for Team Senior
to attack.)
What's the strategy?
You should go this way.
I know that you will come this way.
I can tell
from the direction of your body.
I will hit your face.
If you do that, I will kick you.
- I will hit you for real.
- I will spit on you.
- I will kick you.
- Suk Jin.
I don't know about Haha and So Min
or Ji Hyo,
but you should take off your glasses
if you are after Jong Kook.
Are you serious?
(He takes off his glasses.)
- Let's do this.
- The glasses are in the way.
- Hey.
- Show us what you can do.
I will knock him off.
- Show us.
- Come on.
I will knock him off.
- Show us.
(Determined)
What was that?
Crouch down.
(Jae Suk shows
his mischievous side.)
- What?
- We weren't ready.
I jumped with determination.
We weren't ready.
- You startled me.
- We weren't ready.
- Come to your senses.
In my opinion,
you wouldn't have succeeded
with that shout.
You should shout louder.
- Okay.
- It wasn't loud enough.
- We need to do well.
- Hit high notes.
Let's go.
I don't know where to go.
(With Jae Suk's permission,
he gets ready to take off.)
- I know you made up your mind.
- You are coming here.
There you go. Is it a feint?
(After a no-look pass,)
(he gets thrown on the ground.)
There you go. Is it a feint?
(Suk Jin went down after a shout.)
- Next.
- Next. Come on.
I grabbed the rope too low.
- The first jump was good.
- If you jump from here...
That's too bad.
Will he come here?
He will use his elbows to jump high.
There you go.
- Go backward.
- The trajectory is scary.
The trajectory is scary.
- He will come here.
- That's good.
- It's like a dance.
- Jump.
- How scary!
- Here I go.
Haha is scared already.
There you go!
(Strike)
(He lands on the column
after taking out both of them.)
- Nice!
- Nice.
Good job.
- One shot, two kills.
- Nice.
Doing a run-up helped.
- Okay.
- Good job.
- They took one column.
Se Chan's body was like a rock.
I think Yong Jin will come to me.
Here I go.
Are you aiming for Ji Hyo?
- Let's turn the tables.
- Of course.
Let's show the seniors' spirit.
(The seniors will teach you
a lesson.)
Spirit.
(I fooled you, didn't I?)
What was that?
- Why are you so nervous?
- Good job.
- That's...
- I can't believe him.
- For goodness' sake.
- She became nervous.
- You are so mean.
You were sweating, weren't you?
Yes, you probably did.
I just did this.
Why did you become nervous?
- I didn't see that coming.
- Okay. I got it.
- He is so pretentious.
- I know.
- Here I go.
- It will be a hit...
if you go to Jong Kook.
- It will look cool.
- No. Don't even think about it.
- Bring it on.
- Don't go.
- Go.
- There you go.
Gosh.
- Go.
- There you go.
(He missed,
but Ji Hyo fell off the column.)
That's good.
- That's good.
- Nice.
- I did it.
- Why did you fall off?
I fell off in my attempt
to grab him.
I did it.
- We will win.
- You just need to go up there.
You should have stood still.
But Jong Kook could come here.
If Jong Kook moves to that column,
I will move to this column.
- That works.
- Yes.
Will you move here?
(Will you move here?)
You motivated Jong Kook.
- Jong Kook will jump over.
- I know.
- Then I will move to that column.
- Don't worry.
- That's right. Okay.
- Will that work?
- He might think about going back,
so you need to decide wisely.
Why are you strategizing
when he can hear everything?
- What's the meaning of this?
- Hey.
He didn't hear anything.
It's an unspoken rule.
- That's how it works.
- We don't hear these things.
- He didn't hear anything.
- That's right.
- He doesn't understand.
He doesn't know our strategy.
Really? Is that how it works?
Think of it as a monologue.
- I see.
- Think of it as a monologue.
- He didn't hear anything.
- A monologue.
- That's right.
- I didn't hear anything either.
- It's an unspoken promise.
- I see.
- I had no idea.
- Really?
You could get kicked when I jump.
Be careful.
You need to go up there.
If I do that,
Jong Kook will push me off.
- Then I will take his column.
- You are right.
- Don't worry.
- Okay.
(What will be his decision?)
- There he goes.
- All right.
Good job.
Hold on.
(Jong Kook doesn't fall off
despite staggering.)
- Out.
- What was that?
What was that?
(Jae Suk attacked Se Chan
instead of Jong Kook.)
What was that?
- I mean...
- What was that?
He is out.
I will say...
one member from each team survived.
Round Three will determine
the winning team.
Okay.
(Round 3 will determine
the winning team.)
- For goodness' sake.
- In Round Three,
two members from each team
will attack and defend alternately.
- Okay.
- What do you mean?
Oh, two members at a time.
Team Senior,
do you want to go first?
Shall we go first?
- Let's go later.
- Okay.
- Have them go first.
- Go ahead.
- Are we going first?
- Yes.
Two members at a time.
Her helmet broke.
- Use this one.
- That won't do.
Use this one.
- How about you?
- It's okay.
- It's okay, you punk.
You could get hurt.
No one will know if you keep quiet.
(They suddenly begin
a melodramatic skit.)
In the end...
Give me a break.
(Their terrible acting
would have offended the audience.)
Yong Jin is laughing
because he is incredulous.
That was a ridiculous skit.
We can't hear that line.
- Did you hear something?
- We can't hear that line.
- Jong Kook will begin.
- Here I go.
Come on.
That's nothing for him.
- How does he do that?
- The next person.
Face outward and swing.
Face outward. There you go.
Okay. She did it.
- She doesn't make a mistake.
- She is good.
Who will attack?
- Suk Jin and I will go first.
- Okay.
- Go first.
- Yes.
- We will go first.
Go first and give me a hand.
You should be able to take
that column.
I think will hate myself
if I don't succeed.
- Of course.
- Go ahead.
- Yong Jin, you can do it.
- Jump from here.
Okay.
- Good job.
- Had I failed,
- I would have hated myself.
- It's the easy one.
Suk Jin, will you come here?
No. I will attack her.
- He declared war.
- Lower your body.
Lower your body.
I will attack her and go to you.
- I will grab you.
- Okay.
- You should kick him then.
I will grab him on his way.
(I will grab him on his way.)
I am sorry, Ji Hyo.
Come on.
Okay.
- I got you.
- Okay.
I got you.
(He fails to make anyone fall off.)
Stay still.
Okay.
Don't get excited.
(A senior from Term 2 gets help
from a junior.)
I couldn't kick her
because I was too softhearted.
- I was too softhearted.
- Softhearted?
You kicked me here.
You should have gone straight
to that column.
Why did you take a detour?
- I kicked her.
- You took a detour.
Yong Jin and Suk Jin,
- defend the column.
- Okay.
We need to defend the column.
So Min, just kick them.
It's hard to find a balance
when there are two people.
- Super So Min.
- Get eliminated with them.
Get eliminated with them.
You can't kick me, right?
- He is so annoying.
- You can't come here, right?
You can kick them, right?
- No way.
- Kick Suk Jin.
Just kick Suk Jin.
- Come on.
- Dodge.
(He touches her nose.)
- Okay.
- He touched her face.
(He cheated
in the speed of lightning.)
There you go.
I can't believe it.
You are useless.
Did you see that? I don't know who,
but someone hit my nose like this.
Who did it?
- Who did it?
- Good job. Nice defense.
- I am sorry.
I am sorry.
Who did it?
(Manages to get 1 win
by playing dirty)
- So Min, I am sorry.
- How could you play so dirty?
Who else would it be?
That was so dirty.
- It has to be Suk Jin.
- How could you play so dirty?
It has to be Suk Jin.
I am so upset.
I couldn't even solve the quiz.
I will take both of them out.
Okay. You can do it.
- You can do it.
- I have no mercy.
You will succeed.
You will get hurt.
Gosh, Haha.
He will attack hard.
That's...
(Kicking)
(He succeeded in taking them
both out.)
Help him.
- You got it. Okay.
- There you go.
- Your feet are on the column.
- You can do it.
- Haha.
- Dream is watching.
- You can do it.
- No.
You can do it. Dream is watching.
- You can do it. Dream is watching.
- Haha.
- You can do it.
- Okay.
- Ha Dream!
- You can do it. Okay.
(Dream, I did it.)
- Ha Dream.
- He succeeded.
Ha Dream.
(He succeeded with love
for his son.)
He kicked without any mercy.
Haha, just hug the person...
who tries to take your column, okay?
I should go this way.
What will you do? What's your plan?
- I will kick Haha.
- Haha?
Would it be okay to go this way?
Jong Kook might get you
if you go this way.
It will be better to go this way.
- Everyone can hear...
- Gosh.
Everyone can hear the strategy.
Did you hear something?
- Even the microphones picked it up.
- I didn't hear anything.
- Really?
- Get Haha.
- Okay.
- I will get Ji Hyo.
Don't let him go to another column.
It should end at your column.
If he comes this way,
I will hit him like this.
I learned kickboxing.
You never know what will happen.
Hang on to him.
(They need to beat
Team Senior no matter what.)
Hang on to him.
- That's...
- Good job.
That's...
- Good job. Nice.
- He did it.
- Nice.
- That's good. Get up there.
(He needs to get up
on the column now!)
- You got it. There you go.
- Get up there.
- Nice.
- That's good. Get up there.
- You got it.
- Get up there.
There you go.
(He lands on his back.)
- Hold on.
- You did it.
- Jae Suk did it.
- I told you to hold on to him.
All right.
- I got scared.
- I told you to hold on to him.
- Se Chan.
- I will kick.
You need to eliminate Ji Hyo.
- Don't become soft.
- Guard yourself like this.
Looking into her eyes
makes you soft.
- That doesn't apply to me.
- Don't look into her eyes.
- Be careful.
- Don't get hurt.
You need to aim for the edge.
- Should I run up like this?
- Yes.
- No.
- Start from here.
- Se Chan.
- Here.
Don't listen to Suk Jin.
He never succeeded.
- No. Start from here.
- Go with your gut feeling.
- Here.
- Fall off the column with him.
- Go.
- This is hard.
- I need to go that far.
- Go.
If you push Ji Hyo off
and take the column, we win.
I know.
Judging from how nervous he is,
I think he will come to me.
What? Are you nervous?
- No, not at all.
- Go.
I hate those pink shorts.
He looks too strong.
Here I go.
Good. Okay.
- Slowly.
- Okay.
- There you go.
- Grab him.
- Slowly.
- Okay.
- There you go.
- Grab him.
(Se Chan must take the column
to bring victory to Team Senior.)
(Team Senior's fate
depends on Se Chan.)
There you go.
Hold on.
Come on.
We did it.
You took out Se Chan.
Okay. You did it.
- I couldn't balance myself.
- It was like a cartoon.
You were like Tom
from "Tom and Jerry".
Okay. That was good.
Team Junior won.
(Team Junior won.)
We came close.
I know. We would have won
had Se Chan taken the column.
Seriously.
We did it.
- Okay.
- All right. We lose all the time.
- We came close.
- You came close.
You will receive 50 dollars
per surviving member.
So Team Senior gets 100 dollars
and Team Junior gets 250 dollars.
We did well.
We need to multiply the money.
That's right. We need to do well.
- Can we turn the tables?
- We need to choose well.
If you choose well...
- and get the quiz right...
- Get it right at once.
If I combine the money
you have just earned,
Team Senior has 945 dollars.
- How much?
- 945 dollars.
- That isn't much.
- How about us?
Team Junior has 1,535 dollars.
- That's good.
- Let's choose well.
- If you get the remaining amount,
there is a high chance
you will avoid the penalty.
That's good. Let's choose well.
The 2 of us need to get
over 1,000 dollars.
Let's choose well.
- How about 1,100 dollars?
- That works.
- Get 600 and 700 dollars.
- Let's get 1,100 dollars.
(Team Senior needs 1,055 dollars.)
Why don't we choose the one
in the middle?
I did that before,
but the amount was small.
- Like 100 dollars.
- All right.
- Please pick one.
- Then the quiz...
The one who picked the card
solves the quiz?
The ones who didn't pick earlier.
- Jong Kook and me.
- Then we have a chance.
We are good too.
Let's go.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
(Team Senior with 945 dollars
goes first.)
- I will pick this one.
- Okay.
(Team Senior must get
as much money as possible.)
- The number of cases...
- We need a big amount.
We need a big amount
like 700 dollars.
The other one should be
400 or 500 dollars.
We did it.
- We did it.
- 700 dollars.
All right. 700 dollars.
(Jae Suk got 700 dollars.)
And I got 400 dollars.
That's 1,100 dollars.
- That's 1,100 dollars.
- How did this happen?
You need to get the quiz right
in one go.
Get it right in one go.
Do we have a chance?
Can we still win?
Did they get 700 and 400 dollars?
Pick one without thinking.
Don't think.
You and I didn't succeed once.
- This is good.
- The top ones have more amount.
Okay. I got 600 dollars.
- You are set.
- That's good.
Please.
- What is it?
- Please let it be 1,000 dollars.
- I got 400 dollars.
- Did you get 1,000 dollars?
- 600 and 400 dollars. So yes.
- You got 1,000 dollars.
- 1,000 dollars. That's good.
The four members will go now.
Okay.
We need to get
the first question right.
We will get
Let's get the second question right
at the very least.
All right. Let's go.
I need to get it right in one go.
(With 1,050 dollars remaining,)
Let's go.
(Team Senior must get
the question right in one go.)
Please.
(Team Junior could meet the goal
if they don't retry many times.)
(Haha, Jong Kook,
Suk Jin, and Jae Suk)
Please.
(Write the meaning
of the Chinese characters.)
(1. Yong Jin saw "Blank" Kwang Soo
and became "Blank" surprised.)
(Being good with Chinese letters,
Jae Suk writes the answers fast.)
(2. The "Blank" trend is
to increase the number of "Blank".)
(Thinking)
(Sighing)
Thankfully, I know these.
(Does Haha know
these Chinese characters?)
Let's take a look.
Yong Jin saw lanky Kwang Soo...
This character is "Kim".
"Kim".
Isn't it "Won"?
"Wongeum"?
No way.
What did you figure out so far?
- "Geum" and "Sae".
- What?
"Kim" and "Geum".
What are the words?
Yong Jin.
- Yong Jin saw "Blank" Kwang Soo...
- Kwang Soo.
- It can't be "Handsome Kwang Soo".
- No way.
- Okay. I know the answer.
- What is it?
Yong Jin saw Mickey Kwang Soo...
(He brings up Mickey Kwang Soo.)
Is it incorrect?
- "Mickey"?
- Is it incorrect?
Isn't it "Mickey Kwang Soo"?
(The four Empty Heads
can't figure out one character.)
(These four members are solving
the same question.)
(1. Tall, totally
2. Global, holidays)
(Jae Suk holds up his answer!)?
(Write the meaning
of the Chinese characters.)
(Tall, totally, global, holidays)
(Correct.
You will receive 700 dollars.)
(He succeeds in withdrawing
700 dollars.)
I did it.
(Jae Suk gets the question right
and obtains 700 dollars!)
I did it.
(What remains is
Suk Jin and his 400 dollars.)
(If he gets it right,
Team Senior will avoid the penalty!)
I need to get it right in one go.
(Suk Jin, 400 dollars)
(He knows many Chinese characters.
How will he do?)
All right.
(Suk Jin is correct!)
(He succeeds in withdrawing
400 dollars.)
Okay.
(Team Senior succeeded in
withdrawing 1,100 dollars.)
- We did it.
What was the second blank?
- Totally.
- Really? Oh, it was "Totally".
- "Global" and "Holidays".
Global.
Then we have 2,000 dollars.
We did it. We have 2,000 dollars.
We did it.
(Team Junior remains.)
(With the 1st try, he has a chance
to withdraw 400 dollars.)
(Jong Kook, 400 dollars)
(Jong Kook is correct.)
All right.
(He succeeds in acquiring
400 dollars.)
- Jong Kook, are you done?
- Yes.
(Only Haha remains.)
(Haha, 600 dollars)
(Haha writes something down.)
I got this.
(1. Crazy, utterly
2. Economical, chores)
(He becomes the only one
to fail Level 1.)
(Haha, 600 dollars)
(He shouts
because he is embarrassed.)
(Haha's lonely fight begins
in a shabby way.)
What's the last blank
if it isn't "Chores"?
Haha's answers were
"Crazy", "Utterly"...
Let's see.
Yong Jin saw crazy Kwang Soo
and became utterly surprised.
The economical trend is to increase
the number of chores.
- Did you get the first one right?
- Of course.
- You got the first one right.
- I did it right away.
Team Senior succeeded
with 2,045 dollars.
How much did you get just now?
- I got 400 dollars.
- Four hundred dollars.
(Team Junior needs 465 dollars.)
Then Haha needs
to get a question right.
Seriously.
(Haha needs to get
a question right!)
That's the problem.
- I don't know if he will succeed.
- Seriously.
(Haha gets the second question.)
(Haha, 300 dollars)
(Will he be able to solve
the second question?)
Hold on. He started
with 600 dollars, right?
He just needs to get
one question right.
(Getting the 3rd question right
will give him 150 dollars.)
If he gets one question right...
Let's get the second question right
at the very least.
(His hands move hurriedly,
but the end is nowhere in sight.)
If Haha failed, Team Junior
will receive the penalty.
Jong Kook, did you get it right?
(Haha returns!)
Did Haha get a question right?
(What's the meaning of his smile?)
I think he got it wrong.
What's the current situation?
- Say you got a question right.
- If you got a question right,
both teams have 2,000 dollars.
But if you failed,
one member will receive the penalty.
- I am sure he succeeded.
- We suddenly got...
university-level questions.
University-level, my foot!
Please tell us
if you got a question right.
(Haha has been building up
a smart image recently.)
I think he got it wrong.
You are our hope.
(It's a big opportunity for him.)
- I got it right.
- Which one?
(Haha got a question right!)
- The second one?
- That's good.
- I am a YouTuber.
- That's right.
I am a YouTuber.
(What's the popular phrase
that is used on the web, L.C.S.S.?)
(He wrote down the answer
without hesitation.)
Like, comment, subscribe,
and set the alarm.
(Like, comment, subscribe,
and set the alarm.)
Haha PD!
Let me catch up with Kim Jong Kook.
- Haha.
- I had no idea.
He knows some stuff.
So the 4,000 dollars
of the Comedian Association...
that was stolen by Lee Kwang Soo...
- We took it back.
- was paid by both teams.
- Okay.
- I'm so glad.
And none of you will get a penalty.
- So there's no penalty?
- Thank you.
Kwang Soo, don't do that again.
You jerk.
We have breaking news.
The membership fee of 4,000 dollars
stolen by Lee Kwang Soo...
was just paid
by the Comedian Association members.
Now, the association can
maintain its existence.
Meanwhile, the thief Lee Kwang Soo's
whereabouts are still unknown.
If you ever see Lee Kwang Soo,
please report it to us.
(At the crossroad of choice)
Do you choose an easy option
or a challenging option?
(I choose a challenging option.)
(Selection Type 1: Tiger Moth)
(For me, it depends
on the situation.)
(I always go with an easy option.)
(I never risk my choices.)
(Selection Type 2: Safety First)
This is 100 percent chance,
and that is 50 percent chance.
(They are in a dilemma
where they have to make a choice.)
(Will they choose an easy option...)
(or dangerous luck?)
(They have no one to trust...)
(in the series of choices.)
(They decide their own fate.)
(They can either hit the jackpot...)
(or go broke.)
(What choices will they make
before the quirk of fate?)
(Make Your Own Fate,
Protect Money For Your Parents)