(In the march of time,)
(there are times...)
(and moments...)
(that you want
to hold up quietly...)
(and cherish for a long time.)
(Since July 11, 2010...)
(to July 11, 2021...)
(11 years)
(In the long race of 11 years,)
(there were shining moments...)
(that they wanted to seize.)
- Kwang Soo isn't in the photo.
- What do we do?
(At times like that,)
(they paused for a while,)
(With the people
who are like family,)
(they have taken a lot of photos.)
(Family photo)
(Haha, Ji Suk Jin, Yoo Jae Suk,
3991, Lee Kwang Soo)
If you don't know what to do,
make a V shape.
Can't we do something
cute and refreshing?
Haha, did you know
we'd be taking photos today?
I had no idea.
You're lying. Then why
are you so dressed up?
It's a family photo.
- Is this right?
- I'm not in the photo.
Is there a family like this?
(But before that!)
(The Chattering Special from
last week got great responses.)
(I also want to watch the scenes
that were fast-forwarded.)
(I bet all the scenes
that were cut off are also fun.)
(So we decided to release the scenes
that were cut off last week.)
(The difference between the early
days and current Running Man)
We've come this far
talking about Suk Jin.
We just keep talking.
We've been doing Running man...
- for 11 years.
- It's been 11 years.
A lot of viewers and fans
have watched...
and supported our show so far.
It's so fun to talk.
- This is all thanks to them.
- Of course.
But in the early stage
of our show...
- It was totally different.
- Even though...
the basic theme is similar,
- a lot of things have changed.
- It has changed a lot.
At first, it was mainly
about the Name Tag Elimination.
- Right.
- And it was all about characters.
We rarely talk back then.
- We didn't talk a lot back then.
- We thought...
it was fun to talk, but they cut...
- most of it out.
- Right.
And we mostly focused...
- on our guests.
- Exactly.
So that's what a TV show is
all about. And we still do that.
What really matters is...
- what our viewers find interesting.
- Sure.
That's what we focus on
when it comes to editing.
So why do you think
we are having a talk like this?
- This is...
- It means this is...
- what our viewers want to watch.
- They like it.
That's how a TV show works.
This is when Suk Jin
and I opened up to each other.
We all had our own characters,
and Suk Jin became
the race starter.
And I always followed him.
We were necessary for the race.
We're the ones who started races.
So we became the prison members.
You two had
a lot of talk in the prison.
I still remember the day
when I was eliminated...
even before the lights were
set up in the prison.
So Chan Hee was like this.
- "What?"
- Right.
"Are you here already?"
- "Go back to the race."
- Do you remember that?
- "Come back in again."
- That's how...
Suk Jin and I bonded.
We were really sad.
I was really embarrassed to say
"Race start" to the camera.
I know. It was hard to accept that.
(Advice from the married men
for Se Chan and Jong Kook)
Se Chan, am I on your list or not?
I don't have a list.
I mean, am I on your list?
You? No.
I don't have a list or anything.
I'm not seeing anyone, and...
Isn't it that you're seeing someone?
I'm not seeing anyone.
It's been more than two years.
- Really?
- And people want to set me up,
but for some reason,
I'm being calculative.
- Why?
- I don't know. It's strange.
- When I meet someone...
- You're being cautious.
Right. It's a little...
- I know I shouldn't be doing this.
- I have to tell you this.
I want to say this
to you, So Min, and Ji Hyo.
You should date a lot of people
when you can.
- Right. I agree.
- You should see many people.
Once you get married, you should
devote yourself to your family.
- So you should see a lot of people.
- Do you regret it then?
- No.
- So you didn't see many people?
Is that it?
I mean,
you should see many people,
so you'll be able to recognize...
someone you're right for you.
You should see
more people, Jong Kook.
- Why aren't you seeing anyone?
- Well...
- Maybe he's seeing someone.
- It's not easy...
to meet someone
for people of my age.
- I'm afraid.
- I understand him though.
I understand
Jong Kook can feel that way.
I totally understand.
I was going to set him up
with someone,
- but he said no.
- Forget it.
He wouldn't even go on a date.
He only wants to meet
someone spontaneously.
- That's the only thing he wants.
- When someone sets me up,
- I want to run away.
- He doesn't want that.
Then how would you meet a girl?
I can meet someone by chance.
I think he just wants...
to meet someone when he has
dinner with others or something.
- Spontaneously.
- Right.
He meets her
at dinner several times,
and then he can take her out.
- That's what I'd like to do.
- Spontaneous meetings?
It has to be spontaneous.
I don't want others
to set me up with someone.
Then you should join
a club or something.
What kind of club would he join?
- Like a cycling club?
- He always goes to a gym.
- Cycling.
- He only does YouTube...
- and TV shows.
- Once the COVID-19 pandemic ends,
- Then...
- he can meet...
the subscribers of his channel.
- That must be fun.
- If I keep doing it,
I will meet someone.
(If I keep doing it,
I will meet someone.)
No, Jong Kook should be...
alone just like he's been.
He gives up.
He should just...
enjoy his life alone.
- All right.
- Okay?
Chattering.
- Chatter.
- This is a chat.
(The beneficiaries
of "Family Outing")
Now that I'm
in a van with Jong Kook,
- it reminds me of "Family Outing".
- I know.
- These fields.
- The back seats of the van.
Look at the fields.
"Family Outing" was really hard.
- I know.
- I watched it on TV.
Now I can tell you.
When I did "Family Outing"
with Jong Kook...
- We got exhausted on the way.
- Exactly.
- Did you shoot it for two days?
- Yes. For two days.
And it took us like 4 or 5 hours
to get to the destination.
- It must've been hard.
- Before we even started...
I was really hungry
before we started cooking dinner.
I guess so. You didn't even eat.
And you had to go to work
early in the morning.
Exactly.
- It was crazy.
- It was thrilling...
when you decided the person to work.
It was really hard.
We really hated it.
They were upset
when they got picked.
Seriously,
they all turned their faces away.
- Because...
- When we decided it.
We got to sleep
only for a couple of hours.
- That sounds tough.
- If I get to work in the morning...
and cook breakfast,
- It just kills you.
- that means...
- I can sleep only for a few hours.
- You couldn't get enough sleep.
But as a viewer,
I really liked the show.
I liked it too.
I see.
So I cooked a lot.
Because they felt
comfortable around you.
And we had guests there.
- So he had to guide them.
- Right. I had to do it.
Jae Suk took care of them.
It was really fun
when Jang Hyuk was a guest.
Hyuk was really fun.
So we couldn't...
do the show for a long time.
That's right.
- It must've been hard.
- Because it was tough.
I could see that it was hard.
- And we had to go far.
- It was too far.
And do you know what's funny?
We filmed the show...
- for two days there.
- Right.
So our managers and stylists
didn't have anything to do.
- So they dated each other...
- Romance.
- a lot.
- Right.
It happened a lot.
I bet the managers had a lot of fun.
- They did.
- It must've been thrilling.
So it was the managers'
and stylists' favorite show.
It's "Family Outing".
- You know the manager.
- Right.
He met his girlfriend there.
- That's right.
- Really?
They dated for about 4 to 5 years.
But they broke up.
- Hey.
- He's married now.
You shouldn't say
that they are broken up.
They're broken up.
- They broke up.
- That sounds romantic though.
They were very much in love.
- Gosh.
- That's romantic.
Ji Hyo joined the show,
and she slept there.
- In the situation.
- You know what it was like there.
Ji Hyo, wasn't it hard
for you back then?
- It was really hard.
- Was it?
It was hard.
It's even harder for actresses
to get used to it.
Of course. I wasn't
used to the setting,
and I was nervous.
And I even dressed up
as a ghost at night.
I had to hide.
I fell asleep while I was hiding.
I was supposed to show up.
- Right.
- So the crew members woke me up.
- How could she...
- "You should wake up."
- I was asleep like this.
- That sounds just like Ji Hyo.
I had to surprise the members.
She was like that.
(August 2009)
(She woke up from her sleep
and played a ghost.)
(Her face is all puffy.)
(The sleepy ghost
showed up like that.)
(The ghost is excited
to go back to sleep.)
(She disappears with sleepy eyes.)
So it started the rumor...
- that she's easy-going.
- That's right.
- She just fell asleep.
- All she did was sleep.
Ji Hyo just slept there,
but people thought
she was easy-going...
- and nice.
- Ji Hyo?
I don't know
why we thought that way.
We just imagined what she was like.
Why did we think that way?
When was it? Was it 15 years ago?
It was about 13 or 14 years ago.
Gosh, that was a long time ago.
I know.
This is the same.
After some time, we will be like,
"Back then, we were..."
- "When we did Running Man..."
- "You know Running Man..."
"Has it been 10 years already?"
It wouldn't be that long.
It will happen in about five years.
Why can't I talk about it
10 years from now?
Because...
that's a long time.
I'm sure we will do that.
You'll see.
So how do you feel?
You said it doesn't
feel like a long time.
I know you look a lot older now,
- but what about your heart?
- It's the same.
- Do you feel the same way?
- It's pretty much the same.
- My heart hasn't changed at all.
- I said that before.
I feel the same way
as when I was 20.
So when the elders meet
their friends from school...
- It's just like that.
- They still swear...
and make the same jokes.
This is what they do.
"You blowfly."
"You haven't changed at all."
They just look their age,
- but I say, "You haven't changed."
- That's true.
- That's what happens.
- Let's say there's a gentleman...
who sounds decent and respectable.
But when he meets
his childhood friend,
"You punk."
(They become mischievous boys
when they meet friends.)
That's right.
- "You silly."
- They just act the same way.
"You haven't changed
at all, you punk."
- I'm surprised when I see that.
- Seriously,
- I think Haha is still...
- "Don't say that,"
- "you punk."
- "You silly punk."
Haha is still like
a little kid to me.
He looks like a little kid.
- So...
- I know.
- I understand.
- Sometimes...
I just forget...
that he's a father of three kids.
To me, he's just a reckless punk.
That's when he was young.
Like when we did "X-Man".
- I still remember the time.
- That's funny.
So do you not feel
like you're a grown-up?
When do you feel mature?
I just know...
- Married people will feel that way.
- that I'm a grown-up.
(We will be back with The Day
for Chattering 2 someday.)
(And it's the morning of Running
Man's 11th year anniversary.)
(A pretty wall is set up
at the entrance.)
What is this?
What's going on?
(What's going on?)
(The frog jumps up
to the filming set.)
Why am I the only one here?
(She finds the photo wall
and the sign at the entrance.)
- What is this?
- You should take a photo here.
- A photo?
- Pose for the camera here.
Hello.
What is this for?
What's all this?
(She's asked to pose for the camera
in front of the photo wall.)
- This is...
- This is just a photo shoot.
Then what is this phrase?
We prepared some phrases
for each of you.
But this isn't true.
I'm not like this.
It's a misunderstanding.
You can't define me like that.
You didn't even ask me.
(The guest lover already
forgot about her past.)
We don't even have
guests these days.
I haven't met a lot of male guests
for the past four years.
- Can I take pictures here?
- Yes.
- He's the photographer.
- Should I pose for the camera?
Yes. This is good.
(Posing)
(Always nice to male guests,
always serious about romance)
(Model number 1 is quite brazen.)
- Excuse me for a second.
- Okay.
We got a lot of good photos.
- We can finish it then.
- No, take more photos.
We haven't gotten
the best shots yet.
We need the best shots.
- The other members are waiting.
- We haven't gotten the best shots.
Let me try a bust shot then.
(The model insists on
taking more photos.)
Good.
Look at the camera.
You look great now.
(She tries her best
to get the A cuts.)
Lower your head a little.
You look pretty. Good.
(You look pretty. Good.)
Did you hear that?
(She asked for a longer session
and got more cheesy photos.)
It's done.
(She asked for a longer session
and got more cheesy photos.)
Aren't you going to do
something refreshing?
Something refreshing.
Take a couple of refreshing photos.
(Something refreshing)
(She tries to look refreshing
by twitching her face.)
- Okay. It's done.
- Is it over?
Thank you.
- Will you photoshop the photos?
- Of course.
It looks good.
Sir, you were serious about that.
I look pretty in the photos.
(Sir, you were serious about that.
I look pretty in the photos.)
I thought he was joking.
Hello.
(Next up is the boy in overalls.)
You will take photos here
before we start.
What's this?
- What are we doing?
- We can't see the phrase.
You should read the phrase.
That's what describes you.
Running Man...
(Yang Se Hyeong's little brother,
the king of Empty Head Land)
All right.
That's too normal.
Are you done?
Don't try to be funny.
Just act natural.
Lower your head.
And don't stick out your mouth.
Push your mouth back in.
(Lower his head
and push his mouth back in?)
What's that?
Try to look smart.
Without a smile. That's cool.
That's cool.
(The boy in overalls looks better
with his mouth covered.)
Look at the camera. Good.
What's going on?
What was that?
Done? Thank you.
- Who's next?
- Is he the guy...
- who was here for Kwang Soo?
- Right.
The pictures were great.
- He was here before.
- Really? Is that him?
I'm so thankful.
What's this?
Hello.
- Hey, Tooniverse.
- It's Jae Suk.
Tooniverse? I'm not
a cartoon channel.
- Are you a game channel?
- No.
A game channel for children?
You should take photos.
- What photo?
- We will take photos of you.
Stand here.
- You're wearing a colorful shirt.
- I don't have...
many poses.
(The first pose
of the nation's beloved MC is...)
Jae Suk, that's not cool.
- That's what comedians do.
- Do something funny.
I should wear a suit.
This one is too cute.
(All right.)
It's like
an insurance company commercial.
- K brand!
- D company!
I got insurance from D company too.
(He looks as if he's posing
for a flyer.)
(Making a funny face)
(Influenced by capitalism)
- That's an ad for K brand!
- K brand!
I've been enjoying their products.
The outfit I'm wearing is not good
for charismatic poses.
- What a shame.
- I'm wearing a cute outfit too.
Hello.
- He knew about this, didn't he?
- Hey, you look great.
- I bet he knew.
- Haha.
(Haha arrives in a nice outfit.)
Haha, you look so great today.
- Haha, you knew about this, right?
- No, I didn't know.
- You're lying.
- You look so great.
- Then why did you dress so nicely?
- Do I look great?
Yes, you look amazing.
(Do I look great?)
That's annoying.
I can't even look at him.
- He really looks amazing.
- He looks great.
- Haha.
- He's trying to look cool...
wearing his pants inside out. Gosh.
Haha, you look like Kwon Jung Yeol.
Look at the camera.
- From the band 10cm?
- Yes, 10cm.
- Let's call him "Mr. Dirty 10cm".
- Did you not wash your hair?
- Instead of "Mr. Dirty Mustache".
- Did you not wash your hair, Haha?
I have to admit,
Haha looks fabulous today.
- I didn't expect a photo shoot.
- I know, right?
But I dressed up as a cute guy.
Don't I look cute today?
- I dressed like a little boy.
- He looks playful, right?
Are you two
Super Mario and Papillon?
(Super Mario, Papillon)
- I don't look so bad, I guess.
- You and I look quite great.
You look like a celebrity
since you're standing with them.
- Me? Right?
- Yes.
They're so annoying.
So Min, you don't belong
in that group.
So he's been dressing like this
for his online videos...
for the past two years...
- And his subscribers...
- Oh, that's...
- It's been 1 year.
- 600,000 or 70,000 subscribers?
- Jong Kook has a million.
- We did well.
- I know. It's been successful.
- Indeed.
Hello, everyone!
- Jong Kook, stand there.
- We're having a photo shoot.
- You didn't dress up.
- What is this?
- Hey, Jong Kook looks...
- He's dressed for the beach.
- Jong Kook.
- Okay, that's nice. You look great.
Wait. Mr. Photographer,
do you really think he looks good?
- Stop lying.
- I really think he looks cool.
He looks as if he's attending
a wedding in that outfit.
(He actually goes to weddings
in this outfit often.)
- "I'll drop off my gift and leave."
- That's why...
"I have to go to the gym urgently."
- True.
- "Why, Jae Suk? What is it?"
"Since I'm not
dressed appropriately,"
- "I can't meet the couple."
- "I'll go and watch a soccer game."
- "I can't take photos with them."
- Exactly.
That's exactly how he looks
right now.
- Is it done?
- Jae Suk.
- Thank you.
- You know what I always say.
Of course I know.
- Right.
- "I didn't want to miss it."
"Jae Suk, I just...
So I decided to stop by."
"I had to come.
I should at least see them."
And shortly after he arrived,
he says, "Jae Suk, I'll get going."
(I didn't want to miss it.
I had to come. I'll get going!)
(Then he leaves hastily
to go to the gym.)
"Let's go!"
- He would run...
- "Let's go back now."
- "Where are you? I'm leaving now."
- Ji Hyo is coming.
"Get the car ready."
- There she comes.
- Ji Hyo is coming.
- Hello.
- "Get the car ready."
Please stand over there
and strike a pose.
- Ji Hyo.
"She's Cheon Soo Yeon
before going to the salon."
- "And Song Ji Hyo afterward."
- Please strike a pose.
- "She's in her prime for 11 years."
Cheon Soo Yeon!
- "In her prime"!
- How pretty!
Did you go to the salon?
- She did. Look at her hair.
- Then Song Ji Hyo!
- Cheon Sung Im.
- Did you get your hair done?
- Of course.
- She had her hair blow-dried.
- I had my hair blow-dried.
- You two look like...
You two look like a couple
at an outdoor wedding ceremony.
(His joke caught them off guard.)
- He keeps making jokes like this.
- At a guest house in Yangyang.
- Why...
- Lock your fingers together.
- You two look great together today.
- Indeed.
- Gosh, seriously.
- I thought differently yesterday.
- Really?
- It changes every day.
But today, you two look
so sweet together today.
- Really?
- You look different today.
- Look.
- Oh, my.
- Gosh. He looks so flashy.
- What's going on?
- Hang on.
- He looks so flashy.
- Look at his shoes.
- Jae Suk, look at his shoes.
Look at his shoes.
My gosh. What's that?
That's unbelievable.
Jae Suk, look at his shoes.
(He looks like a leopard
in shiny silver boots.)
- My gosh. Hold on.
- Look at his shoes.
- Why?
- His shoes.
(Shooting a tranquilizer dart)
(But even the tranquilizer dart
couldn't stop...)
(his dazzling steps
with pointy-toe boots.)
Gosh, that gives me goosebumps.
- What's that?
- I'm getting goosebumps.
- I can't bear to watch this.
- It's the highlight of my look.
- Go and stand over there.
- What's that?
- You'll have photos taken.
- How silly.
- What's this?
- Gosh. This is unbelievable.
- What's going on?
Stand there and strike a pose.
It says,
"Health, longevity, blessing".
Is this his 60th birthday or what?
- My gosh.
- Those shoes...
- You're blocking the letters.
- "Health, longevity..."
Are you ready?
Is this his 60th birthday or what?
What's wrong with his shoes?
(Tell them)
(I'm not ready yet to die)
(The humans are singing...)
(while wishing the leopard
a long and healthy life.)
(Health, longevity, blessing)
(The shiny silver boots
have been saved in the photos.)
- Oh, wow.
- How nice.
- That's so unique.
- What's with your shoes?
What about my shoes?
- Those are too shiny.
- Celebrities wear shoes like them.
We see people like him on
"What on Earth".
- I know Suk Jin well, you know.
- I've seen them on the show.
- Suk Jin, wait.
- Why?
I think I can find a chocolate bar
if I unwrap this.
- Hershey's.
- A chocolate bar wrapper.
It looks like
a chocolate bar wrapper.
- Gosh, you guys.
- Suk Jin, I really think...
- They're so shiny.
- My goodness. They're so shiny.
- Why? Aren't they nice?
- Suk Jin, dance for us.
That's great.
- You can tell how anxious...
- My goodness.
- Suk Jin is, right?
- Why? I like them.
- How?
- He keeps stepping back and forth.
- With small steps.
- That's not true.
My stylist gave me two options.
- All right!
- My stylist gave me...
- Okay!
- Let's move on.
- Two options.
- That was great.
- What will we do on this sunny day?
- So I picked these.
- What are we going to do?
- We're all here.
- My gosh.
- This episode we're shooting now...
- Yes.
- will air on July 11.
Do you know what day it is?
- Yes, I know.
- What day is it?
- The day when our show premiered.
- Correct.
Why don't you know that?
Our first episode aired
on July 11, 2010.
- My goodness.
- Then we should invite Kwang Soo.
Let's call him.
Today, you will have
a group photo taken...
to celebrate our 11th anniversary.
(They will have a group photo taken
to celebrate the 11th anniversary.)
First, since you all dressed nicely,
you will pose normally
right where you are standing now.
- "Normally"?
Does that mean we'll take one
that's abnormal as well?
We need to dress normally...
- to pose normally.
- Suk Jin, sit on this chair.
- I'm glad we dressed cute.
- Right?
(Mr. Silver Boots became downcast
as he doesn't look ordinary.)
I must say,
my stylist is not normal.
Why? You look great.
- Suk Jin, honestly...
- I really think those are too much.
- Why?
- Your clothes look fine.
- But your shoes don't.
- These shoes are trendy these days.
- Shoes like these?
- Yes.
- You could've worn...
- Don't they look so cool?
You'll see that everyone
is wearing these in Gangnam.
- I live in Gangnam, you punk.
- You do?
- Why would you swear at me?
- Why would you swear at him?
- Why would you do that?
- I live in Gangnam.
- Why would you swear at me?
- What's wrong with you?
- Gosh.
He's treating me like an idiot now.
- Why would you swear at him?
- Why? What's wrong?
That punk said that everyone wears
shoes like these in Gangnam.
- It's true. You'll see it.
- I mean...
- Why did you call Se Chan "punk"?
- Why did you do that?
- He deserves it.
- You're ridiculous, mister.
- Exactly.
- Don't call me that.
- You want me to sit here? Why?
- Please sit down.
- Please sit.
- Why?
Because you're older than us.
We're having a group photo taken.
- My gosh.
- Sit on the chair for now.
I'll stand next to Haha
so I'll look younger.
Don't make it look like
I'm in a wheelchair.
I'll stand next to Suk Jin.
Suk Jin, you look like
a retired chairman of a company.
A successful shoes company.
Please stand closer to each other.
- Like this?
- I see.
- All right.
- Dad.
- It will look like a family photo.
- A daddy from the 1980s.
- Hey, you're blocking me.
- Is this what you wanted?
Haha, the daddy from the 1980s.
- I'll take a few photos as you are.
- Okay.
(Photos with the tycoon
of the shoe industry)
- All right. We're done.
- Okay!
Nice.
Okay!
Thank you.
You've finished the photo shoot...
where each of you showcased...
- your uniqueness.
- Yes.
It was sad to finish the photo shoot
just like this,
we planned
the Strange Family Photo Race.
- "Strange"?
- What is it?
You will have your last photo taken
with a special theme at the end.
Does a family like this
even exist in this world?
There are seven roles for you
to play,
and you will dress as the person
you'll play.
- Oh, we'll put on makeup.
- I knew it.
You'll get your roles
through an auction at the end.
Oh, we'll have to buy it.
To earn money to spend
at the auction,
you will play games
divided into three teams.
I bet we need more money
to get a better role.
Each of you will receive money
according to the game results.
And you can turn in some of it
to spend as your team money.
(They can turn in their money
to use as the team money.)
- Goodness, you.
- My gosh.
Do you think that will work?
You can spend only your team money
at the auction.
- I see.
- Only our team money?
(They can spend only the team money
at the auction.)
(The character auction begins.)
(Team A, Team B, Team C)
(They can get as many roles
as the members on each team.)
Each team will get
as many roles as...
the number of members the team has.
And then you pick one of them
with your individual fund.
How are we supposed to do that?
I'll team up with Ji Hyo.
We get roles for the team
with the team fund.
- Choosing the team is important.
- Then we choose one of them.
Can you show us how we'll dress
for each character?
I'll tell you
about the characters now.
- First, Dad.
- Oh, "Dad"?
- That's a good role.
- I'll do it.
- I want to be Dad.
- That sounds nice.
- We just have to put on a mustache.
- That shirt looks similar to mine.
- It doesn't look so bad.
- Next up is Mom.
- Mom is okay too.
- Ji Yeon dressed as Mom.
- Ji Yeon looks great.
- She looks great.
Why do you make the staff members
do things like that?
- I think I've seen it before.
- They're wearing matching shirts.
Next up is Teen Daughter.
- Oh, my.
- How cute.
- What's that? That's gross.
- Oh, boy.
- I think he looks cute.
- It's perfect for Jong Kook.
- Why did Nam Joong do that?
- He'd look cute.
Next up is Grandma.
- Grandma?
- Grandma would be...
- Is that Nam Joong?
- Yes.
- He's good at this.
- He has a thousand faces.
Newborn Baby.
Newborn Baby doesn't look that bad.
There isn't much to do
for Newborn Baby.
You can just wear the costume
and suck on a pacifier.
Next up is Dalmatian, the pet dog.
- That's the worst.
- How do we dress like a dog?
- How do we do that?
- That...
(Dalmatian, difficulty level, hard)
- How do we dress like a dog?
- Who will get that role?
- There's an animal character too.
- Suk Jin already looks like it.
- My gosh. That's...
- That would've been Kwang Soo.
- Suk Jin, you just have to...
- And Green Onion, the pet plant.
- What? How do we do that?
- Green Onion?
(Character 7, Green Onion,
the pet plant)
- But...
- That's too much.
- Green Onion?
- That would've been Kwang Soo.
- To get 1 of these 7 characters,
- We're in trouble.
- you will play games in the race.
- A dog and green onion?
I hope I'll be a human.
- You'll get to pick a character...
- Dalmatian is the worst.
- among the ones given to your team.
- Understood.
- Do you all understand?
- It's not a team match.
I'll tell you how we divided you
into teams.
You had photos taken
as you walked in here, right?
- Yes.
Photographer Kim Eui Kyum ranked
your photos earlier.
Those in 1st, 2nd, and 3rd places
are on the same team.
- Those in 4th and 5th places...
- Really?
and those in 6th and 7th places
will team up.
On the same team... We'll team up...
The member in 1st place gets
350 dollars,
and for each rank that follows,
it decreases by 50 dollars.
- Got it.
- 350 dollars at the beginning?
Once Mr. Kim writes down the result,
we'll announce the teams.
Please... I really don't want
to team up with Haha.
- Why?
- Maybe ours are color photos...
while only Haha's is
black and white.
- But to be honest, the teams...
- Yes?
- won't matter in the end.
- That's true.
- I agree.
- The individual role is important.
- That's right.
- We need to get a good character.
In the end, all we want is...
- to avoid the dog or the plant.
- Right. That's the point.
- All the other roles are okay.
- We just have to avoid those two.
All the others are the same.
Two of us will get
a penalty today...
- to put it simply.
- The results are out.
- He wrote the reasons as well.
- Okay.
The reasons too?
The member in first place is...
(The winner who will get 350 dollars
will be announced.)
- I'll tell you the reason first.
- Okay.
"He's dressed appropriately
to the time, place, and occasion."
"And he seemed confident
in his looks."
- It's Haha.
- Oh, yes!
- What did he say?
- I knew it.
Gosh, seriously.
Haha will receive 350 dollars.
- Haha is in first place.
- Oh, he had...
some cool poses.
Next, the member in second place.
- I see why.
- He must've done well.
"He struck cute poses
like a true comedian.
- I bet it's Se Chan.
- Yang Se Chan.
(2nd place, Yang Se Chan,
Cute poses like a true comedian)
- You two are on the same team.
- Right.
I'll receive a lot of money.
I don't care. It's okay.
- Next up is...
- My cute poses.
- the third place who'll join them.
- Right.
(The last person to join the team
of 3 members)
"A beautiful smile".
- Song Ji Hyo.
- Okay!
- That's great.
- Okay.
- This is good. It's not bad.
- This is great.
- We'll be a great team.
- Indeed.
(Ji Hyo with a beautiful smile is
in 3rd place.)
- Okay!
- That's great.
(Haha, Se Chan, and Ji Hyo
become one team.)
- We'll be a great team.
- Indeed.
- Ji Hyo became less loyal.
- This is a good thing.
- Hey, this is a good thing.
- There's nothing wrong...
This is a good thing.
If we team up together...
That's possible. You're right.
- If we team up together...
- Sounds great.
- That'd be great.
- Why?
I really hope that Jae Suk
and Jong Kook will be separated.
- If I team up with Jong Kook,
- Please let them be separated.
- we'll be invincible.
- We'll beat them all today.
- It'll be game over.
- Please.
- The member in fourth place.
- You and I won't turn in any money.
"She struck various poses
but they were a little too much."
Jeon So Min.
Oh, okay. Jeon So Min.
- So Min, step aside.
- In fifth place, joining So Min...
- The fifth place.
- I really hope so.
"He didn't seem confident
in his outfit." Yoo Jae Suk.
That's a relief.
(5th place, Yoo Jae Suk,
Not confident in his outfit)
- Jae Suk.
- I'm glad I'm on your team.
- You're always confident.
- One million subscribers.
- I think he always looks confident.
- That's weird.
- I didn't feel confident.
- He looked okay in his photos.
- The photographer saw that.
The member in sixth place.
"Too many cute poses,
lacks diversity". Kim Jong Kook.
The member in seventh place.
"I wish he had dressed younger."
Ji Suk Jin.
- How much younger must he dress?
- That's impossible.
Do you want me to wear
a newborn baby's clothes?
- You see, to be honest...
- How would that be possible?
You don't look younger than your age
in this outfit.
- Then how should I dress?
- I see what he means though.
I think that your stylist decided
to make you look funny.
I've seen that look in Gangnam.
- So...
- Gosh. I'm worried.
- The teams won't be changed.
- I'm in trouble.
- Okay.
- But... I mean...
- I wish I was on Jong Kook's team.
- I teamed up with Suk Jin.
- Suk Jin is...
- Let's turn in our money, okay?
Before we begin,
we'll put the money in your bags
and give you the bags.
- The hardest thing...
- We should do that.
about being on the same team
as So Min is...
to have a battle of wits.
- I've changed. You know that.
- Who will be Dalmatian?
- Nonsense. You haven't changed.
- Or green onion.
It's up to you.
But let's hand in just a little.
- Okay.
- Let's do that.
- Let's hand in a little.
- Hand in at least 50 dollars.
- That's a promise. It's not a lot.
- For your information,
- I promise.
- the amount that you gathered...
will be announced at the end.
- Hand in at least 50 dollars.
- Let's hand in just a little.
Even if I don't spend any,
you'd have the same amount as me.
- Promise to hand some in.
- Okay. I promise.
- That's a promise, okay?
- I already promised.
- Ji Hyo...
- We have the most money now.
You should hand in
at least 30 dollars.
- We might lose in the second game.
- True.
- Really. 50 from you, 100 from me.
- Let's do that.
- I'll hand 50 dollars in. Okay.
- Then both you and I...
- will begin with no money.
- Right. Okay.
We'll be on the same team
until the end of the day.
That's right.
We'll stick together until the end.
Se Chan,
hand in more than 30 dollars.
- Okay.
- Hurry up.
- You hand in more than 20 dollars.
- Come on. Hurry up.
Okay. Jae Suk,
this is very important.
- Just go already.
- It's so important.
- I said, hurry up.
- How much do you have? Shall I...
- give you 10 dollars?
- You guys won't keep your promises.
(Papillon is sowing
the seeds of distrust.)
Don't you think I know you guys?
I'm so nervous.
(Haha is the 1st to turn in
the team money.)
(Haha made his team members promise
to hand in even a little.)
Please hand in the money
to spend as your team money.
(How much money out of 350 dollars
will Haha hand in?)
(Rummaging around in the envelope,
he hands in the team money.)
Gosh. I met the wrong teammates.
There's a beggar on my team.
This is driving me nuts.
He's driving me crazy.
He stresses me out so much lately.
Do you know he acts like that
even when the cameras aren't around?
(He's been Haha's main cause
of stress.)
My gosh.
- I'll hand in some money.
- That's good.
I trusted you guys
and handed in the money.
I'll hand some in no matter what.
(Protruding Mouth Mario goes next.)
Haha, don't look.
Hey, hand in at least one bill.
Of course I'll do that.
I took out a whole bunch.
You don't have to do that.
(He doesn't expect that to happen.)
He doesn't trust me at all
these days.
(Se Chan, whom Haha distrusts,
also hands in the team money.)
I'm going next.
- Haha.
- One bill?
- What? No, 2 bills.
- 20 dollars?
- It's okay, right? What about you?
- Yes.
I turned in 40 dollars.
- That's a lie.
- So Min.
I really turned in 40 dollars.
How much did they turn in?
I'm not allowed to tell you that.
(Ji Hyo promised to hand in
even just a little.)
How much is it? Hold on.
- Ji Hyo! Hand in 20 dollars.
- At least 20 dollars.
At least pretend you're taking money
out of the envelope.
The individual money
is not important.
Hand in at least 20 dollars.
No, 30 dollars is too much.
- Can't you trust me?
- Just hand in 20 dollars.
- It's me. You can trust me.
- Okay.
(Can't you trust me? It's me!)
- I won't hand in any money for now.
- Okay.
(I won't hand in any money for now.)
(Ji Hyo didn't hand in any money!)
Ji Hyo!
- Please!
- At least open your bag...
Hand in just 20 dollars.
It's so hard to keep a secret here.
Ji Hyo, you didn't hand in anything.
- I did, Haha.
- Ji Hyo.
You should've handed in
at least 10 dollars.
(After Ji Hyo, who is dreaming
of a big twist at the end...)
This is my decision. Here.
(The 2 members of Team Jae Suk
are done too.)
- Go!
- Be reasonable.
- Okay. Let's go. Go now.
- I'm going.
- I'll keep my promise.
- 100 dollars.
I'm going to kill him
if he doesn't hand anything in.
(Jong Kook promised he'll have
his revenge.)
(And the leopard hands in
the team money.)
Suk Jin seems to have a hard time
making up his mind.
- Suk Jin, hand in the money!
- Suk Jin, hurry up and hand it in.
- It shouldn't take this long.
- I think...
- that he handed in 10 dollars,
- Good.
and then handed in 10 more.
20 dollars in total.
No, I handed in everything I had.
Oh, my. What is this?
(After changing into team uniforms,
they move to the next location.)
Where is my seat?
"Yoo Jae Suk", "Jeon So Min",
"Kim Jong Kook"... Oh, here.
Oh, my. This is a school chair.
This brings back old memories.
Is this product placement?
Tell me now.
- Yes.
- Okay.
Oh, my. That looks yummy.
I eat this so often.
I already like this.
It hasn't been released yet.
(The new snack was released
the day after the shoot.)
- It says it's tripe-flavored.
- Hey.
- Try it and...
- That's interesting.
(His nostrils flare
as wide as possible.)
- Does it really taste like tripe?
- Yes.
- It tastes like tripe.
- Many people will eat...
- My mouth is on fire.
- Hey.
Here comes the king
of product placement.
(Here comes the king
of product placement.)
(The man who calls himself the king
of product placement is here.)
The king of product placement
is here. Quiet down.
It's spicy, sweet, and salty.
Do you think that such simple words
like "spicy" or "salty"...
can describe this taste properly?
Then how should I describe it?
Please show me.
(Savoring)
So delicious.
- Is that it? Really?
- That's it.
- Oh, so delicious.
I like it!
- Hey.
- It's so good.
Stop showing the packaging
to the camera.
- Why?
- It doesn't look natural.
Try to hold it naturally.
- By the way...
- Do you think that looks natural?
- Does this look natural to you?
- Just try to look natural.
- Hey, hold it naturally.
- Hey.
Suk Jin,
you should let people see it.
- This would go well with rice.
- Seriously.
(This would go well with rice.)
- With rice?
- Why?
Is it too much?
But it tastes like tripe.
- I always eat tripe with rice.
- My gosh.
- You see...
- I'm not joking. I think...
We're supposed to cook this...
on a grill.
- We need a grill and charcoal.
- Excuse me. Give me a bowl of rice.
That will...
He carries it around with him.
I'm saving some for later.
I'll put it in my pocket.
I'll eat it later.
Hey.
It's hard to take it out,
and the chips will be crushed.
Then where should I put it?
(He puts it under his cap.)
Oh, my goodness. That's brilliant.
I'm impressed.
(He puts it under his cap.)
- You can't tell, can you?
- I can't tell.
- Goodness, you.
The king of product placement.
The P-king.
The P-king. I'm called the king
of product placement.
That was brilliant.
I can't beat him.
All right. I'll give you
the first mission right away.
- Okay.
- We're using a computer again?
Why are you making me use
a computer...
when I don't know how to use it?
The first mission
where you can get...
- money for the auction is...
- We must do well.
Indoor World Trip.
- "World Trip"?
- What is it?
- I want to go on a trip.
- What?
It's a game where you play
using the street view...
of a map website that allows you
to look around the world online.
- Oh, the street view?
- But...
I don't even use
a car navigation app.
Click the street view button
and you can see all these photos.
You can look around the street.
- I know that.
- I use it from time to time.
It shows real-life images.
- Look at the map on your screen.
- Okay.
Type in any location in the world,
and you can look around the street.
(Type in the name of the city
of your choice.)
(Choose any street in the world.)
(You can get real-life images
of the streets.)
(You can also move around,
however you want!)
Can you see the keywords here?
Your team will get points
whenever you find them.
(Example, Keyword,
A person sleeping on a bench,)
(3 points)
(You got 3 points.)
Do we get five points for a giraffe?
- Hold on.
- Five points?
Aren't you good at this?
A giraffe is worth five points?
I don't know how to view this map.
Type in the search word and...
This is too difficult.
- We should go for five points.
- I'm terrible at this.
Just try your best.
You can't look up any streets
in Korea though.
- We can't?
- How about Serengeti National Park?
I know how to use a smartphone...
but not computers.
How do you go backwards?
- Backwards.
- Here.
- Must I rotate the view?
- Yes, like that.
How do you go backwards?
Jong Kook and I are in big trouble.
Neither of us
know how to operate this.
A giraffe and a zebra.
A fully geared-up soldier.
First of all...
- Find one worth 5 points.
- Go for 5 points.
Head to Africa.
Let me tell you
how to use the program.
I can't see anything.
Okay, let's get looking.
I'm sure there's one here.
- I'm at the zoo.
- Nairobi isn't a serviced area.
I'm at the zoo.
(New York)
(Haha heads to New York first.)
(He's mindlessly looking
at the streets of New York.)
I can't head over
to the area nearby.
I want to go that way.
What's that?
What's with the red car?
- Any red car is worth a point.
- Here!
- I found one.
- Show us.
Over here.
What? Already?
(You already found one?)
Over here.
- What? Already?
- Isn't that in Korea?
- No, it's in Brooklyn, New York.
- Over here!
Haha, that is accepted.
- I also found a red car!
- Okay.
Haha, that is accepted.
- I also found a red car!
- Okay.
- The point has been taken.
- It's been taken?
You should've told me sooner.
What else then?
- Tell me.
- They told us earlier.
Has the game already begun?
Tell me what's on the list.
A busker, a jogger...
How can one find all these?
Think where you'll find these
and it'll be easier.
Hold on a second.
- Let's head to New York.
- Hold on a second.
(New York?)
Are we only allowed
to go for one point only?
- That was worth one point.
- I mean,
- can we go for other keywords?
- Sure.
(New York stroller)
(New York: no reviews)
(New York jogging)
("Jogging" turned up a search.)
How can one find these?
- Central Park?
- Take an educated guess.
Go to a place where you know
a lot of people go jogging.
Hold on a second.
- You can only score once, right?
- Yes, take it and it's yours.
Wait, over there.
- Me!
- What are those people in uniforms?
- Show us.
- Here.
- No way.
- I have one.
Where did you find them?
- It's worth five points too.
- Let me see.
- Did you find any?
- In Central Park.
You can find everything
in Central Park.
- Really?
- Head there.
Where?
A boyfriend taking a photo
of his girlfriend.
Shouldn't that be worth more points?
- Exactly.
- You'll find a lot there.
- Where there are a lot of people.
- In Africa or Kenya.
- I think I'll find an elephant.
- Wait a second.
How do you get over there?
I just pointed to a location
and got inside a mall.
- I found a stroller!
- Show me.
A stroller.
(He's worked up.)
- A stroller.
- Show me.
Here's a stroller.
- That's acceptable.
- Nice.
Hold on a second.
- A stroller.
- An alligator.
- I found a stroller.
- Can it be from a zoo?
- I think there will be one there.
- Where?
Guys, I lost my way.
And an elephant.
I was at a place
with many people earlier.
(He looks around,
but there's no one there.)
I was at a park earlier
with lots of people.
An alligator. Can it be from a zoo?
Hold on a second.
I'm in a parking lot.
I'm trapped in a parking lot.
(Nothing's around.)
Don't get trapped in places.
But I'm trapped in a parking lot.
- He's trapped in a parking lot.
- What do I do?
I can't get out of this place.
There aren't any people around.
Was this taken
in the middle of the night?
Why isn't anyone around?
- No one's around.
- Is this mall in Zombie City?
- Not a single person is around.
- What is this?
Where on earth am I?
- Why is it so spacious?
- Which neighborhood are you in?
- I'm currently in Kenya.
- The zoo.
Kenya? Oh, please...
I found an RV!
- Show me.
- Hold on.
I can't swing the view that way.
Must I see it like this instead?
How does one change the view?
Can you keep it down?
But there's an RV here.
- I'm almost there.
- Here!
Stay put, will you?
- It's from Honolulu.
- Accepted.
Okay.
(After hard work,
he finds an RV from Honolulu.)
Why can't I only spot those
worth one point?
Isn't there someone on their phone?
- Let's do this.
- Can someone answer Suk Jin?
Why are you making him
talk to himself like that?
- Let's head elsewhere.
- We're a team, guys.
We recently lost a member as it is.
- Go elsewhere.
- Be good to those who are left.
Unbelievable.
It's supposed to be
a wildlife sanctuary,
so where are all the animals?
There aren't any animals in the zoo.
- Can you believe it?
- The zoo...
I'm in Kenya at the moment,
but I don't know where.
- Why...
- I want...
to be in Nairobi. The National Park.
Why can't I see any people?
Where in Kenya am I?
Ji Hyo, find one, will you?
Wait. I think I stumbled onto one.
Which one?
(He clicked on a random street.)
Haha and Se Chan
scored seven points.
- Don't we have five points?
- Jae Suk, do better.
(He's on a road in Colorado.)
(What?)
- Which one?
- I stumbled onto something.
Look. I found cows!
- Is cow on the list?
- A cow.
- Yes.
- It's on the list.
- A cow.
- I stumbled onto one.
- Show him.
Look. I found a cow.
- Please confirm.
- A yellow school bus?
(Jae Suk urgently
looks for a school bus.)
Here. Someone is reading!
- Over here.
- Wait.
- This person is reading.
- I found a horse.
A street in New York...
has its name written in Korean.
- You're right. That's not it.
- See?
- No?
- It's not actually written there.
It's just like that on your screen.
It's just a tool
to help you navigate.
It's just like that on your screen.
It's just a tool
to help you navigate.
That's computer graphics.
She understood me though.
Over here!
Just so you know, I use a map
made by a Korean company.
(He's proud of Korean culture
and even our maps.)
(He looks around
the familiar Montgomery Street.)
Wait. I think this is a school bus.
- A school bus!
- Did you find one?
- A school bus.
- Is there one?
- No way.
- I found one.
- Nicely done.
- Here it is.
He found one.
I did, right?
Okay. A yellow school bus.
- Ji Hyo, find one, will you?
- Got it. Just a second.
Why aren't there...
any animals in the zoo?
The view is slightly distorted.
- Hey, Se Chan.
- Here.
I'm almost at Starbucks.
That's a school bus, right?
- I can only see roads.
- Okay. A yellow school bus.
Wild animals...
- Why are there no parked cars?
- What on earth?
Wait. Why am I in Itaewon?
- Itaewon.
- Korea isn't allowed.
Head to Italy instead.
What's this?
Here!
Someone getting a ticket
from a police officer.
Did you really find one?
- Here. Do you see the officers?
- Is there one?
Here. Do you see the officers?
(He spotted three
French police officers.)
Look.
Someone's getting a ticket.
It's the police.
- Come on.
- The police.
- That isn't what's happening.
- So he lied.
Are you kidding me?
- He's a fraud.
- Over here!
I should go where
there are a lot of parked cars.
Guys, I'm underground.
- I want to go back up.
- Hey.
- Look.
- I've been there myself.
You can't escape from that place.
Once you're in, you can't get out.
How do you go back above ground?
I'm heading to Broadway.
Don't be ridiculous.
Are you kidding me?
Wait, I found Starbucks.
Someone with a coffee to-go.
Here. Look at this.
That's not Starbucks.
- Look.
- It's Ediya Coffee.
It's not Starbucks.
This isn't Starbucks.
- It's not.
- Check out the straw!
The green one. Nice.
It might be from
Ediya Coffee though.
The straw is green.
(The Empty Head enjoys Broadway
with a surge of confidence.)
Where do I find
a soldier in full gear?
Maybe Iraq.
I found someone doing cosplay.
Over here.
This is Suk Jin
when he goes to the airport.
(Suk Jin at the airport)
That doesn't count.
This is Suk Jin
when he goes to the airport.
That's how he styles himself.
What's he wearing?
Look. This is what
you wear to the beach.
(The humble style Suk Jin enjoys
when he goes abroad?)
- Is that not allowed?
- What was it?
He's more stylish, so no.
(It's not allowed because
he's more stylish than Suk Jin.)
Because he's more stylish?
That was harsh.
- Unbelievable.
- Let's try again.
That's funny though.
"He's more stylish."
I found something!
- Hold on.
- Okay.
A zebra!
- What?
- I found a zebra!
A zebra!
I found zebra.
- Over here.
- Zebra?
- Here.
- That is accepted.
(Kenya scores 5 points
while traveling in Kenya.)
Las Vegas.
Where's Bluebird?
(Jong Kook is now in Las Vegas.)
Downtown Las Vegas.
Get going.
I remember this place.
I totally remember!
Do you mean the street?
This isn't the time
to enjoy the view, you know.
The outlet in Las Vegas.
(Reminiscing)
I totally remember.
This isn't the time to reminisce.
I parked here and walked.
Try finding an alligator instead.
Why did you even go
to an outlet in Las Vegas...
when you only buy the same things?
T-shirts that cost 20 dollars.
Why are the cars
all parked so neatly?
I found a soldier.
- What?
- Let me see.
(A soldier worth 5 points?)
- What?
- Let me see.
- The soldier must be armed.
- And in full gear.
Does the soldier have a gun?
(An armed soldier in full gear)
- And in full gear.
- Does the soldier have a gun?
This person isn't a soldier.
- Someone doing cosplay!
- I already found one.
(Se Chan already found a cosplayer.)
One was already found.
The soldier...
doesn't have a gun,
but there's a pot in front of him.
It's to collect money!
One to collect money.
Cosplayers ask for money, remember?
- It had on a uniform.
- She found a cosplayer.
He doesn't have a gun on him.
- He has that pot to ask for money.
- Maybe it was the Armed Forces Day.
- I found it!
- It must be somewhere.
It's looking good.
- Let's play for 10 more minutes.
- It's a flamingo.
No, that won't do.
I remember this place.
(He found a place
to reminisce about.)
I want to go there.
I think you'll be able to
find yourself on the streets of LA.
He's issuing a ticket!
Wait a minute.
He's...
Can I go to a zoo?
Here it is! A person reading a book.
- Over here.
- I was going to find it.
Look at this person.
I'm certain.
She is reading a book, right?
(It looks like
she's reading a leaflet.)
She is. She is reading a book.
It needs to be precise.
Can't it look like they're reading
a book from the back?
- But she's reading something. Look!
- They said it has to be precise.
But look at her!
- It needs to be clear.
- Fine, I'll show it from the front.
The streets of New York...
The people who have found
the least number of search words...
are Suk Jin and Ji Hyo.
- What?
- Hold on. I'll find one.
Wait! Isn't this a little vague?
- Why does he...
- I think it's naturally taken!
Why does he keep saying that?
It looks like he's taking
a photo of another woman.
(A man taking a photo
of his girlfriend)
He's pushing a stroller, but he's
taking a photo of another woman.
(He's looking at the women.)
- Gosh, why can't I...
- We'll give you five more minutes.
- Only five minutes?
- Let us play longer.
- Yes, let's do that.
- But it's fun.
- It's actually fun.
- It is.
- It brings back memories.
- It's nice.
I want to visit France.
(It feels like the thirst to travel
is being quenched.)
I really want to go.
I had so much fun here.
It feels like I'm on a trip.
(We hope we'll be able to shoot
our episode abroad soon.)
It makes me want to go on a trip.
- I really want to go.
- It's nice to travel indirectly.
I should do this
when I'm bored at home.
I found it! This is incredible!
There's a woman waving her hand!
(Haha found a woman waving her hand
at the camera.)
A woman is waving her hand
at the camera!
There's a woman waving her hand!
A woman is waving her hand
at the camera!
- We accept it.
- This lady...
She's actually waving at the camera.
You earned five points.
Look at this!
She's really waving her hand.
- We got it.
- She really is.
- My gosh.
- Will you keep quiet?
- Here, look.
- There's no bird?
- It must be somewhere.
- I found it.
I should go there.
- We should find a bird.
- A bird is...
- Jae Suk.
- Where are you?
There could be birds on the streets.
Take a look around the sky.
There could be one.
Yes, you can find one that way.
- Five people...
- Haha.
- I found a bird!
- You found one?
It's tiny, but it's here!
Isn't that an airplane?
Come on, that can't be
considered as a bird.
- It's a bird!
- A bird!
- But that's...
- It's a plastic bag!
- No, it's not.
- It's a bird.
- It's a plastic bag.
- No, it's not.
- It is a bird.
- It's a bird.
- Take a look, Seon Myung.
- It's a plastic bag.
- Take a look.
- No, it's a plastic bag.
- You can see its wings, right?
- Seon Myung, it's a plastic bag.
- It needs to be clear.
- It's not a bird.
- A bird.
- It's a bird! It is a bird!
- What do you mean? It's a bird!
- It's a plastic bag.
- Let me zoom in.
- She says it's not a bird.
- No, it is a bird.
- Come on, Seon Myung.
- It's not a bird.
- It's a bird!
- It's a bird. Look at this.
Seon Myung, come here.
- It's a bird!
- It's a bird. Look at this.
Seon Myung, come here.
- It's a bird!
- Come here!
- It needs to be clear!
- It's so clear!
- It's clear. It has wings.
- It's clearly a bird. It's a bird!
- It's a bird. Look.
- Seon Myung, it's a bird.
If it's not clear,
then it's not a bird.
- It's a plastic bag.
- No, it's a bird.
- You can see its wings.
- It needs to be 100 percent clear.
- No! It's not a plastic bag. Look.
- No! It has a tail and a beak.
We've already confirmed
that it's not a bird.
No, Seon Myung can't see it clearly.
It looks like a UFO.
It's clearly a bird.
Isn't it, Yun Sang?
- It has wings. It is a bird.
- It is a bird.
But she said it's not a bird.
What's with her? What's wrong
with Namkoong Seon Myung?
How can this not be a bird?
- It's a plastic bag.
- Come on.
Are you insane?
My gosh, a group of people
is waving their hands.
(A group of people is
waving their hands at the camera.)
Shouldn't you triple the points
I got?
Look at this!
I found a good one, right?
- I think there could be one.
- They're going crazy!
They keep waving their hands
at the camera!
- Stop looking for them.
- Stop looking for those people.
I found someone
waving their hand at the camera too.
There are many people...
- waving their hands.
- You found them already.
I think it'll be easy
to find a train.
It's rather easy to find a train.
But where could it be?
- Don't you know where they are?
- No.
(Their talk somehow
hurts Se Chan's pride.)
Why don't you look up
somewhere like France stations?
- Right.
- Or go to Switzerland.
I'm at the train station in Moscow.
Look. I'll find one.
This is a train station,
but I don't see any trains.
- How frustrating.
- This is driving me crazy.
There's no train.
(There's no train
at a train station in Switzerland.)
How come there's no train?
But we found a lot already.
- Right.
- They found a lot already.
There must be a train. It's
a train station. One should be here.
Isn't there a train coming?
(They're still looking for trains
that seem easy to find.)
This isn't easy.
- All right.
- You found one?
I found it.
- Here it is! I found a train!
- A train!
- I found one too.
I found a train.
(So Min only targeted Moscow
from the beginning.)
I found it.
- Here it is! I found a train!
- A train!
- I found one too.
(Jae Suk also headed to Russia.)
(He found a red train.)
A train.
- A train!
- We accept it.
Vladivostok!
- I looked up " Railroad Museum".
- A train.
Time's up now.
This wraps up...
We have a higher score though.
Team Suk Jin got four points.
(Team Suk Jin is in the last place
with 4 points.)
What did you two do?
Jong Kook just enjoyed his trip.
Jong Kook earned 3 points,
and Suk Jin got 1 point.
And the team in second place...
There's only one point difference.
(Which team placed 2nd
with only 1 point difference?)
The team in 2nd place
earned 18 points.
(Is it Team Haha or Team Jae Suk?)
The team in 2nd place
with 18 points is...
- It's Team Haha.
- Oh, really?
(Team Haha is in 2nd place
with 18 points.)
(We're in 2nd place?)
(Team Jae Suk succeeds in
turning the tables.)
Team Jae Suk is in 1st place
with 19 points.
They succeeded in finding a train.
They found a lot toward the end.
It wasn't a fair game.
He's not good with computers.
It really wasn't fair.
Team Jae Suk
will take 300 dollars each.
Team Haha
will take 200 dollars each.
And Team Suk Jin
will take 100 dollars each.
We'll give you the money,
Team Jae Suk.
(It's time to turn in
money for their team.)
You can give
the whole amount, right?
I will pay the whole amount
and I did too earlier.
- Will you do that this time too?
- Yes, I will.
(Jong Kook is determined to pay
the whole amount.)
- Should we give just 100 dollars?
- Sorry?
Should we give just 100 dollars?
- Let's pay 150 dollars each.
- 150? To be safe?
I think it would be better
if our team...
- Team Jae Suk, you can go first.
- has more money.
(So Min sets off.)
(Will So Min give 150 dollars?)
- One bundle is 50 dollars, right?
- Yes.
We decided to pay 150 dollars.
So I'll just give 50 dollars.
Just 50 dollars? Okay.
(She paid only 50 dollars
out of 300 dollars.)
All right, thank you.
Jae Suk, it's your turn.
So Min, I'm carrying
the whole thing.
Sure. I gave the whole amount.
- I'm carrying it.
- I gave the whole amount.
I'll pay the whole amount.
That's how I am.
- You should do the same.
- I don't have it!
Did So Min pay 150 dollars?
We can't tell you that.
(With suspicious eyes,
Jae Suk hands in his money too.)
I paid 40 dollars, and you paid
20 dollars earlier, right?
You paid 20 dollars too?
Or was it 10 dollars?
- I paid 20 dollars.
- 20 dollars?
- Then that's 40 dollars.
- I think that's enough.
- Then who will pay this time?
I'm so glad I'm not with them.
My head will explode.
- I'll hand in everything.
- Of course.
Do you mean it?
(After the breathtaking
mind game...)
Should I turn in mine this time?
If you seriously... Trust me.
Haha.
Trust me this time. I'm going to
hand in this for our team.
I'll hand it in just like this.
I get headaches
when I'm on the same team as Haha.
- Haha, if you...
- I'll hand it in for real.
Don't you dare lie to us.
We're paying 150 dollars.
You better turn the whole thing in.
(Haha took out the money
he's paying. How much could it be?)
Se Chan, don't try to fool us.
(With Ji Hyo's nagging, Se Chan
nonchalantly hands in the money.)
(Ji Hyo also hands in the money...)
(without hesitation.)
(She's handing in only 50 dollars?)
(She even contemplated
taking out 10 dollars.)
(Ji Hyo's decision to survive
among the cheating men.)
Ji Hyo, why is your team
making it so complicated?
Jae Suk, they're all frauds.
They're frauds, I can't trust them.
I'll go first.
Jong Kook has given up already.
(How will this mind game end?)
Here's the next mission.
- We need to win this.
- What is it?
It's the last chance
for you to earn the money.
- Really?
- It's our last chance?
- It's already the last mission?
- What?
This mission is called
You Can Tell From the Eyes.
(The last mission,
You Can Tell From the Eyes)
The team that isn't playing
will see the words...
that the other team has to
guess correctly.
Let's say the words Team Haha
has to guess...
- are apple, carrot, and onion.
- Okay.
Then the other team
will see those words in advance.
Then the team that isn't playing
can pick five words...
they want to ban.
So that they can't use those words?
The words for our team?
If the team playing uses
the banned words,
- 20 seconds will be added.
- When we describe the words?
If "you know" is banned,
we can't use those words.
Let's say the word is "camera".
You can ban them...
from using
a word like "electronics".
We can ban exact words?
That'd be nice.
It's difficult.
You can't ban exclamations
or pronouns.
Got it.
- Only words?
- Yes.
How about a word like "that"?
- You can't ban conjunctions.
- We can only ban words?
You can't ban any conjunctions
needed to explain.
- We can't ban infinitives?
- No, you can't.
We'll give you a paper to write down
the words you want to ban.
We can choose five each, right?
(Team Jae Suk: Yi Sun Sin,
Ji Suk Jin, spring rolls)
- That's right.
- They'll guess these words.
We need to ban the words
they might use to explain.
These are the words
that they will guess.
The words here.
They can avoid using these words.
- How about banning "politics"?
- What?
- "Politics"?
- It's related to "president".
- They can use that word.
- How about "national assembly"?
- Won't they use this word?
- They won't use that word.
Right.
(They're certain Team Haha won't
use the word, national assembly.)
No, they won't use this word.
- No, they won't.
- They won't use that word.
How about "commander-in-chief"?
They don't know that word!
- They don't?
- Of course not. There's no way.
- Let's use this then.
- They don't know that word at all.
They'll never use that word
their whole lives.
My gosh.
(Team Empty Head
is completely looked down upon.)
- Let's use this one.
- Shall we? Okay.
The words they might use...
There aren't that many.
Even when they need to use
technical terms,
- I don't think they will.
- We keep saying this.
"They don't know this word."
(They can't tell how empty
their heads are.)
- I think so too.
- Right.
- Yes, yes.
- I got it. How about this one?
- How's this?
- Yes!
(They try to come up with words
with little knowledge they have.)
You're so smart!
- Oh, the other way around?
- Yes, that's right.
I think Jae Suk and So Min...
(They'll use this word for sure.)
(Jae Suk knows Suk Jin
through and through.)
(Which words did he choose to ban?)
(Empty Heads
are having a serious meeting.)
What about this?
Let's use the opposite word of this.
It's this one,
- but they think it's the other one.
- Good idea.
- Right?
- Yes.
(Bursting into laughter)
- Right?
- I'm sorry,
but are you guys scientists?
- Are you?
- Who's the leader among you?
- Who's the leader?
Who's the boss?
It's Haha. He's the smartest one.
Excuse me. You there with a beard.
You there with a messy beard.
- I think he meant you.
- Do you think...
He meant Ji Hyo?
(Haha disses Ji Hyo.)
You're the one with the beard?
- Yes.
- The one with a messy beard?
- I was talking about him.
- She has some peach fuzz.
- Sorry?
- What is it?
The one who has hair
everywhere on his face.
Get a pencil...
Ask Young Jin for a pencil...
- and...
- Call Kwang Soo!
He keeps picking on me
because Kwang Soo is not here.
(The prankster found another target
to tease.)
He doesn't go along with Jae Suk.
We need to use this word
for this too.
I got a call.
(I got a call.)
Put him on speakerphone.
Yes, you!
- What is it?
- The one with a beard.
You with a messy beard.
You called the wrong person.
Let me say just one more thing.
Get off your high horse.
(Very tired of him)
There, I'm done.
Now I feel a lot better.
Please submit your papers now.
- Should we go first?
- Yes, Team Suk Jin will go first.
It's fun though.
I'm getting nervous!
We don't have a strategy at all.
We don't need one. Let's just play.
- Just trust me.
- You need to be witty.
I'll explain it well.
- You did a good job.
- You did really well.
- All right.
- They did?
They wrote the banned words
for our team?
Yes, they're the ones.
Ready, start.
Let's do this. Let's do it.
Let's go. We can do this.
Darn it.
(Banned words: Youn Yuh Jung,
seafood soup, plant,)
(vegetable, forsythia)
Just take it easy!
(Given word: Minari,
which means water parsley)
(Jong Kook has to describe the word
without using the banned words.)
Just step on the mine!
You only need to step on it once.
- You need to give up one.
- The clock is ticking.
Vegetable!
(He used the word "vegetable".)
(He uses the banned word
as soon as he started.)
Zucchini. Lettuce.
Sesame leaf.
- Vegetable wrap. Pork belly?
- He must use the other words.
- Meat.
- You might end up...
saying all the banned words.
(You might end up
saying all the banned words.)
- Be careful.
- We're running out of time.
Hurry up!
(They're having so much fun.)
- Did you watch Tae Hyun's movie?
- What?
The movie Tae Hyun was in.
- Tae... Taeyeon?
- You can't use gestures.
- Taeyeon? Which one?
- Yes.
- I meant Cha Tae Hyun. His movie.
- Oh, him?
- You need to stop talking.
- He's very calm.
- He told Suk Jin to stop talking.
He told him to stop talking
when he needs to get the answer.
- "Hello Ghost".
- Yes, I did.
- In the last scene, in gimbap...
- The last scene?
- It's in the gimbap.
- His father is a taxi driver.
Because of what's inside the gimbap,
Tae Hyun finds out the truth
in the end.
What was inside the gimbap?
I watched the movie 10 years ago.
You can't expect him to remember it!
Just say the words!
He can't even remember
what he had yesterday.
- A stem. It's a stem?
- A stem?
A stem vegetable?
Sweet potato stems?
- Which stem?
- You picked the good ones.
- What kind of stem?
- They can't avoid using them.
How does it look? Tell me its shape.
Is it flat? Wide?
Just keep throwing the words.
- I've been throwing a lot of words!
- You should keep throwing them.
Sesame leaf, lettuce,
broccoli, zucchini.
Sesame leaf and lettuce
are not stem vegetables!
(He explodes.)
- You need to describe it!
- What other stem vegetables?
- It's a stem vegetable!
- Which one?
- It's a stem. Think of others!
- What about a stem?
Jong Kook is really mad.
He's seriously mad this time.
I think it'd be better
just to use the banned words.
Just use the banned words.
Pickled radish.
It's a famous movie. The one
that got a big award recently.
The one that got an award?
"Parasite"?
No!
Which famous movie got a big award?
It received an award
from an American award show.
- An American award show?
- A Korean.
- A Korean?
- That's right.
- Youn Yuh Jung!
- No, the movie!
(He said the exact banned word.)
(Suk Jin smoothly said
the second banned word.)
I've been describing a vegetable
all this time!
(Jong Kook has been trying hard
to avoid saying Youn Yuh Jung.)
What is it again?
I can't remember...
- the title.
- I've been describing a vegetable.
They got it!
Jong Kook put his hand
in his pocket! He's really mad!
- They got it!
What's the title of the movie
Youn Yuh Jung was in?
"Summary"? What is it?
"Summary"?
("Minari" turned into "Summary".)
- What did he say?
- "Summary".
He said it's "Summary".
- What is it?
- This is driving me crazy.
What's the title again? Oh, gosh.
It's stem...
You said it's a vegetable!
- A vegetable. Which one?
- The one in this.
- Which one?
- They banned the word "vegetable".
They even banned Youn Yuh Jung.
I even said the word "award".
I bet they banned all these words.
- So that's...
- I bet they included "Academy" too.
He repeated the words.
You can't say it then. You said
they included "Academy".
Let's move on to the next one.
We can get 20 seconds as a penalty.
It's the person you see
when your prostate goes wrong.
Oh, it's a urologist.
- A urologist.
- That's correct.
The answer is a urologist?
- This is incredible.
- Oh, it's the second question.
And what's next? Describe it.
The last question.
Why are you stalling time?
The captain of editors.
A producer.
(They already said
two banned words.)
A captain of editors?
- They're saying all the words.
- It's crazy.
I said he's the captain of editors.
It is a producer
if it's someone who edits.
Shouldn't you think of
some other word...
when I said
it's the captain of the editors?
A captain who edits?
This is crazy.
What's the captain of editors?
We'd be in big trouble if they
included the word "edit".
We're bound to say this word.
We're in the last place anyway.
If the answer was "producer"...
- If the answer was "producer"...
- What are you doing?
If the answer was "producer"...
Just hold on.
If the answer was "producer",
I would have said...
- it's someone who edits.
- You told me to hurry!
- Listen. I'd have said that.
- You can say that later.
- What are they doing?
- Your time is up.
If I said it's the captain of
editors, the answer is Bo Pil.
- I said it in general.
- You can stop already.
- Bo Pil...
- Jong Kook.
The answer is Choi Bo Pil.
The captain of all editors.
Then you could've said
the producer of Running Man!
If I said it's someone who edits,
then the answer is producer!
I was trying
to avoid the banned words.
- That's not it.
- Just apologize to him.
Hey! The answer was so easy!
You could've pointed at him
and said, "It's him!"
We even included the word "him".
(Banned words: This place, producer,
captain, him, next to Chul Min)
(They even included that word.)
- You did?
- We banned "him" as well.
- We banned "him".
- Listen, my point is...
Is it okay to point at you
and say it's you?
Why can't we?
- But they included the word "him".
- We did.
I was only trying to
avoid saying the banned words.
- It's minari.
- We knew he'd say "him".
Suk Jin is hilarious.
Goodness, Suk Jin.
- He was totally...
- He was hilarious.
- told off by Jong Kook.
- They included "producer" as well.
- He should've thought of "captain".
- Why did you make it so hard?
- I mean...
- You could've said...
This is supposed to be hard!
They expected us to use these words,
so it's bound to be hard!
I told you we should just
use those words.
- The main producer of Running Man!
- Jong Kook.
You need to sing.
Don't abuse your vocal cords.
All right. Let's move on
to the next one.
- Use the easy words.
- Here's the question.
- Go.
- Is it easy?
(Banned words: Joe Biden, country,
election, Moon Jae In, captain)
Let's see how they do it.
He is Korea's...
(The word they have to guess
is "president".)
most powerful person.
President.
- Correct.
- They got it.
- I got it?
- It's too easy.
A peck... This is too...
Kiss?
- A deep kiss.
- You can't say that.
The first one.
- First kiss.
- You can't use gestures.
- You can't use that gesture.
- Why not? I only did this.
Hey! This would mean kiss.
I only did this.
It's okay. We got the answer.
- First kiss.
- You'll get a penalty.
They're getting a penalty.
(They move on to the next one
after getting a penalty.)
(Given word: Quadratic formula)
I don't think you can get this.
- Try us.
Don't look down on us. Just try us.
- Do you know this word?
- I'll just use the word. It's math.
- Pi!
- Yes, it is.
- Square root.
- It's all included.
- It's not a symbol.
- Se Chan will never use this word.
He can never say this word.
It's not a symbol?
Then is it a person?
Se Chan will never use this word.
It's not a person.
- 3.14!
- Ji Hyo doesn't know.
- It's not something like that.
- Is it a formula?
- That's right!
Fraction!
- That's it!
- What did you say?
You can't use gestures.
We should've thought of it.
Pythagoras...
It's something like that!
Keep going!
- That's all I know.
- What was that?
Do you know what an equation is?
- Equation. Pythagoras.
- It's something like that.
When people break up
- It's some kind of formula.
- "Love Equation"!
- What?
- "Love Equation".
Darn you!
- A formula?
- That's right.
What is a formula?
(You dumb fool!)
You don't know this?
- What is it?
- You must know this!
- It's a formula?
- I told you...
This is so frustrating.
A formula.
My closest friend's name...
- Geun Sik!
- Geun Sik formula!
It's that one! Geun Sik!
(They don't know how to
apply the hint.)
- "Geun Sik formula"?
- Geun Sik.
- That's right.
- "Geun Sik formula".
That's right. It's similar.
That's it! You're almost there!
- You're almost there!
- "Geun Sik formula".
- "Tenacity"?
- What?
(She only changed one syllable
to make use of the hint.)
- She said it's Geun Sik formula.
- Who?
- What did you say?
- Ji Hyo.
- Geun Sik.
"Geun Sik formula"?
- "Modern".
- You think that's the answer?
- Modern formula!
- Darn it!
(A terrible sight where Empty Heads
copy each other)
- Quadratic formula.
- Correct!
- Oh, it's the quadratic formula.
- "Geun Sik formula"?
They said it's Geun Sik formula.
- "Modern formula".
- That was hilarious though.
- It's the quadratic formula.
You said the banned words
four times, including the penalty.
It's okay.
- We did well.
- That team is in last place anyway.
Don't make it hard,
and say the questions fast.
- Let's do it fast. Okay.
- Let's just say the banned words.
It's better to say the banned words.
- Let's do this.
- I hope the questions aren't hard.
- Let's do it.
- We picked the good ones, right?
We'll break through them.
Ready, go.
Yes, just say all the banned words.
But I think she'll say
the banned words.
(Given word: Yi Sun Sin)
A famous general.
General Yi Sun Sin.
- I got it?
- Yes.
- What was that?
- All right!
(Given word: Ji Suk Jin)
(It's hard to describe Suk Jin
without saying the banned words.)
(Banned words: Not that, here,
old fossil, old, unattractive)
The grandpa of Running Man.
- Ji Suk Jin.
- There you go.
It's way too easy.
(He perfectly described Suk Jin
with just two words.)
- How did he avoid all of them?
- That was too easy.
Jae Suk explained it so well.
Jae Suk, I can see the answer
in your eyes.
This is...
(If So Min gets the last one fast,
they will place 1st.)
Just spit it out.
Vietnam.
It's very tasty.
- Banh mi.
- Food.
(He starts off
by stepping on the 2 mines.)
In Korea, we have lettuce wraps.
In Vietnam, they have...
(Jae Suk used 3 banned words,
but So Min doesn't have a clue.)
They are done.
In Korea, we have lettuce wraps.
In Vietnam, they have...
(He used "Wrap" 2 times
and "Vietnam" 3 times.)
Coriander?
- What could it be?
- How could she not know this?
He gave you everything.
It's like a minefield.
- Go. Go.
- What could it be?
Wrap! Wrap!
Wrap?
I don't know this one. Pho. Pho.
(She says "Pho" multiple times
without knowing anything.)
No, no.
I don't know this one. Pho.
Pho.
Pho. Pho.
- No, no.
- My goodness.
- Hey.
- Banh mi. Banh mi.
- No.
- Keep going.
There is something like a mixed pho.
It's pho, but...
Stop talking about
miscellaneous things.
- But...
- Say the answer.
- It uses...
- Pho.
rice paper. Rice paper.
(They covered all banned words.)
(They stepped on so many mines.)
- Spring rolls.
- There you go.
- You know,
- The one we chose worked well.
you stepped on...
every single mine 16 times in total.
You said every single one of them.
- Rice paper.
- How?
- Vietnam. Pho.
- I can't believe you.
- You said every single one of them.
- So Min.
I couldn't think of the answer.
When I said it's like
the lettuce wrap of Korea,
- you should have thought of it.
- Seriously.
- We chose the banned word well.
- We did a good job.
A minefield!
Here is the result.
First place is Team Haha.
(1st place is Team Haha.)
Geun Sik formula!
- Geun Sik formula!
- Spring roll.
Both teams went...
- well over five minutes.
- Geun Sik formula.
- My goodness.
- How did we go over five minutes?
Since both teams went
over five minutes,
decide with rock-paper-scissors.
- Okay.
- Rock-paper-scissors.
Let us take second place.
- We took the last place twice.
- All right.
Beat us in rock-paper-scissors.
Go ahead.
Rock-paper-scissors.
- Okay.
Let's submit a lot of money
this time.
- I didn't play scissors this time.
- Let's submit a lot of money.
It's your last chance to submit
team money.
1st place, 2nd place, and 3rd place.
The 1st place team will get
350, 300, and 250 dollars.
Then the other teams will get
200 and 150 dollars...
- and 100 and 50 dollars.
- Why?
The other teams will decide...
who will get how much.
(The other teams will decide
who will get how much.)
We should give Haha
the biggest amount.
We will give Haha
Yes. We will give Haha
the biggest amount.
- Me?
- Yes.
- Thank you, but...
- It's advantageous to us.
Haha won't contribute to team money.
- Then Se Chan and Ji Hyo.
- Okay.
We will do that.
Please decide on the distribution...
among the five of you.
- Suk Jin should get more money.
- Suk Jin.
Suk Jin should get more money.
(He is a habitual traitor.)
Suk Jin will get 200 dollars,
and Jong Kook will get 150 dollars.
Between them,
So Min should get more money.
(Team Jae Suk has So Min.)
So Min will get 100 dollars,
and Jae Suk will get 50 dollars.
Don't worry, Jae Suk.
I will submit all the money.
- Really?
- I will submit all the money.
(Suspicious)
Okay. I will believe you.
- We need to submit a lot of money.
- I will go...
- and submit the money.
- Submit a lot of money.
- A lot of money?
- Of course, Haha.
- How much are you thinking?
- I am thinking 200 dollars.
Are you sure?
Otherwise, we won't be able
to avoid the green onion costume.
(It's the last chance to avoid being
the green onion or Dalmatian.)
200 dollars.
Once we bring good costumes,
- we can choose among ourselves.
- That's right.
It's important that we bring
good costumes.
We need money for the auction.
Would he really contribute
200 dollars?
I think I should contribute
this much...
since I have 350 dollars.
I should make a contribution.
I think I should contribute
this much.
(Did Haha submit a lot of money
as he promised?)
(Se Chan said he will submit
200 dollars.)
(He finishes submitting money.)
(Ji Hyo put down 60 dollars.)
(Will she be loyal to the team
and submit a lot of money?)
I will submit this much.
(She betrays the team
this time as well.)
(Ji Hyo has been reborn
after 11 years.)
We need to win.
I will go all in.
(Team Suk Jin and Team Jae Suk
finish submitting money as well.)
The Strange Family Photo Race
to celebrate the 11th anniversary...
has come to an end.
All teams have turned in the money,
so you will decide on the roles
for the family photo...
through the Role Auction.
(The Role Auction)
Here is how
the Role Auction will go.
We combined the team money
you have turned in so far.
Each team will check...
the amount we wrote down.
You should keep the amount a secret
from other teams.
That way, you can decide
to bid more money or not.
Even if you have a big amount,
you won't get other good roles
if you spend too much on one role.
- I see.
- They need three roles...
while we need two roles.
We will have a public bid
for the Role Auction.
Once the role
and the starting price get revealed,
raise the paddle...
and place your bid.
The team that makes
the highest bid...
will win the role.
The team that obtained
enough number of roles...
- will be removed from the auction.
- Two roles.
I see why a team of three is
at a disadvantage.
We were at a disadvantage
from the start.
- I know.
- We will give you the team money.
Don't show it to other teams.
We won't have a problem
if we followed the plans.
I am not joking when I say
that it wasn't intentional.
I got confused.
(Ji Hyo got the taste of betrayal
and turned in only 110 dollars.)
Check the amount
and don't show it to other teams.
(How much team money
did Team Haha gather?)
This is bad.
Gosh.
(A mysterious exclamation...)
Did you turn in all the money?
Not bad.
(and even more mysterious
facial expressions)
- All right.
- You know,
it's nice to see some loyalty
for the 11th anniversary.
You must be surprised.
- No, no.
- The 11th anniversary.
That's why.
I got confused.
(So Min's eyes twinkle
because she saved up money.)
There is a lot.
(How much money
does Team Jae Suk have?)
(370 dollars!)
- There is a lot.
- Yes.
Seriously. There is a lot.
(So Min didn't submit much,
but there is a hefty sum.)
It's meaningless
if the team doesn't have...
much money.
I will turn in 150 dollars.
Did So Min turn in 150 dollars?
You didn't do this alone.
It's a lot.
- All right.
- You know,
I am not joking when I say...
that it wasn't intentional.
I got confused.
(Suk Jin got 400 dollars
and Jong Kook got 300 dollars.)
It's as I expected.
All right.
(The Role Auction begins now!)
Here comes the role of Dad
in the family portrait.
- Let's begin...
- We need to buy it.
- the auction.
- It's a good one.
- The starting price is...
- 10 dollars.
- Dad is a good one.
- Yes.
- 10 dollars.
- 20 dollars.
- 30 dollars.
- Go.
- 40 dollars.
- 50 dollars.
Let's make them use up their money.
- 70 dollars.
(Team Haha bids 70 dollars.)
- 80 dollars.
- 100 dollars.
- Bid 150 dollars.
- 150 dollars.
150 dollars.
(Team Suk Jin bids 150 dollars.)
- 150 dollars.
- What?
150 dollars is too much.
Then the other member
will get the green onion.
Hold on.
How much money do you guys have?
We turned in so much money.
- Hold on.
- How much money do you guys have?
Don't you guys have much money?
- We have money.
- This is our strategy.
There are three of us.
(What could be the strategy
for this 3-member team?)
- 160 dollars.
We should raise the bid.
- 170 dollars.
- 180 dollars.
- 190 dollars.
- 200 dollars.
(Team Jae Suk bids 200 dollars.)
- It's okay.
- 250 dollars.
(Team Suk Jin bids 250 dollars.)
(Did they just bid 250 dollars
for Dad?)
It's done.
5, 4,
- 3,
- 250 dollars is too much.
two,
one.
The bid is closed for Dad.
We did well.
We had to bring it no matter what.
- Hey.
- I am happy we got Dad,
- but we used too much money.
- Suk Jin.
- Look here.
- It's our strategy.
We still have a lot of money.
- Mom.
- So we have...
- We need to get Mom.
- We have 430 dollars left.
- Shall we start...
- from 50 dollars?
- We still have a lot of money.
(Jong Kook educated Suk Jin
from the very beginning.)
(He convinced Suk Jin
until the end...)
(with the leadership
of trust and revenge.)
(They turned in all the money
at first.)
(When they didn't do well
in the subsequent missions,)
(they turned in everything
for the team money.)
(Thus, they saved up 680 dollars.)
It's as I expected.
(Thus, they gained the high ground
despite doing badly.)
There is no way they have money.
They can't trust each other.
I think every team has
about the same amount of money.
- It's neck and neck.
- It depends on the strategy.
- The second role is...
- Mom.
- We need to get Mom.
- That's right.
Mom. It's an easy role, right?
- Let's buy it.
- Shall we start with 50 dollars?
Okay. We will start with 50 dollars.
- 50 dollars.
- 100 dollars.
- 150 dollars.
- 200 dollars.
- What?
- No way.
- 200 dollars.
This is easy.
We don't need to save up money.
- They don't have much money.
- 200 dollars?
They bid 200 dollars.
Did they bid 200 dollars
when they don't have that much?
Do they have that much?
Is Mom a good role?
Isn't it pretty good?
- It's pretty good.
- You just need to wear lipstick.
- That's right.
- It involves the wig, lipstick,
- and outfit.
- It's a simple role.
Hold on. What's the next role?
- Teen Daughter?
- Teen Daughter.
- You should be Teen Daughter.
- Let's get this one.
- Why?
You and I should be a couple.
- Really?
- Yes.
(You and I should be a couple.)
- Let's get this one.
- You know,
that made my heart flutter.
Suk Jin. For Teen Daughter...
Let them have Teen Daughter.
Okay.
- 300 dollars.
They are going all in.
- 5,
- They just need 1 more role.
- four,
- Go, Jae Suk.
three,
Come on.
- two,
- Aren't you going to bid?
- one.
- You should bid.
- What was that?
- Okay.
- This team got Dad and Mom.
- Is it set?
- That was successful.
Yes. That was successful.
- Teen Daughter.
- I think it's...
- a cute role.
- Let's get it.
- Ji Hyo.
Bid 150 dollars.
Let's start with 100 dollars.
100 dollars.
Don't miss this role.
- Let's take this to the end.
- 200 dollars.
200 dollars.
250 dollars.
- My goodness.
- That's a lot.
- 300 dollars.
- They bid 300 dollars.
- Then...
- Wouldn't you go bankrupt?
- 310 dollars.
- Everyone.
I am telling you this
because I have had enough.
Bid only the amount you have.
(I am telling you this
because I have had enough.)
("Bid only the amount you have"?)
How could you bid
the amount you don't have?
We don't know, okay?
We don't know how much you have.
Why would you bid
the amount you don't have?
Cover it.
(Ji Hyo felt bad about
turning in only 110 dollars.)
(180 dollars)
(180 dollars?)
Gosh.
(That means the 2 of them
turned in 70 dollars in total.)
All right.
Turn it in.
(Se Chan turned in 10 dollars
in the 1st round.)
(Haha didn't turn in any money.)
(Clean)
This isn't a good team.
(His teammates could say
the same thing.)
(In the 2nd round,)
(Haha turned in 0 dollars,
and Se Chan turned in 20 dollars!)
(In the last round,
he turned in a meager amount.)
It feels like a waste.
It feels so much like a waste.
(He regretted paying that much.)
(Ji Hyo didn't compare
to Se Chan and Haha.)
You can't do that.
- Then...
- You can't do that.
200 dollars.
200 dollars. 200 dollars.
- What?
- 200 dollars.
- It's a big amount, right?
- Okay. Take it.
- It's a big amount.
- Fold.
200 dollars.
- Hey.
- Don't you even have 200 dollars?
- What are you going to do?
- They are dirt poor.
They don't even have 200 dollars!
Why did you say that?
- The next role.
- Forget it.
- Grandma.
- Grandma isn't too bad.
180 dollars.
I guess they have 180 dollars.
- 180 dollars.
- 180 dollars?
- We can bid 250 dollars.
- That's right.
5, 4, 3, 2, 1.
(Grandma goes to Team Haha
for 180 dollars.)
- Okay.
- Why didn't you increase the bid?
We bought it for a cheap price.
- I know.
- The next one.
We will bid...
- How much?
- 170 dollars.
170 dollars.
Fold.
"Fold."
Newborn Baby is a good one.
We are done.
Thus...
- Why didn't I get Newborn Baby?
- Which roles remain?
It's disadvantageous to be
in a three-member team!
You didn't turn in any money.
- Why didn't you turn in money?
- Seriously.
- This team is a mess.
- I can't believe it.
You should have turned in money!
I am the only one
who turned in money.
- Really?
- I am the only one.
- This is a match for Grandma.
- Then Ji Hyo should get the role.
The team with Mom and Dad
will reveal how much they have.
- Okay. We...
- Do it separately.
- Do you have any money?
- No.
- Not at all?
Did you submit everything?
Jong Kook submitted everything.
(Opening his back)
- Did you submit everything?
- Jong Kook submitted everything.
Did you save up money?
10 dollars?
- Really?
- 20 dollars.
(I have 20 dollars.)
20 dollars.
I knew it. I said
they would have 10 or 20 dollars.
- 10 dollars.
- I can't believe you stashed it.
I know him well.
I knew he would submit everything.
Still, I am proud of you.
- I have improved a lot.
- Seriously.
Suk Jin did well.
Suk Jin, which role
would you choose?
The roles are about the same.
Don't you feel bad?
- What?
- You must feel bad.
All right. Shall I choose Dad?
- All right.
- Hold on.
- It will be funny that way.
- You must feel bad.
- No, no.
- Don't you feel bad?
I choose Dad.
Be Mom.
There is a reason why
I stashed 20 dollars.
- I want to be Dad.
- Mom.
Suk Jin is Dad...
- and Jong Kook is Mom.
- Okay, okay.
Team Jae Suk, reveal how much
each one of you has.
Please help me with this.
Which role would suit Jae Suk?
- Newborn Baby and Teen Daughter.
- Make him Teen Daughter.
Be Teen Daughter.
I will be Newborn Baby.
- Be Newborn Baby.
I will be Teen Daughter.
Now, reveal how much
each one of you has.
It's written on the envelope.
Jae Suk looked determined.
He didn't submit everything.
Who will go first?
Se Chan, go first.
- How much do you have?
- His envelope is thick.
I submitted a lot of money.
- I will end you!
- Be honest.
(By the order of the amount,)
(they will choose
from these three roles.)
- To be honest...
- That's...
- You are less than human.
- I don't know.
Someone counted my money wrong.
I have 760 dollars.
(760 dollars?)
Hey.
You are less than human.
Someone counted my money wrong.
I have 760 dollars.
Ji Hyo, how much do you have?
That's too much.
760 dollars?
- Ji Hyo.
- You have more, right?
You have more, right?
That means he submitted
only a tiny amount of money.
- Hey, how much do you have?
- How much do you have?
(How much money did Haha stash?)
- 870 dollars.
- Hey!
I can't believe them.
- That's too much.
- You got Grandma.
(He is unbelievable.)
- Ji Hyo, how much do you have?
- How much do you have?
590 dollars.
- She left...
- 590 dollars.
She left a hefty sum too.
That's not true.
It would have been disastrous
had she submitted more.
Please pick a role.
I choose Grandma.
Se Chan, please choose a role.
This is meaningless.
Gosh, this is driving me crazy.
- I think Green Onion is better.
- I know.
You have to wear a lot of makeup
for a Dalmatian.
Thus, the roles have been decided.
Let's dress up
and take the family portrait...
- before we wrap up.
- Okay.
I stashed money too,
but they were beyond me.
Please enter.
- Here?
- Which outfit does Grandma wear?
How about me?
Ji Hyo.
Se Chan.
- Yes?
- There is dirt. Premium dirt.
- No way.
- I guess you will be planted.
I don't have a shoot
for "Comedy Big League" today,
but I am seeing
the makeup artists here.
I can't believe
I am seeing them on Tuesday.
(Dalmatian takes the spandex.)
What will Ji Hyo and I wear?
Be quiet, you punk.
Hey, Dalmatian.
Se Chan.
I heard that you are Green Onion.
Put on the spandex.
- Really?
- Why would I put on the spandex?
It's your outfit.
Hey, Green Onion wears the spandex!
That's incredible!
- Green onion has a white stalk.
- You are right.
(Green Onion must put on
the white spandex.)
I see.
It's the worst.
I think you will need to stand
in a pot.
Shall I turn it to the side?
Okay.
- It's done.
- You need bangs.
Teen Daughter is better.
You don't need to wear much makeup.
(Jae Soon, a 16-year-old girl,
looks feisty.)
(He gets a bit of the blusher.)
Thank you.
- Are you done?
- Yes.
- You look pretty.
- Ma'am.
Ma'am, hello.
I should have chosen that role.
You look pretty.
I am jealous. You are done already.
- You will draw the wrinkles.
- Yes.
Is he Grandpa?
I am Dad.
- He doesn't look like Dad.
- Why is my mustache gray?
- You are Dad.
- He doesn't look like Dad.
Why is my mustache gray?
Please give him more ear hair.
(Ear hair will help him live
a long life.)
Dad didn't look like that
in the photo.
There is Grandma too.
- Mom...
- Oh, there is Grandma.
- There is Grandma.
- Dad looks too old.
- I see.
- Dad...
- My bad.
Dad looks like Grandpa.
Grandma shouldn't look like my wife.
How embarrassing!
Honey.
- You look like Grandpa.
- I am supposed to be your son.
I am satisfied
since I will be done pretty fast.
(He begins to transform into Mom.)
That was easy.
Why don't I resemble my mom
even when I put on a wig?
I look too much like my dad.
What are you talking about?
You look exactly like your mom.
- No, I don't.
- You look exactly like your mom.
- Do I resemble my mom?
- Yes. Only you don't know that.
I also don't think
I resemble my mom.
- Really?
- Hey, do I resemble my mom?
- Of course you do.
- How do I resemble her?
- I don't see the resemblance.
- You are the spitting image of her.
Do I resemble my mom?
Jong Kook, when will you be ready?
Are you my wife?
- This is like "My Little Old Boy".
- Seriously.
You do resemble your mom.
- You do resemble your mom.
- You do. Only you don't know that.
Only you don't know that.
You do resemble your mom.
I can't believe it!
- Shall I put it on?
- "I can't believe it!"
- Grandma.
- There you go.
There you go.
Give me a hug.
Go away.
- Give me a hug.
- Go away before I beat you up.
It's Green Onion!
No, I am a person.
He is garaetteok.
- I am still a person.
- He is garaetteok.
Mom.
(Mom enters.)
- I mean...
- Let's film "My Little Old Boy".
Let's film "My Little Old Boy".
Look at her shoulders!
I didn't know
you had such broad shoulders.
- I have broad shoulders.
- Jong Kook.
- How is your body like that?
- What?
Ji Hyo isn't even smiling.
She is serious.
Gosh, look at Ji Hyo.
Ji Hyo.
(She went to the salon
and showed up as Song Ji Hyo.)
- I will be okay, right?
- Of course.
Look at Ji Hyo.
My goodness.
Oh, no.
Gosh, it's a big work. Seriously.
Ji Hyo got a muzzle.
(Ji Hyo, the Dalmatian,
becomes dazed.)
Gosh, it's a big work.
Seriously.
- It's time for Green Onion.
- Enter, Green Onion.
It's time for Green Onion.
(Se Chan thought
he would just put on a hat.)
It will be attached to his head.
Thank goodness I chose Grandma.
- Grandma is infinitely better.
- You chose well.
It's like...
I didn't do this
even in "Comedy Big League".
Is it done?
(He's the organic green onion.)
He didn't do it this much
even in "Comedy Big League".
Seriously, I don't do this
in "Comedy Big League".
(He thought he was used
to all kinds of costumes.)
I don't do it this much
even in "Comedy Big League".
- What are you doing?
- This is...
- What are you?
- Okay.
You look like a prince.
- Gosh, this is...
- It looks like a crown.
This isn't right.
Se Chan, you look cool.
Seriously, this isn't right.
- You look nice.
- This is really...
Look at me.
You'll be in a flowerpot later.
- What?
- A flowerpot?
- Is there a flowerpot?
- Is he going into a flowerpot?
Gosh, that would be really cool.
(The strange family is complete.)
Who goes first?
- Anyone...
- Let's start with Dad.
- Dad goes first.
This is the country
of courteous people in the east.
He looks like a guy
in an American drama.
His name is Francisco.
- He lives in Korean town.
- He looks like a real dad.
(Dad Ji Suk Jin got a year older
with his dyed mustache.)
All right. Who's next?
It's the mother's turn.
Mom.
(She's number 1 of the family
whom the dad is scared of.)
Mom.
- What?
- He's scary.
- He's the mom.
- He looks terrifying.
This is funny though.
Mom is... You can imagine
that I'm having hard times.
My wife is so muscular.
He looks like a mom.
(Next up is a girl who wants
to be pretty, Jae Soon.)
(Next up is the shortest grandma.)
(So Min is the youngest baby
who seems somewhat drunk.)
(The three women of the Jis
who are known to be nice)
- Ji Hyo.
(Now it's the dog's turn.)
Ji Hyo is cute.
You look cute, Ji Hyo.
Ji Hyo is lovely.
This is crazy.
It doesn't have to be Ji Hyo.
I can't recognize who you are.
(Ji Hyo looks
just like a Dalmatian.)
We were going to be Ha-Se-Hyo,
but it didn't work.
Ji Hyo.
- Look at him.
- What?
(Watch out for the dog.)
We were going to be Ha-Se-Hyo,
but it didn't work.
Ha-Se-Hyo is...
We are Ha...
Ha...
(Haha's mischievous joke
makes her even more upset.)
- Dalmatian.
- Go, Dalmatian.
Dalmatian is amazing.
She looks unbelievable.
- Ji Hyo.
- Hey, Ji Hyo.
Ji Hyo.
What do we do with her?
- Ji Hyo, please.
- Ji Hyo.
We should've done that.
The pictures look good though.
- You are an actress.
- We shouldn't laugh.
(The Ji family's pet dog
has a disinterested attitude.)
Oh, no.
But the pictures look good.
Good.
(She's a smart dog
that can hold out its paw.)
You look pretty.
- It looks like a Disney movie.
- Next up is the green onion.
- Green onion.
- Bring a flowerpot.
What? Is he going into the pot?
(He's a pet green onion
of the Ji family.)
- Should I go in there?
- Yes.
(He's being planted in the pot.)
(What?)
What is this?
They can't see the soil anyway.
- My gosh.
- Oh, dear.
We can't even see the soil.
Why the soil...
Se Chan doesn't do this
even in "Comedy Big League".
(The pet green onion is withering
despite the premium soil.)
(He comes back to life
with his yellow teeth.)
- All I can see his gums.
- It looks scary.
Let's take a family photo now.
Dad is intimidated.
I should keep a straight face.
Good.
(Wriggling)
(Ji Hyo is trying to do something.)
Smile a little.
- I need to pee.
- Did you pee?
- What?
- She wants to pee.
- What is she talking about?
- Pee?
She wants to pee.
- She's trying to pee here.
- I see.
You don't have to do that, Ji Hyo.
She's just upset
that she's doing this.
Ji Hyo, that's not necessary.
- Ji Hyo, we're sorry.
- Let's take a picture.
(The family is embarrassed.)
The looks on your faces
are really good.
All right. Only the two
of you should smile.
- An awkward smile.
- Okay.
(They don't look alike,)
Good.
(but the Ji family is
kind-hearted.)
It's done.
- We're done.
- Thank you.
That's it for our
commemorative photo.
- Okay.
- Well done.
(Where's Ji Hyo?)
(Ji Hyo is gone.)
(A witch who grants your wish)
(They are here to make a wish.)
(Ha Do Kwon, Nam Ji Hyun,
Chae Jong Hyeop)
(My wish is to take revenge.)
(I want Do Kwon to be
Jong Kook's trainer.)
(A small revenge)
(I want Seok Sam to be
my younger brother for a day.)
(He should treat me
like his older brother.)
(The members don't want to miss
their chances to make a wish.)
I want to do it too.
(But there's a price.)
Ji Hyo is amazing.
I'll end this.
- Good.
- This is like UFC.
(They feel dizzy
with the UFC-like price.)
(Is it time to confess love?)
(They struggle in unique ways...)
(to get their wish
without paying a price.)
(Will they be able to fulfill
their wishes without paying prices?)
(Make Your Wish Come True
and Pay The Price Later)