(A Monday morning
that is going to be a special day)
- Hello.
- Hey.
- Hello, Ji Hyo.
- Okay.
- This is cute.
Okay.
(The members come in together
wearing hats.)
The hats are difficult to pull off.
- What are we doing today?
- What is it?
(Empty Head Cell)
(He's been good at quizzes lately,
but he doesn't know his place.)
You guys look like beggars today.
- The hat...
- The Beggar Special.
(Sleep Cell)
(Supposedly, she recently had
a haircut to get more sleep.)
- What's with So Min?
- What are we doing with the hats?
- I have a pigeon in here.
- Your head looks...
- A rabbit in here.
- like "The Simpsons."
(Romance Cell)
(A romance expert
who learned love from books)
What are you? You're
dressed in ocher today.
And you're in pink,
but you look scary.
The scariest one is in pink.
(Hangout Cell)
(MBC's man on Saturday who just
released his new song, "Gap")
(Protein Cell)
(A reasoning expert who's feeling
good after a lower-body workout)
- He's scary.
- Shall we start?
- Look at him smiling.
- Terrifying.
Where are Jae Suk and Suk Jin?
- Suk Jin.
- The two old members.
- There he is.
- He always wears a hat like that.
- Jae Suk.
- Are you an archer?
- He looks like Jiangshi.
- Is this "Doctor Zhivago" or what?
Jae Suk, it looks like a thimble.
(Prankster Cell)
(Suk Jin's friend of 30 years
who plays jokes every Monday)
Are you leaving for somewhere?
- He doesn't beat around the bush.
- Madam.
I feel like I should call you madam.
- It feels natural, right?
- Yes.
- It looks good on you.
- You look good in the hat.
- Where's Mr. Ji?
- What?
- Why isn't Mr. Ji coming?
- I know.
I guess he's not coming today.
Is this a special episode
for Suk Jin?
- No way.
- Seriously?
- I guess that's true.
- A special episode for Suk Jin?
Today, we will
help gullible Suk Jin...
- So that's true.
- become more decisive.
It's called Suk Jin's Cells Race.
- Suk Jin's Cells?
- I see.
So we're cells.
Today, you will be Suk Jin's cells.
Every time Suk Jin needs
to decide something,
you will persuade him
to make a good decision.
- Are we supposed to persuade him?
- Is it like "Yoo Mi's Cells?"
I've controlled Suk Jin
my whole life.
Right. You're good at it.
- It's so easy for him.
- This is just meaningless.
Suk Jin is his marionette.
- He listens only to Jae Suk.
- If you force him into something...
too strongly,
he won't listen to you.
What should we do then?
- What?
- what do we do to convince him?
You just let something slip,
and he will bite into it.
- He doesn't like compliments.
- He doesn't.
- You just put a bait.
- Yes.
- So you fish him all the time.
- Of course.
Fish him?
So every time...
Suk Jin follows your decision,
you'll get Gullible Coin
for convincing him.
- I see.
- It will be tricky.
The more coins you win,
the better prizes you get.
But this is of great
advantage to Jae Suk.
- I think so.
- Because they're so close.
It's not like that.
- Suk Jin might change his mind.
- Above all things,
I'm in no mood
to convince him today.
Why not?
- That's just how I feel.
- But Suk Jin will still...
- You feel that way?
- Yes, I do.
- It can't be helped.
- It can happen sometimes.
I know.
Gullible Suk Jin will arrive soon.
First, you will be
his fashion cells...
and pick his outfit.
The clothes and accessories
picked by Suk Jin's stylist...
are behind you.
We have them here?
- I can imagine.
- I have many different clothes.
Once he arrives,
you should take him here right away.
And if he puts on what you
recommend, you will get coins.
- We dress him up.
- Does he know this is about him?
He knows roughly about it.
- Really?
- Then he'd want something special.
He will probably start acting
as soon as he gets here.
- Exactly.
- "What's going on?"
"Hey, what are you doing to me?"
"Why are you doing this to me?"
This is why I'm not
so thrilled about today's race.
- This is going to be...
- He will be so annoying.
- Right.
- You'll see. He won't act natural.
- I'm telling you.
- We're doomed.
You can't expect things
to be realistic today.
- We're doomed.
- It will be all fake.
It will be like a fake documentary.
- A fake documentary?
- A fake documentary.
Actually, after he found out
today would be about him,
he called our writer
almost every day.
- Did he ask for something?
- Seriously?
- He wants to be a star.
- He asked you to prepare something?
He's unbelievable.
He acted like a superstar.
If nothing else,
he can't make a superstar...
because he lacks refinement.
He does.
- He doesn't have the capacity...
- It's not about personality.
- He doesn't.
- He doesn't have...
- what it takes to be a star.
- He's not enough.
Actually, what he has now
is beyond his capacity.
- This is the maximum.
- I know.
He's got talents and everything.
He has a good personality.
But he lacks refinement.
He's a man of poor caliber.
This is beyond his capability.
- I feel bad for him.
- He's about to cave in.
He'll be here in a minute.
Why is he coming so late?
Is So Min wearing a large-size hat?
What's with her hat?
I know.
It doesn't look like Ji Hyo's.
- In the hat...
- It's like an elevator hat.
- That's because of my hair.
- Can you fold it a little?
You should fold it like Jae Suk.
- What's with your hat?
- That's because of my hair.
He'll get here
once he turns the corner.
You don't have to be so nervous.
- Right. No need to be cautious.
- What's the big deal?
He's not so important.
- It's not thrilling at all.
- I mean,
this isn't a prank or something.
Guys, he is very excited
about this. Just play along.
- Who is?
- Does he want a fanfare?
Should we toss him
in the air or something?
- Let's just get this over with.
- Or carry him with our arms?
- Okay.
- Just take it easy.
- Should we carry him around?
- This is no big deal.
What do we do?
(Today's superstar is coming.)
(Even the car looks
conscious of the camera.)
(It looks like he's all prepared.)
Guys, he has just arrived.
Please bring him in.
Should we bring him in?
- Bring him in?
- Do we have to?
My goodness.
Let's take it easy.
- Gosh.
- This is... My gosh.
You don't want to do this, do you?
No, I don't.
(They feel heavy-hearted
to see him get too excited.)
(A few of them get ready
to welcome the star.)
It's all dusty, but anyway.
He will love it. He will think
we prepared this for him.
Suk Jin, get off.
Suk Jin, get out of the car.
Suk Jin.
(There are a lot of cameras,
but he's still in his car.)
- There's a car coming. Come here.
- There's a car, So Min.
(The superstar shows up.)
Where are you going?
At the bakery...
I want to have some coffee.
Hello, Suk Jin.
- You're here.
- Hello, Suk Jin.
What's with your hat?
- Let's go.
- Where?
- Come here.
- Don't pretend you don't know.
- Know what?
- This is a special episode for you.
Obviously, you already know.
- Something's strange.
- No.
- Stop it.
- Why are you playing innocent?
He's playing innocent.
I can't believe this.
You're ruining this already.
- My gosh.
- Okay?
- Welcome.
- Suk Jin.
Ji Suk Jin.
Put this on.
Gosh, it hurts.
- You should throw a die.
- Why?
- One, two, and three.
If you get five...
All right.
(The grand-scale
welcoming ceremony is over.)
They all came off.
- Why did you kick it?
- Why are you throwing a tantrum?
He pretends not to know anything.
Why are you playing innocent?
Since when you were in the car?
- I don't know anything.
- You kept calling them.
- We heard you kept calling them.
- And...
- What?
- I could tell...
- from your outfit.
- What about it?
- He's dressed up.
- He knew there would be...
- cameras around him.
- Why?
- He's all dressed up today.
- He's dressed up.
This is how I always look.
- No way.
- I was on other shows...
- looking like this.
- You're lying.
Why are you wearing
this dusty wreath?
That's...
Gosh, it hurts.
Why are you yelling?
Why are you upset?
It's all black. I like that.
I love black suits.
You know he always...
- carries his bag around.
- I know.
- This thing.
- His bag? You're right.
- He doesn't have it now.
- I left it in my car.
All right. Let me do it.
You're all dressed up.
You look great.
That's a magazine.
- A cartridge belt?
- It looks like a magazine.
(Variety Show Special Forces)
The microphone...
- Come here.
- That's unique.
- That's new.
- It's unique.
This is new, Suk Jin.
(His vision for variety shows
has been upgraded.)
This is new.
I know. This is novel.
- This is new.
- A variety show...
- is like a war.
- It's new.
- The microphone...
- I'm the first one to do this.
The microphone doesn't
always have to be on here.
- That's a stereotype.
- Of course.
We need Dong Geun here.
This is a cartridge belt.
(The upgraded item)
This is real.
- I know.
- Right above his lips.
The audio...
You look like Charlie Chaplin.
We can easily hear him now.
You're Charlie Chaplin.
- He likes it.
- This is quite new.
- I know.
- We can hear you well.
You're the star of the day.
- Stop it.
- We can hear him well.
I don't want to be the protagonist.
We heard that
you called them every day.
- Anyway...
- The writer called me,
- so I answered her questions.
- You knew what we'd be doing...
This really hurts.
Why are you playing innocent
when you know the whole thing?
So what are we doing today? Tell us.
As soon as Suk Jin got off,
he was like this.
"What's going on?"
(Poor acting)
Why...
- Why are you looking for cameras?
- Please, Suk Jin.
This is why...
I didn't want to do this.
Stop it.
You know what we're doing today.
Why are you playing innocent?
Didn't you come here
and rehearse it yesterday?
Why would I rehearse?
Today, for Suk Jin
who is easily swayed...
by others all the time,
- the six cells are here together.
- I see.
Now the cells will...
recommend good outfits
for today to Suk Jin.
- I have something in mind.
- For today?
We will recommend
some outfits to you then.
- Okay. But I get to decide.
- You make the decision.
I bet his stylist brought
a lot of unique outfits.
- Because...
- My goodness.
- Suk Jin is...
- We should be serious.
Suk Jin.
Suk Jin, I love this one.
His stylist...
There are a lot of fancy clothes.
Look at the shoes.
They look cool.
(The place has a lot of fancy items
like a select shop.)
(There are a lot of
nice outfits for a superstar.)
- I love these shoes.
- They are nice.
You should definitely wear them.
Suk Jin, I know what you'd want.
- Suk Jin, today is...
- All right.
a special day for you.
Suk Jin would
love things like this.
I don't look good in it.
- Suk Jin.
- Seriously, it's not for me.
- One person at a time.
- You should try the hats first.
- Look.
This is how it looks.
Actually, I like that.
It looks good on you.
That's nice.
Suk Jin, you should try this on.
This is what Yong Jin does.
Seriously, it's really popular.
- Everyone in "SWF" wears it.
- Everyone wears it.
It's really popular these days.
- It's so cool.
- It's a brand-name hat.
- I know that.
- Just try it on.
- Jae Suk...
- My gosh.
- Suk Jin.
- You have to wear this.
- You look good.
- "You should try it on."
It looks great on you.
Do you mean that?
"You're the protagonist."
Say it one by one.
What do you think?
- It looks perfect.
- Give it a score.
It's over 90 points.
- Show the mark.
- You have to go with that.
I have an outfit in mind.
- I think...
- This is what I recommend.
- I think the fedora is better.
- What do you think?
- It doesn't look good on you.
- It doesn't? What about you?
- I'll go with a fedora.
- You?
I was seriously going to punch you.
I knew it. It's strange.
You look like
a Turkish ice cream seller.
- I knew it.
- Suk Jin, today is your day.
It doesn't look good on you.
- Look at the brand name.
- My gosh.
You don't know much about fashion.
Do you not wear a beanie at all?
A beanie is...
You can put slightly on your head.
Suk Jin.
- It will be okay.
- I don't wear a beanie...
because the shape of my head
isn't so pretty.
Look.
- Just put it slightly on your head.
- It looks pretty that way.
- Like this.
- It looks pretty.
- This is what you should do.
- It looks nice that way.
See? Just put it on like this.
- You can still show the bangs.
- Right.
Let me try it on.
(Let me try it on.)
What's wrong with you?
- Seriously...
- Why are you wearing it?
Do you like fashion?
Just look.
This is so pretty.
- What's wrong with this?
- Seriously?
- This isn't strange.
- It is strange.
- All right then.
- What's wrong with this?
- Let me pick the clothes first.
- It's not bad.
- It looks good on you.
- It looks good.
- Suk Jin, this is nice.
- You look good.
What are you doing?
What's wrong?
Suk Jin, you should
look into a mirror.
Hey, get rid of this!
- This is nice.
- You look good. Where's a mirror?
- There's no mirror.
- This is good.
- It looks good, doesn't it?
- This is pretty.
- Are you serious?
- He never lies.
- Suk Jin,
why did you not wear it before?
- It looks really strange.
- Let's pick something powerful.
- This isn't bad.
- Seriously.
- You look really good.
- It's not that bad.
- I know.
- It's not bad. Seriously.
- You look young.
- Just tidy your hair a little.
Fine! Stay quiet!
Let me pick clothes first.
Suk Jin, let's go
with this colorful one.
- That looks nice.
- You should pick brand-name goods.
- Suk Jin.
- One person at a time.
- One by one.
- I picked something for you.
- This is it.
- Right. I agree.
- They will go well with the beanie.
- But...
But with this hat.
You should wear these
on a day like today.
You can wear them
only when there are cameras.
- This is a famous brand.
- Actually,
- I wanted to try things like this.
- This is...
- I know.
- I wanted to try this,
but it is too much for me.
So if you force me...
Suk Jin, you will spend
all day in that suit.
This is pretty.
- Suk Jin.
- Isn't this nice?
You should pick
something simple like this.
You will be wearing it
the whole day.
He wore something
like that last week.
- This is...
- This is what you wore last week.
It looks cold.
Suk Jin.
- What?
- This is your style.
- It's perfect.
- Isn't it for KCM?
- This is your favorite style.
- It's KCM.
Will you pick one each?
Stand here with what you picked.
You guys are being so loud.
Look at this.
- Leather.
- Suk Jin.
Suk Jin, you should wear shorts.
Suk Jin.
- Forget about it.
- Why?
- That doesn't make sense.
- You can wear socks.
- Hey.
- They will go well together.
- Get out.
- What?
- Why?
- Who do you think I am?
Now that he keeps being like this,
I'm a little annoyed.
He's not listening to me.
I'm just trying to pick what I want.
But it's taking too long.
Do I have to listen to you?
Just pick anything.
Do I have to listen to what you say?
- This is so tacky.
- No, it's not.
- Seriously, I think this is cool.
- This is better.
- Like this.
- It's not cool at all.
- It is cool.
- Don't be ridiculous.
You wear them.
- That's not good.
- They're not talking to you.
This is a special episode for you.
Actually, this makes me feel bad.
Cut the chitter.
- "Chitter?"
- What is he talking about?
- What is chitter?
- Are you Chitter?
Suk Jin, are you talking to me?
- Who's Chitter here?
- Hey, Chitter?
- Am I Chitter?
- Are you Chitter?
- Let's say you are.
- I'll stop talking.
- Okay. You should.
I'm Yang Chitter now.
Suk Jin, this is leather.
Leather? But it's...
- A turtleneck sweater.
- But it feels uncomfortable.
- Then you can wear only this.
- Seriously, it's uncomfortable.
- Without anything underneath.
- I can't wear a turtleneck sweater.
- I brought this because it's cold.
- It's itchy.
Suk Jin, if you're cold,
what about a bench coat?
That's a good idea.
- Hey, I'm a celebrity.
- You said it was cold.
Suk Jin.
I'm a celebrity.
I'm supposed to be fashionable.
Suk Jin, what about a bench coat?
- Suk Jin.
- Okay.
- I'll dress like a celebrity.
- All right!
- I want to look like a celebrity.
- This is it.
This is how a celebrity looks.
I'll dress like a celebrity.
You need leopard-print shoes.
You should definitely wear these.
Can you go around Gangnam
in those shoes?
- Okay. I'll wear them.
- Okay.
- Good. I'll look like a celebrity.
- These are the shoes.
- I'll dress like a celebrity.
- You're so broad-minded.
- I'll look like a celebrity.
- Suk Jin.
You should wear these.
What are you talking about?
- These look good though.
- They do look good.
These are just...
To be honest,
- this is a better fashion choice.
- Of course, it is.
He listens only to Jae Suk.
- I mean...
- You should wear these.
To be honest, these are
better than them.
- These are better.
- This is sophisticated.
- They are tacky.
- These are so pretty.
If you wear them...
These will make you
look like a celebrity.
These are what a celebrity wears.
I can't wear these all day.
- This is better.
- He's right.
They are high-heeled. I'll be tired.
Suk Jin, it's cold. Why don't you
wear a turtleneck sweater?
- A turtleneck sweater sounds good.
- I know. Wear a turtleneck sweater.
The black one.
- You should wear a turtleneck.
- Okay.
Because it's cold today.
- Seriously, this is...
- It's cold.
He is so gullible.
- This is soft. It's not itchy.
- It is soft.
Okay. I'll wear a turtleneck.
Let's go with them.
I'll go get changed.
Okay. Go get changed.
The shoes look good
with the clothes.
(There are cameras everywhere
in the dressing room.)
There's no place where I can change.
- Suk Jin.
- There is no camera.
Where?
I'll cover you.
That might be better.
There's no camera in there.
- Act naturally, Suk Jin.
- Hey.
- What's the matter?
- This is a fake documentary.
- That's funny.
- Think that there's no camera.
I see three cameras in there,
but he keeps saying there's none.
- Just think that there's no camera.
- Where should I get changed?
A TV celebrity wouldn't mind.
Oh, boy.
Right. I should dress as a top star.
Good. I'll dress as a top star.
- Will we recommend him food too?
- Yes, you will.
- They probably prepared menus.
- Of course.
- You will have to convince him...
- Jae Suk must know...
- Suk Jin's food preferences too.
- Jae Suk must know that.
- He's a picky eater.
- Of course, I know what he likes.
- Based on the weather...
- Gosh.
- and his condition,
- Yes.
- I can tell what he wants to eat.
- It seems to me...
- that since you've trained him,
- True.
he keeps worrying
about what you think.
- That's true. I could see that.
- Yes.
- That's not true.
- He'd only take Jae Suk's advice.
But I know Suk Jin very well.
I know what he likes.
It's not easy to convince Suk Jin.
We should make him put on a hat.
Gosh, this mic is annoying.
Gosh, this turtleneck is
so uncomfortable.
- Look at him.
- Hey, you look amazing.
(How could Superstar Ji look
in the clothes his cells chose?)
Gosh, this mic is annoying.
The turtleneck is uncomfortable.
Hey, can I wear the jacket
you showed me earlier?
- This is so uncomfortable.
- You look amazing.
No. It's so uncomfortable.
- I can't put on my mic on it.
- You look great.
The turtleneck was a bad choice.
- That's not true.
- Suk Jin.
- You look fabulous.
- You look like a trot singer.
- Suk Jin.
You look great in that turtleneck.
- This is how a trot singer dresses.
- You're wrong.
- It's so uncomfortable.
- This isn't how a superstar looks.
- You can put your mic here.
- I'm at Sangsu Station
- Put it on here.
- You're at Mangwon Station
(Pleasing his fans)
- Do we have a clip, by any chance?
- He looks like a trot singer.
I think I've seen a man who dresses
like that on "What on Earth."
- I've seen him too.
- Right?
A man who likes to wear
flashy clothes appeared on the show.
Hey, why do you keep making me...
Suk Jin, you look great.
I like how you look.
- How about you put on a necklace?
- Can I have jjamppong, please?
- Gosh, seriously.
- I'll have jjamppong.
- This isn't right. Why...
- Ji Hyo.
- Ji Hyo, the necklace... Oh, good.
- That doesn't look good.
- Layering two necklaces is better.
- Okay. I'll wear necklaces.
- Two necklaces.
- I thought something was missing.
- But Suk Jin...
- Suk Jin, wear a beanie instead.
- Right, I'll take this off.
- That doesn't look good.
- Put the beanie on him.
- This will go well with his outfit.
I'll put it at the back
of your head.
- Wait, you guys.
- Suk Jin doesn't like... Listen.
There's something you don't know.
See? I knew he would take
Jae Suk's advice.
- Suk Jin hates flat front hair.
- I don't look good in it.
- True. Don't make him wear it.
- He likes to keep it up?
- Correct.
- It's not like that.
- That's why he styles his hair up.
- I won't put it on.
- I won't put the hat on.
- But try it at the back.
- No, I don't want to.
- Try it and look in the mirror.
He does everything
that Jae Suk suggests.
- Now, check yourself in the mirror.
- Is he Jae Suk's son?
He's like a good son
who listens to his dad.
- He's acting like Jae Suk's son.
- You look well-proportioned in it.
Right? What do you think, Suk Jin?
- It makes you look...
- It does make me look younger.
You look much younger.
- You look great, Suk Jin.
- Do I?
What is this?
Is this Jae Suk's special?
This isn't fair.
- Don't be like that.
- The best outfit in a few months.
I like it. I wanted to dress
like a top star.
You do look like a top star.
- All right.
- You look fabulous.
The star of the day Suk Jin has
chosen his outfit for today.
Yes.
- He looks great.
- I want to dress like a top star.
For the first time, I feel distant
from Suk Jin.
I feel like I'm star struck.
- Come on. Stop it.
- Everyone will recognize him.
- We counted the fashion items...
- I like the outfit.
that each of you recommended
to Suk Jin.
The number of the items he chose
as Jae Suk recommended...
is 4 out of 5.
(Jae Suk convinced him to choose
4 out of 5 items he recommended.)
- That's unbelievable.
- He's practically...
- Jae Suk's son.
- Exactly.
- He's practically Jae Suk's son.
- That's not true.
He's like Jae Suk's son Ji Ho.
He's Jae Suk's son.
- Two of Jong Kook's were chosen.
- I see.
- Three of Haha's were chosen.
- Okay.
I chose that many items
that Haha recommended?
And he chose one item
that Ji Hyo recommended.
Three of So Min's were chosen.
So Min did a good job.
Se Chan convinced him to choose
two items he recommended.
That's correct,
including the jacket.
- I'd like to apply some hand cream.
- I'll give you some.
- She has hand cream.
- Do you?
It'd be funny if Suk Jin goes
around by himself in that outfit.
Suk Jin, I have hand cream too.
- Suk Jin.
- Here you go, Suk Jin.
- Suk Jin, here's hand cream.
- Hey.
- Stop it.
- I'll give you my hand cream.
(He's giving Suk Jin toothpaste.)
- That's enough.
- This is a special episode.
- I said, enough.
- He should apply this.
Suk Jin, apply this
since it's your special.
- That's perfect.
- Right?
It'd be so refreshing.
Stop it.
(The special hand cream
for the star of the day)
- Give me a chance.
- It'd smell great.
- Absolutely. It'd be refreshing.
- Indeed.
- That'd be funny, I must say.
- Exactly. Apply this instead.
- What a shame.
- It would've been funny.
I wish he had applied it.
As the six members just helped
Suk Jin choose his outfit,
they will be Suk Jin's cells today,
and will influence his decisions.
- Yes.
The cells will receive coins
when he takes their advice.
You can exchange the coins you saved
for prize balls.
And at the end, the number
of your prize balls...
will affect the draw for deciding
two winners...
and one person to get a penalty.
(2 winners and 1 person to get
a penalty will be chosen.)
What penalty do you want?
- Do we get to decide?
- Yes.
- How about no penalty at all?
- I have an idea.
- Right.
- No.
- Let's exempt ourselves from it.
- Let's do that.
Is that allowed?
- It's up to us. We won, you know.
- Yes. It's up to us.
- I agree.
- No penalty today.
How about the one in last place
wear Suk Jin's outfit next week?
- That's a good idea.
- Dress exactly the same as him...
at the opening next week.
- I like the idea.
- As a penalty.
- I'd hate to dress like that.
- Wearing his outfit next week.
- Wearing this outfit.
- I love the idea.
Gosh, I hate it.
- Exactly the same as he's dressed.
- Yes.
Jong Kook would have to make
a new one since it doesn't fit him.
That would be a lot of work.
I must avoid getting the penalty.
- It's the worst even for a guest.
- Indeed.
It's the worst.
Also, there are different rules
only for Suk Jin.
Okay.
You will take the cells' advice...
to make mock stock investments
until the end of the race.
- Stock investments?
- Yes.
You will make
mock stock investments.
- Stock investments?
- Yes.
He's getting excited.
Suk Jin smiled while saying,
"Stock investments?"
Cells, read the given stock charts
to advise him. It's virtual.
- You'll receive 10,000 dollars.
- Got it.
The return you make will decide
the prize or the penalty you'll get.
- For me?
- They prepared everything he likes.
- It's Suk Jin's special for sure.
- That sounds fun.
- Thank you.
- It'll be fun.
- This is his schedule for today.
- Thanks.
- "Photoshoot and interview".
- What?
"Eating at his regular restaurant
and hosting an event".
"Hugh Grant of Jamwon-dong
shopping for a gift for his wife".
- Why a photoshoot?
- Great.
- That's nice.
- He'll pose in that outfit?
- He looks great.
- He seems happy.
Where can we see his photos?
We'll use his photos
for several purposes.
He'll have a photoshoot
looking like that.
Now, let's go inside and continue.
- Okay.
- Let's go inside. It's so cold.
- Hey, Se Chan.
- Yes, Jong Kook.
You should hurry up and vote.
- What do you mean?
- The soccer club.
- Oh, for this week?
- Yes.
Oh, I see. I wondered
what you were talking about.
I saw that you hadn't voted.
- Right. I'm afraid...
- I voted already.
- I don't think I can make it.
- Whether or not you'll be there...
You missed it last week too.
True. But I'm going to drink
with some friends.
- You'll have a drink?
- I mean...
You'll miss the soccer game
to have a drink?
(You'll miss the soccer game
just to have a drink?)
The restrictions related to COVID-19
have finally been dropped.
- So I'll meet some friends.
- That's not acceptable. You guys...
I can't believe this.
Shall I introduce you
to someone I know?
Who?
He can make a fake leg cast.
He's really good at that.
Jae Suk, he'll need to submit
a medical certificate too.
- Really?
- He should submit it.
Then it won't work. He can't forge
a medical certificate.
- That won't work.
- I'll introduce you to him anyway.
- I need my legs to move freely.
- He's good at making a fake cast.
You can still come
to cheer for our team, can't you?
Exactly. You should submit
a medical certificate.
He's really good at making
a fake cast.
That was totally unexpected.
He startled me.
- What?
- What is this?
- Oh, the stock investment?
- Now,
we'll begin
the mock stock investment...
that will save Suk Jin
who failed as a stock investor...
because he let others
sway him too easily.
- All right. Let's do this.
- I see that the stock items...
- The stock items are real.
- That's a lot.
- Is the market currently...
- Yes, it's a real-time chart.
- These are the real-time prices?
- Yes, they're the real prices.
- Suk Jin, you have 10,000 dollars.
- Yes.
You can invest as much as you want
until the end of the race...
with some advice from the cells.
But the market is not
doing well today.
He knows much about stocks.
- Due to the new virus variant,
- I don't even know how to read it.
- overseas stocks dropped sharply.
- Now...
- There are always some going up.
- You can hit the jackpot...
You must turn the crisis
into an opportunity.
- He likes day trading.
- When the market is doing bad...
- And he likes...
- I'm not a day trader.
You like to make risky investments.
I usually buy stocks
that don't fluctuate much...
- But I have only one day, right?
- Correct.
- Stocks like this are good.
- How about K company?
- That's...
- You should buy at a low price.
- You should make a high return.
- Exactly.
- For example...
- Aren't you guys listening to me?
- Only you are listening to me.
- Buy one that'll rise rapidly.
- I have only one day, right? So...
- Until the market closes.
Suk Jin, how about this company?
- Hey.
- You like this company.
I suffered a huge loss
when I invested in that company.
How's the price going today?
Oh, gosh. I bought their stocks
for a little more than 20 dollars,
- Is this refer to A company?
- and then...
I sold them for 11 dollars.
(He calmly told the story
of losing 50 percent.)
Suk Jin, it's
14 dollars and 50 cents now.
- Is that so?
- The price is...
Blue means an increase, right?
- Blue means a decrease.
- I see.
- Gosh.
- Red means an increase.
How can I take his advice?
Suk Jin, you should
take a look at this.
- What is it?
- It dropped but rebounded.
It's day trading.
It seems like a good investment
since it's a large-cap stock.
- No, I don't think so.
- I don't see it.
- Today,
- He never listens to others.
I'll invest
in small and medium cap stocks.
Suk Jin rarely buys
large-cap stocks.
The thing about large-cap stocks...
- He buys unknown stocks.
- He invests in unknown stocks.
- This one went up 15 dollars.
- Really?
It went up 15 dollars today.
- Which one?
- It's an advanced material company.
What's the percentage?
- Suk Jin.
- It's 2.4 percent.
Check this company out.
That one seems to have
a good chance of going up.
- Oh, it refers to the market cap?
- Trust me.
- Okay.
- Just check how much it went up.
Only this game company's
stock price increased, Suk Jin.
- Oh, I get it. If the pandemic...
- It's a pandemic-sensitive stock.
If the pandemic gets worse,
people will have to stay at home.
- They'll just play games at home.
- In any case...
- Then the stock price will go up.
- You're right.
You see, it's
a pandemic-sensitive stock.
Omicron has been detected, you know.
Suk Jin, it's strange.
This mobile carrier is going up.
- The mobile carrier?
- Yes.
- It's going up continuously.
- You must choose wisely.
I think it's a good investment.
Due to the pandemic,
people must use their phones
more often to talk to one another.
The pandemic situation is
really serious, you know.
Suk Jin, superbug-related stocks
seem to be going up.
- Suk Jin, check this one out.
- Yes?
- In only one day...
- It's day trading.
- My, it went up 16 percent.
- It's good, right?
- It could hit the upper limit.
- Blue...
Blue means an increase, right?
Suk Jin, you should buy
the mobile carrier's stocks.
Due to the outbreak
of the new virus variant,
- people use their phones so often.
- True.
- Look. It just went up one percent.
- But...
- It went up in only ten minutes.
- Exactly.
- What are you going to do?
- It's okay.
- That's not good enough for me.
- Suk Jin, come on.
It just went down to 8.6.
I should buy it now.
It was a little over nine
just before.
- I've made my decision.
- What did you buy?
- I'll invest in S company.
- See? I knew it.
- I'll invest 10,000 dollars in it.
- Who...
(He invests all 10,000 dollars
to S company.)
- Who recommended the company?
- I did.
You'll invest all you have in it?
Look how focused Suk Jin is.
- This is so fascinating, right?
- Indeed.
I see why investors can't sleep
at night.
- I wouldn't be able to sleep.
- I don't think I can do it.
- I think I shouldn't try it.
- Right.
All right. Suk Jin made
an investment.
You can advise him to sell it
and buy something else later.
Got it.
Now, Suk Jin will have
a magazine photoshoot...
- and an interview.
- Yes.
I'm small
(The first item on Suk Jin's
schedule is coming up shortly.)
- Exactly.
- Did Suk Jin already lose money?
It's between minus 50
and minus 60 dollars.
(The stock Suk Jin bought is
going down.)
Is that true?
- Darn it.
- Did he lose money already?
Suk Jin, it'll go up again.
Suk Jin, do you think
you can focus on the shoot?
Of course. It's only
minus 50 dollars. That's okay.
- Think that you treated us.
- Exactly. That's what I'll do.
The money you lose will be
deducted from your pay.
(It'll be deducted from your pay.)
That would be awful.
- He'd lose a lot of money.
- Oh, man.
Jae Suk, check the price
of your stock.
I bet it went up.
See? What did I tell you?
Why? Did it go up?
I'm already up by
14 dollars and 30 cents.
- Let me check mine.
- When I saw...
that it was rebounding
after dropping,
- I knew it was a good investment.
- How should I check it?
- I told you so.
- I'm up by 18 dollars and 40 cents.
- Is mine going up too?
- The beginners made a profit too.
- I made a profit too.
- Twenty-five dollars?
I'm currently at minus 64 dollars.
Oh, no.
(He's bad at making mock investments
as well.)
Everyone, forget about the stocks
for the time being.
- I'm losing more than 60 dollars.
- He can't focus on the shoot.
Every second matters.
Hang on. Should I sell it now?
Why would you sell it already?
I'm losing 60 dollars.
- We'll begin the first event.
- Okay.
He's scheduled for a photoshoot...
- and an interview with a magazine.
- Right.
We'll start with the photoshoot.
- Recommend Suk Jin good poses.
- Got it.
We'll upload his photos
and the interview...
- with the title "Fake Interview"...
- "Fake Interview"?
on Running Man's
social media account.
Our fans will like it.
- His interview will be revealed.
- "Fake Interview".
- The fans will be excited.
- Indeed.
Let's meet the photographer
of Running Man Choi Hyung In.
- Oh, Hyung In?
- Hyung In is coming in.
- Hyung In will take photos?
- Hey.
- If Hyung In takes photos...
- Will she use an instant camera?
Hyung In...
- Hyung In is...
- What's that? Hey.
Who uses a single-use camera...
for a magazine photoshoot?
- Please stand in the middle.
- Where should we stand?
- Why a single-use camera?
- On that side?
To be honest, I've had
a photoshoot several times,
- it was always hard to pose.
- By the way...
- Suk Jin, cross your arms.
- Yes?
(The cells started giving him
tips on posing.)
- Cover your mouth. Good.
- You should pose like this.
- That's a good pose.
- How about this?
If you bend your knees like this,
you'll look unnatural.
- Put your hand on your chin.
- Good.
No, that looks weird.
- Oh, like this?
- Yes.
- Yes, that looks great.
- You can get coins here too.
- I like that pose.
- Hold on a second.
- Suk Jin, listen.
- Show me some poses.
- You should strike this pose.
- Try some basic poses first.
Grab your collars like this.
Yes. That's great.
- Stand straight.
- Good. Stand diagonally.
Don't look at the camera. Good.
They don't look at the camera
these days.
- It makes you look better.
- One, two, three.
(The stylish man)
- He looked at the camera anyway.
- Suk Jin, how about this pose?
- That's weird.
- That looks so weird.
- You look awful.
- Suk Jin, you look weird.
- Don't pose like that.
- "Awful"?
- I'm sorry.
- It makes your legs look short.
- Isn't this pose nice?
- Listen.
- No, it's not.
- Try a basic pose first.
- Something like this.
- Right. Try that pose.
- How boring. I want something else.
- I recommended that pose earlier.
- You should try basic poses first.
- No, I don't want to.
- I really don't like that pose.
- Pull your necklaces.
- My necklaces?
- Yes, grab them.
- Like this?
- Yes. That's good.
Keep going. That's great.
(That's great.
Go with a charismatic pose.)
- Go with a charismatic pose.
- Pull the neck. Yes, that's good.
(The wild man)
Grab your necklaces.
- Bite the neck of your sweater.
- Your face looks unnatural.
- Okay.
- Yes, like that.
- Bite it. Good.
- No. Bite it like this.
- Cover your mouth.
- Pull it up. Yes. That's good.
- One.
- Just cover your mouth with it.
- One, two, three.
- It's better to cover his mouth.
- Bite it lightly.
- That's what I'm talking about.
- Don't bite it.
- Just cover your mouth with it.
- That's great.
- Suk Jin, listen. Bite this.
- Just cover your mouth.
- What?
- Bite one of your necklaces.
- Why would I do that?
- I mean...
- I might break my teeth.
- Just lightly.
(It seems like they'll make him
bite everything he can.)
- Bite it lightly. That's good.
- Let go of it.
Gosh.
Bite it lightly.
My gosh. What are you trying to do?
- Why would you lie down?
- The lying pose is weird.
- Bend one knee.
- You look weak, Suk Jin.
- Are you watching TV at home?
- Come on.
- Move your leg...
- Just leave me be.
- Bend one knee.
- You look like an old man...
- watching TV at home.
- Raise your leg a little.
- What is that on his butt?
- What's that?
(He put electrical tape
to cover a hole in his pants.)
- That's hilarious.
- What's that?
What's this? I thought
it was a magazine photoshoot.
- That's so him.
- Suk Jin.
- I'll show you a pose. Get up.
- Or try this pose.
- Suk Jin.
- Try this pose.
Pose like a chicken in chicken soup.
(Try this pose. Pose like a chicken
in chicken soup.)
Suk Jin, why would you do that?
I like this pose.
Is he a cicada larva or what?
(The man like a boiled chicken)
I like this pose.
Is he a cicada larva or what?
- Suk Jin, get up.
- I like that.
- Hey.
- I'll show you a pose.
- I really like the chicken pose.
- Don't just joke around.
- I'll show you a pose.
- Turn around and look back.
- Right.
- Like this.
- You're right.
- That looks natural.
- Of course. Turn around.
Turn your head to any side you want.
Turn your head around.
- Turn your head around.
- One, two, three.
My, that's great.
(He was relaxed enough to wait
until she counted to 3.)
- One, two, three.
- That's good.
- Great job.
Sit on this chair this time.
Sit down.
- Cross your legs, Suk Jin.
- Right.
- Sit straight...
- That's not how you should sit.
- No.
- I'll show you. Move aside.
- Suk Jin, make a playful face.
- Put your hands here. Like this.
- That's a good idea.
- But...
- A playful face...
- Now, sit down.
- wouldn't go with my outfit.
- It'll make you look cute.
- This chair would be better.
- Sit on this one first.
- That's too high.
- Ouch.
(Grunting)
- Suk Jin, sit on the edge.
- That hurt.
- Sit on the edge like this.
- What's wrong with him?
- Put that away.
- Okay. I'll do that.
That reminds me
of old-fashioned family photos.
- Sit down.
- Sit on that chair.
- Sit down comfortably.
- Sit down.
- No.
- Don't do that.
- That's not cool at all.
- Sit down.
- How about I put it upside down?
- Sit down for now.
- That'd be weird.
- That looks funny.
- That's over the top.
- You're supposed to look cool.
- Really? Okay.
- Yes.
- Okay. Sit down.
- Put your hands in the middle.
- Put them on the edge.
- Haha is good at posing.
- Put your hands on the edge.
- Suk Jin.
- Move your legs to the sides.
- Bend this knee a little.
- Let this arm dangle like this.
- That's great.
- Put the other hand on here.
- That's cool.
Put the other hand on here.
- Hey.
- That's the right pose.
- I'm not joking around.
- Hey.
(Director Ha has his own unique
artistic point of view.)
- You little...
- I'm serious. I swear.
- I swear.
- Are you kidding me?
- Okay. Go ahead.
- I like this pose.
- Good. That's great.
- What about the facial expression?
Pull your head back...
- just a little bit.
- Move just a little.
Make an arrogant face.
(Pull your head back
and make an arrogant face.)
- Good. Keep that angle.
- You should look confident.
He looks
as if his face was paralyzed.
- Is his face paralyzed?
- That's not my intention.
(Stiff)
(Superstar Ji's body became stiff
while he was posing as he was told.)
Are you kidding me?
That's not the right pose for you.
Suk Jin, you should strike
this pose.
- That's a good one.
- Oh, my goodness.
- That's an old-fashioned pose.
- That's too old-fashioned.
- That's an old pose.
- It's too old-fashioned.
- Please strike this pose just once.
- It keeps bothering me.
Put your foot on the chair.
- What? On the chair?
- Put your foot on the chair.
- And look at the camera.
- No, that's not cool.
- I don't like this pose.
- Just try it just once.
You must strike a basic pose
like this.
(He made Suk Jin poke his nose.)
What is he doing?
- What is that pose?
- This is a magazine photoshoot.
- He looks upset.
- You should strike this pose.
- Go away.
- Kick him out. He makes me upset.
- It's funny.
- Don't do it, Suk Jin.
- Funny?
- Give it a try.
- Don't do it.
Do it just once.
- Don't take a photo now.
- Take a photo for now.
- Take it.
- Don't take a photo now.
- Come on, Suk Jin.
- No. I don't want to do it.
- You should do it.
- He looks like a teenager.
- It's fitting for social media.
- Suk Jin, sit down. Watch me.
- Can't you recommend a cool pose?
- Check the inside pocket.
- Will you use the chair?
- The inside pocket?
Pose naturally. Good.
You look great.
Take a photo of him now.
One, two, three.
- One, two, three.
- Good.
- Check inside the pocket. Good.
- That's weird.
- Suk Jin.
- Suk Jin, I'll show you one.
Stand straight and pose like you're
adjusting your cuff.
You should strike this pose.
Yes, that's good.
- But he doesn't have a cuff.
- Great.
Turn around a little to this side.
Lift this chair
over your head instead.
(Lift this chair
over your head instead.)
- That's great.
- Hey.
- Don't take a photo.
- What's this?
Don't take a photo. Don't!
- It's done. Great.
- I told you not to.
(The lonely man)
That was great.
- That was great.
- Suk Jin, sit down.
- I don't mind sitting down.
- Sit down and watch me.
I'm sorry. Sit comfortably.
Spread your legs a little
with your knees bent.
- And open your mouth slightly.
- Okay.
Keep your mouth slightly open.
- That's good, Suk Jin.
- She'll take a high-angle shot.
- Tilt your head a little.
- That looks weird.
- Put your feet on the floor.
- Good.
- Are you feeling unwell, Suk Jin?
- Keep your mouth slightly open.
- Just slightly.
- Is he not feeling well?
- Make a dreamy face.
- He looks...
- Do something about his hands.
- Hang on.
- Suk Jin.
- Put your hand on the floor.
- And put this one over your head.
- Yes.
- As if you were grabbing something.
- Yes. That's great. This is it.
Keep your mouth slightly open.
(The marionette of his own cells)
- That's good.
- That's hilarious.
(They made him believe
he looked okay.)
I look okay, right?
- No. You're doing it wrong.
- Your right hand.
(Jae Suk adds a detail.)
He looks like a monkey.
That's great.
Good.
That's it. Great job.
- You did great.
- There won't be any good ones.
You looked fabulous.
- That was good.
- It's hard to pose.
- You did well.
- The photoshoot is over.
Now, Reporter Lee Myung Jae
from Running Daily...
- will interview Suk Jin.
- Myung Jae?
- Recommend him good answers.
- Okay.
The six of you will
sit around Suk Jin.
Suk Jin will sit
in the yellow chair.
- Right.
- So these are our chairs.
Those giving out orders
are usually on higher ground.
- I hope I can get talking.
- As you know,
I'm one to have witty answers.
Make suggestions
and I'll choose one of them.
Suk Jin isn't one
to talk well to the press,
- so you'll offer guidance.
- Sure.
He said Suk Jin has trouble
answering questions.
(Will the cells guide him
through a successful interview?)
And we all agreed.
- Help me answer questions.
- Are you ready?
Yes, I'll begin the interview.
- Right.
- Sure.
Next year marks
your 30th year in the industry...
which is half your life.
Has it been that long?
It's about time you retired.
Please describe you as a celebrity
and you as a human being...
in one sentence respectively.
- As a celebrity and a human being.
- Say you're like dung.
(Childish)
A long one.
(Flustered)
One that's long but thin.
One that stinks.
Seriously?
Suk Jin, that sounds witty enough.
You know how it is...
- There's a rich smell to you.
- Something witty.
Yes, of course.
Give me a sentence that says it all.
Short but meaningful.
You as a celebrity...
and you as an average man.
- Give me some ideas.
- Okay.
- As a celebrity...
- A watermelon.
- Why?
- Why's that?
You as a celebrity
have a flashier side...
just like a watermelon's
black and green stripes.
You're dressed like
a watermelon today.
I quite like that.
- You're dressed like one.
- As an average man...
- Me as a human being.
- As a human being?
- Well...
- Yes?
You're red inside.
- That's how...
- Are you saying I'm passionate?
- What does the red represent?
- Watermelon doesn't seem right.
It's just odd.
- I quite like it.
- It's too old-fashioned.
- You're red on the inside.
It's not the appropriate season.
Watermelon is a summer fruit, right?
I'll keep it in mind though.
He believes in what others say
too easily.
- As a celebrity...
- Give me something cooler.
- He...
- Me as a celebrity.
It's only been three years.
- Hey.
- Is he a rookie?
Is he a rookie?
He's been working for 30 years.
- It's been four.
- He only became...
- a household name three years ago.
- Is he a rising star?
- What do you mean?
- You became a household name...
about 2 to 3 years back.
- Don't be ridiculous.
- He's a rookie then.
- As a celebrity.
- I've got one!
As a celebrity,
he's only getting started.
But as a human being,
he's in his latter years.
- Awesome, right?
- Nice!
The beginning and the end.
Wasn't that a good one?
Suk Jin, what's your answer?
- Right.
- The beginning and the end.
(Surprisingly enough,
that's what he chooses.)
In a sentence each.
As a human being, he's dead.
(How does the superstar of 3 years
see himself?)
- You as a celebrity.
- As a celebrity...
- I have one.
- But I was just about to answer.
- As a human being...
- What she said is cool.
As an average man, you're 56.
But as a celebrity,
you're only three.
- I like that one.
- That one's better.
You can't say
that your life is over.
- You're Hugh Grant of Jamwon-dong.
- That's right.
As a celebrity,
I belong to the public.
But as an average man,
I belong to my wife.
(But as an average man,
I belong to my wife.)
- I like that one.
- You're Hugh Grant of Jamwon-dong.
- That's what you should say.
- I love it.
- But...
- Hold on.
But that's a lie.
As a celebrity,
- I belong to the public.
- Exactly.
This is a lie though.
How can you belong to the public
when they might not want you?
- But I'm a superstar today.
- Besides, this is a lie.
You don't belong
to your wife either.
Forget it.
As a celebrity...
- When you're 60...
- Hey!
(Hey!)
He gave me a cool answer to say.
- Mine was good, right?
- That's not what I mean.
- This will give you everything.
- But you said...
you'd emigrate at 60.
I have to admit it sounded cool.
As a celebrity,
I belong to the public.
How can you be
when the public doesn't want you?
- But as an average man...
- Say you're Yang Jung A's.
(Say you're Yang Jung A's.)
(Yang Jung A used to be
the woman of his dreams.)
(A blast from the past
brings his energy up.)
Mentioning her was hilarious.
Suk Jin belongs to Yang Jung A!
Ask how she's doing.
Tell her to return your calls.
Jung A, I apologize.
- It's just an inside joke.
- You were smiling brightly though.
(His romantic image
takes a rocky turn.)
- You were beaming.
- Let me answer you again.
As a celebrity,
I belong to the public.
- But as an average man,
- Your wife's.
- The bank's.
- You belong to the bank.
- Did you take out a loan?
- Then the bank does own you.
- The bank's.
I've been flying toward
what I want in life...
and I belong to my wife.
It sure sounded pretentious.
It doesn't make any sense.
The word "wife"
seems romantic to me.
Here's your next question.
Can you be any less annoying?
You've been on Running Man
for 11 years.
What does this show mean to you?
He wanted to leave at first,
but now...
(Suk Jin looked for a way out
at the very beginning.)
- But now...
- It's the truth!
- He's not going anywhere now.
- One should give honest answers.
- It's not appropriate though.
- At first,
- you hated the show.
- That's...
That's...
what I would say on
"You Quiz on the Block."
But this is a formal interview.
You should be just as honest.
I'm looking for another cool answer.
You thought you were the main host,
but you weren't...
which upset you. Tell them.
That's what you thought at first.
You thought Haha
had bad intentions at first.
- But later on...
- You didn't like him at first.
You wanted to quit because of Haha.
- We're all a big family now.
- He thought he was a host.
- You invest in stocks, right?
- Right.
Say that it's the only stalwart...
you own.
You're on a roll today.
- Right? You...
- Suk Jin.
You don't own any stalwarts though,
- so that makes no sense.
- It's the only one he owns.
It's the only one.
- Be more like him, guys.
- Say it's like day trading.
That...
That was a good one.
It makes no sense.
Say that it's your only
source of income.
My only source of income?
I'd rather sound cool...
- since I'm a superstar today.
- Cool?
- Okay.
- Make me look cool.
And elegant.
Running man is...
(Running man is...)
It is the only...
The only show you're on.
- I'm right though.
- The other one ended recently.
- "Tteokbokki Brothers" ended.
- It ended.
- There will be a second season!
- Did it end already?
This is the only TV show you're on.
This is the only one you're on.
Is "Tteokbokki Brothers"
over already?
- That's what he'll say.
- No way.
It ended before
we could taste the tteokbokki.
This is the only show he's on.
The only show he's a regular on.
You should be writing what I say!
- Sorry about that.
- That should be your answer.
- Running Man...
- What I said is right.
- It is my only...
- The only TV show he's on.
- It's my only stalwart.
- One he's a regular on.
- Stalwart.
I'm in love with the expression.
Jong Kook is good with his words.
(Running Man?
It's the only stalwart I own.)
- You've been busy in 2021.
- Right.
TicToc, YouTube,
Running Man, and "How Do You Play?"
Being active through
various channels...
opened the doors
to your second heyday.
It's actually his first.
May I ask what made it happen?
Say that it's thanks to Jae Suk.
Say that Jae Suk made it happen.
- It was Jae Suk.
- You said it yourself.
- Self-improvement and...
- It was thanks to Jae Suk.
- Yes, Jae Suk.
- Jae Suk made it happen.
- That's not true.
- Yoo Jae Suk.
Jae Suk's fans will like you
for saying so.
- It's true.
- His fans would appreciate it.
It was thanks to Jae Suk.
- You know it's true.
- I did my best this year.
You'll seem humble that way.
Say that you did as Jae Suk said.
- Say you owe it to all of us.
- Jae Suk...
- and the rest of us.
- You did not get here on your own.
- It was a group effort.
- We made it happen for you.
Say Jae Suk's name though.
I don't want to.
- Why not?
- Say his name.
Because I value
my friendship with you.
It was only a success...
- thanks to Jae Suk.
- You must say his name.
- Jae Suk and...
- It's thanks to Jae Suk.
- I won't say his name.
- Why not?
Check out this headline.
"I Owe It All to Jae Suk".
But that'll make me look bad.
- On the contrary.
- You'll seem humble.
Say that it's thanks to me
and the others.
It was a group effort.
I was able to get this far...
not on my own...
Nothing can be done alone.
Say you can't even change
your own underwear.
That's actually true.
Go ahead.
Say you can't even change
your own underwear...
or feed yourself.
- To get this far...
- Alone?
It's not possible
to get this far alone.
Nothing can be done all by yourself.
Just like your mother raised you
from birth,
Jae Suk raised you
throughout your career.
- You're right.
- He's your stepfather.
- Those younger than me...
- That's true.
It was all thanks to
my younger friends.
- Say Jae Suk's name.
- Say his name.
- You should say his name.
- If you don't say my name...
- Because...
- He's your best friend.
That's why...
- Say Jae Suk's name.
- End it with this.
"Thanks, Jae Suk."
He raised you in variety shows.
- And...
- Thank Jae Suk.
- I...
- Thanks to my seniors...
I only got this far
thanks to my colleagues.
- "Thanks, Jae Suk."
- But most importantly,
name the one who raised you.
- He's like a father figure.
- And Jae Suk...
must be mentioned.
(And Jae Suk must be mentioned.)
- Nice.
- You mentioned us all.
- That's settled.
- We're good.
- Heartwarming, isn't it?
- Of course.
"I Owe It All to Jae Suk."
That would be the headline.
You are known as
the Hugh Grant of Jamwon-dong.
- So Min gave me that nickname.
- Yes, earlier.
Describe yourself
as a husband and father.
Just say, "Hugh."
(Just say, "Hugh.")
Just say, "Hugh,"
and take a deep breath.
- How about...
- I quite like that.
That isn't for me to say.
It's for my wife to decide.
- It's not my place to say.
- No, that's not right.
To be witty,
this is what you should say.
"You should discuss it
with my agency."
- Like a superstar.
- Sensitive questions...
should go through my agency.
With my agency...
Won't I seem arrogant?
That's the point.
I'll sound too arrogant.
- How about this then?
- What was it that you asked?
- In the past...
- What kind of a father are you?
I thought you said "husband."
Father and husband.
Start off with a chuckle and say,
"Yes, we almost broke up."
("Yes, we almost broke up.")
That's how it should begin.
Look. He's loving it.
- It's the Hollywood style.
- You'll seem down to earth.
The Hollywood style.
"It wasn't always
rainbows and butterflies."
It's so down to earth.
- It can't always be good.
- Exactly.
It's so down to earth.
"There were many challenges."
(They add in a few challenges
to make him seem down to down.)
We never almost broke up.
- Say you tried hard.
- That never happened.
I recommend,
"It wasn't always good."
- Well...
- Of course, we fought.
- I'll come up with my own answer.
- Go ahead.
- Of course, we fought.
- Well, of course...
- I always...
- Say you argued today as well.
No, we didn't argue.
- I always lack...
- However,
- you still keep in touch.
- Hey!
Keep in touch?
This morning,
- we almost kissed, you know.
- Almost?
- Why didn't you go through with it?
Why didn't you just kiss her?
How about this then?
You've almost kissed before,
but not for real.
You only "almost" kissed.
I'm a husband...
- who knows he lacks in many ways.
- Good.
- I try...
- And it'll stay that way.
I'm able to work hard...
thanks to my wife's support.
And say,
"It's why I'm thankful for Jae Suk
who introduced her to me."
I'm the one who introduced you two.
I resented you for a while.
Suk Jin, how about this?
- What is it?
- Say...
you're hoping for a second child.
No way.
That's... It's not even possible.
Can you not put on a serious face
when we're only giving you tips?
Why would you put on a serious face?
- It's an interview.
- We were only giving you tips.
- This is an interview.
- You were too serious.
- Having a second child is...
- This is fun though.
- I want to try it too.
- It's an interview.
- I need to be serious.
- Why is it impossible?
You can talk about being a father
in a cool way.
- My wife might be flustered.
- Okay.
What kind of father are you?
(What kind of father is Suk Jin?)
- A father who is like a friend.
- Actually...
- I'm like a friend to my son.
- He really is.
- This is serious.
- I'm really like his friend.
- You play with him well.
- I don't scold my kid.
- That's right.
- I don't nag at him.
- You talk with him on his level.
- You cater to your son.
- I...
- You walk with him on his level.
I work hard to have a perspective
that's similar to his.
I want my kid...
Say that you don't want your son
to live like you.
Thank you for your answer.
Sorry? Don't write that down.
Why didn't you
respond to my answer...
but respond to his?
- They're not supposed to be here.
- Right.
You can only interview me.
- They're not here.
- We're his cells.
- You need to answer me properly.
- Right.
You can't do that.
It's nice that he's like a friend
to his son.
- In other words...
- Just use what I said.
He's never talked to his son.
In another word,
he's not that interested in his son.
That's not true.
Don't write that down!
Why are you writing it?
You should write down when I say it,
not him!
- He should say it himself.
- Writer. No, I mean Reporter.
He'll live his life, and Hyun Woo
will be on his own as well.
You should say that you're
not that good of a father.
- That's what makes it cool.
- No, I don't...
He grew up by himself.
I'm not a controlling father.
The son doesn't control
his father either.
They live their own lives.
I don't tell him what to do.
I tell him to find a job
that makes him happy.
That's true. That's really true.
- I always say that to him.
- He's serious.
Then you should write down
Hyun Woo's answer as well.
Hyun Woo's answer?
"Dad, don't mind me."
(Hugh Grant of Jamwon-dong,
I'm like a friend to my son.)
- Here comes the next question.
- All right.
They say you're bad with ad-libs.
What's your take on that?
- That's true.
- We agree.
I agree too.
- He's keeping silent.
- When he's in good condition...
The fact that I can laugh
about it...
- No comment.
- proves I'm good at ad-libs.
No comment.
If I were bad at ad-libs...
We'll wrap up the interview now.
- No.
- Let's wrap it up here.
- Excuse me.
- Why would you end it?
- Let's wrap it up now.
- Because...
he's run out of ad-libs.
- He has nothing more to say.
- I just laugh it off like this.
No comment, sir.
What do you mean by no comment?
- No comment?
- Did you see...
how he ran out of ad-libs just now?
"I just laugh it off like this."
That's what you call an ad-lib?
- "I just laugh it off like this."
- You call that an ad-lib?
- Can you write that down?
- No. Don't write that.
- "I just laugh it off like this."
- It's the worst ad-lib.
- Don't...
Don't write that down.
- It was too old.
- What do you think?
Please write this instead.
- "I just laugh it off like this."
- The reason I can laugh...
Make sure to keep that.
Make use of Ji Hyo's name
at the end.
- "I just laugh it off like this."
Anyway...
- Anyway, he's out of ad-libs.
- Because it's not true.
Tell them to talk to your agency
about it.
- About his ad-libs?
- Yes.
Or you can say this.
"It's not that I'm only bad
at ad-libs."
("I'm bad at other things too.")
- You'll look humble.
- Well...
- My ad-libs...
- "No matter how hard I think,"
- "I just laugh it off."
- "I can't think of an ad-lib."
No matter how hard I think,
I got none
No matter how hard I think
(No matter how hard we think,
we can't accept that ad-lib.)
- Anyway...
- That was the worst.
(Bursting into laughter)
- What do we do with this?
- "I just laugh it off like this."
- Let's all just laugh it off.
- Let's laugh it off.
The viewers will laugh it off.
All right. So you don't
agree with that comment?
Of course not. Because...
if I were really bad at ad-libs,
- Here's the next question.
- they wouldn't...
- I'm talking right now.
- He cut it off.
- If they really thought I were bad,
- they wouldn't say so.
- "I just laugh it off like this."
Because I'm good at it...
- That was the best answer.
- Because I'm good at it,
they can make jokes like that.
- Oh, no.
- Then...
They can make jokes like that.
(Showing off a slapstick)
That was a nice ad-lib.
- He did a slapstick.
- He turned it around.
He turned it around. My gosh.
- Goodness.
- Anyway,
we'll try our best
to improve his ad-libs.
I actually think...
I have more popular lines
than these guys.
- "I just laugh it off like this."
Goodness, he's in serious trouble.
The next question is
your plan for next year.
Are you planning to make donations
next year?
This is a very sensitive question.
It's very sensitive.
- You should donate some.
- It's about time that you do.
You should.
- He doesn't donate at all.
- That's right.
Let's just sit out
for this question.
(The cells have no intention
to help with this question.)
- Let's see his ad-lib for this.
- Donations...
- "I just laugh it off like this."
We don't make plans for donations.
Are you saying
"I just laugh it off" again?
- Just say "I just laugh it off."
- You should make donations.
- "I just laugh it off."
- It makes you feel great.
You shouldn't make plans
for donations.
- Just say "I just laugh it off."
- Just repeat that.
- Hey.
- Do you have plans...
to make donations?
"I just laugh it off like this."
- That's hilarious.
- I'm always thinking...
- of making donations.
- Right.
Actually, I don't want it
to be known.
That's why he's never done it.
"It won't be known anyway."
"Why would I do it?"
I have made donations before.
But I didn't want to make it public.
Didn't you go around
to look for land to buy recently?
- I did.
- In Dongtan.
Did you sell the land in Paju?
No, I didn't.
Well, I...
Why don't you spare the money
to buy lands and donate instead?
How about donating that land?
Are you going to
just laugh it off again?
Are you laughing it off again?
He'll laugh it off.
He's not going to sell that land.
He'll just laugh it off.
- It's so funny.
- We're sorry.
- That's not true.
- It's so funny.
I'm not that into making donations.
I don't think I need to make
a promise...
- to make donations.
- That's true.
I think I should make donations
when I feel the need to.
I don't want to make donations
for the sake of it.
Does that mean you never
felt the need to make donations?
That's when I...
- That's why...
- Until now?
- I have made donations.
- That's why he still...
- doesn't feel the need to.
- He doesn't.
I have made donations before.
He also wishes to return
all his assets to society.
No, I don't.
All right, then.
(It's good that he's honest.
He doesn't want to make donations.)
You're turning 60 soon, which
the members made jokes about.
I'm not turning 60 soon.
I still got 4 more years.
- No, it's 3 years.
- It's 3 years.
- No, it's four years.
- The new year is around the corner.
- Still, I got four years left.
- I'll be 61 after 4 years.
- That's 3 years, then.
Why is it 3 years?
I still got 5 more years!
You see?
He gets upset so easily.
- I can't say anything now.
- You'll turn 60 after 3 years.
Is there a bucket list
you want to accomplish?
- A bucket list.
- Can you speak up?
- He's a reporter!
- I'm sorry.
- Who talks like that to a reporter?
- How can you speak like that?
- I was just annoyed by them.
- I'm sorry.
- He's rude.
- You'll be in big trouble.
- I apologize.
Is there a bucket list you want to
accomplish when you turn 60?
- A bucket list?
- A bucket list.
I actually do.
- Wasn't it getting a divorce?
- You actually said this to me.
- It's graduating from marriage.
- Graduating from marriage?
- Is that true?
- You told me.
- Explain it.
- It's that...
- You said you wanted to be free.
Earlier...
- Seriously...
- "I just laugh it off."
- You said that on the show.
He actually said it.
He said he'll graduate from marriage
when he turns 60.
It's true that I said that
ten years ago.
It's true. I jokingly talked
about it with my wife.
"Hey, when we turn 60,"
"why don't we
freely enjoy our lives?"
And my wife told me this.
"Make sure to keep that promise."
That's what she said.
I still remember that.
But things have changed.
- Then?
- Things have changed.
My wife is my forever best friend.
- A friend?
- When I'm with my wife...
- Yes.
- Then what does that make of you?
You're friends
with your son as well.
- It's so strange.
- A friendship.
What does that make of your family
if you're friends...
with both your son and wife?
- A friendship.
- A friendship?
It's a friendship.
That's why I have a bucket list.
("I have a bucket list.")
- Going to a nude beach.
- When I turn 60...
I want to go to a nude beach.
(He hopes to visit a nude beach.)
(Superstar Ji wants to visit
a nude beach when he's 60.)
- Hey.
- What?
A nude beach?
Imagine Suk Jin lying
on a nude beach.
- I mean...
- He wants to go to a nude beach...
when he's 60.
That was hilarious.
Right?
- Going to a nude beach.
- His laugh looks fake.
- Imagine him...
being naked.
- And he'll be smiling.
- That's not what I want to do.
- With sunglasses.
- That's not true.
- Don't write that down.
- With sunglasses.
- Don't get swayed by them.
- Going to a nude beach.
I do have one thing
that I want to do.
Making donations.
- Making donations.
- That's hilarious.
Everyone is the same.
What are you writing down?
I haven't said anything.
- Don't write that.
- He'll donate everything.
I only laughed because it was funny.
Going to a nude beach.
- Going back to the soil.
- I want to go on a trip...
- around the world for 31 days.
- Going to a nude beach.
You'll go to a nude beach
for your trip.
(A nude beach tour
for 30 nights and 31 days)
- He'll be naked for 30 days.
- Be quiet!
- He'll be completely tanned.
- You'll be tanned.
You can't go.
You'll be completely tanned.
That was hilarious.
- Suk Jin, that's your beach look.
- A trip for 30 nights and 31 days.
I want to go on a cruise
for 30 nights and 31 days.
You see how they're reacting?
- They've gone quiet.
- Suk Jin.
You can't go with this answer.
- That's right.
- I'll choose the other answer.
Please just write that down.
A trip around the world.
- Going to a nude beach.
- A trip around the world.
He'll be naked.
I kept imagining his back
on the nude beach.
I can't imagine it.
- That was hilarious.
- As you performed well in 2021,
many people are saying
that you deserve the grand award.
- Pardon?
- Right.
If you were to receive
the grand award,
what will your acceptance speech
be like?
- It's already tear-jerking.
- I'm already touched.
- I've never thought...
- I agree that he deserves it.
- of winning the grand award.
- Come on.
Tell them you'll refuse it
even if they give you one.
(Tell them you'll refuse it
even if they give you one.)
- Didn't you say...
- Tell them you'll refuse it.
that SBS is too mean to you?
No, that's not it.
Tell them you'll refuse it.
I've never thought of getting
the grand award.
- You'll cry.
- It's strange...
that we're doing this special
when the award show is nearing.
I know. You deserve it.
- They're making a narration.
- Suk Jin.
- That's not true.
- They must be planning something.
- This is a great storyline.
- Suk Jin.
- That's not going to happen.
- You should look forward to it.
- No, that's not true.
- To be honest,
- it's not like we have...
- We don't have one.
- strong candidates for this year.
- There's none.
That's not true.
Even Tak Jae Hoon is after it.
- Jae Hoon is?
- Yes.
Suk Jin is way better than him.
There's no strong candidate
for the grand award this year.
It has been only two years
since he returned. He's being greedy.
Suk Jin deserves it.
You've been in this business
for 30 years.
I think he's being greedy.
- Tak Jae Hoon is being greedy.
- Anyway...
- You must be getting one.
- I'm suddenly...
You're not getting ready
for it already, are you?
No. I've never imagined it.
His heart must be beating
really fast.
- He lost his focus.
- His heart must be beating fast.
It is beating really fast.
- You've thought about it.
- Just the question itself...
must be nerve-racking for him.
- You've thought about it.
- I'm really nervous.
- I really am nervous.
- Right?
I think I might cry.
- The grand award winner.
- I might cry.
- Ji Suk Jin!
- Suk Jin, you won the grand award!
- Congratulations!
- Suk Jin!
- This is...
- You should hug us.
- For real?
I think I might cry.
I can't imagine it, to be honest.
But you've thought of it, right?
At least once.
- This year's grand award winner...
- Be honest.
I mean, I heard
I'm one of the candidates.
Really?
- They've never heard of it.
- Really? You all know about it?
What do you mean
you're one of the candidates?
- For which award show?
- You're not getting shingles, yes?
- Suk Jin!
- Are you getting shingles?
- You never know.
I heard I'm one of the candidates.
For which award show?
- Suk Jin is at it again.
- Anyway...
I bet it's not only for me
if they give me the grand award.
I'm sure it's meant
for all of us on Running Man.
- That's not fair.
- What are you talking about?
That's not true. It's meant for you.
It's making me become serious.
Honestly speaking, he deserves it.
- He certainly does.
- He deserves it.
Let's move on to the next question.
- I'm going to cry my eyes out.
- That was the last question.
Then we'll wrap up the interview.
Good work, everyone.
There's no way I'm getting
the grand award. No way.
- Thank you.
- No way.
- Good work, everyone.
- Everyone.
- You never know.
According to how the interview went
for Superstar Ji,
Jae Suk and Jong Kook will
receive eight Gullible Coins each.
- That's a lot.
- You got a lot.
- Haha will get seven coins.
- That's a lot.
Se Chan will get five coins.
So Min and Ji Hyo
will get three each.
- Yes.
- You guys did a lot.
We'll move to the next spot
for lunch.
My gosh.
- Se Chan!
- What is it?
I've already lost 300 dollars.
I invested in something else though.
You can sell them now if you want.
You should purchase SK Telecom's
stocks now.
I already made 370 dollars.
- Really?
- Yes! Take a look.
I bought it with the 10,000 dollars
I was given.
Why didn't you buy
SK Telecom's stocks?
I know, right? He should've
bought them when I did.
People make a lot of calls
because of COVID-19.
How much did you lose, Se Chan?
I already lost two percent too.
Why did you buy that stock
in the first place?
Because it was just for today.
I don't buy stocks like this.
- I get it, but why?
- In case they get me wrong.
Suk Jin is not the type
to buy stocks like this.
He doesn't buy stocks based on
info that's already open to public.
He buys stocks based on the tips
that people give.
- You get what I mean?
- The tips they give nonchalantly?
- Yes, those tips.
- Not the tips you get...
- from deep conversations.
- Exactly.
Then you should get those.
There are so many people
who give me tips.
- "I'm only telling you this."
- Right. I'm talking about those.
"I'm only sharing this with you."
Cells, don't only focus
on your stocks.
- It's driving me crazy.
- He keeps asking me.
This is fake money.
By the way,
where are we going for lunch?
It's the place
with Suk Jin's memories.
Where could it be?
I've mentioned a couple of places.
It's this place.
(It's a restaurant in Apgujeong
where Suk Jin's memories are.)
- I know that place.
- It's not only for me.
They all have memories
of that place.
I saw Suk Jin and Jae Suk
in that place.
- Soo Hong was also there.
- We...
I'm not even kidding.
Suk Jin, Yong Man,
- and I...
- You picked the right place.
I saw them chatting for
more than ten hours.
We always started our nights
in that place.
- That place is...
- When was that?
We went there
from the early 1990s...
- That's right.
- to the early 2000s.
After I made my debut
as a member of Turbo in 1995,
I went to Gangnam
for the first time.
- It must be an old place.
- The cells will decide on the menu.
We must have their tteokbokki.
- We must have their tteokbokki.
- Of course.
When we were single,
many incredible women
visited that place.
- That's true.
- That's right.
Many celebrities visited that place.
They did.
Many trainees worked there...
- as a part-timer.
- They did.
- To be scouted?
- Yes.
There were many people
who were scouted from cafes.
- That's right.
- I heard Jung Woo Sung...
- used to work near there.
- That's true.
What about you?
Didn't you wait tables there?
Actually...
- Did you debut early?
- I worked at a cafe.
You did?
- You got scouted from there?
- You must've been popular.
Of course.
They all must've wanted her.
- I see.
- You must've been really popular.
Of course. Not just anyone
could work at a cafe.
Even when I was young.
Have you ever done
a part-time job, Suk Jin?
- I have.
- Where?
I worked near
Ewha Womans University.
- I waited tables.
- In where?
- At a cafe.
- You worked at a cafe?
- Yes.
- Is that from 40 years ago?
Suk Jin. Didn't you work
in the kitchen?
Didn't you work in the kitchen?
No. I was the main waiter.
He worked at a tavern.
- A tavern?
- I waited tables.
- That sounds plausible.
- You dressed up as a servant.
- I was the main...
- You had to lift a rice bag.
- A rice bag?
- At a tavern.
It was a popular place
near Ewha Womans University.
I waited tables.
How much was the minimum wage
back in your day?
- Back in my day...
- Wasn't it in coins?
I bet it was
only three hwan per hour.
I bet you got about four coins.
I bet you only got four.
Or he could've exchanged goods.
Or buckwheat per hour?
Maybe he got two cabbages per hour.
(Two cabbages)
- Maybe he got buckwheat.
- Or two cabbages.
- Or two fishes.
- Or three hwan.
I got sweet potatoes and millets.
Are you happy now?
I love it when he admits it.
- It makes you go crazy.
- I love it.
Let's have some tteokbokki.
We must have tteokbokki
in this cafe.
- It's good to be back.
- It smells like Gangnam.
It does smell like Gangnam.
- I get it.
- What do you mean by that?
It's different.
- They didn't have this before.
- Things have changed a lot.
Suk Jin, why don't you order
some ttekbokki since we're hungry?
We should have tteokbokki.
There are so many delicious things.
They still have kimchi fried rice.
We used to eat
kimchi fried rice here very often.
Guys, their ramyeon is 23 dollars.
It's so expensive.
I want to try it.
Actually, when we were young,
we were so poor...
- that we couldn't eat them all.
- We were poor then.
So we only sat by the entrance.
We sat there to watch the people
that come by.
(They could only watch the people
that come in by the entrance.)
- Goodness.
- Hello.
- I'll take your order.
- It's been so long.
- I know.
I haven't been here for so long.
- Right?
- Suk Jin came back as a superstar.
I know. Back in those days,
he only had drinks.
- That's right.
- Oh, right.
He couldn't eat anything.
- It's because I had no money.
- You're precisely right.
- Right.
- He only had drinks.
- He only sat by the entrance.
- That's right.
- He's right.
- He only had drinks.
For how long did you work here?
I've been working here for 23 years.
So I remember seeing Jae Suk...
- and others.
- He's been here since then.
He knows
the history of all celebrities.
Let's order a seafood stew.
- Let's order two.
- It'd be nice to dip bread with it.
- Let's have that.
- We must have that.
We'll have seafood tomato stew.
Why don't you order
a menu of your memories?
Can you recommend us
which tteokbokki to get?
- What about this?
- Let's have kimchi fried rice.
Let's have truffle oil garlic pasta.
How about pizza margherita?
They still have kimchi fried rice.
We used to eat that a lot here.
Let's have kimchi fried rice.
- Let's have kimchi fried rice.
- We should have kimchi fried rice.
- The two of them...
- We'll have two.
- We used to have this.
We used to serve one fried egg
with it, but we serve two now.
- Really?
- Yes.
You used to give us
only one fried egg.
- We serve two now.
- You do?
It was one of the cheapest menus.
I bet you couldn't have it
because it was too expensive.
Right. It was too expensive.
(He's making fun of the regular
he couldn't see for years.)
Then let's have a dish of pasta.
Or shall we have pizza?
- We must have their pizza.
- Let's do that.
How about pizza margherita?
Let's have pizza margherita.
I also want pizza margherita.
- Me too.
- No, order pizza gorgonzola.
The Hawaiian pizza...
- is the one with pineapples, right?
- No.
- Let's have pizza gorgonzola.
- Pizza margherita...
is their menu to go.
- Let's have pizza margherita.
- No.
- Suk Jin.
You'll stop midways...
- while having that.
- Pizza margherita is good.
- but gorgonzola is...
- Order pizza gorgonzola.
- Gorgonzola is stinky.
- Gorgonzola is one with honey, no?
- That's right.
- But it's too stinky.
What's the pizza
that's most convenient to eat?
It's pizza gorgonzola.
(Sending a signal)
You should pick one.
Just pick pizza gorgonzola.
That's right.
Then let's have pizza gorgonzola.
Why don't you just order
whatever the two of you want?
- Let's order a Hawaiian pizza.
- Looks like they're in charge.
- Let's have a Hawaiian pizza.
- Are we all set?
- Yes, we are.
- Yes.
- We'll have that.
- Let's order drinks now.
We can order that while eating.
Why not? I want to order drinks.
Does anyone want any drinks?
Is there a non-alcoholic cocktail
called Nude Beach here?
A glass of Nude Beach?
I want Nude Beach too.
Can you make a cocktail called
Nude Beach for us?
Can you make one with that name?
- Oh...
- Yes.
- That's impossible.
- We can't.
- "I just laugh it off."
- Why would you make them do that?
Is what we ordered
enough for all of us?
- Yes, it's more than enough.
- Please make it delicious.
- We'll have those.
- All right.
It's nice here.
It's so fascinating that
he remembers you two.
- That must be really expensive.
- Did you choose this place?
No, I gave the staff many options,
and they chose it.
- That's what happened.
- Right.
Why did you dress like that though?
Now that we're on it...
Gosh, you guys.
He looks weird alone.
This is so annoying.
Why did it burst?
- Where?
- It really burst.
Did it really?
- Come on.
- Suk Jin...
Maybe it's corroded.
Corroded?
(A superstar who came by a cafe
with corroded pants)
- This place is a bit...
- They're already here.
They're here.
- We can just eat them?
- Yes, go ahead.
- What should I do?
- Thank you.
This is the seafood tteokbokki.
- Rice.
- Ramyeon and rice tteokbokki.
Ramyeon and rice tteokbokki.
It's the chopped steak.
Look at that.
These are the dishes
I have never had here.
- Thank you.
- What is this?
- Stew.
- Suit.
Not suit. It's stew.
- Stew.
- Stew?
- No way.
- Thank you for the food.
You know,
I never had
a fancy feast like this here.
Seriously.
- I never ate so well here.
- That's right.
My goodness.
(The friends who have been together
for 30 years realized their dream.)
Our plans never succeeded.
We came here with hopes
to meet women,
- but we never succeeded.
- No.
I will be honest with you.
Before going to a nightclub,
we gathered here for a short while.
- I see.
- Then we had...
- a briefing...
- Plans.
about what we will do.
You planned how you will play.
- And...
- "I will pick up the tab here."
We talked about how much money
each member should pay.
We came up with plans at this place.
All of us were from far away.
None of us were
from this neighborhood.
- All of us...
- We were from Suyu-ri.
- Suyu-ri and Myeonmok-dong.
- Really?
Myeonmok-dong. Thus...
Hoegi-dong.
(The big mouths gathered around
from different neighborhoods.)
We had to meet at a place.
- That's right.
- Why didn't you meet there?
- Why did you meet in Gangnam?
- Why did you come here?
- We came here.
- You had no money.
- Why didn't you hang out there?
- We just met someplace else.
- Did you ever talk...
- to a woman you liked?
- No.
- You didn't even try.
We didn't think it would work.
We knew that we were shabby.
There was one forte we had.
- The older members had it anyway.
- Smooth talk.
- I knew it.
- That was...
the only thing we had in Gangnam.
It did work to our advantage.
In terms of looks...
There are times...
women take a break
from partying with handsome men.
(That's how it is.)
- "Let's just laugh today."
- Yes.
To be honest,
- that was all we had.
- I can say this for sure.
Women who hung out with us...
- laughed a lot.
- They laughed all day long.
And we went home afterward.
(And we went home afterward.)
We went home afterward.
After laughing for a while...
They headed home.
- "We had fun." They headed home.
- You were left by yourselves.
We went home afterward.
"I just laugh it off like this."
("I just laugh it off like this.")
Orangeade, lemonade,
and grapefruit ade.
- You can get a latte too.
- I will have a coke.
I want...
iced Americano.
- Do you want it light?
- Yes.
- Me too.
- Let's all order Americano.
- Okay.
Sir.
Then I will order Americano too.
You should get Americano too.
- Coke is...
- I thought you wanted a coke?
No. Americano sounds better.
Order iced Americano.
No.
- Order iced Americano.
- Iced?
- You should drink something cold.
- Iced Americano.
Please give us seven iced Americano.
Can you make it light?
- Of course.
- Please make one cup light.
I will add double shots
for the other six cups.
Please make two cups
with a single shot.
- Please make it 3 cups.
- So 3 cups with a single shot.
You should have it
with a single shot too.
Please make another cup that way.
Four cups with a single shot.
So 4 cups with a single shot
and 3 cups with double shots.
- Okay.
Do you do everything
Jae Suk tells you to do?
I don't do everything
he tells me to do.
Iced Americano was bitter...
when I made it
with double shots at home.
- A single shot is better.
- It's better.
- It was a rich and tasty meal.
- Everything was tasty.
You ordered food...
and shared memories of the past.
- Jae Suk earned 3 coins.
- Did he only earn 3 coins?
- He talked a lot.
- Jong Kook earned four coins.
My goodness. All right.
Haha earned 1 coin
and Se Chan earned 2 coins.
- Ji Hyo and So Min didn't earn any.
- Okay.
Here comes the last schedule
of Suk Jin, the superstar.
Hugh Grant of Jamwon-dong
will buy a present for his wife.
- Suk Jin will use his own money...
- Of course.
because loves his wife.
Go ahead and recommend things
without worrying about the price.
That's right.
We will recommend things.
- We will keep it reasonable.
- Okay.
- To be honest,
- We are quick-witted.
my wife doesn't like presents
that are over-the-top.
- So the price...
- You don't know that.
Seriously.
Have you lived with my wife?
- Of course, we haven't.
- But...
- your wife is fancy.
- Seriously.
The present shouldn't be
overly expensive.
- We know that.
- All right, Suk Jin.
Suk Jin.
How much
are you planning to spend today?
Suk Jin doesn't have a problem
spending 2,000 dollars on himself.
How much
will you spend on your wife?
What's the maximum?
- Is it 500 dollars?
- Suk Jin.
How much are you thinking?
You need to remember
that this is for a show.
- That's right.
- How much are you thinking?
- I bet it's under 500 dollars.
- Under 500 dollars.
- It's under 500 dollars.
- Really?
Under 500 dollars?
Isn't there a category she likes?
- What?
- What's her favorite color?
She likes fancy things too.
Doesn't she have a favorite color?
You didn't say that earlier.
You said
that she doesn't like fancy things.
Come on.
She likes fancy designs.
She wears bold clothes.
- What?
- That's not what you said earlier.
Why are you confusing us?
You know,
she likes ordinary clothes as well.
Don't think about
the brand and price.
- What's her favorite color?
- Style.
How about a scarf?
She should wear a scarf.
Wouldn't it be suffocating?
You are the most suffocating.
(Suk Jin, the human scarf)
Seriously.
My wife's fashion style is...
too different from mine.
She doesn't trust my eyes.
That's why you should trust me.
- She doesn't trust my eyes.
- That's why you should get...
accessories instead.
- Ones that are widely popular.
- I can help you pick one.
How about a necklace?
- A necklace.
- I don't know about a necklace.
- A scarf is better.
- A necklace...
needs to be very fancy.
- Really?
- It's Christmas.
It's your heart
that matters the most.
- Gloves and scarves.
- Gloves make a nice present.
- A set.
- A scarf is a good idea.
You should go and look.
- That's right.
- Then you will be able to find one.
In that case,
can I get something as well?
- No. Why would you get something?
- Just because.
- "Can I get something as well?"
- Buy us a present each.
Of course not.
I will buy you something.
- Jae Suk.
- Go ahead and pick one.
- He is the best.
- Ji Hyo, pick one as well.
Hey, what does that make me?
He is generous enough
to buy his junior a present.
I will buy you a present.
Pick one each.
- Really?
- Jae Suk.
I can buy you a present,
but I don't want to do it
in front of the cameras.
His face turned so red.
- He will be Santa.
- My face didn't turn red.
- Santa.
I don't want to do it
in front of the cameras.
You should pick one as well.
- I wanted to buy you a present.
- He is a superstar.
- Can I pick one as well?
- Yes. Go ahead.
Today, I will pay.
It's okay. You should just get
your wife's present.
No. I actually wanted...
- to buy everyone a present.
- It's okay.
Don't force yourself.
Seriously.
- This is the perfect opportunity.
- I mean it.
Look at him.
He wouldn't have much money.
I have a lot of money.
Look at him.
He is leading a fake life.
His clothes are in tatters.
What is this?
- He is leading a fake life.
- These clothes...
are falling apart.
It makes my heart ache.
We are here.
- It's a boutique.
- A boutique.
- Isn't it nice, Se Chan?
- There are so many things to see.
- There are so many pretty things.
- This is nice.
This is cute.
This is very cute.
- This is like a paradise.
- This is cute.
- Nice.
- There are many cute clothes.
There are so many things I like.
I think your wife would like
a padded jacket.
No. She doesn't wear
- Suk Jin, there are many options.
- Don't look for your item.
Help me find my wife's present.
I will help you.
There are cosmetic products as well.
Suk Jin,
what Jae Suk's said...
made me focus on my item.
Same here.
I can't help but look for my item.
- What should I do?
- This is cute.
Se Chan, I can't help
but look for my item.
So Min, how does this look?
It's pretty.
It suits you.
Stop picking your present.
It has been so long
since I went shopping...
- that I am focused on my present.
- I know.
My concentration level dropped.
How cute!
- Is there downstairs?
- We were too focused on work.
- Jae Suk, there is downstairs.
- It's so nice to come back here.
So Min, this will look good on you.
- It's pretty.
- Right?
- This is exciting.
- This place is nice.
Doesn't Suk Jin seem like
a designer?
- You look like a designer.
- Please choose.
Welcome to my boutique.
- You look like a designer.
- It's hilarious.
- A designer.
- Please choose.
- Ji, the designer.
- This is cute.
What do you think of this?
Isn't it cute?
- It's cute.
- Isn't it cute?
- It's very cute.
If my wife wears it...
- Isn't it cute?
- It's cute.
- How about this?
- But...
she doesn't like rough texture.
Buy her a padded jacket.
It's cute, but the price is...
- How about this?
- The texture is too rough.
(Put it back down.)
How about a padded vest like this?
- Doesn't she like it?
- She never wears such a thing.
This.
Jong Kook headed straight over
to the padded jackets and vests.
She would like a padded vest.
Why doesn't he get one?
I like this.
- I think she would look good in it.
- What?
This light purple top.
She would like it. It's short.
- Really?
- Yes. It's very pretty.
- I see.
- It's the trendy style.
- I don't know what's good.
- It's pretty.
I should check the price.
(He checks the price tag.)
Gosh.
Where was it?
Why don't you buy
something bright like this?
- What?
- This one.
She doesn't wear such clothes.
- No?
- No. It isn't her style.
- I love this color.
- Really?
- The price is good too.
- It's bright, isn't it?
She likes bright colors.
Isn't this cardigan too big?
- Boxy clothes are in these days.
- It's too big.
Loose-fitting clothes are in.
Even if it's loose-fitting...
What's the price?
The price isn't that bad.
You're right.
(The frugal customer is satisfied
by the cheap price.)
- Suk Jin.
- Yes?
(Let's see.)
These are for you.
- Gosh.
- These are for you.
- Come on.
- They suit you perfectly.
Don't they suit you?
- They are cool.
- They match your shoes too.
While they go well with my outfit...
Shall I buy this?
- I think it will suit me.
- It will suit you.
- What?
- It's pretty.
- Shall I buy this?
(The cardigan enthusiast
picked his own present.)
- When she goes to exercise...
- Right? It suits me.
- When she goes to exercise,
- Suk Jin.
she can wear this
over her gym clothes.
- It's pretty.
- I like this.
It's nice, right?
- Do you like it?
- It's nice.
Take a look at the price.
Is it okay? Should I put it back?
- Gosh.
- Put it back.
(It isn't okay.)
Put it back.
(He orders him to put it back
after checking the price.)
Is that really the price?
- Is there one more zero?
- Yes, there is.
Suk Jin, your pants are tattered.
- It's quite expensive.
- Seriously.
There is one more zero.
Isn't it nice?
It's pretty.
Put it back for now.
- It's pretty.
- It's for your wife.
You said that you like it.
How much is this?
What do you think of this vest?
- This vest.
- It must be expensive.
- All right.
- It's really pretty.
- How about this?
- Is it rabbit? Is it mink?
I think it's something like that.
- How much is it?
- It's 1,950 dollars.
Hurry up and put it back.
- Suk Jin, how about this?
- Suk Jin.
This is 790 dollars.
- What is?
- What's her style?
- The cardigan?
- Yes.
Is it that expensive?
Suk Jin.
Please.
Spend money on your wife.
Why do you keep checking...
- the price tag?
- It's not like that.
- You are buying her a present.
Why did you change your mind
after checking the price?
- It's not like that. It's fine.
- It's 790 dollars.
You know, 790 dollars is a hefty price.
It's so pretty.
(Meanwhile, suspicious activity
is detected at the changing room.)
(A forsythia gentleman appears.)
This is it!
What?
Why did you wear it?
It looks nice. It suits you.
This is it.
It suits you.
- This is what you should wear.
- Isn't it menswear?
- Seriously.
- It suits you. You should buy it.
Shall I buy it?
That wasn't my plan.
(He forgot about the mission
and shopped for his cardigan.)
(Se Chan heads somewhere
with a smile on his face.)
Suk Jin.
Suk Jin, in that case...
Hey.
(He puts his hat on the mannequin.)
- Suk Jin, how about this?
- Hey.
So Min. I am going to buy this.
It looks nice.
It suits you.
Suk Jin said it looks nice.
The hat looks nice.
- This hat.
- It looks nice.
- It's cute.
- Why don't you get it?
- How much is it?
Suk Jin, I will hold it.
Why is the hat so hot?
How about this?
Isn't it the hat you were wearing?
You jerk.
(It's easy to make fun of Suk Jin.)
Apparently, this isn't her style.
What's her style?
This is so hard.
Why did you change your mind
after checking the price?
It's not like that. It's fine.
- Ji Hyo, I think this is pretty.
- How about this?
It's nice, right?
I saw it earlier. Isn't it too much?
She likes something like this.
- Really?
- It's feminine.
- It's nice, right?
- Yes.
- It's nice.
- It's a bit...
- This one is cute too.
- She likes something like this.
It would fit nicely.
- She has eccentric tastes.
It's nice, right?
Is it the price on the tag?
Is there a discount?
- No.
- It's so pretty.
- Why is it so expensive?
How much is it?
It's 750 dollars.
It's pretty.
A sweater should cost that much.
- It's pretty.
- Really?
- The shoulders are reminiscent...
of Son Dam Bi
in the "Saturday Night" music video.
- These days...
- It's pretty.
Son Dam Bi
in the "Saturday Night" music video.
My wife does prefer a sweater...
with a V-neck.
She likes a V-neck.
She prefers a V-neck.
(Suk Jin sways
amidst people's opinions.)
The price is nice too.
(Jong Kook is still looking at
the padded vests.)
- Suk Jin.
- Yes?
- Most boutiques...
- That looks nice.
- Suk Jin, listen.
- Okay.
Most boutiques add their own items.
- Really?
- It looks luxurious, right?
- I will show your the price tag.
- Suk Jin.
It's perfect. 465 dollars.
- It's perfect, right?
- It's nice.
Yes. It looks luxurious.
- Look. The color is pretty too.
- It's nice.
Haha, he isn't interested in
that one.
- No?
- I showed it to him earlier.
Move out of the way.
- It's perfect. It's pretty, right?
- I showed it to him earlier.
He doesn't want it
because it's 1,500 dollars, right?
- No.
- I saw it when I came downstairs.
I was surprised
upon checking the price.
It's perfect.
These days,
- people wear oversized clothes.
- It looks very practical.
Totally.
Does it come in other colors?
Will it be okay?
Will she be happy to receive it?
Suk Jin.
It's a sweater
that makes one go, "It's pretty."
It's pretty.
- You have a point.
- Think about it.
That vest seems like
an insincere present, right?
You can buy something like that
anywhere.
- Suk Jin, do you want this or not?
- I am so confused.
- Look at this.
- You should buy this.
- I think...
- Hold on.
this would make the best present.
It's winter.
While it's nice, I don't know
if it would make a good present.
Why? It's pretty.
When you look at it,
- it looks cute and luxurious.
- This is...
Suk Jin, I recommend this one.
- But...
- The price is just right.
- Really?
Still, it's too casual.
- What?
- It's too casual.
This is better.
- Suk Jin.
- Mister.
You have no money, right?
Get out.
Get out if you aren't going to buy
anything.
- Suk Jin, tell me this.
- At home...
- What?
- How much do you have?
- What kind of a question is that?
- What's the limit?
There is no limit.
I want to buy her something nice.
You agreed to everything
under 300 dollars.
- If it was over 1,000 dollars...
- That's not true.
Suk Jin, you saw everything
in this boutique.
You really did.
- It's about time you buy something.
- I think this sweater is nice.
- My wife...
- She wouldn't like that.
likes eccentric clothes.
- Would she like that?
- It would fit nicely.
- Even if it fits nicely,
- It's very pretty.
- the cherries and strawberries...
- I have a problem...
- with its arms.
- The shoulders.
The shoulders will look fine
once you wear it.
Why don't you send her photos?
- What?
- Ask her to choose...
- the one she likes.
- Seriously.
- No.
- A photo of this sweater...
I will buy this one.
- Really?
- Ji Hyo did it.
- Did you make up your mind?
- It looks nice.
Other items didn't make me go,
- "She would like that."
- How much is it?
- I know her style.
- It's cute.
Once this episode airs,
wouldn't people recognize her
from this sweater?
People would go,
"Isn't she Suk Jin's wife?"
It's bound to happen.
- It's bound to happen.
- This is the only one left.
- That's right.
- It's a nice sweater.
- Suk Jin, it fits nicely.
- It's very pretty.
Suk Jin, it fits nicely.
It's pretty.
(She suddenly has a fashion show.)
She can wear it
over her gym clothes.
Suk Jin, it fits nicely.
(Hold on. It looks nice.)
It's really nice.
She likes such clothes.
- Really?
- She does, right?
I knew it.
The vest is 300 dollars cheaper.
That's why Suk Jin likes it.
That's right.
The sweater is 700 dollars,
but the vest is 300 dollars.
It's winter,
so the vest is the way to go.
Seriously.
- This is hard.
- The fabric is soft.
- Right?
- Yes.
She can wear it
when she goes to play golf.
That's right.
- It does look nice. Go ahead.
- Not bad, right?
Swing.
Come on and show us. Show us a shot.
- Nice.
- What did you hit?
- It's nice and practical.
- It's pretty.
- It's practical.
- I am sweating.
- Are you sweating?
- Is it warm?
- Yes. I am hot right now.
My wife did ask me why there are
no short-sleeved padded jackets.
This is it.
You can also wear it
to go for a jog.
(She becomes a jogging model.)
- It looks nice.
- "What?"
- "Honey."
- That's right.
I think she will like it better.
She likes to exercise.
- That's nice.
- I really think that.
You changed your mind
because of the price.
It's because of the price, right?
- No.
- It's fact.
It's because of the price.
Since black is too common,
I will buy this one.
It's a good one.
- I will buy this one.
- It's a good one. Seriously.
She will like it.
She likes light-colored clothes.
Suk Jin is swayed so easily.
Back in the day,
he moved when I said,
"They are having a sale."
"They are having a sale." "Where?"
"They are giving a discount."
"Where?"
(Sale Ji pays for the item.)
Here you go.
We will give a coin to Jong Kook.
Thank you.
It's time to pick the members
who will receive the prize.
You know, Suk Jin is...
in tattered clothes.
Seriously. He is a romantic man.
- He is in tattered clothes.
- He is a romantic man.
- You know,
- He is in tattered clothes.
these clothes are so old
that the overlapping parts...
- are falling apart.
- His bottom is a wreck.
- His clothes are falling apart.
- A wreck.
- He really is...
- a romantic man.
- The overlapping parts...
are falling apart.
According to our record,
Jae Suk has 16 coins.
Jong Kook has 15 coins.
Haha has 11 coins.
Ji Hyo has four coins.
So Min has six coins.
Se Chan has ten coins.
Since Ji Hyo has
the smallest number of coins,
we will convert 4 coins
to 1 prize ball.
(The number of prize balls)
Let's check the stocks.
- I told you to invest.
- Seriously.
A negative return
will earn you a penalty.
- Me? A negative return?
- Yes.
- Did you say that earlier?
- I told you that a penalty...
depends on the result.
(He acts like
he didn't hear the rules.)
(Se Chan recommended buying
stocks in biotechnology.)
(Suk Jin went all in.)
What's the number?
(A negative return will make him
a candidate for a penalty.)
I'm turning it back on. Currently...
(What will be the result?)
Currently... What?
The return is in the negative.
(The return is in the negative.)
(He proved once again
that he has unlucky hands.)
It's 154 dollars.
- Thus,
- It's 154.80 dollars.
Suk Jin will be
a candidate for a penalty as well.
I can't believe it.
Some people earned money.
I did.
He should have listened to you.
Suk Jin.
I told you that there is a prize.
The prize of the day is something...
you can enjoy
with your family at the year-end.
It's Champagne.
Thank you.
- I love it.
- It's a high-end Champagne.
Seriously.
The first two people
will receive a prize.
The last person
will receive a penalty.
It's a close call.
- It's a close call.
- It can be anyone.
What should I do?
I don't want to wear this outfit.
I really don't.
No one wants to wear it.
I really don't want to wear
this outfit.
The first two people...
It doesn't count if the two balls
belong to the same person.
Prize.
- Prize.
- The first winner is...
- Let's do this.
Haha.
- The first winner is...
- Me.
- Jae Suk.
- Okay.
(Jae Suk wins a prize.)
He had many balls.
- I know.
- There wasn't a twist.
Let's drink Champagne.
- He is so lucky.
- Let's drink Champagne, Se Chan.
This ball doesn't count
because it's yours.
Hold on.
How many balls belong to me?
One.
Then mine will be the last one.
- We don't know it yet.
- I also have one.
I had only two,
but I still got picked last time.
- My gosh.
- There's not much difference.
- Prize! Say Yang Se Chan.
- Haha.
(Who's the second prize winner?)
- So Min.
Haha.
(He had only 2 balls,
but he got lucky and won the prize.)
I can't believe this.
I'm so jealous.
- Good.
- Congratulations.
It's a perfect gift
for those who like to drink.
Now...
I'll draw balls
until one of your names is called.
I don't want to get the penalty.
How many balls do you have?
- How many?
- I think I have four balls.
It's good to have
my name picked first, right?
- It's drawn.
- The first one to be exempted.
- I want to be exempted.
- It can't be me.
- Jong Kook.
- Okay.
- I can't be picked...
- because I have only one ball.
- Yes!
I need at least three balls.
It will be funny
if he wears it again next week.
- I know. It's connected.
- All right.
(Who's the next one
to be exempted from the penalty?)
The next one is...
- Yang Se Chan.
- Okay!
(Sighing)
- I survived!
- It's Ji Hyo, So Min, and...
It will be either Ji Hyo or So Min.
(Only Ji Hyo, So Min, and Suk Jin
are left with 1 ball each.)
The outfit is...
Only the members who can fit
into the outfit are left.
It will be funny.
- All right.
- Say Ji Suk Jin.
(Who will be the first one
to be exempted among these three?)
Say Ji Suk Jin.
Jeon So Min.
(Jeon So Min)
- Jeon So Min.
- So Min.
This is better
than winning the prize.
It's a lot better.
It's better than winning the prize.
- It might be Suk Jin.
- I'm so happy.
- I have only one ball.
- It'll be funny to wear it again.
(The last draw to decide
a member to be made fun of)
- It's decided.
- It is?
I bet it's me. Ji Suk Jin.
It will be funny
if Ji Hyo is picked.
- The last one to be exempted.
- I bet it's me.
(Who will be
the last one to survive?)
Song Ji Hyo.
(Song Ji Hyo has survived.)
Suk Jin.
- Two weeks in a row.
- Can you believe this?
(Can you believe this?)
- Should I wear this again?
- He should wear it again.
He will wear it again next week.
You must be happy.
How would I wear these?
They are all worn out.
- I survived.
- This is hilarious.
I was surprised as I tried
to take this off. It just came off.
We are having
a year-end party next week.
- You should come in that outfit.
- That sounds nice.
It sounds perfect.
I think it's perfect for a party.
- It looks good on you.
- I know this is good, but...
(A fancy year-end party
for the grand finale)
(Superstar Ji Seok Sam is back.)
I'm a queen.
(And the other members
are all dressed up too.)
(But the stars of the day are...)
(the 3 guests who brought great
honor to Running Man this year.)
(Cha Chung Hwa, Ha Do Kwon)
(Hur Young Ji)
(They even have special performances
to celebrate the exciting party.)
(With songs that
old people would love,)
(the festive mood
of the party is heightening.)
(But they have to cook...)
(the party food themselves.)
(But they only have
limited amounts of ingredients.)
(A war begins
with some signs of overheating.)
(A life-and-death struggle
to get more ingredients!)
(What's happening
to the peaceful year-end party?)
(2021 Clever Year-end Party)