Shall we?
I wish I were heading home instead.
(It's somewhere in Yongsan
on a spring day.)
- Hello.
- Why is this so short?
- It's good to see you again.
- What did you say?
- Good morning.
- Did you hear what Hyo Im said?
- What?
- "Why is this so short?"
Hey, what did you say?
- As soon as you saw him...
- You look cool.
Let us do things like that.
I'm sure he heard her,
but he pretended he didn't hear it.
- Come here.
- Why would you meddle in?
Let her say what she wants to say.
Hyo Im, you should also
say things like...
"Why is he so old?"
- "His mouth sticks out."
- "He's too tall."
"His gums are sticking out."
- "He has a protruding mouth."
- "He's too short."
- Say that yourself.
- Hello.
Jong Kook is not wearing
leggings today!
He took them off.
Summer is finally coming.
- Summer is here.
- Hello.
- Yesterday, we went...
- You're a sportsman.
We met at a wedding ceremony.
I hosted the wedding,
- And he sang?
- and he sang there.
- Yes, we did.
- You're like a duo.
You should wear a jacket
to a wedding ceremony.
I went to the wedding
wearing a turtleneck sweater.
It was like...
I asked Jong Kook to sing,
and he came out like this.
(Swaggering)
Like Terminator.
(He showed up
with his bulging muscles.)
He wasn't even wearing a jacket.
He was just wearing
a black turtleneck sweater.
"I hope you will be happy."
And he left like this.
- My gosh. So I was...
- People in the hall...
- I was embarrassed. So I told him.
- It's hilarious.
"You should wear a jacket
next time you attend a wedding."
(All right.)
I knew what you meant.
You agreed.
He admitted his mistake quickly.
- Jong Kook is getting tougher.
- My gosh.
- Oh dear.
- Suk Jin.
I heard you called Bo Pil
after the shoot last week.
Did I? I actually call him often.
- Why?
- We solved quizzes the other day.
The episode of Yoo Grand Award
and Kim Grand Award.
What about it?
(They solved various quizzes
in episode 547.)
What about it?
- This is a true story.
- What happened?
- He called Bo Pil.
- And?
Suk Jin thought he answered
most of the quizzes,
so he asked Bo Pil
to make him look smart.
He said it would be funny that way.
I'm serious.
He's right. That's true.
- It's true.
- You...
You just stole some of our answers.
- That's what I thought.
- I know. He took our answers.
- He thinks he answered them all.
- And he wouldn't even let us talk.
We gave our ideas.
He stopped us every time
we tried to answer the quiz.
Stop showing off.
(So it finally happened.)
(Suk Jin completed the equation
moving only one match.)
If we stack two coins...
(They played the soundtrack of
"Sherlock" at Suk Jin's request.)
(This is the onscreen subtitle
in episode 547.)
(And the director wrote onscreen
subtitles that weren't true.)
(The man who went to Ajou University
did well.)
(When you get this kind
of question correct, you look sexy.)
(Suk Jin won
the Empty Heads' envy.)
What Kwang Soo just said is true.
"Make me look like a smart guy."
- "Make me a star."
- "And viewers will find it funny."
I'm sorry,
but that's not what you do here.
- What do I do then?
- You have no ability to do so.
- I just tried...
- There you go again.
The three of them are coming at him.
Let's attack him.
Suk Jin doesn't know what to do
when the three of them attack him.
What? Did Kwang Soo win an award?
Korea Gold Awards Festival?
- He won an award?
- Did you film something?
- What did you film?
- Are you a cameraman?
- No, that's not it.
- What did you film?
It's not like that. I didn't win
an award as a cameraman.
- Do you work as a cameraman?
- They gave me the award.
What's wrong with the photo?
He did that again.
- They asked me to dance.
- He did it...
to ask for an award.
The headline was...
"Dance moves that make
Yoo Jae Suk call him."
That's the headline.
How could you be my son-in-law?
No. That's not what it said.
- How dare you...
- That's not what it said.
(Na Eun's dad becomes sensitive
when it comes to his daughter.)
- It was a different word.
- Are you out of your mind?
- Are you crazy?
- That's not what it says.
They were totally different words.
He meant dance moves.
- That's horrible, you punk.
- It's not like that.
That's not what I meant.
- I just imagined it.
- Jae Suk is really mad.
- I'm going to...
- No wonder he's upset.
Call him Father.
King Kong by Starship is
manipulating the media.
What does King Kong by Starship
have to do with this?
He's your father-in-law.
(Na Eun's dad would come
to Kwang Soo's agency.)
Today's race is about
what all office workers would want.
It's about how quickly
you can get off work.
It's called the Sweet
and Scary Way Home Race.
- What?
- I guess we go home early.
Based on your residential areas,
we divided you into two teams,
Team Mapo and Team Gangnam.
(Team Mapo, Team Gangnam)
- Mapo!
- Gangnam!
(Se Chan and So Min are Team Mapo.)
(Kwang Soo who lives in Seongdong-gu
is Team Gangnam.)
- Gangnam.
- And we have two guests...
who will fight the war
for your way home.
I know one of them.
- Me too.
- I ran into him earlier.
One of them kept chatting away
in the parking lot.
The thing is...
He brought six people.
- Really?
- He had six staff members, right?
And I said...
hello to him, but he pretended
he didn't see me.
- He ignored you?
- He said he shouldn't talk to me.
(Who's the guest coming under fire
from the members already?)
(What? They're coming.)
- That's Choa.
- Hey, Choa.
Choa is here.
- Hello.
- It's been a long time, Choa.
- It's been so long.
- It's Choa.
Choa.
- Hello.
It's so good to see you.
Choa, it's been a really long time.
- Have you been doing well?
- Yes. I've been fine.
Come here.
- It's so good to see you.
- Choa.
It's been a while.
- And there's a candle dripping.
- Hello.
He's a candle dripping.
Who said a candle dripping?
Choa and a candle dripping.
Who said "candle dripping?"
- Isn't he Gi Yeong?
- He's a candle dripping.
- Hello.
- There's a candle dripping.
- Isn't he Gi Yeong?
- Hello.
Where should I stand?
First...
He will get to you. Just stay quiet.
- We have a guest here.
- Come here.
- Stand here?
- Yes.
So we have...
My gosh. This is great.
We have Cho Sae Ho
and Choa here today.
Hello.
- Hello.
- Choa and a candle dripping.
- What?
- A candle dripping.
- Choa and a candle dripping.
- Candle?
Choa, you're back...
after 7 or 8 years.
- Has it been nine years?
- It's been a long time.
- 6 years?
- 6 years.
- It's been almost seven years.
- Right.
- It's been six years?
- That's great, Choa.
You look great.
I'm so glad that I'm back.
- It's so good to see you.
- You too.
- I've been seeing you though.
- You have?
I've seen you on TV
lying down at home.
So this feels so familiar.
That's good.
I've mostly stayed alone at home.
- And I run my YouTube channel.
- Right.
But I don't get to see
many people there.
So I came here to have fun today.
And we have...
veter-ran entertainers here.
(Veter-ran?)
- Veter-ran?
- She hasn't been on TV for long.
She has a lot to say.
- You know what I mean, right?
- Sure.
I totally understand her.
Jae Suk, who will you spit out?
She has a lot of things
she wants to say.
The viewers will understand her too.
You get to talk after a long time.
I didn't get to talk like this
for a long time.
Choa gets to talk to many people
after a long time,
- so she has a lot to say.
- We understand.
So I think I will have
a lot of fun today.
Okay. That was Choa.
- Choa.
(Thinking)
And we also have Sae Ho here.
- He's just...
- Isn't he a candle dripping?
I was hoping you could
welcome me just a little.
People like me
who enjoy working out think...
- Sae Ho defeated Jung Jun Ha.
- I did?
- In a bad way.
- A bad way?
- Seriously?
- In a bad way?
- That's not true.
- He defeated Jung Jun Ha.
Jo Young Gu, Jung Jun Ha,
and Cho Sae Ho.
Don't say that.
He won a complete victory.
A doctor of Korean medicine
recently took his pulse...
and said he has the pulse of a baby.
- He could barely feel the pulse.
- It was weak.
He said I had a toddling pulse.
You should exercise for your health.
- Your real name is Cho Sae Ho.
- Nice to meet you.
- Do you have a stage name?
- It's my real name.
Is your stage name
Cho Sae Ho as well?
I have many different alter egos.
What alter egos?
We don't know any of them.
I used to use the name Yangbaechu.
That's right. He was Yangbaechu.
It's not your alter ego.
It was just a failure.
Was Yangbaechu your alter ego?
I used to work under
the stage name, Yangbaechu.
Isn't Yangbaechu your real name?
- Isn't it your real name?
- Is that your real name?
And your Japanese name is Cabagin.
- Who?
- Your Japanese name is Cabagin.
Stop it.
Se Chan.
- That's enough.
- Okay.
- He's feeling very nervous now.
- All right.
Who would...
- Who would name his son Yangbaechu?
- I know.
- There might be a misunderstanding.
- That's enough.
They call me Coleslaw in the States.
(He still wants
to make people laugh.)
- Sure.
- I understand.
I used to be a big fan of Sae Ho.
You used to be? What about now?
There he goes again.
But now...
Jong Kook says that again.
- He says you used to look cute.
- I really liked him.
I used to be a big fan.
He liked you
when you were Yangbaechu.
I also liked Yangbaechu.
A lot of people want me
to put the weight back on.
But I'm maintaining my weight well.
It will be more fun
if you put the weight back on.
(Touching)
- I see.
- What are you doing, So Min?
His head looks like a chestnut.
- A chestnut.
- Really?
A freshly shelled chestnut.
- I...
- A freshly shelled chestnut?
A freshly shelled chestnut?
- We shell chestnuts like this.
- I know what it is.
- I know. This is what we do.
- We do this with our feet.
Sae Ho's nickname is
a shelled chestnut.
Jae Suk called me yesterday...
and asked, "Are you going
to be on Running Man tomorrow?"
So I said yes. And he said,
"Don't come."
How can I not come?
I have no choice.
So I was like, "I don't think
I have a choice."
And he said, "Just don't come.
I'll take care of it."
How can I not come?
"Then you should come..."
"and stay still
like a stuffed doll."
What is he talking about?
Why would he tell me not to come?
I just told him to stay quiet.
He used to be funny
when he said things like that.
What?
A Grand Award winner is
not supposed to say that.
Kim Grand Award.
That's it. Just let it go.
You have to overcome this.
- When he said the same thing...
- Okay.
I'll come back again
after putting on some weight.
- When he said the same thing,
- Seriously...
- it was hilarious.
- Sae Ho...
This is what Sae Ho
does the most in Running Man.
- It sounds boring now.
- I'm serious.
I thought of a lot of things
that might happen today.
But this isn't what I expected.
Look at that.
He used to look cute
when he did things like this.
Stop that.
- He looks cute.
- Oh no.
He is cute.
- I'm sorry.
- All right.
So...
Sae Ho will support Team Mapo.
Okay. I'm Team Mapo.
Team Mapo.
Choa doesn't live in Gangnam,
but she's going
to Gangnam after this show.
So she's Team Gangnam.
Do you see the opening venue
on the map?
If Team Mapo wins a mission,
they will move one space
toward Mapo.
Good.
It will be fun.
So we have to win the missions
to go this way.
Gosh, this is...
If we finish the race at Dosan Park,
I can get home quickly.
- It's near my house.
- It will be great.
Like I said you can
move one space...
toward Mapo or Gangnam.
If both teams win
the missions in turn,
they might have to go
to the places they already visited.
The team who wins a mission...
can put a sticker of their team
on the roulette.
(The winning team can put
their sticker on the roulette.)
During the mission,
when the clock strikes five
and people start to get off work,
you will stop the mission.
You will spin the roulette
and decide the ending venue.
Then you will shoot
the ending there...
and finish today's episode.
(They will shoot the ending for
about 5 minutes and get off work.)
So even if you were losing,
if you spin the roulette well,
- you can go to your neighborhood.
- Okay.
- The last one is important.
- If we spin it well,
- we can still win.
- That's right.
But you will be more likely to win
the race if you win the missions.
It will be over in the rush hour.
It's more upsetting
that the ending will be short.
It will take more than an hour
to get here from Gangnam.
We have to go all the way there
to shoot the short ending.
To shoot a short scene.
It will be really annoying.
- It's annoying.
- So it's like a penalty.
You will have the first mission...
at restaurants with dishes
that will stimulate your appetites.
- We are going to eat.
- That's great.
- Let's eat.
- This is exciting.
How nice.
(We rented the places and filmed
according to safety regulations.)
So this is...
- This is the place.
- Right.
This is my favorite
tteokbokki place.
- What's that? Tteokbokki?
- Oh, that one.
You can start with number two.
(Which restaurants will they be
visiting today?)
- It must be delicious.
- It's arugula.
This place is crazy.
Pimpinella pasta.
- That sounds great.
- Wonton soup.
- Rice with seafood.
- Right.
This restaurant has...
- great seasoned dumplings.
- Really?
Strawberry croffle.
That must be delicious.
I want to go there.
- Where do you want to go, So Min?
- I want rice with seafood.
Rice with seafood.
What about you, Ji Hyo?
Actually, I like tteokbokki.
- Ji Hyo, that's great.
- Gosh, Ji Hyo.
We should go to Mapo.
You can eat tteokbokki in Mapo.
That's just what I like.
- This isn't about your taste.
- Ji Hyo.
Help us go to the tteokbokki place.
- Okay.
- All right.
You can count on me.
This is what I like about Ji Hyo.
Ji Hyo has no strategies.
She just says what she wants to eat.
- She just goes there.
- She follows her instincts.
But she doesn't get a penalty.
- Right. She always avoids it.
- Then you will have...
the first mission
to decide the first destination.
- Okay. Let's do this.
- We have to win this.
- Good.
- We have to win.
- Mapo!
- Gangnam!
- Mapo.
- You should say Mapo.
- Why do you say Gangnam?
Go over there.
Why do you say Gangnam?
She says Gangnam.
This is the first mission...
for the first destination
on your way home.
It's called Furious Race.
I guess we will run.
You will pick a marble you want.
And on the track you see over there,
you will place the marble
at the starting line.
With the signal, we will remove
the board blocking the marbles.
And we will go to the restaurant
in the winning team's district.
(They will go to the restaurant
in the winning team's district.)
Then go there and pick your color.
- I pick red.
- We don't know it yet.
This is me.
I'm orange.
- Place it here.
- All right.
How should I put this?
Orange!
Red, red, red
- Orange, orange, orange
- Let's go.
- Let's do this!
- Let's do this.
- My marble will win
Mapo!
Mapo, mapo, mapo
Move over.
Why do you push me away?
I need to be on TV.
- Okay.
- Let's go!
Let's go!
- All right.
- Let's do this.
- This is...
- The first game is important.
- Ready.
- 1, 2, 3.
- Go.
- They're moving.
- Orange!
- Red!
They're moving.
Red!
There it is.
Why isn't it moving?
- Whose marble is that?
- Red.
Good, Ji Hyo.
- It's going well.
- It's not over yet.
- This is great, Ji Hyo.
- Go!
- It's almost there.
- Stop.
- Go!
- Ji Hyo.
Good. Hurry.
- Let's go!
- Hurry!
(The marbles are nearing
the end of the course.)
Go!
There it is.
- It's almost there.
- No.
Ji Hyo's isn't moving.
What?
(Who is going to win?)
- Let's go.
- Hurry!
- Okay! Come on!
- Go!
(Kim Jong Kook wins!)
(Jong Kook, Haha, Ji Hyo, Se Chan)
Let's go!
- Come on!
- Go!
(He beat the top 3 from Team Mapo
and came in 1st!)
(1st, Jong Kook, 2nd, Haha,
3rd, Ji Hyo, 4th, Sae Ho)
(From 5th, Se Chan, Suk Jin,
So Min, Jae Suk, Choa, Kwang Soo)
(Screaming with joy)
- We won!
- My gosh.
We won!
- I can't believe he won.
- This is ridiculous.
- Jong Kook, good job!
- My gosh. How did it happen?
- No way.
- How did this happen?
It hit the wall.
It makes no sense.
(Disappointed)
How did it happen?
I can't believe it happened
at the last moment.
How did you do that?
I was in fourth place
up to this point.
- But I came in first at the end.
- How did that happen?
- Exactly.
- It's hard to believe.
- How did it happen?
- Unbelievable.
- That was so unexpected.
- It's hard to believe.
That marble is just like Jong Kook.
- It pushed its way at the end.
- Exactly.
It pushed its way.
- The light blue one, right?
- I didn't even expect it to win.
Wasn't the pink one
in the first place?
- She and we were in the top three.
- Really?
- This is so hard to believe.
- Indeed.
- That was so cool.
- Is it over now?
- Yes.
- Of course.
Then we'll move
to the tteokbokki place at Gangnam.
- Okay!
- Choa, you seem so excited.
- Choa, come on in.
- Okay.
- Where... Should I sit at the back?
- Come and sit down.
Choa, what did you do
during your break?
- Pardon me?
- What did you do during your break?
I just watched TV lying down.
- It sounds very comfortable.
- All I did was sleep.
- It's so relaxing, right?
- Indeed. Hello.
Hey, you and your sister look
so much alike.
- Did you watch the show?
- I was so surprised.
- Thank you.
- Her sister?
- They look so much alike.
- Hey.
You look just like your mother too.
The same goes for you.
When I went to his wedding,
I thought he was wearing
a women's hanbok.
(He found the groom
dressed as a woman.)
- You look just like your mother.
- I was...
- I was so surprised.
- I was surprised too.
- You look just like your mother.
They really are entertainers.
- I look just like my mom, right?
- Yes, totally.
- Right.
- I was so surprised.
- Wait. Where's Sae Ho?
- I'm here.
- I'm right here.
- We don't have many guests today.
Jae Suk, why do you look
so disappointed?
I thought it would be funny
if he had been left out.
(He put on a long face
unintentionally.)
There are the tall and short men
that I like sitting in the front.
- They are my favorites.
- Hens are in the chicken coop
(Kwang Soo, the tall man,
Sae Ho, the short man)
They're like
Seo Su Nam and Ha Cheong Il.
- They can be a perfect duo.
- You know I like them, right?
That's great.
- A tall and short men duo.
- Exactly.
- He's just amazing.
- Indeed.
This is how Sae Ho looks like
since he lost weight.
Imagine Kwang Soo is
only 178cm tall.
- Is that how he looks?
- I see.
- That's how he looks.
- Sae Ho.
- They'll tease you all day long.
- I know.
- So you should...
- But it's okay.
That was the only thing
he said to Sae Ho.
I should overcome it as well.
- Don't be ridiculous, you punk.
- It's just a phase.
- I know.
- Suk Jin, why would you swear?
- It's not like that. The fact...
- What's wrong with you?
The fact that you said
you should overcome it...
means that you haven't been able to
overcome it yet.
So don't even say such a thing.
He hasn't overcome it
in the past 11 years.
- Ouch!
- I'm sorry.
He hasn't overcome it
in the past 11 years.
(He pretends he got hurt.)
- Are you okay?
- You must overcome it.
- What was that?
- You must overcome that.
- It wasn't intentional.
- Overcome it!
That was good.
- Like this?
- Yes.
- You saw that, right?
- I get it.
- You have to smile.
- I see.
You know, Suk Jin calls me
at least 3 times in 1 year.
- Really?
- Yes.
He calls me 3 times in 1 year.
As soon as I picked up,
I said, "Jiseokjin World."
He asked, "How did you know?"
(He called Sae Ho to ask him
to be in videos on his channel.)
- "Can you join our shoot?"
- Of course.
- He doesn't call without a reason.
- Exactly.
- The same goes for Haha.
- Yes.
- Why?
- You have such skinny ankles.
This is one of the criteria
for a handsome man.
- They look so skinny.
- Are you serious?
- Yes. A man with slim ankles...
- You need a handsome face.
What does it have to do
with being handsome?
A man with slim ankles is considered
attractive.
- He's arguing with so many of us.
- Here goes...
"Ji Suk Jin Show" began again.
- The thought of overcoming...
- It's "Punching Bag Show."
Or "Punching Bag Ji Show."
- It's him against everyone else.
- That means you haven't succeeded.
About seven people.
- Don't even think of overcoming it.
- Isn't he amazing, Choa?
- He's amazing, right?
- Yes.
(Choa is surprised to see
everyone attacking him.)
Choa seems more cheerful
than before.
- Really?
- He looks more cheerful now.
- She looks more cheerful now.
- Indeed.
How do you feel
about being a solo artist?
- One of the good things is...
- Yes?
- that I can save time...
- You can save time?
- at a beauty parlor.
- I see.
You had to wait
until your team members were done.
- Yes. We're divided into two teams.
- That's right.
I've never been to a beauty parlor.
- Really?
- Yes.
- You're not wearing makeup now?
- Of course not.
- You have such smooth skin.
- I style my own hair too.
- Really?
- I never have it done by an expert.
He doesn't work
with a stylist either.
- Really?
- I just wear my own clothes.
Based on his behaviors like that,
he shouldn't be called
a TV celebrity.
- He's more like...
- An athlete.
- Yes. He's more like a sportsman.
- A sportsman.
- We should call him a sportsman.
- Like a man in the neighborhood.
- Exactly.
Sae Ho, you go
to a famous beauty parlor, right?
- Of course.
- Me?
Don't you go to a barbershop?
Did you say "babo"
as in "fool" in Korean?
- Isn't it called a barbershop?
- I thought he said, "fool shop."
- It's not "babo."
- Kwang Soo goes to a fool sho."
- Oh, right.
- He goes to a fool shop.
- It's "barber," not "babo."
- I go to this hair salon...
that a friend of mine runs.
I've been a regular there...
- for almost 10 years.
- You can get the same haircut...
at any barbershop
near the boot camp in Nonsan.
- You have a point.
- Yes.
What do you think
about what he just said?
I really don't like it.
- To the point...
- You must overcome it.
To the point that my nose ran.
He took me by surprise.
Suk Jin is not very good
at improvising jokes.
- He's better at defending.
- That's true.
- That's not true.
- He's not good at attacking.
Anyway, listen.
- Stop buying designer goods.
- Here he goes again.
You should buy your own house first.
What is this?
- What is your intention?
- What do you mean?
- Do you mean well?
- That was a piece of advice.
- An honest piece of advice.
- Why would you...
Why would you advise him
like a bossy man?
- I just...
- Jong Kook caught him off guard.
- Gosh, that punk. Listen.
- It has begun now.
It's not like that.
- That was so...
- I mean, why...
- That was suffocating.
- Why would you advise him?
It was beyond pressure.
It was suffocating.
That's not true.
When I'm ready to hit him hard,
I'll call you.
It seems to me
that Suk Jin is in a good mood...
whenever I come on this show.
- Sae Ho.
- He wants to show off.
He takes it all out on me.
It's because they get distracted
by you a little.
- That's true.
- They target you as well.
- We're here!
Suk Jin, smile!
Are we really getting off like this?
- Let's go, everybody.
- Give Suk Jin a drink!
Shall we go and eat
some delicious tteokbokki?
(Let's go and eat tteokbokki
with the best defender!)
How nice. I can tell
how old this place is.
(Banpo A Tteokbokki
with a 30-year history)
All of those bring back
old memories.
Indeed.
(One-pot tteokbokki
with an addictive flavor)
- This is how it looks. It's nice.
- I remember this.
- Just like those old places.
- Those good old days
(And seasoned dumplings
with their own special sauce)
I haven't been here
in such a long time.
We came to Banpo A Tteokbokki,
1 of the top 10 tteokbokki places...
in Seoul.
It's been a while.
I love this place.
- It looks really nice.
- I came here after a long time.
Of course, you didn't think
that all of you would get to eat.
- What?
- I knew it.
Only three members
of the winning team will get to eat.
- From the winning team?
- Only three members?
Even from the winning team?
- That's too harsh.
- The restaurant owner will...
- choose the three people to eat.
- Really?
Yes. The restaurant owner will
choose 3 out of the 5 members.
- Really?
- We need to make a good impression.
- We need a likable face.
- On our team...
- I'm confident.
- I bet Suk Jin won't be picked.
You're wrong. I'm sure
that I'll get to eat.
He's around the owner's age.
- Where is the owner?
- The owner might like him.
The owner might have gone
to the same school as him.
The winning team will not only eat
the food,
but also, you all will move
toward the winning team's area,
and you'll get another slot...
- in the roulette.
- We should win the game.
The losing team will be tempted
to taste the food.
We'll give food
to every member of the losing team.
If anyone eats it,
the winning team will get two slots.
- If anyone can't hold back?
- That's right.
- So Min will definitely eat.
- Of course, we will...
No, I won't eat it.
I'm not an animal. I can hold back.
Also, if any of the two members
of the winning team who can't eat...
fail to hold back and eat,
the team will lose one slot.
Let's begin the first mission.
It requires good teamwork.
It's Quiz Hour.
Quiz Hour.
Okay, okay, okay!
- Great. Okay!
- But...
- He seems confident.
- Yes!
- You...
- It's disadvantageous for us.
- Hey, this is...
- The smartest person here is...
- This is unfair.
- You put all of us on this team.
- We're done for.
- Why is it a quiz?
I bet it was intentional.
They're all Empty Heads.
Suk Jin will call the director
and ask him to make him look smart.
- He drives me crazy.
- Seriously...
- I think I'll do that too.
- How could you ask him to do that?
You're not allowed to call him
anymore.
That's not why I called him.
I just made a suggestion
while we were having a chat.
- Bo Pil got stressed out a lot.
- Bo Pil,
please make me look smart again.
It's rare to see anyone like him.
(This professional entertainer wants
to use the power of editing.)
The first round is about units.
- Units?
- Oh, units?
So it's a math quiz.
The two teams will take turns.
Like inches, right?
Each member has to read
the unit symbol...
written on the sketchbook correctly.
- You have only three seconds.
- Oh, no. I'm worried.
- I don't know many unit symbols.
- Me neither.
- We just have to read it?
- I'm not good at math.
- What should we read?
- A unit symbol.
Is it written in Korean?
- For example, if it's 11km...
- Kilometer?
- And centimeter for cm?
- Correct.
Let's let Ji Hyo go first.
- Those are all I know.
- Why won't you let me finish?
If you say an incorrect answer,
the other team will have a chance.
So you should decide
the order wisely.
- Really?
- Yes.
The first one will be
the easiest question.
- Really?
- And it gets more difficult.
- You should go last.
- Right.
You and Suk Jin go to the back.
- I'll be the second.
- Okay. This will be better.
- In this direction, right?
- Yes. Let's do that.
- Sae Ho...
- Right.
- Ji Hyo or Se Chan should be there.
- Wait.
- Am I in the same spot as him?
- He's the first one to go too.
(Both of them will answer
the easiest question.)
- Am I in the same spot as him?
- He's the first one to go too.
Gosh. I don't like this.
- Gosh.
- Why?
Se Chan is the first one to go too.
We're sitting in the order
of the levels of intelligence.
- And Sae Ho is at that end?
- He's the brain of our team.
He's the brain of our team.
(Sae Ho is treated as the brain
on Team Mapo.)
- It won't be so difficult.
- So Min is the fourth?
(She'll get a difficult question.)
- So Min is the fourth.
- She graduated from college.
I graduated from college.
- That's true.
- Let's do this.
- They have their own reasons.
I graduated from college too.
I majored in comedic acting.
That's so funny.
Choa can't seem to laugh loudly.
- She's embarrassed.
- She's good with numbers.
- She invests in stocks.
- I just...
- That's right.
- We don't know yet.
- Exactly.
You should answer in three seconds
after I show you the question.
Answer right away. Or you're out.
Of course. Right away.
- We can do it!
- I'll go first.
- You can do it!
- The first one will be easy.
Okay. Ready. Go. 1, 2, 3.
- Kilometer.
- Okay. Good job.
Se Chan, what has gotten into you?
- I know that much.
- Of course.
Ready, go. 1, 2, 3.
- Inch, inch.
- Inch.
- "Inch, inch."
- Don't say the answer.
("Inch?")
- My gosh. You don't even know this?
- Don't say the answer.
Let's switch seats.
- I was just a little late.
- Let's switch our seats.
- I knew the answer.
- I'm sure she knows kilometer.
- I was just late. That's all.
- You knew the answer, right?
Does that mean inch?
- You knew it, right?
- Of course, she knows that much.
Here's your question. Ready, go.
- 1, 2, 3.
- Milligram.
- Good.
- Good job.
We all know that.
- He knows it.
- Impressive.
I'm surprised that he knows it.
- I thought he'd say "magnesium."
- Is it my turn?
That's what I thought.
1, 2, 3.
(Frozen)
- You don't know that?
- Do you know this?
- What's this?
- Why don't you know this?
(It's ton.)
- It's ton.
- Ton?
- Ton.
None of you knew?
- What does that mean?
- Okay. Good.
- Ton.
- Ton. You ignorant punk.
- Oh, right. It's ton.
- I can't believe you.
I forgot.
Stop lying. You didn't know.
Right. Ton and on...
I mean, ton and off. Ton.
- Choa...
- I'm so sorry.
- It's okay.
- Don't worry.
- Choa, it's okay.
- I'll go first.
Hey, why did you switch
seats with her?
We have to win.
- Hey!
- We have no choice.
- Why did you do that?
- Ji Hyo.
- Ji Hyo came here too.
I just missed the timing.
I knew the answer. That's all.
- Okay.
- No. I just missed the timing.
- Choa, don't be nervous.
- Okay.
If you get a question wrong,
you move to the next seat.
- Ji Hyo goes first.
- Yes.
- Go, Ji Hyo!
- I'm nervous.
- Ready, go. 1, 2, 3.
- You can do this.
(Milliliter!)
1, 2, 3.
- Milliliter!
- That's milliliter!
- My gosh. Really?
- Everyone knows that!
You really don't know this?
I bet she thought
it stood for medium and large.
- Hey.
- You see it on a milk carton.
It's because I've never seen
the letter L written like that.
Ji Hyo, be more confident.
I just haven't seen
the letter L written like that.
(She has never seen an L like that.)
- Let's go. The first one is easy.
- Gosh. I'm so nervous.
- This is fun.
- I'm so surprised.
Ready, go. 1, 2, 3.
- Millimeter.
- Okay!
- Good job.
- I thought it was Mighty Mouse.
Kwang Soo, you can do this.
I'll succeed.
I'll make sure to get it right.
I'm relieved that she didn't say
M and M chocolates.
Ready, go. 1, 2, 3.
Deci-gla-liter.
(Deci-gla-liter)
(He created a new unit.)
- "Deci-gla-liter?"
- Hey.
- That's so funny.
- What was that?
What's a "deciliter?"
- Did you say "deciliter?"
- What does that mean?
- It's deciliter.
- He got it right.
- Why didn't you say it clearly?
Is it really deciliter?
Didn't he get it right?
He said "deciliter."
No, he said "deci-gla-liter."
- What was that?
- Hey, you imitated him well.
You heard it clearly?
- Okay.
- You did well.
- That was good.
- Kwang Soo seems...
- to know quite a bit.
- Indeed.
Let's start with Ji Hyo.
- You can do this.
- Ready, go.
1, 2, 3.
- Square meter.
- It's cubic meter.
- Right. Cubic meter.
- I didn't expect to see that one.
- It's cubic meter.
- You can call it triple meter too.
No, it's cubic meter.
- Can't triple meter be accepted?
- No.
Hey, Sae Ho, you go first.
You sit here.
Ji Hyo, a number on top
of a symbol is an exponent.
Hey!
(Empty Head's philosophy on units)
The number on top is an exponent.
The letter at the end is liter.
And the first letter is
an abbreviation.
I'd better sit at the end
so I won't look ignorant.
- Let's switch our seats.
- Just sit down.
- Choa, it's your turn.
- Okay.
- Go, Choa!
- You have to do well this time.
Ready, go. 1, 2, 3.
- Featuring.
- Feet.
- Feet!
(Featuring!)
(Haha just said any word he knew.)
- That's feet.
- Listen.
Math is all about abbreviations.
The symbol of feet is ft.
Hey! Listen!
- I think this is the best.
- They're all abbreviations.
Those who were class presidents,
sit in the front.
- So Min, sit here.
- Okay. Go and sit there.
Those who participated
in a math contest, move forward.
Sit down.
Why are you trying to avoid it?
- You go first this time.
- Right. Give it a try.
- Haha will go first.
- No.
- No, no.
- Just this once.
- You go first. You do it.
- Come here.
- Haha, you go first this time.
- No.
Let go of me. Let us decide.
You're not on our team.
- Let go. Dream.
- Haha.
Ha Dream, turn off the TV.
Ha Dream, I said, turn it off.
Come on. Sit down.
- Come here.
- Just give it a try.
Let Haha go first.
Why can't you do this?
- Dream, listen.
- You can do it.
Go and do your homework
or write in your diary.
Haha will do well.
It's too early to write a diary.
Ready, go.
- You can do this.
- 1, 2, 3.
- YD? Yang Dong Geun.
- Yard!
- My gosh.
- It's yard!
- Even he knew it.
- Even I knew that one.
(Yard! It's yard!)
- Yard!
- My gosh.
- How did you not know that?
- I knew it. I'm not lying.
How did you not know that?
My gosh. He didn't know
the symbol of yard.
- I knew the answer.
- You know it, right?
- I know this one.
- It's yd.
- Yard.
He said he knew every question
that others were given.
- Yard.
- It's not confusing at all.
Yard.
- Dream shouldn't watch this.
- He should never watch this.
The questions will be more difficult
since we don't have many left.
- Okay. Good.
- Gosh. I'm worried.
- It was already difficult.
- We're at an advantage...
if the questions are more difficult.
Let's go.
- Ready, go.
- Go, Jae Suk!
- 1, 2, 3.
- What is this?
- Ounce!
- It's ounce.
(He has never seen it before.)
(The answer is ounce.)
(Ounce!)
- Hey, go to another seat.
- Ounce.
(They all got up
and pretended they knew the answer.)
- Ounce.
- It's oz.
- It's oz!
- It's ounce.
- It's oz.
- That's not the symbol of ounce.
- It's ounce.
- It's oz.
(Kwang Soo is
even pronouncing it incorrectly.)
- It's oz.
- That's not the symbol of ounce.
- It's ounce.
- Is it?
- Ji Ho, turn the TV off.
- It's oz.
Ji Ho, turn it off now.
Watch me. Watch carefully.
You should know how hard I work.
You should study hard, okay?
I thought it was Oz
from "The Wonderful Wizard of Oz."
I knew that we would get
that question.
- Was it the symbol of ounce?
- I was right about it.
- It's okay.
- Let's see how well Sae Ho does.
- It's boring, right?
- Let's see.
- Can I take it seriously?
- Of course.
You should get it right.
Wait. Did you say,
"It's boring, right?"
- That's not what I meant.
- How dare you look down on us?
- Hey, come here.
- Our show is really popular.
- You called our show "boring."
- It wasn't like that.
- Boring?
- How could you say such a thing?
- "Is it okay to be boring?"
- "It'd be boring..."
- "if I get it right."
- That's what you meant, right?
Yes. I was asking
if it'd be okay if I got it right.
- Okay. It can be upsetting.
- I'll start now.
- I'm sorry about that.
- Ready.
Set. Go. 1, 2, 3.
- Machi.
- What was that?
(He basically just read it.)
You can't just read it.
(He looked very confident.)
(But he said "machi" confidently.)
(Machi as in "anesthesia?")
- Gosh, seriously.
- Machi as in "anesthesia?"
- Mach.
- Oh, it's mach!
- Mach!
- Machi as in "anesthesia?"
- Exactly.
- Mach!
- Oh, it was mach.
- I didn't know that one.
- Mach!
- It's a unit of speed, you know.
- Gosh.
So "ch" is pronounced like a "k."
What's "machi?"
Hey, listen to me.
I learned all these in college
majoring in business administration.
- I learned all these.
- You did?
Yes. I knew all the answers.
- Suk Jin.
- I'm ready.
Let's do this. Let us all succeed.
- Let us all succeed.
- Okay.
- At least up to Jong Kook.
- We can do it.
Ready, go. 1, 2, 3.
- K bank!
- Bank.
(K bank!)
1, 2, 3.
(- K bank!
- Bank.)
- K bank.
- It's kilobyte.
(Jae Suk thought of K bank
when he saw the symbol.)
Right.
- Kilobyte.
- Oh, right.
- K bank.
- What is wrong with you?
K bank suddenly popped into my head.
It's kilobyte, you know.
- I knew he'd fail.
- I use that bank.
Gosh. This is driving me nuts.
I use K bank.
- That was so funny.
- Kilobyte.
- All right.
- Move.
"K" always stands for "kilo."
- Kilo?
- "M" stands for "milligram..."
- I mean, "milli."
- "M" stands for...
"M" stands for "milli?"
Like millibyte.
Millibyte?
It's So Min's turn.
Ready, go.
- 1, 2, 3.
- Gal.
- Gallon.
- It's the symbol of gallon.
- She doesn't know.
- I don't know that.
- She said, "gal."
- "Gal."
- That was funny.
Se Chan told me to read it as "gal."
He told me to say that.
- It was difficult.
- Let's move on.
- Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
- Gangnam!
If we could continue to your turn,
- we'll win.
- We can do it.
- I have to succeed.
- You can do it.
- Jae Suk.
- Just two more questions.
- We can win this.
- Then we'll win.
- No reason to be nervous.
- Ready, go.
- Go, go.
- 1, 2, 3.
- Terabyte.
- Oh, wow.
- You're so smart.
- Terabyte. Good job.
- It's going to get more difficult.
- Let's do this.
It's going to get more difficult.
I've seen everything I know.
- I learned all of them.
- Ready, go.
- 1, 2, 3.
- Helpagram.
- Gosh. I can't believe you.
- What's that?
Do you know what it is?
(What is that?)
Hectopascal.
- He's so smart.
- Hectopascal.
Gosh. You don't know hectopascal?
He didn't get it right?
- It's hectopascal.
- Suk Jin.
That's the most basic unit
used in mathematics.
Hey, this is the easiest question.
Hecto...
- Exactly.
- Hectopascal!
- Hectopascal.
- What is it?
Hectopascal is the unit of this.
- What?
- The unit of this.
The air... In mathematics...
You know, in the air...
- Continue.
- Kwang Soo, this is 1hPa, right?
- Yes, just this much.
- That's right.
(He defined 1hPa as he wanted
since no one knew.)
Gosh. What a shame.
- Let's get three questions right.
- I don't know any math symbols.
Each team has only one chance left.
- Yes. You did well.
- These questions...
I don't think you can get them right
even as teams.
- Really?
- Let's give it a try.
- Let us answer as a team.
- Let's make it a team game.
- Let's do that.
- Anyone can answer.
- Okay.
- Gangnam!
- Mapo!
The team that gets
this question right will win.
- Can we all answer?
- Yes
- The last one.
- It's a team game.
(The team that gets it right first
will get the final score!)
- The last one.
- It's a team game, So Min.
Ready, go.
- That's...
- Omega.
(- Omega!
- Isn't that Leo?)
- Let me answer!
- Isn't that Leo?
- One...
- Let me answer!
- Let me answer.
- Go ahead.
Sigma.
- That must be...
- Anyone else?
- Magma.
- Let me answer.
- What?
- What did she say?
- Anyone else?
- Magma.
- Ohm?
- Let me answer.
(Choa got the correct answer.)
- What?
- What did she say?
- Ohm.
- She got it right.
- I'm so excited.
- What's an ohm?
- Is there a unit called ohm?
- Yes, in science.
My goodness. I got it right.
- The unit of electrical resistance.
- I've heard of it somewhere.
- Really?
- Awesome.
- How do you know that?
- I've heard of it somewhere.
- Choa did a great job.
- Gangnam!
I thought it was a pimple.
(They look like
they've never heard of an ohm.)
- Ohm?
- What is an ohm?
(They look like
they've never heard of an ohm.)
- Ohm?
- I got it right.
The unit of electrical resistance.
- We won an overwhelming victory.
- Let's move on to the second round.
- Did we lose again?
- Again?
We lost the first round?
- It'll be the Initial Game.
- I'm good at this.
Look at the initials...
and guess the name
of the variety show.
- Nice.
- I know a lot of them.
- Don't worry about me.
- Sure.
- Two from each team will compete.
- Really?
- You two.
- You two can compete.
All right.
- Let's go.
- We've got this.
- Then Choa...
- Go ahead.
- She watched TV a lot.
- That's right.
- Let's do this.
- Jong Kook's a good choice.
- All right.
- Go ahead.
Only the four can answer.
- The rest must stay silent.
- Okay.
Ready, get set,
go.
(SMTM)
Let me answer.
- I don't know.
- Sada...
- What is this?
- What can it be?
- Is it a variety show?
- Yes, it is.
I know what it is.
- I know.
- It's a popular show.
- What...
- Let me answer.
"Popular Restaurant."
There's a word that starts with T.
It ends with "meeting."
- No, that's not it.
- No clues are allowed.
- That's not it.
- Don't help them.
Why can't I?
- That's not allowed.
- Why not?
- What's that?
- Does she know?
- She's giving you a clue.
- Gosh.
Both teams could see,
so I'll allow it.
- Why don't they know this?
- What is it?
Let me answer!
- Let me answer!
"Show Me the Money."
Boom, boom.
(Se Chan receives the necklace that
advances him to the next round.)
- What was this though?
- That was a tricky one.
- The necklace.
- Oh, the necklace.
It was a hard one.
- So Min should compete.
- Go ahead.
We'll swap players.
- Go, So Min.
- Ready, set, go.
Ready, set, go.
(SH)
- Let me answer.
- Sure.
- "The Lee Kyung Sil Show."
- Wrong.
- "The Lee Gyeong Gyu Show." No.
- I know what it is.
It's the only thing
that comes to mind.
- No...
- No?
Suk Jin says the weirdest things...
and then calls the staff
to have it edited out.
It doesn't fit at all.
What is it then?
- Could it be that?
- It isn't.
So that's what it is.
(He talks brazenly
so that the film is easily edited.)
That's what happens
when you're smart.
I think I know what it is.
- What is it?
- It's something like...
"Baby's World."
- "Baby's World?"
- I mean...
- I mean it.
- Sae Ho!
- There was a show by that name.
- As if.
- "Baby's World?"
- How about a clue?
- Sounds good.
It aired on KBS
and one of you was on it.
- Wouldn't it be Jae Suk?
- Who here...
- was on KBS?
- It's either Jae Suk or me.
Why?
- You can't answer.
- You can't.
(Kwang Soo figured it out,
but he can't say it out loud.)
Is this it?
What is it?
(You were on this show!)
Which show is it?
Is it one that you were on?
- No!
- I know!
Are you the one
associated with the show?
Let me answer. It's "Six Heroines."
Okay!
(Team Gangnam answers correctly.)
- Nicely done!
- "Six Heroines."
Wow, "Six Heroines."
So that was the answer.
Let's take the lead from them.
(Both teams scored once
in the second round.)
Okay.
I have a feeling
this will quickly be answered.
- Let's do this.
- Here you go.
"Infinite Challenge!"
Nicely done.
You didn't know
it was "Infinite Challenge?"
It's been a while
since that was chanted.
- It's too much of an advantage...
- It's been a while.
for those who were on the show.
They'd know immediately.
- I was on the show too.
- It was their main show.
Did you hear Sae Ho just now?
He said he was on the show
in its last moments.
Of course.
(He chokes up for some reason.)
- In the last few months...
- We celebrated your 100th day.
(Sae Ho celebrated
his 100th day on the show.)
We're sorry.
He was on the show briefly
before it ended.
We're sorry.
- I was on it for 100 days.
- That's right.
- And it ended a month later.
- 100 days?
- Sae Ho...
- I now feel bad for him.
I choked up for some reason.
- Okay, let's keep going.
- Get ready.
(EENO)
- Yigatan...
- What's this?
Yigatan?
- Yigatan...
- Yigatan?
I just threw it out there.
(The smartest one
of the Empty Head Club knows.)
Give them a hint.
- In the direction of our team.
- Give them a hint.
(He gives them a clue.)
I don't think that's it.
I know! Let me answer.
It's "Emergency Escape Number 1."
(Jong Kook gets it right.)
You were on that show.
- I was the host.
- I was right.
I hosted the show!
(In 2012, 9 years ago,)
(Jong Kook served
as Korea's keeper of safety.)
We're lucky to have had
Jong Kook on our team.
Ready, set, go.
(AS)
Darn it!
- How do you know this?
- What's up with him?
You were clueless
when you had to play.
My gosh. This...
It's easier to see
when you're a spectator.
- I know.
- Not when you're playing though.
(It only seems difficult
for those who are playing the game.)
Let me answer.
It's "Abnormal Summit."
("Abnormal Summit")
It suddenly came to me.
This isn't easy.
"Abnormal Summit."
- Let's tie the score.
- Nice.
- Go, Team Mapo.
- Go!
- What?
- This is a tricky one.
What's with the Ss?
Let me answer.
"Laughing..." No, that's not it.
- What can it be?
- What is it?
Let me answer.
"Sunday to Sunday Night."
("Sunday to Sunday Night")
Nicely done.
- Nice.
- You're on a roll.
- Good job.
- I'm on a roll!
Nicely done!
- Go, Team Mapo.
- Why don't you switch players?
- You guys are doing great.
- Suk Jin...
- Those on the side...
- But us two...
- We're...
- How can you be so clueless?
- Well...
Only Jong Kook
has been able to answer.
- I'm completely clueless.
- Kwang Soo, why were you up there?
What were you up to?
- I displayed reactions.
- What were you doing up here?
- Jong Kook...
- I couldn't figure them out.
This is an oldie.
(Which question will break the tie?)
- And go.
- We need to score this time.
- To...
- Let me answer.
- "Our Joyful..."
- He's right.
(OHS)
- "Our Happy Saturday."
- "Our Happy Saturday!"
- That's the one.
(Sae Ho managed
to pick up the answer.)
- What?
- We were faster.
- What did you say?
- "Our Happy Saturday."
You thought of
"Our Joyful Young Days," didn't you?
I was the fastest, but...
It was "Our Happy Saturday."
I should've quickly
said the other one.
(The Initial Game is over.)
No way.
- I got confused.
- It's the total score that matters.
- The total score?
- Is it the total score?
- Yes, the total score.
- Right.
- We all did a good job.
- Good job, guys.
The winning team
after the two rounds of games...
is Team Mapo.
- Yes!
- Nice!
- Mapo, Mapo, Mapo, Mapo
Mapo will get another slot
on the roulette.
(Team Mapo wins another slot
on the roulette.)
The next game will take place...
at the Korean restaurant
in Dongbinggo-dong.
Let's go!
The other team won,
so we're headed in that direction.
- Do we get to eat then?
- Bring us the tteokbokki!
Let's head to the Korean restaurant.
Ma'am, out of those five,
please choose the three...
who you think will enjoy
tteokbokki the most.
Back when I used to
live around here,
- I ate it a lot.
- I bought a lot of takeouts.
I love you
- I love you, ma'am
- Love you!
Cho Sae Ho.
Really? Why?
- Because I sang?
- You seemed eager.
Love, love, who said it was love?
Who said it was love?
- And Haha.
- Nice!
And Ji Hyo. I'm sorry.
- I'm a fan, you know.
- Thank you.
Ji Hyo!
She didn't even look at me once.
You should've chosen another song.
Winning isn't all that good.
We all get some to taste,
although I won't eat it.
We shouldn't give in.
- Exactly.
- Of course.
- We're human beings for a reason.
- Right.
- That's right.
- Think, people.
Only animals
give in to their instincts.
- Why don't I sit back?
- Sure.
That makes us animals.
Didn't you think of yourself
as an animal just now?
(Barking)
(Growling)
Goodness.
- That's how it's served?
- As a proper dish?
(One-pot tteokbokki
is served to the winning team.)
Ramyeon was added too.
The seasoned dumplings
are to die for.
That must be the seasoned dumplings.
This we must have.
There are ramyeon
and glass noodles. No way.
Darn, this is so good.
I haven't eaten here before, but...
Smash a boiled egg in the sauce.
Choa, you're not eating, are you?
No way.
This isn't what I like anyway.
(While trying to convince himself,
he glances at the food.)
Keep talking, guys.
But this...
- Choa.
- Yes?
Why are you leaning forward?
Think about how it'll be
at the end of the day.
Guys, let's keep talking.
Keep talking.
Only an animal would give in.
(I'm a human being.)
- Kwang Soo.
- Yes?
You're holding some of
the ramyeon, right?
What...
- It's obvious.
- No way.
Someone's going to give in,
so just eat and give up two slots.
The dumplings and pickled radish
are to die for.
Jae Suk!
What?
(He called Jae Suk just in case.)
(He was already
in the middle of eating.)
See? It's over now.
Just eat!
Unbelievable.
(The restraints are off,
and now they start eating.)
Are you all eating?
Of course not.
(They're having their fill.)
Their mouths are already full.
Jong Kook, endure this round...
and enjoy the Korean cuisine
at the next restaurant.
- Haha, look to your side.
- Why?
(Jong Kook joins
the party of carbs.)
The dumplings are amazing.
We're the only ones
who aren't eating.
How is this fair when we won?
- We're on the winning team.
- This is unfair.
- More dumplings, please.
- How can one not eat this?
Team Mapo!
I knew that Jae Suk would cave.
Jae Suk and Kwang Soo.
- I wasn't sure about Kwang Soo.
- His response was hilarious.
- Anyway, I'm feeling great.
- Choa, you can sit here.
- Sit over here.
- Sure.
- I had just about enough.
- Put on your seat belt.
- Sure.
It's been a year since I had that.
(Is she in my seat?)
- Suk Jin...
- Didn't you know?
He saw Choa in his seat and...
- Really?
- He gave her the stink-eye.
- Should I...
- It's all right.
- You can stay.
- This is hilarious.
Suk Jin...
- Why did you glare at Choa?
- I didn't.
- I'm good.
- You glared at her.
- You wanted her to move.
- Hardly.
- I didn't glare at her.
- Choa.
- He glared at her from outside.
- Tell me about it.
- He was shooting lasers.
- That wasn't the case.
Choa, don't let it get to you.
Anyway, that was delicious.
Nicely done.
(They head to the next destination
that's closer to Mapo.)
We'll cross Dongjak Bridge
to the north of the Han River.
- Okay.
- Let's go!
- Mapo, Mapo, Mapo, Mapo
(Okay, let's head toward Mapo!)
- What's important though...
- It's meaningless.
is that we end today's episode
in Gangnam.
- At Dosan Park.
- Yes, that's more important.
So we should come back to
Gangnam afterward...
- and finish there.
- We should finish there.
Sae Ho, you should talk.
- Sorry?
- Me too.
How can you just sit still?
- That's not it.
- You ate the tteokbokki.
- No, no. I...
- You're at work, you should talk.
I'm a pro, so I should only
talk when it's needed.
- This is the time for you to talk.
- Oh, really?
My specialty is talking.
I'm known as Talk Bomber.
- "Bomber?"
- So when will you start talking?
I can if you want me to,
but nobody wants me to talk.
He became less witty
after he lost weight, right?
Yes, he's way too boring now.
Sae Ho, Jong Kook said you became
too boring after losing weight.
He said you lost
your sensibility too.
You became boring
after losing weight.
Is Jong Kook really a good fighter?
- I'm just curious. Is he that good?
- Yes, he is.
He once fought against seven men.
Against seven men?
Before, even his back was funny
when he was sitting still.
Jong Kook, it's because...
Especially his fat neck.
I shouldn't have lost that fat.
- It's gone now.
- I miss it.
I could've asked something like,
"Are there crumbs in between?"
Now there's no fat on my neck.
Between his neck rolls?
Yes, between the rolls.
- It's cute.
- I just can't have it all.
So I chose to be healthy instead.
I got a medical check-up recently.
- Are you much healthier now?
- My cholesterol level...
- got much lower.
- Sae Ho.
Try to talk less.
But you wanted me
to talk more earlier.
- But you need to be quiet now.
- Oh, should I?
We're driving past
a residential area,
so we need to be quiet.
I don't see any houses though.
- Stay quiet.
- This is really hard.
- We're in a residential area.
- Oh, okay.
- But we're on a bus.
- People who work late...
- might still be sleeping.
- Okay.
Sae Ho always says this when I
run into him at a fitness center.
"What's wrong with Jae Suk?"
I always say,
"What's with Jae Suk?"
- Hey, Sae Ho.
- Yes, Jae Suk?
Can you show us how Kwang Soo
works out?
- I think Kwang Soo...
- Let's see what he does.
lifts weights that he can't handle.
- That's kind of true.
- So...
- Normally, people do it like this.
- This one's funny.
- But he goes like this.
- Come on!
(His whole body shakes to
lift the weights he can't handle.)
I don't do that!
- I'd ask, "Why are you doing this?"
- I don't lift like that.
- That's so true.
- What are you talking about?
Yes, you do that.
- He lifts weights like this.
- Kwang Soo does it like that.
Kwang Soo always does this.
- Come on.
- When he works on his biceps,
he goes like this.
(He makes so much noise as if he
bears all the weight of the world.)
- So I thought he was about to die.
- I know.
So why do you always do this?
- Why would you do this?
- I do it unconsciously.
You need to stick your tongue out
to use your strength.
Yes, that helps me
get more strength.
- So why would you...
- He only does it to show off.
When Jae Suk sees me
or Sae Ho at the fitness center,
he always points out our postures.
But when someone like
Gong Yoo comes,
his lips go dry right away.
(When Jae Suk meets a top celeb,
his lips go dry.)
- Because they're top stars.
- Hey, hey!
- Hey!
- "Hi, Gong Yoo."
He gets nervous in front of
top stars.
- He'd bow as he waves.
- Hey, hey!
- He'd also walk humbly.
- That's total nonsense.
He's been nervous in front
of top stars all his life.
- Gong Yoo is younger than me.
- He's always nervous.
Gong Yoo is younger than me,
you see.
(They are all boastful
at the fitness center.)
It's so funny.
Anyway, it's really fun to have
Sae Ho here after a long time.
You can get off at the bus stop.
- He can go home now?
- He should leave quietly?
You're lucky.
The ending is the hard part.
You can go home now.
- But he actually...
- You did enough.
- talked a lot today.
- Thank you for today.
- It was so fun today.
- Thank you so much for coming.
Can you show how Kwang Soo
lifts weights before you leave?
(Doing an encore
of making much fuss)
(Fully using his facial muscles)
We're crossing the bridge now.
This is nice.
- We're now...
- This is what makes it so fun!
- We're going to Mapo now!
- Mapo is indeed great.
(They move to their next spot
by crossing Dongjak Bridge.)
- What is this place?
- It's so nice!
- It's pretty!
- This place is so pretty!
This place is nice.
The atmosphere is a little...
What is this place?
How come it's so pretty?
I love this place.
It's pretty.
The weather is so nice.
It's spring now.
But there's so much fine dust.
- What are you talking about?
- Today's weather is the worst.
- I know too.
- There's so much fine dust.
- I'm just saying it's warm.
- The sky is covered with dust.
Look how the flowers bloomed.
It's magnolia. Magnolias are
the prettiest in March.
Out of 12, Team Mapo filled up 8.
And Team Gangnam filled up four.
- We only filled up four?
- This is annoying.
- Yes.
- That's it.
This is the current status.
We need to win this mission.
But we won twice.
- We just need to win.
- But this is...
This game is advantageous
to Jong Kook.
This game is made for Jong Kook.
All right, let's do this!
It looks like a pillow fight.
It's obviously a pillow fight.
This mission will increase your will
to go home from the designated spot.
It's called The Outlaw on the Road.
The game will begin with everyone
on the balance beam.
- We'll all be seated.
- We'll be seated.
The one who wins rock-paper-scissors
will start first...
and attack the other team.
You can get back up on the beam.
- Oh, we can get back up on it.
- It's over once everyone's out.
- I see.
- Okay, I got it.
It's simple, right?
- This is...
- We'll win for sure.
- Jong Kook is on our team, so...
- Do you want to go last, Jong Kook?
But the game is...
- I can go last.
- It's meant for Jong Kook.
- The outlaw is Jong Kook.
- The last one remaining wins.
The last one to remain wins, right?
We'll have Jong Kook go last.
That's a relief. Thank you.
- You'll go last?
- No.
I'm not good at this.
You should hit Jong Kook.
- Think about it.
- That's right. You should show us.
- You should hit him.
- Show us what you can do.
You've been slain by him
all this time.
He's been attacking you.
That's enough reason to hit him.
You should go up against him.
Show us what you can do.
- Here, Sae Ho. You're the tail.
- Really? I'm going last?
I'm going last?
- Hey, Jong Kook.
- Yes?
You can't attack them.
- Yes, he can!
- Why can't I? I can.
- Can you really?
- He can attack them right away.
Besides, Kwang Soo will be
sitting before him.
I'll do my best so he doesn't
have to hurt the women.
- You're so reliable.
- Of course.
- I'll do my best so that...
- He's so reliable.
Kwang Soo will get rid of them.
- Get up here, Choa.
- Okay!
- This is hard though.
- We crouch down here?
All right, let's go now.
Choa, sit here.
- My nemesis. We finally meet.
- I'm finally meeting you.
I think I'll lose to her though.
Everyone should sit on it.
If they fall by themselves,
- they're out, right?
- Yes.
All right. Play rock-paper-scissors.
(The match between the weakest,
Suk Jin versus So Min))
- Rock-paper-scissors
You can hit each other in turn.
You should kill her at once!
You should kill her at once.
(Gathering his strength)
(Hitting)
- All right! I stood it.
- Kill her at once.
It's your turn, So Min.
- You need to hit him, So Min.
- If you hit...
(Hitting)
(Oh, gosh! That darn...)
- All right!
Did he just curse at her?
- What did he say?
- I mean...
Please edit that part out.
I accidentally blurted it out.
- Choa!
- Yes.
I apologize, dear viewers.
Please move one seat forward.
You just need to keep your balance.
- But this is...
- It's hard to keep my balance.
- It's hard.
- It's hard even for me.
- Rock-paper-scissors
- All right!
- No!
(So Min gets to attack first.)
- Hit her hard.
- Bear with it.
- You need to bear with it.
- Hit her hard.
- Go.
- You need to bear with it.
- Bear with it.
- That was good! Good job!
- She withstood it!
(She faltered a little,
but she got back up.)
- That was good! Good job!
- She withstood it!
- Good job, Choa.
- Choa is really strong.
- Hit her.
- Do not go easy on her.
Don't you go easy on her.
You saw it, right? Hey, hey.
What was that?
(What?)
(She hung on so well,)
(but she falls on her own
as though she's drunk.)
- What was that?
- All right!
- This is driving me crazy.
- She's so weak.
- Everyone is so weak.
- Choa. This is driving me crazy.
Gosh, this is difficult.
(So Min wins 2 times in a row.)
You can fall on your own.
So Min, the nation's favorite man
is here.
- This isn't as easy as it looks.
- All right.
- I'm not sure.
- Let's play this.
- Rock-paper-scissors
(So Min gets to attack first.)
Gosh, this is crazy.
- You won, So Min?
- Yes.
Don't be flustered, Jae Suk.
- Hang on at least once.
- This is...
- Aim for his temple.
(Aim for his temple!)
- His temple?
- Yes, that's the most...
- Like this?
- Don't be flustered.
Look at that ugly... That's it.
(Hitting hard)
That's it.
All right!
(She hit him right on the temple,)
(but she fell on her own.)
- What was that?
- That's it.
- That's it! I got this.
- I got greedy.
I'm out if I fall
while moving up, right?
Of course.
- But this is...
- It's really difficult though.
Be careful not to fall
while moving up.
Ji Hyo looks so indifferent.
Look at her uninterested face.
While moving...
Show us, Ji Hyo.
- Rock-paper-scissors
- All right. Hit her hard.
- Ji Hyo.
- Jae Suk.
- Put strength in your legs, Ji Hyo.
Don't go easy on her.
- Ji Hyo!
- What's with Ji Hyo's expression?
She looks sleepy.
- All right.
- I hit her hard though.
I hit her hard though.
That was a fake shot.
It didn't hurt her,
but it made her feel bad.
That was a fake shot.
- All right.
- It didn't hurt her,
but it made her feel bad.
- Hey, how could you...
- That was...
(Hey...)
That's just hitting him in the face.
She didn't hit him to make him fall!
That wasn't meant for me to fall.
She just hit him.
Ji Hyo.
(It's Jae Suk's turn
to attack back.)
(He only made a fuss.)
Hey, hey.
Why did you hit her so lightly?
(Ji Hyo attacks back right away.)
(Laughing)
Come on!
(He trembles and falls on his own.)
Ji Hyo fell as well.
(After Jae Suk fell,)
Come on!
(Ji Hyo's foot touched the ground.)
Ji Hyo fell as well.
Ji Hyo fell as well!
- You're out.
- I'm out?
- You're out, Ji Hyo.
You two fell at the same time.
It's hard to keep my balance
on the beam.
- Kwang Soo!
- Yes.
- It's hard to keep my balance.
- Don't fall. It'll be for nothing.
Haha, show us what you can do.
That's right.
You should grab it like that.
- Look how he's grabbing it.
- This is...
(He comes up with a lethal move
he used to use when he was young.)
Kwang Soo... Look at Haha.
- Kwang Soo, we must win.
- Okay.
Ready or not
- Rock-paper-scissors
(Kwang Soo gets to attack first.)
- Okay. Kill him with one blow.
- Kill him with one blow.
(Hitting hard)
All right!
(Darn it!)
- All right.
- Well done.
- Well done!
- Kwang Soo.
- Well done, Kwang Soo.
- That was great.
I think he put something
in his pillow.
No, I didn't.
- I didn't put anything in.
- You must win rock-paper-scissors.
Let's go, let's go.
Wait a minute. I hit Haha,
but I got tteokbokki on my pillow.
- Isn't it his blood?
- It's tteokbokki.
(The stain from the tteokbokki
Haha had earlier)
Hey, Kwang Soo!
- Kwang Soo, you need to win.
- You need to win.
- You must win rock-paper-scissors.
- Let's do this!
Ready or not, rock-paper-scissors
- Rock-paper-scissors
- All right.
- Darn you.
- Show us, Se Chan.
Are you at home or something?
- What are you doing?
- It feels like I'm watching TV.
I'm just watching TV.
Ji Hyo.
Hey, Kwang Soo!
- Kwang Soo, you need to win.
- You need to win.
- You must win rock-paper-scissors.
- Let's do this!
I should hit you here.
Or should I hit him like this
to hurt him?
Kwang Soo, he might hit you
from the back.
- You need to be careful.
- You should watch out.
- You need to grab it like this.
- Don't hit me, okay?
(Hitting right in the face)
(Kwang Soo fell weakly
after getting slapped on the side.)
- That worked.
- It's hard not to fall!
It's hard not to fall
after getting hit like that.
- That's the way!
- Well done!
- We still have a chance.
- It hurt.
It was impossible to bear with it.
- We still have a chance.
- Jong Kook.
Jong Kook.
You should win rock-paper-scissors.
- Hey, Jong Kook.
- It was impossible to bear with it.
- Jong Kook, we believe in you.
- Where do I sit? Here?
Jong Kook, it all
depends on you now.
- This is...
- I might have a chance...
to get back at him.
- It's a golden opportunity.
- You must win.
It's a golden opportunity
to hit Jong Kook.
No, I'll lose, so you can hit him.
- Okay.
- Just kill them all right away.
(Team Gangnam cannot
back away anymore.)
You need to win against him first.
(Team Mapo
must hit Jong Kook first.)
- This is hard.
- Please.
- Rock-paper-scissors
- All right. We got this.
- This is good.
- We can win this round!
- You can bear with it, Jong Kook.
(You can bear with it, Jong Kook!)
Se Chan, you're so cool too.
Let me finish you at once.
I'm going to hit his thick thighs...
and finish him at once.
- Hey, Jong Kook.
- This isn't a pillow.
- It's a bag of rice.
- You must win.
- I'm going to make him fall.
- You need to...
You should make him fall even if
you fall with him.
- Okay.
- Yes, you should do that.
Just imagine that you're
on the top of a mountain.
- You must win.
- One...
(Faltering)
He withstood it!
(Se Chan failed to finish him.)
(He withstood it!)
- I'm dead now.
- We got this.
- We got this!
You brats. You're over now.
You're all over.
- You're over.
- I'm dead. I'm dead now.
- I'm dead now.
- Se Chan!
(Burning with anger)
(The muscular monster
is gathering his energy.)
The way Se Chan hit Jong Kook
must've offended him.
(You're dead now.)
(The boatman to the afterlife
is slowly rowing his pillow.)
- Bear it. You can do this.
- It's been a while.
- Clench your teeth.
- All right.
Look at Sae Ho. He's going next.
(Pale)
(Will Se Chan be able to
bear with it?)
- All right!
- No!
(No!)
(Will Jong Kook fall with Se Chan?)
He made it, he made it.
- Kim Jong Kook!
- Kim Jong Kook! Well done!
(It will never work.)
(It looks like he's already
been dead 3 times over.)
- Sae Ho, you can't bear it.
- Show us, Sae Ho.
You only need to win
in rock-paper-scissors!
(It's the last match
on the guillotine.)
- You need to finish him at once.
- Seriously...
The winning team
will be able to eat...
and stick their sticker
on the roulette.
- Hey, hey.
- We must win this.
- Finish him at once.
- It's over if we lose in this game.
- Finish him.
- Cho Sae Ho!
I'll get revenge on him
for all the humiliation I got.
That's right!
You'll get a chance
if you win in rock-paper-scissors.
- Here we go, Sae Ho.
- Rock...
Rock-paper-scissors
You just need to win.
Men always go for paper.
Rock-paper-scissors
- Oh, no!
- All right, we got this.
- All right.
- Jong Kook, let's make this fun.
(He begs for mercy, saying
they should make the show fun.)
Let's make this fun.
It's over.
No, he can bear with it.
It'll be hard for him
to keep his balance.
I think he'll just fall on his own
if Jong Kook stalls for time.
- His legs will go numb.
- You can't do that with your hand.
- It's really scary.
- First...
Should I hit you from the bottom?
- Or from the side?
- I should've won.
How do you want me to hit?
- Give me a chance, seriously.
- Come work out at my center.
Okay, I will.
(Will there be a twist?)
Look at his face.
Please give me a chance.
(There was no twist.)
(Please give me a chance.)
(He neatly got rid of Sae Ho.)
- All right!
- Yes!
- Well done!
- All right!
- It's impossible to beat him.
I should've hit Jong Kook
and fell with him.
I should've won
in rock-paper-scissors.
We'll now move back to
the tteokbokki place in Gangnam.
- What?
(Going back
to the same tteokbooki place)
- What?
- We're going back to Gangnam?
- We're going there again?
- Yes, we are.
But if we win the mission there,
we need to come back
to this place again.
We won't be skipping it?
- Let us have some dessert.
- We're not skipping it?
- We won't be skipping it?
- We're going back.
And we will...
add Team Gangnam's sticker.
- So then... All right.
- All right, we got it.
- We're eating here though, right?
- Yes, you will.
- Nice!
- Let's move inside.
I thought you were jumping.
But it's better for us
to end the shoot in Mapo.
(Spring vegetable seafood jeon
filled with the scent of spring)
That looks so good.
What's this?
That seafood wonton looks so good.
It looks so good!
I like this type of food.
(An appetite booster meal
for spring)
(The losing team will get
only 3 pieces of jeon.)
- They're wontons.
- Wontons.
We need to eat healthy food.
This looks really good.
As you know, only three people
that the owner picks...
from the winning team...
- can have the meal.
- This is so...
I really want to eat this.
It smells great though.
This type of meal will keep you full
the whole day.
We don't need to eat, do we?
I won't eat.
We don't need to eat.
I'm still full.
Tell me how it tastes later.
This is...
- Hello, sir!
- My gosh, sir.
- Hello.
(Ha Myung Soo, the manager
of the Korean restaurant)
(They butter him up
and give him a shout.)
- He's handsome.
- Sir.
- It tastes so good.
- It's such high-quality food.
So you're the one
who made these dishes!
- They're going overboard.
- No matter...
No matter how desperate you are,
you can't say it tastes good...
- when you haven't even tasted it.
- I really want to eat it.
I feel alive after eating this.
Among five of them,
you can pick three of whom
you'd like to taste your food.
I can eat very well.
- When it comes to healthy food...
- You look so good in your uniform.
- I can eat it really well.
- I eat very well too.
My name is Myung Soo,
- Myung Soo?
- so I'll pick Jae Suk.
(Nice choice.)
Thank you so much, Captain Ha.
How is that related?
- But what does that have to do...
- So what if his name is Myung Soo?
I was a big fan
of "Infinite Challenge."
I need to be wherever Myung Soo is.
But Myung Soo is...
Please pick the rest.
I'll pick Jong Kook
as I'm his huge fan.
- My goodness.
- He's healthy.
(Heartfelt double thumbs up)
He needs to pick Choa next.
- Of course.
- Sir.
- First of all...
- Are you going to pick Choa?
- Mr. Ha Myung Soo.
- No...
- Then I will...
- Among all the restaurants,
- I think your food is the best.
- pick Choa.
(He picks Choa without hesitation.)
Move over. Move, move.
- Go away.
- Move.
- He's good. My gosh.
- It's no joke.
- Tteokbokki is the best.
I've never had this before.
Jong Kook, you can stand here.
I'll go over there.
Suk Jin, can you move?
But... Hey.
I can stay seated, can't I?
But it's a seat for us to eat.
Hey, Team Mapo!
- I'm so jealous of them.
- You can't eat!
I won't eat.
- Seriously.
- I ate a lot earlier.
Don't you dare eat it.
(He conducts a random check
when he's eaten it already.)
So Min, you finished
the whole thing.
I see that you cleared your dish.
What are you saying?
You ate all the jeon
except the vegetable jeon.
What?
What does it taste like?
My gosh, Haha.
You just had a bite
of the vegetable jeon.
Are you serious?
- What's going on?
- I can't believe this.
You're nasty, you dirty mustache!
- What's wrong?
- Haha just told us...
not to eat, but he's enjoying it
like a course meal.
What kind of team are we?
(Team Mapo's teamwork is the worst.)
I'm going to have it.
I'll just eat it.
I'm going to eat it now.
(Empty dish)
Do you have a death wish?
(He smiles widely
out of embarrassment.)
You were eating...
(How dare you?)
How can you do this?
(Team Mapo could not overcome
the temptation.)
How is the octopus rice?
- The octopus rice...
- Is it good?
It's aromatic.
The octopus rice is aromatic?
- This is...
- The octopus rice...
- It's savory.
- is really savory.
Wow, this is really soft.
The beef jeon was made out
of Korean beef.
- No, you can't.
- Oh, really?
Se Chan, help me out.
- Force me to eat.
- What?
But this is really good.
No, no! Don't do this!
Don't! Stop it!
(He heads to the table as if
someone forced him to.)
(Shoving his head to the dish)
(Devouring the whole thing)
- Hey!
- He forced Kwang Soo to eat.
- This is...
- He wanted me to force him.
- Hey!
- He had a bite.
He asked me to push him
to the table.
What was that?
Did you have a bite?
- For goodness' sake.
- Suk Jin said...
My goodness.
He asked me to push him
to the table.
Let's move to the next location.
- Are we really going back?
- Tteokbokki?
- I even took photos with the owner.
- I will stay here.
Go ahead.
We are crossing Dongjak Bridge
for the third time.
- We came back to this place
- For goodness' sake.
We took photos with the owner
and said our farewells.
This is...
a famous tteokbokki place in Banpo.
- Really?
- Their tteokbokki is delicious.
Their tteokbokki is delicious.
They serve incredible tteokbokki.
- Listen.
- It's the best.
- Top 10 tteokbokki places in Korea.
- That's right.
I said goodbye to the owner
not too long ago.
We even took a group photo.
Seasoned dumplings are amazing.
I said, "I will visit again."
- You visited again.
- Seriously.
You kept your promise.
I bet the owner didn't know
we would come back so soon.
We came back after an hour.
This mission will give you...
the patience to endure
the heavy traffic on your way home.
It's Open Your Mouth.
Pick two shellfish of your choice...
- and grill them on your brazier.
- Okay.
The team with the shellfish
that opens the latest will lose.
Okay, okay.
- It's time to pick the shellfish.
- Okay.
Some open faster than others.
Some don't open at all.
- Really?
- Some don't open at all.
It all depends on luck.
Kwang Soo, pick two
and put them on the table.
Let's take turns.
I will pick the big ones.
The big ones. Okay.
The bigger ones?
What was the name of the game?
Shut the Mouth?
- Open Your Mouth.
Hey.
- "Shut the Mouth?"
Why would that be the name?
(Why would the name be
"Shut the Mouth?")
Get ready.
(They are ready
for Open Your Mouth.)
Let's do this, Team Mapo!
Let's go, Team Mapo!
Let's go, Team Gangnam!
1, 2, 3.
- Let's go.
(They carefully put the shellfish
on the brazier.)
Don't hit them.
The fire is becoming stronger.
It might be best
to leave it as it is.
Let's go. Let's go.
(Se Chan focuses on
the big scallop.)
It opened. It opened its mouth.
(Se Chan's scallop opens up
like his protruding mouth.)
Did it open already?
- Se Chan's shellfish opened.
- Already?
It opened.
- It opened.
- Scallops open faster.
What's wrong with my shellfish?
- It opened.
- Scallops open faster.
- My shellfish opened.
- Did it open?
It opened. It opened.
- This one opened, right?
- It needs to open further.
- Both of my shellfish opened. Yes!
- Both of my shellfish opened.
- Se Chan succeeded.
- Okay!
- How about Choa?
- One at a time.
- Grill one at a time.
- What?
What's wrong with my shellfish?
Two shellfish.
Okay. I succeeded.
- So Min's shellfish opened.
- Both of them opened.
My shellfish opened.
- Your shellfish opened.
- They opened. I am done.
Okay. My shellfish opened.
Haha, your shellfish will open.
- Kwang Soo.
- My shellfish opened.
Kwang Soo.
Now, Kwang Soo, Sae Ho,
and Haha remain.
- They opened.
(Kwang Soo's scallops
finally begin to open.)
- One more.
- Push it aside.
Push it aside.
Focus on one at a time.
- Wait.
- They opened.
They opened.
- Haha succeeded.
Okay!
Sae Ho, move the shellfish
so that it's above the fire.
- Really?
- Put it in the middle.
- Come on.
- Can I move it?
- Move it.
Move the scallop to the middle.
(The teams' fates depends on
Kwang Soo and Sae Ho.)
- Move it a bit.
- Open!
Kwang Soo, Kwang Soo.
Watch the fire.
Why won't it open?
(The way home depends on
the shellfish.)
(The winning team will get a slot
on the ending roulette.)
- It will open. It's moving.
- It's moving.
- Open!
- Come on!
(What will be the result
of the match?)
- What's wrong with it?
- It opened!
- Haha succeeded.
- Okay!
Please! It opened!
- It opened!
- What's wrong with it?
(Sae Ho's scallop didn't open
in the end.)
What's wrong with it?
- Gangnam!
- What's wrong with it?
- One of Sae Ho's didn't open.
- Why won't it open?
Why won't it open?
- What are you doing?
- What's wrong with it?
You want to go to Gangnam, right?
That's not true.
We will end up going to Gangnam.
This is bad.
Going home will take
an hour and a half.
If we get Mapo
when we spin the roulette,
- we will go to Mapo.
- That's right.
- Let's invite the owner inside.
- Okay.
Jae Suk,
I think she will listen to you.
- Once she comes in,
- Seriously.
I will recommend the two of you.
I will tell her that Kwang Soo
and Suk Jin haven't eaten.
(Jae Suk is full,
so he would rather have them eat.)
It's the owner's daughter.
- Hello.
- The owner's eldest daughter.
We came back after saying goodbye.
We are sorry.
It's okay.
- Hello.
- You will take over the business.
There are five members on the team,
but the two of them haven't eaten.
- Kwang Soo and Suk Jin.
- We haven't eaten.
It doesn't matter, right?
- Do I need to choose?
- Among the five of us,
- please choose 3.
- Please choose 3.
Three people will eat.
- Okay.
- Kwang Soo.
(Kwang Soo will finally have
his first meal.)
(I will get to eat too.)
- Jae Suk.
- Me?
(She skips over Suk Jin
and chooses Jae Suk.)
Thank you. I like this place.
- She skipped over me.
- Thank you. I like this place.
She skipped over me.
He is pretty full.
Jae Suk's stomach will burst.
Be quiet.
Please pick one more person.
The last person is...
(She chooses the last person
after much deliberation.)
(What will be Suk Jin's fate?)
(The last person is...)
- Jong Kook.
- My goodness.
(He is forced to go on a diet.)
- You know,
- Hold on.
the restaurants just don't pick
Suk Jin.
- What?
- You heard, right?
- You heard that I haven't eaten.
- Yes.
You heard, right?
I just wanted to check.
- She heard.
- You heard, right?
- Yes.
- My goodness.
My wife and I ate tteokbokki
at that table.
I am sorry.
- Thank you.
That's so funny.
- I just can't eat.
- Suk Jin told her...
that he hasn't eaten.
He told her that he hasn't eaten.
- All right.
- My goodness.
(Suk Jin can't eat tteokbokki
and seasoned dumplings.)
Gosh.
Let's eat a boiled egg.
- Kwang Soo, eat a boiled egg.
- Thank you.
- Don't eat.
- There are dumplings too.
Your stomach will burst.
I can still eat this.
- Your stomach will burst.
- I can still eat this.
- This is different.
- Tteokbokki is different.
It's a snack, not a meal.
Sae Ho, don't eat it.
- I won't eat it.
- I dropped my chopsticks.
Don't eat it.
Are you eating again?
You had the octopus rice.
(Slurping)
Hold on. Come to think of it,
I only had a small bite of food
behind the screen.
Ma'am, I am disappointed.
My wife loves this restaurant.
- That's your wife, not you.
- Still,
I live in the neighborhood.
My house is near here.
I paid the five-dollar parking fee
in order to come here.
- Stop it.
- I parked my car...
in the parking lot.
- What is your problem?
- Come to think of it,
- I only had a small bite of food.
- Suk Jin, get out.
- I haven't eaten anything else.
- Overcome.
- I can't overcome it.
- Stop it.
I can overcome hunger,
but I can't overcome disappointment.
- I overcame hunger.
- Stop it.
But I am so disappointed.
She heard...
- that I haven't eaten.
- Stop it.
- Seriously.
I haven't been this hungry
during a shoot about eating.
I have been starving all day long.
We will move to the last place,
- a dessert cafe in Yeoksam.
- Okay.
Let's go.
I haven't eaten.
- I really haven't eaten.
- That was tasty.
I am so full.
We have to win.
- We have to win.
- Let's win.
We have to win.
- Choa.
- Yes?
You run a YouTube channel.
After this episode airs,
you should share
behind-the-scenes stories.
- You should do that.
- A review.
- What is your channel about?
- I am curious.
I do song covers.
- You sing.
- Yes.
- Choa is an incredible singer.
- You are too kind.
It has been so long
since I heard her sing.
Would you sing a song
you recently covered?
Which songs did I recently cover?
- That's rude.
- I know. Don't ask her to sing.
- Is it rude?
- Don't put her on the spot.
- It's old-fashioned.
- Suk Jin!
- What?
Please do a voice impression
of Baek Seol Hee.
(This isn't rude.)
(He suddenly gets asked to do
a voice impression.)
(Singing)
(He sings
the background music of the past.)
I feel bad for Suk Jin.
It has been over 30 years.
He can do it right away.
(The old people
burst out laughing...)
(and the young people fall asleep.)
(The addictive voice)
Suk Jin. Jong Kook...
Jong Kook burst out laughing.
I love it.
It has been over 30 years.
It's nice to hear
Baek Seol Hee's voice again.
Thanks to that, Suk Jin passed
the comedian exam.
- Really?
I love you
Me too
- I like you
- That's funny.
Everything in the world
There you go.
- He passed the exam with that.
- That's right.
You are cool.
- You are good.
- The competition wasn't bad, right?
It's like a song...
- from a gramophone.
- I shocked everyone.
(They arrive at P Cafe
in Yeoksam-dong.)
It smells good in here.
- It smells good.
- It smells insane.
- This is the last place.
- Yes.
This time, you will feel
the sweetness of spring.
There are strawberry croffles
and strawberry lattes.
It smells good.
- It smells good.
- The timing is perfect.
- That sounds incredible.
Choa is happy.
They sound delicious.
I really want them.
For the last mission,
you need the hawk's eyes for finding
the route with less traffic.
It's the One Arms and Legs.
- One Arms and Legs?
- What is that?
In the sleeves of a hoodie,
you will put in your arms and legs
at the same time.
You win if you read the word
on your opponent's back first.
- My goodness.
- It's simple, right?
(You win if you read the word
on your opponent's back first.)
We decided on the list of matches
by drawing spoons.
The first match is
between Choa and Se Chan.
(Choa versus Se Chan)
Gosh, this is...
It will be fierce.
Why do you think it will be fierce?
- Se Chan, let's go!
- Of course.
I need to win.
You should put on your shoes first.
I am going to do this without shoes.
I see.
Please put the words on their backs.
- Se Chan, let's go.
- Okay.
Let's go.
Choa will win.
- Se Chan.
- Okay.
- Okay. Let's do this.
- Let's go.
What will happen?
- He has athletic skills.
- Really?
Even if a match is ongoing,
the mission will end at 5 p.m.
Get ready.
(Not much time remains,
so this match is important.)
Get ready.
- Set, go.
- Let's go.
He is fast.
Se Chan.
(Se Chan intimidates her
with big jumps.)
He looks like a frog.
Choa looks so comfortable.
She is fast.
- Seriously.
- Choa really is...
Hey, watch your back.
(Se Chan tries
the short-legged jump.)
- Choa.
- It's almond something.
There you go.
- Se Chan.
- Push him to the side.
- Be careful.
- There you go.
(Choa gets pushed to a corner.)
We need to go to Mapo.
Let's go to Mapo.
Be careful. Be careful!
- No.
- Don't show your back.
Push Se Chan's cheek with your foot.
(Kicking)
(Falling)
You did it.
(Se Chan got pushed away.)
Go, go.
He can't get up. He can't.
It's so shameful.
My pose is so shameful.
- I am so ashamed. I need to get up.
- He can't get up.
He can't get up.
- I need to get up.
- He looks like a chicken.
- He can't get up.
He can't get up.
(Choa nearly flips over Se Chan
in the end.)
- You won.
- He can't get up.
Flip him over.
(Se Chan tries to get out
of the embarrassing pose.)
(Choa aspires to turn the tables.)
- I am so ashamed.
- The word is visible.
It's "Beetle."
(Choa won.)
Good job, Choa.
(They trusted Se Chan,
but he loses in a shameful way.)
- No.
- Good job, Choa.
(Sae Ho punishes him.)
Okay, Choa.
She did well.
Good job, Choa.
Good job.
The second match is...
between Kwang Soo and Ji Hyo.
We haven't seen that in a while.
Kwang Soo will easily see her back.
- He has an advantage.
- Okay, okay.
- Wait a minute.
It's currently 5 p.m.
(They heard the rule
during the opening in the morning.)
(All missions stop at 5 p.m.)
(Then they spin the roulette
to decide on the ending venue.)
(The current time is 5 p.m.)
Since it's 5 p.m.,
the result we have now will decide
the winning team.
Choa won, so Team Gangnam won.
- Okay!
- Yes!
(Did we lose again?)
We won.
Now comes the food.
Jae Suk,
please tell the owner of the cafe...
- that I haven't eaten yet.
- Okay.
I will do that.
Please do that.
I am really hungry right now.
(He pleads
after starving all day long.)
How many slots do we have?
Team Gangnam has 7
and Team Mapo has 5.
Okay.
There isn't a big difference.
If Mapo ends up being
the ending venue...
(That would be the worst.)
- That's right.
- Coming back here...
- will take two hours.
- Seriously.
- It's the evening rush hour.
- I know.
(The strawberry desserts enter.)
Strawberry.
(Their eyes go wide.)
Croissant.
Look at them.
- Look at them.
- They look delicious.
Anyone would want them.
(It's time to soothe the mouth
with a sweet drink.)
We got the latte.
(The losing team got a latte each.)
The strawberries look good.
Don't say anything.
Here comes the employee of the cafe.
- Hello.
- You know,
- My goodness.
I love strawberries.
This is a famous cafe.
I am obsessed with croffles.
Please pick the three members
who will eat the desserts.
(Which 3 members will she choose
for the strawberry desserts?)
Choa.
- Thank you.
- From the start...
I knew Choa would get chosen.
From the start,
Choa and I wanted the dessert.
(The second member is...)
Seriously.
- Jong Kook.
- Thank you.
Does Jong Kook suit strawberries?
- I love strawberries.
- Really?
I love strawberries,
I love strawberries
- Jae Suk.
- Thank you.
(She picks Jae Suk
instead of Suk Jin.)
- Thank you.
Suk Jin will starve today.
(The top 2 celebrities
shunned by the food industry)
- Thank you for the food.
- Thank you.
Thank you. We will enjoy the food.
I will take photos
and post them later.
- They look delicious.
- I am having a reality check.
They look so delicious.
Everyone else got chosen once
except for me.
(I must take photos!)
Why are you taking photos?
(She drinks the strawberry latte.)
- It's so tasty.
- It's so good.
(They keep exclaiming.)
It's a shame that I have to cut it.
Isn't your stomach about to burst?
No. There is a separate stomach...
for dessert.
I love strawberries.
(They made the strawberry croffle
for Running Man.)
(If you enjoy it, it's protein.)
(It's tasty
because it's freshly made.)
(They have no luck
when it comes to food.)
It looks tasty.
It's so tasty.
I love strawberry milk.
You mix it, right?
(Their war of nerves begins
once more.)
What?
It looks so delicious.
I know.
(He takes a peek like a mouse.)
Se Chan, why are you mixing
the drink?
I was just looking.
(Se Chan drinks it in the end.)
(Satisfied)
Let's clink our cups.
(Team Mapo fails to resist
the strawberry latte.)
Keep your friendship high,
keep your love deep,
and keep your glasses level.
- All right.
- Let's go.
It's so good.
- It's so good.
- Our youth starts now.
(They give a toast
because they are embarrassed.)
- It's so good.
- Our youth starts now.
We need to do this right.
- Seriously.
- I am nervous.
If we fail,
our effort will be meaningless.
- The mission is over.
- Okay.
The evening rush hour has begun.
(The evening rush hour has begun.)
(The current location)
(Mapo, Gangnam,
the ending venue candidates)
(It takes 1 hour and 30 minutes
to reach the ending venue in Mapo.)
(If Gangnam becomes
the ending venue,)
(it will take Team Mapo 2 hours
to go home.)
(8 slots for Gangnam
versus 4 slots for Mapo)
Let's go to Mapo.
There are only four slots for Mapo.
- Should I do it slowly?
- 8 slots versus 4 slots.
Spin it any way you want.
Which way shall we go?
You have one chance.
- Let's go to Mapo.
- Go, go.
It will be really funny
if we get Mapo.
You only have one chance.
- I will spin it hard.
- Okay.
You only have one chance.
(I will spin it hard.)
Done.
I have a bad feeling.
(The roulette will decide
who will go home quickly.)
- Mapo.
- I have a bad feeling.
(Half of them will be free
in the evening.)
(The other half will be stuck
in traffic in the evening.)
Really?
(Will they film the ending scene
in Gangnam or Mapo?)
(What will be the result?)
- I have a bad feeling.
- She didn't spin it right.
- Really?
- Gangnam!
(Gangnam is the ending venue.)
We did it.
(The people
who live near Gangnam rejoice.)
(For goodness' sake.)
(The result disappoints Team Mapo
and the production crew.)
We did it.
It almost became Mapo.
A slot for Mapo was
right next to it.
(Had it moved one more slot,
they would have gotten Mapo.)
We barely managed.
- Let's move to the ending venue.
- Let's go.
(They move to the ending venue
that is 15 minutes away by car.)
(Yeoksam P Dessert Cafe)
(Ending venue)
Come to think of it,
so many funny things happened.
Suk Jin was in the winning team,
- but he didn't get to eat anything.
- He didn't get to eat anything.
He starved.
Choa wants to tell you
that you are really cool.
- Who? Choa?
- Yes.
You are so funny.
Why doesn't it show on TV?
- Hey!
- Choa.
We are prohibited from saying that.
- Don't say that.
- Choa.
- You were so funny today.
It's a shame
that it doesn't show on TV.
Suk Jin just wiped off his tears.
I just need five viewers
who acknowledge me.
Five viewers. Are you one of them?
- Yes.
- I just need four more.
Four more?
Didn't you have anyone so far?
- Didn't you have anyone so far?
- No.
(He got acknowledged
for the first time ever.)
He has been that way for 30 years.
We are here.
It would have been bad
had the ending venue been Mapo.
- Everyone.
- Yes?
Today, we had
the Sweet and Scary Way Home Race.
Team Gangnam won.
(Team Gangnam had
the perfect victory.)
Good job.
(Meanwhile,
Team Mapo has a long way home.)
It's too bad that we lost.
Team Gangnam
will have a short way home...
as well as the famous snack
as the prize.
- It's rice cake.
- All right.
- It looks delicious.
- Seriously.
It's really delicious.
Team Gangnam will have
the rice cake...
and Team Mapo will have
a long way home.
(We thank Cho Sae Ho and Choa
for visiting.)
It's too bad!
(Perfect Partner Signal)
(8 entertainers entered
Variety Show Village!)
(3 female guests appear.)
(Seol In Ah)
(Lee Cho Hee)
(Jeong He In)
(They must show off their charms
amidst their rivals.)
(My charms will seep
into your heart.)
(A desperate competition
for a variety partner begins.)
May I enter?
(They follow their hearts.)
(The ones without a partner
become anxious.)
(They keep making
the wrong choices.)
(I am becoming greedy.)
(The drama that shook up
Variety Show Village.)
(The men compete for Woman Five.)
(A liar and a hypocrite.)
(I am done for.)
(Amidst the confusion,
things become a mess.)
(Who will find
the perfect partner in this jungle?)
(I Want to Find
the Variety Show Partner)