(Spring has come...)
(without telling us
where it came from.)
It's coming.
There it is.
It's here.
(What?)
The cameras are here.
(People with dark clothes
and dark faces)
(Who are they?)
(It's a must for idol stars,
the photoshoot on the way to work.)
(Fans gather together...)
(to appreciate the charm
of their favorite stars.)
(But the photoshoot
for the members of Running Man...)
(only has the production
crew members.)
(And that's not all it is.)
(Dear stylists, this is
the production crew of Running Man.)
(We're going to have a photoshoot
on the way to work.)
(So we'd like you to film
your artists in their cars.)
(Okay. We will!)
(Got it.)
(It's the Running Man
photoshoot on the way to work.)
(How will the members look
on their way to work?)
It's coming.
It's here.
- It's coming.
- So Min!
- So Min.
- She's here.
Look over here.
(The first celebrity to arrive
is Jeon So Min.)
- So Min.
- We love you.
So Min!
- Show us your face!
- So Min.
What is going on? What's that?
I don't have a microphone.
Show us your face.
- So Min!
- What are they doing?
(Fake cheers)
- Jeon So Min!
- So Min, I love you.
What are you guys doing?
You're so pretty.
- You're beautiful.
- So Min!
(So Min starts to respond
to the cheers.)
- Look at us.
- So Min!
What are you doing?
- You're so pretty.
- Please strike a pose for us.
(The top actress gets
off her car.)
(They pretend to cheer for her.)
You're beautiful.
You look stunning.
You look amazing.
- You're so pretty.
- I love you.
(As she strikes some tacky poses,)
(the fans don't know how to react.)
Thank you for waiting for me here
when it's so cold.
Can you hear me?
Hello, everyone.
What are you guys doing here?
What's happening?
What am I supposed to do?
Why are you doing this?
What are we doing? My way to work?
Why are you filming my way to work?
(Song Ji Hyo is coming!)
- Song Ji Hyo is coming.
- No.
What are you doing?
What are you talking about?
What is going on?
(Running toward Ji Hyo)
Guys.
(As they feel uncomfortable around
So Min, Ji Hyo's car pulls over.)
Guys. Why are you filming this?
What's that?
There's Song Ji Hyo!
(Dazed)
- It's Song Ji Hyo.
- Song Ji Hyo is here.
Isn't that So Min over there?
Show us your face.
- Ji Hyo.
- What is going on?
- Hello.
- Ji Hyo.
Ji Hyo!
- Please get off here.
- Ji Hyo.
Ji Hyo, show us your face.
What are you doing now?
- We're filming your way to work.
- Let us see your face.
You're so pretty.
Please strike a pose for us, Ji Hyo.
Pose for us.
(Here you go.)
You have such a pretty face.
What is going on?
We have a lot of fans here.
Are they fans?
There's Sung Oh.
They all are our crew members.
Make a heart for us. Please, for us.
(All right.)
What is this?
Are you filming our way to work?
(The photoshoot of So Min
and Ji Hyo's way to work is done.)
- It's coming.
- My gosh.
It's Kim Jong Kook.
He's Kim Grand Award.
Please get out of the car.
(The third one to arrive
is Kim Jong Kook.)
What's going on?
Kim Jong Kook!
Please show us your face.
Did you guys bet money
on me or something?
Jong Kook, show us your ab muscles.
What are you talking about?
- Show us.
- Please, Jong Kook.
- What are you doing?
- You're so handsome.
Please pose for us.
- Do you want me to do a pose?
- Yes.
(He is obedient to his fans.)
What are we doing?
- Make a heart for us.
- What?
Make a heart.
A heart?
(A heart?)
You're scary.
(He's saying harsh words
behind the mask.)
That's enough. All right.
This is so awkward.
Okay. That's enough.
(Next up is Se Chan.)
Are they fans?
What?
He's getting off.
Yang Se Chan!
Show us your face.
Se Chan, you're so handsome.
Look at your gums.
Show us your gums.
(All the cheering makes
Star Yang freeze.)
- Show us your smile.
- Let us see your gums.
- We want to see your gums.
- Show us your gums.
I didn't brush my teeth yet.
All right.
- You look so cool.
- Strike a pose for us.
Am I doing this right?
You're so handsome.
Please talk to us in English.
- Pardon?
- Speak in English.
Hey, don't make fun of me.
Hi. Thank you.
I love you. Gosh, what's going on?
Please show us your handsome face.
Hey, you are...
You punk! Come here.
What is going on?
Show us Empty Head.
- What about Empty Head?
- Empty Head!
(Empty Head has gotten
a lot of fans already.)
(Empty Head)
What's that? Don't make fun of me.
Don't tease me. I should go.
What is going on?
- We love you.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
(He shows off his gums
making a heart with his fingers.)
(The hope of Empty Heads,
Star Yang with pretty gums is here.)
- It's coming.
(The fifth car is pulling over.)
(Yoo Jae Suk shows up.)
It's Yoo Jae Suk!
- Yoo Jae Suk!
Show us your face.
Jae Suk, show us
the grasshopper dance.
You're so handsome.
Seon Myung, did you say crazy?
(Unlike other stars,
he knows himself very well.)
Seon Myung, what was that?
Strike a pose for us.
Will you stay quiet?
- Take off your mask.
- Do you want to be in trouble?
Hey, do you want me
to teach you a lesson?
I'm going to teach you a lesson.
- What are you guys doing?
- Jae Suk.
Bo Pil, what are you doing now?
- What's going on here?
- We love you.
Hey.
- There's Haha.
- Haha!
Hey!
(Yoo Jae Suk is out.)
- Haha!
- Hey. What do you want?
This is mine. Why would I
give this to you?
Why do you want my microphone?
So what is going on?
- Haha.
- You're so cool.
- Pose for the camera.
Strike a pose for us.
I love your pants.
Hang on. I'm not ready yet.
I'm not ready for this.
- What's that?
- It's Kwang Soo!
What are you doing?
- What is going on?
- What's all this?
- It's Lee Kwang Soo.
- He's getting off.
Show us the mosquito dance.
- What?
- The mosquito dance.
Show us the mosquito dance.
- Mosquito dance?
- It's Seon Myung.
- Hey.
- And there's Hyung In.
Please strike a pose
for the cameras.
(These 3 members are known
to be bad at posing.)
(Kwang Soo, try doing ET hands.)
Kwang Soo, try doing ET hands.
(Kwang Soo's specialty,
the trivet hand)
- It looks like an alien.
- You look great.
(The 3 ugly celebrities)
They're filming something.
(Suk Jin is
the last one to show up.)
What's going on?
I'm not ready yet.
It's Suk Jin.
- Suk Jin is here.
- It's Suk Jin.
- Kwang Soo.
- Do you have any raw eggs?
Did we get here on time?
Are we here too early?
(The stylist is acting.)
- Ji Suk Jin.
- What was that?
- Do you want me to get off?
- Yes.
Ji Suk Jin.
I'm not wearing makeup.
- Look at his white pants!
- You look great.
We love you.
I'm not ready yet.
You look amazing.
- You're so cool.
- You're the best.
What are we doing?
Strike a pose for us.
A pose? Gosh.
Show us the moonwalk.
- Big Nose.
- You look amazing.
Hey. What are you doing?
- Hey.
- Bye.
What are you doing?
The stocks fell again today.
How are you feeling?
I feel terrible. See you.
Have a nice day. See you.
(The door is open again.)
Hey!
(White Pants gets off again.)
My gosh.
(Mr. White Pants gives up
and comes back right away.)
(The door is open again.)
(Morning rage)
I can't believe this.
Hey, get out of the car.
Get off. I'll drive.
(What?)
Hey!
You little...
(The photoshoot of his way
to work is over like that.)
- He's wearing white pants.
- I can't believe this.
(The photoshoot of the 8 members
is over with Mr. White Pants.)
Done.
It's over.
(Now they change clothes
to shoot the opening.)
- Why are you doing this?
- What?
You have 30 years of experience.
You don't need a funny outfit.
Let's hurry and start the opening.
- The audio is...
- Hello.
- What's wrong?
- Just stand here.
- Let's begin.
- Hello.
- Start.
- Suk Jin.
- Gosh, Suk Jin.
- You look like No-Face.
- What's wrong with him?
I think he put it on
so we can make fun of him.
- Suk Jin.
- Gosh, Suk Jin.
- What?
- You look like No-Face.
What's wrong?
Do you not know
anything about fashion?
It's not like that.
Fashion is all about new challenges.
- Challenge.
- You shouldn't feel ashamed.
- You look like Piccolo.
- Don't laugh at me.
- He's more flushed than ever.
- No, that's not true.
I don't know what to say.
I can't even make fun of you.
Look at the other
stylists over there.
They're shocked.
- Look at Eun Ju and...
- The other stylists...
Even a rookie comedian
wouldn't wear something like that.
You should bring outfits like this.
They look too conservative.
- This is a weekend variety show.
- This is just too much.
It's not too much.
It's true that fashion
is all about new challenges.
Let me hang my jacket
on your shoulder.
My gosh.
(It's the new human hanger
for SS season in 2021.)
- My gosh.
- I mean...
And it's hanging so well.
- It works well.
- It is a good hanger though.
(Piccolo bursts into laughter
looking at his shoulder.)
What is this?
- Gosh.
- Seriously...
- This is...
- It doesn't slip.
It's still there.
- I'm serious.
Maybe Suk Jin wanted
to wear this himself.
It doesn't look good on him though.
The thing is...
We got this jacket sponsored.
So?
(He can even use the shoulders
like a chin-up bar.)
- I can hang on his shoulder.
- Are you wearing it right?
- Are you wearing it properly?
- Yes.
Can I do chin-ups
with your shoulders?
Is it supposed
to make you look taller?
The weather is warm now,
so my stylist thought...
today would be my last chance
to try this one.
- You should wear it.
- The jacket looks good.
(While they just nod along
with Suk Jin's excuses...)
(People start to scream.)
Someone's here.
What's wrong with him?
- What's going on?
- Is that your cameraman, Kwang Soo?
- He just left.
- It's Brave Girls!
- What?
- Is Brave Girls here?
(Brave Girls?)
(The reason the cameramen just
left their spot during the opening)
- Hello.
- Please look over here.
Please look at the camera.
("Rollin'" by Brave Girls made
a comeback on the music charts...)
(thanks to the power of soldiers.)
(They became popular with a song
released 4 years ago...)
(thanks to the power of K-Army.)
(Eun Ji, Yoo Na, Yoo Jeong, Min Young)
(Big Eyes Queen, Bobbed-hair Queen,
Squirtle Queen, Vocal Queen)
(They are the real stars
for the heated photoshoot.)
- Brave Girls!
- What's going on?
They're Brave Girls.
Rollin', rollin', rollin'
(They join Running Man
after the photo time.)
(He's serious about "Rollin'.")
This is so nice.
Come on here.
It's Brave Girls who sang "Rollin'."
Hurry and come up on here.
Rollin', rollin', rollin'
(This is the real "Rollin'.")
This is it.
This is really popular.
("Rollin'" by Brave Girls)
- Baby!
(They will never forget today,
the day they met Brave Girls.)
Get ready.
Let's get ready to dance.
Everyday.
- Everyday
Let's go!
Rollin', rollin', rollin'
(They feel great joy
listening to the killer chorus.)
- Hey!
Get ready to dance like this.
- The stingray dance.
- The stingray dance. Let's go.
(Here's the stingray.)
Let's go.
(The seafood guys...)
(and dancing stingrays join them.)
(This is how the military stars have
become the nation's beloved stars.)
(The Vocal Queen's finale)
(They topped music charts
with a song released 4 years ago.)
(They're the popular idol group,
Brave Girls.)
Brave Girls!
All right, everyone.
After four years,
they made a splendid comeback
on music charts.
- Congratulations.
- They never die.
- It calls for celebration.
- Sure.
- It's amazing.
- They're Brave Girls.
- 1, 2, and 3.
- Hello, we're Brave Girls.
They must've been through a lot.
Actually, I met them...
on another show.
It's been two weeks.
And they've changed a lot
only in two weeks.
Like how?
- In general...
- Their vibe?
- I can tell their agency...
- The agency's support?
is supporting them a lot.
- Is that true?
- Yes. Sure.
Things have changed a lot
at our agency.
The microphone.
You're not performing
at a military camp.
This isn't a military camp.
You don't need the microphones.
Things have changed a lot
at our agency.
People from our agency are
monitoring us for the first time.
That's right.
- Are they monitoring you?
- Yes.
So...
Other than what Squirtle Queen said,
what else has changed, Min Young?
We don't have to be
on a diet anymore.
The CEO...
Honestly, the CEO is
the one who's fat.
(Honestly, the CEO is
the one who's fat.)
(They feel liberated.)
Is he your age?
- Yes. We're friends.
- Really?
- Brave Brother.
- He's my friend.
He was so happy
that he called me dead drunk.
- To people around him...
- Because he was happy?
- Yes.
- He's really excited.
- He is.
- So the thing is,
it's been six years
since their debut.
And this is their first appearance
on a TV variety show.
- That's right.
- Is that true?
This is the variety show
we've always wanted to join.
We talked about Running Man a lot.
We're honored.
(Thank you, Brave Girls.)
Let's be honest.
You wanted to see us, right?
- Yes.
- I see.
(He sounds so brazen
just like his high shoulders.)
Shoulder King, stay out of this.
Shoulder King, stay quiet.
- Here we go again.
- Let me shake hands with you.
- Okay.
- Power shoulders.
I like your jacket.
- Today...
- Your jacket is...
I heard we'd have
Brave Girls here today.
(They're flustered by his fashion.)
He just asked me...
- what Squirtle Queen means.
- When I heard about Brave Girls...
"What does Squirtle Queen mean?"
He asked, "What does
Squirtle Queen mean?"
So I told him
that it means crossing legs.
He did say that.
He doesn't know anything.
Do you know what it means?
- You're unbelievable.
Today, we're going to have
A Day of Brave Idol Stars Race...
where you can experience
a day of popular idol stars...
with the popular idol group,
Brave Girls.
You will carry out missions
as an idol group of four.
After each mission, you will get
trophies according to the results.
- First place gets five trophies.
- We'll be idol groups.
Second place gets three.
And third place gets one trophy.
And the trophies you win...
will be distributed according to
the seniority decided by the leader.
Really?
(The trophies are distributed
as instructed by the leader.)
The three members with
the most trophies will get prizes.
And the three with the fewest
trophies will get a penalty.
Three people will get a penalty.
That's a lot.
But you're supposed to experience
a day of popular idol stars today.
So the missions will be
judged like music shows.
The winners won't be decided
only by the results of the missions.
We will have special judges
to give you points...
which will be applied
to the results.
Aren't the judges our crew members?
So it's important to gain
favor with the judges.
We've divided you into three groups.
- Okay.
- All right. Tell us.
The first group is...
Yoo Jeong, Jae Suk,
Kwang Soo, and Ji Hyo.
(Idol Group No.1: Yoo Jeong,
Jae Suk, Kwang Soo, Ji Hyo)
The first group is Min Young,
Jong Kook, So Min, and Haha.
Okay.
- Good.
- The third group is...
Eun Ji, Yoo Na, Suk Jin,
and Se Chan.
Okay.
(Idol Group No.3: Eun Ji, Yoo Na,
Suk Jin, Se Chan)
Is he our CEO?
Is that it?
We don't need him as our member.
The CEO can't perform on stage.
(That's how they got
three idol groups.)
Now I want you
to choose your team leader.
The leader won't change today.
- It won't change?
- Really?
They should be the leaders.
You don't want
to be the leader, do you?
Come here.
- I want to be the leader.
- You can be the leader.
- Eun Ji is the leader.
- Eun Ji is our leader.
Squirtle Queen is our leader.
And Vocal Queen should
be our leader.
All right. I'll give you
the first trophies right away.
Right now?
Do you remember the photoshoot
you had when you got here today?
The top three members
with the best photos...
will get one trophy each.
- I was too shy.
- I should've done it right.
First, I'll show you
each of your best shots.
- This looks so good.
- I look like a celebrity.
This is so pretty.
When did they take pictures of me?
Here are the top three.
(Who are the top three
chosen by the SBS PR Team?)
It's me.
So Min deserves it.
Oh, Squirtle Queen.
(These three idols looked confident
on their way to work.)
The top three members
with the best shots...
will get this.
- Thank you.
You get one trophy each.
- It's not for my team?
- They get it personally.
Is this for me?
- Gosh, thank you.
- I don't share it with my team.
Let's begin the first mission then.
- Right away?
- This is the quality idols need.
For the first mission, you should
show off your versatile talents.
It's called the Brave Showcase.
Brave Girls prepared
their specialties for today.
We will have a showcase
where you can show your talents.
And you will get
5, 3, and 1 trophies each...
according to the results
of the showcase.
When the four rounds are over,
the winners will be decided...
by the points you win...
and the scores of the 20 judges
who are reservists...
- and civil defense members.
- Okay.
Staff members who are reservists
and civil defense members.
For your information,
the judges have label stickers.
- That's right.
- It says "reservist."
They will give you scores.
I'm no longer a member
of the civil defense.
Me neither.
(It's important to get
good scores from the judges.)
All right
I didn't know I'd be wearing
this jacket for such a long time.
- It's heavy, isn't it?
- It doesn't seem to end.
I should change my clothes
after the opening.
It's not heavy.
Suk Jin says his shoulders hurt.
(Usually, the opening would end now,
and they would get changed.)
(Suk Jin became impatient
as it went on for longer.)
- Hey.
- You can do whatever you want.
(Actually, earlier on...)
- Won't we get changed, Kwang Soo?
- the winners will be decided...
- Won't we? Why won't this end?
- by the points you win...
(Giggling)
- I heard that we won't get changed.
- Really?
(They will play the games
in their opening outfits unusually.)
The first round is dance,
which is Min Young's special talent.
(Team Main Vocalist,
Specialty: dance, majored in dance)
The team whose members danced...
in the most creative way using one
of the items in front of you wins.
- It's difficult.
- For example...
Can we go first?
- It's better to go first.
- Yoo Na.
- Okay. Go ahead.
- It's always better to go first.
- Is that a sword?
- Yes, I brought it.
We'll dance now.
Min Young will start dancing.
Play an upbeat song.
- Is she going to do a sword dance?
- Let's go!
(She's starting doing
a powerful sword dance.)
What's that?
- She's incredible.
- Go, Min Young!
(She's dancing like crazy
with two swords.)
Faster.
(She's dancing excitedly
as if she'd cut everything.)
I've never seen anything
like this before.
(No other idols have demonstrated
a sword dance before!)
- Gosh. What is she doing?
- She's drunk.
- She's a girl in a nightclub.
- What's that?
- A drunkard is here!
- She's in a nightclub.
- Oh, a nightclub?
- Drink up!
(The drunk girl is enjoying herself
in a nightclub as always.)
(She's looking for a life companion
while drinking alcohol.)
- She's so drunk.
- There she goes!
(The song is reaching its climax
as she gets more and more excited!)
(Throwing up!)
(It's what often happens
in real life.)
- Is she throwing up?
- Oh, she's throwing up?
That's a good one.
(It's exciting.)
(Whispering)
Let's just throw water
at each other.
That'd be the best. Let's do that.
Is this what you want to see?
- You should've told us sooner.
- We'll give it a try.
- We'll do it.
- It's easy to pretend to throw up.
- We'll do it again.
- We'll all take off our shirts.
- They're taken aback.
- Okay. Play a similar song for us.
- Jump in whenever you want.
- Okay.
He's coming.
Is he entering the club?
(The seductive man is entering.)
(I'll show you.)
What's with your face?
(Shaking hips)
(Yang Ssaebssaeb is dancing
like a fish in water.)
What's going on? What's this?
(He's imitating a parvenu dancing
in a nightclub for the first time.)
(But then Shoulder King showed up
with a sword.)
(He assassinated Se Chan
while he was making everyone laugh.)
(What?)
(He has a feeling
that this will fail somehow.)
(Suk Jin is pretending
he's excited.)
(The illogical twist
of the story...)
(made everyone stop cheering.)
- That's all. Thank you.
- You should've killed me at once.
- I don't think that went well.
- You should've killed at once.
You should've killed me
with one blow.
Why? It was okay.
Stabbing me three times
didn't look good.
Honestly, it was funny
until Suk Jin showed up.
Why did you bring a sword?
(He killed the mood
with his sword as well.)
- It'll be funny when it airs.
- It's okay. Don't worry.
Gosh, seriously.
I'm worried. What do we do?
We'll play the music now.
(Team Squirtle is under a lot of
pressure as it's the last team.)
- I'll just follow you.
- Here they go!
(Yoo Jeong stepped up!)
(Twerking)
Yoo Jeong is doing great.
She's such a great dancer.
Let's go!
- Her outfit, I mean.
- Awesome!
Come on. Twerk with her!
Ji Hyo, go ahead and twerk!
Ji Hyo, just do as she does.
That's good.
(Wiggling)
(She's flapping as if there's
something wrong with her.)
Ji Hyo.
(An executioner with a sword
appeared to stop her.)
- That's so funny.
- We did well.
- Yoo Jeong, you did a good job.
- We're done.
We've done everything we could do.
Look. Jong Kook is showcasing
his special talent.
- Stand in line. He might kill us.
- That's cool.
(He's showcasing his real talent.)
He looks like Na Han Il, the founder
of the Haidong Gumdo Association.
We're tallying the scores
of the people in the reserve.
The winning team
of the first round is...
(The creativity is most important!)
(Which team could win
and get five points?)
- Team Main Vocalist.
- I knew it.
(Team Main Vocalist wins.)
- What should we do?
- Why? Oh, I get it.
- The vomiting performance?
- That and the sword dance.
I approve.
(Everyone accepts the result.)
- The second round is...
- Yes.
- the big eyes contest.
- I see. But it's...
- We'll definitely win this round.
- But...
The big eyes contest.
- We'll definitely lose.
- Our team...
- It's...
We have Jae Suk... I mean,
Jong Kook is on our team.
We lost.
I think you don't even have to
open your eyes widely to win.
We'll measure the vertical length
of your eyes.
The person with the highest result
wins.
- Like this?
- Is using hands not allowed?
Sorry? Correct. You're not allowed
to use your hands.
You should open them widely.
- My, what big eyes you have.
- She has such big eyes.
She has really big eyes.
- Kwang Soo also has big eyes.
- I have big eyes.
(Opening his eyes widely)
- He has big eyes.
- His eyes are...
- bigger than I thought they were.
- He has big eyes.
- He does have big eyes.
- Bring it on.
None of them can beat her.
We'll measure the eyes
of the challengers first.
- Kwang Soo will go first.
- Okay.
He has large eyes.
Oh, gosh. Kwang Soo.
- Let me see.
- Kwang Soo...
- Hands off.
- You can't use your hands.
- They're so big.
- Indeed.
(They're frightened by the mad look
on his face.)
- Oh, goodness.
- My gosh. Look at him.
- Stay still.
- Why am I feeling so dizzy?
I'll look.
Open them as wide as you can.
(He used every muscle in his face
he could use.)
- 2cm. It's 2cm.
- 2cm. Yes, 2cm.
- 2cm.
- It's 2cm.
- We might win.
- 2cm.
- So Min has big eyes too.
- I wonder if she can win.
- So Min has really big eyes.
- Also, I have...
- bulging eyes.
- She has big eyes.
Really?
- Measure it right away, okay?
- I'll do that.
(How big could Big Eyes Queen
on Running Man So Min's eyes be?)
(The aggressively bulging eyes)
She looks scary.
My gosh. Look at her.
- She has really big eyes.
- She has very big eyes.
- Her eyes are so big.
- Please.
- They look like they'll pop out.
- That's why she's called a frog.
It's 1.9cm. 1.9cm.
(It's 0.1cm shorter
than Kwang Soo's.)
- 0.1cm. You can check it yourself.
- Really?
- Yes.
- They're so big.
- Jong Kook, you should try it.
- Jong Kook, give it a go.
- You should.
- What? Are you teasing him?
- Let's do this.
Nothing's impossible.
- I have big eyes.
- I know.
- Let me see.
- People just don't know that.
They might be hidden somewhere.
Let's check it.
- Give me just a second.
- Okay.
(Breathing in)
(He's opening his eyes
as wide as possible.)
1cm.
(It's bigger than I thought though.)
I just said the truth.
Only 1cm?
- 1cm?
- Hey, I was quite generous.
(Meanwhile, Kwang Soo and Se Chan
are cooking up a ruse.)
To make my eye look like it's open
when it's actually closed.
(He probably asked for this.)
Okay. Done.
You can close this eye.
Try closing it.
- Did you draw the pupil too?
- Of course.
No. It doesn't look like an eye.
It doesn't look like an eye.
- They're not as big as I thought.
- You punk.
(Se Chan scribbled on his eyelid
and ran away.)
Now...
Kwang Soo had a fake eye drawn
on his face.
What's that?
(The problem is that it doesn't
look like an eye at all.)
What's with that eye?
- Why is the eye so big?
- My gosh.
- Kwang Soo's result is 2cm.
- 2cm.
- I think I'm done for.
- Why?
- It's Eun Ji's turn now.
- I just measured it,
- and it's not as big as I thought.
- Don't worry.
- Eun Ji, it's your turn.
- Let's try it again.
- Eun Ji is the last one to go.
- Eun Ji.
- Be confident.
- Big Eyes Queen.
I'm sure it's longer than 2cm.
- Her eyes are unbelievably big.
- Eun Ji, look up.
Chin down, and look up.
- Chin down.
- No.
- Look up. That's good.
- Look up.
Yes. That makes it bigger.
(Kwang Soo is in first place. What
could Big Eyes Queen's result be?)
I'm sure it's longer than 3cm.
It's about 1.9cm.
- No way.
- Check yourself. It's about 1.9cm.
- Kwang Soo wins?
- Then Kwang Soo is the winner.
- Yes, he's the winner.
- Eun Ji, look up.
I don't believe it.
(Suk Jin is measuring it again
to be fair.)
I don't believe it.
- It's shorter than 2cm.
- Hey.
- Then our team...
- Come here.
- Kwang Soo...
- Oh, my.
- Oh, no.
- I'll measure his eye again too.
- Vocal Queen.
- Please measure it accurately.
I think I should try it again.
Maybe your eyes are
horizontally long.
(He's giving it his all.)
How could his eye be 2cm long?
Maybe they're horizontally long.
(Laughing)
- It really is 2cm.
- Is it really 2cm? Are you sure?
- Give me another chance.
- Is it really 2cm long?
Do I really have bigger eyes
than her?
- My eyes are bigger than hers?
- This is hilarious.
- Kwang Soo.
- I beat them all.
- That's unbelievable.
- Give me another chance.
I have really big eyes.
I have bigger eyes
than Big Eyes Queen!
Isn't it that his skin stretches
well, not that his eyes are big?
- Eun Ji's result is about 1.9cm.
- Wait.
- Let me try it again.
- Measure it again.
- This is your last chance.
- I'm sure it's longer than 2cm.
- This is your last chance, Eun Ji.
- You can do this!
Big Eyes Queen!
- Her eyes look so big.
- Look up.
- Try to open them more widely.
- Eun Ji.
Her eyes take up half of her face.
- That's not good enough.
- Oh, my gosh.
That's not how you should use
your eye muscles.
- You can't get a good result.
- By the way...
You know, Eun Ji...
That will become a meme.
(Mad Eyes King)
Is it really 2cm long?
(It's 2cm long no matter how many
times they measure it.)
- It's true. It's 2cm.
- I think my eyes got bigger.
- Okay!
- We lost.
I'll explain.
Eun Ji, you do have bigger eyes
than him,
but you just can't open your eyes
like he does.
You shouldn't just open them
like you did.
Your eyes look...
Your eyes look much bigger than his
when they're normally opened.
(He's showing his skill
that helped him win.)
- Team Squirtle wins.
- Okay!
(Team Squirtle wins thanks to
Kwang Soo's mad eyes.)
That was awesome.
(It's time for the third round!)
The third round is
Yoo Jeong's special talent.
Singing any songs sadly.
- Yes.
- Sounds good.
- Singing an exciting song sadly?
- Yes.
Regardless of the genre, the person
whose song sounds the saddest wins.
Okay.
Before we begin,
Yoo Jeong will demonstrate it.
- Okay. Yes.
- Yoo Jeong, show us how to do it.
She always smiles
and looks so cheerful,
- but she sings songs sadly?
- She's versatile.
She's unpredictable.
Then...
I'll sing one of our songs
"We Ride."
"We Ride" is an exciting song.
("We Ride" is a refreshing
city pop song.)
(She smiles more cheerfully
especially when she performs it.)
(How will Squirtle Queen
who always smiles sing it sadly?)
(She's immersing herself
in emotion.)
(However, it doesn't sound
very sad.)
(Everyone is forcing themselves
to feel sad.)
(Sad thoughts, sad thoughts,
sad thoughts)
Squirtle Queen!
(Stop it!)
(The party lovers who are still
excited started dancing too.)
Squirtle Queen!
- It sounded so sad.
- It was so sad.
It was so sad that I almost cried.
- Ji Hyo, you almost cried?
- I almost cried.
- Is that true?
- Can't you see my teary eyes?
Ji Hyo actually teared up.
- Do you want to hear a sad song?
- Yes.
It's easy.
- Go, Se Chan!
- Se Chan will sing?
We'll show you sadness.
(Wailing)
The song title is...
He's crying already.
He started crying
even before starting singing.
He's going to sing
"Gee" by Girls' Generation.
I'll sing a song for you.
- He's crying.
- My gosh.
(He's planning to make everyone
laugh until they start crying.)
(He's already crying.)
(He'll sing "Gee" feeling sad.)
He's just crying.
He's not singing sadly.
You are so beautiful
I can't look you in the eyes
You take my breath away
Gee, gee, gee, gee, baby, baby
(Crying his heart out)
- I can't even look at you
- Look at his face.
He looks so ugly.
You just look like an idiot.
(He's just a sad idiot.)
Hey, that's not... Seriously...
- Why?
- That's not...
- It's sad.
- singing sadly.
- Why?
- It sounds sad.
- You just cried while singing.
- I cried because it was sad.
- That's not right.
- It was sad.
- We're all so sad.
- Don't be ridiculous.
Se Chan, can you come out
while crying again?
(The sad idiot appears again.)
(Please... Give me the mic.)
You make my heart flutter
Whenever I see you
My heart pounds
I'm so sad right now.
- My gosh. I can't believe you.
- That was so funny.
- He looked so ugly.
- My gosh.
You can't cry while singing
to make it sad.
- He made us want to cry too.
- I teared up.
That was awesome.
He made me cry.
- We all burst into tears.
- I cried too.
- So Min will go first.
- Okay.
- What song should I sing?
- She's full of emotions now.
Watch carefully. Look at her face.
- She'll cry too.
- She'll cry in ten seconds.
(What is she going to do?)
Looking here
(Sobbing)
Looking there
- She's actually crying.
- Isn't she just crying?
Look at this.
- She actually cried tears.
- She's acting.
- Look at this.
- My goodness!
(Surprised)
She's acting.
That's just acting.
She's acting, not singing.
(She's singing the song from "Dooly
the Little Dinosaur" in tears.)
She actually cried.
(Jae Suk started dancing
to make her laugh.)
(Wailing)
(But she doesn't care
and even started wailing.)
Why do you have to do that?
I don't understand. Why...
- What is this?
- It's so exciting.
(The dance of satisfaction)
- She actually cried.
- My goodness.
(So Min's acting was
fit for a serious drama.)
Good job. We win.
- She cried.
- How does she cry in ten seconds?
- It's okay.
- She's incredible.
- She's currently in first place.
- Her facial expression was good.
- I'm so sad.
- Of course, it was sad.
- It was so sad.
- She cried while singing.
- We need a plan.
- You're right.
We win.
- Yoo Jeong.
- Yes?
- Do you think you can cry?
- No, I can't.
I'm sorry. I can't cry.
I know I should cry, but I can't.
I think Jae Suk can make us sad
by singing without his glasses.
Right. That will be so sad.
I'll be sad too.
It'll be really sad
if he takes off his cap and glasses.
- I'll sing.
- He already looks sad.
(He decided to take off his glasses
to save his team.)
He looks so sad. My gosh.
It's sad because he's ugly.
I felt sad once he took off
his glasses.
It's sad because he's ugly.
Can you play the song I want?
- What song?
- It's god's song.
- When will you start singing?
- You should sing.
- I know I should sing.
- Oh, gosh.
- Hold on a second.
- Stop acting. You should sing.
You see...
"Love and Remember."
"Love and Remember?"
That song is actually sad.
You're supposed to sing
an exciting song.
You should choose an exciting song.
This game is about singing
a song that's not sad in a sad way.
He doesn't follow the rules.
Don't talk to me.
I'm trying to get into emotion.
His face looks even uglier now.
- He's being aggressive.
- My gosh.
- What a mess.
- He rarely acts like this.
This is a total mess.
Doesn't he look weird?
Come here.
Come and look at his face.
- He looks so weird.
- He looks sad.
Now I see why people can't recognize
Superman when he's wearing glasses.
The intro alone makes me so sad.
(How will he make this sad song
sound even sadder?)
Shouldn't he start singing?
Shouldn't he sing?
- What are you doing?
- What's this?
He's even lip-syncing!
- god! god!
- Oh, my gosh.
That's ridiculous. What is he doing?
- What is this?
- You're supposed to sing.
This is just "The Yoo Jae Suk Show!"
What's this?
- Cut it out!
- He's lip-syncing. Gosh.
What are you doing?
Gosh. What is he doing?
His face looks sad though.
What's that?
Your face makes us so sad.
Watching you makes us feel sad.
(He suddenly lied down.)
My gosh.
Why is he lying on the ground?
You shouldn't sleep here.
You shouldn't... Excuse me.
Look at Chan Hee.
He put his camera on his shoulder.
- Chan Hee is going to...
- He'll show his skills.
It reminded him of old memories.
Chan Hee started filming him
in the old-fashioned style.
(Chan Hee's camera)
Do you call this
singing a song sadly?
You should sing it sadly.
Gosh. What are you doing?
I think we should stop him.
- Jae Suk, stop it.
- You should stop him.
Jae Suk, come on.
- Right.
- Jae Suk, come on.
(The overly excited man is
being dragged out.)
That was funny.
- Jae Suk, pull yourself together.
- Slap me.
Okay.
(He finally pulled himself together
after a slap.)
What's wrong with him?
- Chan Hee...
- You should've sung it sadly.
Chan Hee, I'm disappointed by you.
I only grabbed you lightly.
- Did you really have to do that?
- He gets upset about everything.
I'm really upset.
- Why are you always so upset?
- How could he do that to me?
- It was a close call.
- I see.
- We had a discussion.
- I bet So Min won.
Although some of you won't be
happy about the result,
- Team Squirtle wins.
- Yes!
- But...
- He lip-synced...
- I love you
- Why?
- Right.
- He didn't even sing.
He just acted.
Chan Hee, you did a great job.
We made a great team.
I liked the way you pushed me away
with an annoyed look on your face.
He practically twisted your arm.
That's when your performance
became sad.
(The performance with Chan Hee
was the game changer.)
You did a great job.
Your mission scores came out.
We're waiting on the reservists
and civil defense members' scores.
- We might get a high score.
- We did well.
Oh, right. I forgot about that.
It's practically a popularity poll.
- The result came out.
- Let's go!
First of all, the mission scores...
I'll announce the team
in third place...
- based on the total scores.
- The team in third place.
(Team Big Eyes, Team Squirtle,
Team Main Vocalist)
- Okay!
- Our team?
- Yes.
- We're in third place.
- Gosh.
One of the remaining teams is
in first place.
- We're in third place.
- Okay.
- We'll show you the result now.
The team in second place is...
(Team Big Eyes, Team Squirtle,
Team Main Vocalist)
(Team Main Vocalist: 1st place,
Team Squirtle: 2nd place)
Really? Hey, we're the winning team.
- It's hard to believe.
- I'm so happy.
- We're the most popular team.
- Exactly.
I can't... Oh, my. I'm excited.
- This is awesome.
- It's because of her sword dance.
As a result, this team
is the winning team.
Team Main Vocalist.
Team Squirtle is in 2nd place,
and Team Big Eyes is in 3rd place.
- It's okay.
- I can't accept it though.
It's time for you to distribute
the trophies you earned.
The team leaders should decide
the order of getting trophies.
- Can the leader be the first?
- Of course.
So she can get as many trophies
as she wants.
The winner has 5, 2nd place has 3,
and 3rd place has 1.
The team leaders, please announce
the first person to go.
Well... Kwang Soo...
- Yoo Jeong, wait.
- Okay!
- Oh, no. That was a mistake.
- Hey, wait. Not yet.
(The big mistake
that Yoo Jeong made...)
(gave Kwang Soo
a great opportunity.)
- Not yet.
- She'll choose again?
- We'll start over again.
- Come back.
- Hey, Yoo Jeong.
- She changed her mind.
- Why, Yoo Jeong?
- You almost made a big mistake.
- I was going to take just one.
- Yoo Jeong.
She made a mistake.
- Yoo Jeong, you made a big mistake.
- You're right.
- Right.
- I forgot.
Then I'll let Ji Hyo go first.
- Me?
- Yes.
Who goes next?
- Don't you think...
- You should go next.
- Okay. And then you go next.
- You go after her.
I'll be the 3rd,
and he'll be the 4th.
What changed your mind?
You picked me first earlier.
- Drop it.
- Have you all made your decisions?
Just follow the leader's decisions.
- I just want to know why.
- It's up to her.
Right. She should decide the order
as our leader.
The first members,
please step forward.
- Ji Hyo.
- Yes.
The leader gets two...
Eun Ji, you can leave it in the box.
You can take it or not.
It's up to you.
You can leave it there
for your team members.
You can take all of them
if you want.
- Take as many as you want.
- Absolutely.
- It sparkled... Gosh.
- Oh, boy.
(She tried to take it secretly
but dropped it in front of them.)
- She dropped it. My gosh.
- She dropped it.
She dropped it.
- Next.
- We don't even have to go.
- Put it back in there.
- Go on.
I'll be reasonable
and conscientious.
- You didn't take too many, right?
- No.
Next, step forward.
(Kwang Soo, the last person
from his team...)
(tries to find a trophy in the box.)
(Empty)
(Oh, I get it.)
(So this is how you'll do it.)
I didn't get any either.
It was already empty.
- Really?
- Yes.
(I'm sorry, Kwang Soo.)
- We have the most trophies, right?
- Yes.
Yes. We have five.
You take 2 as the leader
and give 1 to each of us.
2 for the leader,
and 1 for each of us.
- Okay?
- Yes. That'd be fair.
Take 2 and give 1 to each of us.
- You're so pretty.
- That'd be really nice.
Must I show them
how many I'm taking out?
No, you can put them
in your bag secretly.
You shouldn't let us know.
- I trust you.
- Take it.
Oh, she's taking one more out.
Stop.
You're taking too many
when you're the first to go.
- She's taking too many...
- Oh, man. I hear them clattering.
- So Min.
- I told you not to do that.
Min Young made a good plan.
- I chose So Min.
- She'll put blame on So Min.
Is that right?
So Min, I heard them clattering.
- I have only 1.
- Let me have 1 too.
You received one
before we began the missions.
- Who's going next?
- Who is next?
(Jong Kook is the third.)
It's taking him so long.
- Hey, do you still believe her?
- Come back, Jong Kook.
We've been doing this
for over ten years.
- It wasn't me. Trust me.
- I'll rip off the bottom.
Oh, I see. I guess...
- you're still holding onto hope.
- It was Min Young.
My gosh. How could they do this?
(Chuckling)
- Gosh.
- Jong Kook, I took only one.
It's already empty? That's so mean.
- We told Min Young to do...
- This is how we...
everything she wanted, and she
actually followed our advice.
- That's not true. It wasn't me.
- My gosh.
Now, we'll move
to the next location.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
We rarely wear...
our opening outfits
for so long like today.
- Exactly.
- I didn't expect this.
I know, right? It's nice.
Just so you know,
apart from Min Young,
the other had already
moved out of their house.
What do you mean by "moved out?"
To look for another career path.
They were close to
quitting this industry.
- To get another job,
- That's sad to hear.
- Yoo Jeong studied for a test.
- Right.
- She studied Korean history.
- Really?
- Yes, Korean history.
- She took classes.
But then your song
received an explosive response.
They were all getting ready
for a new chapter in their lives,
but things took a 180 turn
because of that one video.
Jae Suk once looked
for part-time jobs too.
- Right.
- He was thinking about quitting.
- After becoming a comedian?
- Yes, after.
Suk Jin, what were you going to do
after quitting Running Man?
- Yes, tell us.
- What?
What were you going to do?
Suk Jin took an interest
in real estate.
Real estate?
- But...
- Don't you need money for that?
What's the point in just looking?
There's no need to worry about me.
Worry more about yourselves.
Why would you worry about me?
- Did you just get angry with us?
- Why do you sound annoyed?
I wasn't annoyed.
That was me just voicing my opinion.
No, you were annoyed just now.
My tone was elevated, that's all.
Let's take a short break.
Your identity's crumbling.
- You were annoyed just now.
- You were.
- I wasn't.
- But you were.
Thanks to Brave Girls being here...
Gosh, thank you.
- Your mother must be thrilled.
- She is.
Of course, she is.
Yoo Jeong cried her eyes out
while holding onto her mom.
Who did?
They're all in their 30s now.
- You're older than I thought.
- Exactly.
That's why I find this more amazing.
How nice is it to see people...
find their big break in their 30s?
- It really is cool.
- Thank you.
You're giving hope
to the youngsters of this era.
Why don't we eat quietly?
(He stops Suk Jin
from saying anything more.)
(Suk Jin's patronizing words
are stopped.)
Who was that?
Who talked while eating?
He even described them
as youngsters.
- Youngsters.
- He's right.
And now Suk Jin eats quietly.
If you see me
raising my hands at them,
just think that it was inevitable.
- What was that?
- If I hit them...
Min Young thinks he's the funniest.
- Suk Jin?
- Yes.
He is.
He's been enjoying
his heyday recently.
- It's the Ji Suk Jin Show.
- You know...
- He's had a major resurgence.
- It's true, Yoo Jeong.
- That's right.
- A major resurgence.
- Suk Jin...
- He's had a major resurgence.
We made it happen for him.
The more he ages,
the more childish he becomes.
He gives hope
to youngsters of this world.
Today, you're the members
of a popular K-pop group.
- A four-member group.
- Right.
Just like the nicknames
the members of Brave Girls have,
let's come up with one
for all of you.
We said a few earlier.
- He's Gum King.
- Gum King.
I'm Gum King.
(Pinkish Gum King)
- Gum King.
- Gum King?
- Yes, Gum King.
How is that so funny?
Don't bother memorizing that.
- Gum King.
- You could be...
Call me Nose King.
But you were Shoulder King.
- No, wait.
- I took off that jacket.
- Nose King.
- Nose King?
- Sleep if you're tired.
Ji Hyo is Enough Queen.
- Enough Queen.
- It suits her.
- So Min's the Nutty Queen.
- Nutty Queen.
Jae Suk can be Citron King.
And Haha...
So Min named me Citron King.
- What's that?
- Citron is "yuja" in Korean.
I'm Citron King
because my name sounds like "yuja."
(Citron King, Nutty Queen,
Enough Queen)
What about Kwang Soo?
- Kwang Soo?
- Just Han Ki Bum.
Long King.
- Long King?
- Yes, Long King.
- Call him Long King.
- Then I'll be Short King.
- Short King!
Short King.
(Han Ki Bum's brother Long King,
The short Short King)
- He's Muscle King.
- Muscle King.
(The protein-loving Muscle King)
Shouldn't he be Muscle Queen?
- Muscle Queen!
- Muscle King.
(She seems like a talented golfer.)
Since you all have your nicknames,
we'll play a game with them.
A game?
With the nicknames
coined with love by your fans,
you'll play
Nickname Frying Pan Game.
Play Nickname Frying Pan Game...
with the nicknames
you gave yourselves.
- I'm terrible at games like this.
- You'll also...
be using the beat
in the strawberry game,
as in 1, 2, 3, 4.
Starting with the left shoulder?
- 1, 2, 3, 4?
- Yes.
- Like this?
- Yes, the four beats.
Is your nickname Han Ki Bum?
It should end with King.
He's Long King
while Haha's Short King.
Long King and Short King.
Nose King and...
Is it your turn
if I call out "Ki Bum, two?"
The nickname should end with King.
King?
It wouldn't be Ki Bum King.
(He can't shake off
the image of his doppelganger.)
- Are we playing in teams?
- Yes, teams.
- We're playing in teams.
- Teams!
- In teams.
- Ji Hyo, do well, okay?
- We've got this.
- Yoo Jeong, do well.
- Sure.
- Don't attack your teammates.
- No way.
The judge for this round...
will be the sound mixer
in front of you.
He will single out...
the voices that sound pleasant.
- The voices that sound pleasant?
- Got it.
I love you, Mr. Lee.
I know you're listening.
Shall we start with Vocal Queen?
Sure, we'll start with Min Young.
Go!
- Ting, ting, taeng, taeng
- Ting, taeng, frying pan
- Gum King, four.
- What?
- It's you.
- Out!
- You're Gum King.
Must "King" be added at the end?
- Gum King, four!
- No breaks are allowed.
Gum King, Gum King,
Gum King, Gum King.
- It's tricky.
- Why can't you do this?
Whenever we play this game,
Jae Suk's like,
"Why can't you do better?"
- He's the worst at it though.
- Hey.
- How is this hard?
- Guys, take a look...
and see how terrible
Jae Suk is at this.
We'll consider that
as a practice game.
- Sure.
- Let's do this then.
- I'll start things off. And go.
- Sure.
- Ting, ting, taeng, taeng
- Ting, taeng, frying pan
Sleep Queen, three.
Wait, I got it wrong.
(He got it wrong.)
(Her nickname is Enough Queen.)
Seriously?
- Every day on the bus to school
No, I'm fine
Who has Sleep Queen for a nickname?
We're also on the same team.
- What's your nickname?
- He's terrible at this.
I'm Enough Queen.
Unbelievable.
- I'm sorry.
- Seriously?
What's up with him?
There's Nose King, right?
He's terrible at these games.
Why does he get nervous
all the time?
- His palms are sweaty.
- It's because he gets nervous.
Let me wish myself luck.
- We'll start with Enough Queen.
- Sure.
- All right.
- And go.
- Ting, ting, taeng, taeng
- Ting, taeng, frying pan
- No Ball King, four.
- No Ball King, No Ball King...
No balls?
(No Ball King?)
(What did you just say to me?)
Did you seriously just say that?
Ji Hyo, his nickname is Nose King.
- It's Nose King.
- Nose King.
- That's what I said.
- But Suk Jin responded.
Suk Jin responded,
- No Ball King, four.
- No Ball King.
- You're wrong about me!
- No way.
Nose King is what I said.
- I said "Nose King."
- No Ball King, four!
I'm really sorry about that.
It's the nickname
given to him by his fans.
My children are growing up well.
- What?
- I have proof.
I have children, you know.
- How can you say that?
- No fan would give him...
the nickname No Ball.
It's been scientifically proven
in my case.
- Why did you respond to it?
- Well...
"How can I have no balls?"
- This...
- Anyway, you're wrong.
It'll be another meme of yours.
It'll have a major resurgence.
It'll be a popular meme of yours.
- Anyway, you're wrong.
- Suk Jin, I'm sorry.
- We'll start with Nose King.
- Sure.
Nose King, Nose King.
- Nose King.
- Yes, Nose King.
- Ji Hyo, it's Nose King.
- Nose!
- Ting, ting, taeng, taeng
- Ting, taeng, frying pan
- Muscle King, four.
- Muscle King, Muscle King,
Muscle King, Muscle King.
Nose King, four.
Nose King, Nose King,
Nose King, Nose King.
(The techno warrior)
Did you see him just now?
What about your shoulders?
What on earth was that?
- It's up to me, isn't it?
- Why were you dancing the techno?
I can do what I want.
Why are we even playing this game
if there are no rules?
Why were you dancing the techno?
Because I wanted to.
I'm excited
to be here with Brave Girls.
- Like this.
- But...
- I...
- You're out.
- I didn't get it wrong.
- You didn't.
Call Bobbed-hair Queen too
during the game.
No way. She's on our team.
(Se Chan's urgent words.)
She's on our team,
so don't listen to Jae Suk!
She's on our team.
- Seriously, Jae Suk?
- I got it.
No Gum King or Big Eyes Queen.
- No Bobbed-hair Queen.
- He doesn't even know...
who's on his team.
Don't call out for those
on our team.
Bobbed-hair Queen...
- And...
- Giant Eyes Queen.
Yes, Giant Eyes Queen.
Her nickname is Big Eyes Queen.
- Big Eyes Queen?
- It's Big Eyes.
- Giant Eyes Queen?
- Giant Eyes Queen, my gosh.
- How about we omit the gestures?
- Without them?
- Yes.
- The gestures aren't easy.
Let's try it without the gestures.
- Without them?
- Just clap instead.
- How about this?
- Just clap?
- This?
- Okay, good.
- Yes, just clap.
- Ting, ting, ting, ting
- Taeng, taeng, taeng, taeng
- Ting, taeng, frying pan
- Check out the beautiful scenery.
(Taeng, taeng, taeng, taeng)
(Ting, ting, taeng, taeng)
(Frying pan)
Why aren't you playing the game?
- But it's beautiful out there.
- Why are you enjoying the scenery?
- We have fine weather today.
- It's spring!
Check out the forsythia.
Look at you all on the same page.
He was chanting all on his own,
and no one cared to join in.
- Shall we enjoy the scenery first?
- Take a look.
Okay, it'll be a moment to enjoy.
- We'll purify our eyes first.
- Check that out.
- It's Yangwha Bridge!
- I can understand.
- Look at that.
- It's plausible...
since the sky is clear.
- I can fully understand.
- Spring is here.
Look at the forsythia.
- Okay, shall we?
- Look at the flowers.
- Go for it.
- 1 and 2.
- Ting, ting, taeng, taeng
- Ting, taeng, frying pan
- Squirtle Queen, three.
- Squirtle Queen, Squirtle Queen,
- Squirtle Queen. Gum King, one.
- Nicely done.
Gum King. Long King, one.
- Long King.
- Nice!
- Vocal Queen, three.
- Vocal, Vocal Queen, Vocal Queen.
- Nicely done.
- Gum King, four.
Gum King, Gum King, Gum King,
Gum King. Citron King, two.
Citron King, Citron King,
Citron King.
(The sneak attack...)
(made him crumble.)
- Out!
- Why are you so bad at this?
Can we leave him out
when playing games?
- Se Chan...
- We were on a roll.
Jae Suk...
was trembling by my side.
It's why I tossed it over to him.
He couldn't see straight.
Why are you this nervous?
He wasn't like this
during his "X-Man" days.
That's because
I always hosted the games.
Oh, that's right.
Anyway, we all did well.
Someone, please give Jae Suk
a calming pill.
Okay, let's do this. Go ahead.
And go.
- Ting, ting, taeng, taeng
- Ting, taeng, frying pan
- Citron King, three.
- Citron, Citron King, Citron King.
(He did it this time!)
Big Eyes Queen, three.
Big Eyes Queen,
Big Eyes Queen, Big Eyes Queen.
- Citron King, four.
- Citron King, Citron King,
Citron King, Citron King.
Long King, three.
Long King, Long King, Long King.
(Long King went off beat.)
- That's wrong.
- He wasn't on the beat.
No, he was on the beat.
- That's not it.
- It was a fake.
- Why would you attack me?
- He's on your team!
Why were you looking at me then?
I was only looking at you...
- because it was your turn!
- I know!
- Hey.
- Why would you attack me?
He can't even tell...
whether Kwang Soo
is on our team or not.
- For him...
- I looked at him because...
- Hey.
- He attacked me for looking at him.
So why did you look at me?
(Citron King was doing well until
he attacked his own team member.)
- Let's start with Long King again.
- Okay.
- Ting, ting, taeng, taeng
- Ting, taeng, frying pan
- Vocal Queen, two.
- Vocal Queen, Vocal Queen.
Enough Queen, one.
Enough Queen.
No ball, three.
- No ball, no ball, no ball.
- Hey!
(She attacks again
with the same method.)
He's not "no balls!"
What's wrong with you?
Stop it, Ji Hyo!
- I called for Nose King!
- Hey!
Ji Hyo, you did that on purpose.
It seems like you really
said that on purpose.
- I clearly said Nose King!
- No, it was clearly no ball.
- Ji Hyo.
- It means he's really "no balls."
- She meant it.
- You can't attack him.
- What was she supposed to say?
- She called him "no balls."
But you responded to what she said.
- What?
- Why would you respond to that?
- I didn't mean to...
- But that's how it's supposed to...
You made it sound so natural.
- I heard it as Nose King.
- It's because you responded to it.
No, no. That's not true.
- You need to smile, Suk Jin.
- That's not true.
(Laughing)
(He maintains his character
by forcing his laughter.)
- There you go!
- Okay!
- It's your turn.
- Okay?
(The mission ended with Ji Hyo
calling Suk Jin offensively.)
- Her small remark...
- Everyone got caught on that.
Here's the result.
The result is the score based on
the scores you missed.
Team Squirtle
got the most wrong answers.
Oh, it's our team?
- Oh, no.
- That's not possible.
Jae Suk missed it a lot.
- No, but I got only two wrong.
- If you think about it,
he got a lot of them wrong.
And Team Big Eyes
is in second place.
Oh, we're in second place?
Team Main Vocalist is
in first place.
(The first place goes to
Team Main Vocalist.)
- But this is...
- But...
But we haven't included
the audio engineer's score.
- That could be a game changer.
- While playing the game,
he could've found
your voice annoying.
He scored based on that?
We asked how it was,
and he said he knows
who's going last.
- Really?
- Which team is it?
The team with a high pitch
that couldn't be controlled...
(The team that tortured
the audio engineer was...)
Team Squirtle.
(Team Squirtle is confirmed
to be in last place.)
(Oh, no.)
- She didn't realize it.
- No, I didn't.
- The last team is Team Squirtle.
- But why us?
We need to talk to
the audio engineer.
- He's one funny guy.
- He was annoyed by our voices?
- Come on.
- We tried really hard.
You can't say that to someone
who's working hard.
- But we are working hard too.
- He's working hard.
He's annoyed by our voices.
How could he say that? We've been
working together for so long.
- I know.
- I'm a little disappointed.
How could you say that?
You shouldn't have said that.
The audio engineer knows
what's right.
- He really does.
- He knows what's right.
- I mean...
- He's done this for a long time.
- It's making me uncomfortable.
- You're being too harsh.
There's a team the audio engineer...
- gave a lot of scores to.
- Oh, really?
The first place...
goes to Team Big Eyes.
(Team Big Eyes wins first place.)
Thank you, Director.
- Thank you so much.
- Thank you.
- Thank you for choosing us.
He picked your team because
he's a big fan of Yoo Na's.
- What was that?
- You must love Yoo Na!
This is how you score our teams?
I like the audio engineer better.
The winner of total scores
is Team Big Eyes.
(The winner of total scores
is Team Big Eyes.)
Team Main Vocalist
is in second place.
Oh, no.
- We're doing well.
- Okay.
We'll cut for now.
Please clap once.
(Flinching)
I'll clap. 1, 2...
- You should let Min Young do it.
- Let Min Young do it.
Come on. Don't act up.
- It's not that.
- Stop acting up.
Why do you think Min Young
is seated in the middle?
- You said that to me!
- He only thinks of himself.
You've been doing this for a decade.
Min Young, please clap for us.
- Stop it already.
- Stop it.
I'll clap now.
1, 2, 3.
Doesn't this look so nice?
- My goodness.
- It's all nice.
Know when to budge in.
Seriously, he just wants to
take all the roles.
- Seriously.
- He acts up so much.
Each team will pick a member
to go out first.
Please leave out some.
- You're in first place, right?
- Eun Ji.
Yes, I'll leave some for you.
Why did you put me in fourth place?
I'm sorry, I'll put you
in first place next time.
- Eun Ji, we have five left.
- Yes?
Okay, we have five.
I'll just take one.
Shall I take everything?
- Take as much as you want.
- I mean...
(Team Main Vocalist has 5,
Team Big Eyes has 3.)
(Big Eyes Queen took 3.)
(She runs away after taking
3 out of 5.)
I should take this.
I have no other choice.
I'll just take one.
(Each team earns 1 at least.)
So Min, just take one.
(She can't take off as it's been
long since she's done a good deed.)
(They come inside after
taking the trophies.)
What's this? It's our meal.
(These are the ingredients
of gimbap.)
It's our meal.
What are all these?
These are for gimbap.
- But...
- These are for gimbap.
Take a look at them.
"Today's lunch is gimbap."
"Pick two ingredients
out of the ingredients available."
"If your teammate brings
the same ingredient,"
"you need to return it."
We need to return it
if we have overlapping ingredients?
(The team that leaves the most
side dishes will lose.)
You can now pick the ingredient
you'd want in your gimbap.
So we can pick two?
You can pick two.
I can pick two?
I've been wanting to have gimbap
since yesterday.
(The teams with the most ingredients
will be given more points.)
Jong Kook will pick the eggs,
and Haha will pick
the rice and hams.
But I'm not sure what
Vocal Queen would pick.
I'll pick two.
(So Min picks rice and tuna
after some thought.)
These are the two most
important ingredients.
I'll pick ham.
(Eun Ji picks rice and ham.)
- Tuna!
- Okay.
(Ji Hyo picks rice and tuna.)
(Will they avoid
picking the same menu?)
What's this? Is it rice?
Oh, gosh. It's well-cooked.
(The next to go are Jong Kook,
Jae Suk, and Yoo Na.)
(They're done picking
their ingredients.)
All right.
- What's this?
- This is ours.
Please go ahead.
(The last members
pick their ingredients.)
What did you pick?
Min Young...
- Oh, gosh...
- Yoo Jeong...
Yoo Jeong, did you bring rice?
- Oh, no!
- You couldn't have.
You did well by bringing the tuna.
- Really?
- We can have tuna as is.
If the last member brings rice,
we can have it with these.
It'd be perfect if she brings
rice and tuna.
I'd be happy with
rice and pickled radish.
Rice and tuna.
It'd be delicious if we had tuna.
- I know.
- Of course.
- Like rice balls.
- That'd be perfect.
- I know. You're right.
We have the most important roles.
- We're the most important ones.
- We're the core members.
It's an important choice.
It'd be possible to make gimbap
with just one more ingredient.
I'll pick this.
I'm sure they have it.
You can go inside now.
For our points.
Please...
(They're here.)
No, no.
(Please bring us the rice.)
I feel somewhat insecure.
(Kwang Soo brought rice.)
Kwang Soo brought it!
- He brought rice!
- He really did!
- Well done, Kwang Soo.
- You didn't get any?
Okay!
Well done!
Well done in picking rice.
I thought they'd overlap.
- Please.
- Well done, Kwang Soo.
No, no!
(Haha picked rice as well.)
Oh, gosh.
I told you he'd bring rice next.
I told you he'd bring rice
as though he used his brains.
(They got a new kind of gimbap
that doesn't have any rice.)
- We can't have it.
- Why did you...
- My gosh.
- Why did you bring rice?
I mean...
Bear with that.
(Suk Jin chooses the egg garnish
and clam meat.)
You're lacking rice.
- Why would you have this?
- Why are you eating alone?
- In case they steal yours.
- I changed my mind.
You both brought rice, so...
Please remember this.
- Please remember this, okay?
- Sure.
- All right.
- I'm keeping it with you first.
- Stop it. You're being ugly.
- That's not it.
We'll evaluate the cleanliness,
attitude, and eating habits.
Then the last place goes to
Team Squirtle Queen.
The last place?
My goodness.
We have a chance of
winning first place!
The rest of you...
are tied for first place.
We got first prize.
I'm full.
It's so fun.
(The idols gathered
at the last mission place.)
Oh, it's here.
Oh, so we're going to be
covered in paint.
Okay, I got this.
(They distribute
the trophies beforehand.)
- Here comes...
- I need to get these.
Yoo Jeong.
I'm the only one with no trophies.
You know that, right?
(Pressured)
You don't need to be pressured.
Don't ever pick Kwang Soo.
If I don't, I'll get the punishment.
- Keep that in mind.
- Okay.
Don't you think it'd be fun
for him to get the punishment?
Hey, I'll take first place.
- No, that's...
- We'll play rock-paper-scissors.
You want to play
rock-paper-scissors?
(Suk Jin has no trophies
has he's second-last to go.)
Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
Rock-paper-scissors!
The winner decides it.
- Rock-paper-scissors!
Okay.
The winner decides the order.
Let's not do that.
- Why did you...
- Rock-paper-scissors!
- Okay.
- Yoo Na...
You don't have to go first.
- Okay, since we have five.
- That's right.
I don't have any.
- Be honest.
- I have nothing.
Then we'll get in this order.
1, 2, 3, 4.
I'm sorry.
(He naturally got last place.)
- I'm sorry.
- You aren't mistaken, are you?
- We have decided.
You didn't think wrong, did you?
Tell me again. How shall we decide?
Suk Jin got last place again?
Let's not do that.
Let's not get greedy.
Just because I don't get any,
it's not going to be funny.
- I know.
- So let's make it heartwarming.
- Sure.
- So I'll cry after finding four.
Let's go in this direction.
- Okay?
- Okay.
We should...
- Okay?
- Okay.
(Listening to Suk Jin's directions
made him fall asleep.)
Jae Suk! Don't do this!
He seriously needs to see a doctor!
- Why does he always fall asleep?
- You just came in!
What's wrong with me?
- What's wrong with you?
- You just came in.
"What's wrong with me?"
I just got so bored.
(Everyone falls asleep as soon as
Big Nose starts to talk.)
It's so funny how you faint.
(I just dozed off.)
Please tell us the order
your team decided.
- We're deciding now?
- That's right.
What shall we do, Yoo Jeong?
- I'll take first place this time.
- Okay, you should do that.
- You can take second place.
- Okay, I will.
- That's right.
- Okay.
Right.
(But there's only 1 trophy.)
Then let Kwang Soo take third place.
It doesn't matter
whether I go 3rd or 4th!
You can go ahead.
The one who won first place
can go ahead.
The rest of you, please stay behind.
Hey, Yoo Na. Yoo Na.
- I mean, but we...
- Yoo Na.
Just leave two.
- You can take two.
- That's right.
I know what Yoo Na is like.
I'm sure Yoo Na will take everything.
(I'm sure Yoo Na
will take everything.)
- She doesn't care about others.
- Yoo Na, are you the greedy one?
- Come on.
- Yoo Na.
You stuck your head in there.
Hey. You just...
Next.
I'll just take one.
- Don't fool us.
- I'm serious.
All right. Go ahead.
Okay.
(The members of Brave Girls
took everything they could.)
- All right, next.
- It's our turn.
Why is he going second?
You should just take one.
There's nothing in here.
- Why would you...
- She's using the bag.
- Why is she...
- Are you ripping the whole thing?
Are you all set? My goodness.
I'm sorry, Jong Kook.
I'm so sorry.
You didn't have to go this far.
(Current Number of Trophies)
Here's the last mission.
It's the last mission where you can
complete idol makeup.
This is...
It's called
Nice Makeup Running Salon.
I see.
The team playing offense will pick
two players to play dibidibidip.
And two players to get the makeup.
The 2 teams playing defense
will decide on 3 players to play.
So when one team plays offense,
the two defense teams
play against the other team.
- You need to win to go on.
- I'm good at this.
Each team will get to play twice.
So every team will play six times.
The team that beats everyone
the fastest...
will get higher scores.
The referees for this mission
are the four assistant directors.
They'll give you points
based on how fun you make this.
- We need a strategy.
- So we need to make it fun.
- The four assistant directors?
- Yes, you know them, right?
We'll make the actions
for dibidibidip...
using the highlight dance moves
of "Rollin'."
- Really?
- How?
- The stingray dance.
- Oh, the stingray dance?
(The stingray dance)
The scarecrow dance.
(The scarecrow dance)
- And the floral cup dance.
- The floral cup dance?
That's dibidibidip?
(The floral cup dance)
Dibidibidip, dibidibidip,
dibidibidip.
That's correct.
- She's good.
- Do you have to do it that way?
- Do you have to?
- Dibidibidip
- You have to shake your hip.
- Why do you shake it so much?
- That's how the dance is like.
So Min is good with those moves.
- So Min, show us how it's done.
- This is driving me crazy.
Dibidibidip, dibidibidip,
dibidibidip.
- Dibidibidip.
- She's good.
- Why do you dance like that?
That's what earns her
entertainment points.
(Are you watching?)
Who will play offense first?
Are you good at this, Kwang Soo?
I play this every day.
- Every day?
- I'm serious.
- Then let's try it. Ready, go.
- I'm an expert.
Dibidibidip.
(Wriggling)
You should pose correctly.
That was cool though.
- Okay.
- Ready, go.
Dibidibidip, dibidibidip,
dibidibidip.
(This guy who loves cheating
is only thinking of cheating.)
- Dibidibidip.
- Kwang Soo should play defense.
I can't stop.
You should remember
the entertainment points.
Then Kwang Soo and Yoo Jeong
should play defense.
Ji Hyo and I should play offense.
- Kwang Soo.
- Yes?
- You should win as fast as you can.
- Okay, I got it.
Good luck!
(Good luck!)
All right.
When I blow the whistle,
the conveyor belt will start moving.
- We'll start in this direction.
- Okay.
- He won't go past Se Chan.
- We need to win against them.
- Okay.
- Since our points are at stake.
- You know what I mean, right?
- Yes.
Guys, you need to keep the rhythm
of the original game though.
You need to go like this.
Dibidibidip, dibidibidip.
(The winner will be decided on
mission and entertainment points.)
- We got this!
- Get ready.
- Ready.
- I'll play this seriously.
Dibidibidip!
(The conveyor belt starts to move.)
- Dibidibidip!
- Okay!
(He succeeds in attacking 4 people
at a fast pace.)
(Squirtle Queen is going past
the first phase.)
- Dibidibidip!
- Okay!
Dibidibidip! Dibidibidip!
Good job. Good work.
(The conveyor belt stopped
at phase 2.)
- What is that?
- Good work.
(What is that?)
- Seriously?
- Good work!
He took ten seconds.
(He only took 10 seconds!)
Hey, good job.
Good job, guys.
(It's a big achievement they earned
without trying to make it fun.)
- Now...
- I have no idea how I did that.
- But this is...
- It wasn't fun because of him, no?
- It wasn't fun at all.
- How did I pull that off?
You made it so boring.
It wasn't fun at all.
What's wrong with you?
- That's not it.
- You did well.
You didn't do your part.
- Yoo Jeong, well done.
- What was that?
- Hey.
- But everyone lost at least once.
Kwang Soo, you got zero
entertainment points.
- You got zero points.
- Then what was I supposed to do?
What was I supposed to do?
They lost at once.
You should've taken it easy.
You should've gone like,
dibidibidip, Dibidibidip.
- Don't pay him for today.
- You guys are being harsh.
- You did well.
- What was I supposed to do?
You lost in one cue.
Don't you know how it goes?
- I know. It was too fast.
- What do you mean?
- Right. I couldn't enjoy it.
- You should've done it like this.
You were too fast.
What was I supposed to do
when everyone lost at once?
You scared everyone off.
All right.
- Let's do it again.
- I'm not good at it though.
- I believe in you!
- Do what you're good at.
- Min Young...
- Just make it fun.
You can do it, So Min!
All right. Don't go too fast.
- Dibidibidip. Dibidibidip.
- This is...
- Dibidibidip.
- Dibidibidip. Dibidibidip...
- No, no. That's not it.
- Dibidibidip...
- No, no.
- Dibidibidip. Dibidibidip...
- You can't do that.
- Dibidibidip. Dibidibidip.
- Dibidibidip.
- All right. 1, 2.
- Dibidibidip. Dibidibidip.
(The trainee doesn't quite follow.)
(The culture center lesson
earns her an entertainment point.)
- Let's do this.
- Let's start.
Ready.
(It's Team Main Vocalist's turn!)
Set.
Dibidibidip. Dibidibidip.
- Dibidibidip.
- Good job!
Dibidibidip. Dibidibidip.
Didn't I get you? Dibidibidip.
Dibidibidip. Didn't I get you?
(The trainee shows off special moves
he created.)
(He tries to earn his entertainment
points although it's too late.)
- Dibidibidip. Dibidibidip.
- You're doing so well, Kwang Soo!
So Min!
Oh, no, So Min.
(While So Min is handling
the special moves,)
- So Min!
- Dibidibidip.
(Vocal Queen is going through
the color makeup phase.)
(I'm passing by.)
Dibidibidip. Dibidibidip.
Dibidibidip.
(Confused)
(Bang!)
What was that?
- It popped.
- A feather gun went off.
- My goodness.
- My gosh.
- A feather gun went off.
- Oh, no!
- Well done.
- It looks great.
- You look good.
- That's so cool.
You earned entertainment points.
- She earned entertainment points.
- Oh, right.
- It's actually pretty.
- It looks really good.
- You look pretty.
- It's like a musical.
- She earned entertainment points.
- It's looking really good.
You look so cool.
Here, look at this camera.
Dibidibidip. Dibidibidip.
- Dibidibidip.
Darn it!
My goodness.
Our team is a total mess.
- It's Ji Hyo?
- It's been so long though.
I don't think Ji Hyo can
pass through everyone here.
- You can do it!
Let's stand over there.
- I should stand here.
- Dibidibidip.
It should go like this.
Dibidibidip. Dibidibidip.
(They slowly come up with moves
to earn entertainment points.)
There you go. You're doing great.
- You got this, Ji Hyo!
- You're doing great!
(Earning 1 entertainment point)
(Make a fuss and exaggerate
to earn entertainment points.)
There you go!
It's been so long since
I saw the Macarena dance!
Isn't that the Macarena?
(She's ecstatic.)
I can imitate Squirtle Queen
while I dance, right?
- Squirtle Queen?
- What do you mean?
When did I make that face?
- He looks like you.
- Hey.
- She doesn't look like this.
- What do you mean?
Squirtle Queen
doesn't look like this.
Isn't this what she does?
(He's the reason the soldiers'
fighting power declined.)
Get ready.
(The fake Squirtle Queen
is ready too.)
- Let's do this!
- You can do this!
Se Chan, I'll keep repeating
the floral cup dance.
(Ji Hyo makes a deal.)
Set.
(She will earn entertainment points
at Kwang Soo's expense.)
- Dibidibidip.
- Let's go.
- That's good.
(She promised to do
only the floral cup dance!)
(He is clueless.)
- Dibidibidip.
Gosh, you got me.
- Move on.
- Come here.
(She goes slowly.)
Dibidibidip.
Dibidibidip. Why isn't it working?
- Dibidibidip.
- What?
Why are you going after a beat?
- You are done. Move on.
- Dibidibidip.
Dibidibidip.
- You are done. Move on.
- Ji Hyo!
- You are done.
- Ji Hyo, hang in there!
Dibidibidip.
Ji Hyo, hang in there!
(Kwang Soo is getting
a face full of makeup.)
- You are done. Move on.
- Ji Hyo!
(Colorful)
Ji Hyo, hang in there!
- Ji Hyo, hang in there!
- Dibidibidip.
- Let's go!
(She takes her time
in front of the Squirtle King.)
Let's go!
(The feather gun goes off!)
(As Ji Hyo planned,
the attack fails!)
That was great.
- Yes!
- That was great.
- That was perfect.
- Too bad.
- Listen.
- Ji Hyo.
- Even when she succeeded...
- That was perfect.
Someone... Hold on.
Someone reached out and slapped me.
- That was perfect.
- I got slapped.
- You look so ugly.
- The makeup has been applied well.
- Do you know what's scary?
I think I met eyes with someone.
- No.
- This is...
(I definitely met eyes
with someone.)
- I met eyes with someone.
- No.
- You are an animal, right?
- What?
- You aren't a human being.
- An ostrich.
You are an animal.
- Why does my cheek hurt?
- You look cool.
You look pretty.
There is no way
you met eyes with someone.
It's like "Cats."
Your eyes became bigger.
- There are feathers too.
- The next team.
- Okay.
- I can see the feathers.
I will stand next to Squirtle Queen.
Why? If you stand
next to Squirtle Queen...
(Squirtle King approaches
Squirtle Queen.)
Hey. Is that supposed to be
her facial expression?
When did she make
that facial expression?
He is good.
(The middle-aged Squirtle gets
all the entertainment points.)
He looks cute.
Okay.
Get ready.
(Suk Jin and Yoo Na go next!)
Dibidibidip. Dibidibidip.
- Okay. Dibidibidip.
- He is advancing.
Dibidibidip. Dibidibidip.
(Squirtle Queen defends herself
pretty well.)
- She is good.
- Dibidibidip.
Dibidibidip. Dibidibidip.
(Standing still)
Why won't you do it?
(He has no intention to play
the game.)
What are you doing?
- What is that?
- Why aren't you playing the game?
- Dibidibidip.
(The game ends!)
- Jae Suk, why didn't you play?
- Seriously.
- You should have played.
- I forgot.
- Did you forget?
- I see.
- I forgot the dance moves.
- It's understandable.
- Jae Suk, you get a warning.
Where did her face go?
Where did Yoo Na go?
How did this happen?
- Here comes a member of "Cats."
- Hey.
- Can you see?
- It's like a masquerade.
- It's like "Cats."
- Can you see?
- No.
- Midnight
Seriously.
- The feathers landed on her face.
- This is unbelievable.
The feathers landed on her face.
The two of you are like
the members of "Cats."
Suk Jin, come over here.
- Where?
- You need to play the game.
Okay.
Why does Suk Jin keep trying
to get out of it?
Suk Jin.
- I played the game so much.
- Why did you become exhausted?
I played the game so much.
- Should there be six people?
- Yes.
You have to play the game.
Okay. We have to play the game.
Dibidibidip.
- That's cheating!
- Okay, okay.
(They fail in the end
because of Foul King!)
Dibidibidip. Dibidibidip.
Dibidibidip.
(Ji Hyo and Yoo Jeong
of Team Squirtle fail as well!)
Team Squirtle is done.
- Really?
- The other two teams should go.
- Okay.
- It's our turn, right?
The leader will decide
which members will go.
As for our team,
the leader will decide.
I will go,
- so give me a few trophies.
- What?
- It's up to the leader.
- No, no.
It's up to the leader.
- It's up to the leader.
- I think she will pick me.
She keeps looking at me.
Just accept your fate.
Don't do it. Don't pick me.
Don't pick me.
It's up to the leader, right?
- Yes.
- Let me take a trophy.
Overcome it!
Good luck!
I don't have a single trophy.
Suk Jin's turtleneck top
will be dyed prettily.
That's good. He still has it.
- Mr. Turtleneck Top.
- He still has it.
(Mr. Turtleneck Top
shows off his energy.)
- He still has it.
- Let's go.
Live a long life! Live a long life!
Who will do this?
Will you be my partner?
- I will be your partner.
- Make sure you succeed.
- He still has it.
- What is this?
- Suk Jin.
- You imitated Song Chang Sik.
Suk Jin, I will go really fast.
- Dibidibidip. Dibidibidip.
- He still has it.
Suk Jin still has it.
Let's get ready to laugh.
Hey!
Hey! Why are you adding paint?
Gosh, they are adding more paint.
Hey!
There is enough. Listen.
- This is incredible.
- There is enough.
- What is up with you?
- I am surprised to see them...
- move in unison.
- Stop it.
- They are passionate.
- Hey.
You don't need to work so hard.
You won't get paid more!
- Hey.
- My goodness.
It's fine.
They added so much paint.
- Everyone knows...
- They added so much paint.
- that it will be funny.
- Seriously.
- It might not even open.
- It will be funny.
(It's closed shut with paint.)
- Will it open?
- It might not even open.
Gosh.
- Hold on. I will take off my socks.
- Good luck.
- He is taking off his socks.
- Let me be first place this time.
- Seriously.
All right.
Let me be first place this time.
I am doing this much.
- I will think about it.
- Come on!
- Good luck!
- You never know.
Suk Jin, I will do this speedily...
- for real.
- This is nerve-wracking.
- Suk Jin.
- How else...
- were you going to do it?
- I am getting so many thoughts.
All right.
(It's Team Big Eyes' last chance.
How will the round go?)
All right.
Get ready.
I will keep doing this.
Dibidibidip. Dibidibidip.
Dibidibidip.
- Hey!
- Dibidibidip.
Dibidibidip. Dibidibidip.
Dibidibidip.
- Hey! Do it properly.
- Dibidibidip.
Dibidibidip. Dibidibidip.
(He recreates the dance.)
(From Tae Kwon Do...)
(to breakdancing)
(It's a match
between a spear and a shield.)
Dibidibidip. Dibidibidip.
(Meanwhile,
Suk Jin gets painted prettily.)
Oh, no.
(Thick)
(When the dancers run out of ideas,)
(the game ends!)
Suk Jin, that's too bad.
What is he going to do?
I could see his moves.
I couldn't win.
You guys shouldn't have done that.
- I couldn't win.
- That's no way to treat a senior.
Seriously.
(Here comes the senior.)
Hey, you. Come here.
Hey.
I will scold them.
Kwang Soo, come here.
They made everyone uncomfortable.
- Come here.
- Guys.
- You shouldn't have done that.
- Hey.
- Why did you play around...
- I am sorry.
- while this was happening to him?
I know it was for a show,
but it's still unforgivable.
I was trying to make it funny.
Let go of me. Hey!
(He probably has
an angry facial expression.)
I was trying to make it funny.
Let go of me. Hey.
Let go of me.
That's no way to treat a senior.
- Hey.
- You can treat me that way.
But Suk Jin is a different matter.
Come to your senses.
- Hey.
- He was born in 1966.
- He is 56 years old.
- But you guys...
- I am the one who is angry.
Let go of me.
- That's no way to treat a senior.
- I understand.
Suk Jin, I will tell them.
I... Hey!
I won't do it again.
- Don't do it again.
- Okay.
Suk Jin, I talked to them.
Let's go!
- Let's go!
Let's laugh about it!
- Okay.
This is... Hey.
- Jae Suk.
- You scolded them, right?
- That's right.
I scolded them until they teared up.
- I won't do it again!
- I am sorry.
- I won't do it again.
- They teared up.
It's so nice
to see Jae Suk step up.
- Jae Suk thinks dearly of him.
- It's heartwarming.
- Despite the camera, I had to.
The way they treated Suk Jin
made me so angry.
- I know.
- I talked to them.
Good job.
I almost turned things upside down.
- I did it for you.
- Jae Suk.
Get your acts straight!
I am sorry.
- I am sorry.
- He is so funny.
- For goodness' sake.
- I am sorry.
The last round remains.
- Dibidibidip. Dibidibidip.
- Okay!
- Dibidibidip.
(Team Main Vocalist fails!)
Okay.
After I announce the final results,
the trophies will be distributed
one last time.
Firstly, the mission points
follow the records.
- That's good.
- Okay.
- 20 points.
- We placed 1st, right?
Then there are
the entertainment points.
- I bet our score is high.
- Our score would be high too.
- Look at my face.
We were on another level.
(Team Big Eyes, Team Squirtle,
Team Main Vocalist)
Suk Jin made everyone laugh.
There we go.
- There we go.
- Thank you.
It's a high score.
(What will be
Team Squirtle's total?)
It's a high score.
(Team Squirtle)
- Okay.
- That's good.
- We are currently first place.
- We did well too.
Let's see.
(Team Main Vocalist)
(Team Squirtle places 1st
and wins 5 trophies.)
Yes!
(Team Squirtle places 1st
and wins 5 trophies.)
Yes!
It's okay.
We placed third.
(It's time to take the trophies.)
Please decide on the order
within the team.
The leader will decide
through rock-paper-scissors.
That's the leader's decision.
Suk Jin keeps saying
that they will be criticized.
- You guys will be criticized.
- What are you talking about?
This is a variety show.
- Why would they be criticized?
- I don't mind.
- Let people criticize us.
- Why would they be criticized?
She doesn't mind. Let's just play...
- rock-paper-scissors.
- I am just worried about them.
Just win in rock-paper-scissors.
Just win.
Rock-paper-scissors.
(They play rock-paper-scissors
and Suk Jin actually wins.)
Okay! I won.
- Really?
- That's no fun.
(After winning,
he suddenly slaps the ostrich.)
What was that?
- Hey.
- Why...
- Why did you slap him?
- I just wanted to slap him.
- Did you slap him?
You were ridiculing me
with your face.
I was just standing here
with a blank face.
I was feeling bad for you.
You were ridiculing me.
Why did you slap him?
You looked at me
as if you were ridiculing me.
I was just looking.
For goodness' sake.
The next team.
As for us,
- I will go first this time as well.
- Do what you want.
- Again?
- Yes.
- Hold on. Don't you have a trophy?
- I do.
Then what is your problem?
Your words are too rough.
How could you talk to her like that?
She is simply doing her best.
Isn't this our last chance?
- Isn't this our last chance?
- Yes, it is.
- The first members will begin.
- Okay.
(They take the trophies
according to the order.)
- Go over there.
- The first members.
(The current prize candidates
and penalty candidates)
(But the last distribution
could change the final rankings!)
It's time to count the trophies.
- Okay.
- I don't have many.
So Min.
I have three.
(So Min of Team Main Vocalist)
You took one each.
Jong Kook, you are next.
- I have 2.
- You have 2.
I might not get a penalty.
- Haha.
- I have two.
- Really?
- Two.
How many does Min Young have?
- Min Young.
- It's hard for her to count them.
(She has so many trophies.)
- Min Young was relaxed.
- Did you give one?
(How does she have so many?)
She has so many.
You should be the winner today.
- 4... 7.
- 7.
Seven?
I have seven.
Min Young, that's incredible.
Ji Hyo.
I have three.
Jae Suk.
- I have two.
- What?
- Two?
- Kwang Soo.
- One?
- I don't have any.
You don't have any?
- Oh, no.
- He will get the penalty.
He will get the penalty.
- Yoo Jeong.
- I have six.
Six.
Min Young will win.
- Go ahead.
- Five.
She has a lot.
Eun Ji.
Four.
Eun Ji has four.
- Se Chan.
- I have three.
- Suk Jin.
- I have three too.
- 3?
- Having 2 puts you at risk.
- You lose if you have 2.
1 or 2.
First place is Min Young.
(1st place is Min Young,
Vocal Queen.)
2nd place is Yoo Jeong
with 6 trophies.
3rd place is Yoo Na with 5 trophies.
Brave Girls took all the trophies.
The prize is
a variety of supplements...
that are good
for idol singers' fatigue.
Thank you.
- Thank you.
(They take the supplements
for fatigue.)
The bottom three members
will get the penalty.
Kwang Soo will get the penalty
for sure.
Since 3 people have 2 trophies,
they will play rock-paper-scissors.
Jong Kook, Jae Suk, and Haha.
Rock-paper-scissors?
Only one person will be spared.
There is only one opening.
Is it to go
through the conveyor belt?
- I will tell you afterward.
- Rock-paper-scissors.
- What could it be?
- I want to avoid the penalty.
- All right.
- Rock-paper-scissors.
(Who will be the one person
to be spared from the penalty?)
- Rock-paper-scissors.
(Jae Suk wins.)
(He keeps his face clean
and avoids the penalty.)
- Jae Suk.
- Did you win?
Did you win?
No way. Why is it my teammates?
Okay!
I won.
I accept the result.
Here is the penalty of the day.
- There are three buckets.
- I feel bad.
One bucket has black paint.
Oh, no.
One bucket has water.
One bucket has confetti.
You need to get the one
with confetti.
I will get that one.
- Confetti.
- Water wouldn't be so bad.
(Who will have the worst ending?)
Kwang Soo, we need to survive this.
- Okay.
- This is incredible.
1, 2, 3. This seat is for number 1.
Pick a seat and sit down.
- We need to choose.
- Number three.
(They sit in front of the bucket
of their choice.)
Did you pick a seat?
(The result)
(Jong Kook is 3, Haha is 2,
and Kwang Soo is 1.)
You made your choice.
I sat here from the start.
I am dirty anyway.
We will open the buckets.
Open them.
(They open the buckets.)
(Startled)
On the count of three,
pour the contents over their heads.
One.
(Jong Kook wants to go home
in a dry state.)
Two.
(The other two want to avoid
the black paint.)
Two.
(Which bucket contains
black paint?)
Three.
(The ones who got water and confetti
are relieved.)
- Thank goodness!
- That was fascinating.
(As usual,
Kwang Soo had the worst luck.)
My goodness.
(They get to see
Kwang Soo's bad luck in person.)
That was fascinating.
- Thank goodness.
(Jong Kook and Haha are happy
that they avoided the worst.)
Thank goodness.
(This crow got his makeup done
until the very end.)
Thank goodness.
(Confetti service)
I got so lucky.
Let's hear a few words
from Brave Girls.
- Please come this way.
- Okay.
The situation is a bit messy
to hear their words.
I am sure they had fun.
We made them a mess.
Kwang Soo, I am sorry.
Would you move out of the way?
(Kwang Soo is a crow
that needs to be removed.)
How was it today? Go ahead, Yoo Na.
It was really nice to have
a great experience today.
- So...
- Who are you?
Hello, I am Yoo Na of Brave Girls.
You are Yoo Na.
- Bobbed-hair Queen.
I had so much fun.
- Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you.
(We thank Min Young, Yoo Jeong,
Eun Ji, and Yoo Na.)
(When a warlike day ends,)
(another war starts in the form
of the evening rush hour.)
(What if you could decide
the fate...)
(on the road?)
(Mapo)
(People who live near Mapo
including Cho Sae Ho)
(Gangnam)
(People who live near Gangnam
including Choa)
(If you mess up, going home
will take an hour and a half.)
(A war for a faster route home
began.)
(Read the following abbreviation.)
(Ha Dream, turn off the TV!)
(Let's go to Gangnam.)
(Read the following abbreviation.)
(Ji Ho, turn off the TV!)
(This is how hard I work!)
(When they fail the mission,
they go to the other team's area.)
(10 minutes...)
(or 1 and half hours?)
(Which team will get to avoid
the evening rush hour?)
(The Sweet and Scary Way Home)