Let's just... have a go at it.
Should we?
[Running Man vs. Laws of the Jungle]
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Those that challenge
nature with their bodies!]
[The beasts of wildlife-
They know no fear!]
[Welcome to the jungle-
Laws of the jungle!]
[And... those who run
for their lives every day!]
[Battle skills earned from
years of chasing.]
[When it comes to competitiveness,
no one can even come close!]
[The strongest in the city.
Teamwork is their name- Running Man.]
[These two teams are facing
each other head to head.]
[A bloody battle to determine the
strongest team in variety land.]
[The two teams fighting for their pride
more than anything else!]
[A warm and sunny spring morning
in the midst of the spring blossoms.]
[A lake full of blinding sunlight.]
- Hello!
[Team Running Man- Yoo Jae Suk(Captain),
Suk Jin, Jong Kook, Gary, Ji Hyo, Kwang Soo.]
- Good morning!
- It's a great morning!
- Where's Ha Ha?
- Hello!
What is Ha Ha up to?
[What is the flag for?]
What's the flag for?
Are we doing another
Running High episode?
- I bet Dong Hoon is up to something.
- Why is Ha Ha nowhere to be seen?
Where's Ha Ha?
[Just then...]
[An arrow?]
[Someone's shooting an arrow
at the RM Team?]
Be careful!
No! Don't touch it!
You're the one who shouldn't touch it.
- Get away.
- You're the one who shouldn't touch it.
- Let me see that.
- Song Ji Hyo...
Song Ji Hyo doesn't even look at him anymore
and just kicks him out of the way.
- Don't you think that's rude?
- Aren't you the master of fighting?
- Song Ji Hyo, you're the best.
- She's the best.
- This is something you see in historical dramas.
- What is that?
[There's a letter attached to the arrow?]
A challenge!
[A challenge?]
'I'm coming for you, Yoo Jae Suk.'
[Someone is challenging them?]
[Kim Jong Kook, we're going deplete you
of all your muscles today!]
- What is this?
- 'Gary, have you been well?'
'Song Ji Hyo! Did you get home alright
after drinking the other night?'
- What is that?
- Were you out drinking?
- With who?
- Who were you out drinking with?
What are you doing, Song Ji Hyo?
- Who is this? Where is this person?
- Who were you out drinking with?
- I wasn't out drinking!
- It says so right here!
It's asking you if you got home okay
after drinking the other night!
- I know! What is going on here?
- What is this all about?
From the looks of it,
several different people wrote these.
The way they expressed how they're going to
deplete Jong Kook of all his muscles...
This person obviously doesn't know
what they're talking about.
- The way they talk sounds so sleazy.
- Don't you think?
[Just then...]
[A swarm of people carrying a flag is seen
on the other side of the river?]
[Could these people be the challengers?]
How many people are there?
- Isn't that 'Laws of the Jungle' Team?
- 'Laws of the Jungle'?
- Is that Jin Woon?
- What is Dong Hoon doing?
[Laws of the Jungle Team: Kim Byung Man (C),
Jung Chul, Woo Jin, Hye Bin, Jin Woon, Ha Ha?]
[Why is Ha Ha with them?]
The Laws of the Jungle!
[They face all sorts of challenges and
defeat without any hesitation!]
[Champions of the wild having conquered
various jungles all over the world!]
[And now, they're here to
challenge the RM Team?]
Seriously, Jin Woon...
- Don't shake their hand, don't do it!
- Is there a need for all this animosity?
[Drawing the boundary right from the start?]
- Don't try to act friendly towards us.
- Hello.
- That traitor.
- What are you looking at?
- Don't you know that I'm a master fighter?
- What?
- What is he doing there?
- One, two, three, four!
The Jung, the Jung...
The laws of the jungle!
- What are you doing, Dong Hoon?
- I see that he's betrayed us again.
- What?
- What team are you standing with?
[30 minutes ago.]
What's going on here?
When I was told to bring on one person
from our opposing team...
- you're the one who I thought of.
- There it is!
- Byung Man...
- Yeah?
I'll show you what
causing mischief is all about.
Betrayal is my middle name.
[And within moments,
he's already a part of their team.]
Do you even know who I am?
Don't talk to us right now. We're here
because we have something to say.
- What?
- What is it?
So why aren't you saying anything?
Why are they passing it off
to each other?
There's no need for us to even
say anything.
Let's just... have a go at it.
Oh yeah?
[You want to have a go at it?]
[Running Man vs. Laws of the Jungle.]
We'd like to challenge you!
[Too weak.]
Your voice is so high pitched.
Your voice is higher pitched than mine.
As I've said before,
God doesn't give you everything.
These good-looking guys with their muscles...
just listen to their voices.
We'd like to challenge you!
[Is he mocking him?]
Kwang Soo for example...
he has a nice voice.
- Yes, he does.
- But God didn't give him the face.
Why are you being like that?
There's something else he didn't give him.
Something even more prominent than looks.
- What is that?
- A butt.
[God especially didn't give him a butt?]
- He has no butt!
- Why do you need to mention that?
His butt is just missing.
I really wish I could strip naked
right now.
It's because I feel so unjust
by what was just said!
But anyways... which one of you recently
went out drinking with Ji Hyo?
- Jin Woon.
- Jin Woon?
[What?
With Jin Woon?]
- You two...
- But you always tell us that you're busy!
- You don't even join us for dinner!
- When did I ever go out drinking with you?
Did you get home safely?
[Panic?]
- What's wrong with her?
- Gary...
- What are you going to do, Gary?
- How can you do this to us?
- You seriously are...
- Am I just for you to use on TV?
Stop calling me so much when
I'm busy working.
[An unfounded setup
putting Ji Hyo in hot water.]
[Battle mode - UP!]
All of us have already
marked one of you as our targets.
- Really?
- Isn't Jung Chul going for Suk Jin?
- I'm sure it is.
- No, I didn't mark him.
- Then who?
- Me.
In the time that I haven't seen you,
your face has aged a lot.
It's because of all my trips to the jungle.
You look like you could be my ancestor.
[Competitive right from the start.]
- Didn't you write something about Gary?
- What about you, Hye Bin?
I'm taking on Gary.
- Shouldn't you take on Ji Hyo?
- You should take on Ji Hyo.
Song Ji Hyo is mine.
You just wait and see.
Hye Bin is a rare treasure that we have
in the variety land.
- Remember Leesadon?
- Of course, I know Leesadon.
I heard that you could keep on spinning
for 24 hours straight.
- Wasn't that over 10 years ago?
- I can't spin like that anymore.
- Why?
- Because I've gotten too old for that.
- How can you say that you're old?
- All that spinning has made me anemic.
- Then who's Jung Chul taking on?
- Mr. Kwang Soo... I'm in charge of him.
Kwang Soo.
- Just call him Kwang Soo.
- Why does your challenge sound so awkward?
- It's because we still feel awkward.
- But not for long.
- There's some awkwardness.
- Yes, I can see that.
- Then Byung Man, you're...
- You. You're mine.
You.
You're mine.
It's okay.
It's going to be okay.
- It's okay!
- Your pride is on the line!
These are the candidates for
the 2014 Olympics!
[A skirmish candidate?]
- I'm going to bend you in half!
- You don't have to sound so harsh!
He knows all the tricks!
I hate to bring this up now,
but I had a really tough time last year!
[A fiery declaration of war!]
This is your pride on the line!
But still, it's okay!
- You have to show him.
- Show him what you're made of!
- Jae Suk.
- Me?
[Let's do this!]
- Face him with confidence!
- Byung Man's really good at martial arts.
- It's okay, you can still do it.
- But having watched Running Man...
This isn't about martial arts.
This is all about the use of the brain.
- It's brain and speed.
- No, that's not it.
It may look like that, but when
it boils down to it, it's strength.
- Look at him.
- What are you talking about?
[Strength is something Mr. Capable
dominates on Running Man?]
- You have no idea how much I use my brain!
- Brains or strength?
I swear on my life that it's strength.
Byung Man, since you've been in the jungle,
you've just aged so much!
- Byung Man!
- Are you about to start crying?
[I guess the jungle really is
one tough place...]
- You're being too sweet to Byung Man!
- Don't let him shake you up!
Apart from the jungle aging you,
it also really slims you down.
I really have lost about 8 kilos.
- I can see that.
- My poor Byung Man!
[Did he fall under Jae Suk's spell?]
You can't weaken your resolve
against him!
- I totally fell under his spell.
- You can't get sucked in by him.
- What are we doing today?
- Here is your mission.
The mission that you will be
taking on today is...
It's Laws of the Jungle vs. Running Man,
Running Man vs. Laws of the Jungle.
It's a survival race.
[Running Man vs. Laws of the Jungle,
Survival Race.]
[Each time a team loses at a mission, a
member of their team will become a hostage.]
[Hostages cannot participate in the name tag
elimination game at the end of the mission.]
[The fiercest competition in history
where both the teams' pride is at stake.]
[Will it be the Jungle's adventurous spirit
or Running Man's pride?]
[Running Man vs. Laws of the Jungle]
Wouldn't it just be better to send
Suk Jin to the other team?
Hey!
- While we go off playing our games...
- All by himself out of 12 of us...
He was the only one who was wondering
about how one gets eliminated.
- Suk Jin is curious about elimination.
- When can I start resting then?
[Running Man vs. Laws of the Jungle,
Start!]
- What does that say?
- Where do we go? The water park?
[Location for the first competition:
The waterpark.]
It's been a while since
we've been to a waterpark.
- I guess we're going something in the water.
- We're going to be fighting in the water.
We're strong in the water.
- Byung Man and Jin Woon...
- They're really strong.
- Byung Man can't be taken lightly.
- He's no joke.
- He has a very low center.
- That's what I'm saying.
He's the best when it comes to
anything balance related.
Eliminate Jong Kook first, no matter what.
Then we'll win for sure.
Okay, I got it.
And if we lose, then we send one of our own
to be taken as their hostage, right?
- We have to send one of our own.
- Then let's send Woo Jin.
[The first hostage to be sacrificed from
the Jungle Team is Woo Jin?]
- If not Woo Jin, I think Jung Chul.
- Jung Chul?
But if we think about it,
if Jung Chul is to go over there...
I think the other team is going to feel so
awkward that it's going to kill their spirit.
- Send me. Send me to them.
- He wants to be sent!
[Great teamwork where they can discuss
the order of who will become a hostage.]
Okay, we're here.
[Arrives at their first location.]
We're here.
Our honor is at stake here.
- Let's win this thing!
- Let's go.
[First battle location-
Outdoor waterpark.]
The jung... the jung...
the laws of the jungle!
- We're here to challenge you!
- But this thing here...
This thing is bigger than the captain.
The first mission for LOTJ Team
vs. the RM Team.
Your mission is...
[Waterpark five course relay.]
The first team to succeed all five courses
within 199 seconds wins the mission.
This is all about teamwork, and
when it comes to that, we're the best!
[The five courses that have been set up
in various spots throughout the park.]
We will show you a simulation of
the missions you'll have to accomplish.
- Okay, we're ready for the simulation!
- Don't they usually play songs during this?
[First course- Flipper jump roping.]
[The first runner starts off with
a basket containing the balls.]
- You have to hit it with your head?
- After hitting it with your head...
- Wow, this is hard.
- You have to put flippers on?
You have to do all of this within
199 seconds?
- You have to jump it ten times.
- How are we going to do that?
[Course one- Jump rope ten times.]
- This isn't going to be easy.
- This is going to be tough.
Once that course is complete,
go on to the second course.
[Course two- Take off the socks underwater.]
The person wearing the red socks must
remove them while staying in this position.
[Course three- Underwater Alkaggi.]
[Use the black marble to knock the
white marble off the board underwater.]
- This is your third course.
- I guess you're able to do that underwater.
[Course four-
Catch the ball while hoola hooping.]
[The simulation man
makes the mission look simple.]
I bet he works out all the time.
Look at his muscles.
Look at the muscles in his arms.
Byung Man needs to do that five times.
[Course five- Take the slide down
and make the goal.]
- You have to ride that?
- Are you being serious?
[Must come down the slide with the basket
that you initially started the mission with.]
[As long as one goal can be made,
the mission is a success!]
- How are we going to do all this?
- All within 199 seconds?
[Waterpark five course replay-
End of the explanation.]
Why don't you try it, Suk Jin?
[Flipper jump roping not as
easy as it looks.]
- You can't do it.
- Let me try it again.
[It seems as though even one jump
is going to be difficult for this man.]
[Oh?
Did he get the hang of it?]
[Oh my...]
[Big-nosed Brother putting on
an exhibition.]
- What are you doing?
Hey, Ji Hyo...
He has pants on underneath.
Don't get the wrong idea.
- He has pants on.
- Don't misunderstand what happened.
He has pants on underneath.
What are you doing?
- It's okay, he has pants on.
- What is he doing?
- Hurry up and put your pants back on.
- Why are you taking your pants off?
[LOTJ Team-
Young Jin Woon's turn to practice.]
- You have to do it ten times.
- He's good at this.
You have to jump high and slow.
- There you go!
- Great job!
Five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
[Wow... even manages a double swing?]
We've got this in the bag!
Why do the double swing when
that wasn't even called for?
- Why did you do that?
- I wanted to see if I could.
- Are you showing off or what?
- What are you doing?
- Why is he doing that?
- We decided to show off his skills.
- Look at how happy you look!
- We're challenging you!
You guys are way too
hung up on yourselves!
To be honest,
I don't know why I did that myself.
I think Jong Kook should do this.
[Time to practice the hoola hoop.]
I think you need to do this one.
- I'm not good with hoola hoops.
- There's no way you can do that.
[Is Kkuk really the man for it?]
- Wow, Jong Kook...
- He can't do it!
- I don't think you're the one for that.
- Why isn't this working?
- Who's going to do it from our team?
- I used to be so good at this!
That's really heavy.
- You think you can handle that?
- Hye Bin, that's...
- Wow, Leesadon!
- She's doing it!
[Leesadon is resurrected!]
[Will she be able to catch the balls too?]
That's scary!
- Hye Jin, you have to catch the balls!
- Wow, that's scary.
- Wow... how did you do that?
- The fact that you did that is impressive.
- I'll do this one.
- You only have to catch three.
- Since I only have to catch three...
- A guy has to catch five.
- I don't think I can do that one.
- I don't know which one to do.
[The Running Man team is getting an
apprehensive feeling about the mission.]
[Ready for their first attempt.]
Running Man Team!
Let's show them the difference
between the jungle and the city!
- Let's show them!
- I'll show them!
Let's show them!
- City!
- Our pride is on the line!
[R1- Suk Jin. R2- Ji Hyo, Jong Kook.
R3- Jae Suk. R4- Kwang Soo. R5- Gary.]
[Start]
- Suk Jin, you can do this!
- You've got a good start!
- You have to set the balls back further.
- Why did you put the balls up so close?
- What are you doing?
- You have to put the flippers on first!
[Big-nose certainly is
the black hole for the team.]
What are you doing?
[Fails as expected...]
Calm down!
- One, two, three, four...
- Come on!
- Seriously!
- that's okay, you can do it!
One, two, three, four...
[Ah, again...]
- What the heck is the matter with him?
- Calm down!
Ji Suk Jin!
[It seems as though he might use up
the 199 seconds all on his own.]
He's going to use up
199 seconds all by himself!
Get ready!
It'll be our turn soon!
Suk Jin will never be able to jump
ten times in a row!
Seven, eight, nine, ten!
[Ah... he trips on the tenth jump.]
- Nine.
- You only got nine jumps!
Let's give up on this round!
- Let's just keep going!
- It's been more than two minutes.
What are you doing? Seriously.
- It's been more than two minutes!
- What the heck are you doing?
[The Chief is getting some rest underwater.]
[Fail- 199 seconds is up.]
- 199 seconds is up already.
- He used up the time all by himself.
- Why are you so greedy with the time?
- It feels like 199 hours have passed.
- I can't do ten.
- You failed.
- Gary...
- Gary, you give it a try.
[Switching out with Gary?]
- This is hard.
- You try. Getting ten is impossible.
This is so annoying!
- This is so annoying!
- Isn't it annoying?
I feel like I've contracted the rage virus.
What are you going to do?
Not one of you can do it.
How is it that none of us
can even do anything?
That's good. You do that one.
Don't waste anymore of your energy.
Don't waste your energy.
You can do it.
[Mr. Capable- Tackling even
the jump rope with his strength.]
That guy seriously...
[Ultimately switching out the first player.]
[The Laws of the Jungle Team's attempt.]
[R1- Jin Woon. R2- Jung Chul, Woo Jin.
R3- Byung Man, R4- Hye Bin, R5- Ha Ha.]
Let's see how good Jin Woon is!
I'd like to challenge you!
- I'd like to challenge you!
[Start]
There he goes!
- You dropped one of the balls!
- Okay!
He dropped one of the balls.
He took too long to get
the flippers on!
- Why are you taking so long with them?
- It's good! Keep it up!
- The jump rope is all twisted up!
- They left it in a twisted knot!
Someone twisted up the rope!
[Darn!]
One, two, three, four, five, six,
seven, eight, nine, ten!
[But he succeeds at first attempt.]
[Second course-
Taking off the socks underwater.]
Let's keep calm.
Are things going well under there?
[Succeeds at taking off the first one!]
[Succeeds at taking off the second one!]
Did you do it?
[Third course- Alkkagi underwater.]
Start!
[An expert?
Facing the challenge with an ease.]
[Total concentration with
his eyes wide open.]
[Third course- Success!]
- He succeeded.
- Okay! Success!
[Must hurry to the fourth course!]
[Fourth course-
Catch the balls while hoola hooping.]
- How is she doing that?
- Great job! You caught one!
[Need to catch three to pass.
Succeeds at catching the first one!]
Keep your gaze upward!
[Succeeds at catching the second ball!]
It's okay.
What if we succeed this
on our first try?
[If she catches one more ball,
then they pass the fourth course!]
Just one more!
[Success!]
[Now to the final fifth course!]
Quickly, quickly!
[Fifth course-
Ride the slide down and score the ball.]
Nice, nice, nice!
[There's not much time left!]
[Fearful Ro-Ro gets on the slide.]
Why isn't he coming out?
Did he get caught along the way?
There he is!
[And down he comes!]
The balls!
Where is the basket?
[He just need to take the basket and
make a goal with one of the balls!]
[Darn!
He lost three of the balls!]
[Will he make it?]
[If he can just score one,
then they pass all the courses.]
[Goal in!]
[Succeeds at passing the five courses!]
[199 seconds mission...
what is their record?]
Your time is 240 seconds.
[Ah... 240 seconds!]
Can you give us more time?
We were great considering
that it was our first attempt.
Hye Bin, you did great.
- Let's do this!
- I'll get it done in one try, okay?
- I think he's cleaning up the area.
- I'll get it done in first attempt.
We've got ourselves an
Olympic athlete here.
[R1- Jong Kook. R2- Suk Jin, Jae Suk.
R3- Ji Hyo. R4- Kwang Soo. R5- Gary.]
Fighting!
- There you go!
- That's good!
[Mr. Capable's quick speed!]
- Let's do this!
- You need to get ten!
One, two, three...
You have to succeed at first attempt!
You're going to lose your energy.
Slow down, slow down.
One, two, three, four, five, six,
seven, eight, nine...
[Ah... on the ninth one!]
This is how it depletes your energy.
Five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten!
[Finally!]
Quickly!
[Why is he ringing the gong again?]
- Quickly!
- Why do that again? We don't have time!
[Off to the second course-
Take off the socks underwater.]
[Big-nose Brother is the black hole
with everything that he does.]
What's taking you so long to get there?
Why are you so heavy?
[Oh no, the balls...]
Come on, that's just too much!
[Oh my... all the balls!]
We don't have any balls left!
Why couldn't you do that?
[Fails from having lost all their balls.]
He's way too heavy.
I think Ji Hyo needs to do this one.
- Everyone...
- Yes?
If both teams agree,
I'll lessen the first course to five jumps.
- No, we refuse.
- No! Let's just do ten.
Why are you refusing it when
everyone else is okay with it?
It gives us a better advantage!
We can't give them any leverage!
- Five. Let's just do five. Those that agree?
- By show of hands. One, two, three!
[Ultimately deciding on five...]
[Agrees on five jumps.]
- In that case, let's just settle on five.
- Yes.
- I'll do it then.
- Okay, let's just let him do it.
- Okay, we're good.
- Running Man Team, get ready.
[R1- Suk Jin. R2- Ji Hyo, Jong Kook.
R3- Gary, R4- Kwang Soo, R5- Jae Suk.]
- Fighting!
- Fighting. Stay calm!
Think of this as your last chance!
Fighting!
[Wow!
Succeeds at his first attempt!]
- You succeeded!
- Run!
[Off to the second course-
Taking off the socks underwater.]
- Here!
- Quickly!
[Strong Kkuk lies in wait.]
Show them what you can do
instead of just chattering away!
- That's a very good point.
- That's what you need to do!
- Concentrate on taking off the socks.
- You're almost there!
- He's almost got it off.
[Success!]
[Third course- Gary]
Go!
[Even though Chief Byung Man,
who's an expert made it look easy...]
[Keeping control isn't easy
due to the buoyancy.]
It's okay!
[A relaxed spectator.]
[Finally succeeds!]
[Must hurry to the fourth course!]
We may be able to pull this off!
- Kwang Soo!
- Set it down over there.
[Kwang Soo's in charge of
the hoola hoop.]
Look up!
It really hurts!
Listen to that sound.
Just listen to that sound.
- Just endure it!
- It hit him in the pit of his stomach.
- Hurry it up!
[The clock is ticking.]
- There you go! Now, look up!
- You're doing good!
- Nice!
- Just look up!
[He caught it!]
[A guy must catch five.]
- Three!
- Look up!
- This is your last one!
- Keep it going!
[Just one more!]
- You have to keep it going!
- Just keep it going!
[Success!]
[Now to the final fifth course!]
Hurry up!
I don't think I can do this.
[Not much time left on the clock!]
[Must get down the slide quickly
and score their goal.]
[Needs to be careful to
protect the balls in the basket...]
[Oh no!]
[But as long as he scores one ball!]
[Please...]
[The last ball.]
[Ah...]
[Fail]
- You should've thrown it better!
- You're totally a younger Suk Jin.
What are you doing?
Your record was 211 seconds.
Jong Kook!
- Can you do the hoola hoop?
- Do better next time around.
[No one is interested
in doing the hoola hoop.]
- Let's switch!
- No, you do it.
[Back to the Jungle Team's turn.]
- Fighting!
- Let's do this!
Jung Chul!
Let's do the battle call!
- The laws of the jungle!
- Fighting!
[R1- Jung Chul. R2- Woo Jin, Jin Woon.
R3- Byung Man. R4- Hye Bin. R5- Ha Ha.]
- Fighting!
- Jung Chul, fighting!
- Let's stay calm.
- Even Suk Jin did it earlier.
[Will he succeed at his first attempt?]
[Pass!]
[Here I come!]
[Second course-
Take off the socks underwater.]
Show them what you can do, Jin Woon!
Jin Woon, take off the socks!
Kim Jong Kook used his strength earlier.
Stay calm.
Watch how Jin Woon does this
and learn from him!
[Succeeds at taking off his first one!]
Stay calm and take your time!
[Succeeds at taking off
his second one right away!]
Nice!
[Already heading off to the third course!
Underwater alkkagi.]
[Underwater submersion expert,
Kim Byung Man.]
Go, go, go, go, go!
[It seems as though he may even be
able to stay down there to play badook.]
He's taking longer this time around.
How can Byung Man not even breathe?
[Calm]
Check and see if Byung Man is breathing!
[Success!]
Byung Man has gills.
[Off to the fourth course.
To the sole female on their team, Hye Bin.]
[Ah... didn't catch the first ball.]
Take it easy.
Take it easy and catch the ball.
There you go!
[Succeeds at catching the second one!]
[Just one last ball.]
[Pass!]
[Now off to the final fifth course!]
[Chief Byung Man running along together!]
Run!
Quickly!
Run faster!
[Finally arrives to the summit with
Chief Byung Man at his heels.]
But why is he running with him?
[Last course- the slide.]
[Please!]
[Chief Byung Man goes down
the slide too!]
[Now if he can only make a goal!]
Dong Hoon is really good
at making shots.
[Amazing!
The time isn't up yet!]
He's going to score right away.
[The ball unfortunately
hits the side and misses!]
[Will he make it this time?]
[Goal in!]
[Passes all five courses!]
[How can this be...]
We did it!
[What is the record?]
[193 seconds- Success!]
One, two, three, four.
The Jung, the Jung, the laws of the jungle!
[The Laws of the Jungle Team wins!]
The first victory goes to
the Laws of the Jungle Team!
Running Man Team now has to choose a hostage
who won't be able to participate in the final.
Please choose your man.
[Big-nose Brother left behind
on his own.]
Okay, please shout out the name of your
chosen hostage on three.
- One, two, three.
- Ji Suk Jin.
- He's your chosen one?
- We already discussed this.
- But you can keep playing the games for now.
- When did we discuss this?
- When did you discuss this?
- It wasn't a long discussion.
We've already decided last year.
We know since we've been doing this
for three years already.
[Heading off immediately
to the next location!]
- I can't believe we lost.
- Yeah, we won!
What was it that you said?
That Running Man Team can't be beaten?
What did you say?
[A giant horizontal bar in the water?]
As you can see behind you,
your next mission is...
the group horizontal bar competition
Group horizontal bar competition?
[Second mission-
Group horizontal bar competition.]
[All the members participate in the fight,
and the team with last member standing wins.]
- But Byung Man's really good at hanging.
- Byung Man, he's really good at hanging on.
- Wow, this really is...
- This game is for Byung Man's benefit.
There aren't many of us who can
even cross the horizontal bar.
- Crossing this is a mission for us.
- Why is he looking at me?
- How many certifications do you have?
- He's amazing at sports.
I have eight certification
just in water sports alone.
[Seriously? Eight certificates
just in water sports alone?]
And did you know that Hye Bin used to
do rhythmic gymnastics?
- Really?
- When I was younger.
They have the total advantage.
This team isn't one for us to
go up against right now!
But does Jung Chul always have
that sad expression on his face?
I actually have a very happy
expression on my face right now.
What's your nickname, Jung Chul?
- Your nickname when you were younger.
- During my school years?
When I used to be in school,
I was nicknamed, 'Fly-paper'.
Why were you called that?
Because when I used to get in fights,
I stuck myself to a person and didn't let go.
Then he would be perfect for this mission.
[Then does this mean that this mission
would be perfect for him?]
Then let's see what Fly-paper can do first.
[Filled with expectations to see
what Fly-paper can do.]
[Best out of three-
Aquatic horizontal bar competition.]
Wow... this isn't going to be easy.
I already can't even reach.
[Neither of the teams' floats offer
them any room to move around.]
[Uh... he's short.]
- We have to win this time.
- Of course we have to win.
- Fighting.
- Fighting!
The Jung, the Jung,
the laws of the jungle!
[First round- Start!]
Let's go!
We can't be hasty about our attack.
He's going up.
Byung Man is going up to the top.
[Oh my... climbing up top right away?]
[Expert at air walking.
Kim Byung Man walking with a fast pace.]
[Walking on top of the metal bars
as if he's walking down the street.]
[Within moments, he arrives on
top of the Running Man Team.]
[Fly-paper Jung Chul continuing the drive
and getting on his way!]
Stick yourself right there.
I'm coming.
I'm sticking myself to the spot.
[What!
Even Hye Bin?]
[We're from the jungle!]
[Tree climbing is a part of our
everyday lives.]
[These members have conquered
the wilds of the jungle.]
[You can call us, Spiderman.]
- What was that?
- Who was that?
[What the heck?]
[The expert of the jungle
falling off his tree.]
[Woo Jin terminates himself.]
[Not every member of the
Jungle Team can be good.]
[This man looks like he's just
lounging around in his living room.]
- They look like they live up there.
- Look at how comfortable they look.
[Even Jin Woon is
getting in his attack mode.]
They're all up there now.
They're like zombies!
[Crowing in on Running Man members.]
[Concentrating their attack on
Jin Woon first!]
[Huh?]
[A forceful attack?]
[Running Man having found their chance
forcefully attacks!]
[But Jin Woon is hanging on!]
[Ro-Ro finally sets off to help Jin Woon!]
[Almost having been exhausted
by their concentrated attack.]
[Short Ro-Ro takes care of
eliminating himself on his own.]
[Jin Woon doesn't go down alone!
He ousts Yoo Hyuk along with him!]
Someone lost their pants!
Someone's pants are floating over there.
[Laws of the Jungle Team
concentrates on their attack!]
[Female warrior Hye Jin kicks around
without any hesitation.]
[Complete chaos.]
[Gary - Out!]
[Laws of the Jungle Team's blind attack!]
[Claiming their spot on the horizontal bar.]
Nice!
[Just then, even Hye Jin
steps up her force of attack!]
[Ji Hyo - Out!]
[Running Man members finding themselves
in the midst of utter chaos.]
[Just then...]
[Kkuk power!]
[The beastly power of this man who makes
even the impossible become possible.]
[Total power that knows no boundaries
between land and water.]
[Running Man Team's counterattack.]
[Their big hurdle, Byung Man is eliminated!]
[Kwang Soo's plan to take him
down with him!]
[A battle between Running Man's Jong Kook
and Jungle Team's Hye Bin and Jung Chul.]
Stick it out!
Fly-paper! Fly-paper!
[Jung Chul showing his namesake of
sticking like fly-paper to the bars.]
[A two against one
joint attack with Hye Bin.]
[What?]
[This man was still alive?]
Behind you!
Behind you, Jung Chul!
[Remaining survivors-
Running Man 2 vs. Laws of the Jungle 2.]
[Fly-paper sticking it out
with determination.]
[And black hole Big-nosed Brother is...]
I'm sorry!
Hye Bin tells him that she's sorry.
[Hye Bin mercilessly kicking him down.]
[Big-nosed Brother - Out!]
Hang on to him!
You have to hug him.
Hug and hang onto him!
There you go!
[I'm the fly-paper!]
[Fly-paper Jung Chul's plan
to hang on tight!]
[Just then, Hye Bin moves in
on Kkuk's hand!]
[Jung Chul and Jong Kook - Out!]
[Laws of the Jungle wins!]
[Fly-paper Jung Chul's major
role in the win!]
Fly-paper!
[Second round]
We don't need a plan.
Just kill them!
- Hey!
- Jong Kook is alive and on fire.
He's on fire to get the Fly-paper.
I really thought that I had some
sticky paper stuck all over me.
Hye Bin is no joke either.
[Her blind attacks befitting of
a female warrior of the jungle.]
Why don't we start this out with
a one on one face-off?
[One on one face-off first?]
Kim Byung Man is going to be
our first fighter.
Why me?
You can do this, Kwang Soo.
He's not in the jungle anymore.
Kwang Soo, go.
Okay, fine.
[Round two - Start!]
[Giant vs. Shorty]
[But as expected, when faced
with the expert of the wild...]
[Getting into an advantageous point within
a matter of moments.]
[Extreme danger]
[Help from a teammate is on the way!]
[Moves in like a bolt of thunder.]
[Within the blink of an eye,
it turns into a group face-off.]
[Kwang Soo and Ro-Ro are out!]
[Byung Man and Jin Woon
jointly attack Yoo Hyuk.]
[And ultimately falls into the water.]
[Hm...]
[Bowl cut style Yoo Hyuk.]
[Remaining survivors-
Running Man 4 vs. Laws of the Jungle 5.]
You have to help him!
Jong Kook is going to get him otherwise!
Jin Woon!
You have to get Jong Kook!
[Expert vs. Mr. Capable]
[A real battle between the
two strongest warriors.]
[Hm...]
[So cozy...]
Gary, you have to get
Byung Man off of him!
[Ultimately falls in the water!]
[Byung Man and Kkuk are ultimately
ousted simultaneously.]
[Running Man's Suk Jin and Ji Hyo
vs. Laws of the Jungle's Jin Woon.]
[Big-nosed Brother is in danger!]
[And is ousted without a fuss.]
[Running Man's Ji Hyo vs.
Law of the Jungle's Jin Woon.]
We can't let this go to
the third round!
- But how am I supposed to...
- Just do it!
- Hug her and dunk her!
- Hug her and let her fall softly.
[Huh?]
What are you two doing right now?
You're supposed to be
playing the game!
What are you two doing right now?
[Blank Ji desperately
clinging on to Jin Woon.]
[Ji Hyo in danger!]
You're doing good!
[Gently...]
[We won!]
[Laws of the Jungle wins!]
[Running Man Team has to pick
another hostage from their team.]
I'll do it.
You can oust me.
- Just oust me.
- You guys are making me tear up.
For the sake of our team...
- I'll eliminate myself.
- No, I'll eliminate myself!
No, I'll eliminate myself!
Just eliminate all of us together!
- In that case...
- No, I'll sacrifice myself!
It's me.
Let's just do it that way.
- One, two, three.
- Yoo Jae Suk!
[Yoo Hyuk as hostage- Agreed.]
What is this?
It looks like it's set up for a sled.
Do we just sit here?
[Sit on top of the special stage that's
been set up on top of an ice rink.]
I wonder what we're
going to do here?
Running Man vs. Laws of the Jungle.
Survivor Race.
Wait!
Our team is going to read it.
Just because you guys won the
last two missions...
You're crowding me, so just sit down.
- Why aren't our two slaves coming over here?
- We're not slaves, we're hostages.
Why are you calling us slaves?
We're not your slaves.
Please read it for us.
Running Man vs. Laws of the Jungle.
Survivor Race.
Find the real expert!
You're really feeling feisty now.
Find the expert!
[Fly-paper's mood has improved
considerably after ousting Mr. Capable.]
Everyone will act as if you're an expert.
But there's only one real expert.
The person who's going to act it out has
to act well as to not get caught.
- We're all set then!
- And that's how you win.
[Must find not real expert,
and not the poser in order to win!]
- What is that?
- It's a sled.
The reason why we're doing it here is
because of that sled.
[The mission is being carried out in this
cold ice rink because of the sled being used.]
This is the first category that
Running Man Team will be doing.
What is 'Expert actress'?
[Expert Actress]
Expert actress?
All six of you will be calling someone.
But there will only be one person who
will be talking to a real actress.
And the rest of you will be pretending
to be talking to someone on the phone.
- That sounds easy.
- I think that'll be easy.
I'm really obvious with things like that.
I don't know what to do.
- We're all good at things like this.
- We're all good actors.
We may not know who it's going to be,
but one of us will be talking to an actress?
- A real actress?
- We're calling a real actress?
- Is it a real actress?
- It's an actress?
Who... who are we calling?
Ji Hyo's a good actress,
and Suk Jin's really bad.
[Having turned around while RM Team
decides who'll be making the real call.]
- We're really going to be talking to this person?
- Wait a second.
- I can't believe that we'll be talking to her!
- Isn't she really busy?
I know her very well.
[Just which one of these members will
really be talking to the actress?]
- Hello?
- Hello!
[It seems like
everyone's talking to someone...]
It's not Gary!
[One of them is really talking
to a real actress.]
Suk Jin, just hang up the phone.
- How about one at a time?
- Can you take turns talking one at a time?
Have you been well?
- Pass!
- Why?
- You're not it!
- Let me talk on the phone!
You look awkward even to me.
[And Ji Hyo?]
Yes, we just need to talk
for a little while.
If you can talk to me for about a minute,
I would really appreciate it.
[Is he talking to someone for real?
Yoo Hyuk has a big smile on his face.]
[And Big-nosed Brother?]
- Pass!
- He says pass!
- Kwang Soo.
- She says she's filming right now.
- Just hang up if you have nothing to say.
- Of course, we're filming right now.
I didn't mean us.
- Seriously?
- I'm serious! Serious!
Didn't you tell me that he
can't act earlier?
[Mr. Capable talking with his face
hidden behind is hand.]
People usually hide their face
when they're not feeling confident.
Okay, Jae Suk.
[Smiley face Jae Suk's turn.]
I really want to react to this call right now
but if I do, the other team...
Suk Jin, just hang up!
I told you, we're all set with you!
- Gary, you can hang up too!
- I'm talking on the phone right now!
Why do I have to hang up?
What's wrong with everyone?
Can you all just keep it down?
- Do you even know who this is?
- Do you have any idea who this is?
- You have no idea who I'm talking to!
- Do you even know who it is?
I'm going to hang up now.
Bye!
Who were you talking to?
Just tell us who you were talking to.
- Can we tell them?
- Can we reveal who it was?
- Everyone at the same time.
One, two, three!
- Son Ye Jin!
- Angelina Jolie.
- Did you say Son Ye Jin?
- Son Ye Jin?
- I was talking to Son Ye Jin too.
- No, you weren't. Tell us the truth.
- I really was talking to Son Ye Jin!
- He said he was talking to Angelina Jolie.
- Angelina Jolie?
I'm her Korean language teacher.
Jolie?
I'm Galie.
What's her favorite food?
You food... what like?
Okay. Chapagheri?
(Chapaghetti- Popular ramen)
Chapagheri?
- Chapagheri?
- I wonder if it's Gary?
Galie... that's funny.
I think Suk Jin down to the right are fake.
And the other three are possible real ones.
The feeling I got is that it's one
of the three up front.
- Kwang Soo?
- I don't think it's Jong Kook.
I don't think it's Jong Kook either.
Kwang Soo, why don't you ask the person
on the other line a question?
Ask her who her favorite member
is on Running Man.
Who's your favorite member
on Running Man?
- Yes!
- We're set. It's not him.
[Kwang Soo disqualified?]
[There's no way an actress would say
that Kwang Soo is her favorite?]
- He almost had me.
- Seriously...
- Who next?
- How about Jong Kook?
- Ask Song Ye Jin what her birthday is?
- Her birthdate?
Hello?
Look at how awkward he's acting.
It's definitely not him.
- It's not him.
- Ye Jin, what is your birthdate?
- Don't stutter. Don't stutter.
- When is your birthday?
April... 28th?
Okay, I got it.
Jae Suk, this time, you ask
Son Ye Jin when her birthday is.
[Jae Suk has to ask her the same
question this time?]
To be honest,
I'm not that close to Ye Jin.
- That's okay.
- It's okay?
Listen, Ye Jin... they want me
to ask you for your birthday.
July...
- What year was she born?
- July 26th.
- July 26th?
Okay, no more questions.
You've got ten seconds to give your answer.
[Must choose the one person who was talking
to the actress within 10 seconds?]
Okay, it's not Gary, not sure about Ji Hyo,
and it's not Suk Jin either.
I think it could be Kwang Soo.
What if it's really Kwang Soo?
Why do you all think that
it's not me?
- Why do you keep thinking it's not me?
- Could it be Gary?
Our show is on a level where it's possible
to get Angelina on the line now.
- Of course, she can!
- Even Jackie Chan's been on our show.
You think it's Kwang Soo?
- I think it's Jae Suk.
- I think it's Jae Suk too.
But I think it could be Jong Kook too.
[Could it really be Jae Suk?]
- It's now time to give your answer.
- I thought it was Jae Suk at first.
- But I think he's lying.
- What about Song Ji Hyo?
[Ji Hyo's silence is making her
even more suspicious.]
[Which one of them was really
talking to the actress?]
- I really think it's Jae Suk though.
- Okay, let's just go with him.
- Okay.
- One, two, three!
Yoo Jae Suk!
Okay, the other person
is still on the line, right?
We're going to start with Gary
and see who the person was.
But if it really is Angelina Jolie,
wouldn't it be just unbelievable?
- That would be just amazing.
- Angelina Jolie...
Then Kang Gary,
please say 'hello' to the other person.
- One, two, three.
- Hello, Jolie?
Hello?
Hello!
Hey, talk to me!
Hello?
[Gary was a lie.]
[Then could it be Ji Hyo?]
Hello?
You can say something.
- Hello?
- It's not her!
[Ji Hyo also was a lie.]
[Time to check Suk Jin.]
We can just skip over Suk Jin.
- You don't have to check?
- No, we don't.
Hello?
Ye Jin?
[Talking into a dead phone.]
[Time to check Kwang Soo.]
My turn?
- If it really is Kwang Soo...
- Ye Jin?
Hello?
[Kwang Soo was really
talking to the actress!]
[And that person is...]
[The goddess, Son Ye Jin.]
- Hello?
- Hi.
Hi, Ye Jin.
- Hi
- This is Kwang Soo.
I know.
[Is she disappointed
to be talking to Kwang Soo?]
Why does it have to be you?
Why does it have to be you I'm talking to?
I'm very sorry for that.
- You're sounding so awkward right now.
- I really don't know what to say!
You're acting like
one of the fake ones right now.
We won, Ye Jin!
I didn't know myself.
She just laughed.
[Is Jin Woon her fan?]
- Hello.
- Hello!
- Ye Jin!
- Stop pretending that you're her friend!
- Seriously!
When are you coming on our show?
- Hello?
- Hi, Ye Jin!
I got married!
I'm sorry!
Ye Jin!
- What are you saying right now?
- No kidding. Why would she care?
Where are you right now, Ye Jin?
I'm the spy today.
What?
You're the spy?
[Is she still immersed in the spy role
that she played the last time she was on?]
Ye Jin, who did you say was your favorite
member of Running Man was earlier?
Gary.
[Her favorite Running Man member?
Gary!]
Of all people, she picks Gary?
- Jong Kook is disappointed.
- After all the help I've given her?
- I'll put Chief Byung Man on the phone.
- Yes, please.
Hey, Ye Jin.
- It's been a while.
[Acting like they're really close?]
Um, it's very nice to meet you.
I really wanted to act like
we were close.
- I really thought you two were close.
- I really wanted to act it.
- Ye Jin?
- Yes?
I know that you're busy,
but it's nice to hear your voice.
Well, I really do love Running Man.
I know that you must be busy,
but if you can fit it into your schedule...
- If you have the time...
- Okay, I'll come on the show again.
- Yes, you should come back.
- Come back on our show.
- Yes.
- We... we really like you!
I love you!
I love you, Ye Jin!
- Ye Jin... we really do like you.
- Ye Jin!
I got married!
Thank you, Ye Jin.
- Yes, thank you.
- Thanks again.
[Miss Son Ye Jin, thank you for taking the
time out of your busy schedule to talk to us!]
- She's just so pretty.
- She has such a kind heart.
- She really does have a pretty heart.
- In the midst of shooting her drama too.
She really did take the time out of her
precious schedule to help us out.
Anyways, the important thing is that
Running Man Team won the first round.
[With the score even at 1:1,
it's time for the final round.]
It's the final round.
We'll win this.
- Come and get it!
- We'd like to challenge you!
- Expert in acting.
- What is that?
Five of you are going to be sitting
in a very uncomfortable seat.
And just one of you will be sitting
in a comfortable seat.
- Thus...
- They have to find that person?
They have to find the person who really
is sitting in the comfortable chair.
- Then let's do the acting.
- We'll do the acting.
Hey, no way!
Look at what we're sitting on! No way!
[Oh my...]
[Even though it feels like sitting
on the sofa for the expert...]
[To us, it's a seat of torture.]
We'll guess!
- No, we'll act!
- I think it would be better for us to act.
- Let's act.
- Jae Suk, I sat on that thing before.
You can't act on that thing.
- Jae Suk, we can't do that.
- No, we'll do the acting.
- Jae Suk, I've sat on that before.
- Jae Suk! We can't do that!
[Laws of the Jungle will be the one
to guess the actor this time.]
- This isn't going to be easy.
- I still sit on that when I'm home.
[The real expert using the cone for
a chair when he's at home?]
Just how painful is this thing?
Why did you say you want to do this?
- This is going to kill me.
- Ouch!
- Why did you say we were going to do it?
- I told you we should do the guessing!
[Ways to tell who's really
sitting on the cone.]
This is how they'll sit.
Their upper body is going to straighten out.
[It may even be possible to tell right away
if they're asked to shake in their seat!]
Let's just start this thing.
- Okay, please turn around.
- Turn around.
Set, go!
Can you straighten out your back
and say, 'Hooray'?
- Hooray!
- Get up from your seats.
- Shouldn't we stay seated?
- Why?
- You can stand up.
But it's possible to hear the chair sound.
I don't think getting up is right.
We're already standing up.
Okay, sit back down.
- Stand up.
- Why are you doing this?
Sit back down.
Okay, time to start the wave.
Set, go!
Starting with Gary.
It's fine if you have to push yourself,
but I want you to turn a full circle.
- Like that?
- Sure, I can do that.
- I can do that.
- That's dangerous though.
Jae Suk can start.
Gary can start then?
That was very natural.
How did you do that?
How did you do it?
Do it the best you can.
Just support yourself and do it.
Spin around.
- I bet that really hurts.
- Those three are out.
[The current three are sitting on the cone?]
I'm not sure.
2Guaranteed he's sitting on the cone.
- Guaranteed he's sitting on the cone.
- 5000 percent he is. I bet all my money.
Here I go.
Why did you come up with a
game like this?
Why do we have to sit on the cones?
[His face is turning beet red.]
His height is getting shorter by the second.
- Is that cone embedded in your body?
- I did it the best I could.
I really did it the best I could.
[Why don't we take a look?]
[Sitting and turning
right on top of the cone.]
[Wow...]
- I really did it right in the center.
- I did it on the center too.
- Are we all set then?
- I did it right in the center.
- I was right on.
- Why don't we ask them to do one more thing?
How about this? Asking them to
do this to the next person?
[Pressing down on the person
next to them.]
- That's a bit...
- Do you by chance have an ambulance ready?
If you do, then I'll do it.
Why don't you show us how
close you can be?
Starting with Gary.
Ji Hyo, you have to put
your weight on him.
Please don't do that.
Let's break up.
Wait.
Why are you pushing my hand away?
- Let's do it right.
- Why are you shoving my hand away?
Seriously, just do it right.
That's good!
Kwang Soo...
Please go easy on me.
- Kwang Soo...
- Can I get on his shoulders?
Yes, that's okay.
Don't do that!
What you're doing isn't right!
I bet Suk Jin has the
comfortable chair.
It's Jong Kook's turn?
[Yoo Hyuk to press down on Mr. Capable.]
[Mr. Capable refusing adamantly.]
You have to do it too!
You're the one who wanted to do it!
Let's see how well you do it.
[Jong Kook to press down on Jae Suk.]
- Go easy on me.
- Just easy on him.
Go easy.
How can you... how can you
press down right in the middle?
[Jae Suk's current situation.]
You have ten seconds to discuss your answer
and you have to say the name out loud.
This is hard.
As for the people that I'm sure about,
Jong Kook and Jae Suk are sitting on the cone.
Jong Kook?
[Who's the one person sitting
on the comfortable chair?]
- What about Suk Jin?
- It's either Gary or Ji Hyo.
I think it's Ji Hyo.
Don't you think it would be less
painful for Ji Hyo though?
- You may be right.
- Just hang on a little bit longer.
- I really can't stand it any longer.
- Can you hurry this along?
Why don't you come over here
and try sitting on it?
You give it a try!
- Did you even try this?
- Try a simulation before you do this again.
- You want to choose Gary or Ji Hyo?
- I think Gary.
- Gary?
- Let's go with Gary.
- One, two, three.
- Gary!
Gary!
[Gary is chosen to be the one
sitting on the comfortable chair.]
Just one of them are sitting
on a comfortable chair.
You chose Gary, right?
Let's check and see if you're right.
Look straight ahead.
[Time to reveal the answer.]
One...
Two...
Three.
[Jong Kook is the sitting on
the comfortable chair!]
[They were deceived by
Mr. Capable's acting!]
I never even imagined it would be him!
Your acting really was...
- I did it with everything I had!
- I never even thought it would be him.
Jong Kook never does anything
that's bad for his health.
[Mr. Capable, the one who hates
being in pain the most...]
He never does anything
that's bad for his health.
I don't like having to endure any pain.
That's actually pointier than the ones
used the last time I was on the show.
And you turned 360 degrees on that thing.
[Time for the real expert
to show us his skills.]
- It's no big deal for Byung Man.
- This is comfortable for me.
This is comfortable for me.
That was very difficult for us.
Gary, can you spin around again?
How did you do that?
It gets deeper into you when you turn.
Gary just turned around on that thing.
[He's enduring it so well.]
We could see you sinking deeper into it.
Do you know that you started
sinking in deeper?
- Try it. It's hard.
- Try sitting on it.
It's not easy.
What about the Fly-paper?
I bet he'd be good at it.
- Fly-paper can stick it out.
- Fly-paper can't do it.
See? I told you he can't do it.
This is extremely painful.
[Pain that can't be understood
until they experience it themselves.]
- How did you do that?
- You have no idea until you try it.
Thus, Running Man Team wins the
'Expert Competition'.
[Find the real expert!
Running Man Team wins!]
- You pick who you're going to send.
- Who's coming over?
[Who's the hostage that the losing team,
Laws of the Jungle is going to choose?]
I bet it's one of these three.
Jung Chul, Woo Jin or Ha Ha.
- Have you decided?
- Yes.
Then shout out the name
on the count of three.
- One, two, three.
- Noh Woo Jin.
[Woo Jin is now a hostage of
the Running Man Team.]
What are we going to do now?
[Must take off the name tags off
the hostages first.]
[Exchanging their hostages.]
[What role will the hostages be playing?]
We'll move on to the final location
with your hostages.
- Where are we going?
- To Paju movie village.
- Isn't being here better?
- It is since my junior is the chief.
So what is this all about then?
[The two hostages preferring
their current situation?]
Running Man, fighting!
I will do anything that I'm told to do.
[Final mission location-
Paju 'E' village.]
- Do you know what your crimes are?
- Which way do I go?
I shouted out, 'Running Man, fighting'
in the car about a hundred times.
- Come here!
- They said I didn't sound sincere.
How about letting the hostage read it?
- Here.
- Read it clearly in a loud voice.
Final mission, name tag elimination.
I can't feel your sincerity!
The team with the last surviving member in
the name tag elimination game wins.
But if you find your hostage and put
their name tag back on them
the hostage will then be able to
participate in the name tag elimination.
Who do you think you're
pointing at?
Let's lock them up somewhere.
[Both team to start the race after
locking up their hostages.]
We have to lock them up
somewhere safe.
[They can choose where they're going to
hide their hostages on their own.]
- It's nice in here.
- It's nice and warm in here.
Okay, then I'll just stay here.
[Hostage Jae Suk in lockdown.]
I'll sit here quietly.
[Hostage Noh Woo Jin in lockdown.]
[Hostage Big-nose being taken to
the shabbiest of the hiding places.]
[Hostage Big-nose in lockdown.]
[All the hostage lockdowns are now complete.]
[Just then!]
[Referees coming out of nowhere to
suddenly blindfold them.]
- What is this for?
- What are you doing?
- Are you taking us elsewhere?
- You're separating us?
[All the members being scattered about
and separated from one another.]
[Taking each player to a different place
with the blindfold over their eyes.]
You can now take off your blindfolds
and start the game.
Three, two, one.
Game, start!
[Running Man vs. Laws of the Jungle-
Chase game, Start!]
[The real battle starts now!]
[Running Man vs. Laws of the Jungle.]
[The jungle team naturally blending in
to the bushes in their hunt.]
[Lightly flies up into the air to
climb up onto the wall!]
How are you going to get up here?
[Chief Byung Man
making his own path in his search.]
[Mr. Capable's surprise attack from
his ambush position!]
[And in the opposite direction
is Kwang Soo!]
Byung Man!
How am I supposed to catch him?
What the heck was that?
[Having escaped danger in lightning speed
to get himself back to safety!]
But... since he's never done it before,
he doesn't know to check his back.
He didn't see me hiding in the bushes.
[That's right...
it's all about ambush attacks today.]
[Jung Chul and Ha Ha on the other hand
are on a search for Noh Woo Jin.]
Noh Woo Jin!
Woo Jin.
Woo Jin!
Noh Woo Jin.
[Where is he?]
We have to find Jae Suk.
[Ji Hyo and Jong Kook agreeing to
find their mate, Jae Suk first.]
[Huh?]
[He found him!]
[Hye Bin having lying in wait
in the empty refrigerator!]
[An ambush!]
- Please don't do that.
- Jong Kook...
[Stuttering his words from
the shock of her attack.]
- I have no choice but to eliminate you.
- You can't.
- Hye Jin...
- You can't use force on a girl like this.
Just get out of here then.
Ji Hyo!
Hurry up and help me!
[Just then!
Blank Ji appears to rescue him!]
[Savior Blank Ji coming to rescue Kkuk,
who's known for his weakness towards women.]
- Just grab onto her.
- Are you putting that on me?
[Kkuk uses that moment to reattach
Jae Suk's name tag onto his back.]
[Running Man Team rescues Jae Suk
from his imprisonment!]
I had no idea that it would be Jong Kook.
Wait!
- Please don't!
- Hye Bin...
[Jeon Hye Bin - Out!]
[Hye Bin unfortunately gets ousted after
staying hidden in the fridge for 30 minutes.]
We had no choice.
[On the other hand, players are starting to
face-off with each other in various spots.]
[If they let their guard down even for a
second, they're sure to get ousted!]
[Ha Ha - Out!]
[Ha Ha, out.
Ha Ha, out.]
We are Running Man!
Running Man forever!
[So you're back to your sanity...]
Jong Kook!
Jong Kook.
He saw me, he saw me!
He saw me.
Gary... Gary!
[Flagging down Gary who's
holding onto Suk Jin's name tag!]
Hurry up and go in there.
He's to the left!
Suk Jin!
- Suk Jin, where are you?
- I'm over here!
- Over here!
- Where?
[If he rescues Suk Jin, all members
of the Running Man Team remains!]
- Come over here.
- Where are you?
I'm behind the stage.
[Gary discovers Suk Jin!]
- It's a total war outside.
- What?
- Okay, let's go!
- Quickly.
[Succeeds in rescuing Suk Jin
from his imprisonment!]
This is going to be an easy win.
[Running Man Team may win
much easier than expected?]
[There's no way...
we'll allow that to happen!]
[Even the Easy Brothers are
basking in their elation today.]
Pil-Chok-Cross!
Why don't we have a face-off?
Man to man.
[Climbing onto the tree?]
[It seems his plan is to use his unique
talents from Laws of the Jungle?]
[Kwang Soo turns his attack
on Jin Woon!]
[An intense 2:2 face-off that they can't
stray their concentration away from!]
[The chief and Jin Woon are retreating?]
Those two are the strongest players
from the jungle team.
- Let's break them.
- We can eliminate them.
Pil-Chok-Cross.
[Totally different glint in their eyes.]
- The Easy Brothers are going to oust you two.
- Suk Jin, don't back away from them.
Suk Jin, you have to face them.
[Now that they've come to their senses,
they realize that they're retreating.]
Let's not be like this!
[Facing each other once again!]
Are you kidding around right now?
[Easy Brothers standing their ground!]
Hey, Kwang Soo!
Are you getting him?
What the heck is this!
[Byung Man attacks from below!]
[Take down! Brings Kwang Soo down by
crumbling his balance with his leg!]
[Within moments...
he turns the battle around!]
[He eliminates Giraffe's name tag!]
[And heads straight towards
Impala right away!]
[Impala's name tag eliminated!]
What the heck?
Is he allowed to use methods like that?
He was using his martial arts
moves on me!
[Easy Brothers having been
taken down by force.]
- Let's finish this.
- Yes.
[Is this the sing of
Laws of the Jungle Team's win?]
[Laws of the Jungle Team manages to
free their member Woo Jin from his jail.]
Should we just go get them?
Woo Jin!
The Jung, the Jung, the Laws of
the Jungle! Fighting!
Hey!
- Woo Jin!
- Sorry, Jong Kook!
- You're really...
- I'm sorry!
Let's go this way.
Jae Suk, this way.
[Planning out their moves
to capture Woo Jin!]
They went that way!
Jin Woon! They went that way!
Look out.
You have to look out over there.
[Byung Man having been lying in wait...]
[Heads straight towards Jae Suk!]
Where did you come from?
[Waiting to attack him from behind!]
[Big match-
Jae Suk vs. Byung Man!]
Grab him.
Grab him right now.
[Woo Jin coming to join the fight!]
[Just then, Gary rushes in
to help Jae Suk!]
[Ace Ji Hyo in extreme danger!]
[Ji Hyo's in danger!]
[Yoo-ruce Willis rushing in to rescue her!]
[Woo Jin's surprise attack!]
[Gary coming in to guard him!]
[Succeeds in eliminating
Woo Jin's name tag!]
[Mr. Capable Jong Kook!]
[Eliminates Jung Chul's name tag!]
Noh Woo Jin, out!
Park Jung Chul, out!
[Jungle Team is back in danger.
Byung Man and Jin Woon are the sole survivors!]
Let's finish this.
[Running Man Team's survivors-
Jae Suk, Jong Kook, Gary and Ji Hyo!]
[All the experts in
the chase are still alive!]
[What is the jungle team's plan?]
Wow... earlier, Byung Man...
I saw him climbing up there earlier.
- Did you see him climb this, Ji Hyo?
- Yes, I saw it.
It was no joke.
- He climbed up there like it was nothing.
- He just flew up there.
Byung Man, seriously...
how do you climb up the tree so easily?
[Nothing they can even do while
watching him do what he did.]
The tree?
I can climb it too.
- You can do that too, Kang Gary?
- Of course, I can. Anyone can do it.
Anyone can do that.
Why can't I?
But...
I think in our situation, it's better to face
them whether it works out or not.
If we keep this up, I think
we'll be chasing each other all night.
[If they keep running, there will be no end!
No other choice but to face them!]
[And just then, the only two that they see
in their view are Ji Hyo and Gary.]
We shouldn't stay separated.
[Gary getting flustered after
seeing them move in on them.]
[Byung Man and Jin Woon
move in on Gary!]
[But Gary is a master of fighting
who is eighth level in martial arts!]
[Byung Man turns his attack on Ji Hyo!]
[Guard Gary rushes in to protect her.]
What are you all doing right now
with me in the middle?
[Sees a chance and ousts Ji Hyo!]
[Turns their attack on Gary immediately!]
[Even though it's Gary,
taking on those two is a tough feat.]
Gary, you're really fast!
[In the blink of an eye,
it turns into a bloody battle!]
Grab one of his arms.
[Oh... if it stays like that...]
[The hand on the name tag!]
[Jin Woon's hand slips!]
[Comrade Yoo-ruce Willis arrives!]
[Gary having withstood their attack!]
- If it was just one of them...
- Let's go, Jin Woon.
Let's get some rest before we continue.
- Let's rest up a little.
- Are you okay, Gary?
[A brief break time from their exhaustion.]
- Wow, Gary... he's so fast!
- I know.
[Extremely surprised by the swiftness
and the skills of Running Man members.]
I almost got eliminated.
- How was it?
- I thought I was in a street fight.
It's a relief that I was able to
help you just in time.
You know that feeling of wishing that
just someone will come to help you out?
- Where in the world is Jong Kook?
- I don't know, he's always off somewhere.
I don't know what he's off
doing by himself.
I have no idea where he went.
[How frustrating...
I will get a chance to ambush them!]
Wow... I never thought the anxiety level
would be this bad from watching it on TV.
Did you really feel anxious?
When I was being held hostage,
I really thought I was a hostage.
So you realized what it's like?
- Oh! It's Ji Hyo!
- Ji Hyo!
- Who ousted you?
- Jin Woon.
[Ace also enters the tiny jail cell.]
Can't you give us a bigger cell?
- I really feel like we're in jail.
- Can't you give us some snacks or something?
So that we can munch on something?
- I'm really hungry.
- Can you feed us?
[Like the calm before the storm...]
[In the midst of the calm eeriness...]
- There they are.
- Where?
They're over there.
[Jae Suk and Gary coming face to face
with Byung Man and Jin Woon!]
- This is such tight quarters.
- Jong Kook... we have to keep an eye out.
I wonder where Jong Kook is?
Don't go too far ahead.
We have to stick together.
They're wondering where Jong Kook is.
They're nervous about Jong Kook.
[Not able to get too close in case
Mr. Capable is lying in wait for them.]
There's no one else here.
Where's Jong Kook?
We don't know where
Jong Kook is either.
[Nervous energy!]
You have this gentle smile
on your face...
but your body feels like a rock.
- How are you so strong?
- You really are strong.
[The strength of Running Man members
that the Jungle Team is shocked by!]
- I got stronger since starting Running Man.
- You're all so strong!
- Ever since I started Running Man...
- We got stronger since Running Man.
[Their muscles having come from
all the chasing around they've done.]
Both of you are really strong.
Let's end it right here.
[It's time to decide who
the victor will be!]
[A face to face battle!]
[Imminent attack!]
[Jae Suk's back is left unguarded!]
[Byung Man seizes the opportunity
and moves in on Jae Suk!]
[Yoo Jae Suk - Out!]
Where in the world is Kim Jong Kook?
[Two against one!
Gary is in danger!]
Hey!
[Mr. Capable moves in!]
[An ambush attack!]
[Jin Woon retreats as
Mr. Capable moves in!]
Jong Kook!
I'm not ousted yet! Hurry!
[Jin Woon using every ounce of strength he
has to stand up to Mr. Capable!]
[Jong Kook, please...]
[Having endured it for a long while,
Gary ultimately gets ousted.]
[That means there's only one person
left remaining...]
[I'm... Running Man's Mr. Capable!]
[Laws of the Jungle's Byung Man and Jin Woon
vs. Running Man's Mr. Capable.]
Wow... he's freakishly strong!
He's several times stronger than Gary.
[Come and get me!]
[The final face-off with both
the teams' pride on the line!]
We have to get him!
[Wow! He throws his body
down in a defensive mode!]
[But Jong Kook gets his hand
on Byung Man's name tag again!]
[Chief Byung Man, out!]
[Oh my!]
[Jin Woon... gets his hand...
on Mr. Capable's name tag!]
[Jin Woon...]
[Eliminated...]
[Mr. Capable's name tag!]
- What happened?
The Jung, the Jung,
the laws of the jungle!
His name tag is gone!
[Laws of the Jungle Team
is the ultimate victor!]
[In celebration mode!]
One, two, three, four!
The Jung, the Jung, the laws of the jungle!
The Jung, the Jung,
the laws of the jungle!
Ugh, he's so hateful.
Ha Ha is so hateful.
[The winning prize...]
[Six gold rings.]
The Jung, the Jung,
the laws of the jungle!
[Thank you to the cast of Laws of the Jungle
for showing us their wild side.]
Subtitles by DramaFever
[The notorious theft-
The criminal is the Traitors' Club!]
[Leader Kim Sa Kyung is called in to
bring the criminals to justice.]
[Sexy leader, Uhm Jung Hwa-
The premier Madonna of Running Agency.]
You detectives are a joke!
[To the mountains and the sea!
Desperate chase to capture the criminals!]
Do you even have any evidence?
I'm going to get the evidence.
[But in order to arrest them,
they need the physical evidence.]
Are they even feeding you?
We have to capture them!
[Detectives bloody search in order to
get their hands on the physical evidence!]
[Playing detectives and
not-so-bright criminals!]
[Will it be a perfect crime,
or will they be brought to justice?]
[Next week's Running Man-
Arrest the Traitors' Club!]