[Chuseok Special- The Mighty Inheritance]
[One crisp fall morning...]
[Madame Go's family members are
called in for an emergency family meeting.]
Oh!
I'm here as your corporate family lawyer.
I used to be a prosecutor.
[Firstborn grandson of the
younger daughter- Ha Ha.]
This...
I remember this!
- When we were given our inheritance...
- Yes, that's correct.
Okay, I got it.
Today, I'm going to make sure to...
I'm going to see this through to the end.
[Just then, another person competing
for the inheritance makes his entrance.]
[Second born son of the older daughter-
Jae Suk.]
I'm glad that I'm not in the same family
as that loser over there.
[Exchanging friendly words of greeting.]
[Instead of greetings of cheer on this holiday,
it's greetings of insults.]
- What did you say?
- Hello, everyone.
Here comes the real loser right there.
[Second born son of the younger daughter-
Kwang Soo.]
The second son?
You're my younger brother, you brat.
- Brother! How have you been!
- I haven't seen you in ten years.
- Brother! I've missed you!
- Have you been well?
- It's so good to see you.
- You two are going to ruin the family.
- What's going on over there?
- He's from the firstborn's family.
- The enemy of my parents!
- What did you say?
Your parents are still alive.
Listen to him. He doesn't even know
his parents are still alive.
- Here comes the ruffian of the family.
- Please let him be your family.
[Third born son of the older daughter-
Jong Kook.]
Why does the family keep switching up
on us each time?
- What's going on here?
- You're my little brother.
- That's what I mean. What's up with that?
- Seriously.
- Look who it is!
- Welcome!
He is the firstborn son of the
older daughter's family.
[Sensing that he's the older brother?
Firstborn son- Suk Jin.]
He's the oldest grandson.
Welcome. He's the younger son-in-law
of the younger daughter's family.
[Younger daughter family's
hip hop loving son-in-law, Gary.]
Please accept my greeting!
- You look just like my father.
- Okay, I understand.
- I'm your dad for the day?
- Yes.
- He's the dad?
- He's our dad.
- How is Gary the dad?
- Then who is this supposed to be?
[Then the empty seat would be...
Suk Jin, Jae Suk, and Jong Kook's mom?]
If she's supposed to be Suk Jin's mom...
[Just you wait... your mom is coming.]
Here comes our next family member.
Ji Hyo is the younger daughter of the family.
[The younger daughter of the family, Ji Hyo.]
Your mom is so young!
- You're jealous, aren't you?
- Your mom is such a looker.
My mom breastfed me!
[Mentioning the fact that
he was breastfed out of nowhere.]
So who's the youngest in our family?
I see that his seat is still left empty.
The youngest grandson is about
to make his entrance.
I hope it's someone fitting of our family.
- Hey!
- Wait, that's...
[Ji Hyo's youngest son making everyone's
jaw drop in shock.]
[An actor known for his rebellious roles-
Yoo Ah In.]
- My son! He looks just like me!
- Welcome.
[His perfect looks makes one question
the validity of his DNA gene line.]
- My son looks just like me!
- How did this happen?
[Was his youngest son an accident?]
You're the youngest grandson?
Oh my, my baby brother!
My baby brother!
I have missed you so!
[The youngest son's astounding good looks
standing out against the other two sons.]
- I'm the youngest son?
- You're the youngest son of that family.
I'm your oldest brother.
But it's really nice to meet you.
- That's your dad.
- He's your father.
- That's your mom.
- It's good to see you, my son.
[First time meeting between the mommy
and her youngest son.]
- This is unbelievable.
- She's my mom?
- They're your parents.
- My youngest son.
- There's your seat, my son.
- Everyone, please have a seat.
- The older daughter is about to come out.
- Our mom is coming!
- All our family members are here!
- Our family is a 'clubber'!
- Yeah!
There's no way.
He belongs in our family!
How can you even say that?
He's my son!
Yoo Ah In, and Yoo Jae Suk.
Get it?
The older daughter of the family
will now make her entrance.
- Mom!
[Just who will show up as the mother of
these three old brothers?]
[Confident and charismatic strides.]
Mom!
What!
[Wait... that loud and boisterous voice is?]
[The nation's beloved mother,
Kim Hae Sook.]
Welcome.
- That's a real mom!
- Welcome. She's the older daughter.
Why are you calling out for your mom?
- Mom!
- Why do you keep calling for me?
[Their mom's force making them bow
their heads down in automatic response.]
- Mom!
- I can't believe that it's her.
- It's a real mom. She really is our mom.
- She's your real mom?
[The three brothers' charismatic mom,
Kim Hae Sook.]
- So would she be my sister-in-law?
- Yes, she's your sister-in-law.
Sister-in-law!
Have you been well, sister-in-law?
Yes, I've been very well.
So what's going on here is that
Madame Go Dong Wan is our grandmother.
- Our grandmother had two daughters.
- We're your three sons.
- Over there is our first cousins.
- That's your younger sister's family.
Why haven't you greeted me yet?
Just hurry up and pay back
the money that you owe my family!
- What did you say?
- All you do is borrow money from us!
What did you say!
Pay back the money?
[His aunt's force is overflowing.]
Anyway, I will now explain the reason
why I have asked all the family members
to gather here again today for
another family meeting.
Madame Go Dong Wan really wanted to be
here to read her will and testaments herself
but she had a meeting at
the White House to attend
and she also had an urgent
M & A meeting to attend...
- Don't act like you know what you're saying.
- and thus, she wasn't able to attend today.
Therefore, acting on her behalf as the
family attorney, I will read it out for you.
My beloved children,
listen very carefully.
My beloved children...
Listen very carefully.
There's not many years left to live
for this mother of yours.
All this land and the countless numbers
of buildings that you see behind you...
You are aware that this is all
a part of my vast fortune, don't you?
[All this land and the buildings?]
I love you, mother!
- She's your grandmother.
- I mean, grandmother!
She's your grandmother.
It seems as though the time has come for me
to pass my entire fortune down to you.
As you all know already,
I've lost all my appetite lately
and it's really added on to
my lack of energy.
What a joke.
You're totally fat.
Mom!
You will have to pass
a series of hurdles today...
and make your way to the
final location.
And to the daughter and her family
who makes the ultimate dish...
[The ultimate dish?]
My unbelievably vast fortune will be passed
down to that daughter and her family.
Thus, I hope that you all put in
your best efforts today
in order to create the ultimate dish so that
you may be the one to inherit the fortune.
[Feeling confident?]
- The fortune will be ours.
- We're all set.
You have to win each mission
in order to win the items that will be
very useful to you at the final location.
So I hope that each of you will
do your best to win these missions.
Lastly, Madame Go Dong Wan has personally
written letters for each of the teams.
She has asked me to hand them to you, and
I will give one to the older daughter first.
To my beloved daughters.
Find your way to the swimming pool
in the woods...
The summer special episode
ended last week.
- Why are we going to the pool again?
- Why do we have to go to the swimming pool?
There's nothing we won't do if it means
we'll win our inheritance.
[Mommy Hae Sook scolding her sons and telling
them to think about winning the fortune.]
She needs to experience being in the
pool before she realizes what it's like.
She doesn't know what it's like right now and
that's why she's just focused on the fortune.
You're telling us that we have to go in the
water in this weather we're having right now?
What is there that we can't do right now if
it means we'll get our hands on the fortune?
Look at how I'm even
wearing my glasses right now.
I'm going to do everything I can today
to get my hands on that inheritance.
- I can see the swimming pool over there.
- I can see something.
[A swimming pool is slowly coming into
their vision from afar...]
- It's a flying chair.
- It's a flying chair? No way!
- Mom, can you go flying off that chair?
[What do you think of this resort?
It'll go to the winning family...]
- This resort belongs to our grandmother.
- It belongs to our grandmother?
[I've prepared a game most families like to
play when they gather together for Chuseok.]
Who plays games like this on Chuseok?
[If my daughters chooses the wrong card,
their sons will get dunked in the water.]
It means if you pick the 'Ddong-kwang' card,
we'll go flying into the water.
- Then moms aren't getting dunked?
- 'Ddong-kwang' card.
- Don't you think mom should experience it?
- How can you want that for our mother?
- Be quiet!
- Yes, Mom.
After all the years that I've breastfed you!
[Feeling betrayed by her youngest son whom
she breastfed to help him gain his muscles.]
- How could you want me in that water?
- Mom.
You're relieved now that you
know you won't be in that chair, right?
Yeah, I feel so much happier.
Mom, you have to pick the right card.
- How do we get over there?
- We have to walk.
We have to walk into the water?
Seriously?
Did you think that you could fly there?
[The chill of the fall air that can be felt
down to their bones.]
[The harshness of the variety world that
Ah In is feeling for the first time.]
[The eldest son having borrowed his mom's
float to get over to the chairs.]
[Automatically clenching his fists as soon as
his body experiences the chill of the water.]
This isn't the right time of the year to be
in the water right now.
There are five cards under the blankets that
are placed in front of the two mothers.
[Iconic cultural game, 'Hwatu',
is placed in front of the mothers.]
As you can see, one of them is
the 'Ddong-kwang' card.
The two mothers will take turns to
choose a card.
And if you pick that card, the male members
of that team will get flown off their chairs.
A total of five games will be played,
three wins out of five draw
will complete a round of the game.
And the first team to win the first
three points will win the whole game.
- Do you all understand?
- You just have to win 15 rounds, Mom.
You just need to win 15 rounds, okay?
[It's pretty simple, huh?]
Have you seen my mom in the movie,
'The Naked City'?
- She's very quick with her hands.
- She does have very fast hands.
Don't forget that I used to
chew on razor blades.
[Having shown how charismatic she can be
in her role as the infamous purse snatcher.]
I used to chew on razor blades,
so don't mess with me.
- Remember her role with Im Dal Hwa?
- She was a thief in that movie too.
- She had dome romance in that movie.
- Then is Dal Hwa our dad?
- Dal Hwa's our dad?
- Dal Hwa is our dad.
I didn't know that Dal Hwa was our dad.
Notice how you all look very different?
That's because you all have different dads.
[Mom's explosive confession.]
What are you saying right now?
Our mother...
our mother was a very big romantic.
The two mothers will determine who goes first
by playing a round of rock-paper-scissors.
Rock-paper-scissors!
- Okay, Song Ji Hyo wins.
- How could you do this to me?
You!
Song Ji Hyo will pick the first card.
- But this is really...
- I'm getting really nervous back here.
'Ddong-kwang'!
[Draws 'Bi-Kwang'- Pass!]
- This is really nerve-wrecking.
- I'm getting really nervous.
- I'm getting nervous.
- Draw 'Ddong-kwang' card!
- Mom, be careful.
- This is driving me crazy!
You're going to make us this nervous
first thing in the morning?
[Being made to feel extremely agitated on an
empty stomach first thing in the morning.]
It hasn't even been an hour
since I woke up this morning!
Little brother!
This is what you call a variety show!
Mom, draw your card.
Mom!
['Pal-kwang'- Pass.]
Oh, Pal-kwang!
Mom!
This is making me so nervous.
[Only three cards left to choose from.]
[Their stomachs hurting even more to be
so nervous on an empty stomach.]
My stomach is rumbling.
I can't even tell you how nervous
I am right now.
The middle one looks good.
'Ddong-kwang'!
[Choosing the middle card, as
instructed by her husband, Gary.]
[Wow... pass!]
- Have a very nice trip.
- You have to pick the right one!
- This one!
- Pick the one right in front of you!
- This is seriously driving me crazy.
- Pick it up together on the count of three.
[One of the two families will get
flown into the air.]
[Just which of the two will draw
the 'Ddong-kwang' card?]
[Where...]
[am I going?]
[Just shaved ten years off their lives.]
Mom!
[Hae Sook's family is in a celebratory mood.]
[Automatically breaking out in a dance.]
Our mom is best!
Ah In. How do you
feel now that you've seen it?
I want to be in the chair.
He has to get dunked in that water
for him to come to his senses.
[I guess he's not afraid of it yet...]
Please mix up the cards again.
Mom, I want to go back home in
my nice and dry clothes.
In nice and dry clothes.
[Acting like a child to his mom because
he doesn't want to play in the water.]
- You're my junior, aren't you?
- Yes.
Then you know what to do.
[Thinly veiled threats.]
[A reassuring mom to have in your corner.]
- Our mom is the best.
- Her style is very similar to Jong Kook's.
[That is my mom after all.]
- Let's go. Rock-paper-scissors.
- Rock-paper-scissors.
That's right.
[Did Ji Hyo heed Hae Sook's threats?]
You're one smart cookie.
[Hae Sook passes.]
- That's our mom.
- That is our mom.
[Ji Hyo's family feeling anxious.]
- It'll be 'Ddong-kwang' right away.
- 'Ddong-kwang' card!
[Blank Ji also passes.]
[Sitting on pins and needles.]
I'm going crazy sitting here.
It's nerve-wrecking for us too
since we can't see anything either.
One, two, three.
[Passes again!]
[The magical touch of their mother's hand.]
Aunt!
You used to be a gambler, weren't you?
- Song Ji Hyo will now make her draw.
- Pick the card in front of you.
No, one to the left!
- I'm going to listen to my youngest son.
- She's not going to listen to her husband.
I listened to my husband earlier,
so it's my son's turn now.
Please help us go home in our dry clothes!
[Who will it be this time?]
[Again!]
[Our mom is the best!]
- What did I tell you?
- This family has no luck!
You keep listening to the kids,
and you'll ruin our family!
- Our mom's the best.
- Mom!
- Mom! Listen to what dad tells you!
- Let's just all die together!
I'm so sorry!
Mom, mom, mom!
We may be able to go home in
our dry clothes after all!
The resort will be ours!
It'll be ours!
It's ours!
I hope she picks Ddong-kwang right away
and you get dunked in the water.
[Could it happen three times in a row?]
If it happens again,
our mom really is a hustler.
Rock-paper-scissors.
[Hae Sook wins the round of
Rock-paper-scissors again.]
Just what is it that you're
not good at?
[Hae Sook's sons in a very upbeat mood.]
One, two, three.
[Passes again!]
Ddong-kwang!
Our aunt will get?
[Thank goodness.]
Oh my gosh! I'm so nervous!
I seriously feel like
I'm going out of my mind.
Please help us go home in
our dry clothes.
Mom!
You have to pick the right one!
[Their dreams of going home in nice and
dry clothes are shattered.]
Okay, let the real party begin!
Okay, let's do this!
We're all wet now!
That's the real way to have fun
if you're going to play in the water!
It's okay, Mom!
[The two sons having been given
a cold wake up call.]
Ah In, are you seeing all this?
[That's going to be me soon.]
This is going to be you soon.
[All their fears dissipated the moment
they were dunked in the water.]
I don't fear being dunked
in the water anymore!
- Let's do this!
- Let's see how far we can take this!
- Let's see this through to the end!
Mom, you have to cheat the cards.
[First set-
Ji Hyo- 1 : Hae Sook- 2.]
There you go!
[Hae Sook wins the game of
Rock-paper-scissors three times in a row.]
There you go!
[Bi-kwang - Pass!]
The party's begun now, so don't worry
and choose with confidence.
[Blank Ji also passes.]
Just fling us off the chair right now.
Mom, I don't want to go in
the water again.
[Sings a song out of the blue
with his utmost sincerity.]
Mom, I'm so cold!
- I'm really cold.
- I don't want to go back in the water.
- That's the one!
- Mom, that's the one!
[Whew! Pass.]
- This is really stressful.
- You're down to two cards again.
Go with the one in front of you.
- Which one will the son pick?
- The one to the left.
You're picking the one on the left again!
Darn!
This family can't agree on anything!
Okay, I'll go with this one.
[Blank Ji going with her son's
wishes again.]
[Just who will flip over the Ddong-kwang?]
[Party time!]
What is wrong with our family!
You!
[Hae Sook's family wins the first set.]
[Brothers, I'm so sorry!]
We won.
We won the first round.
Since there are only three of us,
one of you will have to go again.
[Suggesting that they decide who goes
with a game of hand flip.]
Just do what your older brother tells you.
You three are squabbling too much.
Hand flip!
[Big-nosed Brother and Kkuk.]
- I didn't want to be chosen!
- Mom!
[Oh no...]
[A dead grasshopper in the water...]
- No, don't do it!
- That's not how you grab it!
[This is how you do it...]
[You must show your respect
for the grasshopper.]
[Shaking his head in despair...]
- We can save it!
- Scalpel!
[The grasshopper having lost its life
in the swimming pool.]
Goodbye.
Here, have a seat.
Have a seat.
To be honest, I'm not
that much younger than our mom.
Sit down.
Please just sit down.
[His older brother's tear soaked confession.]
Rock-paper-scissors.
[Round two.]
[Invincible in the game of
rock-paper-scissors?]
- She's like you, Suk Jin.
- I must take after our mom.
[It seems as though Big-nosed Brother's
skills must be hereditary from his mom.]
One, two, three.
- Just relax and pick one.
- Let it be the ddong-kwang!
[Relax and enjoy the flight.]
- Mom, mom, mom!
- Mom!
Mom, mom, mom!
Mom, what are you doing!
[Having picked the wrong card
right off the bat.]
Ah In looked really happy to see
them getting flown off their chairs.
[Ah In seeming to be too happy to see
his cousins flung off their chairs?]
Mom, mom, mom!
Our mom doesn't mess around.
I can't believe that was her first draw.
Mom, since we're already in this state,
pick the card again and let's just end it.
What are you talking about?
[Seeming too excited all on his own.]
[Wow... a master at rock-paper-scissors.]
- She won again?
- Pick one on the count of three.
[Will she pick it on her first draw again?]
Draw the card!
- Ugh, I'm so nervous.
- This is really nerve-wrecking.
Ddong-kwang.
- Ddong-kwang.
- Please!
Why do I feel so nervous!
[All the men feeling their hearts
about to thump out of their chests.]
- Mom!
- Don't pick the Ddong-kwang.
One, two, three.
[Passes again.]
Thank you, Mom.
This is making me so anxious.
[About to lose his mind?]
[Feeling more anxious as the number of
cards to choose from diminishes.]
You have to draw the Ddong-kwang
in order for me to survive.
Go with the one on the right.
Okay, my son.
I'm going to listen to my son.
[Listening to her son,
and choosing the card on the right.]
Three!
[With her youngest son in the seat,
she chooses Ddong-kwang twice in a row.]
I can go home in my nice and
dry clothes!
Mom, let's just get it over with.
Pick the card again.
I didn't have a choice in the matter.
She got to choose the card.
She didn't get a choice in the matter.
Let's make this a clean win, Ji Hyo.
- Rock-paper-scissors.
- Don't win. Let her pick again.
[As always, Hae Sook wins the game.]
I can't believe she won again.
Mom, don't just win at the rock-paper-scissors
but stop drawing the Ddong-kwang card.
What does it matter if you keep
winning at that?
Just put them out of their misery,
and end this round for them.
Just draw the card right out the door,
and end this pain for them.
[Her sons asking her to just end it
and put them out of their misery.]
Draw the card.
Draw the card!
[What will she draw?]
[Oh my...]
[My goodness...]
Mom, I'm really cold.
[No need to cower in fear any longer.
Three times in a row...]
[How can this be?]
[Second round victory goes to
nice and dry Ji Hyo's family.]
[I'm so sorry.]
I never even imagined that the round
would end like this.
[Three times in a row... amazing.]
That was a great way to end the game!
[But there's still another round
left in the game.]
Since our youngest brother is a guest,
let him do it one more time.
- As for the other player...
- Why don't you do it like this?
- Ah In can...
- We'll take care of it ourselves!
We'll take care of it ourselves!
[Getting smacked for trying to help.]
Why are you butting into
our family's business?
- This is our family's matter.
- Yes, you're right.
No, but I've got a really good solution.
[But the cousin insists on
butting in to the end.]
[Ah In and...]
[Kwang Soo?]
- What was that for?
- What?
[The unlucky Giraffe having been
chosen to take the seat again...]
[The final round with the fate of
the resort hanging on the balance.]
Mom, mom!
Please dunk Ah In in the water.
[Their goal is to get
nice and dry Ah In all wet?]
I'll dunk Ah In in the water myself.
Why, Mom?
Why would you want to do that?
Rock-paper-scissors.
[She just may become a legend
of rock-paper-scissors.]
She's good at rock-paper-scissors, but
she's also good at drawing the ddong card.
- Ah In. Ah In...
- Send him in the water.
- That's the card.
- Send him flying.
Send him flying gin the air.
[Wow... there it is.]
[The machine malfunctions, and only
Kwang Soo gets dunked in the water.]
I'm sorry, but you need to
get back up there.
Why do I need to get dunked again
when I just got dunked?
[So confused...]
Only he needs to get dunked
since I just got dunked myself.
We only need to get dunked
once, don't we?
What wrong have I ever done?
[It's working just fine now.]
Did you see Ah In?
Did you see his face?
[His first cold taste of the variety world.]
[Welcome...
Your first flying chair experience, right?]
[Totally... speechless.]
That was cool.
Remember what Ah In said about
it looking like it would be fun?
It really is a ton of fun!
He says it's fun.
- How do you feel now, Ah In?
- Seriously... it's not that bad.
[Pretending to be fine.]
All of you are just scaredy cats.
Hey, what do you mean, we're the scared ones?
You screamed the loudest out of all of us.
[His false sense of confidence
being called out on.]
Kwang Soo got dunked in the water again
over a technical mistake.
[Kwang Soo being dunked unfairly due to
a malfunction wasn't even acknowledged...]
No one even cares about
what happens to me anymore.
Kwang Soo just gets dunked again
as if it's a given.
Rock-paper-scissors.
[She wins Rock-paper-scissors again.]
[Dubbed the new goddess of
Rock-paper-scissors.]
- What in the world is going on with her?
- I can see that Ji Hyo's mad right now.
- What's gotten into you, Mom?
- Mom, send Ah In in the water again.
- Yes, send him back in the water.
- One, two, three.
[Pass]
This is driving me crazy.
This is driving us in our seats crazy.
It's really nerve-wrecking for us too.
Okay, Song Ji Hyo.
One, two, three.
[Blank Ji also passes her turn.]
I'm going to pick it from this side.
[Taking their flight in turn?]
- Wow, doing it like that was cool.
- That was cool.
Okay, fine.
I got it now.
So you're going to fling us in the air
in turn like that, is that it?
Oh no, I feel awful!
This is how you party!
[What kind of a party is this?]
What are you thinking having a pool party
in this kind of a weather?
- Pick the card, pick the card.
- Please!
One, two, three!
[Frozen as ice?]
- What's wrong? I thought you weren't nervous.
- No, I'm really enjoying this right now.
- Wow, this is so much fun.
- You're having fun, you say?
- This is really a lot of fun.
- Don't lie, I can see your lips trembling.
[Continuing to insist he's having fun
even though his lips won't stop trembling.]
Just pick whichever one you want.
Don't be nervous, it's okay.
- Which one?
- Pick the one right in front of you.
- This one?
- Yeah, that one.
No, I don't know.
- No, don't pick that one!
- Pick whichever one you want.
- One, two, three!
- That one!
[Pass]
My heart is pounding.
[A fifty percent chance.
Only two cards left in the mix.]
[Husband Gary recommends that she
chooses the card to the left.]
- Are you sure?
- How about my youngest son picks?
- My youngest son can pick.
- I'll go with my dad's choice.
[Youngest son, Ah In goes with his dad,
and chooses the card to the left.]
Pick the card in the middle!
- Listen to me for once, and pick.
- I think you should pick the middle one.
Let's go with the one our
youngest son chose.
[Going with the card on the left as dad, Gary
and youngest son, Ah In instructed.]
One.
Two.
Three!
[Wow...]
[Guess who it is?]
[Starts to clap automatically.]
It always works when my youngest son
and I are in sync.
Okay, let's do this.
[Taking out his anger on the
older brother.]
[Round Three-
Ji Hyo- 2 : Hae Sook- 1]
It's okay, Mom.
Don't worry. I like being in the water.
I don't think...
we should do water games anymore.
[Water games are no longer feasible?]
Thank you to all our viewers for having
watched and enjoyed all the water games.
- But as for these water games...
- We'll see them again next summer!
Water games... goodbye!
And seashore games... goodbye!
- And rice paddies too.
- Oh right, the rice paddies.
Rice paddies... goodbye!
Goodbyes to the seashore mud flats,
swimming pools, rice paddies...
and what's our next goodbye?
Goodbye to Ah In?
Let's just round it out to an even goodbye.
Four goodbyes at once.
- One, two...
- Goodbye, Ah In.
Three.
[Goodbye...]
[Ah In.]
[Just as they said...]
I can't believe that happened.
- I feel so bad.
- You scare me.
I can't believe you sent Ah In flying like
that right after you said goodbye to him.
- I feel so bad.
- 'Goodbye, Ah In.'
Goodbye, Ah In.
The current score is, two to two
at our third round.
Kwang Soo, you're totally soaking wet.
He looks like a wet dish rag.
How can you compare me to
a wet dish rag?
How can you say that to your nephew?
[Holidays should be spent with your family...
Adverse effects of too much family time.]
This is the final round.
This round will determine the winner.
[The fate of grandmother's resort
is balancing on the line.]
- Fighting.
- Mom, we have to win this.
Fighting.
Since this is the last round,
why don't the two mothers say something?
- Say something to your sons.
- Goodbye, Ah In.
Mom!
- What about Kwang Soo?
- Why don't you just get a scarecrow instead?
You just keep ignoring me
more and more as the time goes by!
I don't think the cameras are even
filming me anymore.
Hey, you're like nothing but
a shadow right now.
- The resort will be ours.
- Yes!
- Rock-Paper-scissors.
[Wins the rock-paper-scissors game
all the way through to the end.]
- This is the final round, right?
- This is the decisive round.
- I feel so anxious.
- Flip the card over on the count of three.
- Here we go.
- Fighting.
[The final decisive round with
the fate of the resort hanging on the line.]
Two.
Three!
Come on!
[Pass]
- Goodbye, Ah In.
Ji Hyo, can you say goodbye
to Ah In one more time?
[Everyone seems to want to hear Ji Hyo
say goodbye to Ah In?]
Does our family not care about
inheriting the resort for ourselves?
This is all your fault!
[What is it that we're working
so hard for?]
- Our family apparently doesn't care.
- Goodbye, Ah In.
[Ji Hyo's family cares more about dunking
Ah In rather than getting the fortune.]
- One... two...
- Let's do it. Pick the card!
Three!
- Goodbye, Ah In.
- Let's send them away.
[Goodbye]
[Guess you're not getting the resort.
Goodbye, Ah In...]
- The spell worked!
- 'Goodbye, Ah In' spell worked!
Goodbye, water games.
Goodbye, seashore mud flat games.
Goodbye, rice paddies.
Goodbye, Ah In!
- We won. The resort is ours.
- We won?
Thus, Orange Team wins!
[Team Hae Sook wins!]
Resort is ours!
- Our mom is a hustler. Our mom is a hustler!
- Goodbye, Ah In!
The winning team may first
choose one of these two boxes.
- Which one should we go with?
- We need to go with the 'Top' box.
- You're choosing that one?
- Yes, we'll go with this.
You can't open the box until
I tell you to.
- Yes, we understand.
- Make sure to keep it with you.
You can open the envelope and figure out
where to go for your next location.
[The letter contains their next location.]
[You must be hungry after
playing in the water...]
- No, I'm actually more cold than hungry.
- It says to go to the 'D' restaurant.
[Yes!
We're going to go eat!]
Mom!
- Mom, let's go.
- Let's go quickly.
- The resort is ours!
That's the most I've laughed
in a very long time.
- We're off to a very good start.
- I have a good feeling about this.
- We seem to fit very well together.
- So the resort is ours right now?
- Yes, it is.
- Then we need to get the land next.
[Slowly gaining all the fortune one by one.]
We're going to have to do a good job
in the next game too.
I'm going to keep everything in
my possession for now...
and I'm going to give it little by little
to those of you who are good to me.
- You're not going to give us a lot?
- No, just a little bit at a time.
[Ji Hyo's family reminiscing
about their time in the past.]
It seems just like yesterday that he was born,
but our youngest is already 28 years old.
- I remember when he was still in diapers.
- How old were you two back then?
I was a year old.
And I was eight years old.
Honey, we should take the kids
and go live in America.
- Why, Father?
- Why would we move to America?
- So that we can go clubbing together.
- Why would you go clubbing at your age?
You should focus on staying home more.
I'm so sick and tired of having to
sleep in Room 34, Father.
I remember grabbing a glow stick
on my one hundredth day celebration.
- We're here.
- Yes, we're here.
[Arrives at the restaurant.]
[Traditional Korean restaurant overflowing
with regal charm and history.]
[But inside the restaurant...
is a setup for some sort of a game?]
Aren't you going to feed us?
I don't think we're here to eat,
but we're here to play a game.
[You don't think that we're just going to
feed you for free, do you?]
The two daughters need to
come up here first.
- He asked for the two daughters.
- Come up here and get your letters.
We don't have to ride this up there?
- Is this for the older daughter?
- Yes.
[I know that you're all working very hard.]
[I've prepared a mission that will
test your taste buds' knowledge.]
[Your second mission is,
'Food Battle of your Five Senses'.
that will require the usage
of all your five sensory skills.]
You have to scoot up to the table
on your cushions
and you have to place your cushion
on top of the table first
in order to be given a chance
to answer the question posed.
[First person to place their cushion on
the table will get to answer the question.]
The family with the most members to answer
the questions first will win the game.
- Yes, I understand.
- We're confident we can win this.
- First up, we'll play an auditory game.
- Auditory game.
- I can do this.
- We will get started.
[All of the different sounds
that are made when cooking.]
[Will they be able to guess what dish is
being prepared from hearing the sound?]
- You have to guess which dish it is.
- Okay.
Okay, we will now start the questions.
[It's not a very familiar sound.]
Something is being taken out
of a package.
Something's being taken out.
[Ha Ha's going to try to
guess the answer?]
I think I know this sound.
Okay, Ha Ha.
Ha Ha?
Ramyun?
Didn't it sound like that?
Like a package being torn open?
I have absolutely no idea.
[Listening to it again
still doesn't seem to help any.]
- Is it the sound of a fish being cleaned?
- Taking out the organs?
[Hae Sook and Ah In races forward.]
[Ah In's cushion slips off.]
Kim Hae Sook.
- That's our mom!
- Kim Hae Sook's cushion made it.
- It's fish...
- Yes?
I didn't hear it all the way through.
So it's either spicy fish stew,
broiled fish, or pan fried fish.
[Huh? Three different answers?]
Since all I heard was the fish being cleaned
and I raced up here after hearing that...
So I'm saying it's either spicy fish stew,
broiled fish, or pan fried fish.
- You can't give three different answers.
- Just one answer.
- You have to give just one answer.
- You're doing great, Mom.
Spicy fish stew!
Then broiled fish.
Broiled cutlass fish?
Broiled cutlass fish!
[Madame Kim,
the Queen of Stubbornness.]
Mom, you did good.
Here's your hint.
It's something you eat often.
- It's easy to make, and you eat it often.
- Really?
[Just what is the dish behind this sound?]
[The sound of a cucumber being sliced.]
I have no idea.
[The definitive sound of
crabmeat being opened!]
[And after ham is grilled to perfection.]
[All our viewers...
Can you guess what it is by now?]
- I think she knows what it is.
- Whatever. Let's just get up there and see.
- Grilled buttered calamari.
- Grilled buttered calamari?
- Take back the buttered out.
- Calamari...
- Grilled margarine calamari.
- Hey, that's the same thing!
- What kind of an answer is that?
- That's the incorrect answer.
It's something that's easy to make,
and something that you eat often.
Jae Suk, is it this?
Jae Suk, what if it's this?
(Kimbap)
- Your answer is?
- Grilled ham.
Hey, he says that's not it!
- What were you thinking?
- I was just saying what came to mind.
- You know that's not it.
- You have to come up with your own answers.
- I was thinking of something else.
- Tell me what you were thinking.
Just tell me what you were thinking.
I think I know what it is.
It's very common, isn't it?
- Yes, it's very common.
- Found everywhere?
- It's very common.
- Kimbap.
- Come on, that's not it.
- Kimbap?
- Kimbap!
[Correct answer]
[Finally starting to get what all the
mysterious sounds were.]
I still don't get it.
[Time to check the answer.]
[One- Sound of cucumber being sliced.]
So that was the sound of the knife
hitting the cutting board.
[Two- Unwrapping the crabmeat.]
[So that's what that sound was!]
How are we supposed to know that those
sounds are the sounds of making kimbap?
It's because of what he said
about it being a very common dish.
Of course! You need to baste it
in sesame oil for it to be true kimbap!
I want the ends.
[Ha Ha of Ji Hyo's family
gets the correct answer.]
For the next round, it'll be a taste test.
Taste test is one thing
that I'm confident in!
You have to come out here to
the table and get in line.
You have to line up in front of the table.
I'm confident that I can do this.
You have to be remain honest,
and keep your eyes closed.
[Keep your eyes tightly closed!]
You cannot open your eyes.
[Some sort of fried food?]
[Kwang Soo is up first.]
[Fire!]
- What?
- What is it?
- What's wrong with you?
[People in the back feeling nervous
after hearing Kwang Soo's screams.]
[Finally starting to
attempt to taste the food.]
- What is it?
- What's wrong?
- You have to finish what you're eating.
- Why, what is it?
You have to keep your eyes up front.
You can't look behind you.
- What is it?
- What's wrong with him?
- What's wrong?
- Okay, time for you to tell me your answer.
I've lost my sense of taste.
- What? You've lost your sense of taste?
- I can't taste anything.
Tell me what you think it is.
- Fried oranges.
- Fried oranges?
There are no such things
as fried oranges.
What are you talking about?
What was that?
I thought that you threw a fire lit
match into my mouth.
You should cool it down before
you shove it in our mouths.
Yes, I understand.
Okay, we'll do another round.
[Off they go again!]
- Okay, you have to close your eyes.
- Kim Jong Kook, it's fried food!
[I don't care if it means I can
take the victory!]
Just shove it down his throat.
[Fried food that he wouldn't even
normally glimpse at sideways...]
[Health conscious body lover who cares about
his body more than anything else.]
Hang on a second.
- Is it hot?
- Why is it so hot?
You have to finish what's in your mouth.
You have to put it all in your mouth.
[Aren't you going to chew it?
Aren't you going to swallow it?]
He doesn't know much about taste
because all he eats is chicken breasts.
Try to guess what it is.
What is this?
- Can't you tell just by tasting it?
- Time for you to give your answer.
Why is everyone having
such a hard time with it?
This is no joke.
[Still thinking about it.]
- You have to tell me what it is.
- He's going to say fried oranges too.
No, it's not an orange.
It's going to taste like fried oranges
no matter how many of them you try.
- Grapefruit!
- Grapefruit, orange... it's the same thing.
Fried grapefruit?
[That rare... fried grapefruit?]
Is that your answer?
- No, that's incorrect.
- It must be something citrus.
[It seems as though it must be
something fruity of some sorts.]
It wasn't grapefruit either.
Fried orange, fried grapefruit.
Same difference!
I'm sure it's an orange.
It's something that I've never had before.
[Something he's never had before...]
[Just what could be inside that fried batter?]
[The identity of what's inside is...]
[Gummy worms!]
- Okay, prepare yourselves.
- I think it's something rare and expensive.
Ready... go!
[Back to the table!]
[While everyone is stuck in the melee,
Ah In pushes himself forward!]
[What about the cushion?]
Your cushion!
[These four didn't even budge an inch
because they were tangled up in a mob.]
[Getting himself poised seriously
to taste the food.]
It's really hot.
[Will Ah In's taste buds
tell him what it is?]
- Everyone can now open their eyes.
- It's fried food of some sorts.
- You can't look behind you.
- I keep smelling fried food.
Can't you go lighter on the batter?
So there's not much of whatever's inside,
and there's a lot of batter?
So it's 90% batter, and 10% filling?
Ah In, can you peel off the batter
inside your mouth?
Don't try to overthink it too much.
There you go.
Think.
- This isn't fruit.
- Really?
- No, it's fruit.
- I'll give you five seconds.
[He must give his answer
within five seconds.]
Two.
One.
Wait!
Just wait.
[Begging desperately?]
[Rebel resorts to begging
when desperately cornered?]
- What are you doing?
- Don't think too seriously about it.
- Aren't you done eating it yet?
You know what it is.
Say what it is that you're thinking.
- What are you doing stalling time?
- Ah In!
What's happened to you ever since
the flying chairs?
- Five, four...
- It tastes like jelly of sorts.
Fried gummy worms?
- Yes, fried gummy worms.
- Fried gummy worms?
- I think he's got it.
- Really?
Yes, you've guessed correctly.
- Yes, you've guessed correctly.
- Seriously?
Yes, it was the fried gummy worms.
Are you telling me that you fed me both
the gummy and the fried batter?
[Oh... the master of taste buds?]
Wow, that's pretty impressive.
- He's got it.
- How did he guess that?
- Seriously?
- You really have the ultimate taste buds.
- I can't believe you got that.
- That was amazing.
- How did he guess that?
- How did he know that?
[Ji Hyo's family passes the round
thanks to their youngest son, Ah In.]
This was it.
Fried gummy worms.
Ah, it was gummy worms.
- Ah, this was it?
- The gummy worms?
This was it.
[Everyone grabbing a piece
as soon as they're brought out.]
- This is what it was?
- It's pretty good.
Everyone should try making this at home.
It's really good.
- This is really good.
- It's good.
[Fried gummy worms tasting much
better than anyone had anticipated.]
[But one person remains stoic in the back.]
Yeah, it's really good.
- This is really good.
- How did you ever guess this correctly?
- It's all melted and gooey on the inside.
- How did you ever guess this, Ah In?
[The dish is amazing, and Ah In
is amazing for having guessed it.]
I knew that it wasn't real fruit.
You're acting much differently now
that you've guessed it correctly.
You're acting a bit cockier than before.
It's all melted on the inside.
This time, it'll be a sense of touch.
I'm really bad at things like this.
- Oh my God.
- Is it that bad?
Don't do that!
[Did they just see something
really frightening?]
You have to keep your eyes closed.
- It's moving around a little.
- Seriously?
- Why are you saying all that?
- This is a little... ugh!
Okay, you may now open your eyes.
[The unseen terror.]
It's moving around a bit,
and it's a little slimy too.
[Older daughter Hae Sook is the only one
eagerly making her way forward.]
Okay, go ahead.
Just know that it could bite you.
He's lying.
- He's lying to you. That's a lie.
- You have to stick your hand in a bit more.
- You're not there yet. A little bit more.
- What the heck?
You have to touch it.
[Frightened more than she should be
no thanks to the people in the back.]
Yes, that's it.
[This is it! Mackerels.]
- It's okay, Mom. Don't be afraid.
- Okay, no more!
Wait, hang on.
[Her stubbornness showing through again.]
[The rule enforcer steps in!]
[Insistent mother still not
pulling her hand away.]
- You have to stop!
- You have to stop touching!
You can't touch it anymore!
- You have to step back now!
- You have to stop touching it now.
I came out on this show at my age,
so give me a little break.
[The flustered corporate family lawyer.]
She's my mom!
Okay, you have to stop touching it now.
Okay, you're now finished.
[Attempting to glance a peek inside.]
- You have to take your hand out.
- I didn't see what's inside.
I didn't recognize it
because I have bad eyesight.
Okay, what is your answer?
Mackerel.
- Mackerel?
- Spanish mackerel.
[Attempting to give
her multi-answer once again.]
- It's a fish.
- What kind of a fish is it?
I don't want to tell you what kind it is.
It's my choice whether I tell you that or not.
- Fish.
- What kind of a fish?
- It's a fish!
- I got that, but what kind of a fish?
That's for me to know.
What kind of a rule is that?
It's a fish.
I don't know if it's a mackerel,
or Spanish mackerel, so I'll go with fish.
Hey, Lady!
- Don't you think that you're being too much?
- What do you mean, 'Hey, Lady'?
That's my mother that you're talking to.
[The two cousins battling it out
over her ambiguous answer.]
It's either a mackerel or Spanish mackerel.
Come on, give me a break!
They're both fish!
- Come on.
- Just give her a break.
[Trying to get him to go easy on her since
she hasn't been on a variety show in a while.]
You can't argue your way
out of this one.
This is my first time out on this show.
I'll give you this much.
It's one of those two answers.
- Really?
- It's one of those two answers.
Is it two letters or three letters?
- I can't tell you that.
- Just show me with your fingers.
- With my fingers?
- Yeah.
Fish.
Mackerel.
- Mackerel?
- Are you sure?
[Finally gets the answer!]
That's the correct answer.
This time, it'll be about your sense of smell.
My nose is like a dog's nose.
With your eyes closed...
[Using your sense of smell...
guess the three side dishes.]
You can't eat it.
Wait a minute.
- Okay, no more smelling.
- That's egg roll up.
[The correct answer is...]
[Stir-fried dried squid.]
[Dried black beans... and egg roll up.]
What is your correct answer?
- Egg roll up.
- Egg roll up?
He really does have the nose
of a bloodhound.
- Perelli leaves.
- Perelli leaves?
No, that's incorrect.
[What could it be?]
[It seems as though the stir-fried squid
is throwing everyone off.]
What's the second side dish?
No, you can't eat it.
Wait.
[Sticking his nose in there.]
- I'm not touching!
- You're not touching?
I think I have an idea.
- It's egg roll up.
- Egg roll up.
It's something that's cooked in soy sauce.
I can smell soy sauce in it.
[It's time for you to give your answer.]
- The soy sauce has been...
- We got it, so spit out the answer!
- You have to give your answer.
- The soy sauce...
- It's been simmered in soy sauce.
- This isn't a cooking show.
- Egg roll up.
- Egg roll up?
- Pickled garlic root.
- Garlic root?
- Is your nose stuffed up?
- What did you say?
I just didn't know.
I wasn't sure what it was.
- I think my nose may be stuffed up.
- Mix up Ji Hyo and Gary.
I'm not going to say anything else.
Just mix up Ji Hyo and Gary.
- You're right here, aren't you?
- No.
I'm going to beat you.
[Still able to find his frenemy
even with his eyes blindfolded.]
I'm going to beat you!
- You'd better be careful.
- I'm sorry, what I did was wrong.
How did he know that I was here?
Can he see me?
- Egg Roll up. Black beans.
- Stir-fried squid.
- Stir-fried squid?
[Ah... so close!]
[No, that's not it!]
[Still able to single out Ro-Ro
even with his eyes blindfolded.]
- Salted squid.
- Salted squid?
- That was so close.
[Kwang Soo's turn.]
[Just like Kwang Soo's friend
whom we saw in the past...]
[Kwang Soo sticking out his tongue
and licking his way towards his food.]
Okay, the second dish.
You can't stick out your tongue.
- No, you can't stick out your tongue.
- What was the clue you gave earlier?
Okay, no more.
What is your answer?
- Egg roll up.
- Black beans.
- Stir-fried dried squid.
- Stir-fried dried squid?
Stir-fried dried squid.
[Correct answer]
That's the same thing as stir-fried squid.
Isn't that pretty much the same thing?
[Their undeniable hunger.]
[Their frenzied grab for the food.]
You know what my mom calls this?
She always called this stir-fried squid.
- She always called this stir-fried squid.
- Wait, I didn't get any rice.
I'm hungry!
Thus, the Green Team wins
the Food Battle Game.
[With three wins in a row, Ji Hyo's family
wins the five senses game!]
The winning team may step forward and
choose one of the boxes.
- You have to pick the top box now.
- Sure, they should.
It's your choice, Ah In.
- I want to go with this one.
- Then go with that one.
Go with the one you want.
[Oh... going with the low box again?]
We get the top box again?
[Have your ultimate taste buds
been brought back to life again?]
[Move onto the mural village.]
[Next mission location-
'B' village in Daegu.]
- Look at all that.
- That's beautiful.
[Everyone's astounded by the beauty
of this fairytale like village.]
[I have made songpyeon for all of you
and hid it throughout the village.]
Either find the songpyeon yourselves,
or steal it from each other
and the first team to place ten in the
pot and put the lid on wins.
[Find ten songpyeon and
place them in your own pot.]
There are two home zones that you will find
placed across the street from each other.
You will find a huge pot
in your own home zone.
You will find that songpyeon has been
hidden throughout this village.
Each team has to find and place ten
of them in each of their own team's pots.
[First team to find them and place all ten
in the pot wins the game.]
Mom, you're going to see
a war break out.
That's what I'm predicting.
You'd better prepare yourself for this.
[Whatever it is that you're imagining,
it's going to be much worse than that.]
Once it's in the pot, we can't
steal it from each other, right?
- No, of course not.
- You can steal from each other's pot?
- There's no such thing.
- There are no rules in this game!
- Bite and tear if you have to. Fight!
- We have to cover this with our body.
There aren't any lids for these pots.
[Must find the lids to cover the pots with
to keep their songpyeon safe.]
Since Kwang Soo is strong,
and he's good at cheating...
- He doesn't care about hitting or biting.
- He's good at stealing from others.
- They're going to be pretty large in size.
- Guys like Kwang Soo...
He won't care if it's you,
or anyone else for that matter.
He won't care if it's you.
No, it's because he hasn't seen
the real scary side of me yet.
- Then you can show him.
- I will.
[Readying herself for battle.
Hae Sook's fearsome warning.]
Let's all get together and say 'fighting'.
- One, two, three.
- Fighting.
[Steal the songpyeon battle- Start!]
[Starting out to find their songpyeon first!]
Where could these songpyeons be?
Wow, this place is so pretty.
[With all the painted murals on the walls,
finding the songpyeon is even more difficult.]
That looks so delicious!
[Blank Ji coincidentally finds
a pot filled with real songpyeon!]
[Looks delicious.]
Wow, you really have a big mouth.
Most women would eat it like this.
Wow, this village is huge.
Hello.
Do you have any songpyeon?
You have songpyeon up there, don't you?
[Interrogating one of the villagers.]
You have songpyeon up there, right?
[It's right here!]
Have you seen any?
[Discovers a songpyeon exactly
where they instructed him that it would be.]
Thank you!
Hello.
[Ah In discovers his
second songpyeon already!]
There's another one.
I see another one over there.
[Without any hesitation,
he discovers his third songpyeon!]
I see another one over there!
[Another one?]
- There are so many of them!
- You found one?
How many have you found?
- Three.
- You've already found three?
[Running around and
finding all of them on his own!]
[Ah In having discovered
four songpyeon all on his own!]
- Who's guarding the pot right now?
- There's no one there.
Ji Hyo!
[Jae Suk of Hae Sook's team
discovers one himself.]
I can't believe you guys hid one here.
[Finds another songpyeon immediately.]
Hey, Kwang Soo.
Jong Kook.
Ah In.
Just stay right there for now.
[Bluffing each other as if
they have their own backup waiting.]
- Should we just go our own separate ways?
- Move.
- Goodbye, Sir.
- Okay.
Move.
Don't you think that I should
do something about this right now?
- Move.
- I need to do something for my team.
This is your role, so get out of the way.
You've already done enough.
You'll get a split second on screen for this.
Move.
- I'm going to take those from you.
- I don't think you'll be able to do that.
You've gotten much stronger, I see.
Aren't you even afraid of me?
- Don't you find me the least bit threatening?
- No.
[You just wait and see...]
[Meanwhile...]
[Mother Hae Sook stuffing
her songpyeon under her shirt.]
[Disguising herself into a woman
who's had a little too much to eat at lunch.]
[Ah In is approaching in her direction.]
I wonder why this door is open.
I should go keep my songpyeon safe.
Mom.
- Why are you heading this way?
- Mom, is this songpyeon?
- Can I see?
- No, I wouldn't know.
Mom.
I already told you that I don't know,
so must you get so close to me?
- Mom, let's take a little breather.
- You like salted crab, don't you?
I even sent you two rice cakes, didn't I?
Mom, I really want to work hard.
I want to be a son that you can be proud of!
I'm working very hard myself right now.
Ah In, must you really take the one
songpyeon that I found?
Mom.
Don't do this to me.
[Kwang Soo appears out of nowhere
and moves in on Hae Sook!]
[It's only a matter of time before she
gets her songpyeon taken away from her?]
[Big-nose coming to her rescue
after he heard her screaming out loud.]
- What do you think you're doing?
- Don't mind him.
- Are you seriously going to do this?
- What are you doing?
- Don't you think that you're being too much?
- You're the only one who came here to help?
[Just then, Jae Suk also shows up
to her rescue.]
We were just passing through.
Take theirs away from them.
[Team Ji Hyo's Ha Ha
also runs over to their rescue.]
[Trying to take each other's
songpyeon away from them.]
[Total chaos]
No!
[Ah In manages to steal one of
Jae Suk's songpyeon!]
[Ah In steals one of Jae Suk's songpyeon,
and runs for his life!]
[Protecting their stash is definitely
much more difficult than finding them.]
[Hae Sook placing Giraffe,
the instigator under lockdown.]
Wait, they're gone.
[Mr. Capable shows up at the scene
a second too late.]
[The only way to survive is to escape.]
Ah In took one of mine.
- Come here, Lee Kwang Soo.
- Why did you let him take it away?
- Three of them came at me out of nowhere.
- Give it to me. I'll hold onto it.
Hey! I don't think we'll be able to
take that one away from them.
You come here.
[Taking their easy prey Ha Ha with them?]
[It seems as though they want to
question him about something.]
- Get rid of Kwang Soo.
- We don't want you coming in here.
He's going to spill the beans
about where your home zone is.
So just be aware of that.
[Haroro being threatened
and tortured for answers.]
[Under torture, Haroro's loyalty goes...
right out the window.]
Kwang Soo's butt.
[Kwang Soo's butt?]
Come here.
[Ha Ha must've talked!]
[Examining his butt just
like their informant told them.]
[A humiliating scene for the Giraffe.]
[Ah... how humiliating.]
- Just go away now.
- I gave you the information you wanted.
- Okay, you may go now.
- I hope you'll leave me alone now.
[How dare you even say that now!]
I couldn't stand the torture.
How was I supposed to
stand their torture?
They took my pants down
in front of all these people.
I knew that Kwang Soo's butt
wasn't that plush.
[Current songpyeon score-
Hae Sook- 3 : Ji Hyo- 4.]
We have to be more careful with this.
Jae Suk saw it earlier.
[Hae Sook secretly making her way
to the enemy camp's home zone.]
[Heading into the room in front of
her opposing team's pot?]
[Convinced that their songpyeon are
hidden somewhere nearby.]
- They have to be in here somewhere.
- Hae Sook, what are you doing?
No, nothing.
What are you doing in our house?
- No, I was just checking things out.
- Isn't it nice and warm in here?
Yes, it's nice and warm.
- Where have you been?
- Excuse me?
I wasn't doing anything in here.
[Pretending like she just came in to
rest in the warm and cozy room.]
[Meanwhile, the rest of the men are focusing
more on stealing each other's songpyeon.]
These hyenas are back again.
[Mr. Capable's defense moves.]
Ah In, hurry up.
We can take his away from him.
[Having given up on finding the songpyeon,
they're focusing on stealing the songpyeon.]
No!
[Ah In succeeds in stealing
Jae Suk's songpyeon again!]
[Who's hand will this songpyeon fall into?]
[That's our Ace!
Nice catch, Blank Ji!]
[The time is now!]
[Now's the chance! Hae Sook
searching every nook and cranny.]
[Hitting a very specific target.]
How could you hit me there so hard
from such a close proximity?
[Because he is Mr. Capable...
Maximum distance, maximum pain.]
Where?
Where did they hide them?
I found it!
[Inside the washer?]
[Wow! Discovers three of her
opponent's hidden songpyeon!]
[Mother Hae Sook having pulled
more than her weight!]
- Are we all set after we take this one?
- No.
All of ours are gone.
Someone came and stole ours away.
Already?
They're gone already?
Kwang Soo.
- Thanks.
- Huh?
- Why are you thanking me?
- Thanks for telling us about the washer.
[Framing him as a traitor.]
[A character so easy to frame.]
I really didn't tell them anything.
It really wasn't me.
Hey! You're the only
one who could've done it.
You told them, didn't you?
- I didn't tell them anything.
- Kwang Soo's in trouble.
[Danger! Extremely angry
Blank Ji is approaching!]
- I didn't tell them anything.
- Hey!
How can you do this to
your own team?
- Huh?
- I'm seriously going to lose my mind.
Look at how my husband is over there
feeding the rabbits right now.
[Daddy Gary have lost it and
is busy feeding grass to the rabbits.]
I'm going to leave this godforsaken world.
Hubby, come over here.
This isn't the time to be doing that.
I'm going to live with these rabbits.
[Do you know what we went through
to get those songpyeons?]
- We were shocked ourselves.
- You know that it wasn't me, don't you?
[Ji Hyo's family is falling apart
at the seams.]
We never should've had him.
How can you say that?
How could you say such a thing?
[Father upset at the birth of
his second son?]
Your father seems to be very upset right now,
so you should go take a walk on your own.
No! You're the one
who put me in this situation!
- Go take a walk and let him cool off.
- Dad!
- Go take a walk, Kwang Soo.
Just go study abroad.
[How to take care of his problematic son?
Send him away to study abroad.]
- Just leave us.
- It really wasn't me.
The elders of this village have decided.
We've decided to banish you.
[Not only from his own home,
but he's banished from the whole town.]
A son like that will be our ruin.
[Ji Hyo's current songpyeon count- Eight.
Back to searching the village.]
There it is. Is that it?
I found one!
[A family full of ace players!
Ah In discovers another  songpyeon!]
Hey, Ah In!
[Haroro immediately discovers
one for himself as well!]
Hey!
We've got them all.
[Ji Hyo's family all of a sudden
having gathered all ten that they need!]
We just need to get these
back to the pot.
[Songpyeon that can be seen
sneaking out of the bag.]
[Hae Sook sees it like a hawk,
and swoops down to snatch it!]
[Hae Sook getting in the way of
Ji Hyo's family's success!]
Stop filming and just run!
Hurry up and put it in there.
[Hae Sook and her boys getting out all
the songpyeons that they've kept hidden.]
- Here, put it in there.
- How many do we have so far?
- How many is that?
- Two, four, six.
Put your three in there right now.
That makes it nine.
We need one more. Where's one more?
[There's six,
and add three more from Jong Kook's shirt!]
- Did you get it all in there? How many now?
- There are nine.
- Two, four, six, okay nine in here.
- We need one more.
[Jong Kook having hidden one away in his
VJ's bag from early on in the game.]
[They must be stopped!]
[Ah... gets the last one in the pot
by the split of a hair difference!]
[Arguing up to the very last moment.]
The have nine in there.
There are nine.
No, we have ten!
[Hae Sook's family succeeds in
gathering all ten songpyeon!]
[We were so close.]
[A total of ten with the addition of the last
songpyeon Hae Sook stole from Gary.]
[And again, the time has returned for
the winning team to pick the box.]
[Hae Sook's family chooses the low box.]
[Ji Hyo's family thus is given the top box.]
[Time to shop for the final cook-off!]
[Hae Sook's family is the first to arrive.]
[And Ji Hyo's family soon arrives thereafter.]
- Okay, everyone has their boxes?
- Yes.
- It's time for you to open your boxes.
- Really?
[It's finally time to reveal what's in
the boxes that they've been carrying around.]
[Just what could be in those boxes?]
What's in here?
[Huh? A plastic bag?]
[The difference in those two boxes are
the difference in the size of their bags.]
- I bet the other one is bigger.
- This one is definitely bigger.
[The plastic bags from the 'top' boxes are
much bigger to put more things in.]
We won't allow you to use any
ingredients that you carry in your hands.
Yes, I understand.
You have 100 seconds from now on.
[Their allotted time to shop- 100 seconds.]
[They don't even know what they're cooking,
but they're off to shop!]
Let's make braised ribs.
- What should we make?
- What are we making?
- How about kimchi?
- Kimchi?
- What are we buying?
[Have to decide what to make,
and get the ingredients for it...]
Kimchi!
Let's make kimchi and rice cake soup.
What am I supposed to do here?
- What are we going to make?
- I don't know what I'm getting.
[Grabbing whatever they find
into their plastic bags.]
What are we making?
What are we making!
Ribs.
Give us meat to make braised ribs.
- You're making braised ribs?
- Meat to make braised ribs.
[It seems as though Ji Hyo's family
is leaning towards making braised ribs?]
- We need to get cooking oil!
- I got the cooking oil!
- Sesame oil!
- Grab the sesame oil!
[Sesame oil is also a given.]
- Did you get the meat?
- What else do we need?
We need some seasoning.
We need rice cakes for the rice cake soup.
[Mother Hae Sook is going to go with
the rice cake soup and kimchi?]
- We need eggs.
- What are we making?
I don't know.
I was just told to get the eggs.
What are we making?
We need to get kimchi!
- Here it is.
- No, we need to well fermented one.
Just take one of each.
Just put them all in the bag.
[Ah In, the confident cook,
goes off to grab all the seasoning he needs.]
Black pepper!
[Grabbing up all the necessary
ingredients that he can think of.]
Salt!
Just grab whatever!
I'm sorry, but we're in a huge rush!
You need to hurry!
[Trying to get the lady to slice up
the ribs at top speed.]
You don't have to cut it so neatly!
60 seconds have passed!
I'm getting the rib meat right now.
Thank you.
- 30 seconds left on the clock!
- Onions!
You have to get the seasoning!
I have no idea what I'm buying.
We don't even know what we're cooking yet.
Come here, Kwang Soo!
20 seconds left on the clock!
Here, put it in here!
- We can't fit any more in here.
- Yes, we can fit it.
Three!
Two!
One!
Time's up!
[Shopping time is over!]
- Stop!
- Stop.
[Having stuffed the bag as much as he could.]
[Did they even get what they needed?]
- Why did you get those things?
- Because I had no idea what we needed.
[Hae Sook's family having grabbed whatever
they saw from not knowing what their dish is.]
[But they realized that they haven't
picked up any seasonings that they need.]
- All we did was grab a lot of kimchi.
- Why are there so many bags of kimchi?
[They were so intent on their dish that
all they grabbed were seven bags of kimchi.]
[What to do...]
Why did you grab this?
[Who put the razor blades in there?]
[He tried to sneak his own
personal shopping item in there?]
Leave that one out.
[Will they be able to make
braised ribs with these ingredients?]
- Thank you.
- Have a great day.
- Let's go.
[After having completed their shopping,
they're now off to cook!]
[Thank you all for coming out
to cheer us on.]
[Off to their final destination with
their cars stocked with food!]
[Final location-
Daegu's traditional village.]
[The largest collection of traditional
residential homes in the city of Daegu.]
[The ultimate final cooking competition
is about to take place here...]
This way?
I'm so jealous of their big bags.
Now, with all the ingredients that you
bought in the 100 seconds that you were given
you have to complete your dish
in exactly one hour or less.
You have to stop your cooking
once your one hour is up
and you will have to submit your dish
for judging in the state it's in.
- Yes, we understand.
- You have exactly one hour.
One hour is all the time you have to cook.
Ready, set, go!
[Allotted time to cook- One hour.
Time to start cooking!]
[Having the final discussion to decide
what dish it is that they should cook.]
We can make kimchi rice cake soup.
Yes, we only need to make two dishes.
[Team Hae Sook's menu- Kimchi rice cake soup
with braised kimchi and chicken.]
Let's make those two dishes,
and submit the one that tastes better.
[Team Ji Hyo's preparations for
braised ribs are getting well under way.]
[Everything's going very smoothly
under Ah In's instructions.]
- Ah In.
- Yes?
Do I need to clean these abalones
with a toothbrush?
You don't really need a toothbrush.
Scrub their shells against each other.
He's a total chef over here.
Do you hear him talking over here?
[A new side to him we never knew!
Ah In cooks like a chef!]
We are going to cook a dish that embodies
the elements of the sky, earth and the ocean.
[A dish that embodies the sky,
the ocean and the earth?]
You're surprised to hear that, aren't you?
[Meanwhile, Hae Sook and her boys
are the embodiment of relaxation.]
Yes, just put all that in there.
[Kimchi]
[And more kimchi...]
[We know it's kimchi rice cake soup,
but that much kimchi?]
It's really good that way.
[And even more kimchi...]
- Don't you think that's way too much?
- No, it tastes better this way.
- Really?
- And later on when this boils...
[With that laughter,
her credibility goes out the window...]
[Half water, and half kimchi.]
- Just trust me for now.
- Yes, sure.
- Mother, would you like for me to do it?
- No, it's okay.
[Now it's time to cut up the chicken,
just like the way she cut up all the kimchi.]
You have put some knife marks on it
for the seasoning to soak in.
Have you noticed how our mother
is really good at improvisation?
When she missed her mark with the knife...
[After she missed with her mark,
she just states that she meant to do that...]
Because what I saw was her missing
the mark and cutting into the chicken wrong.
That's when she said it's good to
put some knife marks on the chicken.
- You didn't mean to do that initially.
- You didn't, did you?
I don't think any of you are my sons.
None of you are helping me out.
- Mom, do you want some help?
- It's just that we know you, don't we?
[Ji Hyo's family are busy preparing all
the vegetables for their braised rib dish.]
Honey, how about spicy?
- How about spicy?
- What about spicy?
We're trying to decide whether we should
make it spicy or soy sauce based.
- Spicy. Let's go with the spicy version.
- Okay, spicy.
It's hard, isn't it?
[Oh my goodness...]
Why isn't this knife working?
[Monday married couple seeming to
have a very good and happy marriage.]
Today is our mom and dad's
wedding anniversary.
No, I'm serious.
And they said it's possible that they might
conceive another child tonight.
Don't say things like that out loud!
We're such a happy family.
I don't want any of you
to come home tonight.
Yes, Dad! We won't
come home until late tonight.
Staying out late is how you can be
filial to us.
Our dad's dream is to become
a long distance daddy.
[Long distance daddy.]
[I can't believe him.]
Take the kids and go to America
once the winter starts.
- Wow, look at what they've got over here.
- It's total chaos over here.
- This pot smells like alcohol.
- What are you cooking?
[It's just your basic
spicy braised rib, chicken, and abalone.]
- They already told us.
- It's because...
Ah In lived in Daegu for a long time when he
was little and he's used to the cooking here.
And Ah In has decided...
- That's why I decided to make this dish.
- Yes, that's right.
- But...
- But why are you adding chicken to it?
- That's what I'm asking.
- That's why, the bird from the sky...
abalone from the ocean...
- and the cow from the earth...
- From the earth.
That's why...
we refer to ourselves as the Triad.
[So that's why this is the Triad?]
You don't have to keep skimming that.
We're going to have to rinse it anyhow.
[You should've told me that sooner.]
You don't have to do all that work.
Am I not the second born son?
I feel like for some reason
that you seem more like our servant.
[He appears more to be their servant
rather than their second born son.]
- Son.
- Yes?
- I'm going to go get something to drink.
- Sure, go ahead.
- Keep an eye on the pot while I'm gone.
- Sure, see you in a bit.
We'll see you soon.
But you know what?
- Don't you think we need some onion in here?
- It's not just that.
I can say this now that she's gone.
But there's way too much kimchi in here.
- All it is, is kimchi.
- She put way too much in there.
But you know what?
That soup does need a lot of kimchi.
- We need a lot of kimchi in that soup.
- I can understand that we need a lot.
[Will all this kimchi be enough
to season the soup's flavor?]
[Meanwhile, Chef Ah In is confidently
whipping up the sauce for his dish.]
[Adding in the garlic, soy sauce
and the hot pepper paste.]
[With other seasonings and grain syrup
to give it extra flavor...]
[Yummy]
[Using the traditional way to eliminate
the order and rinsing all the meat.]
Are you not adding any water in there?
I'm going to add that in after I
saute this first for a little bit.
[Saute, then braise with the vegetables,
and it's all done!]
That looks really good.
- Yes, I think it'll be fine.
- You think?
[Hot blooded youth Ah In is transformed into
an honorable chef in the kitchen.]
[And this guy...]
[What is he doing?]
Hey!
What are you doing!
Why are you cutting that pear
with a pair of scissors?
I have to puree this pear.
I couldn't find any knives.
We never should've had you!
Do you know how hurtful it is
to hear you say that?
Oh my, it's almost done.
[And this guy is still...]
- How is that going?
- Kwang Soo.
Go wash the carrots.
- Why are you talking to me that way?
- Didn't you used to sing too?
Here, think of this as your mike,
and go take this with you and wash it.
Your son is in the middle of
doing something.
Look, he's like Edward Scissors hands.
- What are you doing?
- I have to puree this for the dish.
Every little thing that you do
irritates the heck out of me.
Dad!
- Ugh, seriously.
- Just what do I mean to this family?
- Dad, tell him the truth.
- I just can't stand the sight of you.
[Dad... why do you keep treating
me this way?]
Do you think that I'll leave this family
just because you treat me that way?
[Pain in the butt son.]
[Next week... A dreamlike story that
the Giraffe will experience.]
Dad, where are you?
Don't open the door for anyone!
[The Giraffe will get to
meet his real father!]
It's him! He's the
one who always torments me!
It's this guy!
He's the guy!
Dad!
[Somehow... now only
20 minutes remains on the clock.]
[Huh? Why is she taking out all the broth?]
- It won't come to a boil.
- Why are you taking out the broth?
It won't come to a boil.
We need for it to come to a boil.
- That's going to start boiling soon.
- Really?
Then put it back in?
Mother, what about what you said
to us about putting our trust in you?
Mom, what's wrong with you?
This is your first time making it, right?
No, that's not it.
It's just that this kitchen
is an unfamiliar one to me.
You've been the eldest daughter of
this whole family for the past few decades.
I have tried to use all my cooking know-hows
of the past 50 years into this dish.
- This really makes it feel like a holiday.
- It's finally boiling.
Mom, what is this?
[This golden colored powder...]
[All that powder that can be seen
piled up on the ladle is...]
[It can't be powdered beans, nor sugar...]
What is all that powder?
Aunt, what are you doing?
[Continues not to tell them anything...]
[And secretly adds the powder into
the boiling soup broth.]
Seasoning?
No, this is definitely not MSG seasoning.
It's a special ingredient I brought from home.
- You brought that from home?
- Yes, I did.
[The kimchi broth with the special powder...
will it taste like anything now?]
- Should I add in the vegetables now?
- Add it in there!
[Ji Hyo's family finally adds in
all the vegetables.]
- Wow... look at that.
- Don't you think that's too much?
- There's not enough sauce for it.
- That's too much vegetables.
Who chopped this radish?
- Who chopped this radish?
- Kang Gary.
- Dad, what is this?
- That is one thing that I'm not good at.
- Should we take some out?
- No, it should be okay.
[Adding in the rest of the sauce
that Ah In made without sparing any.]
[Hae Sook and her sons are trying to
taste the dish to see how it is.]
It's lacking something,
but I can't put my finger on what it is.
- Then let's add more kimchi in the soup.
- The soup doesn't need any more kimchi.
[More kimchi?]
Mom, just use a pair of scissors to cut it.
Just use scissors.
- Use scissors to cut it.
- You have to stop putting in all that kimchi.
[She put all seven bags
of kimchi in her soup!]
[Her special powder or whatever
is added to the soup some more.]
We should've made a smaller batch of this.
This is too much soup.
I can't figure out how to season it because
we're making such a huge batch of it.
I'm only used to making
family sized portions at home.
I told you earlier that we put
too much water in the pot.
- We gave you some of our ingredients.
- Thank you.
We can't put that in here.
No, we can't.
Jae Suk, we can't put
stuff like that in the soup.
- No, you can't.
- What are you trying to put in there?
- It's really lacking something in taste.
- No way, you can't put that in the soup.
Then put that in here.
[Just then, Hae Sook and her boys
add in all the rice cakes.]
- You did need a lot of kimchi in there.
- See? You do need a lot in the soup.
It looks really good
with all that kimchi in there.
Aren't you the youngest of all of us?
So why are you just sitting there talking?
- Why aren't you even doing anything?
- I'm arranging things around here.
Why would you be arranging anything?
- I'm making sure that everything goes well.
- Why are you the one to be doing that?
- Seriously... you're such a brat.
- Why did you raise him to be such a brat?
- I'm sorry. I shouldn't have.
- He has no respects for his elders.
I think I breastfed him for way too long.
- I just focused too much on him.
- You gave him too much of your attention.
You've always been very good to me, Mom.
How's it going with that soup?
- Is it boiling?
- Do I look like a reporter to you?
- Do I look like your beck and call boy?
- I was just asking you a question.
We're not over hanging out at
Kim Hae Sook's house right now.
This is our home, and this is our mom.
[Don't talk to him like you're on a set.]
I just wanted to know what
kind of a situation we were in.
Now... you've only got
ten minutes left on the clock.
We have to let it simmer some more so that
the rice cake cooks all the way through.
It's almost done now.
We just need to add the glass noodles to it,
and let that cook through.
- Let's see.
- Let it simmer some more.
[All the members of Ji Hyo's family
getting a taste of the dish.]
- It's good.
- All the meat is cooked through.
[The delicious looking triad of
the braised dish is now complete!]
That soup is finally starting to
bubble and boil.
You were so worried that it wasn't boiling,
but look at how it's bubbling over now.
- What is that on top? Eggs?
- Yeah.
Aren't kimchi soups supposed to have
that clean and crisp taste?
But adding some eggs as a topper
could really deepen the taste.
[Ji Hyo and her family adds in the abalone
for the sea element to complete the dish.]
Did Ah In do all the cooking?
- No, we all did it together.
- Look at that.
[Add in the final touches... and voila!]
[At last, both teams' dishes are complete!]
[Judgment time!]
Please place your dish on the table
that you see in front of you.
Madame go Dong Wan would like to
say something to all of you herself.
That's our rich grandmother.
You all worked very hard to create your dish.
If any of you utter even a single word
about who made what dish...
I'm going to flip that table over
and dump everything onto the ground.
You have to let it go because
she's our rich grandmother.
Thank you everyone for
your hard work.
These dishes that all of you
worked so hard to create...
It is now time to judge
which of two is the better dish.
- Who's going to do that?
- For fairness of the judging...
We have asked a panel of judges who are
known for their sensitive taste buds.
Please welcome citizens of Daegu
as your panel of judges.
[A full stand.]
- Wow, there are so many of them.
- Wow.
- There has to be a hundred of them.
- There are so many of them.
[100 of Daegu's finest citizens to
judge their dishes.]
This panel of judges that you see will fairly
judge to see which dish of the two is better.
We will now start the judging.
The judges will start by tasting the A dishes
and move on to taste the B dish.
Once finished, please come over to the ballot
and cast your vote as to which was better.
Will row one please step forward
and start the judging?
We ask that you judge fairly.
[The first dish to be judged-
Course A, kimchi rice cake soup.]
Okay, the rest of the first row
can step forward.
Please step on forward.
[Now tasting Course B-
The braised triad of meats.]
[Casting their votes by writing down either
A, or B depending on what they preferred.]
[Everyone taking the judging very seriously
according to their facial expressions.]
[One by one, all 100 of the judges
gets to taste both the dishes.]
[Which of the two teams will
get more votes?]
Okay, there are only
ten more judges left to go.
The judging is now almost over.
[The final judge casts his vote.]
- Give your judges a round of applause.
- Thank you all for your hard work.
[A round of applause for
both of the teams as well.]
Okay, to the daughter and her family
who wins this competition...
I will give this valuable ladle
to that daughter and her family.
- Is that real gold?
- It's a gold ladle?
This ladle perfectly seasons any dish
that you dip it into.
[The ladle seasons the dish the moment
that it's dipped into anything?]
- So that's why it's the ultimate ladle?
- Is there even a fortune then?
It's the ultimate ladle.
Okay, the team that will be
the recipient of this ultimate ladle is...
with 71 votes out of a hundred...
71 votes?
- 71 votes? Really?
- That's a lot of votes.
I wonder who that is?
[Hae Sook's kimchi rice cake soup,
and braised kimchi and chicken?]
[Ji Hyo's braised triad of meats?]
Team B, Team Ah In wins!
[Ji Hyo and her family wins
the ultimate competition!]
[The braised beef dish must've
struck a chord with the judges!]
[The golden ultimate ladle is passed down
to Ji Hyo and her family!]
- Thank you.
- Really?
Yeah, I think it's real gold.
A round of applause in gratitude to all of you
for allowing us to come to your village today.
[Thank you to the panel of judges for
coming on the show to be our judge.]
- Thank you.
- Thank you!
And even though this is the last day
of the Chuseok holiday...
we wish that you have a very joyous holiday,
and we will see you again next week.
- Thank you!
- Goodbye, Ah In!
Goodbye!
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Everything...
started from one single book.]
[A book that was given to them
by a young woman.]
[It was a loving collection of all the fan
letters that were sent in to Running Man.]
[They will run for the love
shown to them by that young woman.]
We have to use the pictures
to find the girl?
[Use the picture in the clues
to find the girl.]
[All the missions are already in
the book of pictures.]
Let go!
[Little girl... are you watching us?]
[A surprise race for the love
of the little girl.]
[A project to complete the picture book
for the love of the little girl.]
[Who will be the one to complete
the mission?]
[Running Man's first ever
individual top secret project.]
[Next week's Running Man-
Search for the little girl.]