[The ultimate power house]
[vs. a coalition against Mr. Capable.]
[January, 27, 2013 - Seoul City Hall]
-There's no need to fear Kim Jong Kook.
- Let's just go up against him.
Let's not let him push us back.
- Hey! Hey...
- Come here.
I just ran into Jong Kook.
Make sure you don't run into Jong Kook.
- Why?
- Jong Kook is running around in a thin shirt.
Really?
He's running around in his thin shirt and
said he'll kill anyone who crosses his path.
- He's going around saying that?
- You can't run into him!
- Seriously?
- What's going on here?
He's totally scary right now.
He's crouched in this position.
All you can see are his eyes.
Where is he right now?
[He's very close by.]
[Lying in wait.]
- Who does Kim Jong Kook think he is?
- He's Kim Jong Kook.
[Attack!]
[The shock and the terror!]
- He's so scary!
- He got me!
[Ji Suk Jin?]
- What is that?
- Do you see what's on his back?
[Another name on his back?]
- What is that?
- Why does he have 'Ji Suk Jin' on his back?
- What is that, Suk Jin?
- I really have no idea!
- What's going on?
- I really don't know!
- Hey! It's Ji Suk Jin!
[The coalition being shaken
from the core.]
- I'm serious! I have no idea!
- Just catch him!
[A win that no one can predict.]
[Reincarnation]
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Reincarnation: A soul being reborn in
a new body to begin a new life.]
[Reincarnation - The seven couriers.]
[January 27, 1938 - Seoul]
[A building in Dongdaemun.]
[This man is...]
I feel like a painter today.
Seriously...
These clothes are so warm.
I thought I'd be really cold,
but these clothes are really warm.
This is embarrassing.
Sir, this is really embarrassing.
People can't recognize me
in these clothes
and they're just staring at me wondering
why I'm walking around in this clothing.
This is embarrassing.
[A crowd of people following
in her wake.]
[Staring at her surroundings, she realizes
she's the only one dressed thirties style.]
I'm seriously so embarrassed!
This is driving me crazy!
Look at how short this skirt is too.
Just what in the world is going on here?
[Unable to stomach the
embarrassing ladies' style.]
Seriously... having to walk around
Dongdaemun dressed like this...
[Subconsciously hunching their
shoulders due to their costumes.]
Why do I have to wear a costume like
this? This is so embarrassing!
Why did I have to put this on when
there are so many people around here?
What are you making me
do right now?
2,000 won for a chance
to take a picture with me.
Who is this person?
- Take the subway to the city hall.
- You want me to take the subway?
Dressed like this?
[Everyone is headed to their destination,
the City Hall.]
They must have some grand project
prepared for us today.
This is something the son
of a General would wear, isn't it?
I wouldn't know just from the clothes,
but with the hat added to it...
Am I going to get to become
Kim Doo Hwan today?
Is there going to be some action today?
[Unlike others, he seems to be happy
with the costume attire.]
Fashion is all about the confidence.
[When in fact, his attire brings
on the flashbulbs.]
Can you in the puffy coat
get out of the way a little?
He's our PD.
Did you hear her, puffy coat man?
Puff coat PD.
Get out of the way.
Listen to what the ladies are telling you.
People can know who I am
with this name tag.
[Letting everyone in his surroundings
know who he is.]
My name tag is on my back!
My name tag...
What is this?
This is my first time riding the subway
since coming here from the Joseon era.
[Even his walk is befitting of that era.]
I totally startled myself just now!
I startled myself with my own reflection
because I couldn't recognize myself!
So this is what I look like right now?
[Are you the same guy whom we've
seen in our history books?]
What is this object used for?
Do I just put it up against this?
Oh my goodness!
[A wavy entrance?]
[Amazed by everything he sees.]
Aren't these the same kind of
rice cakes I used to eat in my neighborhood?
Are these honey rice cakes?
I'll take one of these.
[Purchases a package of
honey rice cakes.]
[Must hurry to city hall.]
[Familiar party songs being played
over the speakers from his neighborhood.]
They're playing a song that
I've heard many times.
- Would you like to try one?
- Sure, I'll take one.
[Respecting his elders.]
Father, you have to bite into it gently.
Otherwise, the honey will burst out.
Oh my goodness!
The honey got all over you.
Father, you have honey all over you.
[A well-mannered 'Gae-man'
in front of all the elders.]
- Isn't it good?
- Yeah, it's good.
Even a single bean must be shared
in order to build your relationships.
And the nation may be reunited...
[Giraffe more noticeable than usual.]
But I'm still...
the last king of Joseon.
[Comrades... to the city hall!]
[That's...]
Make sure to verify this piece
of paper when you get to Sinchon.
In Sinchon?
[A piece of paper that he received
from his comrade...]
I totally forgot about this.
[My dear comrade...]
[My dear comrade?]
Comrade, comrade... my dear comrade!
My dear comrade...
[You are needed to head an important mission
as a representative of a secret organization.]
[A secret organization...]
[The seven couriers.]
[We have information that there's a treasure
chest at the city hall containing gold bars.]
[Information that there's a treasure chest
containing gold bars at the city hall.]
Find the treasure chest that's being
kept in the Mayor's office at the city hall...
and find all the keys that are being
kept hidden in the copy room.
[Find the keys!]
A key that's being kept
hidden in the printing room...
[The location of the hidden key is
different for each courier...]
[The seven couriers that have been dispatched
by seven different organizations...]
[There will only be one victor!]
It's 1938?
- 1938?
- It's 1938 right now?
1938...
[The seven couriers.]
[An epic drama that travels through
the span of time.]
[Find and take the gold treasure chest that's
being kept hidden at the city hall!]
[A timeless gigantic action-packed event.]
[Just which one of the couriers will
take possession of the gold chest?]
Then am I a martyr today?
Undertaking an important mission for
the sake of this country...
Martyr Gae.
I'm supposed to be a part of
a secret organization?
[His tongue getting all twisted up in knots
from the enormity of the mission he's to face.]
[Finally arrives at the city hall station.]
What the heck?
[Her unchanging skills even with
the flow of time.]
Look at what I have to wear when
your clothes still look so normal!
- Comrade Blank...
- Comrade Yoo...
- We have to get to the city hall.
- We're a part of the secret society.
- We have to get to the city hall...
- For the unification of Korea...
[Excessive commitment to the mission.]
With my teeth gritted...
I will protect our nation of Korea!
I will protect it.
- Comrade Yoo, let's protect it.
- Comrade Blank...
- Look! It's our comrade!
- Who? Who is it?
[Another courier?]
- Comrade Gae!
- What is it?
- Comrade Gae...
[Courier Gae's attire drawing other people's
stares and their laughter.]
- The image I've seen in the history books...
- That's correct.
I took the Running Machine to come
to this time in history.
- Comrade Gae...
- Comrade Gae!
- What is this that you're wearing?
- I took the Running Machine here.
- Your shoes...
- Comrade Gae, that suits you so well!
[Seoul City Hall]
[Comrades Gae-Yoo-Blank,
having arrived at the city hall.]
[Comrade Kkuk is also close to arriving.]
[Comrades Lee and Ji at a full sprint.]
Let's go in.
[Place where their mission is to take place.
City Hall.]
[But this place...]
[As if time has slipped backwards
80 years into the past...]
[Everywhere they look are people dressed
in clothing from the past era.]
[A place where the time stopped flowing.]
[City hall as it was back in 1938.]
[Even the games that they're playing are
games from the past era.]
I'm the last king of Joseon.
- You're a King?
- You look like you're a student.
[What game are you two playing?]
This is 1938...
Even though I can't believe it...
How could something like this
have happened?
[In a place where the time stopped flowing...]
[You must carry out your mission.]
[This is how all the seven couriers
came to gather in the same place.]
I must find the Mayor's office.
The gold treasure chest
is in the Mayor's office?
[Comrade Blank checking her paper
once more time.]
Check the treasure chest that's being kept
in the Mayor's office at the city hall.
Mayor's office...
[This is none other than the
Mayor's office!]
[Deep inside that office...]
[The treasure chest!]
[The courier's mission...]
[Open up the treasure chest and
take over all the gold bars!]
[But the number of keys that are needed...]
[There are a total of seven!]
[Now that he's verified the chest,
time to search for the keys!]
[ The location of the keys...]
Where can I find the keys?
- What are you searching for?
- Nothing!
[Comrade Jae Suk having come to the
Mayor's office to verify the treasure chest.]
This is by the country's orders.
- What are you looking for?
- Nothing!
It's nothing!
[In order to open up the treasure chest...]
[Number of keys needed are seven.]
Then it means that all of us
needs to find our keys?
[In that case...]
Does it mean that one person needs to steal
all those keys and open up this chest?
Look here, Comrade Gae!
Why are you saying those words out loud
when you should be whispering it to yourself?
- Who is it?
- A lion is headed this way.
- A lion.
- Welcome.
Kim Doo Hwan...
Kim Doo Hwan, what are you doing here?
[Possessed by the spirit of
Kim Doo Hwan.]
- You got a fedora...
- What did you say?
You came wearing a fedora.
Who are you supposed to be?
I was just farming on my land...
I was just farming when I got conscripted.
Don't you think he's here for the
unification of our country?
- What are you?
- Comrade Kkuk...
Is this the treasure chest?
- There are seven of them.
- Then we each need to find one?
- There are seven locks.
- There are seven locks?
[Each of the courier knows the location
of where their one key is hidden.]
[All those seven keys must be in possession
in order to open up the treasure chest.]
[Couriers heads out to find the keys.]
[Gary's key hidden away in
the press room.]
[Jong Kook's key is on the
balcony somewhere.]
[Jae Suk's key is by the window...]
All three of the traitors have
gathered together in one place.
Let's seriously win together!
What is it?
- I saw it first! It's mine!
- It's mine, you traitors!
- It's mine!
- Wait!
We can have it...
we can share it amongst ourselves.
As long as we throw our greed aside...
- What is this?
- I think we need keys for these locks.
They're all locked.
- How many locks are there?
- There are seven of them.
Need all the keys to open it.
Let's stay hidden here and take the keys
from the people that walk in here.
Once we oust them, don't you think their
keys will undoubtedly become ours?
[Plotting their ruse instead of
searching for their keys.]
- Let's fight them!
- Do you want to do it or not?
[Before even five seconds go by,
the group erupts into an argument.]
Let's all stay together until only
the three of us are left. Please!
- Let the three of us be the last survivors.
- Yes, seriously.
- Yes, seriously. No going back!
- No betrayals either!
[Bad habit of his hand going into action
whenever he sees an opportunity.]
[This is the traitor's DNA.]
[If they keep this up, they won't even find
any of their keys and fail the mission.]
- We'll all let go on the count of three.
- One, two, three!
[Doubt anyone will let go...]
Where's the press room?
[But that woman is...]
[A woman of mystery catching the eye
of Comrade Gae.]
[A woman of marrying age
bumping into Comrade Gae.]
What did you do that for?
- I dropped all my papers.
- I'm so sorry!
This is my first time here.
- Are you okay?
- Yes, I'm fine. Thank you.
It seems as though you like
'Jingle Bells'?
- You're totally my style.
- I am?
[Disappears after making her comment?]
Wait! You can't...
You can't just leave like that!
[Huh?]
[Could 'Jingle Bells' be
another clue of some kind?]
Why... why did she bump into
my shoulder?
Just why would she do that?
What is this?
[A place where people are curiously
tossing their balls around.]
[Something feels suspicious...]
What's everyone doing?
What is this?
What are you guys doing?
What are you doing?
[Huh? The balls they've been playing with
are thrown towards Comrade Kkuk?]
[A sudden frontal assault?]
What are you people...
What is this?
Why are they throwing their
balls at me?
There's nothing here.
This is extremely important!
They're coming! Run!
What is this?
[The moment he's handed the bundle,
he gets chased after by a mob!]
- Catch him!
- What the heck?
What's going on?
What? What? What is it?
What? What is it?
Press release? Wait...
[Comrade Gae discovers a press release.]
What's going on?
- Gary!
- What's going on?
Why? What's going on?
[If he doesn't hand over the bundle,
they just might chase him back to 2013!]
[Could the key be inside that pouch?]
[The key is inside the pouch!]
[Comrade Gae finds his key!]
[Barely succeeds at getting away
with the bundle.]
What is this?
[What's wrapped up in that bundle?]
Just what is inside this bundle?
[Just a pillow?]
There's nothing in here...
[All he can manage from the shock
is an empty laugh...]
- It's nothing?
- It's nothing.
- Why were they after you if it's nothing?
- Why are you standing there watching me?
- Why are you...
- I was watching out of curiosity.
[Comrade Gae with a hardened expression
after having found his key.]
Everyone... let's do this!
[Blank Ji quickly noticing his
hardened expression.]
What are you doing?
That mere scrap of paper...
Wait! You can't take that from me!
[Scanning the contents within moments.]
Wait... the important part...
You didn't get to see the
important part yet!
[Getting rid of the evidence.]
Spit it out!
I said, spit it out!
[Wait, something...]
[He dropped his key!]
Ji Hyo!
[Emergency situation.]
[To so simply lose the key
he worked so hard to find...]
It's not time for this yet!
[Comrade Blank handing his key
back over to him for now...]
[ Why did it fall out so easily?]
I can't believe this fell out like that.
Ji Hyo, it's not time for all that yet.
You really are so clumsy.
Even back in 1938,
Kang Gary was this clumsy!
What is this?
What are all these neon signs
doing in this little room?
Is this a dance place or something?
- Just pretend you never saw it.
- Okay.
But in exchange,
you have to make me a promise.
What is that?
If I get into any trouble...
- You have to help me.
- I will help you out unconditionally.
Okay.
[Due to his clumsy keeping of the key,
Blank and Gae coalition is born.]
[Comrade Ha's key that's said to be
hidden near the copier.]
Here is a copier...
How am I to look for it in here?
Where could it be?
I found it right away.
Here it is...
Here it is.
[Comrade Ha finds his key.]
[In an attempt to confuse others,
he puts the pouch back in its place.]
I found it.
What? What is it?
Why are you guys moving?
[All the people are suddenly...]
What's going on?
Why are they all acting like this?
What is this? A musical?
What? What are you all doing?
Why are you all acting like this?
[People from the Joseon era just
keep on dancing without any response.]
[Disperses as soon as Gary arrives?]
[Unable to recognize him right away,
Ha Ha finally discovers Mr. Gae in the midst.]
- I didn't know what was going on.
- I didn't either.
- Did you find your key yet?
- No, I just got here.
I think that's the prettiest outfit I've
ever seen you wear on Running Man.
It suits you perfectly.
[Detective Jae Suk searching every
possible window sill that he runs across.]
[After checking his surroundings first.]
[The silk pouch!]
[Detective Jae Suk also finds his key!]
[Now that he's got his key
in his hands...]
[Next is...]
This is really important!
[Huh?]
Wait! I don't want it!
I don't want to take it!
[False bundle that keeps being
handed to him every chance possible.]
I don't want it!
I said, I didn't want it!
[On the run again with all his might!]
I don't have anything!
Just leave!
What's going on?
[As even that happens whenever he
runs into the bundle carrying man...]
- What's wrong?
- What's going on?
I wonder what's going on.
Why... why did he insist giving it to me
when I said I didn't want it?
- The bundle?
- Yeah!
Where did it happen?
On the first floor.
Why does he insisting on giving it to me
even when I tell him I don't want it?
[Now that we think back,
the bundle is only given to Jae Suk...]
It's something you need.
[He said it was an item he needed...]
[But all that happened was
he got chased after by the mob...]
[But...]
[If by any chance all these events...]
[Weren't just a coincidence?]
[What if 'You' of the past was
'Me' in the present?]
Why are all these people here?
[Kwang Soo in search of his key.]
[Why are all these people...]
Hello.
I'm the King of the Joseon era.
Will everyone please stop
their movements?
Man Soo, it's so nice to see you!
Oh my, I'm sorry.
What is this?
Is there something going on?
[Hint to finding the key, Azerbaijan.
Seems as though he doesn't know the country.]
Hyun Kook!
Oh... I'm sorry.
What is this?
Why are they all behaving like this?
Who are they mistaking me for?
Who is Hyun Kook?
- What the heck?
- Cha Dol!
[Being condemned everywhere he goes.]
[What are these events
happening to the Giraffe...]
Hey!
This is strange.
[An area full of all dapperly dressed men.]
What are you doing?
Why are you being like this?
What's going on?
Why are you being like this with me?
[Is Comrade Blank being
forcefully detained?]
[Kneeling down before her?]
Please accept me!
[A sudden love confession?]
[Comrade Gae suddenly butting in.]
[Unbelievable...]
Hug him!
Love triangles existed even
back in 1938?
- Don't you think this is a bit too harsh?
- What's too harsh?
[Same coupling even 80 years ago...]
Who are you to take my
lady away from me?
- Hey, let's go!
- Let's go!
Who are you?
You chased away all my suitors who
were about to confess their love for me!
I don't want you seeing them.
- They're not much to look at.
- Seriously!
A man knows other men best.
Don't see any of them.
If you date a man like that,
it'll just make things difficult for you.
What difficulties are there?
You're the high maintenance one!
All he did was give you some flowers.
What do you mean,
just give me some flowers?
- When these flowers are full of fragrance.
- Why would you even need any flowers?
When you're more beautiful
than any flower already.
Anyway, Kang Gary...
you weren't any different in 1938, I see.
[But anyways... what's going on now?]
[Detective Yoo with
the key in his possession.]
What... what are you going around doing?
[Discovers a fascinating object.]
What is that? A dog?
Where did you get that thing to be
pulling it around with you everywhere?
Huh?
I'm sorry.
- Why do you all keep...
- Why do they keep hitting you?
- What's that?
- What is that?
[All the comrades gathering around
the fascinating camera device.]
What is that?
It's a camera. What else could it be?
- What is that?
- Hey, that thing is expensive.
[Unable to take his eyes away...]
Kwang Soo, strike a pose.
[Immersing himself in posing
for the camera.]
Very cool.
What are you doing?
- What are you doing?
- What do you think you're doing?
This is what this camera is
used to shoot.
How would you know that?
- It's used to take back shots.
- Is it really?
[Seeing how they're all so at ease,
does it mean they've all found their key?]
[All seven keys have to be together...]
[To be able to open up the treasure chest.]
I told you, I haven't found it yet.
[Everyone should have found
their key by now.]
- As of now...
- You keep talking quite a bit.
- Wait...
- You're acting very suspicious.
What are you doing?
- Are we starting now then?
- Let's get started.
- Okay, let's do it then.
- Let's do it!
Are the five of you
working together right now?
Why don't we all go our separate ways for now?
[Comrade Kkuk sensing that
something is up.]
You have to make up your
mind right now.
[Which team will Comrade Yoo join?]
- One!
- Okay.
- Let's go.
- Let's get him!
[Targeting Comrade Kkuk first
for being the strongest?]
- This isn't going to be easy.
- You were being the loudest!
- Wait...
[Comrade Yoo goes after the Giraffe?]
It wasn't me. I didn't do it.
It really wasn't me.
[Comrade Giraffe fails the mission!]
[A sudden ambush that
he hadn't even fathomed.]
- Kwang Soo!
- Don't let him know anything.
[Is Comrade Giraffe's mission
over this simply?]
[Everyone still remaining confrontational.]
So this is why people are always
telling me to watch out for Yoo Jae Suk?
- The key!
- The key...
[Comrade Yoo now with two keys.]
- Wow... he has two keys now?
- So it means everyone has their keys.
I have to oust Kim Jong Kook somehow.
Kim Jong Kook... he won't even budge.
It's him again!
It's that man again!
[The man with the bundle again!]
Why that man... seriously, what the heck?
Why are you doing this to me?
You're going to need this.
I'm for real this time!
[Desperately passing off the bundle
every time he sees him.]
Yes, I understand.
I'm seriously about to go crazy.
What are you afraid of?
- What's that bundle for?
- There he is!
- It's already on its way up.
- Suk Jin... second floor... third floor!
[A life on the run with the bundle.]
[Where did he go?]
Gary...
- What are you doing here?
- Gary!
[Blank-Gae coalition in hiding.]
- I think Jae Suk went in there.
- With his bundle?
Hey! There he is!
Jae Suk!
What is that?
[The group breaks out in their dance
as soon as Ha Ha arrives.]
Over at the end!
[Comrade Yoo backed up into a corner.]
- Listen to me.
- What's in that bundle?
- What is it?
- What's in there?
Hurry up and open it.
- Quickly.
- Show us what it is.
- Then I'll... show you what this secret is.
- Yes, show us the secret.
- Tell us.
- Inside this...
- There's money in this bundle.
- Money?
Let me see it then.
[If they catch him in his lie,
then he's going to get ousted...]
- Why don't we talk about this?
- I'm sorry.
[Uses the moment Comrade Ji
has his guard down to eliminate him!]
You don't all need to see this, do you?
Gary, this is why... this is why...
[Comrade Big-nose having been deceived
and eliminated within a flash of a moment.]
We don't all need to see this.
[This is Comrade Yoo's killer instinct.]
- Are you really...
- Wow, you're really scary!
- Go stand away from me.
- No, I'm not like that!
[Two people are already...]
[I have to survive no matter what
to complete my mission.]
[Gains Comrade Ji's key.]
[A total of three keys!]
[If he can get the remaining four keys...]
[Okay...]
This means Jae Suk now has three keys.
Oh my goodness!
[Discovers the Tiger lying in wait.]
- You really startled me!
- Why?
- Do you know that Jae Suk is no joke?
- Why? What's he doing?
Suk Jin... Jae Suk totally tricked him
and ousted Suk Jin.
Jong Kook...
please take care of Jae Suk.
- Okay.
- He's in there.
I know.
[Come to me... Comrade Yoo.]
[What? He's headed into the room
Jong Kook is in?]
[You came...]
[Just what...]
[Even though he tried to turn
after luring him in...]
You've got some nice skills.
[He's congratulating him on
eliminating two people?]
It was just a rare chance.
You have to... know to recognize the
chance within a split second.
You're frightening.
[Who is he calling frightening?]
What else can I do if I don't want
to be the one getting ousted?
I guess you're right.
Very cool.
[Gauging each other out.]
I've never once beat Kim Jong Kook
when we're the only two sole survivors.
[In that case...]
[Is right now the chance?]
[Is he about to eliminate
Comrade Kkuk right now?]
[Now... now's the chance!]
[I've been had...]
[He was eyeing Comrade Yoo
the same way.]
How can this be?
You were just about to oust me, right?
That's why you followed me?
I had a feeling you would,
so that's why I was hiding back there.
[So he noticed...]
Darn!
Why you! I'm not going
to let you get away with it!
- Kim Jong Kook!
- Ultimately, people don't change.
[He really is Mr. Capable.]
The keys.
- Why don't you hand them over?
- Having to give him all three keys...
[Transferring all three keys into
Jong Kook's possession.]
I can't believe I've been
deceived like that.
betrayed like this.
[When I've eliminated two of the
comrades with my own two hands...]
What is this?
Single cells?
[Solitary prison confinement?]
[That's right! All the eliminated comrades
are being kept confined in solitary cells!]
But... why aren't they announcing
who's been ousted today?
Right? They haven't announced me.
They haven't announced anything.
I usually feel some comfort when I hear the
announcement of who's been ousted
because I know that things are slowly
starting to come to an end, but...
do I have to keep staying here?
It's going to be a long day.
Why is the jail so small?
This isn't the proper amenity for jail.
Everyone is being confined in
a solitary cell today.
Solitary cells?
What wrong have I committed
to bear such a heavy price like this?
[Will they... all stay in
solitary confinement like this?]
This really is too much.
Ah! Yoo Jae Suk...
What have I done that's so awful to
have to be in solitary confinement?
Shouldn't I at least know who's been
ousted so that I can...
[Tiger out on full strike mode since there
are only a few survivors left remaining.]
[Comrade Capable on the chase!]
[Real action.]
- Hurry!
- Hey!
[Stop right there!]
[This right here...
is Mr. Capable's real image!]
[The Tiger showing his claws...]
[Comrade Ha earns himself a
solitary prison confinement.]
[Absolute exhaustion.]
[Only people remaining now are,
Tiger vs. Black and Gae coalition.]
What should I do?
I'd hate to tear you two apart.
[Solid Blank and Gae coalition.]
It really would be the end for us.
- That's right! It's totally obvious!
- Who's betraying whom right now?
Ji Hyo, you want to oust me then?
And hey, it will be Ace versus Ace!
[Does he call that a proposition?]
[Just then!]
[Comrade Kkuk comes after Comrade Gae!]
[Blank and Gae coalition
trying to work together.]
[Ji Hyo's in danger!]
[Comrade Blank's name tag!]
[Forcefully thwarts his moves,
and counterattacks!]
[Ultimately, even
Comrade Blank is eliminated.]
What am I supposed to do on my own
without you now?
Good luck.
Good luck with what?
I'll see you in a minute.
Hey, Ji Hyo!
I'll see you in 32 seconds.
[Comrade Kkuk vs. Comrade Gae.]
I really would like to win for once.
[Just who will get all seven keys and
get to open the treasure chest?]
Please don't be like this!
[Ultimate power house, Mr. Capable,
Comrade Kkuk!]
[And a man who's end we
can never predict.]
[Random Mr. Capable, Comrade Gae.]
[A real battle between these two.]
[Gary grabs his at the same time!]
[The keys are mine!]
[The battle between these two...]
[Who will get to open up the
treasure chest?]
It's not a situation to get involved in.
But what else can I do?
[Just who...]
[January 27, 1938 - The final battle.]
[A short while later.]
[The treasure chest was opened.]
- The recording is over.
- What?
You're now free to go.
What in the world is going on?
Why isn't anything getting announced?
- We'll let you go.
- To where?
I'm just free to leave?
What is this? We're to just leave
without anyone telling us the results?
Really?
Kim Jong Kook, you're dead!
[The treasure chest being opened...]
[But... there's nothing in there?]
[January 27, 1938]
[The seven comrades that were gathered
together at the city hall.]
[In the end, they weren't able to
successfully carry out their mission.]
[And...]
[The tumultuous years pass on by.]
[January 27, 2013 - Seoul City Hall.]
[The stepping stones that connect
the past to the present.]
You've been reincarnated.
[From 1938 to 2013.]
I've been reincarnated?
You've been reincarnated.
Why would I be reincarnated when
I haven't even died?
I've never been dead?
It is now the year 2013.
[Reincarnated comrades who've traveled
80 years in time.]
[An old chest and a picture that's
placed in front of them?]
[A treasure chest that was discovered
at the city hall in 1938.]
[Even though there's evidence the chest was
opened with the use of the seven keys]
[none of the contents were found inside.]
[Also, none of the seven keys
were ever discovered from the site.]
[Even though the final man standing used the
seven keys to open up the treasure chest...]
[The treasure chest was found empty!]
[Two chests were originally produced in an
effort to thwart any attempts of theft.]
[But the whereabouts of one of
the chests are unknown.]
Then does it mean that the real
treasure chest is somewhere else?
[Then does it mean that the real
treasure chest is still elsewhere?]
Oh my God!
[The treasure chest that was opened was
a decoy used to thwart theft attempts!]
Seven couriers were sent by different...
isn't that us?
The final member of the seven couriers
had all seven keys right up to the end.
Are you asking us to find out
who that last person was?
[The final man standing from 1938 has
the seven keys to the real treasure chest!]
So that's why you kept us
locked up in our rooms?
So that we can't find out the results?
So that we can't know who ended up
with all the keys?
Seriously...
I wonder who has the seven keys?
[Ji Hyo knows that the final two survivors
were Gary and Jong Kook.]
It's either this man or this man.
This man really looks just like the picture.
[The last two survivors, Mr. Capable and Gary
facing their final battle in 1938.]
[Just who is the last man standing
that has possession of all seven keys?]
Okay... what does this mean?
[Unable to comprehend.]
If you can give me some information
a day before the recording...
If you'll give me some information separately,
I'll study it and come better prepared.
Don't you think that I'm left too much
out in the dark with this situation?
Who was ousted after me?
I don't know anything.
Your present mission is to start figuring out
what it is that happened back then.
[Who was the person that opened up
the treasure chest in the past...]
[Also where's the real treasure chest?]
- Jae Suk.
- Suk Jin.
- Suk Jin...
- Hey, who ousted you?
- I was betrayed by Kim Jong Kook.
- Really?
Our mission is to find out who
that last person was, right?
- Yeah, we have to find that person.
- Then we need to work together.
- It's most likely that it was Kim Jong Kook.
- It was either Kim Jong Kook or Kang Gary.
- Gary really is...
- He's a random Mr. Capable.
For some reason, he's really strong and
pulls through in the end.
[Could it be random Mr. Capable,
Gary who pulled it off in the end?]
It was Ha Ha and then Kwang Soo, right?
- After Ha Ha, it was... there's Jong Kook.
- Where?
[Just then the likely suspect
Jong Kook makes his appearance!]
- Guys... where are you going?
- Wait...
Jae Suk!
- You traitor.
- Jae Suk, if I was the last person...
If I was the last person, why would I be
going around looking for you guys?
- Be quiet, you traitor.
- Jae Suk!
Jae Suk, if you think I have the keys,
shouldn't you be attacking me?
- What did you say?
- If I had the seven keys...
It's because it's still too dangerous. There
needs to be at least three people for you!
- Jae Suk, come here.
- Why?
Guys, it's not me. Guys!
- Let's just see each other later.
- I'm telling you, it's not me!
- I know it was you!
- It was Gary!
You're lying!
Seriously... what a liar!
[Mr. Capable insisting it wasn't himself...
was he the final man left standing?]
If I'm to oust Kang Gary early on...
then other people are going to be convinced
that I was the one and come after me.
Even if I don't oust Kang Gary...
[Just then!]
You startled me.
This is really urgent.
This is extremely important!
Make sure not to get it taken away!
Hurry up and escape. Hurry!
What are you doing?
Why are you doing this?
[A mob of men dressed in black
are chasing after Jong Kook!]
What are they doing?
What's going on?
[Without even knowing what's going on,
he's getting chased with the case in hand!]
What the heck?
There's nothing even in here!
[An empty case? Just what in the world...]
There's nothing in the case!
I was totally fooled.
Totally fooled.
Just what in the world is going on?
Wait, now that I think about it, earlier...
[Now that he thinks about it, this scene...]
Back in the past... the bundle!
[1938]
[Now that we look back,
the same thing happened to Jae Suk!]
[There was a mob of men chasing after
the bundle back then too...]
What is this bundle?
[Mr. Capable having witnessed
this scene in hiding.]
[Yeah... this is similar to what happened
in the previous life!]
Earlier, there was a mob of guys who
were chasing after Jae Suk with the bundle.
[Past and the present- A similar situation...
What's the connection here?]
[On the other hand.]
[The other suspect, Gary who is
loitering around the hallways.]
- What's this? What are you doing here?
- Hey, Gary.
- I was giving myself a foot massage.
- You were giving yourself a foot massage?
[The two elders getting their
feet massaged.]
- You... it was you, right?
- What?
- It was you, right?
- Back in 1938.
- What about 1938?
- The winner.
- Say something that makes some sense!
- I don't think it was Gary either.
- How could I be the winner?
- Suk Jin, it's not Gary.
- Jong Kook said it was you.
- What are you talking about?
- Kim Jong Kook said it was you.
- Why would you fall for that?
He and I were the last two left...
But his claws are
fully out of his paws right now.
If his claws are out too,
on top of his build...
To be honest, he's just way too scary.
I ran with everything I had
back in the city hall...
but Jong Kook was barely running
when he caught up to me.
And all he did was just barely nudge me
when I fell over like a little deer.
Your story of what happened
is very detailed.
[A very detailed relay of what happened
to earn both their trusts.]
I can see him doing that.
- I don't think he's lying. It's too detailed.
- He's not lying.
This is what Jong Kook said to me
as his lips turned white...
"I'm going to maintain my
character today."
- That mental... wow...
- You have to believe me.
I don't think the three of us will be enough.
We need to get Kwang Soo and Ha Ha too.
- Come on. Let's go.
- We need Kwang Soo at least.
- Yeah, we need him.
- Let's go.
What Gary said at the end about Jong Kook
saying he wants to maintain his character...
[Encounters Giraffe who doesn't know
anything that's going on.]
- We're so glad we ran into you.
- We were looking for you.
- Kwang Soo...
- I'm sure you all know...
- That I'm not the one with the keys.
- No, you don't have them.
[Of course, you don't...]
Kwang Soo, it's Jong Kook.
Kim Jong Kook.
- Jong Kook is the winner.
- I was the other last survivor earlier.
Kim Jong Kook won.
Should we start from the top and
work our way down one by one?
Yeah, that's what we should do.
In order, one by one.
[Is Ace Ji Hyo about to join the group
to thwart Mr. Capable?]
You're asking who ousted me?
- Did Kim Jong Kook oust you?
- Yes.
I remember! I remember
what happened 80 years ago!
- You remember, don't you?
- Kang Gary was standing next to me.
And Kim Jong Kook was there too.
- We were all going back and forth...
- We kept going around in circles.
And then I grabbed Kim Jong Kook
by the collar around his throat.
And then Jong Kook ripped off
my name tag.
Then you don't know for sure if it was Gary
or Jong Kook who survived to the end either?
Right, but think about it carefully.
Who do you think survived?
- It was Kim Jong Kook!
- That's an obvious question.
Also, Jae Suk...
[On the other hand]
[A Tiger in hiding!]
Jong Kook!
Why are you after me?
Jong Kook... are you wearing spandex?
Jong Kook... what is this?
- I'm really sorry.
- Why? What?
- There's just no other way.
- Why me all of a sudden?
You're all going to band together to
oust me anyways, aren't you?
- No, we're not!
- I didn't win in the past life.
- Then who did?
- Someone did. Someone else won.
[He's saying it wasn't him?]
[Everyone's saying that it wasn't them.
Then just who was the real winner?]
When I saw Jong Kook earlier...
I noticed that his hand was wrapped up
in a bandage. I will grab onto that pinky.
I'll bend that pinky backwards.
If you do that...
you could end up dying today.
- First...
- No one can escape, okay?
- Suk Jin, no running way.
- Let's not run away.
Ji Hyo...
- That's not my style.
- Jae Suk...
You're most likely to do that.
- Look at this!
- Look here.
- Look at the giraffes!
- 'Are there five like-minded people?'
- That's us! That's us!
- Over here! Let's join hands!
- 'Are there five like-minded people'?
- That's totally us!
[Five giraffes in the poster!]
- Let's go.
- I suddenly feel very courageous.
- Let's go!
- Let's go.
[Five against one!
Is the heaven on their side?]
Let's just face him straight on.
Let's not back down from him.
- Come here.
- Jae Suk!
I just saw Jong Kook.
Make sure you don't run into him!
- Why?
- He's running around in a spandex shirt.
Seriously?
He said he's going to kill anyone
who crosses his path.
You have to make sure not to
cross his path.
What the heck is this?
Is this a game or what?
[Yoo-ruce Willis is talking
a big game for now...]
It looks as though he just painted black
war paint all over his body.
[100% real! Bloodier atmosphere
than any other time!]
Why are you trying to scare us?
I'm not just trying to scare you.
See for yourself. You'll be shocked.
He's listening to us somewhere right now.
I felt it down to my bones.
He's crouched down like this.
All you can see are his eyes.
- He's listening to us?
- I can just see him hiding somewhere...
I actually really like Jong Kook.
- What did you say?
- Who here doesn't like Jong Kook?
- I really respect him.
- What's with you guys?
[That's right... I'm listening to everything.]
Just who does Kim Jong Kook
think he is?
He's Kim Jong Kook.
Just who does Kim Jong Kook think he is...
[They're coming...]
He's hiding out somewhere.
[Wild Tiger's ambush attack!]
How scary!
[Harrowing hunting scene that
they witnessed for themselves!]
Seriously, Kim Jong Kook!
[Underneath Jae Suk's name tag is
the name, Ji Suk Jin?]
[Just what does that mean?]
- Why does it say Ji Suk Jin?
- I seriously have no idea!
- What is this?
- I don't know!
Why is my name on your back?
- What is this?
- I don't know!
- Let's not overreact.
- It's not me!
- Without a doubt, one of you...
- Don't listen to him! Just get him!
- The seven keys... the keys!
- We have to do it now. Now's our chance!
I'm not the one who has the keys!
- We have to go. We have to get him.
- Come on!
[If they don't get him now,
they may never get Mr. Capable!]
- We can't lose him now!
- Get him!
[Stop in their tracks out of fear
in the midst of chasing after him.]
We all have to go after him together
for this to work.
This is so frustrating.
In my previous life and present life...
Ah... seriously!
- What do you think of what's on your back?
- Why does it say Ji Suk Jin?
Why don't you try to figure it out?
So whenever a name tag is ripped off,
it shows the person that they ousted?
It's not that?
Then what could it be?
Tell me if you're going to tell me.
I'm mad enough as is already!
Seriously... I'm about to lose my mind.
Why do things like this always
happen to me in the final battle?
If you can guess what it means by the
time you arrive in jail, we'll let you live.
Ji Suk Jin?
I don't think this is going to work.
Let's just get going.
You really are insulting me.
- He's way too scary.
- But why is my name on Jae Suk's back?
Wait, I think we need to figure out
what that means first.
If we rip off someone else's name tag,
maybe we'll figure out what it means.
- Jae Suk...
- Suk Jin, who ousted you earlier?
Jae Suk.
No, that's not it. That can't be it.
[Even with all five of their heads together,
they still can't figure it out.]
[Wait...]
You've been reincarnated.
[They were undoubtedly told early
that they've been reincarnated.]
[Could it be connected with
how they've been reincarnated?]
Reincarnated...
The names are in white with
a black name tag background, right?
Hey...
[Now that they think back,
the name tags look awfully familiar...]
[1938]
[The name tag...]
The name is in white against
a black background.
Doesn't it means that Suk Jin has been
reincarnated in Jae Suk's body?
- Then isn't Suk Jin really Jae Suk?
- Jae Suk is me!
Didn't Suk Jin get reincarnated
as Jae Suk?
Ah! Reincarnation!
[That's right! They've been
reincarnated as someone else!]
[1938]
Yoo Jae Suk, you...
[Big-nosed Brother crossing the
stepping bridge out of 1938.]
[Ji Suk Jin... He's been
reincarnated as Yoo Jae Suk.]
[This is the secret behind reincarnation.]
You've been reincarnated.
Jae Suk is me!
[Jae Suk of 2013 is Suk Jin of 1938!]
We've been reincarnated as
someone else!
I'm someone else,
so the real me is someone else!
The person who had the keys 80 years
ago isn't the same person anymore
but it's someone else!
The name of the person who won 80 years
ago is stuck on someone else's back!
That's right! People can
be reincarnated as dogs too!
Then Jong Kook can be any one
of us right now!
[Then who did the suspect Jong Kook
be reincarnated as?]
Then we don't know which one of us
could be Jong Kook right now.
For example...
- Jong Kook is one of us...
- Wait.
Then even in the present,
I'm still the race starter?
[Bingo! Since Jae Suk is Suk Jin's
reincarnation and the first to get ousted.]
[The constant race starter.]
This is really strange.
Seriously though...
Jong Kook won 80 years ago, right?
- Right?
- That's what our belief is right now.
- But that could be wrong too.
What do you mean,
it could not be?
No, that would make no sense.
Someone else is on Kim Jong Kook's back.
It could be any one of you.
Kim Jong Kook is amongst us right now.
What's happening now...
is somehow connected to 80 years ago.
Then we've all been reincarnated right now?
This isn't just a coincidence.
It's all connected somehow.
There's something else other than the
past and the present being connected somehow.
[They must find out who the winner from
80 years ago has been reincarnated as!]
- We have to find the treasure chest anyways.
- You're right.
Okay. Let's look around.
[Tiger in shock himself from the sudden
attack that he sprang.]
But...
When I ripped off Jae Suk's name tag
earlier, it said Ji Suk Jin underneath it.
But crazy enough...
the incident from the previous life where
Jae Suk was given the bundle happened to me.
In my opinion, on my back...
Yoo Jae Suk's name is stuck on it.
[If that's the case...]
Let's search around.
- Chul Soo!
- Oh my gosh.
- I'm sorry.
- What's this? What's going on?
- I know this person.
- Who did this happen to?
- Why did that person hit me?
- Who had this happen in their previous life?
- Who did this happen to?
- This happened in the previous life, right?
- Who was it?
- Who did this happen to?
[The person who was battered by strangers
just to have them apologize in the past?]
- I'm sorry.
- Oh my goodness!
- Who did this happen to in the past?
- Which one had this happen to them?
[The person who was unjustly beaten
up like this in the past life...]
[1938]
Chul Soo, it's great to see you!
I'm sorry.
Hyun Kook!
Cha Dol!
[The person who was beaten up all day...]
Who's the one that had this
happen to them in their past life?
Who had this happen to them?
Did this happen to you in your past life?
- No.
- It didn't happen to you?
[Giraffe from the past life...
has been reincarnated as Impala.]
[Isn't anything going to happen?]
[Huh? Who are all these people?]
What are you doing?
[After being dragged
into middle of the room...]
[Huh?]
[Wait! This is... this is...]
Accept him!
[A public proposal that Ji Hyo
received in her previous life?]
[No way!]
Will you please accept my love?
[This situation somehow...]
Kiss him!
- Kiss him!
- Don't do this!
Don't do this!
[A big fat kiss twice on his head!]
I get it now...
I get it now.
I'm Song Ji Hyo.
[That woman of 1938...]
[Has been reincarnated as me.]
[Mr. Capable going into hiding for now
in fear of becoming everyone's target.]
There's Jong Kook.
- Let's talk. Let's just talk.
- Can you give us your word?
[Mr. Capable proposing to work things
out by calmly talking things through.]
[There's no real need to attack Jong Kook
even if he was the winner in 1938 anymore.]
Since all of you think that I was the
winner, let's go find me first.
[Proposing that they go to find who
the past Jong Kook has been reincarnated as.]
- Let's go find him.
- Let's go find Kim Jong Kook first.
Let's go find him and see if
that person was the winner or not.
Me from the previous life... even though
I haven't experienced anything yet
I did have a certain situation
happen to me.
But I did see Jong Kook being
pelted with balls.
- You got pelted by balls?
- Yes.
[Jong Kook from 1938 got hit
by flying balls!]
[1938]
What is everyone doing?
[As Jong Kook walks on by...]
[They suddenly started
throwing their balls at him!]
What are you guys doing?
What's wrong with you guys?
Everyone has something
happening to them.
[They didn't know the meaning of those
events back when they were happening...]
- Then then one getting hit by balls...
- That's me.
- Getting hit by balls is me.
- I saw him getting hit by balls.
[If they see anyone being beaten by balls,
that person was Kim Jong Kook in past life!]
This is...
Wait...
Wait...wait!
What's wrong with you guys?
Why are you doing this?
What are you doing?
Why are you doing this to me?
[Giraffe being pelted by
countless flying balls.]
In the previous life, this was...
[You've figured out why
you're getting pelted, right?]
My head really hurts!
[Remembers seeing a person getting hit by
flying balls in the past life back in 1938.]
Those people that were playing
catch with those balls...
Who were they throwing the balls at?
I'm sorry. Do any of you remember
anything about the past life?
Anyone with the memory of
the past life?
Wait! Just a minute!
[Instead of responding with words,
they respond by throwing balls.]
This isn't what's important right now!
[What difference does it make if
he was a tiger in his past life...]
Who was it?
[The Tiger that shouted out at the world...]
[Has become a Giraffe that gets
beaten up by flying balls.]
[On the other hand...]
[Who was I in the previous life?]
Then someone else...
Oh my... oh my!
I'm sorry!
[Wait? This scene is...]
Wait, wait, wait...
[Familiar music sheets...]
[A familiar face?]
I've seen you before.
By any chance... in the past life...
- You're so beautiful.
- Oh my goodness.
- Then goodbye.
- No, you're more beautiful than I.
[It's a phrase that could give hint to
who she was in her past life...]
Carrying those sheet music around...
[The woman dropping her sheet music
after bumping into someone...]
[Who did it happen to in the past life?]
[Who do you think it was?]
[That's correct! It was farmer Gary!]
- Was it a woman with sheet music?
- You startled me.
- That's right.
- Tell me honestly.
- About what?
Tell me honestly since you and I
worked together in our past life.
I know. But why don't you take your hands
off of me and we'll talk? You're scaring me.
Okay then. Let's stand like this.
- Gary...
- Yeah?
If you were the winner...
If you were by any chance the winner in the
past life, you have to protect me right now.
- Are you Kang Gary?
- Yeah.
- Do you know who I am?
- Who are you?
I wonder if this is fate
playing a joke on us?
He gave me a bouquet of flowers.
I thought he asked for a hug in the past,
but this time, he asked for a kiss...
So I ended up getting kissed by a man.
- You got kissed?
- Yeah.
- You got a love confession?
- That's right.
I feel a little confused right now.
Since we're the Monday Couple,
I'm supposed to like me in this situation.
[Monday couple who's souls have been
switched during the reincarnation.]
Anyways... the woman with the sheet
music came up to you?
- Yeah.
- Really?
Gary...
Tell me honestly.
After bumping into her...
I lied on my way down here to see you
because I thought it was you.
- Were you the winner in the past life?
- No, I wasn't.
The thing that you need to think
carefully about right now...
is if by any chance,
my name tag gets ripped off...
- If my keys were to end up going to...
- Yeah, the keys will get handed over.
Will you be okay if that person
ends up being Jong Kook?
No, even if you were to get ousted,
the keys won't get forfeited.
Jong Kook has all the keys already!
[Gary insisting to the end that the
winner from the past was Jong Kook.]
Hey, what did you have
happen to you?
- I kept being forced to drink water.
- Who did that?
I approached a group of people and
they kept forcing me to drink water.
- Wait a minute then...
- What did you have happen to you?
- I received a bouquet of flowers.
- That means you're Ji Hyo!
Ji Hyo received a bouquet of flowers
in past life, right?
Then what did Jong Kook have
to go through?
Balls... Jong Kook got pelted by balls.
- But...
- I can tell by Kwang Soo's expression!
- Look at Kwang Soo's expression.
- Whatever the case...
No matter the case, who we've been
reincarnated as isn't what's important.
[This man who used to be Kim Jong Kook
in the past life...]
- No...
- You got hit by balls, didn't you?
You got hit by balls, didn't you?
- No... it wasn't that.
- You...
[Impossible to control
his own facial expressions.]
- I did see people throwing around the balls.
- Yeah, okay?
Just tell me the truth.
I know you got hit by the balls.
- Don't try to fool me like this.
- Look at him.
[Always breaks into laughter
whenever he tries to lie.]
You'll know for yourself if we
went there.
If we were to go and you see who they
were throwing the balls at
you'd know who Jong Kook is.
Then let's just go and see.
Since I'm not sure of the situation yet,
let's go where the balls are being thrown.
Then who had to drink the water?
Who drank the water in the past?
The reason for that being Kwang Soo,
in the past life...
- I saw Kim Jong Kook...
- Look at you smiling again.
It's not because of that. I just
had something funny happen to me.
- Why don't we just go and see first?
- Okay, let's go.
- On the seventh floor...
- You lead the way.
[The reincarnated fool Giraffe...
what will become of his fate?]
[Arrives at the fateful basketball court!]
I'll go in first then.
[As suspected, nothing happens.]
Why don't you go in, Ji Hyo?
[Kwang Soo's turn to enter the court.]
Which way shall I go?
Where?
[A slew of balls being thrown at him
like a meteor shower.]
[That's why you should've just
told the truth earlier...]
- Come here, come here.
- What I did was wrong.
Hey, you need to be careful. You're
going to get chased right away now.
You're now Jong Kook's immediate target.
Just trust me.
- Let's work well together, the three of us.
- Seriously.
Ji Hyo! Hurry up and rip it off!
[Gary and Ji Hyo attack Kwang Soo!]
[Ace Ji Hyo jumps in the fray!]
[Gary succeeds in eliminating Kwang Soo!]
Kim Jong Kook...
How could you do this to me?
[If Jong Kook was the winner in the past,
then the keys are now in Gary's possession.]
- Here.
- What the heck?
[But where are the keys,
and why is he being rushed off to jail?]
[Could it be?]
- Tell me honestly.
- Tell you what?
Why isn't there anything?
Shouldn't there be keys after this?
[Then does it mean that the winner wasn't
Jong Kook in the past, but it was...]
In my opinion, I think the writers
are just not giving us the keys right now.
- Let's just go downstairs and talk.
- Are you joking?
You think this is
my first time on Running Man?
[Something is suspicious about Gary!]
Hurry up and tell me!
[Gary surprise attacks Ji Hyo!]
[The ultimate face-off
between the Monday Couple!]
[Gary succeeds in eliminating Ji Hyo!]
- Ji Hyo, I'm sorry.
- Gary!
[Gary - Mayor's office.]
[That's right, it was me...]
[1938]
[Mr. Capable vs. Gary as the
final two survivors!]
Please don't be like this.
Wait... wait.
[Two people who know each
other so well.]
[They both grabbed onto each other's
name tag simultaneously!]
[Oh my goodness!]
[Gary eliminates Mr. Capable!]
I won! I'm the final winner!
[Kang Gary was the ultimate winner
in 1938!]
[The seven keys needed to open the
treasure chest came into his hands!]
[After his victory, Kang Gary unlocks
the locks one by one.]
What kind of gold will it be that
sets my heart beating?
This isn't it...
[Opens up all seven of the locks.]
Now... I'll get to order around
my own servants...
And I'll buy myself ten cows.
And get myself a pretty little wife.
Then I'll build myself a nice
home in Gangnam.
Welcome to my world.
[An empty chest?]
[The chest that he went through the trouble
to open was a deploy to thwart off thieves!]
Kim Jong Kook... after catching that lion,
that tiger...
and I got my hands on the seven keys,
but what the heck is this?
Why?
What is this?
[2013]
[The keys that disappeared from the
Mayor's office in 1938...
[Is now in the Mayor's office in 2013?]
What are you going to do about all the hair
you yanked out along with the name tag?
I'm really sorry. But...
- I really wanted to work together too...
- You think you can go up against him?
I can't trust you either.
- Ji Hyo, I'm sorry. I'll...
- You fool!
I'll give you 2% of my gold.
Give me 10%.
- Okay.
- Since I'm going to have a bit.
[Promises to give her 10% of his prize
considering their partnership 80 years ago.]
[Ji Hyo - Out!]
[Gary rushes off to the Mayor's office
where the keys have been preserved.]
Let's go.
[Huh? What is Grandmother
Dong Wan doing there?]
What are you doing here, Dong Wan?
- Have you come for this?
- Yes.
Here are the keys.
[The seven keys are once again
in Gary's hands...]
These are the keys that I had
80 years ago.
Since you look like a nice man...
I'll tell you a secret.
Okay.
Just a single person out of all of you...
has been reincarnated in the same
image as their previous life.
[There's someone who's been reincarnated
in the same image as their previous life?]
[Wait...]
Two of the same treasure chests were
produced originally to thwart off thieves.
But the whereabouts of one of
the chests are still unknown.
Then the chest I opened in my previous
life was a decoy?
Then it means I have to go find
the real treasure chest now?
[The treasure chest he opened
in 1938 was a fake...]
[Then the person who's been reincarnated
in their original form must know the location.]
- Is it just one person?
- One person.
- Then can you tell me who that is?
- That's a secret.
Why, Grandmother?
Then how important is the information
that one person knows?
That's as far as I can tell you.
Go find that person. Then
you'll get what it is that you're after.
- Good luck.
- Yes.
[Just one person who's been
reincarnated in their original image...]
[The whereabouts of the real
treasure chest is known by him alone!]
What? What is it?
[A mob dance flash?]
[But.. that's...]
[1938]
This is like a musical.
[The song that he danced to in 1938...]
[And in 2013, it's 'Gangnam Style'.]
This is a signal as to who I am.
No... I can't stay here.
[On the other hand,
the prisoners of the present are...]
[Bored...]
Let's play a round of paper-rock-scissors,
and draw a mole on the loser's nose.
[Thinking up of games to pass the time
out of boredom.]
- Seriously?
- Just a single round.
Paper-rock-scissors!
Another round?
I'll draw it small.
I can see the black with my own eyes.
I can see the black with my own eyes!
I can see it right here.
I was looking down here
but my vision all of a sudden got black!
- That much is called for...
- Jae Suk.
I drew it small enough that you can't see
with your eyes, and it's cute.
[Please make sure to check their faces
later to see how it all turns out.]
[Gary starting to thoroughly check
around for the real treasure chest.]
[The person who's been reincarnated in
their own image from the previous life...]
[That person definitely knows something!]
I can't believe a place like this exists
underneath the city hall.
[Gary heading down to the civil agency
in the basement of city hall.]
[Who could it be...]
[Who's been reincarnated
in their original image?]
Ji Hyo!
[The four remaining survivors who have
all finally converged at the same place.]
Seriously...
I don't know what I should do here.
- Let's just end it. It's time.
- Yeah, Dong Hoon.
[Gary is suspicious of Ha Ha who
hasn't been seen around too much today.]
[An unforeseen circumstance!
Even Mr. Capable is on the move!]
- Why are you moving?
- So I can protect you.
[All the four remaining survivors
are now out for themselves!]
[A breaking point!]
- I don't know who to go for!
- Trust me! Just trust me!
[Desperate state of anxiety
not knowing who to trust!]
Just trust me!
- You sure are quick!
- Look at how good you are in your spandex.
Your shirt is really...
[Now that we take a closer look...
it's these two again!]
[The fateful destiny...
that travels through time!]
[Mr. Capable eliminates Gary!]
- You're really quick.
- What is that? You had something?
[Rule: The seven keys he had must
be handed over to Jong Kook.]
- Then who won the last round?
- I told you, it was Kang Gary!
Then you really won?
When I was given the keys earlier...
[He reveals the secret Grandmother Dong Wan
told him earlier in the Mayor's office.]
- That Grandmother told me a secret.
- What did he say?
There's one person amongst you who's been
reincarnated in their original image.
It's him then.
- It's him.
- Ah...
This is the end of what I
have to tell you.
[Ha Ha is awfully suspicious!
What secret is he harboring?]
- We have to catch him!
- I think he knows something!
[Corners him into a dead end!]
That grandmother is such a jokester!
[You know... Grandmother Dong Wan?]
[Just what is the secret Ha Ha has?]
[1938]
[Ha Ha back in 1938 as he arrives
at the city hall on a secret mission.]
Young man over there...
come here for a moment.
[Grandmother Dong Wan calling
Ha Ha over?]
Hello, Grandmother.
Best of luck in the new year,
and prosperous health to you.
- You... came to find the treasure, right?
- Yes!
Gold... I came to find the gold bars.
It's in a treasure chest!
- Want me to tell you how to get it?
- Yes!
The truth is...
there are two treasure chests.
To thwart off any possible thieves,
they made two exact same chests.
The real chest between the two
that you'll see in the Mayor's office...
- Is the one on the right.
- The one on the right?
[He wasn't late getting to the office,
but he was in fact the first to arrive...]
The gold...
This is so heavy!
Quickly... I need to hide this somewhere!
Where should I hide this thing?
Why are you telling me this?
You want me to do something for you?
I'm telling you this since you're
the first one to arrive.
I'm the first one here?
Have you ever heard of the term,
reincarnation?
Reincarnation?
In your next life... you will be the only one
who'll be reincarnated in your own image.
- The only one?
- Just as you are now.
You'll be reincarnated with the same
memories and the same image as now.
[Therefore, only the reincarnated Ha Ha will
know the location of the hidden chest!]
Don't tell anyone about this.
[Ha Ha is the only one who knows
where the treasure chest is hidden!]
[If he can only get the keys in his hands,
everything will go as he planned!]
- You know something!
- So it wasn't a lie.
I bet if we oust him, we can find out
where the treasure chest is hidden.
I wonder...
why that grandmother did this to me?
[If Suk Jin and Jong Kook wants to find
the treasure chest, they must oust Ha Ha!]
We should've just ousted you
no matter what.
[Ha Ha is in a situation where
he just can't give up easily!]
Come on... come get me!
[Planning on sticking it out
through the attack.]
- This is good.
- Grab him by the wrist.
Let go! Let go of me!
I'm so close!
Close to what?
The victory is right in front of my eyes!
I know where it is... it's so close!
- You saw, didn't you?
- You're something else!
I'll hold onto him, and you rip it off.
[It seems as though Suk Jin has made up
his mind to work together with Jong Kook.]
- Suk Jin, you have to rip it off!
- Okay!
Hurry up and rip it off!
Why aren't you ripping it off?
Hurry up!
[Suk Jin attacks Jong Kook!]
[Coalition, my butt! There's no
friendship on the road to victory!]
[Tiger vs. Impala!]
[Suk Jin eliminates Mr. Capable!]
[2013 topic of conversation:
Big-nosed Brother ousts Mr. Capable!]
No one make a move!
2013 is my year!
Suk Jin! You're awesome!
[Ah... his broken dreams of winning...]
[The seven keys are now in
Suk Jin's hands.]
[The man with the keys vs. the
man who hid away the treasure chest.]
You really are awesome today.
- I'm getting greedy now.
- Good!
I'm feeling greedy too.
I'm tired. People who fight like us
get tired out too easily.
- That hurts!
- Sorry.
[They both have their hands
on the name tag!]
[They both...
have the name tag in their hands!]
I ripped it off first...
I got it first.
I was first!
Ha Dong Hoon is the victor!
With all my strength,
I beat Ji Suk Jin!
The victory is mine!
This is unbelievable!
[Haroro with the seven keys
finally in his hands.]
Since I'm the only one who knows
where it's hidden...
[The location of where he hid away
the treasure chest 80 years ago!]
[The same place in 1938...]
[In a side hallway of city hall...]
[In the same location in the
city hall of 2013!]
This is unbelievable!
Want me to help you?
I thought I almost had it...
But what does it say on your back
anyways? Here it is!
The place where the past
meets the present.
So the location of the treasure chest
was on your back?
[If Ha Ha had been eliminated,
hint to the location could've been earned.]
- This is where I hid it.
- You hid it?
- I hid it away.
- You knew where the treasure was?
I hid it here 80 years ago.
I haven't been able to sleep for 80 years.
I'm a total insomniac.
I think for the first time in 80 years,
I'm going to be able to sleep tonight.
Do you know who you have to thank
for being the winner today?
- It's thanks to you.
- It's thanks to me, right?
Yes, even though it's thanks to you,
I did great today.
[Even though the gold prize
hasn't been brought back yet...]
[Since this is gold from 1938,
Ha Ha wins the gold!]
This location speaks of where I hid away
the gold 80 years ago.
But the gold has been moved over to
the new building just as it was.
[The gold that he hid away hasn't been
touched in its basement location since.]
Wow, I can't believe...
In the third strong man race we've had,
Ha Ha is the victor!
[The ultimate powerhouse, Ha Ha!]
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Prepare yourselves, Running Man!]
[The ultimate fighter,
Chung Sung Hoon has arrived!]
[An utter chaos in
the midst of all the terror.]
[The winner of national boxing match
try-out, Lee Si Young!]
[Korea's representative fighters
have come to hunt on Running Man!]
[Fighter Sung Hoon vs.
Mr. Capable Jong Kook.]
[A face-off based on strength
of a different level!]
[Who will be the king of strength?]
[Next week on Running Man,
The Bounty Hunters.]