[Running Man:
That Winter, That Typhoon Blows]
[Yoo Jae Suk and Kim Jong Kook]
[Ji Suk Jin and Lee Kwang Soo]
[Ha Ha and Gary]
[Song Ji Hyo]
[Lee Yeon Hee]
[Go Ara]
[A storm-like reversal.]
[There's a real brother and sister
amongst the group?]
[Conspiracy, and truth coming to light.]
[Running Man:
That Winter, That Typhoon Blows]
[That Winter, that typhoon blows]
Subtitles by DramaFever
Let's start filming.
[Prologue of Running Man mini-series,
That Winter, That Typhoon Blows.]
My name is Oh Soo.
[This man is the real Oh Soo.]
[What is Kwang Soo thinking
to pretend he's Oh Soo?]
When I was little...
I was left abandoned in
front of an orphanage.
At that orphanage...
[Your height is the only similarity
you have to the real Oh Soo.]
[You're still not finished?]
My sister will get to see me soon.
[Now, who are you supposed to be?]
[Are you... Ha Soo?]
Mister, why don't you just go back in?
Thank you.
(Who is he talking to?)
[My name is none other than...]
[Joker?]
My name is In Song.
Where did my Hye Gyo go?
There's something I want to
do for Hye Gyo.
[A really short brother that
doesn't exist in the original show.]
Hye Gyo!
- Mister...
- Why are you calling me Mister?
- I can't find Hye Gyo.
- I'm Oh Soo.
- What?
- What's with the tears?
[Were you peeling some onions
before you came here?]
I'm always so emotional.
You look really dirty and grubby.
[Ta da!]
[The guy in the long red coat
slowly walking towards them.]
Go wait outside.
- Me? You're asking me to leave?
- Go bring the car around.
Why do I need to bring the car around?
- Just go!
- I'm Oh Soo!
What are you doing here after I've
generously bought you your coat?
- Are you talking to me?
- I'm talking to the both of you.
[Just because they have long coats on,
they're all pretending to be Oh Soo?]
- You're going to go crazy?
- What do you have under that shirt?
Are you wearing a t-shirt underneath
that shirt?
You don't know this style?
- Seriously...
- Don't you know this?
- You're really tacky, aren't you?
- People like him still exist?
You're supposed to wear a shirt underneath.
What is this you've got going on?
[You're caught too.]
- It's my scarf.
- What did you say?
It's my scarf.
[Whenever the Giraffe is around,
the teasing automatically starts.]
Are you dumb or something?
Who is that?
Sparta...
Is that someone's bodyguard?
[Judging by the way he looks,
he seems like the head bodyguard...]
What is this?
How is that any way to speak to me?
- What?
- What is he saying?
- Jong Kook... what kind of acting is that?
- What's wrong with it? That was cool.
- How is that cool?
I'm Oh Soo.
I'm Kwang Soo.
What is this?
- You really shouldn't make it so easy.
- You're really...
You really shouldn't make it
so easy for me like that.
You always beat me to it.
I really wanted to do that.
- It's all about the timing!
- It's seriously so upsetting!
You have to be a little quicker on your toes.
You always have to be on your toes.
The one who stays on his toes
can pull off more pranks.
'The one who stays on his toes
can pull off more pranks.' - Jae Suk
[Pulling off pranks first thing
in the morning.]
He's my butler.
[Butler Big-nose?]
Butler, why did you follow me here?
Why isn't there any space around here
for me to land my plane?
I'm telling you this right now,
but Suk Jin's really awful at improv.
Even though he comes
from a comedic background...
in all the years I've known him...
when it comes to improv and
dialect speech, he's absolutely hopeless.
Who is that walking in?
- What is this?
- We don't want to buy anything.
Welcome to my shop.
Gary... you're driving me insane.
I'm really about to lose my mind.
Why are we all dressed like this today?
Today, all of you are the most successful
CEO's in the Republic of Korea.
[Most successful CEO's of Korea?]
Of a large corporation?
Why don't you start by ordering
yourselves a drink?
- Really?
- I'll take a caramel macchiato.
I'll take your order whenever
you're ready.
Please tell me clearly.
What's this?
Kiwi? I'll take the kiwi juice.
- Kiwi juice.
- Coke.
- Coke?
- I want a carbonated beverage.
- A carbonated beverage?
- I'll take a sparkling water.
- Okay.
- Iced tea for me.
I'll take an iced tea as well.
- Iced tea?
- Yes, iced tea.
Yes, I got it.
- But Song Ji Hyo isn't here.
- I'm sure she'll turn up sometime.
- If Ji Hyo's not here today...
- Then we're going to have female guests?
- Since she's not there today...
- You think Song Hye Gyo will be here?
[Full of anticipation]
- Since Sa Yeon was here two weeks ago...
- That's right!
[That's right!
There's no way it could be the Tuna again!]
- You think it could be Bong Sun?
- Ah, there's Bong Sun...
- Bong Sun...
- Or what if it's Kim Sook?
[Could it be either Bong Sun
or Kim Sook?]
[Just which female guests will
make their appearance today?]
This seat next to me was empty earlier.
Don't you think he hit me a little
too hard just now?
When did I ever hit you that hard?
If you're going to switch your seats,
this is your last chance.
In that case, I'll drink the kiwi juice.
- Okay then, go ahead.
- I'm just kidding.
I'll drink the kiwi juice.
[Is Butler Big-nose switching
to the kiwi juice?]
[All the CEO's acting very indecisive
towards the end.]
In that case, I want the kiwi juice too.
[Pondering]
10 seconds.
We've got 10 seconds left to decide.
[The final 10 seconds.]
Five, four, three, two, one...
- Kiwi juice.
- I want the cola!
- One!
- I want the kiwi juice.
[Ultimately going for the kiwi juice...]
I want the cola!
[Fickle hearts of the CEO's.]
- I'm glad I switched.
- You all changed?
[Jae Suk's final decision is
the iced tea.]
[Passing on the ordering information
to the ladies lying in wait.]
Cola, kiwi juice, carbonated beverage,
and iced tea.
Yes, you just need to  choose
one of those.
[Just which one will they choose?]
One iced tea to table one, please.
- She's coming... someone's coming!
- Someone's coming... someone's coming!
- Someone's coming!
- Who is it?
- Whoever it is, I can tell she's pretty!
- She's pretty?
- From what I can see, she's pretty!
[Who's the beautiful young lady
bringing out the iced tea?]
- She's so beautiful!
- Wow!
[A member of their family, Blank Ji.]
[Disappointed?]
- Song Ji Hyo!
- So pretty! Song Ji Hyo!
Song Ji Hyo!
Why is it this table?
Jae Suk, what is it?
What's wrong with you?
- Jae Suk, you look like you're about to cry.
- But you've always favored Ji Hyo.
- When you were with Sa Yeon...
- I normally favor Ji Hyo.
But today was my chance.
With all the beautiful female guests...
- Are there beautiful guests in the back?
- They are unbelievable.
- See? She said they're unbelievable!
- Really? They're that pretty?
- Yay!
- Yeah!
[CEO Yoo and Candy girl Blank Ji:
First couple of the day.]
Candy girl?
How is Ji Hyo a candy girl?
CEO?
- CEO?
- Ji Hyo, I'm sorry to tell you this...
What kind of a CEO goes around
wearing a bright red coat like this?
How seriously tacky!
- What do you mean, tacky?
- Look at your bright red coat!
And are you wearing black dress pants?
- I'm wearing a t-shirt underneath too.
- Seriously!
[An already entertaining Jae-Blank couple.]
- Next drink, please.
- Do we need to close our eyes?
- We've got ways to go yet.
- Let's close our eyes.
[Who is the second candy girl?]
- What is it?
- Who is it?
- What's the drink?
This doesn't count!
- What's up?
- This can't count!
[The second candy girl is...]
[The famous natural beauty, Go Ara.]
- She really is unbelievable!
- Who is it?
- I'm so nervous!
Quiet!
[Which beverage did she choose?]
Who ordered the sparkling water?
[Hiding away by the pillar?]
- Weren't you two a team before too?
- Excuse me?
- You two were a team before too.
- Yes.
Why are you looking away from her?
Could this be fate?
I'm...
- going to order the sparkling water.
- Sparkling water.
[It's not fate, but random.
Ara chooses the sparkling water.]
Thank you.
- Ara's gotten even prettier.
- I originally had the sparkling water too.
You've changed too, Jong Kook.
- What are you doing?
- You've changed a lot too.
What do I do?
I feel like I'm going to lose it.
- You said you were tired this morning.
- Yes, well...
- You said your lips were all chapped.
- I'm okay now.
Your heart feels like it's going to
pound right out of your chest, right?
- Your heart is about to burst.
- I'm going to put the sunglasses on for now.
[Suddenly putting on his sunglasses?]
The thing I'm really upset about...
is the fact that Ara has this
satisfied look on her face.
- I'm really jealous.
- Did you really pick sparkling water?
Also, I'm telling you this now...
- It's okay to have high hopes.
- What?
- It's okay to have hopes for the next guest.
- Who's the next guest?
[The last guest that Blank Ji
is reassuring everyone about.]
The next guest, please come on out.
- Who could it be?
- Who is it?
[The next candy girl is...]
- There she is!
- She's here?
- Is she really out?
Is she here?
I'm going to stand and take a look.
- Jong Kook!
- No, I'm just going to take a look.
- Is she pretty?
- How is she? Is she pretty?
- You may open your eyes.
- She really is unbelievable.
- Who is it?
- Wow, she's really skinny!
Is it who I think it is?
[Your candy girl is here...]
[Goddess of purity, Lee Yeon Hee.]
[She is the last candy girl of the day!]
- What did you order?
- Kiwi!
- Cola.
- Kiwi juice!
I ordered the cola earlier.
- How can she be so pretty?
- She's unbelievable.
[The drink Yeon Hee has is...]
[Kiwi... kiwi!]
[Please let it be cola...]
Why are you stalling?
Who ordered the cola?
[CEO Gae is chosen!]
[A riotous restaurant scene]
I was the one who originally
ordered cola!
Why are you drinking all that
by yourself?
I'm... going to go with cola.
[Goddess of purity, Yeon Hee chooses cola.]
I think I know who ordered the cola.
[The customer who ordered the cola is,
CEO Gae.]
- What?
- You're a celebrity too.
[A starstruck celebrity at
having seen another celebrity.]
Just keep it down.
- No, I can feel my face getting hot.
- Look at her in the face!
What are you doing?
Your mission for the day that you'll be
doing with your beautiful partner is...
It's the Running Man mini-series trilogy.
[Today's mission:
Running Man three part mini-series.]
By the end of the mini-series...
if you find the person you're destined
to be with, you'll be the final winner.
[Find the person of your destiny!]
- What does that mean?
- What do you mean by that?
Could she not be the woman
I'm destined to be with then?
[You will soon find that out
for yourself.]
You're all going to have to
start playing various games...
- There are three members to your team?
- Yes.
You have to choose a couple
out of the three of you.
[One out of the three is
destined to be alone?]
Have you decided on your couple?
- Yes.
- We've decided.
Hey... we should at least flip for it.
Pil-Chok-Cross!
[Lashing out in anger?]
- We've already made our decision.
- We should at least flip for it!
[Ultimately deciding on playing
the 'Lovers point' game to decide.]
I...
I, Ji Suk Jin...
- I want to be coupled with you.
- There you go.
[Ro-Ro's choice is?]
Get lost!
- Ha Ha, it's your turn.
- My turn.
[Short CEO Ro-Ro's turn.]
I...
I like you.
Be my partner!
Get that filthy hand away from me.
[Their catastrophic relationship...]
- Kwang Soo, this is entertaining!
- This is really entertaining!
[What will be the Giraffe's decision?]
[Peculiar sense of nervousness?]
Okay.
Why don't you each say
something first?
To who?
Good.
[Humiliating sight]
[A truly eclectic Traitors club.]
- What?
- He says, what...
No!
- No?
- That's right.
In that case, get lost.
[Ro-Ro and Giraffe couple is born!]
I can't believe I lost to him.
[The couples have been
decided for now...]
[But what cruel fate awaits them?]
[Couple matching is over!
To the second floor for the drama shoot.]
I'm holding your hand right now only because
I was told I had to hold your hand.
- There's no need to even tell me that.
- Hurry up and move it.
Oh my, this is a little embarrassing.
Candy girl, my candy girl, this way.
You're so tall that I can't even
hold your hand very easily.
[And...]
[Bringing up the rear is
the Traitor Club.]
[Giraffe, the specialist of betrayals.]
[Specialist of scheming, Ro-Ro.]
[The weakest link, Big-nose.]
What about me?
[A provocative pose?]
[That Winter, That Typhoon Blows:
Scene one's script handed out.]
You should put some lotion
on your hands, Ji Hyo.
I'm sorry, but she's trying to read.
- Oh yeah?
- My candy girl is trying to read.
And I'm talking to my candy girl.
- You're blocking my candy girl's view.
- Yes, I apologize.
Running Man mini-series, scene one.
[Running Man miniseries,
That Winter, That Typhoon Blows- Scene one.]
[The 'R' Group CEO having fallen in love at
first sight for the female lead in a cafe.]
He participates in a game of
'The couple flower is blooming'
with the woman who's always bright and
cheery despite her poor background.
Just which of the couples' love will have the
power to make the flower bloom in full?
The man will carry the woman either
in their arms or on their backs...
and the couple that remains to the
very end will be the winner of the game.
Out of seething anger for not
having become a part of a couple...
you've taken all the female leads'
shoes away from them.
So the gentlemanly CEO's will have to play
the game while carrying their ladies.
For the male couple as well...
[Who's the candy girl on this team?]
[Who's the candy girl?]
- I'm the candy girl.
- Why are you like this with me lately?
- Kwang Soo's the candy girl.
- We'll take care of our own team.
Since I chose you,
I'll make the decision here.
Okay, I'll protect you.
- I'll be the candy girl.
- Good.
- You can let go of her hand now.
- I can?
You knew what you were doing.
- They said you can let go of my hand now.
- Really?
Mr. CEO...
Oh my!
I'm candy.
- You look so pretty!
- Unbelievable.
You look like some foreign rock star.
[Older sister Blank Ji fixing
his hairstyle for him.]
Excuse me...
Your CEO is me.
Who are you?
What is this?
- Nice!
- Why was I doing that?
- Ji Hyo, why are you looking out for him?
- I need to get my head on straight!
- Why did you hit him?
- What did you say?
[One noisy filming set.]
- What?
- You stay back, candy girl.
- I'm sorry, but you're scaring my candy girl.
Only the couple that remains alive to the end
without being caught by the seeker wins.
I think that man may have had
too much to drink last night.
[Did you have too much to drink last night?]
[Awkward acting skills.]
My candy girl and I have come
to an agreement.
We're going to split the prize right down
the middle after we win the race
and that's it!
- That's it!
- We're going to have a nice clean break.
- A clean break!
- Why?
You guys are a weird couple.
She's so light.
I can't even tell she's on my back.
She's light as a feather!
- Are you ready?
- Yes!
[Fascinating...
A penguin with a giraffe on its back.]
[Scene One: Restaurant.
That Winter, That Typhoon Blows.]
- Are you ready?
- Yes!
[Running Man mini-series,
That Winter, That Typhoon Blows.]
[Scene one]
The rose of Sharon is blooming!
I'm giving you one warning.
[Ro-Ro and the Giraffe shamelessly
denying their move.]
Come on, let's get going.
[What?]
I'm sorry.
I've just made a mistake.
No, I didn't mean it!
[The ultimate power of the seeker
with the fate of the couples in his hands.]
It's my choice!
I'm sorry, I'm sorry!
Take your time.
The rose of Sharon is blooming!
[Totally caught during the move.]
I've got you.
Out... you're out.
[Yoo-Blank couple, totally caught.]
You're being very cocky right now.
The rose of Sharon is blooming!
He's caught... he's totally caught.
[Why did you and I have to meet...]
- I'm not moving!
- Hurry it up!
Hurry!
Hurry up and just end it!
I need to touch up my hair a bit first.
I'm sorry.
I was wrong!
[The tall candy who's as long
as the long coats they're wearing.]
Suk Jin, I was wrong!
[The partners equally cruel to
one another.]
The rose of Sharon is blooming!
[Did he slip?]
[Desperately holding on.]
Please do it slowly just once.
The rose of Sharon is blooming!
[Huh?]
[Who's moving?]
[Candy girl's real identity revealed.]
Out.
[Giraffe and Ro-Ro ousted.]
- I'm going to be very quick.
- Okay.
[Letting go of the seeker's hand
without him knowing...]
[and if they escape without getting caught,
the couple can be resurrected.]
The rose of Sharon is blooming!
[Catch them!]
[Giraffe and Ro-Ro in danger!]
Out.
[As predicted, the odd couple is
the first to get eliminated.]
[It's the long-legged CEO Kwang's
turn to be the seeker.]
The rose of Sharon is blooming!
- You can't move right now, right?
- Correct.
The rose of Sharon is blooming!
[All the couples moving very slowly.]
[Huh?]
[No way...]
You were very harsh
with your words earlier...
[The tiger CEO is being transformed
into a lion CEO.]
I feel like I'm seeing you back
in your Turbo days.
Thanks.
[His younger days?]
The rose of Sharon is blooming!
Let me fix you up a little bit.
[Showing his naked eyes.]
The rose of Sharon is blooming!
If you keep an expression like that on
your face, you're going to get eliminated.
[Covering his eyes back up
with the glasses.]
The rose of Sharon is blooming!
[Lion eyeing his prey?]
What are you doing?
[Faking?]
[Yoo-Blank couple, out!]
[Thus, only the final two couples
are left remaining.]
[The final seeker is... Ro-Ro.]
I'm totally...
You know that I'm cutthroat, right?
[You want to see my moves?]
It only took him four hops!
[See that?]
[Above their expectations?]
[Which couple of the two will survive?]
Here I go.
You're light as a feather.
Am I even carrying someone on
my back right now?
I thought you were wearing a toupee.
- That scared me.
- It was a scary sight.
[The CEO's long coat
being dragged behind him.]
Who do you think you are?
A matador?
- You think you're a matador?
- What are you doing?
[Even though he's trying to be cool,
his attempts are seriously...]
- His hair looked so funny earlier.
- It did look cool.
It looked like this.
Like this... looked like this.
It's G-Dragon's hairstyle!
[Gae-Dragon...]
- Let's go.
- He's G-Dragon.
Here we go.
[Rose of Sharon is blooming: Final round.]
The rose of Sharon is blooming.
The rose of Sharon is blooming!
[Upping the speed?]
- Hang on...
- The rose of Sharon is blooming!
The rose of Sharon is blooming!
Get us a new seeker!
[Come closer]
The rose of Sharon is blooming!
- Slow down.
- The rose of Sharon is blooming!
[Try it.]
The rose of Sharon is blooming!
It's about time for someone to mess up!
[Too much on his vocal chords.]
He's making me dizzy.
The rose of Sharon is blooming!
[Almost time to slap him?]
[Unable to make a move.]
The rose of Sharon is blooming.
The rose of Sharon is blooming!
- Stay strong.
- The rose of Sharon...
The rose of Sharon...
[Just which of the two will be caught?]
[Catching up to them
at a lightning fast speed!]
[The Gary and Yeon Hee couple
is eliminated.]
Did you get caught?
[Jong Kook and Ara wins!]
The winner of the 'Rose of Sharon' game is,
Kim Jong Kook and Go Ara.
Is this a makjang drama?
Only the winner couple of this game
will get to see the final scene early.
[The winning couple gets to see
the final scene early?]
You will find a car waiting for you outside,
and the final scene is in that car.
While heading to your next location,
you can check the final scene in the car.
- The final scene?
- It's the final scene.
Don't you think that's too big
of an advantage?
Also, only the couple that won can go on
to the next destination in the car.
As for the rest of the members...
the men and women will go separately
to your next destination.
- Okay, I understand.
- This is what we wanted.
What does that mean?
Ji Hyo and I are finally getting along!
- We're finally on the same page!
- We're just learning how to work together.
We're going to head out first then.
- We're going to head out first.
- We'll see you later.
- Okay, see you there.
- See you later.
We're going to go in our car.
See you later.
[On to the second location.]
We'll see you at the next scene.
I'll see you at the next location.
That's not entertaining.
[We'll see you at the next location!]
[What are you doing?]
What are you doing?
There are some lines that just
shouldn't be crossed.
- You're the only one who can do it?
- Come here!
We'll go with yours, Jae Suk.
- Yes, I understand.
- Use mine too.
Thank you.
Hit the slate in an
entertaining way for us.
[In the most entertaining ways.]
You can't hit the slate like that!
How is that entertaining?
- Try to make it funny.
- You don't think that was funny?
Seriously!
[This is how you do it.]
[The correct way to hit the slate.]
Come on, seriously!
- As always...
- You don't even know the basics.
This much should be a given.
These guys don't even know that.
See?
They're going to use mine again.
[See you soon at the second scene.]
[Jong Kook and Ara heading out
together to the second location.]
Is that nice imported car for us?
Seriously...
- What's that?
- What is that?
You guys are riding in that car?
[Unhappy with the difference
in their rides.]
Why?
Why can't we ride in this?
What's wrong with you guys?
What goes around, comes around.
- Should we take a look?
- Yes.
[The final scene that only the
winning couple can see.]
[A box?]
[A man and a woman holding the box together
in front of the house on the next page.]
I think...
since this is the final scene
we're looking at...
[Jong Kook's guess is that the ending is of
a couple walking away with a treasure?]
They're being given a treasure!
I think this is what's going to happen.
Let's take a closer look.
I'm sure there must be a reason why
there's a close-up of this box.
[Is this box something they're going to
have to find later on?]
[Jong Kook and Ara who have an
advantage over the other couples.]
Let's do our best and win today.
What is this?
This car smells like men.
[The men's car stinking of male scent.]
[All the members are to come to SBS gym
where the second scene will take place.]
Let's just get there quickly in silence.
- Let's go.
This is my first time driving with a girl
since I've been on Running Man.
You can use casual speech with me, Ji Hyo.
Yes... okay.
I really didn't think you were going to
come to China back then.
[Having been totally shocked at
Ji Hyo's surprise appearance.]
I kept suspecting Jong Kook.
I really... want to rip it off.
I really want to rip someone's
name tag off this time.
You didn't get to rip off anyone's
name tag off the last time?
- No, I didn't.
- Really?
I didn't get to rip it off even once.
No matter who wins today, my goal
is to rip off someone's name tag today.
- I really want to rip it off.
- Who's name tag do you want to rip off?
- I really want to get Jong Kook.
- Jong Kook?
I want to rip his name tag off
the moment we start the race.
Really?
Since he's so impossible for
anyone to eliminate.
[I will rip off Mr. Capable's name tag!]
Okay, come on in.
[Jong Kook and Ara couple enter
hand in hand.]
This looks like what I used to have to do
when I was on the show, X-Man.
What is this?
[The rest of the members also arrive.]
Lee Yeon Hee, please step forward.
You look beautiful even from the back.
[Gary's just happy to be
Yeon Hee's partner.]
Part two, 'R' Group athletic competition.
The two people who are having
a secret affair
test their feelings for one another by
playing a round of 'Couple's Dodgeball.'
But a sudden terminal illness
comes to find the couple...
[Terminal illness?]
But a sudden terminal illness
comes to find the couple...
The woman faints after being
hit by the ball.
This is starting to turn into
a makjang drama.
The CEO who tries to block all the throws
with his own body to protect her...
Winning the game of dodgeball
is the only way
of getting the approval
from his father, the chairman.
The woman must be hit by the ball
for the couple to be ousted.
The remaining couple wins.
- The woman has to be hit to be ousted?
- These two are going to be fun to watch.
So in order to help you out in your
search for your destined partner...
we're going to play this game by
switching the partners around.
[Partner switch up]
- Great!
- What do you mean, great?
What are you saying?
[Partner switch up confusing everyone.]
Is there really a reason
for us to be doing this?
The reason being, you know
this is a Running Mini-series...
and in every drama,
there's always a climatic issue.
I really like climatic issues.
Can't you do this in the
morning drama style?
Chance!
This time, the ladies will have the chance
to choose their partners themselves.
They can do this by going up to the person
they want, and giving them a back hug.
A back hug...
That's how we'll choose the partners.
Ladies, please take a step back.
Then this is random.
This is seriously driving me nuts.
This is seriously...
[Who will be the new couples to be
born out of this round?]
Until you are told,
you can't turn around.
- I understand.
- I'll keep my eyes closed.
Let's just be cool about this.
[The first candy girl, Lee Yeon Hee.]
[Who will she select?]
- I can hear someone's footsteps.
- The sound of those footsteps...
- It's giving me hope.
- The footsteps are going further away.
[Yeon Hee can't easily make up her mind.]
I can hear her... there she is.
She's right here.
[Where will she go?]
[She chooses CEO Gae again!]
Ji Hyo.
I'm positive it's Ji Hyo.
Is it Ji Hyo?
[Now it's Blank Ji's turn.]
[Blank Ji teasing all the CEO's.]
Is she behind me?
- I'm going crazy! Stop teasing me!
- What's going on?
Why are you making all that noise?
- I'm getting nervous.
- I feel like I'm going to go crazy.
Hey... I can smell someone's perfume.
I can smell someone's perfume.
[Blank Ji selects CEO Ha.]
That smelled like Ji Hyo's perfume.
All I can smell is Jong Kook's cologne.
- Okay, keep your eyes closed.
- This is the last one.
The last one.
This is the last one.
Honey!
[The last candy girl, Ara.]
[Runs full speed ahead
without any hesitation.]
- I'm right here!
- Honey!
[A fierce back hug!]
[Is it even a surprise?
Ara chooses CEO Kkuk again.]
You may turn around.
[The two ecstatic couples and...]
[And the remaining three who weren't
able to become a part of a couple.]
I'm stuck in this situation again?
- What are we supposed to do now?
- Miss Blank. Don't you think that was rude?
I have my right to choose!
The situation I'm in...
I can't be too happy about this either...
- This is just unbelievable.
- Ji Hyo!
A true candy girl does not
betray her partner.
- Seriously... as predicted...
- As predicted...
The three of you need to choose which
two are going to become a couple.
Again? Are we going to be
doing this all day?
[We have to play another couple game...]
Hey, I like you!
- I like you!
- Hang on a second.
Hey, I like you!
[Fascinating couple]
Doesn't Kwang Soo and Suk Jin
look like a couple?
They totally look like a couple.
- Jae Suk, I don't think you...
- What are you talking about?
Kwang Soo and I are a couple.
[Huh? He and Kwang Soo
are a couple?]
[Awesome]
- Uee!
- I miss you!
- He's right! Those two really are a couple.
- Over... the selection is over.
[The older hunter being thrown
out to the curb once again.]
- Forget it.
- Uee, I miss you!
What the heck is this?
It's been like this all day!
[I'm the lone couple hunter.]
Don't be disappointed that
you're not part of a couple.
- We have a good role for you to play.
- What is it?
Two couples are going to partner up together
to play against the other two couples.
And Ji Suk Jin,
who is not part of a couple...
since the ball may go
out of bounds...
[Wait, that means...]
He's the ball boy?
It's a role that will get you
on camera quite a bit.
So what you're saying right now is,
you want me to be the ball boy?
Why are you trying to
turn it around?
[Big-nosed brother explodes.]
He's asking why they're
changing the story.
My family thinks I left this morning to film
Running Man but I'm here to be the ball boy?
[Anyway...]
[Part two: Dodgeball park.
That Winter, That Typhoon Blows.]
Go all the way to the end.
To the end.
[Rule: If the woman of your team is hit,
then that team is out.]
You got that?
You have to protect me.
- Who's the woman on your team?
- Me.
Really?
This is the innocent style.
But still a woman with taste.
- You're attractive.
- You're very attractive.
[This generation's ideal woman, Jae Soon.]
[Time to decide who will go first.]
[Mister hunter guy]
[The judge will be the Mister Hunter.]
- I'm just going to run in there.
- Get in there and get it.
- We have to get in there and get the ball.
- Let's really do this.
I'm going to block them off,
so you grab the ball, okay?
You're going to rip your pants again
if you're not careful.
I'm going to block them all off.
[Unguarded!]
[An opportunity as soon as
the game starts!]
What are you doing?
Hey, what are you doing?
[The lightning fast protective instinct
that Gary's showing the team.]
[Trustworthy Gary-guard.]
[Mr. Capable's fierce attack
they were just able to evade.]
- This is a ferocious game.
- Over here!
[In danger again!]
[Barely escapes it again.]
Please just stay behind me!
[Finally gets the chance to attack!]
[A game reversal!]
[Bulls eye!]
[Blocks with his whole body
twice in a row!]
[Giraffe's sacrifice.]
[The ball goes back to the other team.]
[Fierce]
- What the heck, lady?
- Can a girl do that?
- I've been working out a bit, what!
- Can the girl do that?
[Athletic Jae Soon's fierce attack.]
Is that really a girl?
Look at the way she's standing!
[Huh?]
[Giraffe and Jae Soon's combo attack!]
[Save us]
[Superpower fireworks show?]
[Huh?]
[Danger]
[But he blocks it...]
[Blocks his head again...]
[Jae Soon and Giraffe barely
escapes their elimination.]
[Gary has a chance!]
[Jae Soon and Giraffe - Out!]
- You should've blocked it!
- You should've blocked the ball!
Wait, I tried my best!
[Kwang Soo and Jae Suk to
step out of the bounds.]
- This is too funny.
- This way?
We have to stand over here?
[But they're still able to keep participating
in the game from outside the lines.]
We can play from out here,
and we can still win this together.
[There's still a chance.]
Fighting!
[Their plan is to pass the ball
back and forth quickly.]
[Kkuk has his chance!]
This is a tight game.
[If anything, the game has become
more thrilling with one team being ousted.]
[Her legs are left unguarded?]
[Haroro barely gets the ball away
with the tips of his fingers.]
[What?]
[Please give me the ball!]
[Who gets the ball is up
to Mister Hunter.]
You've still got it, Impala!
- Your expression was nice.
- Thank you!
[Mr. Gary wins the ball.]
[This is nice.]
[CEO Kkuk not leaving any
open spots for an attack.]
[The attack barely misses.]
This game is fun.
[Escapes it again!]
[Blocks it with his thighs!]
[If it goes that way...]
[Is it the candy girls' turn to cheer?]
You've still got it, Ji Suk Jin!
So cute!
They're so cute!
Give it to the last one!
[Jae Soon's dirty dancing.]
[Her dancing skills bringing out
the ferociousness in others.]
[Give it to me!]
[The woman who doesn't know the
meaning of giving up.]
Get away from me!
Okay, Ara!
[The ball goes to Ara!]
I like this role.
This isn't bad at all.
[Kkuk and the Giraffe concentrating
their attack on Guard Gary.]
[Yeon Hee grabs the ball!]
[Nice throw!]
Good job!
How did she throw it like that?
- Yeon Hee's no joke.
- She's good.
[An emotion-filled attack?]
[A concentrated attack!]
[He grabbed the ball!]
[Mommy!]
[The rage-o-meter is through the roof!]
Jong Kook, calm down!
You can do this!
[Haroro, you scoundrel...]
[The ball flew by like a
bolt of lightning!]
[A ferocious revenge by
the enraged tiger.]
Why did you have to lose the ball?
[Another bulls eye!]
[Please save me!]
Hang on a second.
Is it the fireworks show?
[Been waiting for this moment...]
[Huh?]
[Jae Suk not interested
in the fireworks show.]
We have to oust them quickly.
[The nervous energy is back in the game.]
We have to oust someone.
[Gary's lightning fast deflect!]
[Another immediate attack!]
[This one is blocked too!]
[Gary guard barely blocking
the ball with his hands.]
[But just then!]
[Blank Ji is in danger!]
[Blank Ji is left unguarded.]
[Ha Ha and Blank Ji, out!]
This is actually better.
[The game isn't over yet.]
This is more even.
[Jong Kook and Ara vs. Gary and Yeon Hee.]
[Kkuk and the Giraffe casually
passing the ball back and forth.]
[Huh?]
[Immediate danger]
[The impassible Kkuk!]
[Huh?]
[Whenever the ball is in Big-nose's hand,
everyone automatically starts to dance.]
[Ara breaks out into the
Impala song too!]
[Throwing in some footwork?]
She's throwing some skills in there.
[What?]
[Haroro's pass misses.]
[Yeon Hee's in danger.]
[She's hit... what?]
[She catches the fierce throw?]
[This is Yeon Hee's shocking
dodgeball skills!]
- What the heck was that?
- Unbelievable!
[The goddess of dodgeball is born!]
[Huh?]
[The originator of clumsiness, Blank Ji.]
What the heck is that?
[One track mind for the ball.]
You can't come inside the lines.
I only saw the ball.
I'm sorry.
[Kkuk's fast play.]
[Danger]
[Misses his attack!]
[A non-stop attack!]
[What?]
[Yeon Hee's in danger!]
[Of all people for the ball to go to,
why did it have to be the Giraffe?]
[Yeon Hee, out!]
[Jong Kook, Ara and Kwang Soo, Jae Suk wins!]
We won!
[The goddess of dodge ball
seemingly disappointed.]
That couldn't be helped.
[Immediately moving off to play-offs:
Jong Kook and Ara vs. Kwang Soo and Jae Suk.]
Kwang Soon!
Yes, Honey.
Don't worry about a thing, Kwang Soon.
Just believe in me!
This is the play-offs.
Gary and Yeon Hee couple.
[Gary and Yeon Hee couple to
assist Kwang Soon and Jae Suk.]
[And Ha Ha and Blank Ji to
assist Kkuk and Ara.]
Everyone please stay within the lines.
- My girlfriend is so tall...
- I can't get fully concealed.
[Miss Kwang Soon unable to fully conceal
her tall body.]
My girlfriend might take a hit
on her head.
[Time to decide who'll go first.]
[Extremely fast Kwang Soon.]
[Totally getting worked up
over dodgeball.]
- I'm overly excited!
- You can throw the ball.
[Starting off with a pass play.]
Kwang Soo, you can throw...
[Full speed]
[Grazing the tiger's head.]
[Save me.]
[Dance time?]
[Zebra couple's dance shake.]
[Full of nervous energy even though
the ball hasn't even been thrown out.]
Jae Suk!
Grab the ball!
[Danger]
[Fast Kwang Soon!]
Your girlfriend is very good
at avoiding the ball.
Your girlfriend is good at avoidance.
[Blocks it with his face.]
[Unable to control himself
whenever the ball is in sight.]
Your girlfriend is throwing the ball.
[The giant girlfriend with fast throws.]
Get the ball back, quick!
[Huh?]
Why is your girlfriend so
good at the game?
[Kwang Soo loses it.]
[A hit to the face]
I knew a day like this was
going to come!
[Overtly excited Kwang Soon
causes trouble.]
Jong Kook, that's a girl for now.
You can't do anything about it.
You have to be more understanding
as the man.
Let me go.
I got it.
- This is unbelievable.
- That really is unbelievable.
I know that really hurts.
I know it does.
My girlfriend is acting like this because
she's excited to be outside.
- It's just been so long.
- Seriously...
This is the first time I've been
outside since the age of two.
[Kwang Soon's first time
outside since the age of two.]
- She's just so happy to be out.
- I've been caged up inside.
What to do...
I'm going to break up with her
at the end of the week.
[Suddenly declaring his intentions
of a breakup?]
How can you say that?
- This is the last week for us.
- I've bought you everything you wanted!
- Hurry up and break up with her.
- I'm serious.
- I'm going to.
[Back to the game.]
[You just wait and see...]
Stand up.
Don't try to hide.
[While they're too busy cowering,
the ball is quickly passed!]
[A direct hit on Kwang Soon!]
[The quick pass succeeds!]
[Jong Kook and Ara wins!]
They just keep winning.
Kim Jong Kook and Go Ara will be given an
advantage from having won this game.
They won again!
[Part three to immediately start.]
[We won!]
We won all thanks to you.
[Jong Kook and Ara couple happy
to have won again.]
We got something again.
[What advantage have they
won this time?]
- We've got something.
- Let's take a look.
It's a different picture.
[A different picture than earlier?]
The box from earlier is now open.
- It's gold.
- Ah..  it is?
So the ending from earlier...
[The ending scene from earlier...]
[The couple holding the mysterious box...]
[Then what is the meaning of this box?]
So the couple's been given the box,
and now they've opened it.
So inside the box are two pieces of gold,
and a ballerina figurine.
[Jong Kook and Ara at an advantage from
having seen the inside of the box.]
I think they're each going to
wear the piece, right?
Okay, the Running Man mini-series...
[The actors are to now move on over to
'M' hotel for part three of the drama.]
What if we're not destined to be together,
and we end up getting separated?
No, we're not going
to be separated.
Who is it?
[Kwang Soo getting in the ladies car.]
Kwang Soo...
Want some?
What is it?
Is it lip balm?
It's a lip tint.
Come here.
You can't let yourself go like that.
Brush your hair a little too.
Pull your lips back.
[Kwang Soon doing as
her older sister tells her to.]
Very pretty, Kwang Soon.
Look in the camera.
Go like that.
[Do I look pretty?]
[We're so sexy...]
- Seeing myself like this...
- You think you're pretty?
To be honest, to be between you two
like this, you can't really tell.
[You really can't tell?]
[Putting on the cute act.]
[Kwang Soon, please stop.]
[The final filming location,
Ilsan's 'M' hotel.]
Part three of the mini-series...
[At last... the final story to
That Winter, That Typhoon Blows.]
'R' Group's inaugural party.
Introduce the woman you love
to the chairman.
The chairman is stunned and
adamantly objects.
- He's going to object to your relationship.
- What did you say?
A birth secret that could mean
a revelation of a real brother and sister...
[Brother and sister!
A birth secret!]
- This is total makjang.
- No!
[A shocking makjang stunner
that's revealed at the final location!]
Part three of Running Man mini-series...
is the shocking birth secret.
[Final story: The birth secret.]
Out of the nine of you...
a pair of real brother and sister
exists that were separated at birth.
Who's the brother and sister?
Find the clues of the identities of the
siblings that are hidden throughout the hotel
and piece them all together to find out
which pair is the real brother and sister.
This is fun.
What if Ara and I...
What if Ara and I are siblings?
Once the brother and sister meets and
goes to the DNA testing center...
It's going to test your name tag to
tell you if you're real brother and sister.
Once it's been verified that you're real
brother and sister
you will be able to inherit
the chairman's vast fortune.
Also...
those of you who are not real
brother and sister...
find who the real siblings are
and eliminate them.
If you take the name tag you've ripped off
to the DNA testing platform
and set the evidence on there...
Today's the day!
- Today's the day!
- Then this is...
So we can't be carefree about who's
name tag we rip off ether.
Since we don't know who could be
the real siblings amongst us.
[Will the real siblings separated at birth be
able to reunite to inherit the fortune?]
[Or will someone else eliminate the
real siblings to steal the fortune?]
[Final Scene: The hotel.
That Winter, That Typhoon Blows.]
[The final scene]
Do we have to search through
all these rooms?
Where could it be?
What could be the hint?
[Confused without knowing
what the hint could look like...]
[At the same time, Ara is...]
The music box...
[The box in the drawing...]
The music box?
The treasure box?
And... the picture of the man
and the woman.
That's all that I saw.
Music box?
So I just need to find
the treasure box!
The treasure box!
[Could the clue as to who the siblings are
be contained in the treasure box?]
It could be somewhere around here.
I wonder if I've gone too far.
Okay... stay strong, Jong Kook!
I hope he finds his way too.
It's not in here either.
[Could the treasure box be the hint box
as Ara suspects it to be?]
[These guys are searching aimlessly
without knowing what the hint looks like.]
But... I'm sure Jong Kook knows something.
What is it that you saw?
I didn't see anything.
[Playing dumb]
You don't see anything?
I heard that there was a sketchbook
or something like that...
- What?
- I was told he saw a drawing.
What did you see?
- Come on, tell us.
- I seriously didn't see anything.
- There was no sketchbook.
- Since you saw both, just tell us one.
- Jong Kook!
- I said, I didn't see anything.
[The box...
I have to find the treasure box...]
[That has to be it!]
[Ara discovers the music box containing
the hint to the siblings' identity!]
It's a blood test confirmation.
[The siblings' biological mother's
blood type is 'O'.]
[Once they figure out the father's blood type
they can figure out the sibling's blood type.]
I was looking around for boxes,
then I saw this on the box.
This stays between the three of us.
The mother's blood type is 'O'.
- I...
- What's your blood type?
- Me?
- Yes.
- Do I have to tell you?
- It's okay.
Then I'll keep that to myself.
Why are you being like that?
I can find out on the internet.
Then you can look it up.
Yeon Hee... what's your blood type?
- Why don't you want to tell us?
- I really want to win this time.
I'm going to search on my own.
I get that you want to win,
but tell us your blood type.
Don't try to take the easy way out.
What do you mean, easy? I'm just
asking you about your blood type.
Type 'O' is usually a woman.
So we're searching for the possibilities.
What blood type could come from type 'O'?
But type 'O' can be a parent to
every other type.
[If they can find the father's blood type,
they can figure out the sibling's blood type.]
Do we... have to pay for the water?
- How much is it?
- It's 1,000 won.
1,000 won?
Can I have 1,000 won?
No.
- I need something to drink.
- Then get what you want.
[Wait... that's?]
Come here, Jae Suk.
[Ace appearing out of nowhere
like a ghost.]
Ji Hyo, that's not it.
I think you must be misunderstood...
- But that's just kept in there.
- Hand it over, Jae Suk.
- Hand it over.
- Why are you seriously being like this?
- Jae Suk, are you going to be like this?
- Seriously, what's wrong with you?
- Huh?
- I should show this...
Okay!
- What is it?
- Are you really going to be like this?
- You don't want to? Then I'll...
- Fine, hang on.
I said, fine!
Just put it back in there quickly.
- Okay.
- Seriously! Where did she come from?
[No choice but to share
his hint with her.]
All I was trying to do was buy some water.
Lots of thick black hair,
and on the taller side...
[A list of family's physical traits.]
And the eyes...
so these are the siblings' parents?
[If they can use this to figure out
who the siblings are...]
Tall with lots of thick dark hair...
[Kwang Soo?]
This one would indicate that.
It also says that the sister
has pale and clear skin.
Could it be Yeon Hee?
That sounds like Ara too.
- Your skin is on the pale side too.
- I don't have pale skin.
- Really?
- My skin is darker.
Really?
Nice clear voice and a broad face?
- Kim Jong Kook.
- Kang Gary.
- What about Gary?
- He has a broad smile.
- How is Gary's broad?
- Jong Kook's is pointy.
But his whole face is broad
with a robot-like chin.
That's what Kim Jong Kook's face is like.
All I thought about was
his pointy chin.
Kwang Soo can actually
be included in this too
but this part of the eyes being bright
and intelligent looking doesn't apply to him.
[Bright and intelligent looking eyes-
Kwang Soo's eliminated?]
- Yeon Hee?
- On the skinnier side...
Yeon Hee?
- Taller and slim...
- Yeon Hee?
- With full lips?
- But she doesn't have the fullest lips.
- Ara?
- Ara has fuller lips.
[The more they look at the list,
the more possibilities they're seeing...]
[Who are the real brother and sister pair
this list is referring to?]
[Tiger and the Giraffe searching
the outdoor pool.]
Whenever you walk like that...
[Huh?
The sound of a dog barking?]
Why... why is the dog barking
like that?
Kwang Soo... there's no way that dog
is here for no reason.
I thought that maybe the dog would have
some sort of a key around its neck...
- But I don't see anything.
- Right? there's nothing.
Why is it acting like that?
What?
What does that mean?
[This barking dog...]
[What is it trying to tell them?]
[Who's over there?]
- Yeon Hee, want some information?
- Yes, tell me.
- I'm just wandering around the rooms.
- You haven't figured anything out, have you?
[The Big-nosed Brother seems
to be searching around for something?]
Come here.
- I'll show you something.
- Did you find a hint?
Of course, I did!
I've been doing this show for years!
You already found something?
You can't tell anyone about this.
What I have here is a letter the dad wrote
to the mom before the second child was born.
- It's a love letter.
- Before the second child was born?
To my loving wife...
Seeing you peacefully sleeping with our
firstborn made me want to write a letter...
Our child with a lot of personality,
and excitement...
I know it's hard work to raise this child
who loves to do the shuffle dance...
Could it be Gary?
Gary with his dancing?
Not very talented in studies...
The child isn't a very good student.
We were all pretty bad students.
The letter also says the son
likes running.
Isn't Gary good at running?
[Little by little...]
[The profile of the brother is
slowly starting to take shape...]
[Kwang Soo discovers the box
containing the clues!]
Kwang Soo...
You found one, didn't you?
I can hear the music.
[He's eating the hint found
inside the box!]
[Jae Suk finally breaks his way in.]
Kwang Soo...
Hand it over, Kwang Soo.
[Nothing goes right for Kwang Soon.]
[Takes the hint out of his mouth...]
Go Dong Wan?
['R' Group-
Corporate attorney, Go Dong Wan.]
[Looking for a fax to contact the fax number
that was found on the business card.]
[That scoundrel!]
Hey, Lee Kwang Soo!
[Why is he running away like that?
What is he up to?]
If you were going down to the first floor,
why couldn't you have taken the elevator?
[First floor lobby]
Can you tell me where your
fax machine is?
- It's in the business center.
- Business center? Thank you.
[Giraffe in a rush to find the fax alone
in order to find out what the hint is.]
[Even locking up the door.]
You!
Hurry up and open up the door
before I call all the guys.
Hey, Lee Kwang Soo!
- How do you work this thing?
- I'm calling Jong Kook right now!
Kwang Soo...
If you keep being like this,
I'm going to text everyone!
Kwang Soo, that's not how you work it.
I said, that's not how you work it.
[Giraffe not caring about his methods
once he sees an opportunity.]
Excuse me!
Can you give me the key
to the business center?
- Jae Suk, do you know how to work this?
- Yes, I know.
Where did Ji Hyo go?
- Where did Ji Hyo go?
- She went to get the key.
The key.
We have to be quick.
I'm going to lock the door.
[He's just as clueless
about how to operate the machine.]
- Jae Suk... I opened the door for you.
- I know.
[Blank Ji rushing back after
having acquired the key.]
It doesn't fit!
- Ji Hyo's back with the key.
- It doesn't fit.
Seriously...
I'll try to hold her off.
I'll try to hold her off
as long as I can.
[He really is trying hard...]
Hi, Ji Hyo.
[Just a simple pull of the door.]
[The same result as if the three of them
happily came in together.]
- I was going to tell you all about it.
- Don't even mess with me.
I think I really must be unlucky.
Jae Suk... this is the output tray.
- That's the output tray?
- This is it... this is where you insert.
- Where?
- You put it in here...
- Something's coming out.
- I don't think that was right.
Why is this coming out?
[Huh? What did they press for blank
sheets of paper to keep coming out?]
Why are all these blank sheets
of paper coming out?
Why do these keep coming out?
- Jae Suk...
- Why do these blank sheets keep coming out?
[Sending a blank feed of fax
isn't going to do anything...]
[Must fax some sort of a message for
a response to be faxed back...]
I can't believe I'm working with you
two clueless people!
[The nerve to even say those words...]
How could you have sent something
without writing a message on it first?
[Must send in their question to
Attorney Go Dong Wan...]
Ask him who the male and
the female is.
I don't think he's going to answer
such a point blank question like that.
[He's not going to answer such
an obvious question as that...]
[Jae Suk's inquiry]
- You have to ask a question.
- I asked for a hint.
Don't you have to write it
in a question form?
It's Gary.
Yes, Gary.
Kwang Soo, where are you?
I'm on the third floor right now.
[This is the first floor...]
[Giraffe's non-stop lies without
changing one facial expression.]
- Did Jae Suk find anything?
- You can't even tell that he's lying.
- I don't think he found anything.
- I really thought we were on the third floor.
[Giraffe's lies are so believable that they
all thought they may be on the third floor.]
Okay, Gary.
I'll call you later.
Okay.
You haven't found any hints?
No.
[Jae Suk is faxing his request for a hint
over to Attorney Go Dong Wan.]
I'll call you later, okay?
Okay.
You telling him that you'll call him later
was a lie too, wasn't it?
Well... I can just call him
back tomorrow.
[An immediate reply from Attorney Go!]
[Who are you?]
Give him my name.
Since I found the hint.
[Since they only have one chance at asking
the question, no other choice but to...]
There's no need to sign it too.
[Even though this is
their one and only chance...]
[The question asked is,
'Is Kwang Soo the brother?']
Doesn't this feel like something...
you'd see in a movie?
If they take this long in a movie...
- We'd all be dead by now.
- It'd be over.
I was just making a comment.
[Could Kwang Soo be the real brother?]
This is Attorney Go Dong Wan.
I've done a lot of research,
but from what I've gathered so far
I don't think you or Ji Suk Jin are it.
[Attorney Go's verdict:
Kwang Soo and Suk Jin are not the brother!]
[Yeon Hee discovers the dog
Jong Kook and Kwang Soo saw earlier.]
What do you know?
Where's your owner?
Stand up.
Stand up!
There you go.
[Unlike earlier, the dog is
very calm with Yeon Hee?]
The dog is starting to show
interest in me.
Do you know something?
Where's the hint?
[Cozying up to Yeon Hee as if
it wants to play with her.]
You're cute.
[What is the purpose of this dog?]
[On the other hand,
Gary still hasn't found a single clue.]
I wonder if there's something in here.
Why is it making sounds?
[Finally discovers a box
containing the clues!]
Gary... you found something!
[Yeon Hee picks this moment
to walk into the room!]
How did you find me?
[What did he find in the box?]
[It looks like pages from a magazine?]
Hey...
Yeon Hee, I think I got it.
[Gary seems to know what the clue
is referring to?]
Fold it back up.
This is...
Yeon Hee...
I just got chills down my spine.
Is it Ddak-ji?
[This was folded into the shape
of a Ddak-ji?]
[When it comes to Ddak-ji,
Gary was once the King of Ddak-ji.]
[And Jong Kook too for having
turned over the Ultimate Ddak-ji...]
[And Jae Suk always comes to mind
when Ddak-ji is mentioned...]
[Possible candidates for the brother.]
[Narrowed down to these three?]
[If pieced together with the other clues...]
Jae Suk?
Right?
You're thinking of Jae Suk too, right?
- Does Jae Suk like to run?
- He's a fast runner.
When a person is a fast runner,
it means they used to run a lot as a kid.
- You don't think it's you, do you?
- I'm positive it's not me.
[Yeah... I think Jae Suk is the brother...]
We all need to get our
heads on straight.
[After having seen the fax,
Kwang Soo's busy sharing his information.]
- What I just said...
- What confuses me is...
- We...
- You and I are not it, right?
- No, we're not.
- Then how does this work?
If you and I aren't it...
[If the person is found not to
be one of the siblings...]
[They must rip off the name tag of the person
they think to be it to win the race!]
Then we need to find the heir quickly.
[Now the Easy Brothers just needs to
eliminate the rest without hesitation.]
Then if we were to rip off his name,
do we just take it to the DNA platform?
No, that's not it.
You are given only one chance.
[Ha Ha seems to be proposing
something...]
Can we work together as
a team again?
If you can give us a solid proof
that you're not the brother.
If you can give us solid proof, then yes.
You have something, don't you?
See this... look at this!
[Ha Ha hid away the hint he found
inside his sock!]
[Suk Jin, out!]
Kwang Soo... I have this.
Are you with me or not?
- I'm with you.
- You're with me?
[Anything is possible in
the Traitors' Club!]
[Suk Jin's letter clue goes to Ha Ha.]
Since it was two against one,
I knew that I had to eliminate one.
What are you guys doing?
What's going on here?
Hang on Jae Suk.
Kwang Soo...
- Way's going on?
- Wait. It's not me.
- What's going on?
- What do you mean, what's going on?
Are you by any chance, the brother?
[The possibilities from the remaining
survivors are diminishing in numbers.]
I'm not really sure
if I'm the brother or not.
What do you know, Jae Suk?
Pale skin...
- You have pale skin too.
- But...
Kwang Soo definitely is not it.
I know.
- Eliminate him.
- Okay.
[Deciding to eliminate Kwang Soo first
since he's a threat of danger.]
Kwang Soo, come out here.
- What?
- Come out here, Kwang Soo. Hurry!
[Why is he acting like that?]
Come out here!
- Move your finger.
- Kwang Soo, hurry.
[It's Jae Suk!]
Extremely jovial...
[A mischievous little boy
who's also a good dancer.]
[Likes to run...]
[And a Ddak-ji expert.]
Also very excitable.
Could it be Jae Suk?
[The brother who's about to inherit
the vast fortune is...]
[It has to be Jae Suk.]
Come out here. There's no one out here.
Open the door and see for yourself.
I'm leaving.
[The Giraffe steps out of the room...]
[And attacks?]
What are you doing?
What's wrong with you?
[Kwang Soo, out!]
[With nothing to lose,
the Giraffe attacks anyone in his path!]
You sneaky little fox.
Forget this.
- You and Suk Jin aren't it.
- Dong Hoon has a hint hidden in his sock.
[The traitor's gene is rooted
in his DNA.]
[While Ha Ha is being targeted...]
[Yeon Hee's hand is...]
[Feeling certain that
she's not the sister...]
[Eyeing the real suspect,
Jae Suk's name tag!]
[Yeon Hee eliminates
What just happened?
[Jae Suk is ultimately eliminated.]
[Could he truly be the real brother?]
[Running away with Jae Suk's hint
in her possession.]
We can't let Dong Hoon see that.
So hurry... come here and sit down.
They found a lot of clues.
What is this?
Gary, this is a list.
- Smaller face...
- The mom's side is...
I think it's all referring to
the traits of a woman.
An egg shape.
A small and egg shaped face.
That's all us girls.
Ara's face is like that too.
First... this part about the pale skin...
- That's all of us again.
- No, Ji Hyo's skin is darker.
So I don't think it's Ji Hyo.
So that would leave me and Ara.
I think it's between you and Ara.
If the father's side has smaller eyes,
and has monolids...
So it could have been passed
down to the child.
But looking at this list, a lot of it
seems to be referring to Jae Suk.
- This sounds like Jae Suk too.
- And this one.
With a nice voice and a broad face.
But this face...
Jong Kook's face is developed like this,
and Jae Suk's is like this.
[Jong Kook with a rectangular face,
vs. Jae Suk's protruding face.]
[Jong Kook's starting to sound
like a good possibility too...]
[Could it be Jong Kook?]
So the mother's blood type is 'O'.
So what we need to find quickly is
the father's blood type.
[Must find the father's blood type.]
If the door's open, then it
means someone's already checked?
[Carefully checking each room
that hasn't been searched through yet.]
- I don't think it's in here.
- I don't think so either.
Check the safe.
[Rechecking the safes and the drawers.]
Check the safe, Ara.
- Jong Kook!
- Is it in there?
[Discovers a box containing a clue!]
Let's see.
There was a key... here it is.
[Yeon Hee is searching the outdoor
lockers with Gary.]
You want me to start opening
from the bottom?
[The four finally faces off.]
[What is the truth?]
[Could there be a real brother and sister
amongst this group of four?]
- What are you talking about?
- This is just a drama.
- You can't trust him.
- This is not real love.
- Ara...
- How can you talk like that?
- Do you know who the siblings are?
- Do you know?
- Do you know who it is?
- Ara, do you know who it is?
I assure you, it's not me.
- Do you know who it is?
- I think I know.
[Jong Kook and Ara seem to be
searching for something specific...]
- You're the sister.
- How do you know that?
[Yeon Hee is the sister?]
Yeon Hee, it's you.
How did you get separated
from your father?
What's the definitive clue that you have
that proves I'm the sister?
- Tell me what your proof is.
- The blood type...
- I don't think we should tell them that.
- Ara, is it the blood type?
It's the blood type.
The blood type we saw together earlier?
- Yeon Hee, be careful.
- What we saw earlier together?
- It's your blood type.
- What blood type?
- It just said that the mom was type 'O'.
[Yeon Hee who knows as far as
the mom having type 'O'.]
And the last thing we found...
The father has type B.
[Father's blood type is B.]
The dad has type B.
- So whether it's the daughter or the son...
- Whether it's the son or the daughter...
They have to have either
B or O type, right?
- It has to be either type B or O.
- You're right.
[In that case, the children's blood type
has to be either B or O.]
- What did you say Jae Suk's was?
- B.
B?
Yeon Hee's is B too.
[Suspect Jae Suk's type is B,
and Yeon Hee's type is also B.]
All we know is that the
mom has type O.
That's all we found.
- I'm type B.
- The last thing we found...
- Is the father type B?
- Father is.
- So the father has type B?
- What's Jae Suk's blood type?
Type B.
- That's right.
- Type B.
- If type O and type B...
The only possibility would be
either type O or type B.
You're type A and I'm
also type A.
I'm type A too.
[The sister is Yeon Hee.
In that case...]
This is a love letter the dad wrote to
the mom before the second child was born.
This part here about the child
being very lively and excitable.
And loves to dance...
[And a hint no one realized...]
[The wife is an 'Announcer'.]
A small egg shaped face.
[The features from the mother's side
describes Yeon Hee.]
Smaller eyes with monolids.
I think a lot of this is
describing Jae Suk.
This sounds like Jae Suk too.
Jae Suk's face is like this.
Jae Suk's always liked Ddak-ji
ever since he was a kid.
[The barking's dog's meaning...]
[It's the same kind of a dog
the siblings used to raise as kids.
[That's why the dog was so calm
when it saw Yeon Hee.]
[And at a closer look,
it didn't bark at Jae Suk either.]
[But no one caught on to that truth...]
[The brother and sister who are to
inherit the vast fortune are...]
[Jae Suk and Yeon Hee.]
[Blank...]
Jae Suk is your brother.
Poor Jae Suk, what do I do?
[Her true brother that she
eliminated with her own hands.]
[Then the person who ousts Yeon Hee and
takes the two name tags wins the race!]
We don't know who the ultimate
winner is going to be yet.
You are the beholder of
both name tags right now anyway.
Where do we go?
[Gary's protective instinct over
poor Yeon Hee is awakened.]
Ara, come here.
Come stand by me.
Come this way, Ara.
This way... this way.
Run!
Run, Yeon Hee!
[Yeon Hee sprints towards
the DNA testing machine!]
[Preparing to put her name tag along with
her brother, Jae Suk's on the podium!]
[Yeon Hee first put Jae Suk's name tag...]
[Ara is relentless with
her attack on Yeon Hee!]
[If Ara places Yeon Hee and Jae Suk's
name tag on the podium, she'll win!]
Ara, did you get them up there?
[Two name tags are finally
placed on the DNA testing podium!]
- We could be wrong.
- No, we're not wrong.
[Are Jae Suk and Yeon Hee
the 'R' Group's successors?]
[99.9% match!]
[Jae Suk and Yeon Hee are siblings!]
- You should've ran a little faster.
- You two are brother and sister?
[Since the DNA has been tested,
the inheritance will go to Ara!]
Who's the brother?
- Who's the brother?
- Brother!
It's me?
[The siblings reunited!]
And you eliminated me?
[The end result is that
this was a messy makjang drama.]
[No inheritance was earned,
and the sibling relationship is ruined.]
['R' Group's fortune goes to Ara!]
How could you have done this to me?
You're my little sister?
There was one definitive clue that
none of you were able to pick up on.
- What was it?
- There was one left to find?
[A shocking evidence that will take
the brother and sister by surprise.]
- It's a picture,
- I'm so heartbroken.
- What is this?
- Who's picture is this?
What is this picture?
Jae Suk, it's you!
- It's me.
- Is it really you?
- This is a picture of me as a kid.
- Really?
- Verify that it's you.
- This really is me.
- It's you?
- Is that Ara? I mean, Yeon Hee?
- That is me.
- Your real picture?
[If they had seen this picture sooner...]
The ending to the drama is...
It's not about the brother and sister.
[The final story is that of lovers,
not the brother and sister.]
The sister doesn't even know it's her brother
and just ends up killing her brother...
We'll just say that the drama ends
with the story of two lovers.
- I shouldn't have done that.
- Why did you do it, Yeon Hee?
- Sorry.
- That's unbelievable.
So the vast fortune that
Attorney Go has...
[Hands over the 'R' Group fortune.]
Open it up.
- Let Ara do it.
- Fine!
Finish up the drama as you've seen
in the script drawing.
[The finale to be carried out as seen
in the drawing.]
[The gold inheritance found
inside the wooden box...]
[are put on the male and female lead.]
[And they lived happily ever after.]
[That Winter, That Typhoon Blows]
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Patient number 850714-
Symptoms: Fits of rage.]
[Year 2013 - Rage virus breaks
out all over earth.]
[Humanity's loss of ability to laugh...]
[Save humanity by finding one last
laughter vaccine left on earth.]
You can save humanity.
[The fate of humanity
rests in our hands!]
[Avoid attacks by those infected,
and infiltrate the vaccine holding facility.]
[The laughter vaccine's disappeared!]
[The one last chance to return
laughter to humanity.]
[Next week's Running Man - Virus.]