[Running Man - Asia Race]
[A special episode that will take them
across Asia starts now!]
[After Macau... off to Vietnam!]
[Over land and sea...
a total spectacle of a race!]
[Running Man - Asia Race]
Subtitles By DramaFever
[Cheongju International Airport]
[Mr. Gary makes his appearance]
I'm still not used to the time change
since being back from the States.
And here I go again, heading overseas.
[A world star?
A frequent international traveler.]
So we're going to Macau?
I wonder what'll happen in Macau?
[Mr. Gary, always living life to its fullest
faces the biggest challenge of his life?]
[Blank Ji makes her arrival too,
dressed like a celebrity actress.]
Hello.
[Blank Ji, a woman who knows no fear!]
To all our fans overseas...
just wait a little bit longer.
I'm... coming your way!
[Traitor Giraffe,
is he being crowned the Prince of Asia?]
Macau is the best!
[Jae Suk and Ro-Ro
also make their appearance.]
[Scaredy cat, Haroro, tears and all?]
This is Cheongju International Airport.
[A crowd motivator
no matter where he goes.]
[Is the National MC about to become
the International MC?]
I'm sorry, but I had to wear my sunglasses
because my eyes are all swollen up.
This way, this way!
[No matter where he goes, the laws of
nature don't let anything go his way.]
Why isn't Jong Kook coming?
- You're all aware he has other obligations?
- Yes.
[Even though he can't go with them
due to other obligations...]
[Mr. Capable will soon shock everyone
with his dramatic appearance.]
Are we heading straight to
Macau right now?
- Let's go.
- Let's go!
[Off to Macau!
Running Man's Asia Race.]
[First destination - Macau!]
[Running Man members full of anticipation.]
[Just what kind of adventures
will they find?]
Everyone... the person you are sitting
with right now is your teammate.
Really?
Then this means Jae Suk is going to
be scolding me all day today.
For now, everyone relax and
enjoy the flight.
[Teams- Jae Suk, Ha Ha;
Suk Jin, Kwang Soo; and Gary, Ji Hyo.]
- Hurry up and say something.
- Oh, bye... see you in Macau.
[Heading towards Macau]
[Gary's know-how on how to
pop the ear drums.]
It looks as though you two are
heading off on your honeymoon.
No, we're going on our farewell trip.
I'm going to be scolding him
during the whole trip.
[Bubbling over with excitement for the trip.]
What the heck?
[A stewardess appears out of nowhere
to hand them something?]
[That is...]
Is this your phone number?
[What?]
What do you mean, phone number?
Why would she give that to you?
Why would she give you her number?
[We apologize in his place...]
- Thank you.
- Kwang Soo, what does it say?
[Once the tablet PC's been turned on...]
[A map?]
[Fisherman's wharf]
[Running Man in Macau]
[Meet with the secret agent in Macau airport,
then head to the Fisherman's wharf.]
- Where's the Fisherman's wharf?
- And who's the secret agent?
- Is the agent our guest for the day?
- We have to approach a secret agent?
How are we supposed to make our approach?
As soon as you get off the airplane...
right from the airstrip...
As soon as you get off the airplane,
you have to start your search
for the secret agent.
- Starting from the airstrip?
- Airstrip?
Don't you think that the scale
has become too big?
Is this going to be a blockbuster?
You haven't had your breakfast yet?
(Teasing Ha Ha for his pronunciation)
[Macau International Airport]
[Running Man members arrive in Macau]
[Running Man's Asia Race starts now!]
[The landing airstrip alerting them
of their race starting.]
[With it being the airstrip... A quiet
landing without a screaming welcome.]
- Come on, we don't have much time.
- What the heck is this?
Jae Suk, what are you doing?
- Come on, Jae Suk!
- What the heck are you doing?
[Starts out by handing them their
allowance to carry out the missions.]
How much is this?
- This is about 70,000 won.
- Are the fans waiting out there?
[Anyways... the Asia Race starts now!]
How can we get started already?
As soon as you're off the strip,
you have to go and get changed.
Kang Gary, come on!
- What about the secret agent?
- Aren't we supposed to find the secret agent?
[Could it be?]
[Are they the secret agents?]
[Where's the secret agent who's
supposed to be carrying a bag?]
[Inside the airport]
[After having changed into team uniforms,
their race to find the agent starts now!]
[Could the agent be amongst
these countless number of travelers?]
- Today...
- Running Man?
Running Man?
- Why are you suddenly mentioning Running Man?
- Do you have a bag? A bag?
[Asking everyone they run into
about the bag.]
Running... Running Man's bag?
Sticker?
No?
[Secret agent... where are you hiding?]
[The members starting to
feel a bit more anxious.]
[Ace Blank Ji]
[Discovers suspicious looking people?]
Excuse me...
Are you Korean?
- Running Man... bag?
- Sticker?
[Discovers the bag!]
You really are amazing, Ji Hyo!
Okay, thank you.
You guys aren't Koreans?
- No, we're not.
- I see. Thank you.
Thank you!
- Wait, what do we do with this?
- We need to take it with us over there.
We can just head over there first, right?
Where was it again?
- You don't even remember the name?
- Hudson? Was it the Hudson Bridge?
- Hey! Did you find it?
- What the heck?
Hey, where did you find it?
[After being the first to succeed,
Gary and Ji Hyo head to the city of Macau!]
[A crowd of fans to welcome them
at the airport entrance.]
[Such a warm and grateful greeting.]
[To the Fisherman's Wharf!]
Where do we go?
[Heading straight to the taxi
to get them on their way!]
Mr. Driver... can you take
us to the Fisherman's Wharf?
- Fisherman's Wharf?
- Yes!
[Did he understand what was being said?]
Thank you.
Let's go!
[In the midst of all the warm welcome,
Gary and Ji Hyo are first to take off!]
No, no one's found it yet.
Ji Hyo, you really are amazing.
Secret... you're not, are you?
You're not?
Are you a secret agent?
[Could it be a bag?]
Do you have Running Man bag?
[Asking to see if he has the bag.]
- Running Man bag?
- Running Man bag.
Okay... okay, thank you.
[Jae Suk finds the bag!]
- How did you find it?
- I saw it over there.
[The same old story?
Easy Brothers not having any luck.]
Running Man bag?
[What a huge crowd for a city
where the population is only 600,000.]
I had no idea so many people
would show up.
Do you have...
- Running Man bag?
- Do you have?
- A Running Man bag?
- Running Man bag?
- What kind of a bag?
- I don't know.
- It's a bag. Silver... silver.
Silver?
Like this?
Yes!
[Secret agent!]
[Finally discovers the bag!]
- Let's go.
- Suk Jin!
[Easy Brothers also head off to
the Fisherman's Wharf as the final team!]
[Wow! A huge welcoming crowd!]
[A giraffe costume?]
Lee Kwang Soo!
[Fascinating turn of events? Who knew
Kwang Soo would be so popular here?]
[Giraffe riding high off their energy!]
[Giraffe's fan club]
Wow... Kwang Soo,
you're the best overseas!
- Thank you.
- Thank you, Macau.
I love you, Macau!
I'm going to win today.
I'm going to win for my fans in Macau.
Macau-Man...
for my fans in Macau.
- What's Macau-Man?
- Would it be Fisherman-Man?
[Las Vegas of the Orient... Macau!]
[Asia's little Europe]
[A place with bright neon signs...]
[And 30 different countries'
world cultural heritage sites coexist!]
[This is where
Running Man's Asia Race will start!]
[Macau Airport- Fisherman's Wharf]
It's beautiful here.
Yes, it is.
[The driver is kindly explaining
the scenery to them.]
He's talking about the casino.
We're here to shoot 'Running Man'.
I only have 50,000 won to
my name right now.
- What is this?
- Can we look at this right now?
Should we take a look?
[Opening up the bag they received
from the secret agent.]
[It's locked!]
Having to do a mission the moment
we land is really discombobulating.
I feel like we're being thrown into a race
from the moment we set foot.
I know. I'm getting the same feeling as
when Chu Sung Hoon was on recently.
[Fisherman's Wharf]
There it is.
[Discovers the Running Man flag.]
- What do we call that?
- That... Running Man Flag.
I'm sure he understands.
- Thank you.
- Thank you, Sir!
[Gary and Blank Ji are currently
in the lead.]
[Fans are also here to greet them.]
We sincerely welcome you to Macau.
Here is your first mission.
[Their first mission in
long-awaited Macau is...]
[Find the person who holds the key
to your locked bag.]
- We have to find another person?
- From where? Where do we start the search?
Starting from this spot
to the end of the street.
[From the entrance all the way
down to the end of the street.]
[A gigantic outdoor park where shopping malls
and restaurants line up and down the street.]
[They must find the person who holds
the key to their bag in this location!]
We have to start running again.
- We're in first place. No need to rush.
- This is no time to relax.
- This isn't like you.
- But we're in first place.
Do you have a key?
A key?
Key?
[Could this young lady resting on
the bench have the key?]
- Key?
- Maybe she has it!
[Did they already find their key?]
[Are Gary and Blank Ji on a roll today?]
Big!
Very big size!
I want a small size!
Why are you playing with me?
[A master of Konglish...]
Thank you.
- Stop right here.
- Gary's already here.
Thank you.
You're so very kind.
[Same as the other team,
Off they go to find their key!]
- Hello!
- Key? Key?
Key?
- The streets are so beautiful!
- They really are.
This place is so romantic.
[A beautiful and secluded spot
next to the ocean...]
[Full of lovers]
- Want to grab a cup of coffee?
- Americano? Iced Americano?
What is this place?
[Just then,
something catches Blank Ji's eyes.]
- Excuse me.
- Jewelry.
Gary!
[None other than the epitome of
any woman's fantasy, a jewelry shop!]
- Ji Hyo, pick something out.
- This is a diamond!
[Her eyes are already fixed
on something.]
- Can you buy me one of these?
- Yeah, okay.
How much is this?
In Hong Kong currency,
it's 184,000...
184,000...
184,000 won?
Did you say, 184,000 won?
- In Hong Kong currency.
- Oh, 184,000 won in Hong Kong currency?
[Converted into Korean currency, it's...]
2.8 million won!
- This one is three carats.
- Three carats?
- You're really good at speaking Korean.
- Do you by any chance have a key for this?
[Key to the bag?]
- We need a key right now.
- We need to open up this bag.
If you have the key,
can you give it to us?
- How do we say this in English?
- I don't know.
You don't know?
Okay, thank you.
This... keep it, okay?
Kang Gary, okay?
Keep this name, Kang Gary.
- Kang.... Mr. Kang.
- Yes, for Ji Hyo.
[Macau's lovers fitting right into
each other's grooves.]
- I wonder if anyone's found it yet?
- Is it not in here?
[But anyway... where's the key?]
Key? Key?
That's her personal key!
I'm getting a feeling, a feeling...
The sunglasses... sunglasses.
He's wearing sunglasses like in the movies.
Excuse me, excuse me.
- Do you have a key?
[Key?]
- CEO...
- You're so handsome.
You know in those foreign films,
you see a CEO walking around like that?
- You look like a CEO.
- He looks like that.
CEO style.
He's so cool.
- He has... three building and helicopters.
- Wow... with the phone and the sunglasses...
- With a ship and sports cars... wow...
- I'm going to do that when I go back.
I'm really going to do that when I go back.
[Even the hairstyle?]
[Asia's Prince arrives.]
- Key?
- Do you have a key?
[Draws in the most popularity even here.]
- Pil!
-Chok! Cross!
[Their mood is totally uplifted.]
We are easy...
[Huh?]
[They're not really going to break out
with this song...]
[The song their 'Teacher' JYP created
for them last year... 'The Easy' song!]
[Come on... they can't know this...]
[What? They know this song?]
- I know! JYP wrote that song!
- JYP!
- You know everything!
- How did you know that?
Can I sing it with you?
[By request, starts singing, 'It's Easy'.]
[Seriously... of all the songs,
it had to be this one?]
Pil- Chok- Cross!
- Thank you.
- You're awesome!
Macau is awesome!
I love Macau!
[Just then, when Kwang Soo is
feeling overwhelmed with joy...]
[From the other side,
Jae Suk is moving in.]
Where are they all...
Where are you all going?
- Where are they going?
- Don't go!
Where are you going?
- Where are you going?
- Why are you asking me who's out there?
- Don't go!
- It's Yoo Jae Suk!
It's someone who just looks
like Yoo Jae Suk!
He just looks like Yoo Jae Suk!
Are they all running because
they saw Yoo Jae Suk?
[Their five minutes of fame is over
before it really even takes flight.]
Hey, baby...
[Trying out 'Pil-Chok-Cross'
on the little girl heading his way?]
[Asian Prince's popularity crashes.]
Everyone looks so busy.
[On the other hand...]
This is great weather.
[A laid back tourist?]
[A rather tall gentleman...]
[A somewhat suspicious looking man...]
I have no idea what's what around here.
[And...]
I can see Gary!
[A mysterious woman, avoiding Gary...]
[Who are these people?]
Why don't we ask this person?
- Excuse me.
- Excuse me...
- Do you have a...
- I need a key.
- I don't know.
- No?
[He says he doesn't have a key...]
- You liar! You liar...
- Come on, let us try it out!
Wait, wait... sorry.
[Tries to open the lock]
You are not a liar.
I'm the liar.
How are we going to find the key?
I'm sure there are some suspicious
people walking around here.
[That suspicious person...]
[That suspicious person...
is inside this flower bed.]
[Oh... the gardener is coming...]
The man... the man is
spraying me with the water.
Who's that?
Look over there.
[Caught!]
Who's that?
Who are you?
Who is that?
[Catch her!]
[Chasing after the mysterious woman!]
Huh?
They're chasing someone!
Who?
Who is that?
[Jae Suk is right on her tail!]
Excuse me!
[That woman is none other than...]
- Hey!
- Am I right?
- It's Hye Jin!
- Hye Jin!
- What are you doing here?
- See? I thought it was her!
Hye Jin, what are you doing here?
[Actress, Han Hye Jin]
[True beauty that can't be kept hidden
behind a simple disguise.]
[Does she have the key?]
- Where's the key?
- The key?
Key?
- What to do? Everyone's here!
- Hello.
[Easy Brothers also arrive on scene.]
When did you get here?
- How did you get here?
- Why don't we go this way?
Hye Jin, come this way.
[Taking Hye Jin away?]
Hye Jin, when did you get here?
[So that's what it was... it's a guest!]
[A suspicious looking man walking around
looking very much at ease.]
- Suk Jin, we have to find it.
- A guest has our key.
- Suk Jin, we have to find a guest.
- Is it okay to be caught so soon?
- It's okay.
Sit here.
Sit down.
- Okay... give us the key.
- Okay, healing camp...
Hye Jin used to be on that with us.
This is 'Healing Camp', the Macau edition.
[Macau edition?]
- Give us the key.
- The key?
The key...
- Are you two on the same team?
- Yes, we are. Look at our color.
- Now, the three of us are the same team.
- Oh, really?
[She does have the key!]
Then I bet there are other guests here
other than Hye Jin.
[This person.]
[Traipsing all over Fisherman's Wharf.]
[Guest... guest...]
Where are you going?
[There you are!]
[Long-legged Giraffe on the chase!]
Suk Jin!
[An unbeatable focus...]
I'm coming!
[Finally gets the lock to open.]
[A mission envelope?]
It's a mission card.
[The team with the bag and the person
who provides them with the key are a team.]
[Go find Gladiator Go Dong Wan
at the Coliseum.]
[But you have to take your guest
in the lady chair.]
[Automatically breaking out into a clap
at the mention of a lady chair?]
- But it's okay since Hye Jin is light.
- We're so lucky that we found her.
Even from a quick glance,
I can tell Hye Jin is light.
Wait!
- Suk Jin!
- Who is that?
[On a full out chase...]
- Wait!
- Catch him!
Wait!
[Who is this person with
a surprising level of stamina?]
[Total exhaustion.]
[Blank Ji and Gary who don't have a clue
as to what's going on yet.]
Do you have a key?
To this bag?
Dong Wook, what are you doing here?
[Dong Wook...
just falls right into their laps!]
[Actor, Lee Dong Wook.]
[Now a familiar face in the variety land...
he is also a guest of the day!]
I'm sorry.
I guess we got lucky running into you.
We just stopped in here to ask
a question ourselves.
Do you have the key?
[Easily hands over the key...]
- Thank you, Dong Wook!
- I'll buy you a cup of coffee!
- I already had some.
- You already had some?
- Then how about a cold glass of tea?
- No, it's okay.
- Water will be fine.
- Do you have any citron tea?
Dong Wook's actually close friends with
all of my hip hop friends.
[Exchanging rap verses]
[Starting out by exchanging rap verses out
of their excitement of seeing each other.]
[Checking their mission card after
having opened the bag.]
[The team with the bag and the person who
provided them with the key are now a team.]
[Go see Gladiator Go Dong Wan
at the Coliseum.]
[But, you have to carry your guest
in a lady chair...]
Okay, thank you.
- We won't know until we try it first.
- Why? You've done this a lot in your past?
Here's our chair.
Hye Jin, get on.
- I'm pretty heavy.
- No, it's okay.
- Wow...
- You really are kind of heavy.
I don't think we thought that one through.
Where are you keeping the weight?
[Stretching out their muscles first.]
There's some difference in what we were
expecting as far as her weight goes.
- There's some difference.
- I didn't think...
- You're heavier than I expected.
- My back really is...
[Giving the chair another try.]
- Towards the front.
- I feel bad.
- No, it's okay.
- It's okay.
But you could've sat down
from the front.
[Still not getting the hang of it.]
You could've come up to the front and sat
down but you're going about it backwards.
Since it's all about trial and error,
let's give it another try.
This is all about trial and error.
[How will this time go?]
The good thing is,
the coliseum is right ahead.
- Really?
- That is such a relief.
- I'm trying to stay tensed up.
- Just sit comfortably.
- Comfortably?
- No, no... not that.
- No, no... not that. Please.
Hye Jin, not that.
I don't think that'll work.
A little to the back.
- To the back?
- Yes.
- I think you need to straighten up a little.
- Was I being a little too sexy?
Was I being a little too sexy?
[Shocks them with her blunt mentality.]
One, two, three.
Wait, wait...
Your mentality really is...
it's a little on the wild side.
- Her mentality is like Sa Yeon's.
- You're a little strong.
Her mentality isn't your norm.
[Not even the slightest bit prudish.
Rather brute and straight forward.]
She doesn't even act flustered,
but says, 'Was I being too sexy?'
Are you trying to be a sexy woman?
Hye Jin... I don't think we have to
worry about our communication here.
- Okay.
- And she says, okay!
[Befitting of Queen of talk shows,
she has plenty of confidence!]
From the front.
- From here? That's too far.
- We have to start from here.
[This team is also trying to get started
by giving their guest a ride in their chair.]
Wow... look at how big his feet are!
- He's really tall too.
- He's tall with big feet.
He just has a nice body.
Ji Hyo, on the count of three.
One, two, three!
Right... head to the right!
- Right.
- To the right!
[This is Blank Ji's power!]
- To the right.
- To the right! To the right!
[To the Coliseum!]
One, two, three!
[Who will be the team to take over the
opening mission of the Asia Race?]
[Coliseum]
[A sword?]
[Gladiator Dong Wan]
[And a sword?]
[Yellow Team arrives first.]
[Jae Suk and Haroro's lady chair
having struggled to come the distance...]
You worked hard.
[Worrying more for him since
he's still a newlywed?]
You guys will have an advantage
for having come in at first place.
[Their advantage for coming in
at first place is...]
This is none other than...
the first sword that will off the race.
[The first sword]
[In that case...]
[Huh?]
What are you normally like?
I'm getting really curious.
- Since we have to be on the same team.
- I can tell you're really blunt.
[Full of curiosity... and not very cautious.]
She's very blunt.
She doesn't hold much back.
- Standing next to her...
- Who would think to do what she did?
- On a show like this.
- To think to do that...
- Ji Hyo! We can do this!
- Coliseum is straight ahead.
- Over there... Ji Hyo...
- Coliseum is right up front.
We can do this!
Ji Hyo, just hold on a little longer!
- If this is too much, I can get off.
- No, it's okay.
Song Ji Hyo!
You're better than any other man!
[Ji Hyo... better than any
other two men combined.]
- Ji Hyo... you're not to be messed with.
- Just a little bit more.
- Look, it's Dong Wook.
- Wow...
[Even the Easy Brothers having
wasted their efforts arrives on site.]
- Where do we have to go?
- This will now be your team members.
- This is going to be insane.
- This is all over.
Since the game isn't just for the day,
your team members can change at some point.
- Team members can change?
- Really?
There can be a variety of things
that may happen.
As you may already be aware,
I can't tell you how and what may happen.
- Yes, we're very well aware.
- Just give it your best at each game.
Isn't that the fun of Running Man?
Why are you speaking like that?
[Is this Hye Jin's style?
A very straightforward reaction.]
- Seriously... Hye Jin's is no joke.
- I couldn't help you out with that one.
The name of the mission that
you will have to carry out is...
The secret of the nine swords.
[The secret of the nine swords]
Please show everyone the sword.
[This is the first sword.]
- There's a number on it.
- Yes, this is one.
- This isn't sharp. It's fake.
- Is there one through nine then?
Along with the sword you've
just seen...
the nine swords are now scattered throughout
Asia for a reason unknown to us.
- Asia?
- Throughout Asia?
Not just Macau, but Asia?
[In order to find all nine swords
that have been separated...]
[Running Man will start their path
down the expansive journey.]
[The team to gather all nine of the swords
in their possession is the ultimate winner.]
- I will tell you your next mission location.
- Where is it?
- Macau Tower.
- I saw that earlier.
This is where your next mission
is going to take place.
Wait a minute...
[If it's the Macau Tower...]
I heard that bungee jumping off of
Macau Tower is the tallest in the world.
- To do that, you have a sign a waiver.
- What waiver?
- And I heard they give you a black shirt.
- Why?
Because in China,
black symbolizes death.
- Hey!
- What are you saying right now?
[Saying such a thing so casually...]
I'm just telling you what I've heard.
No, this is just what I heard.
[They can't expect us to do
that bungee jump?]
[The shock]
[The terror]
Get yourself together!
[The tallest bungee jump in
the world at 233m.]
[Off to Macau Tower.]
Kwang Soo is really popular.
Kwang Soo...
[Do they find him fascinating?]
[Asian Prince's popularity
gaining momentum once again.]
[Intoxicated by the popularity.]
[Ah... were they laughing at him?]
Kwang Soo...
you're really popular overseas.
[Giraffe, totally intoxicated by
the level of his popularity.]
Kwang Soo is like
the Prince of the southeast.
They're saying that he's the
Prince of Asia right now.
Kwang Soo's the Prince of Asia.
[Something that they never even
dreamed of in the past.]
- Look at all these adorable teenagers.
- They're so cute.
You guys are like their Idols.
- Where?
- Macau Tower... Macau Tower, please.
[Through the streets of Macau-
Off to Macau Tower!]
Ji Hyo, you and Dong Wook
are the same age.
- Born in '81.
- Oh, '81?
- I knew that.
- Then let's lower our speech.
Dong Wook... Dong Wook!
- This is a little embarrassing.
- It really is embarrassing.
I hope that we can laugh over this...
and build some good memories
in Macau.
Running Man, Macau.
[Countless number of fans
in this location too!]
[Flabbergasted by yet another crowd
of fans gathered to greet them.]
Why are there so many people here?
- What is this?
- Oh my gosh!
[This is none other than...
The Macau Tower!]
[Tower's height: 338m]
[Macau's most famous landmark!]
[Just as it boasts...
an unbelievable height!]
[No matter where one is in Macau,
the tower can be seen from anywhere!]
- What is this?
- Oh my gosh!
[Looking up at it from the ground
is enough to make them shudder.]
- We're not expected to climb up there?
- This is just absurd.
Hye Jin, take a look at this.
This isn't right.
How are we supposed to get up there?
Jae Suk, what is that?
[The world's tallest bungee jump!]
No, no way.
Don't even look at that.
[Just looking up at the height is enough
to make their mouth drop open in wonder.]
- What is this?
- That's way too high.
We have to bungee jump?
Look at that!
[Half excitement, half fear.]
- No way!
- Look at that over there.
- Look at how sweaty your hands are getting!
- Are you going to jump?
- Are you nervous because you're jumping?
- No, no way.
Are your ears popping too?
[It's so high up
that even their ears are popping.]
[61st floor at 233m-
Arriving at the observation deck.]
There is no way.
- This is seriously...
- Jae Suk, you're not going to, are you?
- Of course, I'm not!
- What are you wearing right now?
Why are you wearing that right now?
[What's the mission that awaits them here?]
[Choose one of the following
for your next mission...]
[No exclusions for the
two-man team either.]
- This is it?
- It's a very simple mission.
You have to correctly guess the
three letter word.
[A letter will be earned for each of the
three missions that are completed.]
[You succeed once all three of the missions are
completed and all three letters are combined.]
But why are you wearing that?
I'll show you the mission menu.
[Sky jump, sky walk, mast climb.]
[The sheer absurdity of it makes
her break out in laughter.]
This really isn't right.
Would you like to see a video clip?
Is this the sky walk?
No, it's the sky jump?
[Menu one - Sky jump]
[The tallest bungee jump in
the world at 233m.]
And while you're dropping to the ground,
you must look at the letter down below.
- What?
- We have to look at something too?
[Menu two - Sky walk]
[A breezy walk around the building at 233!]
When you walk around the perimeter,
you're going to be able to see a letter.
[Must collect one character at a time around
the building to put together the letter.]
This is ridiculous!
[Menu three - Mast climbing]
[Climbing up the ladder to reach
the tippy top of the tower!]
[And as guessed, must climb all the way
to the top to earn one of the letters!]
[Must complete all three menus...
to complete the word and succeed the mission!]
[Today's Running Man...]
[Flying through the sky
to their heart's content!]
The ladder?
I want to go home.
There's no way.
How are we supposed to do this?
You have to make your selection.
What if we don't see the letter
after we make the jump?
Then you'd have to do it again.
[If you can't decipher the letter after
making the jump, then must jump again.]
This is absolutely ridiculous.
Our PD, Lee Sae Young made
the jump yesterday.
- You must be seriously crazy.
- Seriously?
Are you even sane?
[PD Lee Sae Young having tested out
the mission personally the day before.]
It's fun.
As you can see, I'm still alive.
- How can this be any fun?
- Your face has gotten really weird.
- What are you talking about?
- Your face looks much flatter.
- I think you must've lost your mind a little.
- Your mouth looks all twisted around now.
I think I can do the skywalk.
- I think I can do the skywalk too.
- I think I can too.
[Skywalk seems the easiest?]
[If you take it too easily,
you're going to hurt your big nose...]
[The urgent thing to do at the moment
is to figure out who's going to do what.]
[The problem is,
all the missions seem just as difficult.]
- Climbing the ladder, or walking around...
- This really is...
I have such phobia of heights.
Even jumping off of 100m...
I really thought it was never going to end.
I thought I was going to pass out.
Let's not do the sky jump.
Let's do the other two of climbing up and
walking around the perimeter.
We can guess the word by
obtaining two of the letters.
- That's the only thing we can do.
- I'm sorry, but I can't do more than that.
I'd gather up the courage to do it if I could,
but this really is...
Then I'll try doing the skywalk first.
- I'll try that first.
- You will, Hye Jin?
[The bravest person on their team.]
You can bungee jump,
can't you, Dong Wook?
- You can bungee jump, can't you?
- I can't do that.
- Dong Wook, that's really unexpected.
- I really can't do things like this.
You're supposed to be cool
and show us how it's done.
I'm an entertainer!
- You're an actor!
- I got awarded Rookie of the Year by SBS!
But you're an actor!
Lee Dong Wook...
They're all so scary!
I all of a sudden have the
urge to go poo.
- Me too... I feel like that too.
- My stomach hurts!
What the heck is this?
I'm so scared!
I don't think I can do any of it!
Why did I come here?
- I'll do the skywalk, and you bungee jump.
- I can't do that. I can't bungee jump.
- Suk Jin, that's not it...
- I'll do the skywalk and the climbing...
- And you can bungee jump.
- No, I'll do the other two.
- I really can't bungee jump.
- I can't do it either. You think I can?
Feel how hard my heart is beating.
[The men on the Green Team's hearts are
beating like the runaway train.]
Get yourself together!
- This is just a bad dream.
- This is no time for you to be like this.
I'm so glad I'm just a guest.
How about we just guess
what the three letters are?
Answer!
Running Man!
- Macau!
- How about you do the skywalk ten times?
Would you rather walk the skywalk
ten times or bungee jump once?
I'll walk the skywalk ten times.
Why are you seriously being like this?
Get yourself together!
Get yourself together.
What's wrong with you?
Seriously?
[Will it...]
[be even feasible to
complete the mission today?]
[Haroro, having requested the skywalk,
gets fitted for his safety gear.]
Check again, check again.
Kwang Soo, seriously...
[Yellow Team's Jae Suk and
Blue Team's Kwang Soo climbing the mast.]
[Skywalker, Hye Jin,
still feeling pretty steady.]
[It's not as though he can make the
only girl on the team, Ji Hyo to do it...]
[And I don't have the guts to
jump myself...]
Seriously though...
[His psyche is taking a vacation
elsewhere...]
This isn't the time for you to
be spacing out like this right now.
Why do I feel so sleepy?
Skywalk?
[Gary of the Green Team chooses skywalk.
What of the other two members?]
What about the climbing...
you think you can do it?
I'll do the bungee jump.
I'll bungee jump.
[Huh? What did you say?]
[What? Dong Wook
volunteers to bungee jump?]
I'll bungee jump.
I'll do it.
You're going to be fine once
you relax a bit.
[Green Team's Lee Dong Wook offers to
do the 233m bungee jump.]
You're going to do the jump?
[Immediately becomes big news.]
[Very cool, Lee Dong Wook.]
- Dong Wook...
- Lee Dong Wook!
Lee Dong Wook!
[Even the other team members can't help
but cheer him on and encourage him.]
That's so very cool.
- How much does he weigh?
- 42 kg.
- You don't have to shout that out loud.
- You look like you're out of it.
You look like you're only here physically.
[A chance no one could've predicted!
Will Dong Wook really be able to jump?]
I have to climb up even higher than this?
This isn't the top?
Kwang Soo...
Jae Suk... this isn't the top.
Jae Suk, stay strong.
[Need to climb much higher than
the 61st floor observation deck.]
[Where's the end...]
Kwang Soo,
I'll see you when you get back.
[Already gasping for breath after
having climbed up one floor.]
The ladder is perfectly perpendicular.
[Ji Hyo reacting as though she's just
seen something very impressive.]
- Don't go, don't go!
- Don't go!
Don't go out there!
- What is this? Ji Hyo!
- What are you doing? Don't go out there!
[The two men keep throwing a fit!]
- Come here... come back here!
- It's just landing over here.
- Come here.
- Hurry up and come back here!
- Just come back here!
- Come on!
- Come here!
[What's wrong with them?]
[These two are having problems with
just standing where they're at.]
- Kwang Soo...
- What have I ever done to deserve this?
What is the big deal about
the three letter word?
[On the other hand,
on top of the observation deck...]
[Ha Ha and Hye Jin of the Yellow Team
head out on the skywalk.]
[This is... what you call an aerial walk.]
[The thrill of walking on the catwalk
atop 233m in the air!]
Hye Jin, walk slow.
The problem is...
[Hye Jin walking with confidence and ease.]
[And Ro-Ro walking as though
he's walking towards his death.]
- I'll keep an eye on you, so keep walking.
- Okay.
Mommy...
[Just walking alone is hard enough,
but have to collect all the characters too...]
Hye Jin... wait.
Hye Jin, I'm sorry.
I really do respect you tremendously.
[Haroro looks as though he may even faint
if he doesn't at least hold onto her hand.]
[But just where are these letters?]
It's a miracle in itself
that I'm walking right now.
I'm sorry to say that I'm normally
scared of a lot of things.
I was born a scaredy cat... please!
Hye Jin!
Even though I really like you,
I can really get mad at you!
Don't ever do that to me again.
Seriously!
- I'm serious. You have to promise me.
- Okay, okay.
- Are you looking for the letters?
- I'm looking, but I don't see anything.
I really can't look around right now.
- Look over there.
- I can't look.
[Even though they've been around half the
perimeter, still nothing in their sight?]
Why don't I see anything?
I really want to walk like a man too.
I wish I can walk around like a man.
[Relying on the support of a woman's
hand like a real man.]
[Just where are the letters?]
- I think I might faint.
- Why don't I see anything?
I think we've walked around a full circle,
but we haven't found anything.
- We've already walked a full circle?
- Yes.
- But how is it that we didn't find anything?
- We need to find it quickly.
[It seems as though they've missed it
during their first round out of fear.]
The letters must be really small.
I wonder if it's written on the floor?
- Hye Jin, you're not scared?
- No, I'm not.
- I think you're going to have to do it again.
- Okay.
Really? You'll do it?
I don't see it.
Where is it?
Can I walk around one more time?
No, no... I can't.
Let's get back inside.
[Green Team's Dong Wook,
moving to the bungee jump diving board.]
I love you, Dong Wook.
- Are you going to jump right now?
- I'm here, but not sure if I can do it.
Wow, you're awesome.
- Wow, that's awesome.
- Fighting.
Running and jump?
And don't stop?
[After saying it out loud,
the visualization of it makes him panic.]
- Wait, wait, wait...
- He just has to jump now?
[Going back and forth on his decision
every five seconds.]
This is really scary.
Fighting!
You can do it, Dong Wook!
[Everyone is cheering Dong Wook on
regardless of which team he's on!]
- You're burdening me. Stop it.
- Okay, we'll stop.
[Okay... he is standing on the platform...]
Okay, just jump as far out
as you can.
[Empty... the mind...]
- Set... go...
- Wait... wait...
[Calls for a halt
as soon as the countdown starts.]
- Slow... let's take this slow.
- My legs are shaking.
He's really frightened right now.
- That has to be scary.
- I'm sure he's scared.
You can do it!
Lee Dong Woo, fighting.
Lee Dong Wook, fighting!
Okay.
[Dong Wook completes
his preparation for the jump!]
Look at the walls of the building as you jump.
You'll see letters written on it.
What... what did you say?
Are you ready?
Yes.
[Completes the preparation to jump once
more after having calmed himself down!]
[Countdown]
[Calls for a halt once again.]
I seriously understand.
[Will be really be able to jump?]
[I don't want to regret not jumping...]
- Go!
- Okay!
[Countdown]
[In the midst of all their encouragement...]
[Dong Wook, taking on the challenge of the
tallest bungee jump in the world at 233m!]
Fighting!
Running Man, fighting!
[Up in the air at 233m...
I throw myself into the sky...]
[Very first bungee jump
experience of my life...]
[The fact of 233m being the highest
in the world isn't what's important...]
[But the satisfaction of knowing
that I won against my own fear...]
This is amazing.
[A scenery that the onlookers
are having a tough time believing.]
[Dong Wook succeeds at the tallest
bungee jump in the world at 233m!]
Where's the letter?
[Oh?]
[He discovers the letter!]
'Na'? What does 'Na' stand for?
'Na'?
[Green Team succeeds in obtaining
one of the three letters!]
[An enthusiastic welcome by the local fans
to uplift his spirits!]
[I did it!]
[Envious...]
Awesome...
that was so cool... so cool.
[A bow in thanks to the fans
for their encouragement.]
[And up in the observation deck,
they can keep watch through the screen.]
Dong Wook, you're the best!
Why do I suddenly feel like a loser?
[Even though that was awesome,
I still can't do it...]
[On the other hand,
as for the mast climbers...]
[Ace Ji Hyo is the only one who
keeps on climbing up without any hesitation.]
I'll just call you 'Sis' from now on
since you're more courageous than I.
And I'll call you 'Mom'.
But this is much harder than I expected.
[With each floor that they climb up,
Kwang Soo and Jae Suk screams out in fear.]
Why do you keep screaming, Jae Suk?
You still have a long ways to go.
Kwang Soo, I'm seriously...
so scared!
[Kwang Soo is in a trance like state
with his eyes fixed straight forward.]
Jae Suk...
I feel like I'm going to lose my mind.
Where is the top?
[Still a long ways to go...]
Jae Suk, I...
I just...
- Can I just do something else?
- What else are you going to do?
You're not going to say
bungee jump, are you?
Ji Hyo, this is better.
Even if this is tiring, this is still better.
Jae Suk, I'm getting so drowsy
right now.
I think bungee humping would be better.
Just get it over with in one jump.
[Unable to comprehend.]
I'm going to end it in one shot,
so let's you and I make a deal.
What kind of a deal?
None of your team members are
going to jump anyway, right?
- But you still need the bungee letter.
- Yes, I need it.
[Exchange bungee letter for
the mast letter.]
I'll take that deal.
[Sensing the attractiveness of the deal,
they're competing for the contract.]
I'll use this helmet somehow
to notify you of what's going on.
- Then, I'll just...
- Okay, go on down.
I'm going to go down and
see how you two handle it.
- I promise to work hard and get it done.
- I will do whatever it takes.
- Don't worry about a thing.
- You promise?
- Yes, of course.
- Really?
Are you sure you can
handle the bungee?
If anything, I'm seriously
about to fall asleep right now.
You really are something else.
People may say whatever about Jong Kook,
but you really are the best.
You really are the top dog here.
[At the same time, Gary of the
Green Team is walking the skywalk.]
I really hope I find it on my first try.
[After having tried the skywalk himself,
realizes just how high up he really is.]
Oh? What's that?
What's that?
[Huh? What is that piece of
paper up there?]
Even if I jump,
I don't think I can reach that.
Gary, you can do it.
You can do it!
[Having transformed into a preacher
of self-confidence after his bungee jump.]
Try jumping.
What the heck am I doing out here?
[100% sympathetic of his situation.]
It's really scary out there.
[Trying the jump one more time.]
Two...
- It's like he's bungee jumping.
- Look at how scared...
[Too bad...]
I can't reach it!
This is up way too high!
Don't move!
Just stay right there!
[Oh! He did it!]
I got it, I got it.
[The piece of paper shows...]
[the character, 'Ae'!]
[Green Team earns a character
from the skywalk!]
[Now, he has to find the other character
to complete the letter.]
Wow...
We're up really high!
I've always wanted to live up high...
but I like the ground.
Human beings need to live with
their feet planted on the ground.
I don't think this is right.
[Checks below the catwalk.]
[A piece of paper?]
[There it is!
A piece of paper hanging off the rail!]
[He can see it, but how is he...]
[Life sure isn't easy...]
[Trying to ease away his fears
by forcing himself to sing.]
[Gary succeeds in getting the
piece of paper!]
[And on this piece of paper...
'sae' is written on it!]
I found it... I found it!
I came so that I may have you!
Goodbye!
Wait... what were they again?
Remember.
[Discovered two characters
to make up a letter.]
[Green Team discovered the letter,
'Sae' out on the skywalk!]
[On the other hand,
up on the bungee jumping board...]
Are you ready?
- Are you ready?
- Yes.
[Totally blas Ace
without even a trace of nervousness.]
Seriously... I'm seriously proud
to be on your team.
- We're not on the same team.
- The fact that we're both members of RM.
I feel proud too.
But if I can wish for something...
it would be that you at least
take the same amount of time that I did.
[If Ji Hyo jumps at once,
then Dong Wook won't look as cool...]
[Releasing the final safety clasp.]
- Just a moment...
- The helicam...
[The ease with which she waits for
the aircam to be ready to start filming.]
[The helicam finally arrives!]
[Helicam is ready to film Ji Hyo's jump!]
Song Ji Hyo!
[All her fans sending her extra bit
of courage through their cheering.]
[Ace Ji Hyo completes her preparation
for the jump!]
[Countdown]
[The only female member of Running Man,
and at the same time, Running Man's Ace!]
[She is... flying!]
[Ji Hyo takes flight!]
Ji Hyo!
[Without even
the slightest bit of hesitation...]
[Just jumps into the air.]
[Just enjoying the freedom the highest
bungee jump in the world has to offer.]
Wow! This is so much fun!
[Ace Ji Hyo, succeeds the
233m bungee jump!]
This is awesome!
[Even ten men combined together
can't compare to her!]
She really is amazing!
What an amazing woman!
[Verifies that 'Na' is the letter she'll trade
the other team for as per her agreement.]
Since she jumped at once like that...
I don't feel as good about my jump
as I did earlier.
- She really is something else.
- She's on a whole different scale.
[The first time is always the hardest.]
Blank Ji!
[She really is without a doubt...
our precious Ace...]
[At the same time...]
[One man without
a single thought in his head.]
[No, make that two men.]
[Both having been stuck in the same
position and spot for the past 20 minutes.]
I'm so scared right now.
[Will they... be able to see the letter?]
- She's back!
- Ji Hyo!
- Ji Hyo, are you okay?
- Was it fun?
- You weren't scared?
- It was so much fun!
- It was fun?
- It was totally fun!
The moment I started thinking it was
taking awhile to fall, it was over.
You really are something else.
But there was something that
I was reminded of at that moment.
I wondered if maybe I looked too
unattractive because I jumped too readily.
Actually, Dong Wook felt that way
because you made the jump look too easy.
Don't worry about things like that!
You were amazing.
What kind of a woman is this?
She really is worthy of my liking.
I am kind of curious...
[Huh?
Is Hye Jin showing some interest?]
Since a couple of people have jumped,
I bet it looks exciting.
Having watched them jump,
it's starting to look easier now.
- Decision time, decision time...
- It's really fun.
If you jump,
our team gets all three letters.
- Then you're going to do the other one?
- I'll get it done somehow, someway.
I'll seriously do it.
[Hm... should I?]
[A moment later]
This is scary.
- It's scarier if you hesitate.
- Just do it.
- But where's Ha Ha?
- He went off to do his mission.
[Went off to do the skywalk mission so that
he can accomplish something of his own.]
Just keep the eyes on the paper, and jump.
One, two, three.
Okay!
[Catching the piece of paper with 'Ae'
written on it in one try!]
I'm a man... I'm a man!
[Good for you...]
I'm not afraid!
I'm going to be a cool dad!
How in the world am I to do this?
[Ultimately gets down flat on his belly.]
[Automatically keeps
breaking down in sobs.]
Seo Young... got it!
I got it!
[Barely manages to succeed
in getting the paper!]
[Checks that the second character
is, 'Sae'.]
I'm so scared I'm going to fall off this!
Don't ever... don't ever do this again!
[Haroro having done his share of the work
for Hye Jin who's gone off to bungee jump.]
Hye Jin!
Hye Jin, I did it!
You did it?
Hye Jin, you're so cool!
Hye Jin, you're my hero!
Aren't you scared?
- I'm so scared!
- You can do it, Hye Jin!
Hye Jin, you're my hero!
You're the leader of 'healing camp',
and the icon of courage.
Open the door.
[Speaking in gibberish... doesn't
seem to be quite sane at the moment.]
Did you get it?
Did you get the letter?
Suk Jin... I'm serious when
I tell you this.
I only did it because I thought if I didn't,
I wouldn't be respected as a human being.
I had to do something since
Han Hye Jin is doing all this.
[Han Hye Jin's first bungee jump
attempt of her life!]
Han Hye Jin, fighting!
- Han Hye Jin, fighting!
- I'm so scared!
[I can't even ride the rollercoasters
at the amusement parks...]
[Will I be able to do the highest
bungee jump in the world?]
[Without any hesitation...
just trust in myself.]
[Her beautiful challenge...]
[The fear is only for a moment...]
[Even the toughest part only
lasts a moment...]
[And after that,
you're left with nothing but a smile.]
[All the men made to feel even smaller
with this turn of events.]
Amazing!
I'm so happy...
[Hye Jin succeeds at the
233m bungee jump!]
[And even verifies that the letter from
the bungee jump is 'Na'.]
Na?
That was fun.
[On the other hand, at the tippy top of
the tower where time has stood still.]
If you climb this ladder up to the top,
you'll see a blue piece of paper to the right.
If you scrape off the paper with a coin,
you'll see the letter underneath it.
So I'm going to give you the coin
you're going to be using right now.
Use this coin to scratch off the surface,
and come back down once you see the letter.
[The road just keeps on getting harder...]
You have to scratch off the surface
in order to see the letter.
[Is it really that necessary to
bite down on the coin like that?]
Be careful.
Jae Suk, are your eyes open?
Jae Suk.
Jae Suk...
Please...
[Discovers the letter, 'Doh'.]
[I... survived.]
[Now it's Kwang Soo's turn
from the Blue Team.]
Kwang Soo, you can't stop.
Just keep climbing.
Kwang Soo,
don't stop and keep going.
Kwang Soo...
[His face looks as if it's aged several years
during this mission.]
[Finally barely makes it up to the spot.]
[By using every ounce of energy
he possesses in his body...]
Why stick this up here upside down?
You can spit the coin back out now.
Did you both see the letter?
Yes, I saw it.
You don't need to go back up, right?
[That's not even funny...]
[Each teams starts to guess what
the three letter word is with their letters.]
- 'Na'... 'Na'.
- 'Na'?
I got 'Sae'.
What could it be?
[Blue Team mission one letter with there
only being two members to their team.]
Suk Jin, you can do this!
Suk Jin, Suk Jin...
'Sae'...
[Anyways, all three of the teams
completed the mission!]
[Blank...]
[The two mast climbers who took quite
some time to climb down from the top.]
Are you okay?
[Per their deal,
a mast letter for the bungee letter.]
[They must correctly guess the word
in order to gain the second dagger!]
I need to hear what it is.
Us too.
Did you hear what it is?
[As soon as the deal is made,
breaks out into a full powered run!]
[The first team to guess the word
correctly wins the dagger!]
[Green Team is the first to arrive!]
- Hurry!
- I need the correct answer.
[Jae Suk, without any energy to run.]
Everyone needs to get in line.
[What is the three letter word?]
- I found the letter, 'Sae' on the skywalk.
- Then the letter, 'Na' on the jump.
And... from the mast climb,
the letter, 'Doh'.
- But what's the word?
- We know what it is!
Senado.
Correct.
[The correct answer is,
'Senado Square' in Macau.]
[Green Team wins the
Macau Tower mission.]
[The second dagger goes to
the Green Team.]
This place... Senado Square.
We can just head over, right?
- Go!
- Okay!
- Senado Square.
- Is it Senado Square?
[Yellow Team is also cleared to go!]
I'll see you later, Kwang Soo.
It's Senado Square.
[At some point,
darkness comes finds its way over Macau]
- It's just a cylindrical barrel.
- Oh my goodness...
It's that thing over there!
Look at that thing!
See that thing on top?
[From here... and even higher.]
Where you see the disc is where you were,
and I had to climb up even higher to the top!
Where you see the twinkling light up top
is where I had to go!
Ha Ha, look over there.
Do you see the dotted lights up top?
- Yes, I see the light twinkling.
- That's where I had to go!
- That is just absurd...
- I seriously thought I was going insane.
I went all the way to the top
where you see the antenna.
While... no one is around to see it,
just cry and get it all out.
I was totally deceived!
Kwang Soo and I were totally deceived!
[In an attempt to avoid the height,
got dragged away to an even higher spot.]
You know those people who climb up those
heights with a smile on their faces?
You know how they have those
picture displayed on the walls?
They're all computer graphics.
I swear that they are.
[He can swear that they're edited?]
I'm positive they edited the smiling face
over these panicked looking people's faces.
So they just dragged the sides of the lips up
to make it look like they're smiling?
Not crying is the miracle.
If people don't cry from that, it's a miracle.
[Still sobbing]
[The sounds of Jae Suk's cries resonating
through Macau's night skies.]
Senado?
I wonder what we're going to do there?
Since it's supposed to be a square,
I'm sure it'll be a bigger place.
[What kind of a mission will
await them at this square?]
[Senado Square and its surroundings.]
[Macau's national heritage site as well as...]
[being the number one attraction in Macau
is famous for its jerky stalls.]
[And next to that is the beautiful
St. Paul's Cathedral.]
[What is the mission that awaits
them at this location?]
[On the other hand...]
[At Hong Kong International Airport...]
[Did someone just land?]
[Mr. Capable, Jong Kook.]
What are you doing here?
I can't believe that you're here.
[Kkuk having landed in Hong Kong...]
[He needs to start making his way
towards Macau...]
[But somehow, his fans are aware of his
arrival and scattered throughout the place.]
Bye, thank you.
[Have a safe trip to Macau!]
[And through the warm hospitality
of his Hong Kong fans...]
I'm to take that helicopter?
[Let's get you there quickly and
start shooting the show...]
[Boarding the helicopter.]
[Beautiful night skies of Hong Kong.]
Anyway...
I wonder how much they're all going to
tease me about my injured foot.
[No way for Mr. Capable to save
his face on that one!]
[Arriving in Macau in no time at all.]
[Fans are gathered here as well!]
[Wow... all of you are amazing!]
[Even worrying for the well-being of
Mr. Capable after seeing that he's injured...]
[Stay strong, Tiger!]
You didn't have to bring me any flowers!
You really didn't have to do that.
[It's because we really need to get you to
the site and start shooting quickly...]
There are two people who are
desperately awaiting your arrival.
- Two people?
- Yes, two people.
What do you mean, two people?
Why are there two people?
[Those two people are...]
[Easy Brothers...]
I love Thailand, Macau... and Hong Kong.
And China.
And Korea.
[Who could they be...]
[St. Paul Cathedral]
[Already a huge gathering of a crowd.]
[Members finally arrive at Senado.]
Are you all being careful with the
safekeeping of your daggers?
- Yes.
[This mission is...]
[Go find seven foreigners
who meet your conditions.]
[Go find seven people who can speak
the Korean language.]
Seven people?
Go find foreigners who are
taller than Ha Ha.
[Seven foreigners who are taller
than Ha Ha.]
- That's not going to be easy.
- That's way too easy!
[Everyone here?]
[Easy Brothers' mission is...]
[Find seven foreigners with
glasses on.]
[Start the mission!]
- Since there are only the two of you...
- Yes?
Before you go off to find
your foreigners...
[Before they go off on their search?]
- Are we going to be spies?
- No.
You're at a disadvantage since
there are only two of you, right?
We've pretty much been relegated to
coming in last all day today.
- I know.
- That's why...
There will be... one other person
who will be joining your team.
- That person is...
- Is it another guest?
That person will be carrying around
a bouquet of flowers.
We have to go find the person?
Go find the person who's carrying
around the bouquets of flowers.
[Find the person... who's carrying
around the bouquet of flowers.]
[We never said that it was a guest...]
I came on today determined to
make a love connection with someone.
[Then give it your best shot
with this person.]
Don't you think it'll be an Idol?
[Full of excited anticipation]
Bouquet of flowers...
[Carefully searching throughout the area...]
I don't see anyone.
[Someone carrying around
a bouquet of flowers...]
[Oh!]
[A bouquet of flowers]
[But, wait a minute...]
[Those familiar biceps...]
No way!
- No way!
- Jong Kook!
What took you so long to get here?
What took you so long, Jong Kook?
You didn't have to get all
dressed up for us!
Promise me that you'll never leave
us ever again!
You should've came earlier!
- Hey...
- Do you know how we've been treated?
- Why is it both of you?
- Promise me that you'll never leave again!
You're ours. We don't
have a single dagger right now.
- Then the three of us are a team?
- Hurry up and take this off! There's no time!
What are you doing!
[The moment they see Mr. Capable,
their sorrow of the day comes flooding in.]
- Your foot isn't injured, is it?
- Suk Jin, I'm sorry...
[Mr. Capable with an injured foot.]
- I'm sorry about this.
- We need to rethink this.
- You hurt your foot?
- It's just slightly uncomfortable.
Are you Mr. Kim Jong Kook?
It's very nice to meet you.
- I think we've got the wrong person.
- No, it's not that.
Suk Jin... Suk Jin, what are you doing?
You can't be like this!
The body isn't everything here.
Our minds have to be in sync as a team.
No, when it comes to you,
the body is everything.
- It's just very slightly uncomfortable.
- So you can still participate in the mission?
- Of course!
- Can I kick it to make sure?
- You can't kick my foot!
- Then can I step on it?
Don't do that!
[If you guys can't believe me...]
[I'm still Mr. Capable!]
[I'm Mr. Capable who ousted
Chu Sung Hoon!]
[I'm still alive...]
[Reverting back to revering in
his presence.]
- Hurry up and get this on him.
- I told you to believe me and that I'm fine.
[Easy Brothers immediately
becoming submissive.]
Seriously...
- Other teams each have a dagger right now...
- We don't have a dagger?
- No, we don't have one.
- What have you been doing? We need a dagger!
Hey... you have no idea how hard
we've both been trying!
People weren't even acknowledging us!
This is the first time we're being shown
on this broadcast on this episode right now.
[What are you talking about...]
Hello to all our viewers,
my name is Lee Kwang Soo.
We're in Macau.
We've been here all along too!
[From this moment on,
it's 'Kkuk-Easy Brothers'.]
They all look so tiny.
[Other team members busy
carrying out their mission at hand.]
- How long...
- Forget it. He's taller than you.
[Is it way too easy of a mission?]
- Follow me, follow me!
- Follow?
- Follow me!
- Follow!
[Easily finds three to four people
within moments.]
It's really nice here.
[Jerky market overflowing with tourists
regardless of the fact that it's evening.]
This market really is pretty.
- Anyone speak Korean?
- Does anyone know how to speak Korean?
- Our mission is way too hard.
- This is really tough.
You know kpop?
Listen... listen to me.
One, two, three, four.
Okay, okay... you?
[Huh?
That's a song by Leessang?]
- Okay... okay!
- We've already found five people.
We have to find foreigners
wearing glasses.
Can you stick this on my back?
[Wanting to play the name tag game!]
No, please don't mention it.
Thank you.
- I love you!
- Thank you.
- Wearing glasses...
- We have to find people with glasses.
- Hey!
- Do you see someone?
- She'll be perfect.
- Want to play a game with me?
- Okay.
- Okay, okay.
[Big-nosed language being understood
rather easily.]
- Where?
- The lady with the sign.
[Verifying their height]
[Everyone passes for being
taller than Ha Ha.]
- Come on!
- Let's go!
- Just a choo choo train.
[Off to the cathedral.]
[Quite a large crowd in the
area already.]
- Now that it's night, the atmosphere...
- Wow, it's killer.
[Thankful to all the fans for having
waited in a neat and orderly fashion.]
[Even a lady giraffe is in attendance.]
[The Green Team have also completed
gathering up all seven of their people.]
[Blue Team also completes gathering
up their seven people.]
[Kkuk especially receiving
a lot of love from the crowd.]
They really are all wearing glasses.
It's a tug of war.
[Three-way tug of war]
[Everyone's surprised after having
seen the rope lying on the ground.
[Another surprise after seeing
Mr. Capable in attendance.]
- Why did you come?
- What do you mean?
[Overabundance of excited welcome for
Kkuk, the latecomer.]
[Even though they're glad to see him, of all
things it has to be a tug-of-war mission!]
- Where have you been all day?
- You can't spring tug-of-war on us now!
[It's completely unknown as to who
the dagger will go to this time...]
[Each team with seven recruits
on their side.]
- Shouldn't we be testing them out?
- Okay, you can check it out.
- Who's your favorite Running Man member?
- You.
- Huh?
- Lee Kwang Soo.
Pass!
- Who's your favorite Running Man member?
- Not you. Gary...
Disqualified!
- Why? Why is he disqualified?
- Why?
[All three teams succeeded in bringing
seven recruits who meet their requirements.]
This mission...
is a tug-of-war.
[As predicted,
it's the tug-of-war mission.]
[Blue Team's confidence is flying high with
their warrior, Mr. Capable on their side.]
Why did Jong Kook have to
come on the show now?
As you can see,
it's a three way tug-of-war.
Each team may grasp one of the lines,
and pull it towards them...
Behind the last person on each team,
you'll all find that there's a bell attached.
You have to ring that bell
to win the game.
[Must ring the bell to win the game.]
Since we need someone strong to pull,
I'll stand up front.
- And Kwang Soo, you can go to the back.
- This is our Jong Kook right here!
You can formulate all the plans, Jong Kook.
Since Kwang Soo's tall,
he can go stand all the way at the back.
Suk Jin and I can stand up front,
and everyone else in the middle.
- Fighting!
- Pil chok cross!
- Guy...
- Everybody...
- Everybody... ah... fighting?
- Ah...
- Full power.
- Full power?
Believe my team...
I believe in my team.
[Captain Gary being received
by a round of applause.]
- Trust me.
- Okay!
- Okay, fighting...
- One, two, three, fighting!
The game starts the moment
you're all up.
[The team that wins two out of three
wins the game.]
[We're on the winning team's side!]
Ready...
Set...
[Who will be the winner of tug-of-war which
will determine who'll get the third dagger?]
[If the person at the end rings the bell,
then that team wins the round.]
[The end of the line where even finding
the balance is a difficult task.]
[Screaming... with their teeth gritted...]
[A victory that's not so
easy to acquire...]
[The war gets more and more
prolonged...]
[The bell!]
[The bell is just barely out of his reach!]
[Just then...]
[Yellow Team's Ha Ha is almost at the bell!]
[Not easy even for
the Giraffe with his long arms.]
[Will Haroro ultimately be the one?]
[What a loss...]
[Everyone doing their best without any
knowledge of what's going on in the back!]
[Just a little bit more...]
[Yellow Team wins!]
[Could it be the power of the team members
who are all taller than Ha Ha?]
[In the midst of the enthusiastic cheers,
the first victory goes to the Yellow Team!]
[Encouraging his team members
for fighting hard during the battle.]
I was this far away.
[Time to formulate a battle plan.]
[Suggesting they match their beats
to pull at a faster rate.]
[Even though they can't communicate as
easily, their desire to win is all the same.]
Suk Jin, why don't you go to the back?
I think we'll be able to work
better that way.
[Prepare for the second round.]
Are you sure this plan is a good one?
Leaving this big gap like this?
[Blue Team using extreme measures.]
[Giraffe wave...]
[Cheers and battle cry that can be
heard all throughout Macau.]
[Ready]
[Start]
[Will Yellow Team pull off another victory?]
[Or will the victory go to another team?]
[The tail for the Yellow Team
is once again, Haroro.]
[Green Team's tail, Dong Wook.]
[Power up, short little arm!]
[Staying tight in all three directions.]
[Unable to make any advances.]
[Injured Mr. Capable]
[Just a little bit more!]
[It's Haroro once again!]
[Will the victory be theirs?]
[Almost!]
[Yellow Team wins two out of three!]
[Yellow Team's unbelievable winning streak.]
[A victory that could only be won
by having worked together as one.]
They're really strong.
[Yellow Team wins the mission.]
[The third dagger.]
[On top of the first dagger, they now
have possession of the third dagger!]
- We don't have any?
- No, we don't.
- What have you been doing all day?
- We were waiting for you.
This team is now just beginning.
[Now finally getting started as a team...]
[To all the fans that cheered us
on enthusiastically...]
[We sincerely thank you.]
[The last dagger of the day...]
[Is at the hotel!]
[The secret of the nine swords-
Find the 'R' marked flag.]
[Macau's 'S' hotel]
[Somewhere in this expansive hotel...]
[Find the 'R' flag.]
Where is it?
Where's the 'R' flag?
[Asking the front desk?]
- Do you have a 'R'...
- Huh?
'R'?
Do you know 'R'?
[It seems the front desk
isn't the spot...]
How are we supposed to find it
in this large place?
Wow, this place is so huge.
Huge!
[A monstrous shopping mall
that's connected to the hotel.]
This is amazing.
Do you have a Running Man flag?
[Find the last dagger...]
Look up there!
Welcome Running Man.
[Wow! A welcome message!]
Isn't that amazing?
Welcome.
Welcome Running Man.
Jong Kook, look at that writing.
Look at the letters on that
cascading water.
Wow... that's awesome.
- I think something may be over there.
- There has to be something over there.
[Oh! The 'R' flag!]
Wow! Here it is!
Here it is!
[The 'R' flag on top of the steps!]
Isn't this it?
- It's alive!
- It's a person!
[Wow... it's alive and moving...]
[The dagger!]
- I had no idea that it was a person.
- I had no idea either.
[Succeeds at finding the 'R' flag.]
It's nice to meet you.
- Is this right?
- Did we really just find it?
- We found it.
- You found it?
Amazing...
[This is... the fourth dagger.]
Oh my goodness!
[Mission complete.]
[The next morning.]
[8 a.m.]
Good morning.
[Hye Jin remembering to bring
the dagger with her.]
I kept dreaming...
that I had to keep running everywhere.
[Dong Wook is also ready to
go for the day.]
Good morning.
Did you sleep well?
I think I need to hurry.
I was supposed to meet my team
10 minutes ago. I'm 10 minutes late.
- I feel a little bad.
- Seriously...
I feel a little bad.
Can you guys match my pace?
Why don't you guys match my pace?
[And heading off to somewhere immediately...]
We're heading towards the airport.
We are going to the airport.
I think we really are headed
to the airport.
[Airport?]
[Macau International Airport]
I think we really are going somewhere.
Even all our luggage is here.
- Isn't that all our stuff?
- Where are we going?
- Where are we headed today?
You're packing up already after having
unpacked all that stuff yesterday?
Where are we going?
Seriously?
You will now all be heading to Vietnam
to find the rest of the daggers.
[Vietnam?]
Where's Hanoi?
Hanoi, Vietnam!
You're taking us to Vietnam now
when we just arrived in Macau yesterday?
[Macau yesterday and Vietnam today?]
This really is on a blockbuster scale.
It's not like we're going from
Kwangju to Busan or something.
[From Macau to Vietnam!]
[Hanoi, Vietnam]
[Find the rest of the daggers here.]
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Way above their wildest dreams-
Another adventure is about to start!]
[Welcome to Vietnam]
[Satisfying all the senses,
Delicious Hanoi.]
[Second episode of
The Asia Race spectacle!]
[Heading towards the
long-awaited highlight.]
[And finally... the Secret of
the Nine Daggers will be revealed!]
[Race that keeps you awaiting breathlessly!
The final battle that awaits them!]
[In order to obtain the legendary dagger...
a vital battle still awaits them!]
[Secret of the nine daggers,
Continues next week.]