[The legendary group of delinquents
that rule the school.]
[Where it started it all-
The legendary Go Dong Wan senior.]
[The legendary book bag
that he left behind.]
[Find the secret papers hidden within.]
[The unforgiving battle
between the delinquents.]
[Who will take ownership of
the legendary book bag?]
[The Legendary Book Bag]
Subtitles by DramaFever
[R Headquarters- Secret Police Force.]
Hello!
My name is Lee Kwang Ja!
[Criminal Investigation Inspector-
2013's Top Police Officer.]
[Inspector Lee Kwang Ja-
Perhaps the tallest officer in all of Korea.]
We have discovered the secret location of
the documents that we've been searching for.
[Officer Lee Kwang Ja to find the
cache of secret documents?]
The legendary book bag that
Go Dong Wan left...
We have information that the documents are
to be found in the book bag he left behind.
You have to find that legendary book bag to
get your hands on those documents.
Covertly?
We aren't the only ones that are
after that book bag.
Take a look.
What is this?
If you look on that sheet
you'll see a list of eight delinquents who
want to become the legend themselves.
I've once been beaten by this student.
[Delinquent student, Kim Jong Kook!]
All those delinquent students who are
trying to become legends themselves
are also after the legendary book bag
that we are seeking.
Therefore, you have to go undercover
as a student of that high school
to get your hands on the documents within
that bag without losing it to them.
Am I the only secret agent?
- You are the police agent on this task...
- You have to explain it to me some more.
Don't interrupt while your superior
is talking and just listen.
I will do my best!
I will be the best officer that I can be!
Every time a mission is completed
a hint will be revealed
regarding the legendary book bag.
So I have to be the only one to get that hint
without anyone else knowing, right?
Even if those that end up on your team
find out about the hint
you have to covertly act on the hint alone,
and you have to try to keep it to yourself.
I have to try to divert them.
In the event that your secret agenda
and mission is compromised
your secret identity will be revealed
to the whole cast.
- Then you'll be left on your own.
- What?
You must now change into your school uniform
and infiltrate the group of students.
This is an undercover operation?
Give that sheet back to me
so that you're not caught with it.
Take a quick look through it and
get on your way.
[Speedy memorization that he couldn't master
even back in his high school days.]
Okay, I got it.
I promise to succeed the mission!
[The secret documents will be mine!]
I will do my absolute best police work!
[Secret agent, Lee Kwang Ja-
Mission accepted!]
[Transformation complete.]
- Isn't that the crazy girl?
- That's Kwang Ja.
She terrifies me.
[The girl whose reputation precedes her.]
I heard that she won't stop growing.
Does this mean that us three are a team?
- Trai-Tors-Club!
- Today's the day.
- Today is the day.
- Today's the day we get out revenge.
[Their weekly goal is to betray and win.]
Even though everyone disregards us,
we are the winning team.
[Ha Ha- Always protecting his own position
by resorting to trickery.]
I've been a high school delinquent
for the past 26 years now.
[Ji Suk Jin- A high school delinquent
for 26 years.]
- Look at those two!
- Look at them!
- Hey, what are you guys doing?
- What school are you guys from?
[Yoo Jae Suk- Delinquent from Apgujeong.
Nicknamed, 'Yoo Hyuk, the king of dancing.']
Hey, it's Song Ji Hyo!
It's Song Ji Hyo!
- It's Song Ji Hyo!
- She's the bully!
Hey, are you that infamous Song Ji Hyo?
[Song Ji Hyo- Beautiful foul-mouthed
delinquent who rules Ilsan.]
All of you, shut up.
- She really startled me.
- You'd better watch yourselves.
- Watch yourselves.
- What is he saying?
- What did you say?
- You're Song Ji Hyo's lackey, aren't you?
What did you say?
- Are you a boy or a girl?
- She's a girl!
- That's a lie!
- How can you say that to a girl?
She's a boyish looking girl.
It's the muscle boy.
[Kim Jong Kook- Muscle boy with
a weakness for girls.]
[Gary- Master of martial arts, but has a crush
on a girl at the neighboring school.]
My boyfriend.
What did you say?
Get away from me!
Come on, can't you be nicer to me?
Hey, I can't believe you hit him
with the back of your hand!
- How could you hit me like that?
- Who told you to crowd me like that?
[The top button that he never
manages to fasten.]
Why is a student going around with
his top button unbuttoned like that?
It's suffocating to have it
buttoned up all the way.
Look, he has a big chest.
[Abnormally large and muscly chest.]
When are you going to grow one?
What are you looking at?
- Look at his chest.
- Who is that?
- Is that...
- It's the real delinquent!
[Who's the real delinquent here?]
[Chun Jung Myung- Master of Jujitsu hiding
behind the facade of his sweet face.]
- Hello.
- It's Chun Jung Myung!
Don't mess with his skills!
[Silent and deadly opponent who knows
how to use his martial arts skills.]
Hey, he won't go easy on you just because
we're shooting a show.
[He's not the type to really joke around.]
And did you see how serious
Jung Myung got?
Is the hand that he grabbed feeling okay?
[Jung Myung's formal style.]
Even though he may always have
a big smile on his face
his martial arts skills and
physical strength are no joke.
Jung Myung is a very sweet guy though.
- He's very sweet.
- He is when he's smiling.
- Look at that.
- Look at his arm.
- What's wrong with your arm?
- What happened?
Did you get into a fight yesterday?
You didn't?
- Were you showing your moves while fighting?
- You were showing off, weren't you?
[The same man who didn't hold back, and
showed everyone what he was capable of...]
[has returned to the show after upping his
skill level with the knowledge of Jujitsu.]
[His inexhaustible stash of strength that will
grab the delinquents by their collars.]
Suk Jin... what is this that you're doing?
What is that?
[His hand moves that won't even
be able to kill a fly.]
Someone else is here!
Who is that?
[Another student?]
[Kim Min Jung- Nicknamed, 'The Night Queen'.
No detailed information.]
It's Min Jung.
- Hello.
- Min Jung isn't much of a delinquent.
She's the pretty delinquent.
Not much of a threat.
What are you doing, Ji Hyo?
[Blank Ji showing Min Jung who she is,
as soon as she sees her?]
- You and I are on the same team!
- What? What did you say?
[The birth of new feuding siblings.]
[These guys are the legendary delinquents?]
[Team Tiger- Three.]
[Team Delinquents- Three.]
[And... Team Traitors- Two.]
[I will deceive them all
and complete my mission!]
All of you guys are the infamous group of
delinquents from your own schools.
And Lee Kwang Soo will be a girl
for the remainder of the show today.
- What?
- You're Kwang Ja.
Since there's one girl per team,
Kwang Soo will remain 'Kwang Ja' all day.
Even though you may all know this already,
Ji Hyo has a picture floating on the internet
that proves that she was really
a delinquent back in her days.
[Her legendary sullen nature that wasn't
to be messed with even back in the day.]
If anything, Ji Hyo's calmed down
as she's gotten older.
- She's not to be messed with.
- No, don't believe anything he says.
- Why are you saying all that?
- Look at her right now.
She really is no joke.
- You will all be given a mission today.
- Yes, I understand.
You will now be given your mission.
To my juniors.
Guys, I'm your senior, Go Dong Wan.
Please read it in a feminine voice.
I'm searching for a junior who can
succeed me once I leave.
[His legend- Having graduated to
move onto college after 17 long years.]
The one who finds my legendary book bag will
become the new legend of high school.
To the schools that come in at first and
second place in the competition I've created
they will be given a hint which will help
them find the hidden location of my bag.
The team that can gather all the hints
to find my legendary book bag
will become the ultimate winner.
I wish you all the best in completing
your mission in finding the book bag.
Your loving senior, Go Dong Wan.
So we just have to find the
legendary book bag?
- This is it. Today is the day.
- We're really going to win this.
[Secret Agent, Kwang Ja-
Okay... it's finally starting.]
[Traditional village in Bucheon.]
[They're driving?
Since they're all over the age of 20...]
- I think we're going to a rice paddy.
- Where?
- A rice paddy.
- We're going to a rice paddy?
- Yes.
- Seriously...
We just did something at the rice paddy,
and we're going back to it already?
I doubt we'll be doing
the same thing.
- I'm not sure.
- I doubt it'll be the same thing, right?
- But we have Jung Myung on our team.
- Yes, Chun Jung Myung.
Of course.
Jung Myung knows what he's doing.
- How can I know what we're doing?
- Jung Myung's really competitive too.
Even though he's always smiling,
he's actually fiercely competitive.
- I'd be afraid of him if he was my opponent.
- Yeah, I would be too.
- But we're on the same team.
- Yes.
I'm glad he's on our team.
Let's go.
[First to arrive is, Team Delinquents.]
Please get yourselves ready
and first team to enter the game arena
will automatically move on to the final round.
- You may go.
- Let's go. Quickly!
- The final round!
- Wow... could it be?
- The second team is already here.
- Where?
The first team to enter the game arena
will automatically move on to the final round.
- The final round?
- Okay!
[The final round will be mine!]
[The place that they're running to is...]
[Rice paddy ice skating rink.]
They've filled the field with water again.
[A specially prepared ring
in this quiet and peaceful field.]
- Hurry, Ji Hyo!
- Kwang Ja will win.
[Will it be Ji Hyo, or will it be Kwang Ja?]
- How is that important right now?
- Hurry, Ji Hyo!
[I'm a girl...]
- What are you doing, Kwang Ja?
Hang on, I have to tie my hair.
Don't you know what girls are like?
Hurry!
[Which school will the final round go to?]
[Both feet are up on the platform!]
The winners are, Yoo Jae Suk,
Chun Jung Myung, and Song Ji Hyo.
[The final round goes to, Team Delinquents!]
Song Ji Hyo beat you and set both of her
feet up on the platform first.
[Team Traitor's Kwang Ja having lost their
chance to move on by getting her hair tied.]
Nice.
Welcome everyone.
The first game you'll be playing is called,
the 'Rice Paddy Ridge'.]
You have to make sure that your female
teammate can get across the field without
getting their clothes wet in the process.
If you look behind you,
you'll see a stack of boards.
You'll be using those boards to build
a bridge for your female teammate.
One member from each team can go
get the board and return with a board
and the female member can stand on it
and wait until another one is placed for them.
Come here, Ji Hyo. We're
already moved up to the final round.
- The guys can't touch the girls, right?
- No, they can't.
Can the girls touch each other?
- The two women can touch each other.
- Okay.
What do you mean, they can?
Kwang Soo, I will give you my energy
to leg trip the girls.
[Ambitious Secret Agent, Kwang Ja.]
Ready!
Set!
- Hang on a minute.
- Do you see what he's doing?
- You have to start!
- Can you get rid of this thug?
[Others can't even budge a muscle with
the Tiger exerting his strength on them.]
Just shove Kim Jong Kook aside.
- You just wait. Your turn is coming.
- What did you say?
- I just told you to wait your turn.
- Let's go. Fighting!
- Fighting!
Fighting.
Ready.
Ready, set!
[Moving quickly to start
building their bridge.]
Hurry! Hurry!
[Not a bit of hesitation on the rice paddy
even in the midst of the hot weather.]
You have to put it down straight!
- Hurry!
- You have to hurry!
[Must start over from the beginning
if you fall in the water.]
Okay, walk over.
[Team Traitors bridge proving
to be not so steady.]
[Min Jung is carefully making her way
forward one step at a time.]
- Aren't you going to set that down?
- Hurry up and move up a step.
[Kwang Ja enjoying her game of
playing in the mucky water.]
You have to put it down better so that
I don't keep falling in the water!
- On my goodness!
- Carefully. One step at a time.
- You have to set that down. Suk Jin!
- Hurry!
[Team Tiger almost makes it
onto the platform already.]
[Kwang Ja is still having fun
splashing around in the water.]
[This won't do...]
You said that the girls are allowed
to touch each other, right?
[Drop kick?]
[Let's splash around in the water together!]
Hurry up!
Hurry up and set down the steps!
[Having to start over from the beginning
and crossing the bridge again.]
Lower your knees and bend down.
[Hard to find their balance on
top of the paddy bridge.]
[Kwang Ja also gets on her way.]
[Wow... look at her move!]
[Succeeds in crossing the bridge!]
You wouldn't have won so easily
if you were playing against us.
- You just wait because we're coming for you.
- Chun Myung is readying himself for this.
[Seemingly relaxed]
What if Chun Myung makes one of his moves?
Chun Myung, you can't do this, okay?
What are you doing
to a girl right now, Jae Suk?
- I'm helping you dump out the water.
- What are you doing to a girl?
- I'm helping you dump the water out.
- Don't do that.
Can the girl team member say a word
of encouragement for their men?
Why don't you say something cool
to Min Jung?
Didn't you say that you were going to
say something to Min Jung earlier?
- You said you'll show us something, right?
- Kwang Soo.
What about the song we made up earlier?
Why don't you sing that for her?
You made up another song?
- Sing it right now.
- Go on and sing it for her.
- One, two, three, four.
- Min Jung's face is so beautiful!
So beautiful!
- Even her body is beautiful!
- Beautiful!
- Even her personality is beautiful!
- That's a pretty nice song.
- You liked that song, didn't you?
You are inside my heart!
- That's it. She fell for it.
- She's liking that right now.
- I think she fell for that song.
- Round two.
[Team Tiger vs. Team Traitor- Round two.]
[Team Traitor's two male students unable
to budge from the Tiger's grasp.]
[Gary takes the opportunity to carefully
set down the first board with ease.]
- We have to get going.
- Okay, it's my turn. I have to go.
[Please let me go!]
Hang on to him!
Cling onto him, Dong Hoon!
[Resuming their building of the bridge
by switching out the players.]
That's too far up.
That's too big of a gap.
[Relying on Kwang Ja's long legs to step
further out, and building as he sees fit.]
[The construction coming to a halt
whenever they encounter the Tiger.]
Cling onto him!
[The construction of Team Tiger's bridge
steadily coming along.]
[You're not going anywhere!]
[Full of desire to go build their bridge,
but they just keep circling in their place.]
You have to let me go!
- You have to let me go!
- Don't let him go no matter what!
[Tiger's tightly woven bridge steps.]
[Mere two spaces?]
[Putting faith in his long legs to
start making his way forward.]
One more!
[No!]
[Frontal face plant like a tree
being knocked down.]
Look what you did to my wig!
[Team Tiger not paying any attention to
Kwang Ja and steadily making their way up.]
Kwang Ja's going to get started again.
[Kwang Ja unable to watch the other team
making progress in their game.]
I'm sorry!
What I did was wrong!
[Everyone back to their starting line.]
- It's four spaces.
- Hurry!
[Sloppy construction.]
Can't you build it right?
Don't you know what you're doing?
[Min Jung already having crossed
the halfway mark.]
[You're not going anywhere!]
[Min Jung taking another step forward.]
One more!
[The final board for Min Jung
to make her way onto the platform.]
[Kwang Ja's mere wish is to take
at least one solid step forward.]
[Team Tiger wins!]
- Take better care of Kwang Ja!
- What were you guys even doing?
[Team Traitor not having been able to do a
thing with the Tiger standing in their way.]
- Kwang Ja barely made a move.
- Hey, Kwang Ja.
Kwang Ja.
You couldn't make your way with
the two boards we set down?
[Kwang Ja showing some anger.]
Hey, you try it.
Why don't you give it a try?
[Giving it a try with just two boards?]
Jong Kook... if I can get it done with two,
let's go for another round.
- Okay, I got it.
- If I succeed with just two boards.
- I think you can do it.
- You can do it.
[Will he really be able to do it
with just these two boards?]
Challenge.
[I have to cross that bridge!]
Every time you pass your mission,
you'll gain a hint about the legendary bag.
[Secret Agent Lee Kwang Ja-
Win the mission and gain the hint.]
[I have to gain the hint!]
[The unsteady bridge that he has to
cross in two leaps.]
[Getting a good dose of the grimy water.]
[Darn...]
- Okay, off to the final round.
- Yes, let's do it.
[Team Tiger and Team Delinquents
are moving onto the final round.]
Okay, ready for the final round.
This is a battle between Ji Hyo
and Min Jung.
Ji Hyo!
- Don't hold yourself back at all.
- Yes!
You just show her what
you're made of.
[Loosening up?]
Why are you loosening up, Jung Myung?
- Why are you doing that?
- You saw that, didn't you?
- Why are you loosening up like that?
- He's just warming up.
- Just what is it that you're planning to do?
- Why are you doing that?
- Jung Myung, you need pay them back for us.
- Yes, I will.
- Chun Jung Myung, fighting!
[Please stay tuned for the ultimate
UFC battle on the rice paddy!]
[The delinquents go head to head!]
[Strength vs. Strength.]
[Gary rushes forward to install
the first board for his bridge.]
Where do you think you're going?
[Student Grasshopper caught in the tight
grasp of the Tiger.]
[Ah... his shirt...]
[A fierce struggle.]
Jung Myung!
[Breaking out his moves?]
Hurry, Jong Kook!
He's crazy!
Jong Kook, hurry!
- He's crazy!
- Hurry!
[Wow... two of them at once?]
[Wow... Jung Myung has both of them
locked in his tight grasp.]
[All the delinquents tangled up
in a tight knot.]
Gary!
What is this!
[Gary barely makes his way
out of the tangle.]
[Is this a game or a battle?]
[Jung Myung moves quickly to
construct their bridge.]
[Without Jung Myung, the Tiger is able to
remove himself away from the tangle.]
[The bridge is almost complete!]
One more!
Jong Kook, one more!
[The Grasshopper kicked off
the platform by the Tiger.]
One more!
Jong Kook!
[This was not meant to be
a wrestling ring...]
Chun Jung Myung!
Let him go!
[For the first time in this show's history,
Jujitsu moves make an appearance...]
- Use your legs!
- Is all that really necessary?
[Screams of panic and pain
can be heard from all over...]
He's pinning me down!
[What you're seeing is not a scene
from a UFC championship...]
One more!
I just need one more!
Don't let him go!
[Jae Suk makes his way over to put
another board down for the bridge.]
[This won't do...]
[Min Jung attempting to leap the rest
of her way onto the platform?]
[Team Tiger succeeds.]
You should've done that sooner.
[No kidding,
you should've done that sooner...]
[Team Tiger wins the first round.]
Jung Myung!
You had me pinned to the ground!
You did the same to me!
[Jung Myung having used his
Jujitsu moves on his opponents.]
- Did you see what he did?
- He can't keep me pinned down like that.
Look at this.
What is this?
How could he have ripped your shirt
down the middle like that?
It's because he had me locked
in such a tight grasp.
What were you doing up there?
- What happened to you?
- I considered abandoning ship.
[The rough battle made him consider
abandoning the game.]
He should not be allowed to
battle us like that.
What are you talking about?
I don't even weigh that much.
[What?
The Tiger doesn't weight that much?]
- I weigh 78kg.
- That's a lie!
- I'm telling the truth!
- That's the weight without your muscles!
I know that you weigh over 90kg!
- Don't even try to lie to me!
- I'm telling the truth!
[Now that they think about it,
they're lucky to have lost?]
Come on, let's win this thing!
Ready.
- This is the last round.
- Wait, I have to sneeze.
- I had to sneeze.
- Isn't he just so handsome?
Can you replay that look on his face?
[Team Tiger vs. Team Delinquents.
Round two.]
[Lightning fast Tiger and Jung Myung.]
[The female students starting to break
out into physical brawls themselves.]
Hurry up, Jong Kook!
[Body check.]
They both fell in the water
because of you!
[The two shrimps falling victim
to the fight between the two whales.]
Jong Kook, you need to
grab Jung Myung.
[Guerrilla training on his own.]
You need to grab him.
You have to lay them down faster!
[While the game and the
battle is going on...]
Hey, what are you doing?
Hurry!
Gary!
The third knob!
You have to lay it down faster!
[Breaking out his moves again...]
He's got me in a headlock!
[Using his skills to lock
the Tiger down again.]
Jong Kook!
Bite him!
[And as the icing on the cake,
Jae Suk lands a bite on his head.]
It sounds like something good
must be going on here.
[The Tiger experiencing some agony
after being bitten by the Grasshopper.]
Come on, Jong Kook!
It's no time for you to be just lying there!
[While Jung Myung has the two locked down
with his Jujitsu moves...]
[Team Delinquents bridge is almost
nearing its completion.]
Jae Suk bit me in the head.
He bit my head.
[Take that!]
[The relentless attack of the teeth.]
Just what kind of a game are they
playing up there?
[Jujitsu master comes back as soon as he
escapes from the bite happy Grasshopper.]
[The agonizing and relentless torture.]
That tickles!
Hurry up and build the bridge!
My turn?
[Team Delinquent's bridge is
almost complete!]
Ji Hyo, don't go!
No, don't go!
[Team Delinquent just needs Ji Hyo
to cross the bridge onto the platform!]
[Min Jung trying to stop Ji Hyo
from making her way across the bridge.]
[No!]
[We'd like to repeat- This is not
a scene from the UFC Championship]
I can hear Ji Hyo starting to cuss.
[You can't go!]
We have to build the bridge!
Gary, we have to build the bridge.
[Nonstop skinship on the show today.]
Just what in the world is
going on up there?
We should do it too!
[Biting the foot this time?]
- That's my foot.
- That was your foot?
[Mistakenly having bitten
Jung Myung's foot.]
[Attacking the Tiger's foot.]
Hurry up, Ji Hyo!
[The delinquents are tangled up
in a fierce battle.]
Please stop that.
I can't win against you using
normal methods.
[Darn...]
[Ji Hyo starts to make her move.]
[Crossing the bridge in ease.]
[Success]
He bit me in the head and my foot!
- Don't bite me.
- I'm going to bite you in the armpit now.
Can't you tell him not to do that?
I'm sorry for having confused your foot
for his and biting you earlier, Jung Myung.
[Apologizing for having bitten him
by mistake earlier.]
Seriously, Jae Suk.
Jung Myung was very quick to tell me
that I was biting his foot.
This is the final round!
- Jae Suk, bite him and kick him.
- Okay. Don't worry, Ji Hyo.
Tear him part, Jong Kook!
- Tear him apart? Okay.
- Fine, I'll show you.
- Just tear him to shreds.
- This is it!
Okay, is everyone ready?
- This is the final round.
- Jung Myung can do this.
Final round.
Ready!
Set!
Jung Myung's starting already.
[Using his martial moves again.]
We just need to win this round!
This round is it!
[Gary is the first to escape
from the melee.]
[Jujitsu Jung Myung uses his moves again
to escape from the Tiger's clutches.]
[Using biting Grasshopper's weakness
to tickle him to release his grasp.]
Take him down, Jung Myung!
Hurry!
Hurry, Jong Kook!
[The final show of their fierce competition.]
[Full of excitement.]
This is entertaining!
[Team Tiger leading the race
by the split of a hair.]
[You're not going anywhere!]
[A full frontal attack.]
[Suppressing the Tiger
with a blow to his head.]
[The Tiger losing his senses from
the surprise blow to his head.]
[Biting Grasshopper taking advantage of
the moment to construct their bridge.]
[Jujitsu Jung Myung tying down
both of them.]
[Not letting go of his grasp.]
Just take off your shirt!
Don't pull down my pants!
We're burning up over here!
This has been going on for two hours!
[Fierce UFC battle happening
right here on the rice paddy.]
He's trying to turn this game
into a UFC Championship!
[Team Delinquent's bridge is
almost complete!]
[Crosses the bridge onto the platform!]
[Team Delinquent wins!]
Jung Myung hit me on the head
with the board!
[First time in the history of a variety show?
A blow to the head with a board...]
I heard the thud!
[Jujitsu Jung Myung
doing a number on the Tiger.]
I got hit on the head.
The winning team is, Team Yoo Jae Suk,
Chun Jung Myung, and Song Ji Hyo.
Coming in at second place is,
Team Kim Jong Kook, Min Jung, and Gary.
Everyone, there are three different
hints in these envelopes.
Yes.
You chose number three. Look at
it discreetly and don't show anyone.
[Second place winner, Team Tiger
chooses hint number three.]
Since the team that came in at last place
can't take this last remaining hint...
- No!
- Give it to us!
- No! Why are you doing that?
- Hey!
[That hint... I really need it!]
I have to get my hands on that hint
without anyone else knowing about it.
When did you get so evil?
- Pick up the pieces.
- Hey!
It's because you wasted time tying back
your hair.
- What's the point with that face of yours?
- You think you know about women?
That's right, I know!
[Thus, Kwang Ja failed at her attempt
in gaining a hint...]
[Go to Yeouido.]
World Cup.
- World Cup?
- Yes, World Cup.
- That's all that was written on there?
- Yes, just 'World Cup'.
I have no idea what that's telling us.
[Insufficient information.]
What happened earlier on that field
is no different than a martial arts match.
Do you know that?
That felt really good.
What do you mean, that felt good?
- We should've been quicker.
- No kidding.
- I saw Min Jung showing some attitude.
- When?
'Jong Kook, just tear him to pieces!'
Wow, I think that was the first time
I've ever heard anyone say that.
I can't believe those words came out
of this sweet actress' mouth.
Our plans for today are
falling apart again.
- Maybe today isn't the day?
- Come on, Suk Jin.
- Kwang Soo, let's seriously show them.
- Dong Hoon.
There was nothing I could
do in that game.
If we're not careful, we may not be
able to gain a single hint all day.
Our future is starting to look bleak.
We're all starting to lose hope again.
I can't even see the path
in front of us.
I also felt like we really didn't mount
too much towards the end of the game.
[Han River Public Park in Yeouido.]
This game will test your speed.
Speed?
What is it?
- It's a three person relay.
- Okay.
- This is it. This is the game.
- You have to make sure to do your part.
Delinquents' specialty,
skipping class for snack time.
You've all skipped
your share of classes, right?
We don't do things like that.
We take school very seriously.
You are all the types of students who will
skip your classes to run off for snack time.
The second relay player will stand
on top of the hill.
The second relay runner will receive a bag
from the first person and run to the store.
Then the second runner will buy and bag
all of the items that the first person chose
and return to their team.
Then the third runner will wait in their spot
for the second runner to return
and wrap their bodies in a rug to
roll down the hill.
Once down the hill, lay out the rug on
the ground for all three to eat the snacks
and the first team to finish eating
their snacks wins this race.
Kwang Soo's good at eating fast
because he has such a large mouth.
I can eat really fast.
Is everyone ready?
Yes!
[Ready]
- Min Jung, fighting!
- Let's win this.
- Ji Hyo!
- Fighting!
[Everyone seems to be confident
about the Skipping Mission.]
- I'll put them in this bag.
- Song Ji Hyo, fighting.
- Fighting.
- We really need to get the hint.
Okay.
[Time for the first runners to start picking
the snack items written on table tennis balls.]
[Stir fried kimchi.]
[Team Delinquents- Stir-fried kimchi, burger,
roasted chestnuts, cup of ice, chicken leg.]
[Sausage]
[Team Traitors- Sausage, potato chips,
bread, white milk, yogurt.]
[Chocolate]
[Team Tiger- Chocolate, warm honey water,
kimbap, cola, hardboiled egg.]
- Why are you looking so glum, Min Jung?
- Not at all, Gary!
[Sensing something for Team Tiger.]
Did you hear Min Jung?
'Not at all, Gary!'
[All the delinquents are now ready.]
Nice, nice!
[Big-nosed Brother focusing on the win,
and shoves the girls aside.]
- How could you do that to a girl?
- Look at him go.
Nice, Jung Myung!
[Second runners are off to the store!]
[Enters the store as fast as lightening.]
Where did they go?
Where are all the balls?
Bread.
Potato chips.
- Potato chips.
- Chicken leg?
Potato chips.
Roasted Chestnuts?
[Team Delinquents- Stir-fried kimchi, burger,
roasted chestnuts, cup of ice, chicken leg.]
Where do you keep your pastries?
[Team Traitors- Sausage, potato chips,
bread, white milk, yogurt.]
[Team Tiger- Chocolate, warm honey water,
kimbap, cola, hardboiled egg.]
[Delinquent Ro-Ro is all over the place
looking for the bread.]
- Where are the chicken legs?
- They're behind you.
I feel like the calm before the storm.
Someone's coming.
[Someone already got everything?]
[Delinquent Gary.]
[Team Tiger's Gary is the first to
make it back to his teammates.]
I need a chicken leg, please.
- Where can I get a cup of ice?
- A cup of ice?
Yes, a cup of ice.
Bread, bread, bread...
[Still looking for his pastry.]
[Who will be faster?
Will it be Jung Myung, or Ro-Ro?]
[Throwing the bag down the hill first.]
[Third runner, Tiger, getting the rug out
to prepare himself to roll down the hill.]
Out of my way!
Where is Jung Myung?
[Second runner, Jung Myung,
is on his way back to his teammates.]
- Hurry!
- You did good.
[Who will be first to roll down the hill?]
Hurry!
[The Silver Tiger rolling down the hill.]
[Now, it's time to eat their snacks!]
Hurry!
[This delinquent is rolling down the hill
as if he's bouncing off of it.]
[Last roller, Kwang Ja, is also getting ready
to roll down the hill in her rug.]
[Full speed ahead!]
[How far are you going to go?]
[Engine Kwang Ja not knowing
how to stop.]
- Stop rolling!
- That's enough!
- There's even ice?
- You have to shake it up.
Come over here!
I'm really dizzy!
[Everyone enjoying their snack time.]
- There are only five pieces!
- There's no time for this right now.
Hurry up and come over here.
You should've bought a smaller one.
[Everyone's sharing their snacks nicely?]
[Sausage, potato chips, bread,
white milk, and yogurt.]
I will do my best!
[I will show you what a good
agent I can be!]
[Eat everything in sight!]
I think they're already done eating.
[Team Tiger is almost done
with their snacks.]
[Giving the Tiger a piece of chocolate?]
[Which is immediately fed to Gary.]
There's another piece, Jong Kook.
Here, eat it.
[Eating with determination.]
[Let's just finish this all up.]
That team's already done eating.
[Success?]
Okay, Red Team passes.
[Team Tiger succeeds!]
[Time to determine the second place
between the two teams.]
[Hamburger]
I can tell that they picked
something bad.
I can tell.
[Less burdensome, roasted chestnuts.]
[Following the hamburger,
his next draw is, fishcake skewer.]
You have to choose carefully,
Jung Myung.
[One container of ice cream.]
- Can I re-pick?
- You can't do that.
No, this isn't right.
What did you pick?
Can I take a look before I pick?
You can't do that.
Fair play, please.
How many have you picked so far?
Your stomachs are going to explode.
[Chicken skewer]
I'm seriously going to lose my mind.
You can't look.
What are you doing?
[His last snack item is...]
[Bread]
- Why is he laughing like that?
- What did you pick?
- We're in big trouble.
- Jung Myung!
- Yes?
- What did you pick?
I really am so sorry.
[Team Delinquents- Bread, chicken skewer,
fishcake skewer, burger, a tub of ice cream.]
[Team Traitors- A cup of ice, sausage,
stir-fried kimchi, roasted chestnuts, yogurt.]
- Shouldn't he be back by now?
- What is he doing?
[Huh?
Gary coming onto the scene?]
[To protect Blank Ji?]
[What is he...]
[Their menu is much simpler
compared to their opposing team's.]
[A feast fit for a king for this team.]
Those guys... wow, look at them.
Look at the way he's eating
that ice cream.
We're not here on a picnic, Jung Myung!
You're acting like we're out here
on a picnic right now.
[Want some?]
[Team Traitors is already preparing
themselves to whistle.]
I'll whistle first.
I can't believe you picked
all this stuff.
- Okay.
- Yay!
[Team Traitors succeeds.]
- Today's the day.
- Today really is the day.
I'm sorry.
[Team Tiger gets the first hint for
coming in at first place.]
What are you doing?
[This delinquent gets caught trying to
steal the other team's hint.]
[Team Tiger chooses hint number one.]
- You're good at picking things like that.
- Okay.
[Team Traitors chooses hint number two.]
Don't even look at Jung Myung.
You have to be careful.
[Fifth floor]
[Gallery]
You didn't see, did you?
No, I did see.
It's a three letter word, isn't it?
[Suk Jin's awkward act of denial.]
[The Legendary Book bag is getting closer.
Off to the next location.]
[Go to the boxing ring in Sungbookdong.]
We're going to a boxing ring.
I wonder what we'll have to do there.
- Oh my, a boxing arena?
- Yeah.
You don't think
they expect us to spar, do you?
Come on, no way!
[Arriving at the third mission location.]
[Welcome to the boxing ring.]
[Legendary delinquents-
Let's see what you've got in the ring!]
What is this? Are we really going to
do something in the ring?
Why are you even trying to get in there?
[His legs are too short...]
Get in through the lower rung.
[There are some people who just can't seem
to manage even with long legs...]
Your next game is called...
'The Legendary Fist is Crying.'
- The first is crying?
- It's happening for real today.
Can you let the girls
go up against one another?
[Kwang Ja wanting to go up against
the girls for being a 'girl' today.]
- That's what I'd like.
- Okay, I understand.
Song Ji Hyo, get out here.
[You should be more careful about
who you choose as your opponent?]
Choose a representative from each team
to get in the ring with the gloves on.
- Yes?
- Then what?
While that person is in the ring warming up,
that's when the mission will be told to them.
- So the person has to be in the ring first.
- There's no knockout punch, right?
Isn't the person that breaks down crying
the loser of the round?
If the person's nose starts to bleed,
then that person loses.
Even though many
different situation may arise...
You will all have to prepare yourselves
for what may happen within the boxing ring.
[Wait...]
[Mr. Capable.]
[Jujitsu master.]
[Amateur boxing champion.]
[What do I do...]
Not a single person from our team
has any experience with boxing.
Look at how Jung Myung is helping
Jae Suk with the gloves.
[Players for the first round-
Jae Suk, Gary, and Suk Jin.]
Wait... Gary is an experienced boxer.
You're not expecting us to box, are you?
Everyone must wear their hat backwards
so that your face is easily visible.
And you must also take off
your glasses.
- My glasses?
- In case you get hit in the face.
[Is there going to be a real match?]
The three players must come
into the ring.
[Time to warm up.
Three players to the center of the ring.]
Keep that up and
you'll give yourself a nosebleed.
Why?
Do you want a nosebleed?
You don't want to give yourself
a nosebleed, do you?
- Do you want a nosebleed?
- Why, do you want one?
Gary, can I ruin your face
some more?
There's nothing you can do
to ruin it any further.
My face is already at its worst.
Suk Jin looks like he's already
been through a round in the ring.
[Boxer Gae slowly finding his rhythm.]
[Oh... he's so fast!]
What are you doing, Gary?
[I'll show you my lightning fast jabs
from ten years of experience with boxing!]
[This man is pretty awesome...]
He's no joke.
Why are you doing that to me?
Why are you treating a girl that way?
Seriously!
You just hit me for real!
[An accidental contact.]
What the heck...
who do you think you're punching?
- Come on, Suk Jin!
- Is my nose bleeding?
[One person who can't seem to
join the others in their laughter...]
You don't think we'll be
boxing for real, right?
We can't go up against Gary.
What was that?
[Then sound of the bell could be heard,
and what's that bowl for?]
What is that?
[What could it be?]
[Pick up the bowl and
break it over your opponent's head.]
[Not so easy to pick it up
with their gloved hands.]
[Big-nose barely manages to grab it first.]
[All he has to do now is to break it
over someone's head.]
I've got this.
[Leaping into the air to break it
over Gary's head.]
[It didn't break!]
[It probably hurts even more
since it didn't break...]
You're doing great, Ji Suk Jin!
[The bowl is still in Big-nose's hand.]
[It still didn't break!]
[Boxer Gae sees his chance,
and goes after  the bowl!]
The bowl didn't break.
[Wow... again!]
[Almost broke his head in his attempt
to break the bowl.]
- It didn't break.
- I don't think it broke.
- It's not breaking easily.
- Go after Jae Suk.
[Their fear escalates as the bowl
remains unbroken.]
[Hitting it directly on
the point of his hat.]
[Boxer Gae sees
the perfect opportunity this time.]
[At last... it's broken.]
[Round one- Break the bowl.
Boxer Gae wins.]
Sorry for that.
- I grabbed the bowl first.
- What the heck.
- Okay, next players into the ring.
- Just go for it, Jung Myung.
Since Jung Myung's going in,
you have to get in there.
Why would I go in there?
[And Mr. Capable too!]
[Scared to death.]
[Kkuk showing off his boxing skills
in an attempt to intimidate others.]
His jabs are pretty slow.
The jabs are actually supposed to be short
like that when you're boxing.
You're good.
[Kkuk receiving compliments
from the little kid.]
You're a shy one, aren't you?
Hit like a man!
[Ro-Ro's 'Hollywood style' boxing that
does nothing but disorients others.]
[His version of Ali's moves.]
You want to do this for real?
Don't get yourself worked up for nothing.
I know what it feels like
not to be able to do anything about it.
- There really is nothing you can do about it.
- The only thing I can do is call my mom.
[Calling his mom is the
only thing he can do?]
Jung Myung is looking for his chance.
[He really is all over the place...]
We're all warmed up.
I'm already starting to
sweat over here.
Come on, why don't you shadowbox?
[Time for the mission!]
[Huh?]
[A 500 won coin?]
[Pick up the coin in put it in the piggybank.]
[Jung Myung shoves Mr. Capable aside.]
[Not easy to pick up the coin
with their gloved hands.]
[While Mr. Capable is briefly out of it...]
[Oh my goodness...]
[He's got it!]
[Here's the piggybank.]
Jong Kook, come here and
do something!
- Come and do something!
- Jong Kook!
[During that time...
Jung Myung succeeds!]
[The legendary fist-
The second round goes to Jung Myung!]
[A celebration over his win.]
He did great and won while Jong Kook
was out of it and just lying there.
I think I got whiplash
when he body checked me.
- That's how you play this game.
- I lost consciousness.
That's what you do to us
every single week.
I'm telling you that I lost
consciousness there for a moment.
Why doesn't anyone care about
what happens to me?
I'm a person too!
[Ah... you are?]
[Mr. Capable is... a human being too...]
[Round three-
A match between the women.]
[Secret agent Kwang Ja with
a determined gleam in her eyes.]
Ji Hyo, when he's acting like that,
punch him in the upper lip.
So that his lips look like this,
and he can't even talk afterward.
[Wait...]
[Let's try to remember something about
these people from the information sheet...]
[Song Ji Hyo- The beautiful delinquent who
rules all of Ilsan.]
[Kim Min Jung- Dubbed 'Queen of the night'.
No further details.]
I've got it.
[I'm Lee Kwang Ja...
I will uphold the pride of my position.]
[Girls... come at me.]
[The legendary fist- Round three.]
You're doing good, Lee Kwang Soo.
[Checking each other out first.]
I can see Ji Hyo assuming the
correct stance.
- I can see Ji Hyo wanting to do it for real.
- She looks like she wants to box for real.
I actually learned how to box in the past.
- Seriously?
- For real?
Wait.
- You really took boxing lessons?
- I took lessons for a few months.
- That's quite a long time.
- Did you master everything within that time?
Wait.
[Kwang Ja pretends to lose her balance
to throw herself on Min Jung.]
Who cares?
We're all girls in here.
Is he out of his mind?
[It's getting to that time...]
[The sound of the mission is heard.]
[Grab the stick and hit the xylophone.]
- You're doing good.
- Ji Hyo.
[Grab the stick and hit the xylophone!]
[Min Jung resorting to manhandling Ji Hyo.]
[Women's round is proving to be a
bloodier battle than the men's!]
[While the other two girls are fighting,
Kwang Ja goes after the stick.]
Grab it by the rounder end!
[An advantageous situation for Kwang Ja!]
[Can't reach so fails to hit the xylophone!]
[Kwang Ja drops the stick.]
[Who will win this round?]
Hey, she has no respect for you!
[I'm going to ride on
your back for a moment, Ji Hyo.]
She has no respect for you
during this game.
[Takes care of Kwang Ja
with one single punch.]
[Even if everyone is laughing at me...]
[I'm Lee Kwang Ja, the undercover cop!]
[Kwang Ja gets back on his feet,
and goes back to punching Blank Ji.]
[Blank Ji Hyo explodes!]
[Beating him up with the stick?]
[You are still alive, aren't you?]
[Blank Ji succeeds in getting her hands
on the xylophone stick.]
[A full body block.]
What are you doing with your gloved hand?
Punch Kwang Soo!
[Take Blank Ji's punch!]
[Kwang Ja is knocked out!]
Just leave him down there, Ji Hyo.
[Don't you dare act out to me.]
Do you really need to go that far?
- What is going on here?
- Watch out for Ji Hyo's left punch.
[Ace Ji Hyo's undeniable punch.
Truly a work of someone experienced.]
Get it away from her!
[Are you trying to eat it?]
[Kwang catfish tries to
swallow the stick whole.]
Hey, Chun Jung Myung!
[Jung Myung grabs onto Kwang catfish
from outside the ring.]
[Is this pro wrestling?]
- Is the judge seeing this?
- You have to call out on that one!
[In the midst of all that chaos...
the stick falls into Min Jung's hand.]
[Min Jung takes the stick... and clang!]
[My goodness...]
[Min Jung comes out of nowhere
and wins the round!]
Jung Myung grabbed Kwang Soo.
[The final verdict on Jung Myung's
participation from outside the ring?]
Following the rules of WWE when it
comes to aiding your teammate...
What are you saying?
I thought that this was boxing!
That just means that don't come
anywhere near him.
Thus, the Red Team wins the game.
[Team Tiger wins the Legendary Fist Game.]
[Oh... this isn't good.]
- Okay, we've got the first place team.
- Yes.
It's now time to determine which of
the other teams will come in at second place.
Once you start to warm up,
we'll give you your mission.
We have to come in at second place, Ji Hyo.
It doesn't matter that we didn't win first,
but we just need to come in at second place.
[Time to warm up first.]
This is no time to go easy on her
just because she's a girl.
It's all over for us if we lose this round.
[Blank Ji's stable stance.]
You're not doing it right.
Ji Hyo's much better than you.
You have to lead with the left hand.
- Kim Jong Kook.
- Yeah?
I'm looking forward to when
you turn 80 years old.
I'm just waiting until you become
an octogenarian.
[I will get my revenge once you become
a weak octogenarian.]
[He's still too much of a threat at 70,
so he's waiting until he turns 80.]
[Grab the pen and
lift it up above your head to win!]
[There's nothing else left to lose!]
Why aren't you using your fists?
There you go.
Use your fists, Ji Hyo.
Ji Hyo.
[Blank Ji is putting him in a leg lock?]
[Unbelievable.]
[Blank Ji...
is there anything that she can't do?]
Ji Hyo!
[Wonder woman Song Ji Hyo!]
[Ruining Haroro's self-confidence.]
[Wonder woman and
angry little kid's fierce battle.]
[The pen is in Haroro's hand!]
[This battle has turned into a battle
of pride between these two delinquents.]
[Amazing!
Blank Ji is attempting to leg trip him?]
I'm sorry, but can you give me a break?
[Realizing that he can't take her by strength,
so he resorts to begging?]
My mother-in-law is watching this.
[Mother-in-law...
Can you turn off your TV for a moment?]
Hit him on his side, Ji Hyo.
[No other choice but to do this
in order to get the hint.]
Nice.
[Just then...
he stands from his stance!]
[I'm... a dad!]
[A round of applause breaks out over
his lifting of the pen!]
[I'm... a man!]
[An emotional ceremony
to celebrate his victory.]
[Head-butts... the camera.]
[Finishing off the touching ceremony
with a huge burst of laughter.]
- Good job, Ji Hyo.
- You're awesome.
Ji Suk Jin, Ha Ha, and Lee Kwang Ja
takes second place.
Only those two teams will
get their hands on another hint.
[First place winner- The Tiger Team.]
[Chooses envelope number one.]
[Team Traitors sticks to their previous choice
and selects envelope number two again.]
- Korean History museum.
- Go to Korean History Museum.
I wonder what that hint means?
Gallery.
Fifth floor.
So it means the gallery on
the fifth floor?
Let's just go up to the gallery
on the fifth floor as soon as we get there.
- Okay.
- We have to see what's up there.
We're in big trouble with
only one hint.
But we still have
Chun Jung Myung on our team.
[Having Jung Myung on their team is more
reassuring than having the hints?]
Why are you suddenly saying that?
- You all did great.
- Where is this place?
[Secret agent Lee Kwang Ja-
Heading to the final location.]
- We can do it as long as we're determined.
- This is the final round.
- Let's look at the hint.
- We chose number two both times.
Let's see what it says.
The gallery?
[First hint- gallery.]
[And the second hint that
they just gained...]
- Wait.
- What? The gallery again?
[Gallery]
- The writers!
- Seriously?
[All the same numbers mean
the same hint.]
Then it means that we're not any further
ahead than the team in the last place.
[Okay... this isn't a bad situation for me,
since I'm the secret agent here.]
[The final location-
Republic of Korea's History Museum.]
We don't really know anything,
so we're in big trouble.
- The only hint we have is the World Cup.
- Yes, World Cup.
It's the gallery, right?
[How unfortunate for them...
Two of the same hints.]
- Let's do this.
- Today really is the day.
- This has to be our day.
- I can't believe we got the same hint.
[Wait a minute... earlier...]
We will give you your mission once you arrive
at the final location without others knowing.
Secretly?
[I can't get caught...]
- Let's go.
[Getting on the elevator to
find the gallery.]
- I don't want to lose.
- I really want to win today.
[Kwang Ja looking for a way away from
them as not to arouse their suspicion.]
[His expression always looking so dour
whenever he tries to lie.]
I'm so sick and tired of losing.
Look, there's the gallery.
- Our hint said the gallery, right?
- The gallery.
[I have to get away from these guys
so that I can get my mission.]
Okay, we're here at the gallery.
I think we should start searching.
I wonder if there's something
inside the gallery?
Watch your backs.
[Everyone's focusing
on searching the gallery.]
[Just then...]
[Kwang Ja sneaks away from
the rest of his teammates.]
It's top secret information.
[The legendary book bag is amongst the nine
bags that each student is carrying.]
[The real book bag is marked with a symbol.]
[The legendary book bag is one of
the nine bags that they're carrying!]
[One of the nine bags that they've been
carrying all day is the legendary book bag!]
The real book bag is marked
with a symbol.
[Once the bag is found,
find the secret document inside the bag.]
[And oust all other student members.]
[Secret mission-
Oust all other student members.]
[I have to... oust these guys?]
I have to oust all the other students?
Just the fact that I'm still alive
is a miracle in itself.
How am to supposed to oust
all of them?
[All those scary delinquents...
and I'm to oust them all by myself?]
[The sudden terror and trepidation.]
No one else knows that I'm an
undercover cop, do they?
[Since no one knows my true identity...]
[I still have a fighting chance.]
The gallery on the fifth floor.
[Team Tiger with the most
amount of hints heads up to the gallery.]
[Deducing that the legendary book bag is
somewhere in the gallery on the fifth floor.]
We have to search all the likely places.
It could be enclosed in a display like this.
Yeah, we have to search very carefully.
[Huh?]
[Min Jung is looking a little suspicious...]
[Why is she suddenly looking so alert?]
[Carefully pulls out a cellphone...]
I bet something is hidden around here.
Search around in the inside, Jong Kook.
I'll go search the outside parameters.
[Walks away from her teammates to walk
into an empty room all by herself?]
[Wait... this is?]
[It's the exact same text
that Kwang Ja received!]
[Just why did Min Jung receive the same
mission text as Kwang Ja did?]
[Just what is the identity of
this woman?]
[7 a.m. this morning.]
[A lone woman walks into an empty cafe.]
[What is Kim Min Jung doing here?]
Agent Kim Min Jung.
- It's nice to meet you.
- Yes, me too.
You graduated from the academy
at the top of your class
and you did an outstanding job of
capturing the criminal in Thailand.
I have a special mission for one of our
top agents, which is you.
[The truth is, Min Jung has been
a secret agent all along!]
[She was given the same order that
secret agent Kwang Ja received.]
So that means...
one, two, three, four... one against eight?
Can't at least one of them
be on my side?
I can't really tell you that.
So that must mean that there's
at least one person on my side.
[Agent Lee Kwang Ja
and Agent Kim Min Jung.]
[Each going undercover without
the knowledge of the other's existence.]
[They're not aware of
each other's existence.]
[Kim Min Jung was another
undercover agent all along.]
[Casually infiltrating the ring of delinquents
as 'The Queen of the Night'.]
[Min Jung having perfected her mission of
going undercover and hiding her identity.]
[This is the reason why she worked
so hard all day to win.]
I'm sorry, guys.
[Since it'll be tough for me to oust them all
on my own, I'll utilize my team members.]
[And the other secret agent over here.]
- Gary.
- What is it? You startled me.
[The two undercover agents facing off with one
another without knowing each other's identity.]
We have to eliminate each other's
name tags, right?
[Wait... how did she know that?]
[I was sure that the delinquents only knew of
the mission to find the legendary book bag?]
Why are you thinking that this is a
name tag elimination race?
- This isn't a name tag elimination.
- You startled me.
I thought we had to eliminate
each other's name tags.
[Min Jung suggesting that all the delinquents
eliminate each other's name tags.]
I thought that the winner was whomever
that found the book bag?
I thought that the person who found the
book bag was the winner of the race.
[The undercover agents...]
[With two different plans...]
[Wait...]
Can't one of them be on my side?
[I'm sure that there's at least
one other undercover agent here...]
[Just which one could it be?]
[Will these two be able to realize
each other's identity?]
The legendary book bag.
[Delinquent Jong Kook firmly believing in
his hunch that the book bag is hidden here.]
I wonder where it could be hidden.
[Discovers a suspicious looking arrow sign
drawn onto the floor.]
[The arrow is leading to a door.]
[Team Tiger's hints- Fifth floor; Gallery.
Team Delinquent's hint- World Cup.]
[He finds something!]
[The 'R' box!]
Hey!
- Gary!
- Hey!
Hey!
Gary!
- Gary!
- I can hear Jong Kook screaming.
[What did he discover?]
I can hear Jong Kook screaming.
[I have a bad feeling about this...]
- Gary!
- Yes, Jong Kook.
Hurry up and come here.
[Rushing off to Jong Kook's side.]
[Everyone gathers around in front of
the room of mystery.]
The bag must be in there.
- That's Jong Kook's bag.
- What is that in there?
- Can you all back up?
- I need to talk to my teammates.
- We'll get back to you once we've talked.
- You've already found it?
We're going to stand out here
and watch.
See what's in there.
We have to know what's
in there too.
[Inside the 'R' marked chest...]
[A piece of paper that contains more
information on the legendary bag!]
See? That's why I told you that I think
we need to eliminate their name tags.
- Let's rip this up.
- So the others can't see.
[Secret agent Min Jung ripping
the paper to shreds.]
- Ming Jung!
- You're ripping it up?
[I'm grateful for what you're doing, but...]
Can't you let us see it first?
[Destroying the piece of papers so the other
delinquents can't see what's on it.]
- We're coming out.
- We're all coming out right now.
- Min Jung, tell us what you read.
- Let's get away from here for now.
[Min Jung keeping her secret.]
[The other students remain clueless.]
You just told me that they ripped up
whatever was in there, right?
- There was a piece of paper in here.
- Inside this box?
It said that there's a special mark
inside that bag.
So it means that the bag could be
one of ours.
- Yes, you're right.
- Is the mark under our name tags?
- No, it said the mark is inside the bag.
- Inside the bag?
So we should all check our bags to see
what could be inside the bag.
So we should check and see if we can
find something inside our own bags.
[This man is clever...]
[Could Jong Kook be the other agent?]
[But I guess he always acts like
an undercover cop.]
- Min Jung, should we check yours first?
- What about me?
[Deciding to check Min Jung's bag first
with Gary on the lookout.]
Gary, stop searching your own bag and
keep your eye on the lookout.
- Don't look at your own bag right now.
- I'm just so curious.
[Mr. Gary unable to
sustain his own curiosity.]
I'm so curious.
[Unable to sustain his curiosity
and looks again in his bag.]
Why does he keep looking in his bag
even after we told him not to?
[If the other teams sees what he's doing,
they may figure out what's going on.]
It could be inside crevices like this.
Did you say that the mark was
inside the bag?
Don't say things like that
from over there!
Okay, I'll just sit here quietly.
[Detailed Jung Min and relaxed Gary
are total opposites.]
- You can't say things like that out loud.
- Okay.
[From what I can see...
Gary definitely is not the other agent.]
Hello?
You want to meet?
- Hurry up. What are you doing?
- Come here.
[Team Tiger calls
Kwang Ja out to them alone.]
- You're my opposing team.
- Okay, but come over here.
[Come here.]
Why are you grabbing my hand?
What is it that you guys know?
Do you know how this is
supposed to end today?
Do you know what we're supposed to do
for this mission today?
[Agent Kwang Ja pretending not to know
anything even though he's fully aware.]
No, I don't know. Why do you
keep asking me all these questions?
You don't know anything, right?
Then shouldn't you be working with us?
Because we know what's
going on here.
- Is the legendary book bag one of ours?
- No, it's not that.
We have to find the bag somewhere
from within this place.
You have to eliminate
Chun Jung Myung's name tag.
- If you do, we'll tell you everything.
- We'll tell you.
[Plans to use Kwang Ja to eliminate their
fiercest opponent, Jung Myung.]
[I know that I have to
eliminate him, but...]
Why do you keep cornering Kwang Soo?
[Just then, everyone else comes to
gather around where they're standing.]
- Jung Myung.
- Yes?
- Jung Myung. Why are you staring?
[Jung Myung isn't interested in anything else,
but to go head to head with Mr. Capable.]
[The real man wanting a real face-off.]
[You just wait.]
I heard there's a hint within the bags.
- I don't know what to do here.
- Why?
- You have to work with us.
- Is your bag the legendary bag?
[Ace Blank Ji with
her undoubtedly sharp eyes.]
I think our bags definitely
have to do with something.
So there is something inside our bags.
Maybe we'll find something
if we open our bags.
[Inside our bags?]
- I didn't see anything in there.
- Don't you remember the last time?
I think I may know.
Maybe we eliminate the name tags...
[Yes, I think I need to utilize this...]
I don't think it has anything
to do with the name tags
because I kept seeing the other
team members clutching onto their bags.
But what if they're faking it to divert us?
[In order to get these guys
to trust me...]
I think I know.
Min Jung already checked her name tag.
But nothing even happened.
- Really? She checked hers?
- Yes.
- But she didn't get ousted?
- I don't think it's the name tags.
[Just what is it that Kwang Ja
is planning?]
Want to try it?
She tried to steal my book bag,
so I ripped off her name tag.
- But what if this ousts him?
- I told you that nothing happened.
- You sure she didn't get ousted?
- Yes.
Okay, then I'll rip it off.
[Everyone pretending to be okay with the idea
and wanting to rip each other's tags off.]
- You told us she didn't get ousted.
- Are you sure that she didn't?
- Yes.
- Okay, then let's give it a try.
[His plan seems to be working.]
Try it.
I don't think this will get us ousted.
- Wait.
- So this won't oust him?
[Jae Suk's name tag is ripped off!]
Okay, stick it back on.
[It worked...]
Yoo Jae Suk, out.
- Why am I ousted?
- I didn't think that would get you ousted.
[Yoo Jae Suk's book bag will now go to
the person who ousted him.]
[Doing everything within his power
to maintain his composure.]
- I guess you're right.
- We were just testing it out amongst us!
- But Min Jung didn't get ousted?
- I thought you ripped off Min Jung's name tag!
- Then why didn't Min Jung get ousted?
- Maybe you didn't rip it off all the way.
You did this on purpose, didn't you?
No, I didn't.
I don't know anything about the mission.
[Laughing out of
the absurdity of the situation.]
- I do feel a little bad.
- I'm sorry too.
Don't do that from now on.
[About to go out of his mind.]
- We don't even know what the mission is.
- I have no idea what's going on here.
I'm sorry, but hand over your bag.
- Director...
- Give us your bag.
[The easiest elimination in
the history of Running Man.]
You guys can't do this.
[Kwang Soo's plan of ousting Jae Suk without
laying a finger on him is a huge success.]
[Still unable to believe
his current situation.]
I'm not the person that should be going
up to the jail right now.
I have a job to get done down there.
[Jae Suk- Out!]
- I can't believe that happened to Jae Suk.
- I do feel bad for him.
[Jae Suk's elimination still has them
reeling from the shock of it all.]
Jae Suk's elimination was such a surprise.
[Okay, I've eliminated Jae Suk.]
[But in order to get rid of him...]
I wonder whose bag is the
legendary bag?
[After three years of being on Running Man,
their abilities puts Sherlock Holmes to shame.]
I bet one of our bags is the legendary bag.
[How did they know that?]
[Everyone is starting to carefully
search through their bags.]
Hurry up and tell us what
you saw, Kwang Soo.
I didn't see anything.
I don't know anything either.
Then let's do this.
The other team needs someone
like Kwang Soo.
[All of them agreeing to send Kwang Ja in
to the other team to act as their spy.]
- I don't know what'll happen today.
- I'll be back.
[I need to start working
on the next step of my plan...]
The other team may get intimidated by
all of us acting like we know something.
It's better than not doing
anything, right?
Let's go there and act like we
know something.
- Ji Hyo, you lead, okay?
- Staying here isn't going to do us any good.
- I think we should go over and see them.
- They'll know I ousted Jae Suk.
That's why I don't think I'll be
able to eliminate Jung Myung.
- But what if...
- But I got Jae Suk ousted.
[Kwang Ja coming over and pretending
to join their forces.]
- There they are.
- They must be thinking the same thing we are.
[Everyone gathering up in one place.]
- I doubt you can know anything.
- You know something?
- You know anything?
- No, I don't.
Why don't we just simply
eliminate each other?
That's a nice and simple plan.
Let's just eliminate each other.
[Jung Myung finally wanting to start
eliminating each other's name tags.]
[He's starting to make his move.]
[This is dangerous.]
[Once that strong player starts to move,
that'll put me in danger too!]
[An outbreak of chaos could shed light
on the identity of the two undercover cops!]
[Jung Myung makes his move!]
[Min Jung is in danger!]
[Just then...]
[Secret agent Kwang Ja locks on
his target, Jung Myung!]
[While Mr. Capable is holding Jung Myung
tightly in his grasp...]
[Jung Myung's name tag!]
[Kwang Ja eliminates Jung Myung's
name tag!]
[Jung Myung disappointingly gets ousted before
he can even get his hands on a name tag!]
[This is insane.]
[Fearful Kwang Ja makes her escape.]
Kwang Soo just eliminated Jung Myung.
[Chun Jung Myung... Out!]
[Okay, now...]
[If I can just eliminate
Mr. Capable and Gary...]
[There are so many people to eliminate...]
[Which one of these two secret agents
will succeed in their plans?]
[Jong Kook is doing whatever he can
to protect Min Jung.]
[Ace Ji Hyo springs a surprise attack
on Ha Ha to eliminate him.]
[Ji Hyo starting to eliminate others
in order to gain the victory for herself.]
[What luck is this!]
Did you think that you'd be safe after
eliminating one of my team members?
[This is starting to look pretty good
for the two secret agents.]
Wow, Song Ji Hyo.
[Ha Ha- Out!]
[No marks indicating that Ha Ha could be
a secret agent under his name tag.]
[Okay, it definitely wasn't Ha Ha.]
[Ji Hyo eliminates Gary's name tag!]
[Could it be?
But it wasn't Gary either.]
Song!
Song Ji Hyo!
You're on fire!
It's me.
[Oh no... Mr. Gary's feelings are hurt.]
[Gary- Out!]
[Now there are five remaining survivors.]
- Come on.
- Come over here. We won't touch you.
- I don't trust you.
- Why don't you trust me?
- No, I don't trust you.
- Come here.
[Ace Ji Hyo seemingly having a good chance
at gaining the victory for herself.]
[Let me think about this for a moment...]
[Her eagerness to eliminate others...
She really is Ace Ji Hyo!]
[If I just leave her be,
that'll put me in danger too!]
[And my own protector, Jong Kook
could be put in danger too!]
[I'm sorry, Ji Hyo.]
[Min Jung inching her way
behind Ji Hyo's back.]
[Min Jung eliminates Ji Hyo's name tag.]
I'm so sorry, Ji Hyo.
I'm sorry, Ji Hyo!
Why did you do that, Min Jung?
[What is this stroke of luck?]
I'm sorry, Ji Hyo.
I have my own reasons!
- I'm sorry.
- Come here.
She's the epitome of a traitor.
[This is it.
The legendary book bag will be mine!]
[The secret document inside the
legendary book bag will be mine!]
[This is the final battle!]
[Jong Kook remains oblivious to everything
and continues to protect Min Jung.]
[Jong Kook has Kwang Soo in
his tight grasp!]
[Min Jung falls back into danger!]
[Just who will take possession
of the legendary book bag?]
[Jong Kook attacks Kwang Ja!]
I will be the best cop that I can be!
I will return upon the success
of my mission.
[I will...]
I will return upon the success
of my mission.
[By the split of a hair,
Kwang Ja's name tag is eliminated.]
[Ah... I was so close...]
[Agent Lee Kwang Ja fails
her mission.]
What is that?
What is that 'undercover cop' mark?
- You were an undercover cop?
- Wait a minute.
- What?
[Undercover cop...]
[Kwang Ja, it was you?]
[I had no idea...]
[And I tormented you all day...]
[What have we done to each other today
as fellow undercover cops?]
[Kwang Ja... I hadn't
even fathomed that you'd be...]
- You were an undercover cop?
- No!
[Kwang Ja fails her undercover mission.]
[Oh no...]
[I'm sorry, Kwang Ja.]
[I'll complete the mission
for the both of us.]
[Immediately turns their attention
onto Big-nosed Brother.]
[Easily eliminates him
with the help of Jong Kook.]
[Acting like they won the mission.]
What was that about the undercover cop?
[Undercover cop?
This is it.]
[Undercover cop, Min Jung
Eliminates Jong Kook's name tag!]
[Succeeds in eliminates every one
of the delinquents.]
[I did it!]
- Min Jung?
- Why is she an undercover agent?
You didn't know that either?
Why are you an undercover cop,
Kwang Soo?
[The two undercover cops' mission was
to eliminate all the other members.]
I barely stopped myself from
eliminating you first.
[Which one of these bags
is the legendary bag?]
[The secret document is said to be
inside that bag.]
[Oh?]
[Discovers the mark!]
[This bag had originally belonged
to Jae Suk from the beginning...]
[There's something in there!]
[Discovers the top secret document!]
I found it.
I found it!
[Undercover cop, Kim Min Jung...
Mission succeeded.]
[The name that could start a war.]
[The return of the wolf.]
[Middle aged wolf, Park Myung Soo.]
[The world who came to claim
even the Sunday nights for himself.]
You can't go in there by yourself.
You have to wait for me.
- Don't let him fool you.
- He's deceiving you.
You think I could win an award for this?
[A lamb that keeps getting
chased by the wolf.]
[Lamb, IU, who can handle anything.]
[The lamb who could bring the
claws out from the wolf.]
[The purely innocent lamb is long gone.]
[She's returned as a lamb who's even
stronger than the wolf.]
One more.
let me do it just one more time.
[It's time to start working together.]
[Survive or be vanquished...]
[The wolf and the lamb-
Who will be the victor of this war?]
[Next week's Running Man-
The wolf and the lamb.]
Subtitles by DramaFever