Subtitles by DramaFever
[Children's Day Special-
The ultimate heroes are headed your way!]
[A race amongst beasts]
[And...]
[The legendary battle
waiting for its finale.]
['King of Ddak-ji' title that he's
protected with his own life.]
[The moment that he flipped over
the ultimate ddak-ji...]
[You stole that title away from me.]
[Ever since,
I have been waiting for this day.]
[The legendary King Of Ddak-ji-
The final battle.]
[Choonchun's 'C' Development Center]
[1:00 p.m.]
What's this?
[Jae Suk arrives first on his own.]
This is making me nervous.
Is our guest going to be some
star athlete?
[Whenever clothing like this awaits them,
it's never very good news...]
No way.
Come on... seriously!
[As always, Jae Suk is in green!]
This is really making me nervous.
I'm sure someone is coming on the show.
I'm sure we'll have a guest, but...
Whenever there's a setup like this,
something big usually happens.
I think I should go upstairs
and hide out for now. Right?
- Should I go hide?
- For now.
We're going to start out with a race,
aren't we?
I'm going to be serious,
and play very earnestly today.
[The other members also start
to arrive one by one.]
Are we starting out with a race again?
[Everyone seems to be unhappy with
the idea of an opening race.]
I'll see you later.
The seventh Running Man is now entering.
I'm... am I the last one to arrive?
[All the Running Man members
are now here.]
I wonder who's going to be on today?
I was thinking about it on my way here...
Usually on days like this...
you know what happens, don't you?
Remember Chu Sung Hoon on the show?
It was like a nightmare in
the middle of the night.
[The legendary opening race.]
[Chu Sung Hoon's appearance
at four o'clock in the morning.]
Ryu Hyun Jin, Chu Shin Soo...
[The major leaguers that took the members
by the storm and left them in their awake.]
They always do something like this whenever
a really strong guest comes on the show.
I made a promise to the viewers that I'm
going to work very had no matter who it is.
Okay, I'm busy.
Need to go.
Wait...
I'm talking right now!
You can talk to your own camera.
I keep being reminded of the time when
Hyun Jin came on the show.
I thought he was a bear that had escaped
from the local zoo or something.
[I wonder who's coming...]
Eighth Running Man is now entering.
The perfect angel.
However...
There are beastly instincts
hidden within.
Beastly instincts?
[The first guest of the day
makes his entrance.]
[Gifted with the two faces of Janus-
charismatic and explosive personality.]
[Cha In Pyo]
Hello.
[The original muscle man-
The almighty guest!]
Since it's Children's Day...
I will do my best.
[On fire with motivation.]
Cha In Pyo now makes his entrance.
- What?
- Cha In Pyo?
[We're dead.]
Cha In Pyo now makes his entrance.
- Cha In Pyo with all his muscles?
- In Pyo!
- Wow... he's seriously competitive.
- His competitiveness is no joke.
- Wow...
- That is one tough guest.
[A man full of passion, Cha In Pyo.]
In Pyo really gets into it.
[I will show you what passion means.]
Ninth Running Man.
Huh?
- Ninth Running Man..
- Ninth?
[The surprise isn't over yet!]
Number one candidate for
next generation's Mr. Capable to-be.
next generation's Mr. Capable to-be?
[With a youthful smile on his face,
yet a man stronger than anyone else.]
[Ricky Kim]
[The strongest member of
'Laws of the Jungle'.]
[Jungle gladiator, Ricky Kim-
Fearlessly challenger of nature.]
Are we starting right now?
I feel like a gladiator.
Starting like this right away.
Number one candidate for
next generation's Mr. Capable to-be.
- Ricky Kim is now making his entrance.
- Ricky Kim?
Ninth Running Man,
Ricky Kim now makes his entrance.
No, no!
Not Ricky Kim!
I'm dead if Ricky Kim catches me.
Are you guys determined to
get us killed today?
Are you trying to get us killed?
This really is too much.
Ricky Kim is Jong Kook's level.
[Certainly is Mr. Capable of next generation!
Preparing himself for the chase.]
You'd better watch yourselves.
Today is looking very bleak.
Today is looking so very bleak.
That should be it, right?
You think there are any more?
They usually save the strongest person
for the very last with these things.
Tenth Running Man...
Tenth Running Man.
What is this?
The eternal titan of force.
The Nation's representing center.
Huh?
The eternal titan of force.
The Nation's representing center.
What?
National representative?
[The commander of the ultimate guests!
The ultimate final guest...]
[Republic of Korea's
living basketball legend.]
[207cm in height- 'National Treasure Center']
[Seo Jang Hoon]
[Shattering all previous records
is nothing to this man!]
[Korea's living basketball legend
who needs no further introduction.]
[An athlete who recently retired
this past March after 26 years of playing.]
I'm worried if I'll even be able to keep up
now that I'm retired and a bit out of shape.
Why don't you try going up
against Kim Jong Kook?
But Kim Jong Kook...
he's  like a master at what he does.
After having watched the show...
I don't think it's about the strength,
but it's all about the skills.
- But I will do my best.
- Thank you.
Seo Jang Hoon now makes
his entrance.
[Did his brain get short circuited
from the shock of hearing the news?]
[Let's just hide.]
[Name tag elimination race played
with the strongest of any guests in history.]
I'm in trouble.
This is big trouble.
[Four. Three. Two. One...]
Start!
[Race of the beasts - Start]
Who is that?
In Pyo!
It's In Pyo!
This is a big problem.
In Pyo!
It's In Pyo!
I said, it's In Pyo!
Get down here!
It's In Pyo!
That man leaves no room for mistakes.
No room for mistakes!
He wouldn't leave even an inch
of room for mistakes.
[Jae Suk in an extreme state of nervousness
from knowing In Pyo's personality.]
Do you see how he is right now?
Usually...
if you want to catch your enemies,
you have to expose yourself.
He's coming!
[Without even an ounce of desire to face
him, he just runs away for his dear life!]
[Did he see someone?]
It's Ricky Kim!
[He runs away to escape from In Pyo,
but gets caught by Ricky instead!]
[Breaks out into a dead run!]
It's Ricky!
[Huh? Ricky stops in the middle
of his pursuit?]
I just wanted to say hi,
but he ran away from me.
I just wanted to say hi.
He's much quicker than I thought.
[Jae Suk barely having escaped
with his life intact.]
I thought I was dead.
I thought I was dead for sure.
[Peek-a-boo!]
- In Pyo!
- Hello.
[This time, it's In Pyo?]
In Pyo... it's In Pyo!
So this is where you've been hiding?
[Having reached exhaustion from his
attempt to flee from everyone.]
Why is it that you're always acting so
scared when we do this stuff?
[Upset with having to run away all the time,
he takes his anger out on poor Gwon Yeol.]
You have more fear than I do.
Why are you the one getting scared
from having seen In Pyo?
[Hello!]
[In Pyo springs a surprise attack!]
[Every ounce of energy leaves his body
from the shock of seeing him.]
- Why are you doing this to me?
- This is a race.
Do you really need to go this far?
I caught you earlier,
but I just caught you again.
I just caught you again.
I'm so glad to see you!
Well I'm not glad to see you!
- I have to get going.
- Seriously!
In Pyo, seriously!
- Jae Suk... thank you!
- That's how he is!
You should've told me that
In Pyo was standing right there!
[Yoo Jae Suk - Out!]
You should've seen his expression.
His eyebrows were raised like this and...
There he is again.
- Seriously... why are you being like this?
- Don't be upset.
Why are you running around with
your zipper undone like this?
[Full of feverish energy!
The Cha fever is now fully unleashed!]
- You went easy on me, didn't you?
- What?
- You went easy on me, right?
- On you?
Because you were trying to be nice.
Yes, In Pyo.
I went easy on you.
- I did go easy on you.
- You really are a nice person.
I heard that you practically raised
Lee Jung Jae by carrying him around?
[A recent article that was all over the news
of piggy-backing Lee Jung Jae around.]
Ripping off my name tag is good and all,
but keeping me down with your knees like that...
[Jae Suk having lost his pride
and the race simultaneously.]
Thank you.
[Always ending things with a 'Thank you'-
Such good manners.]
He really doesn't leave anything out.
[On the other hand...]
All the exercising I've been neglecting...
I'm making up for it here.
[Breaking out in laughter
after having seen something?]
- There he is.
- He's coming this way.
[Why are they all overreacting so much?]
[Wow... Tiger and the Giraffe unite!]
- We're taller than you.
- We're taller.
[This is their plan of attack for
going up against Jang Hoon?]
We're much taller than you right now!
- The way I'm seeing this right now...
- You can't get past us.
This is the ultimate chance for me to
eliminate Jong Kook right now.
- Show him how fast we can be!
- Show him!
Show him, Kwang Soo.
Grab him. I know that you can do it.
I'm not very interested in Kwang Soo.
- Kwang Soo's really good too.
- You have no idea how formidable I can be!
- Hey!
- But...
Why is it that as I see Jong Kook's name tag
from the back, my hands are starting to itch?
[Mr. Capable's name tag bewitching
his own teammate.]
Don't misunderstand my intentions.
I think it would be a good idea
to protect your name.
Are you playing around right now?
What the heck? Who's doing that?
[As expected...]
Hey!
Stop it!
Hey, you scoundrel!
[Impossible to work together due to
the Giraffe's traitorous DNA.]
- Stop that, Kwang Soo!
- Jong Kook! Look!
[In the midst of this chaos,
Cha In Pyo starts heading their way.]
[Attack!]
- Long time no see.
- Hello!
And Gary, your donation of clothes
to the people in Africa...
- You sent several truckloads to my house.
- Seriously?
[Gary's act of generosity
that no one was aware of.]
Then I'll stay out of this for now.
- Where do you think you're going!
- Alright!
I don't know who's side I should be on!
Jang Hoon, you take Kim Jong Kook!
Jang Hoon, you take Kim Jong Kook.
[Pushing Mr. Capable, his toughest enemy
off to Jang Hoon?]
I really want to rip that off.
Move!
[Springs an attack on Gary,
who left his guard down for a split second.]
You fool!
[Ousted in a blink of an eye!]
[Gary is very easily ousted!]
- I can't believe that happened!
- How did that happen?
Ricky, don't come too close.
I...
[In the moment everyone seem to
momentarily let down their guard...]
[In Pyo seizes the moment they took to
greet each other to attack Ricky!]
[No one is safe in Ricky's eyes!]
[Almost took ten years off his life!]
There's no way you can let your guard down.
This is a real battlefield!
What was that?
[Total chaos where there are
no friend or foes in this battlefield!]
[In the meantime...]
[Two members of the Traitors Club who've
been staying in hiding from the beginning.]
- Really?
- We can start by eliminating our own members.
[False dreams of winning again.]
[The only safe way to hug amongst
the Traitors Club members.]
- That's our special hug.
- Why do I feel unsafe about being here?
I feel nervous too.
Seriously...
I feel more nervous being here with you
than I would about being with Cha In Pyo.
[Will these two...
be able to pull it off today?]
If we join our strengths...
I don't think there will be many
who'll be able to beat us.
In that case...
[Just then!]
[Ro-Ro starts approaching Ricky
from behind!]
Actually...
It's harder than I thought to keep your
hold on someone, so I lost two people.
There's a method of doing that.
[Attempting to approach through
the break in the window.]
[Kkuk is trying to divert Ricky's attention
elsewhere after having seen Haroro's approach]
So how...
[Cover blown]
[You dummy!]
Suk Jin!
[As expected, Big-nose betrays him.]
[Big-nose betrays Ro-Ro so that Ricky
doesn't suspect that he's Ro-Ro's ally!]
- You're so frustrating.
- Suk Jin!
[The promise made between these two
ultimately ends in betrayal yet again.]
Let's go up to the rooftop.
Let's all go up to the rooftop.
Okay? Let's all just face each other
out in the open space.
[In Pyo still overflowing with energy.]
[I need water.]
- I have some water here, Ji Hyo.
- No, it's okay, In Pyo.
- Just don't come close to me.
- I have some in my bag.
- Look at that glint in his eyes!
- His eyes are scaring me!
Look at his eyes!
Jang Hoon, you take care of Mr. Capable.
[Ricky ambushes In Pyo!]
[Ricky eliminates In Pyo's name tag!]
Ricky Kim!
I can't believe you did that to me!
We even rode here together.
But... what are we going to do now
that you've ousted In Pyo?
There are only two of us left now.
[Cha In Pyo - Out!]
- Suk Jin betrayed me and eliminated me.
- Really?
Cha In Pyo, out!
In... In Pyo's ousted?
- Oh my...
- In Pyo!
[Hides away his laser beam eyes,
and timidly enters the jail cell.]
- Who ousted you?
- Ricky.
- Ricky ousted you?
- I've raised a little tiger.
I told Ricky that... there are three
branches to American government.
- CIA, FBI and DTA.
- What's DTA?
Don't Trust Anybody.
(DTA)
[Don't Trust Anybody]
- Now that we're here on Running Man.
- There's a sense of elegance to this man.
You're saying that I'm not funny, right?
He just said that I'm not funny, didn't he?
It's not that you're not funny.
But don't you think he's elegant?
Can you show me rage filled
teeth brushing later?
- In Pyo doesn't do things like that.
- Oh yeah, I forgot about that.
In my attempt to brush my teeth like that,
one of my teeth broke off.
I had to get a dental implant.
Air always leaks through there.
[Stay tuned for this man's black hole-like
charm that will enrapture you today.]
[Only one door left acting as a barrier
between Ricky and the rest of the members.]
You go out first.
Go ahead.
[The original Mr. Capable
Jong Kook makes his move!]
- There they go.
- Really?
[Immediately faces off with each other!]
Shut the door.
Just shut the door on them.
[A battle between the two men.]
[Strength vs. Strength.]
[Getting flustered over the strength
shown by Mr. Capable.]
[He rips it off!]
- Who ripped it off?
- Ricky's been ousted.
[At the end of a very close fight,
Ricky Kim is ousted!]
[Flustered by Ricky's elimination,
Jang Joon starts to back away.]
- You're really going?
- Where are you going?
- I'm going home early. This is exhausting.
- Jang Hoon...
- I've been too sedentary since my retirement.
- Are you tired? This is tough, isn't it?
- This is exhausting.
This is something else.
Let me have the door handle.
[Feeling nervous,
so he's attempting to close the door.]
[Huh? What is that look he's exchanging
with Big-nosed Brother?]
[Let's do this together.]
- What? What are you planning on doing?
- He's been a junior of mine for a long time.
Really?
[I don't think so!]
[Members trying to stop their
alliance from forming.]
Hey, hey!
Hey!
[Jang Hoon rips off Big-nose's name tag
after proposing an alliance!]
You must watch Running Man all the time!
- That was a classic move!
- You know what Running Man is all about!
[Even knows to showcase the name tag of
the one eliminated for others to see.]
[Ji Suk Jin - Out!]
He was thinking the exact same thing
that I was thinking of doing.
- That was awesome.
- Where's he going? Are you going home?
Kwang Soo.
[Is Kwang Soo going after Jang Hoon?]
- Jang Hoon!
- Yeah?
Jang Hoon...
How about two against two right now?
- Let's go two against two.
- I told you, I watch the show all the time.
Giraffe!
What are you saying to him right now?
- Nothing!
- You!
Hey... you!
Lee Kwang Soo,
you're plotting something again?
He asked you to be his ally, didn't he?
I already know from having watched
the show quite a bit.
- I can't trust this guy.
- You can't trust him!
I can't trust him.
[Jang Hoon attacks the Giraffe!]
Wow, you're strong.
You're really strong!
[Unexpected battle of strength vs. strength?]
Should I just rip it off?
[They simultaneously grab
each other's name tag!]
[The Giraffe... was faster!]
[How can this be!]
Kwang Soo, you won?
That's unbelievable.
Seo Jang Hoon, out.
- I eliminated him!
- Kwang Soo...
Jong Kook!
I eliminated Jang Hoon!
- Jong Kook, I... come on!
- Kwang Soo!
Hang on a minute!
[Tiger immediately turning
around to attack.]
- Jong Kook! Come on, how could you...
- Kwang Soo...
Jang Hoon!
I'm sorry! What I did was wrong!
- Jong Kook!
- Kwang Soo, wait!
- Hang on a second!
- Kwang Soo...
[But, just then!]
Hey!
[Blank Ji, having stood by quietly
to watch the scene unfold...]
[Ambushes the Tiger!]
We could've talked this out when
I finished with him.
[No matter what the case,
Blank Ji is the winner of the opening race!]
I was really shocked this morning.
I had no idea that the three of you
would be on our show today.
It's the Cha-Seo-Ri trio!
[Guests formal introduction-
Cha In Pyo, Ricky Kim, Seo Jang Hoon.]
It's a special race today
to celebrate Children's Day.
- It is Children's Day today.
- With all of you, who love kids.
[That's why guests who love kids
have been invited to the show today.]
The final winning team of today's race
will donate 1,000 pairs of
tennis shoes which are very befitting of
our show to children in need.
[In the name of the winning team,
1,000 pairs of tennis shoes will be donated.]
- Wow!
- In the name of the winning team?
We'll be making a donation
through our show today?
Wow... I bet Cha In Pyo
will work very hard today.
[Fired up with motivation.]
To Song Ji Hyo who stayed alive to the end
in our opening name tag elimination game...
- Please accept this envelope.
- Wow, Ji Hyo!
[Opening winner, Blank Ji-
Wins the 'R' marked golden envelope!]
[An envelope that will give her a great
advantage at the final mission.]
Today's teams will be divided up
into teams of twos.
[Today's teams will be divided up
into two member teams!]
They have been divided up into teams
with a lot of history and deep relationships.
- But this isn't a couple's race.
- First up is Cha In Pyo.
- He will be teamed up with Yoo Jae Suk.
- What history does he have with me?
- You've done variety shows together.
- We've done one show together.
- Next up is Ricky Kim.
- Yes?
He'll be teamed up with Kim Jong Kook.
- There's no way!
- We're screwed!
- This isn't fair!
- They're the dream team!
We were on the show 'Dream Team'
together in the past.
Next is Seo Jang Hoon.
He will be teamed up with Ha Ha who's known
as the Basketball Ace on Running Man.
[Basketball Ace- Seo Jang Hoon and Ha Ha.]
We're the best!
- He doesn't seem very happy about it though.
- I told you not to do that.
[Two basketball lovers who have always
been close are teamed up together.]
The team that came in last in the
last race will get to go first.
- Go and change your clothes first.
- Men definitely need a good woman.
Men definitely need to meet a good woman
to have luck in their lives.
[Monday Couple with the good woman
is the first team to get on their way.]
[Go to the rail bike trail and find
the Running Man landmark.]
I think we're going to be riding
the rail bikes.
Jang Hoon, I've had quite a few
experiences of winning the race.
If we combine your tall stature and
my short stature together...
we can attack both the upper
and lower extremities together.
If we combine my tall stature and your
short stature, wouldn't that just be average?
No way, Jang Hoon!
Wow... you're just leaving me speechless.
If we combine your strength and my speed,
it's game over, Jang Hoon.
- Your speed?
- Yeah.
Jang Hoon, I'm the Kim Seung Hyun
of the variety land.
[Jang Hoon having watched Ha Ha for so long,
is having an even tougher time believing...]
Jang Hoon, what should we call our team?
- Hoon-two.
- What?
- Oh!
[Seo Jang Hoon + Ha Dong Hoon=
Hoon-Two.]
Hoon-Two-Cross!
- Thank you so much for inviting me on.
- Please don't mention it.
I know that you're struggling with
a sore throat and all right now.
- Thank you so much for being on here.
- I'm the one who should be thanking you.
I'm truly thankful.
I'm just thankful that it's
a sore throat and not pneumonia.
[In Pyo's positive thinking of being thankful
for a sore throat instead of pneumonia.]
I think you're very wise.
- Are you happy?
- Excuse me?
- Are you happy these days?
- Me?
- Yes, I'm happy.
- How do you relieve your stress?
- I'm not that stressed.
- You don't drink alcohol, do you?
- No, I don't drink.
- And you exercise?
Yes, I exercise.
I think I get most joy out of talking
and spending time with my friends.
- Is your blood type 'A'?
- No, I'm type 'B'.
[More and more, it's starting to feel like
Jae Suk is the guest on the show.]
I think it's really amazing that even
when you look on the internet
people have nothing but complimentary
things to say about you.
And it really makes me
somewhat curious about you.
- I wonder what it is that people...
- You're not about to say 'Thank you' again?
- You haven't said 'Thank you' again, right?
- Look into the camera and tell the viewers.
[Chuncheon Kimyujeon Station]
- Okay, let's go!
- Go, go!
- My clothes are too small.
- They're too small?
My clothes are way too small.
I don't know what to do about this.
- Yoo-ruce Willis?
- Yes, I am.
- What are you going to call me?
- What?
- Tidy Pyo.
- I'm only going to do enough for my namesake.
- No, don't do that.
[It seems he's not happy with his nickname.]
It will be more advantageous for you
to get there quickly.
Ugh, my legs hurt.
[Arriving at the rail bike platform.]
Oh yay!
Rail bike!
[Complete your mission while riding
the rail bike to win the shoes]
[and shoot it into the goal
at the station.]
As you ride the rail bikes along,
you're going to see various mission points.
Once you succeed those missions,
you will win yourselves a sticker.
And you will win the same number of shoes as
the number of stickers you collect later on.
And you will then use those shoes to
carry out further missions later on.
- I understand.
- Can we get going then?
Aren't those clothes
too small on you, Jang Hoon?
Please help me out with this.
- This is where you get on.
- Where do I sit?
- How many km is this?
- 8.2 km.
[Wow!
A whopping 8.2 km!]
- He says it's 8.2 km.
- Wow, that's really far.
It's Yoo Jae Suk again.
Yoo Jae Suk again!
- Seo Jang Hoon!
- Stop it.
Do you want to get beat?
Yes! Hoon of Seo Jang Hoon,
and Hoon of Ha Dong Hoon!
A cozy team!
Hoon-two Cross!
Seo Jang Hoon!
Lee Kwang Soo!
Thank you!
It's not like when you were overseas.
I will win this mission for you!
Hey! Lee Kwang Soo fervor doesn't really
last as much as it did overseas.
Stay strong, everyone!
[Shouldn't what we shouted out
be enough?]
Jae Suk, now that we're all seated
on the rail bike like this...
How does it feel?
How does it feel to be on these bikes
for the first time in so long?
Why do you keep saying 'thank you'?
You're on Running Man right now.
Don't do that, Jang Hoon.
- It's fun!
- What do you mean, it's fun!
[Ro-Ro and Jang Hoon bickering nonstop
without any moment of silence.]
In Pyo's back here
thanking me for everything!
Ha Ha, thank you!
In Pyo's back here thanking everything!
- We're going to get going now!
- Let's go!
Go, go!
Thank you!
[With the send-off from all these fans...]
Let's give everyone a round of applause!
Fighting!
[Rail bike- Start!]
- I feel like we're going on a picnic!
- Yay!
This feels really great!
Song Ji Hyo, Kang Gary!
[Monday Couple full of excited energy!]
How long are we going to
sing this for, Ji Hyo?
I really want to take in the
nice scenic ride.
[Along the beautiful
mountain and lake trails.]
[Automatically breaking out into a song,
and the spirits are automatically lifted.]
Hoon of Seo Jang Hoon,
and Hoon of Ha Dong Hoon!
Hoon and Hoon is Hoon-two!
We are Hoon...
Two!
Cha In Pyo is the best!
- Cha In Pyo!
- Just get him a train ticket! (Pyo=Ticket)
- What did you say?
- Train ticket!
You watch your mouth!
I'm Tidy Pyo!
Did you see?
Did you see that?
Keep it down, little kid!
Keep it down!
Go to school!
Shouldn't you be in school?
Hello!
[A peaceful rural village.]
- Now that we're riding along the rails...
- What are you going to say now?
- You're scaring me!
- With these beautiful mountains...
Doesn't it feel therapeutic
to be out here?
It would be therapeutic if I sat here in peace
but I can't get that because of you.
It would be therapeutic enough to
stare out at those mountains
but it's not therapeutic at all with
your incessant questions.
If there are things that you've been wanting
to say to your wife but you haven't...
I tell her everything!
I tell her everything I feel.
Because I'm such a chatterbox, I go
home and talk to her about everything!
Okay.
Okay...
- What is it?
- A tunnel! There's a tunnel coming up!
- Tunnel?
- Why? Is something up there?
- What? Tunnel?
- Tunnel!
[Staring intently?]
In Pyo! Why are you
staring at the tunnel like that?
It's because I want to rip off
your name tag.
It's because I want your name tag.
In Pyo's eyes shoot laser beams!
[In Pyo's eyes have the ability to
shoot off laser beams!]
- We're heading into the darkness!
- We have to be careful where we go.
If we go into the darkness,
our face isn't going to show up on TV!
What is this?
[Rail bike heading into the tunnel.]
- I can't see anything, Ji Hyo!
- Go away!
- Ji Hyo! I can't see anything!
- I said, go away!
I'm scared!
Ji Hyo, I'm scared!
Duck down, Jang Hoon!
You might hit your head!
Duck your head down!
- No!
- What's going on?
- I can't see anything!
- Our face isn't going to show up on TV!
- Ji Hyo!
- Get away!
- What's wrong with you?
You're supposed to be the man here!
Ugh! Why is that tunnel so short?
Ugh!
I almost had a chance!
What do you mean, you had a chance?
Can we just keep heading
into tunnels?
- Coming out of the tunnel like this...
- Yes?
- You know the scene in the movie...
- 'Peppermint Candy'?
[The infamous scene from the movie,
'Peppermint Candy'.]
[Re-enactment?]
I want to go back!
[Cha In Pyo's 'Peppermint Candy'.]
Did you see that?
You saw that?
You have to know this.
I didn't ask him to do that.
In Pyo did that all on his own.
- This is the kind of man In Pyo is.
- I want you to do that for me too.
- Why would I do that?
- Just show it to me once.
Then let's do it together.
One, two, three!
I want to go back!
Do it!
I want you to do it with me!
Why won't you do it with me?
Do it!
Come on and do it!
Do it with me!
Say, 'I want to go back'!
- Hurry up and do it!
- Seo Jang Hoon!
- Do it! Do it!
- Seo Jang Hoon, do it!
Do it!
[Bratty Ro-Ro not resting even
for a moment.]
207 centimeters is beating up
162 centimeters!
- If I had been teamed up with Ha Ha...
- If you'd been teamed up with Ha Ha...
I would've just gone back home.
- Aren't there going to be anymore tunnels?
- There's another tunnel coming up.
Where!
There is another tunnel!
[Another tunnel!]
There is another coming up!
- I hope this tunnel is like a kilometer long.
- A kilometer?
A kilometer?
[Heading into the tunnel
Kang Gary's been hoping for.]
Yay!
It's a tunnel!
- Ji Hyo! I can't see anything!
- Get away from me!
Ji Hyo, I can't see!
[Does he really have a fear of the dark?]
Hey!
Why are you turning on the light?
Turn off the light!
Turn that light off!
[Gary not liking the spotlight today.]
Look at the beams of light up there!
[What are those light beams
coming from inside the tunnel?]
[Club?]
It's music!
What is that?
[Immediately breaking out into a dance?]
What is this?
[A worldwide sensation-
'Gangnam Style'.]
[A tunnel dance party!]
[Jang Hoon being forced to dance.]
[So bothersome...]
Say what?
[Everyone breaks out into
the horse dance!]
[So bothersome!]
- Is everyone rested up?
- Yes.
- You'll be doing the pedaling from now on.
- Really?
[They must pedal on their own
to keep going from this point on.]
[Rail bike mission- At each mission point
that they'll be arriving in...]
[Succeed the mission and win the stickers!]
- Let's go.
- This is...
We can't go too fast.
We'll pass by it if we do.
[Still excited Monday Couple.]
[Coming out of the tunnel
and heading towards Gangchon.]
Wow... this place is perfect for a date.
[The beautiful scenery,
a perfect spot for a date.]
- I think there's something up there.
- What do you see?
Hey, Kang Gary!
- Let's rest a little!
- Aren't you going to pedal?
Okay, but there's no rush.
- You have to pedal with me!
- No one's behind us, Ji Hyo.
- Kang Gary!
- Okay, okay!
- Round one!
- Where? Where is it?
[Arriving at 'R1'.]
[Other teams are starting to arrive
behind them one by one.]
I think I see something up there.
- What is it?
- This is the 'R1' mark.
The game you'll be playing here
is the absolute pitch game.
Absolute pitch?
You know that I'm a singer, don't you?
Both members have to say the phrase given in
the right pitch and pronunciation in 30 sec.
- One person at a time?
- Yes, one person at a time.
- You'll have 30 seconds.
- In higher octave?
- Are we going to be reading something?
- What is it?
I don't know either.
- I'll go first.
- Okay.
[Gary and Ji Hyo- Challenge.]
Set, go.
[Chuncheon chapssal het chapssal.]
- Chuncheon chapssal het chamcham...
- Hey!
How am I supposed to do this?
[Current singer getting his tongue twisted
around by the pronunciation and pitch.]
[Fail]
- That's really hard.
- So this is how the new order is.
- I'll go first.
- Okay.
[Must head to the next location
if the mission is failed.]
- But Ricky is...
- I came from America.
- Can you give me an English phrase?
- Give him an English phrase.
Your team will have a full minute.
- Really?
- We get a minute.
- I'm really good at this game.
- Why are they getting a minute?
Why is this team getting a minute?
- Because he's from America.
- He's from America.
- What kind of a rule is that?
- Then you do it in English!
I'll give you a minute, so do it in English!
Okay, I'll move on.
[Okay... that's what we thought.]
You have to get going to
your next location.
- Are they leaving already?
- What's going on, Gary?
- You're leaving already?
- Yes.
You have to head to your next location
if you fail the mission here.
- Really?
- You have to do a good job.
There are still a lot of people here.
Me first?
Should I go first?
- You go first.
- I'll go first.
Set, go.
[Kkul dduk chal dduk kong dduk]
- It's over.
- He's not going to get it.
This isn't easy.
He's not going to get it.
[Oh?]
[As predicted, a difficult game for Ricky.]
- You're not going to get it.
- Anyone who can read can do this.
[But he's over here failing repeatedly...]
Keep it down!
You said 'gul ddeuk'.
You're not good at this.
- You're pretty bad at this.
- No way they're going to get this.
You know this game, right, Jang Hoon?
[Total concentration.]
[Not much time left on the clock!]
I got it the first time around.
- You didn't succeed.
- Time's up.
[Fail]
Everyone try this then.
- Make them all try this.
- Why would we do that?
- You all give this one a try.
- Just get going on your way.
- Just go on your own way.
- Go and leave us be.
- You have to get going on your way.
- Seriously!
- Get going, Mister.
- Ddukbokki.
- Ddukbokki!
It's so good!
Even though playing the game
is important
it's not good manners to be solely playing
the games while at a place like this.
[Gary's word of wisdom-
Games can wait until after a good meal.]
Team Hoon-two.
Hoon of Seo Jang Hoon!
Hoon of Ha Dong Hoon!
Team Hoon-two!
Jang Hoon, where are you going?
- I'm really getting sick of you.
- What are you saying?
- I'm getting sick of you.
- Why aren't you doing it?
[Big and tall brother getting sick and tired
of the little kiddo.]
I feel so bad for Jang Hoon.
Why did you give him such small clothing?
His jacket looks like a
belly shirt on him.
- Give him a triple XL or something.
- Who wears belly shirts anymore these days?
Get us a new bike for him too
while you're at it.
- Tidy Pyo is getting really antsy.
- I know. Let's get going.
If he doesn't start playing soon, he's
going to start asking me questions again.
[Mak guk soo dak gal bi]
[Kiddo Ro-Ro is doing a great job!]
[Big and Tall Brother's turn.]
[Oh?]
[Success]
Hoon of Seo Jang Hoon!
Hoon of Ha Dong Hoon!
Team Hoon-two!
Jang Hoon!
Did they succeed?
- Come this way!
- They succeeded?
They were really good.
They got it on the first try.
[Ro-Ro and Jang Hoon win
their stickers from having succeeded.]
- We did it to together.
- Hey, we've got 30 seconds.
- Stick that on, and be on your way.
- Yes.
In Pyo.
Let's do this!
[His voice is starting to get more hoarse
as time goes on.]
- In Pyo, what was that?
- Are you okay?
[Tidy Pyo's lethal allure wetting the appetite
of the viewers to join his fan club.]
You are too much fun.
I'll be the president of your fan club.
Fighting!
Set, go!
[Wang ahn heung paht jjin ppang.]
- Go.
- Can you do this?
It's because of my implant.
I can't get the pronunciation.
Why are you saying anything
about an implant?
[First time hearing the excuse of an implant
in the midst of playing the game.]
[The time is ticking...]
- I have an implanted tooth.
- Implant...
[Fail]
Just give us 20 seconds.
We wasted time talking about the implant.
I didn't have a real chance to do it yet.
[Wasted all their time from
talking about the implant for so long.]
We only had 30 seconds,
but we talked about the implant.
We'll acknowledge that.
We did talk about the implant.
- I will give them a break on that.
- No, we can't do that.
- This is driving me crazy.
- I'm going to join your fan club.
Go!
- Okay, let's go.
- Thank you, In Pyo.
Here's another one.
- What could this one be?
- Stop right here.
This mission is peel and
eat the potato.
You two first need to have your one arm
around each other's shoulders.
You have to have one arm around each
other and use only your other free arm
to peel and eat the potato.
Finish eating and whistle within 30 seconds.
Set, go!
- Okay.
- Ji Hyo, that's really hot!
- That's so hot!
- Hurry! We've only got 30 seconds.
- We've only got 30 seconds.
- Do we have to peel the skin off too?
- We have to peel the potato skin?
- We have to peel the skin.
- Ouch! That's hot!
- That's really hot.
- That's really hot!
- Don't put the peel on my leg!
- It's too hot on my legs!
- This is just too hot!
- Just eat it!
- Let's just eat it!
- Hurry!
[Time over]
This is too hot!
It's because we couldn't get
this peeled.
Why did you do that to me?
[Kkuk and Ricky's turn at the challenge.]
There you go.
Let's eat it.
- Hot!
- That's so hot!
[The heat permeating in their mouths.]
[Getting stuck in my throat!]
[Wow- They ate it all!]
We have to whistle.
[Ricky succeeds!]
You have to swallow it.
Swallow it altogether.
[He just needs to finish eating his potato.]
[Time over]
[Fail]
How did you do that?
- I ate a lot of it though.
- I ate most of it.
- I think there's food up there.
- I think so too.
[Jae Suk and In Pyo's turn.]
- It's all practically peeled already.
- This is way too hot!
In Pyo, this is really hot.
- Who's going to be able to eat this?
- Just eat it.
[These two each sticking half a piece of
the hot potato in their mouths.]
[Hot]
[Writhing their body around in pain.]
[The time is slowly ticking...]
I bit my tooth.
Are you okay?
Is it your implant?
- Are we good? We succeeded, right?
- You failed.
Why?
Is your implant okay?
[That aside, the real worry is Tidy Pyo...]
Since there are people following behind us,
we have to get there really fast.
- Let's hurry and succeed the next mission.
- Okay!
We have to hurry!
It's really far.
Even though the scenery is nice,
we don't have the chance to enjoy the view!
- I think we're losing bad.
- Yes, In Pyo.
- You can pretty much bet on coming in last.
- But you're Yoo-ruce Willis.
- That has nothing to do with this.
- When is Yoo-ruce Willis coming out?
- That's not every day.
- Only during water gun fights?
- That's Yoo-ames Bond.
- Ah.
- And who's Yoo-hyuk?
- Yoo-hyuk, that guy is...
He comes out once in awhile
when there's dancing involved.
So you're Yoo-ruce Willis, Yoo-ames Bond,
Yoo-hyuk and I'm Tidy Pyo?
Yes, you're Tidy Pyo.
I guess that's fair?
- I want something cool too.
- You need one too.
I don't want anything like the Cha-minator.
[Cha-minator?]
That's pretty good.
Cha-minator suits you.
- Cham-bo?
- How did you know I was thinking that?
- I don't like that.
- I was going to call you Cham-bo!
Cha-perman is pretty decent.
Cha-perman!
You can be the Cha-perman!
- You do seem like a superman.
- Cha-perman!
[Cha-perman.]
- Just where in the world is the next one?
- My legs are hurting!
Can we stop now?
Why is the fourth one so far away?
There it is.
[Gary and Blank Ji succeeds at 'R3'
and arrives at 'R4'.]
We're here.
What is this?
- You know what this is, right?
- Cookie stick.
Yes, it's a cookie stick.
['R4' mission- Must eat the cookie down to
1.5cm within 30 seconds to succeed!]
Do we only have one chance
to do this?
- Hang on. I need some lip-gloss first.
- Why are you putting that on?
Why are you putting that on?
- It's because my lips are dry right now.
- I need some water too.
Here it is.
We can do it more than once
within those 30 seconds?
You just need to succeed
within 30 seconds.
- Here.
- The opposite way.
I have to eat the chocolate?
Let's do this the first time.
Let's succeed in our first try.
- One try, okay?
- Okay.
We've already done this before.
Hang on.
We've already done this before,
but I'm feeling nervous again.
This is driving me crazy.
Why am I getting so nervous?
Let's get this done in one shot.
- Set, go!
- This is no big deal.
We don't mess around with
this game anymore.
- Success!
- Yeah!
- There's barely anything left!
- We're not embarrassed by this.
[Gary and Blank Ji succeeding
with their first attempt.]
Yes!
- I don't think any other teams can do this.
- How are other teams going to do this?
- You're not...
- This can't be?
1.5cm.
It has to be 1.5cm or less, right?
- You've got 30 seconds to do the mission.
- I'm not prepared for this yet.
Seriously...
Is this your first time?
- Is this your first time with another man?
- This is my first time.
- My first time. I'm really...
- In that case...
Why is your face getting red?
If you just hold it and stay still,
I'll take the lead.
- I'll trust you to do this then.
- Okay.
Set, go!
- Hey!
- What!
How close are you going to get?
[Another attempt.]
[Face is getting red.]
[Totally forward and aggressive?]
Is that snot that I just
got in my mouth?
Fail!
[Fail...]
Is the time over?
Let me at least check how long it is.
How are we expected to succeed
this mission?
[More than 3cm in length...]
Why were your lips trembling like that?
- I was feeling really embarrassed.
- You must've lost your mind.
- It's because that was my first time.
- Do you like me or something?
Suk Jin...
- It's over.
- I think it's over.
Let's hurry up and go.
All these gnats...
[Jang Hoon, who doesn't like to be bothered
is getting beleaguered by gnats.]
You should've been dancing
like that back there!
I think there were pictures
taken of us on the rail.
- Thank you.
- This is going to be a lifelong memory.
Thank you.
We're both frowning in the picture.
Seo Jang Hoon!
Did you have to pass through
an army of gnats back there too?
Did you see all the gnats back there?
- You didn't get any in your mouths?
- We succeeded our mission.
- Gnats?
- An army of gnats!
- Wow... your picture came out nice.
- I wonder what I was glaring at.
Your picture came out really nice.
You look very charismatic in the picture.
I just have my eyes opened.
These are the steps where you'll be
playing basketball with your shoes.
- Basketball with our shoes?
- Do you see the yellow heart up there?
The team with the most number of shoes
in that yellow zone wins the game.
Even if it's grazing the line,
we will accept that for a point.
- That little heart up there?
- The yellow heart.
- The one way up there?
- That's impossible!
- Our writer landed five in there earlier.
- No way!
- That's absurd!
- Show us a video proof.
- I'm trying to help you be more comfortable.
- You think this is comfortable?
- I'm giving you a chin rest.
All those stickers that you've gathered by
succeeding your missions?
Depending on the number of those stickers,
we will give you extra shoes.
You all have the shoes you're wearing
to play the game with
and as many extra shoes as the number
of the stickers that you've won.
What about us?
[Jae Suk and In Pyo who didn't succeed
at winning any stickers.]
In Pyo has hard time seeing,
and he also has an implant.
Don't you think he needs to be
compensated for that somehow?
If he has such a hard time seeing,
why has been glaring like this the whole time?
It's because he has a hard time seeing!
It's making me get teary eyed right now.
Are any parts of him normal?
The reason why In Pyo's glare is like that...
It's not because he's fierce,
but it's because he has bad vision.
Jang Hoon apparently burned his hand on the
potato and he had to show it to me.
He showed off his fingers to me
and told me he burned his fingers.
You can't use excuses like that.
You know what he kept saying to the
staff members earlier?
He asked if the staff members deliberately
brought in the gnats to bother him.
[Adorable grumbler who's dissatisfied
even with the state of nature.]
It's because the gnats were only
in that small area.
I'm embarrassed to be going around
with him as my partner now.
Does everyone understand the rules?
- Yes.
[Suk Jin and Kwang Soo to start off
the game with their two stickers each.]
Challenge!
- I think we can do this.
- Lets do this!
You've still got it, Ji Suk Jin!
[Sends it flying off in the right direction!]
[Fail]
- Kwang Soo!
- Challenge!
Lee Kwang Soo!
[A chant that dies off quickly.]
It certainly doesn't last long
like it did overseas.
- It's like those gnats.
- Why do you keep saying that?
[The crowd is already settled down.]
- Challenge!
- He's blessed by the variety gods though.
- I bet he'll do something.
- Sorry!
I heard that it's a lie.
[Giraffe becoming victim to
Yoo-hyuk's joking around.]
People over there were cheering you on,
and people over here called them out on it.
- Why did you have to tell me that?
- You should know the truth!
[Giraffe loses his drive,
and fails at his first attempt.]
Don't block the camera.
- One more time.
- Let's go.
[Kicking off the shoe with all his might.]
[It's flying off in the right direction...]
- It's too short.
- Okay, a little bit stronger with the kick.
The kick is too short.
- Too short!
- Coming in too short is his constant issue.
- That was too short.
- Being too short is his problem.
- He's always too short.
- Jang Hoon, fighting!
- Wow, he's so tall!
- He's so tall!
I've never seen anyone
taller than Kwang Soo before!
- Jang Hoon is much taller than Kwang Soo!
- She said he's taller than Kwang Soo.
Kwang Soo does look much shorter
than usual right now.
[Come on...]
Are you joking around right now?
So cute!
Get out of my way.
You're so exhausting!
He tells him to get out of his way,
and said he's annoying.
It's not the game that's exhausting,
but you're the one exhausting me.
- Here I go!
- You know what his nickname used to be?
[Kkuk's turn at the challenge.]
His nickname used to be poop fly.
[The shoe is in the air!]
[Now if it'll just roll down one step!]
[Ah...]
- That's too bad.
- I thought you had it for sure.
- Challenge.
- In Pyo!
[Cha-perman Tidy Pyo's turn.]
[The music that we're reminded of
whenever that glint is seen in his eyes.]
[Just like that fierce glint in
his eyes back then...]
[1994- 'Love is in your embrace'.]
I'm getting that feeling again.
[Imitating him from the scene.]
[Hm...]
[Just sends it flying off into the air
without any direction...]
Jong Kook didn't teach me right.
- Don't do things like that.
- No, I didn't!
[Yoo-hyuk's turn.]
Anyone who scores
even one is going to win this.
This is really a one-time opportunity.
The best method is to throw it up really high
and have it roll down to the goal.
- I have to hit it above it, right?
- Yeah, throw it above it.
[Did he do it?]
[Bounces off the step into
the yellow heart?]
[Wow!]
[Success!]
[Amazing!
Directly in the yellow heart!]
I did it, In Pyo!
[Amazing...]
- That's unbelievable!
- The variety gods are with you!
The variety gods have not abandoned me!
That's unbelievable!
- That was amazing!
- It landed right in the middle!
We have to knock it out of there.
I'm getting nervous now.
[Will Blank Ji be able to do it?]
[Fail]
[Random Mr. Capable Gary also fails.]
[Yoo-hyuk's shoes holding steady.]
[Last turn with Kwang Soo at the bat.]
There's no way he's going to
knock that out of the way.
[No way...]
[Did the variety gods bless him
again today?]
[Unbelievable-
Almost knocks it out the way!]
[However with the accurateness of
Yoo-hyuk's landing, he wins the game!]
[Too bad. He almost knocked it
out of the way...]
[The battle of the variety gods?
Anxiety ridden final moments.]
This is something to be proud of!
[Jae Suk and In Pyo wins!]
[They win the mysterious envelope!]
[Go to Namsan's branch school and
find the Running Man landmark.]
I really hope we get to do something
that requires us to use our strength.
The really important thing is who's left
laughing at the last moment.
- Really?
- We just need to be the last one laughing.
[Arrives at the mission location.]
[Chuncheon's
Namsan Elementary branch school.]
[All the separate teams each
arriving at the athletic field.]
- What is this?
- What is this chair for?
What is this?
It's marked with the 'R'.
[What is this one single mystery chair?]
Your next mission...
is the king's throne game.
- King's throne?
- That's what we're playing?
Yes, King's throne.
Do you see the chair in front of you?
The moment that you hear the whistle
sounding the end
the team that's left sitting on
that throne wins the game.
[Even at a quick glance,
it's a battle of strength?]
- What are you expecting of us?
- Strength!
Only one person can sit on the chair
and the other person on the team can fend off
other teams' attempt to steal the seat.
But to be honest, Jang Hoon is too big
for any of us to fight off.
If you look behind you,
we've drawn a white boundary line.
You have to start from outside that line.
- Jang Hoon is way too big!
- Gary and Ji Hyo have the biggest disadvantage.
- How are we supposed to shove him off?
- This is almost too embarrassing.
[Grumbling about it being too humiliating
if he doesn't win this game...]
And also, Jang Hoon chatters on a lot.
He's nonstop!
[Adorable chatterer and grumbler.]
And don't you have anything larger
for him to wear?
No kidding.
- You can see his belly.
- What is this supposed to be?
He's the only one wearing
a belly tee around here.
You look so sexy!
[Way too small on Jang Hoon...]
Order of winning is very
important right now.
Winning isn't what's important,
but the order you come in is important.
- Is that right?
- The order we come in?
[Darn...]
Okay, you have two minutes
for the first round.
Set, go!
[Ricky Kim showing his determined
focus right from the beginning.]
- There's no reason to sit down now.
- Ji Hyo!
[Ji Hyo somehow steals the seat
away in the midst of all that chaos.]
I'll protect you, Ji Hyo!
You just sit tight!
[Resorting to tickle tactics.]
You're being too much!
Get out of the way!
Hey, stay put in that seat.
[Giraffe with his ability to
withstand all the tickling.]
[Lifts up his long legs to eliminate him.]
That's hilarious.
All you have to do is lift up the legs.
[Ejected from their seat before they
even have the time to get used to the seat.]
All you need to do is lift up the legs.
Lift up the legs, and they fall over!
- You can't do that to the seat.
- You have to sit on it.
- You try it, Jang Hoon.
- Sit and wrap your legs around.
[Is it finally Jang Hoon, the Goliath's turn?]
All we have to do is lift up his legs.
[He's falling over too?]
[The National Center
easily getting flipped over?]
- Watch out for his head.
- Are you okay?
- Yes.
- Are you okay, Jang Hoon?
- 30 seconds left on the clock!
- We have to flip him over!
[Cha-perman uses that moment
to steal the seat!]
[Must withstand the next 30 seconds!]
[A fierce battlefield!]
[The throne is mine!]
[Total chaos!]
[The Tiger somehow sits himself down
in the midst of all that chaos!]
[Utter chaos]
[Power of the tiger... come to me!]
[Only five seconds left on the clock!]
[Time over!]
[Jong Kook and Ricky wins!]
Ricky!
We finally did it!
- Strength!
Strength!
What the heck was that?
Now we have third, fourth
and fifth place left.
[Easy Brothers came in at second place.]
Seriously...
Set...
Can we take a 30 seconds break?
- Jang Hoon is...
- Go sit down there for now.
He's not good at the games,
and he's too big of a softie!
He says he feels too bad about
using his strength on others.
[What is this?]
What are they doing?
What are you two doing?
We're we too quick to get in this position?
We jumped the gun, didn't we?
I think we were too premature.
[Too premature with their plan
to withstand the attack.]
In Pyo, you were too premature.
You were too premature about this.
Who cares?
I'll just stay.
You've got 20 seconds left.
I'll push him forward.
I'll push him off the chair.
[The throne not looking so secure.]
[Yoo-hyuk ejected from
his seat within a second.]
[Just who will come in at third place?]
- No!
- Get off!
[Oh? Cha-perman?]
[Huh?]
[Cha In Pyo steals the seat!]
It was me!
It's not me?
In Pyo... In Pyo!
- You need to get off of me.
- Why is Jang Hoon not doing anything?
Why are you bad at these games?
Cha In Pyo and You Jae Suk wins!
- In Pyo, you did it.
- You really won at the last minute.
[Cha-perman's reverse in
the final moment.]
- You really stole that at the last second.
- It really was at the very last moment.
- This is the type of man In Pyo is!
- Wow, at the very last moment.
You really took that at the very last second.
- Seriously...
- What is he doing with that belly shirt!
- Hey...
- He's a total goof!
- He really is a goof.
- But he grumbles nonstop!
But do you know what he's
going around saying to us?
He's saying that if he plays seriously,
he's going to hurt everyone.
What do you mean,
you're going to hurt someone?
[Feeling humiliated...]
- Leave me alone.
- Why are you trying to look cool?
- I'm going to go crazy?
- What's going on with you?
I don't think those two are
going to be able to lift him off though.
[This is so embarrassing...]
- You have to trade your places around.
- 30 seconds on the clock.
Why even bother trading places
when there are only the four of us?
- Unbelievable.
- There is goes grumbling again!
- All he does is grumble!
- It's Eun-two, not Hoon-two.
Quietly-grumbles.
(Play on Korean words)
Yeah, he's really bad.
[Extreme dissatisfaction.]
This is really humiliating.
So can we get this show on the road?
The time on the clock is 30 seconds.
- 30 seconds? That's short.
- That's a short time frame.
Set... go!
Ji Hyo... don't overexert yourself.
Yeah, grab him and get him
out of the way.
[Is he telling Ro-Ro to take care of Gary?]
Wait, Ji Hyo...
I...
I'm really sorry about this.
You know it would be too humiliating
for me to come in at last place.
What are you doing?
You have to sit down, Ji Hyo!
[Blank Ji's on the seat!]
[Monday Couple wins!]
Ji Hyo!
Ji Hyo, you did it!
What the heck?
Jang Hoon!
What right do you have to
get ticked off?
Jang Hoon! What have you
done to get ticked off about?
Seo Jang Hoon really didn't do anything.
He just hovered over Ji Hyo...
[Too mannerly to throw Ji Hyo off the chair,
and the game ends with him hovering.]
- He's too much of a gentleman.
- He should've taken Gary!
He's a real man.
That's a real man.
- Why didn't you get her off the chair?
- How was I supposed to do that?
You should've done what you
did to Jong Kook!
Gary and Ji Hyo, come here.
As you all already know,
Jong Kook and Ricky are in first place.
- First place!
- And second...
Third, fourth and fifth place consecutively.
You have to remember this order.
We will now immediately move over
to our next location.
- Let's go.
- The final battle isn't far off now.
In Pyo love...
- I just joined his fan club today.
- In Pyo is...
Even though he may be
a bit older now
he still has youthful vitality,
and is skilled with his words.
He really is a treasure to the variety land.
- Please continue your love for him.
- Please keep showing your love and support!
- Inpyolove.net.
- Dot net!
- I hope you show him lots of love and support.
- Seo Jang Hoon, get out here!
Seo Jang Hoon, get out here.
[Calling him out to a duel?]
We need to determine who's the boss
within our team.
- Seo Jang Hoon, get out here.
- Hey, Jang Hoon!
Jang Hoon, go and show him
what you've got.
- This is so humiliating.
- Think of this as your own neighborhood.
This is too humiliating.
Jang Hoon, take ten seconds and show him.
- But if I do this and lose... no way.
- Jang Hoon!
Bring out the beast inside you!
[A nervous goliath.]
I have a weird feeling
that I'm going to lose!
Jang Hoon's really stressed out right now
because of Ha Ha.
[Been stressed out all day
because of Ro-Ro.]
Jang Hoon's more stressed about being with
Ha Ha rather than being on the show.
Ugh, I'm so embarrassed!
You can't lose here.
- This round is...
- Do I really have to do this?
Yes. This is to determine
who the weakest player is.
[The battle to decide who the
weakest player of the game is.]
You will have 20 seconds.
[20 seconds on the clock.]
I'm going to bet my money on
Ha Dong Hoon!
I bet everything I have on Dong Hoon!
- I also bet on Ha Dong Hoon!
- Ha Dong Hoon for me too!
- Okay, 30 seconds.
- Just do 20 seconds.
[Even through all the grumbling, he
still does everything that's asked of him.]
I feel like we're back in elementary school.
[This feels like a fight between the big and
the little kid back in elementary school.]
- It does, doesn't it?
- Ten seconds left!
[Ten seconds left on the clock!]
Throw him out!
[They're finally at it!]
[A real match between the
Heavyweight and the Lightweight]
[Jang Hoon wins!]
Why are you using your
strength only on me?
Why couldn't you do that earlier?
Why!
Are you happy that you won?
You happy now?
Look at me!
Let's do it one more time!
He's stressed out.
He grabbed your head like
it was a basketball.
This is so aggravating.
[What is the next mission that stressed
the importance of the winning order?]
[At last... the highly anticipated
final mission!]
- What is this?
- What could it be?
Is it a dance competition?
- What is all that?
- Ah! Those are the 1,000 pairs of shoes!
[A thousand pairs of shoes on top
of a specially prepared stage!]
If we win this, a thousand pairs of shoes will
be donated in the name of Easy Brothers.
This is really cool.
Running Man really is very cool.
A thousand pairs of shoes?
[Touched by seeing the thousand pairs of
shoes that are to be donated.]
These shoes are going to be donated to
people who have no shoes to wear.
[More meaningful than any other prize!]
A pair of shoes can give hope to a person
and get them back on their feet.
But I really think that I'm
being drawn in by Cha In Pyo's allure.
[Falling in love with In Pyo's generous
and giving heart.]
[Everyone sign up for
In Pyo's love website!]
- I signed up today too!
- Everyone should sign up.
I'm so impressed by In Pyo's personality
that I joined his fan club.
Our final race for the special
Children's Day episode today is...
- What is it?
- Is it a top spinner game?
It's a game that the children voted to be
one of their favorites on Running Man.
- What could it be?
- Ddak-ji?
[The final mission, Ddak-ji battle!]
[To start off the game,
each team receives two Ddak-ji's.]
Everyone get their Ddak-ji?
Then those of you who won mission envelopes
will now receive their benefits.
You will receive an extra certificate which
gives you the chance to exchange your Ddak-ji.
We have one of those too!
[Gary, Ji Hyo and In Pyo, Jae Suk each
possess one of those certificates!]
You also have been given
one of the certificates.
Okay, the team that came in at fifth place
will compete with the team in fourth place.
- That's good!
- So you work your way up?
And the winner of those two
will battle with the third place winners.
The winner of those two will battle
with the second place
and finally, the winner from that battle will
have the final match with the first place.
You don't need any more Ddak-ji,
do you, Jong Kook?
The win is as good as in the bag!
We don't need any more Ddak-ji!
- First place has a great advantage.
- They have a huge advantage.
- They pretty much won this already.
- It's not because we're in the first place.
But we have the advantage
because of me. Right, Jae Suk?
It's because of me.
It's not because we're in the first place,
but because of me.
- He seriously...
- Ddak-ji King!
Then let's start this.
[The old and new king of Ddak-ji...
who will be the ultimate victor?]
[Fifth place Ha Ha and Jang Hoon vs.
Fourth place Gary and Ji Hyo.]
[No going easy this time!]
[Ddak-ji- start!]
- Chance!
- Fighting!
This is the best part about playing Ddak-ji.
Gary wears those runner shoes when
he's about to break out his moves.
- He's about to bring it.
- His shoes gives him leverage.
[It flipped over!]
[Gary eliminates one of Ha Ha and
Jang Hoon's Ddak-ji!]
[Gary was pretty good with
the Ddak-ji too now that we think about it.]
Gary's really good at this.
[Ha Ha and Jang Hoon's chance
to counterattack!]
- This is your chance!
- Get closer, Jang Hoon.
- Okay.
- Don't move from that position.
You can hit it, right?
You just need to hit it.
- Hit it from the top.
- You just need to hit the Ddak-ji.
If I don't hit this,
then I'll be humiliated again.
- Hit it from the top.
- Just hit it really hard.
- There you go.
- Your form doesn't look right.
You have to hit it directly above it.
[Very different than when he
used to play basketball...]
Is it over?
Is first round over?
[Ha Ha and Jang Hoon - Disqualified.]
[Gary and Ji Hyo move up to
the next round.]
- Why is he so good?
- Is it over for us?
[It's over...]
[Jae Suk and In Pyo vs. Gary and Ji Hyo.]
[The battle between the original Ddak-ji king
and the Ddak-ji genius.]
If we don't get it the first time,
Gary will definitely flip it over.
He's that good?
- Let's not think too much about it.
- Don't think too much about it.
There's no reason to even
think about it.
- Let's do this.
- I'm not thinking about anything at all.
- Let's not think about anything.
- Please.... just one chance!
- Just give us one chance.
- No thoughts!
If you play this too much,
you start to lose your strength.
[Jae Suk easily eliminates one.]
The Ddak-ji king has returned!
Yes!
[Ddak-ji king showing us what class
is all about from the beginning.]
Let's do this again.
- Nice!
- That's good, Ji Hyo!
- Nice job.
- That's good.
- That makes it harder to flip over.
[Not even budging.]
- She stomped that to the ground.
- That didn't even move.
- That's right.
- That's how you do it!
- Good!
- You're better than Jang Hoon.
- Yeah.
- I had a feeling I'd lose.
Please... just one more chance!
Oh my!
[Missed hit]
- What luck is this!
- What was that?
- I can't believe I did that!
- How could that have happened?
- You're acting really happy about this.
- In Pyo...
- All that nervousness sapped me of energy.
- You have to hit it right in the middle.
- Don't be too nervous about it.
[Ddak-ji king's turn to counterattack!]
[He flips it over!]
[If he flips over one more of Gary
and Ji Hyo's Ddak-ji, the round is over!]
You have to take this very seriously.
Gary's team is a very strong team.
- If we don't get it here, we're in trouble.
- I'm sorry, but who's the champion?
- We have to make it entertaining, right?
- Okay, I got it.
We have to keep it entertaining.
- There's your chance, Gary!
- You can do this, Gary!
This old man keeps walking around watching
with his hands in his pockets.
Where's your home?
Are you from around this neighborhood?
- Ask him if he's hungry.
- Isn't this fun?
You're so tall!
- You're a sight around here.
- You're really annoying Jang Hoon.
Would you like some noodles?
Listen... Gary has to concentrate right now.
[Ddak-ji genius Gary...
will he able to overcome this obstacle?]
I can do this.
- I hit it on the mark too.
- That was a good hit.
If I don't flip this over,
we'll be in danger.
[Jae Suk eliminates all three of
Gary and Ji Hyo's Ddak-ji!]
Very cool.
[Oh.. not bad...]
- That was very cool.
- I wish you the best of luck.
Thank you.
I will win this for both of us.
Go out there and flatten Jong Kook, okay?
I will make it to the finals no matter what.
Next team, come on up!
[Suk Jin and Kwang Soo vs.
Jae Suk and In Pyo.]
What are we going to do?
[Even though he's down with a bad cold...]
[But since he's on the show today,
he's going to show off his tough side!]
Stay back.
You may get hurt if you're too close.
I would've taken off my jacket if I was told
that it was okay to do that earlier.
- What kind of a slamming method is that?
- It's In Pyo's special move!
[The legendary master moves!]
[Definitely psyching himself up.]
I'm really going to sign up
as a member of his fan club.
[Focusing and gathering up all his senses.]
We're accepting new members to
Inpyolove.net!
- Please.
- Everyone keep it down.
Give me at least one chance!
Look at the laser beams
shooting out of his eyes.
What if he misses?
- Don't pay attention.
- I'm sorry.
[In that one blow of Ddak-ji...]
[All his energy is being focused.]
[Total miss.]
[Oh no...]
What was that?
Where are you throwing that thing?
I can't see very well with my sight.
Someone get him a pair of glasses.
[Is he blaming his miss on his old age?]
He's serious about having bad vision.
- Ugh, I'm cold.
- I'm going to lose my mind.
[After taking off his jacket with fanfare,
now he's cold all of a sudden...]
- He says he's cold now.
- You should've just hit it normally.
[Suk Jin and Kwang Soo's turn
to counterattack.]
- There we go. In Pyo!
- He didn't flip it over?
- No, he didn't flip it.
[Takes it off again.]
Which one?
Which one is mine?
The blue one.
That one right there.
[After his show of his legendary moves,
he's slightly confused.]
Show us your legendary moves one more time.
You mean moving my arms,
back and shoulder muscles around?
I don't think he's going to hit it.
Back muscles, shoulders and your sides...
you have to move it altogether.
- Back, shoulders and the sides together.
- I have another move.
Flesh, flesh, my round flesh.
Make my flesh as tight as a board.
Where did my flesh go!
[Raising the bar for side exercises
to a whole new level.]
This is your side exercise.
Flesh, flesh, my round flesh.
Make my flesh as tight as a board.
- I can't get my balance.
- Are you okay?
Hurry up and do this!
[That exercise isn't used
in a time like this.]
This is what you do instead.
What's that now?
This is working your S-line.
Let's all take a walk... thank you.
What is his deal?
He's driving me crazy.
[Stops in the middle of a flip!]
- That should've flipped over!
- You almost had it!
[In Pyo finally having figured it out.]
- You get it now, right?
- I get it now.
[He flips it over!]
- That was good, Kwang Soo.
- I did my best though.
[Jae Suk and In Pyo still have
two Ddak-ji's left over!]
- You still have on left?
- No, we have two left.
- Wow, Kwang Soo...
- This is our chance.
Let's do this, Kwang Soo!
[Giraffe's confidence is way up!]
[I will end this!]
[Is he already depleted of his energy?]
- You're already out of energy?
- You have to recharge yourself.
[Ddak-ji king's counterattack.]
Why is everyone taking off their clothes?
[It flipped over!]
[If he flips one more over,
Jae Suk and In Pyo are in the finals!]
It only hit the side.
I wasn't going to take off my clothes
since I don't like doing that.
But why is it that you don't look threatening
at all when you take your clothes off?
If anything, you look really cute.
- You look like a honeybee.
- Ji Suk Jin, the honeybee!
[Ji Suk Jin's special honeybee outfit
in honor of Children's day!]
- The honey is mine!
- It's honey!
Why didn't my stylist bring me
something more fierce looking?
You know those shirts with
bolts of lightning painted on them?
- What the heck is this?
- It's honeybee shirt!
It should've been a shirt with
skulls or something on it.
Just hurry up.
[Jae Suk and In Pyo move on
to the finals!]
[Rather than calling it the finals...]
[It's time to determine who the
true Ddak-ji king will be...]
[Legend of Ddak-ji, Yoo-hyuk that
everyone first saw...]
[The one day...]
[That legend... came to an end.]
[Even though he lost his throne...]
[The battle was lost due to a mistake.]
[The Ddak-ji King... is Kim Jong Kook.]
[But today...]
- You want to win really badly, don't you?
- You're so spiteful!
- You really want to win, don't you?
- You really are so spiteful.
Since you haven't won at all lately.
[You dare to steal my throne?]
[Today, someone will be crowned king...]
[And the other will fall from grace.]
[Jae Suk and In Pyo vs. Jong Kook and Ricky.]
[Flattening it as much as possible.]
-  Ddak-ji of rage.
- Have you seen  Ddak-ji of rage before?
[In Pyo is definitely the ultimate
teammate one could ask for!]
He's just doing pushups.
- He's much worse than me!
- He's just doing pushups!
He's just doing pushups.
Pushups of rage.
Here I go.
- Here I go.
- Go ahead.
- Why didn't it flip over?
- This isn't going to be an easy battle.
You have to loosen up a bit first.
Remember from earlier.
It's all about your balance.
Like this, In Pyo.
You need to hold it like this.
There you go.
No!
Loosen up your thumb.
You have to give it a burst of power
at the very last moment.
Everyone... thank you, seriously.
- You know that I'm thankful, right?
- Put all your passion into this!
Put all the passion in your life
into this hit!
There you go!
[Too bad!]
Why is everyone getting so worked up?
I didn't think it was going to flip.
Why are you talking so much?
He really does talk a lot.
[The current Ddak-ji king's
higher level of attack.]
[At last...]
[Who will become the ultimate Ddak-ji king?]
[Remaining Ddak-ji count-
Jae Suk and In Pyo- 1; Kkuk and Ricky- 2.]
[Jae Suk's last remaining Ddak-ji
holds out!]
[The most nerve-wrecking moment of Ddak-ji
in the history of all Running Man Ddak-ji games.]
- Let's spin the camera. Let's go.
- This is your chance, Jae Suk.
[Will the Ddak-ji king's throne
be returned to the original king?]
There's too much of a gap
under that thing.
I'm the original Ddak-ji king.
I have to beat Kim Jong Kook.
Seriously...
I will reclaim my title as Ddak-ji king!
No, no, no...
No!
- This is your chance. It's okay.
- Oh my God!
[Every chance is a moment of danger!]
We've got our chance!
- If he flips this over, I'm finished.
- It's okay. He won't do it.
Here I go.
Please don't flip over.
- I thought you had it.
- Ah, I thought I had it.
- Look at how nervous everyone is.
- I thought that was it.
- You can do this!
- I have to get it this time.
[Throwing his whole body into
the attack!]
Why is everyone letting Ddak-ji
do this to them?
[Who knew that one Ddak-ji could
become so cutthroat?]
You can do it!
[Each throw drains them of their energy...]
You can do this.
[It didn't flip over!]
We're almost there.
[Even those watching from the sidelines...]
[And those in the match...]
[It's sucking all the energy
out of them.]
Why is this so nerve-wrecking?
[Ddak-ji king's final match that's bringing
everyone to the edge of their seats.]
[More and more...]
[These two are throwing everything
they have left into their throws!]
I'm a fan of both of you!
[Stirring up the crowd!]
[A fair crowd encouraging on both the
old and the new king!]
[Too bad!]
This is the 'Fist of Fury'
that legends speak of!
- The two-horse carriage!
- Misery loves company!
[Hit it]
[Beat it]
[Throw it]
[And throw it again]
[A long drawn out battle befitting
a battle between the two kings!]
- This isn't coming to an end.
- That sounded good though.
Massage... massage his arms.
I should've done better.
I'm sorry.
If I come on the show again,
I'll make sure to be better prepared.
[Even giving words of encouragement...]
I'll come back once I get my
implant back in.
[Ten minutes passes on by...]
[20 minutes passes on by...]
[30 minutes passes on by...]
[But the Ddak-ji between the two kings
refuse to flip over.]
- Would you like a massage too?
- No, it's okay.
I don't know what's going on here.
Please stop!
- Please stop this battle!
- This man is going to collapse!
I'm hitting the slate!
Why is this such a big deal?
Stop tormenting my brothers!
- Can we do something about the Ddak-ji?
- If both of you agree to it...
It's possible that the Ddak-ji isn't flipping
over because it's been hit so much.
- Would you like to trade them out for new?
- I think that would be best.
Ricky and In Pyo can come forward and
choose one each for your team.
[Each team trades up for a new Ddak-ji.]
They're trading in for a new Ddak-ji!
It's time one of them flips over.
[Who will be the ultimate winner left
standing after this drawn out battle?]
I have a better feeling about this.
- With the new Ddak-ji.
- Right?
Okay, here I go.
This may be the end.
You look exhausted now, Jae Suk.
I thought it flipped over because
I only caught a glimpse of the hit.
[It flipped over!]
[Yoo-hyuk beats Jong Kook,
the current Ddak-ji king!]
[After an hour of a long,
drawn out battle!]
Congratulations, Jae Suk!
[Even though Ricky still has
his Ddak-ji left...]
- You're just about to begin your fight.
- Hey.
Get out of here!
[If he succeeds in flipping over Ricky's
Ddak-ji, he will return to being the king!]
[The Ddak-ji king is... Yoo Jae Suk!]
[The return of the Ddak-ji king!]
[Even though he lost,
this champion also gave it his best.]
[Looking more happy than he would at
an end of the year award ceremony.]
Yoo Jae Suk!
[Now that the competition is over,
takes the time out to thank the opponent.]
Ricky!
Next round is
Seo Jang Hoon vs. Song Ji Hyo!
Is it over now?
That was unbelievable.
[The bloodiest battle Running Man
has ever seen in its history!]
On this Children's Day, in the name
of Cha In Pyo and Yoo Jae Suk
one thousand pairs of shoes will be
donated to those in need.
[In the name of Cha In Pyo and Yoo Jae Suk,
one thousand pairs of shoes were donated.]
This makes me so happy.
This truly makes me so happy.
I will take this Ddak-ji game to America
and spread the game out there.
- Yes, you should try that.
- Why didn't we think of that?
- It was so much fun.
- I think people would really enjoy it.
How was today for you, In Pyo?
Being on the show with all of you today
brought me such joy and happiness.
With today being Children's Day on May 5th
I hope that the children receive
their new shoes
and it helps them grow their hopes and dreams
and that they'll go after them wholeheartedly.
In Pyo has such a generous heart.
- To be with such amazing people...
- You'll come back again, won't you?
- You should come back again soon!
- Please come back!
Since you've got some time right now
with your less hectic schedule...
- Please come back again.
- You should definitely come back.
In that case...
- We'll definitely have him back.
- Thank you for being on the show today.
Thank you!
Jang Hoon, are you two
playing each other?
- I don't know about that guy.
- Who's winning?
Are you trying to determine who the
weakest Ddak-ji player is?
Subtitles by DramaFever
[On a bright spring day-
A challenge that comes to Running Man.]
What is this?
Is it the Laws of the Jungle Team?
- The jungle?
- Let's go.
Look at how pale you look.
[The two power teams are facing each other!]
[Running Man vs. Laws of the Jungle-
A battle with their pride on the line!]
[There cannot be two suns in the sky!]
[Determine the strongest team
of variety land!]
[Veteran Running Man vs.
Beastly Laws of the Jungle.]
[Rescue the kidnapped teammates!]
[A fiery battle with the teams'
reputation on the line!]
[Next week on Running Man-
Running Man vs. Laws of the Jungle.]