[Gentleman's Dignity]
[The War of the Flag!]
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Athletic Department]
[Goal of this competition!
Win first place no matter what!]
[Captain Kim Jong Kook, Ace Song Ji Hyo,
Race Starter Ji Suk Jin.]
I'm the captain of
our high school's athletic team.
You're late on your very first day!
I'm the captain of this place.
What kind of crap are you
spewing out?
What are you talking about?
I'm the captain of this place.
What do you know about athletics?
But I'm the captain of this place.
I'm the captain!
Me!
Hello, Teacher...
- What are you saying?
- Not everyone's here yet?
Teacher...
I'm the captain. How dare
you go around saying you are?
- Don't you know that I'm the captain?
- I'm the captain!
- This is an all-boys school.
- I may have a skirt on, but I'm a boy too.
- Who's the captain here?
- It's me!
[While everyone's arguing amongst
themselves about being the captain...]
[Caption of Athletic Team, Kim Jong Kook.]
- Captain, you're here!
- Hello, Captain!
- We're just...
- What do you think you're all doing?
- We were just playing captain!
- I was just scolding them all!
- He was arguing that he's the captain!
No, that's not true!
I'm nothing but your personal coat hanger!
- I'm serious.
- It looks like someone is still missing.
[Now that we take a look around,
someone is missing?]
Jae Suk...
Why...
[A member of the theater department
at Gentleman High School, Yoo Jae Suk.]
You used to be a member of the
athletic department here at Gentleman High...
but you couldn't forget the passion
you have for your inner desire to act
so you transferred to the
Theater Department.
Okay?
- Well...
- That's how it is.
What do you mean, that's how it is?
Transferring departments like I have
is a very sensitive issue...
- This person was Athletic Department's star.
- Who was?
[A former star of the athletic department, but
now a new member of the theater department?]
[Gentleman High School's
Captain of Theater Department, Kim Soo Ro.]
Jae Suk!
[The right way to greet someone on this
show is to rip off their name tag.]
Why would you rip off my name tag
the moment we see each other again?
This really does feel good though.
I knew that you were going to be on today
as soon as I saw this.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Thanks.
[Just then, another student heads
towards the Theater Department.]
Jong Suk!
[Gentleman High School Theater Department's
best looking student, Lee Jong Suk.]
[Played the role of a rebel with a kind heart
in a recent drama and won over many hearts.]
What is this?
[A warm atmosphere with all the
top young actor's entering the stage.]
- How have you been, Jong Suk?
- Have you been well?
Jae Suk, you seem to be close to
Lee Jong Suk as well?
- Of course, Jong Suk and I are close.
- We're close.
We're real close to anyone
who's really hot right now.
[Another 'Hot' young student
is seen walking their way...]
[Theater Department's tough guy
makes his entrance!]
[Gentleman High School Theater Department's
tough guy, Kim Woo Bin.]
[Statuesque height! A hot star who's known
for his tough and manly acting skills!]
Look at how good-looking, and tall he is!
[One hot and sizzling Theater Department.]
Come stand over here.
This is my first time meeting him.
[Woo Bin and Jae Suk's first meeting.]
- This is my first time meeting him.
- This is your first time meeting Woo Bin?
- You haven't met this hot star before?
- No, this is my first time meeting him in person.
- You're all very tall.
- Jae Suk, you're pretty short.
[Theater Department's average height
is over 180cm?]
Jong Hyun!
[Gentleman High School Theater Department's
Idol hopeful, Lee Jong Hyun.]
I can't believe he's here today.
[His third time on Running Man!
Already like a member of the family.]
I forgot Jong Hyun was on
'A Gentleman's Dignity!'
I told you I know everyone
who's really hot these days.
- Even Jong Hyun is on the show today.
- This is a great group.
What are we going to be doing today?
Is someone else coming?
It's Hyo Rin!
- It's Hyo Rin!
- It is Hyo Rin!
[Gentleman High School Theater Department's
sole female member, Min Hyo Rin.]
[Attractive actress gracing the big and
small screens alike, such as 'Sunny'!]
We needed a girl on our team!
[A warm greeting?]
- How have you been?
- I've been very well.
But... everyone here is so tall!
- Come here... come stand over here.
- Okay.
- I'll come stand over there.
- Yeah, come here.
[Feeling most comfortable standing
next to Jae Suk?]
You're all overtly tall.
They're all just overtly tall.
You're all students of the
Theater Department today.
Today's race is Theater Department
vs. Athletic Department.
It's Gentleman High School's
club competition.
[Theater Department vs. Athletic Department.
Gentleman High School's club competition!]
The winning team of each competition
will take over the school flag.
If the team loses the competition,
they'll lose the flag to the winning team.
The team that can hold on to the flag until
the end will be today's ultimate winners.
[Determined Athletic Team]
- Your first mission of the day is...
- What is it?
We're not doing it with the other members?
[Athletic Team members still don't know
who the members of the other team are.]
- Look at this!
- What is it?
[Choose two members from each team
for the competition.]
[Enter two at a time
to eliminate the others' name tag.]
[Every time a person is eliminated, another
team member will enter to replace them.]
[The last person to remain will be the final
survivor of the competition and earn the flag.]
[Name tag elimination right from the start!]
We're going to start today's race
with name tag elimination.
- This is really...
- So we have to pick two people right now?
[Two players from each club to enter.]
[Whenever a person is eliminated, another
member from that club will enter to replace.]
No matter what the case is...
I guess we're going to lose.
We can't beat Jong Kook!
He hates hearing that the most!
[A phrase the game adversary
hates hearing the most!]
I'm sorry.
You have to be more positive
when living your life.
Soo Ro hates hearing
things like that the most.
So we should start by choosing
two people first, right?
This is your third time on Running Man,
isn't it, Jong Hyun?
- Yes, this is my third time on the show.
- You've played this game before, right?
Yes, I've played it every time
I've been on the show.
I haven't exactly done very well.
[Having been eliminated by Mr. Capable
every single time he's played it.]
Jong Hyun told you himself.
He just laughs the whole time
and then goes home.
Since we don't know who's on the
other team, we should be very careful...
[Must be cautious about their plans since
they don't know who their opponents are.]
- Kwang Soo's not a weak player.
- Kwang Soo can be a strong player.
Not a single one of us here...
would be lacking against anyone.
Not a single one of us would
fall behind anyone we encounter.
I can win against anyone when it
comes to the name tag elimination game.
We have to start by taking the upper hand
for us to last to the end.
Woo Bin and Jong Suk...
and Hyo Rin and Jong Hyun...
- Let's get this done today.
- Of course.
Where do we need to go?
What's that?
[Ones chosen must enter the battlefield
with their eyes blindfolded.]
This is scary.
[The first ones to enter the field,
Kim Woo Bin and Lee Jong Hyun!]
Watch out for the steps.
We're going to have to show them
what we're made of.
[The first one to enter the field,
The Easy Brothers!]
We're now on the
second floor of the basement.
I'll get out first.
I'll get out here.
- I'll see you later.
- Okay, see you later.
This is scary.
- Only Kwang Soo is going to get out here.
- What?
We're getting out separately?
We're not getting off together?
Why aren't we getting off together?
[Theater Department vs. Athletic Department.]
Let's go!
[Members of Gentleman High School's
Theater and Athletic Department, welcome.]
In just a moment...
we will have the two clubs face off with
one another in a name tag elimination game.
We will have a name tag
elimination game.
Yes!
At this moment... you will all take off your
blindfolds and enter the arena simultaneously.
Club face-off name tag elimination...
Start!
[Even the members lying in wait
are feeling the nervous energy.]
- I wish there was a live broadcast.
- Live broadcast would be nice.
[Theater Department vs. Athletic Department.
The real face-off starts now!]
During last year's enrollment...
I really wanted to be admitted
into the acting department.
But the acting department...
did not accept me.
[Giraffe wasn't accepted into the department
two years ago because of his looks.]
[On the other hand...]
[Woo Bin and Jong Hyun meeting up
to form a strategy.]
Hey... I think I just saw Suk Jin.
[Theater Department aggressively
seeking out their opponents.]
I found him!
- Come help me.
- Who is that?
[Athletic Club's Kwang Soo vs.
Woo Bin and Jong Hyun of the Theater Club.]
[Attacks as soon as he sees him!]
Suk Jin!
- What is it?
- Suk Jin!
Who are they?
Where are they?
There are two out there.
- Hello.
- Who is it?
[Starting off with a happy greeting.]
[Woo Bin sneaks up from behind while
Jong Hyun distracts them with his greeting.]
[A full-on battle right from the start!]
[Greetings are over!
Jong Hyun and Impala facing off!]
- You're going to use your strength on me?
- Get down from there!
[His ambush is a success!
Woo Bin now sneaking up on Impala!]
Kwang Soo!
Shall we just battle it out?
Like men?
Kwang Soo... let's switch spots.
- Why are you asking me to do that?
- You take Woo Bin!
- Let's not be like this amongst ourselves!
But I've already called dibs on Jong Hyun!
No, I called dibs on him first.
I called dibs from the moment I saw him.
Hurry!
[Imminent face-off]
[An endless play of attack and defense
like a fierce judo competition.]
- Suk Jin...
- What?
Even just the fact that we haven't
run away from these two yet is very...
- Of course!
- That's a great feat in itself.
Jong Hyun... go over to Kwang Soo.
Go over to Kwang Soo.
[What? He's telling him
to attack Kwang Soo?]
Suk Jin, what are you doing?
Why are you sending him over to me?
[This is what you call loyalty
between the Easy Brothers.]
- I was just trying to help you out.
- What?
Suk Jin... how could you do that to me?
[Giraffe makes his escape!]
[Easy Brothers' relay of betrayal!]
[It's Big-nosed Brother who's
in danger this time!]
Okay, I'll help you eliminate Kwang Soo.
Lee Kwang Soo!
[When it comes to betrayals,
Giraffe has one up on you...]
That Lee Kwang Soo!
[The moment Impala is left alone,
he is easily ousted!]
[Recruiting a member of Athletic Club.]
- Does this mean one of them is dead?
- Exactly.
Jong Hyuk and Woo Bin are out there
doing a great job.
I wondered who was eliminated?
I wonder which one of our opponent's
was ousted?
Recruiting a member of Athletic Club.
I knew this was going to happen.
Jong Kook.
[Is it time for me to step in?]
Let's go.
[Mr. Capable of the Athletic Club
entering the arena.]
- Watch your back.
- We have to win this.
We have to win this. You know that, right?
We have to win this!
Okay... we have to win
no matter what.
- It was Suk Jin, wasn't it?
- I'm sure it was.
[In that case...]
[Race, start!]
[Mr. Capable is on the chase!]
We have to keep going like this.
Since those guys are older than us...
When they get exhausted,
they'll just give up.
- With our youth...
- With our youth?
We're going to win this
with our youth.
- Should we take this to the end?
- Of course.
- Until Jong Kook comes out?
- Let's make sure your name is on tight.
[Mr. Capable with his blindfold
still covering his eyes.]
[Huh? Giraffe is going to guide
Mr. Capable in himself?]
What the heck is that?
You should've told me that
was in my way.
[Petty vengeful acts towards the Tiger.]
What are you doing?
[The clueless Tiger is bumping into
everything in the room.]
[Giraffe... what are you thinking?]
Athletic Club replacement member
completes his entrance.
You can take off the blindfold now.
Jong Kook!
[Immediately gets chastised.]
- What the heck is going on out here?
- Jong Kook...
It's Kim Woo Bin and Jong Hyun
on the show.
Ah, Jong Hyun...
But all Suk Jin did was just sit back to watch
what's going on without doing anything.
- It looks like you've been through a battle.
- It was no joke.
So I just... left Suk Jin behind
and escaped.
- What is the matter with you?
- I had no other choice.
- What do you mean, you had no choice?
- They were both coming at me.
[Mr. Capable is now fully apprised
of what's going on.]
[Okay... in that case...]
[These two are still unaware of who the
replacement is from the Athletic Club.]
Ji Hyo!
Ji Hyo, come here!
Over here!
Ji Hyo!
[The strategy is to pretend Ji Hyo is
the replacement by calling out her name!]
[A plan to lure them out for
Mr. Capable to attack them in an ambush!]
- Ji Hyo!
- Hey...
Kwang Soo's alone right now.
Let's go now and eliminate him.
Ji Hyo!
Ji Hyo, over here!
They're right here!
[Okay... nice.]
Ji Hyo!
[Woo Bin and Jong Hyun chasing down
Kwang Soo without any suspicion.]
Ji Hyo!
Come here.
[Discovers Mr. Capable!]
[An immediate retreat!]
[Mr. Capable is on the move!]
Kwang Soo, you're so obvious!
[Mr. Capable's appearance immediately
turns the tables around.]
What if Kim Jong Kook is out there
as soon as we enter the game?
[His curiosity is too busy hunting down
his own teammates at the moment.]
Let's get this over with quickly.
[The four men caught in a face-off
in a dead end hallway.]
[No more room to run!]
[Extreme nervous energy!]
[One second of hesitation can mean defeat!]
This finally feels like a race!
[Woo Bin and Jong Hyun of
the Theater Club are cornered!]
[A fierce physical battle!]
Get him!
[Both... at the same time!]
[Kwang Soo beats him to it
by a split of a second!]
[Kim Woo Bin, Out!]
[Mr. Capable and the Giraffe vs.
Judo athlete Jong Hyun.]
[Jong Hyun breaking out his judo moves.]
What the heck is this?
Come on, what is this?
[Jong Hyun sticks it out for a while,
but unfortunately is ousted in the end.]
[Recruiting a member of
the Theater Club.]
Recruiting a member of
the Theater Club.
[Next member to go in, Jong Suk.]
- Fighting.
- Your hand... your hand is really cold.
I wonder if it was Jong Hyun
who got ousted?
[Another announcement?]
Recruiting a member of
the Theater Club.
It's another recruitment call?
[With Woo Bin and Jong Hyun's elimination,
two members of the Theater Club are called.]
- Hyo Rin.
- You want me to go in now?
[The sole female member of the club,
Hyo Rin also goes in as replacement.]
Yes.
We're in big trouble.
I'm positive Kim Jong Kook is out there.
Kim Jong Kook really is something else.
Suk Jin!
[Theater Club's Jong Suk and Hyo Rin vs.
Athletic Club's Jong Kook and Kwang Soo.]
Suk Jin!
[Kwang Soo... lure them over to me.]
[Giraffe actively luring them in.]
Where is Jong Kook?
[Opposite to his plan, Jong Suk is
the one who attacks Kwang Soo!]
Wait... wait!
[He's about to get ousted right now,
let alone lure anyone in!]
[Mr. Capable runs over
after hearing all the commotion.]
[Total chaos!]
No!
Jong Kook!
Where have you been?
- Why are you already here?
- I've been watching this whole time.
Don't even move an inch
away from me.
Is Jae Suk waiting to come out last?
[Jong Suk and Hyo Rin run to safety
after having seen Mr. Capable.]
What a nice picture to see a boy and a girl
running away together like that.
You guys make a nice picture!
[Oh my goodness... while holding hands?]
[Is this the birth of a new school couple?]
[As if a scene right out of
a high school drama!]
- Jong Kook, let's hold hands too!
- What?
Why would I hold your hand?
- Let's hold hands like they did.
- Why?
- Let go of me right now!
You hide right here,
and I'll go hide over there, okay?
I didn't take this seriously enough.
And here I thought I was a good runner.
[The challenge of Running Man's chase that
has to be experienced to be believed.]
You two...
Come up to the rooftop after class.
[What's he saying?]
- He's just trying to lure us right now.
- Come up to the rooftop.
No...
[Since they keep escaping no matter what,
must try to lure them back in somehow.]
No!
We're not going to follow you.
I've never seen you been so adamant like this
when I watched the show on TV before.
No kidding.
[Giraffe feeling overly confident
with Mr. Capable covering his back.]
Let's go.
[There they go!]
No, no, no...
[Hyo Rin stepping up to
save her teammate.]
Wait!
[Giraffe becoming extremely flustered at
the joint attack by the theater couple.]
Jong Kook!
[Calling out Mr. Capable's name
over and over...]
Jong Kook!
[Lee Kwang Soo, Out!]
[What's taking him so long?]
Jong Kook!
[The next recruitment Haroro starts searching
for Jong Kook the moment he's in the game.]
[But something feels...]
[Discovers reflection of Jong Suk and Hyo Rin
waiting in ambush-mode in the mirror!]
[Running away is key!]
There's nowhere for me to escape to!
Hello!
[Theater couple's plan is to oust Ha Ha
before he can meet up with Mr. Capable.]
[Haroro is in danger of becoming
ousted the moment he steps into the game!]
Wait... this guy...
- Hello.
- It's nice to meet you.
[It's nice to meet each other, but let's
save the formal greeting until later.]
[Easily caught due to his short strides.]
[The theater couple not being
shy about becoming aggressive.]
Jong Kook!
[Commonality of all the weaklings:
When in danger, call out Mr. Capable's name.]
[Haroro is ousted less than a minute
after entering the game!]
Where is my teammate?
Bye!
[Complete exhaustion.]
Recruiting a member of the
Athletic Club.
- It's the Athletic Club again!
- Wow!
Jong Suk and Hyo Rin are
a lethal team!
How can this be?
- Recruiting a member of the Athletic Club.
- Again?
How did this happen?
He got ousted the moment he went out?
Ji Hyo...
- I'm going out there. I'll see you later.
- Okay.
She's not even fully awake yet...
Okay, here's what's going on.
Min Hyo Rin and...
[Now that we take a look at this...]
[It's the ultimate combination,
Mr. Capable and Ace!]
Where did he get ousted?
I think right over there.
There they are.
They're down there.
- They're down there.
- What do we do?
They just saw us.
- We just have to face them.
- Facing them is the only thing we can do.
Should we go down there?
They're coming down.
They're coming down right now.
Then I'll... I'll grab Kim Jong Kook,
so you try ripping off his name tag.
But I...
- I'm pretty much out of energy right now.
- They're down here now.
[The two male and females teams
finally coming to face one another.]
[The theater couple is automatically
starting to backtrack.]
- Hello.
- Jong Suk...
- Wait... Wait, Jong Kook.
- Jong Suk.
- Ji Hyo, I'm a huge fan of yours.
- Yes, I'm a fan of yours as well.
- Thank you.
- While watching you earlier...
[Mr. Capable and Ace target
Jong Suk first!]
[Hyo Rin barely manages to pull
Ji Hyo away...]
Jong Kook, how about you
come here first?
No, don't listen to her!
She's so tiny that
I don't know what to do with her.
- Ji Hyo...
- Look at how she's getting pulled!
- Hyo Rin.
- Why are you dragging her around?
What do I do?
[Jong Suk is also being shoved around
by Mr. Capable.]
[The ultimate defense!
Lay down on their backs.]
What are we being
reduced to doing right now?
I'm sorry!
[Lee Jong Suk, Out!]
I don't know what to do with her.
[Easily ousted the moment she
flips herself around.]
[This is the dangerous power of
Mr. Capable and Ace!]
I really didn't know what to do
with you because you're so tiny.
- I'm sorry, but you worked hard.
- Good work.
Theater club...
recruiting two members.
Recruiting two members of
the theater club.
- Now that it's come down to this...
- Soo Ro...
Let's finish this right now.
[The last two members of the
Theater Club finally entering the game.]
[Ousted members of the club
all await in the van.]
- That's some serious stuff.
- It's no joke, is it?
- Who did you get ousted by?
- I'm so exhausted.
This is really exhausting.
To be perfectly honest,
I didn't know it would be this difficult.
I didn't know they ran so hard like
they do when I watched them on TV.
All those guys are all pretty strong.
- Ha Ha was no joke, was he?
- Seriously.
Ha Ha was really fast.
They're all so fast.
[The final two members of the Theater Club,
Soo Ro and Jae Suk, enter the game.]
[Behind the enemy lines adversary,
and the grasshopper.]
[The honor of the Theater Club
rests on their shoulders.]
There's Jae Suk.
- Look at them... Song Ji Hyo too.
- Come over here.
- I said, come out here!
- You come over here!
[Battle of wills. Telling each
other to come over to them.]
Come outside!
[Soo Ro is lying in wait to
ambush them.]
Song Ji Hyo!
What are you doing right now?
I'm a member of the Athletic Club!
- Don't you see the pants that I'm wearing?
- Come out here!
Do you not see the leggings
that I'm wearing right now?
- Come out!
- Come out here.
What? Are you scared? Are you
scared after seeing the pants I'm wearing?
- You seem scared!
- What are you going to do about it?
What are you going to do
by wearing those stretchy pants?
Just come out here!
Jae Suk... why are you
out here alone?
Our Theater Club just worked
out that way.
- Why?
- How come?
It's personal family business!
- Why? What's wrong with your family?
- We've had some things come up at home.
- Family issues?
- Yeah!
- Hurry up and get over here.
- You come here!
- Who else do you have with you?
- You guys come over here.
- Who's the other person?
- Who else do you have with you?
- Who is it?
- You guys come over here!
[Strange feeling... It seems
Jae Suk is trying to lure them in.]
[Jae Suk's plan is to lure them in
to where Soo Ro is waiting for them.]
Something doesn't feel right.
I feel like you're trying to lure us in.
Who's the other person?
I'm getting... a really strong
and weird vibe right now.
- Right?
- Yeah.
It's a really strong vibe.
Let's get Jong Kook first.
Come over here.
I can see you over there.
I can see your eyes over there.
I know!
- I'm standing here for you to see!
- Who are you with?
I said, I'm standing here
for you to see!
[At last!]
[Life-long rivals, Soo Ro and Jong Kook
come face to face!]
- Hi, Ji Hyo!
- Hello!
[During the days of 'Family Outing',
these two used to be as close as brothers.]
[Even their greeting is full of nervous energy
from being aware of each other's strengths.]
- What brings you on today, Soo Ro?
- It's been awhile!
- What are you doing here?
- Jong Kook, it's Soo Ro!
I was wondering who else
was on the show today.
Soo Ro!
[Want to greet each other with a hug,
but the opponent's back is too tempting.]
It's starting already.
How about a hug, Ji Hyo?
- Soo Ro...
- Let's just settle for a handshake.
That's right!
[A hidden sword behind his greeting!]
Why is your handshake so cold?
No breaks because you're a girl.
[Staying alert and vigilant
while facing off one another.]
[Full of nervous energy]
[The position is slowly...]
[Soo Ro and Jae Suk somehow get
Mr. Capable and Ace cornered.]
[Mr. Capable and Ace in danger!]
[Has Jae Suk in a tight grip!]
[Just then,
Mr. Capable starts his attack too!]
[And Soo Ro immediately counterattacks!]
[Simultaneously grabs each other's name tag!
Who will be faster to eliminate?]
[Soo Ro... was faster!]
[Happened in the blink of an eye!]
[How can this be?]
[Mr. Capable, Out!]
I can't believe that happened.
[This is the power of the Game Adversary.]
[The final member of the Athletic Club,
Gary enters the game!]
- Gary, what are we going to do?
- Jong Kook got ousted?
- Do you know who it is?
- Who is it?
- It's Kim Soo Ro!
- Seriously?
What are we going to do?
We're in big trouble.
- Who else is left besides Soo Ro?
- Jae Suk.
Jae Suk!
What are we going to do?
Those two are really strong.
We're in trouble.
What are we going to do?
[Will the Monday Couple be able to
recoup their position?]
- Should we go that way?
- There you are. Come here, Gary.
Hello, Soo Ro.
Have you been well?
- Hey, Gary!
- Gary, we should at least shake hands.
- Yes, Soo Ro.
- You two are left now?
We don't shake hands on Running Man!
Shaking hands could be
dangerous on our show.
- You stay right there!
- Wait... wait!
Wait, Soo Ro!
[Total fear]
Don't you think that this is
too unevenly matched?
That's how we felt when Jong Kook was
still in the game.
- Soo Ro...
- It was the same for us with Jong Kook.
[Theater Club cornering them
into a dead end hallway.]
What's with that glint in
your eye, Soo Ro?
Soo Ro...
- He says he's going to end it now.
- What is it that you keep trying to end?
[Men of the Theater Club attacking
regardless of Ji Hyo being a girl.]
Gary...
[Gary's shocking counterattack!]
- Gary...
- You're kicking us now?
[At this rate,
the Monday Couple is going to be...]
[Oh?]
[Blank Ji takes the moment of opportunity
amidst the chaos to grab Soo Ro's name tag!]
[My goodness!]
[Kim Soo Ro, Out!]
[Blank Ji does something even Mr. Capable
couldn't do and ousts Soo Ro!]
[ Theater Club's Jae Suk now left
all on his own!]
[Monday Couple promptly moves in
on the Grasshopper!]
- It's your turn now!
- Gary!
I can't believe this is happening to me!
- How can this be happening?
- Ji Hyo...
Ji Hyo, here it is!
Get it, Ji Hyo!
[Jae Suk's counterattack!]
[Do not underestimate Jae Suk's strength!]
Hurry up and rip it off, Ji Hyo!
Gary, I can't get it!
[Gary, Out!]
[Club competition's ultimate face-off,
Blank Ji vs. Jae Suk!]
- Ji Hyo, how can you do this to me?
- Ji Hyo! Pinch him!
- Stop tickling me!
- You can't do that!
You have to win!
Don't let her win!
[Song Ji Hyo wins!]
Ji Hyo, you're really something else.
That was a given.
[Club competition, winner of
name tag elimination: Athletic Club]
Ji Hyo ousted them both.
[Blank Ji having ousted both
Jae Suk and Soo Ro's name tags!]
Song Ji Hyo, you've still got it!
Since you've earned the flag,
make sure to keep it very safe.
And you may board the car
and move on to our next location.
- Great job!
- Our Athletic Club is the best!
[What did the three of you do?]
- We have to win the next game.
- Of course, that's a given.
- Theater Club, fighting!
- Fighting!
I've just become an enemy of
that other club right now.
I've been marked by the Athletic Club.
We're going to head over to the
sports park in Song-do!
- Okay!
- Let's go!
- Athletic Club!
- Athletic Club.
You still got it, Athletic Club!
Don't go anywhere else!
That's a good line.
- Are they here?
- Open the door.
Why don't we sing the song?
[Provocation]
You guys better watch yourselves!
Theater Club has lost it!
- That's weak!
- Let's see who's talking after this!
That's so disappointing.
We should've taken the flag.
What do you think of today, Woo Bin?
What did you think of the first round?
What did you think of your plays?
We had no plays.
- We just went around together.
- Really?
Jong Suk looks a lot like I did
when I was younger.
- Really?
- Yeah.
[Do I?]
- Jae Suk.
- Yes?
I've seen you around when
you were younger.
[There's a witness.
Who does he think he's trying to fool?]
Then how young are we
talking about here?
[Arriving at the mission location.]
Shall we get out of the car?
[We're going to win this time.
Theater Club, fighting!]
I feel like we've been here before.
What's this?
- This is a store.
- Let's buy something to eat.
- I'm hungry.
- We need to eat something.
- What are they selling here?
- Are you selling any cup ramen?
Hello!
- Wow, that looks good.
- There are a lot of goodies here.
I like this fried udon soup.
I'll take a roll of kimbap.
[An enjoyable snack time.]
- What is this? What are they eating?
- It's a store.
- Soo Ro!
- Jong Kook!
[The two competitors finally greeting
each other the proper way.]
[Theater Captain, Soo Ro
overflowing with masculine strength.]
[What's the mission?]
[Each club write down the name of
three games that they feel confident in.]
[And choose two of those three games,
and win two out of three rounds.]
However, the loser team must pay for
the total cost of the winning team's snacks.
We're going to win this
no matter what.
- Since you guys are going to pay...
- What is it that you keep eating?
Let's all eat as much as we can!
I've already ordered a ton of food.
[Pure happiness as if they're back
in school visiting the school snack shop.]
It feels good to see
all my old classmates like this.
Classmates?
Are you ripping on me right now?
- You look more like their teacher!
- Can't you tell I'm Class of 2013?
Just look at the way you look.
I bet you were the ugliest in your class!
- What did you say?
- Your face looks like a miniature squid!
You're totally a sight.
Should we play a dunk shoot game
for our pick?
[With total faith in his tall classmates,
antagonizing Ha Ha to his heart's content.]
- We've got Kwang Soo over here.
- Kwang Soo.
We're not scared of you guys!
Since Woo Bin and Jong Suk
are really tall...
are there any games where we can
utilize their height?
- How about a relay?
- That's right.
How about doing the splits to connect
the legs to see who can get the most length?
[Turning in the games
that they each want to play.]
Each team turned in three games each?
- Yes.
- The first game is...
- Okay, the first game.
- It's a game submitted by the Athletic Club.
It's a relay game of who
can eat the fastest.
[Speed eating relay...]
- Who can eat the fastest.
- Ah, eating?
I already ate two ramens.
This team's already full of food.
[Current hot stars Woo Bin and Jong Suk still
have to remain cool when they eat?]
They've got the wrong idea.
We've got good eaters over here too.
- I'll show them what I'm capable of.
- I'll show them what tacky truly means.
How are we going to do this?
- We already have the food picked out.
- Okay.
Eggs, ice cream, ramen, chocolate,
water and cola.
The moment that someone says
start to the game...
we start eating the fastest we can in turn.
Once you're done eating, you have to whistle.
[Before the next person can start,
the current eater must whistle.]
[1- Hard-boiled egg; 2- Cup ramen;
3- Ice cream; 4- Water; 5- Cola]
- Okay.
- Okay, I'm going to start the timer.
You don't need to drink the broth too
in the cup ramen, do you?
You don't need to drink the broth too.
You just need to eat the noodles.
Set... go!
Song Ji Hyo, take your time!
- Wow, you're eating that in one bite!
- There you go... nice!
- It's okay, take it easy.
- Just swallow!
- Just swallow it.
- Don't push her.
- It's okay, take it easy.
- This is a battle with your own self.
It's okay, you can do it.
Song Ji Hyo, lose!
Lose, Song Ji Hyo!
Song Ji Hyo...
[Almost...]
- No, she didn't do it.
- Yes, she did!
- No, she's all set.
- She ate it all.
[Next up is cup ramen!]
[Burns his mouth by trying to eat it
without even blowing on it first.]
- Lose, Gary! Lose, Gary!
- You're almost there! Just a little bit more!
[Remaining unafraid of
such little things as heat.]
- You're almost there!
- You don't need to drink the broth!
Blow on it a little!
You'll burn yourself!
[Is he already done eating?]
[Heat over taste.]
- You're there.
- You're done eating, so whistle.
[Is he embarrassed?]
[Three: Ice cream]
[Brain freeze]
[Ice blast to the brain.]
- Just shove it in there!
- You have to eat it faster!
Just shove it in there!
Lose, Ji Suk Jin!
- Don't even think about spitting it out!
- Just endure it!
- You can do this!
Here, drink some of this ramen broth!
[Ramen broth?]
- Hurry, hurry!
- That is so disgusting!
[The broth seem to be working.]
[Now he just needs to whistle!]
You've still got it, Ji Suk Jin!
He did it!
[Four: Chocolate]
[Oh my!]
[Human chocolate grinder.]
[Did you see that?]
[You're all dead!]
[The inventor of the game who scarfed down the
food in an amazingly short amount of time.]
- Hurry up and swallow it!
- One, two, three!
- He can't.
- He can't do it yet.
He ate it too fast.
There's too much left in his mouth.
[He still has a mouth full of chocolate.]
Ha Ha, you can't do it!
- He did it!
- Okay!
[Five: Bottled water]
- How is he doing that?
- Does he have a water faucet in there?
He's like a water faucet.
[He looks like he's going to
succeed in a single swallow!]
[Huh?]
[Why would he hit his throat?]
You have to do it over!
[Calms down and finishes the rest.]
- Why would you hit my neck?
- He's not very good.
[The final bottle of cola.
Giraffe drinking it down like lightening!]
How is he drinking cola like that?
[Guzzling it down as if he's
putting gas in the car.]
[Wow! Already finished!]
Are you a giraffe or something?
[Amazing]
[Oh my...]
[He's supposed to whistle,
but another sound comes out of his mouth...]
[The store breaks out in an uproar
with that one sound.]
[Trying to remain calm.]
[Athletic Club finishes all six rounds.]
[Athletic Club's record is...
Four minutes and 55 seconds.]
[Will the Theater Club be able to beat
four minutes and 55 seconds?]
You just watch what we do.
[Hyo Rin to start off by eating
the hard-boiled egg.]
Set... go!
There you go!
Hyo Rin knows what she's doing!
Hyo Rin's played a little back in her day!
[Played a little back in her day?
Hyo Rin peels the egg without any hesitation!]
That's right!
Hyo Rin knows what she's doing!
[I'm Min Hyo Rin...]
[Do I looked like I played around
a bit back in the day?]
[Scarfs down]
That's right! Look at her!
She's definitely played around a bit!
- Did you see the way she smacked her egg?
- You've played around a bit, haven't you?
One more... one more bite.
- Okay, you got it.
- She can eat really fast.
It's not easy.
Whistling isn't going to be easy.
- Okay!
- She hasn't whistled yet.
She's got it!
[Now it's Woo Bin's turn
to eat the cup ramen.]
Show them how you can eat that.
Hurry up and eat it.
Why are you blowing on it? Just eat it.
[Quite cautious unlike his
tough guy image?]
You have to eat it quick.
That's right. Nice, Woo Bin.
Nice, nice!
Hey, Gary...
he's quite a different picture from you.
Is that the way you're
supposed to eat?
Done. He's done with the ramen.
Woo Bin, you have to whistle now.
[Are his eyes starting to water?]
- It's okay!
- It's okay, Woo Bin! Don't cry!
- Don't cry!
He got it!
- You know what to do, right, Jong Suk?
- You can do this, Jong Suk!
That's right!
[Automatically reaching for the
ramen broth.]
- Just once... just once.
- He can only have one sip!
- Did the ramen broth help!
- We're all set!
[Predicting their win?]
- Lee Jong Suk!
- Eat it slow!
Jong Suk...
[The unbearable cold...]
It's okay, Jong Suk!
Jong Suk, it's okay!
[Suddenly bouncing around?]
But he still looks cool.
[Even as he's chomping down on his ice cream,
he's still maintaining his cool image.]
He did it!
[The Game Adversary Soo Ro's turn
to eat the chocolate bar.]
[Scarfing down]
- You dropped some. Over here, here...
- That doesn't matter.
[The single shot of chocolate is too much
for even Soo Ro with his sweet tooth?]
[With his gaze fixed on something afar,
he shoves more chocolate in his mouth.]
Why don't you put another piece in?
[Wait, wait!]
[Shoves the final piece
of chocolate in his mouth.]
- I bet his mouth is too dry.
- You got it!
You got it!
[Jong Hyun's turn to drink the water.]
Here's finally something Jong Hyun's good at!
[Anxious]
[Already having stopped once,
how will he do this time?]
He's not going to make it.
[Hm?]
- There's some left!
- There's still some left!
[Total chaos]
- He's got it.
- He has to whistle!
- He's got it!
- Drink the cola!
[Final round! Jae Suk's turn with the cola.]
[Barely suppresses his reflex
to spew it out.]
[Same thing as the Giraffe.]
It's not easy.
[Impossible to whistle.]
[Theater Club completes their mission.]
[Were they faster than the Athletic Club's
four minute and 55 second record?]
We were much faster.
- I don't know how this is going to turn out.
- I think we did better than them.
[The Athletic Club's record was
four minutes and 55 seconds...]
[The Theater Club's record is in
the four minute range!]
You know it can't be 57 or 58 seconds.
- 58... 58 seconds.
- Four minutes...
47 seconds!
[Theater Club:
Four minutes and 47 seconds.]
[Theater Club wins!]
[The reason for their defeat
is the Giraffe?]
- We did it.
- Jong Hyun, for the first time on the show...
The current score is one to one.
The final game will be a game
submitted by the Theater Club...
and it's a relay of the splits.
[Current score is tied and the final
game is 'Relay of the splits'!]
- How are we supposed to do that?
- No kidding.
- Most of them have long legs.
- How are we supposed to do that?
- It's to see who can get the longest length?
- Yes.
[The team to get the longest distance by
connecting their legs in a split position wins.]
Don't you think this is unfairly
advantageous for you guys?
No, we didn't.
Can't we just have fun with this?
Look at how long their legs are!
These guys aren't the most
athletic people.
[Their physical stature may be superior,
but their athletic abilities are unknown?]
I'll go first.
- You know that I'm not good at this, right?
- Yeah, I know that.
You need to change your pants
before you do that
They all need to connect in a line.
What are you doing over there?
[A barrage of criticism]
I'm just trying to stretch out my legs!
[Keeps on getting into strange poses.]
What?
I have my own style of doing this!
[Everyone shocked at his way of
doing the splits.]
[Screaming out in agony from having
to withstand holding the position.]
Hyo Rin...
[Rule: The next person's foot must touch
the foot of the person in front of them.]
[With her strength...]
Hurry up and get next to her.
- What do I do?
- Your foot has to touch hers.
[Okay, it's our turn now...]
[Woo Bin and Jong Suk with their
superior statures.]
[Will they be able to stretch out
like they strut down the runway?]
- Your foot has to touch hers.
- Hurry up!
Hurry up!
Hurry!
[Huh?]
[That's it?]
[They are longer, but their flexibility...]
That's not going to be enough!
Go further... stretch out further.
They're not as flexible
as I thought they'd be.
[We suggested this game thinking
we'd have an advantage...]
Jong Suk, stretch out more!
Woo Bin!
Jong Hyun!
They're all so tall.
[Finally, it's the Game Adversary's turn.]
Woo Bin!
Jong Hyun!
[What will be the record for this tall bunch?]
[Marking the spot with
a piece of white tape.]
They got a good distance.
It's a bit longer than it was originally.
Look at him... what's he doing?
He's pulling out his socks further.
- That's cheating!
- We don't have to accept it though.
[Stretching out this side too.]
[What?]
[Eliminating the trickster.]
[The Giraffe suddenly finds
himself barefoot.]
You saw that, right?
You saw what Soo Ro did?
He doesn't care about being fun
or entertaining at all.
Why do we have to live to
be entertaining for others?
Okay, you can do it now.
- Suk Jin, you start first.
- Here, bend your knee like this.
[Captain Capable's instructions
on how to do a proper splits.]
Why am I the first one to go?
- This hurts! Hurry up!
- Do it just like he did.
[A game that incites their anger even
if it's dragged out a second too long.]
Ji Hyo, you're doing great!
Ji Hyo, that's good!
- You have to do the same.
- Hurry!
Hurry up and do it!
[Must hold the position for five seconds after
the last person is in position to count.]
[Will they be able to break
the Theater Club's record?]
[Theater Club's record.]
[If their feet aren't touching,
then it doesn't count.]
[Will they?]
- They're touching... they're touching.
- Hurry!
[What's the Athletic Club's record?]
Hurry!
We won!
[They beat the record!]
[Athletic Club wins the splits game!]
Athletic Club wins the
snack store game.
[Three rounds of snack shop games,
Athletic Club wins!]
You still got it, Athletic Club!
Since we lost this game because of me,
I'll take care of the tab.
[Soo Ro is taking care of the bill?]
How much is it?
[Athletic Team takes the flag again.]
[After having changed their clothes,
Athletic Club is the first to enter the pool.]
[But...]
[What is that on top of the water?]
[A giant platform divided into two parts.
Could this be?]
[Even entering the water is a form of
training for the Athletic Club.]
- Athletic!
[As for the Theater Club, even entering
the water is like a scene out of teen drama.]
Look at how well-mannered they are.
[Say what?]
[Not the least bit threatening.]
Look at what this guy looks like.
[Mr. Capable's threatening looking muscles.]
He has a washboard stomach!
[He must've been shocked from
having seen Mr. Capable's washboard abs.]
[Theater Club is a bit worrisome.]
Athletic Club and the Theater Club...
You are about to begin your
second period.
[Special activity hour!]
[Aquatic battle: The last person left
standing on the float is the winner.]
[Athletic Club's rowdy cheer for themselves.]
[Best out of three.
First round starts now!]
- Come here!
- I'm going to shove three of you off!
Get ready for your first round...
[Aquatic Battle:
First round - start!]
Get a good hold of Jong Kook.
[Jong Kook vs. Jae Suk]
Min Hyo Rin, you come out here!
Come out here, Min Hyo Rin!
[Big-nosed Brother targets
Min Hyo Rin as his target?]
- Min Hyo Rin, come out here!
- Stop hiding and come out here.
We vow to eliminate you.
When Ho Dong used to do it in the past,
it was actually kind of scary, wasn't it?
Ho Dong used to be very good
at things like this.
Ho Dong's really good at this stuff.
Ho Dong even flipped Jong Kook
over in a backflip once.
[I'm the one who did the flipping...]
[This scene that's still
crystal clear in our memory.]
Oh, you flipped him over?
Then I guess I'll be an easy one
for you to flip over?
[Would you like for me to flip you over?]
Shouldn't Soo Ro be stepping up
to the front from your team?
Someone needs to be a fodder
for the cannon blasts.
What do you mean, a cannon fodder?
I'm about to take one for the team
standing up front like this.
[Ten years... shaved off of his life.]
[How is he saying he's going to
protect anything in that state?]
You've still got it, Kim Jong Kook!
Hey, hey, hey...
Don't be scared, Woo Bin.
Don't be scared.
Wait, hang on...
Why am I the one standing
up front like this?
[When all the other men of the Theater Club
are taller and studier than he is?]
When you're all sturdier than I am,
why am I standing up here?
You're all...
[A hundred years shaved off of his life.]
You're all scaredy cats!
If it wasn't for Kim Jong Kook,
you'd all be nothing but bowling pins!
[They'd all be bowling pins
without Jong Kook?]
[A cluttered mess]
[Okay... now's the chance!]
[Mr. Capable attacks!]
[A tangled mess in moments!]
[Submerging as a group!]
[With Mr. Capable's barreling attack,
everyone's eliminated as a bunch!]
[With Kwang Soo eliminating Jong Suk,
and Suk Jin shoving Hyo Rin off...]
[The first round is
the Athletic Club's win!]
[Still flabbergasted with it having
happened in a blink of an eye.]
[Jong Hyun's legs already
giving out on him.]
What's wrong with this Theater Club?
[At this rate, the Theater Club
may not win a single round?]
You guys are way too easy.
- The first round goes to the Athletic Club.
- Let's go.
[Gary up to the front lines?]
[And Theater Club's front line
is headed by Jong Suk!]
Gary's not going to be an easy opponent.
He's very strong.
[Round two of aquatic battle starts now!]
Is this an individual fight?
It is, isn't it?
[Initial battle of the wills
while carefully testing each other out.]
[Even though Jong Suk attacked...]
[It's Gary who wins the fight.]
[Ah...]
[Was that too cool of me?]
I told you to take him seriously.
[Jong Hyun steps up next.]
All kill!
[Black belt in judo Jong Hyun
vs. Sometimes Mr. Capable, Gary.]
[Jong Hyun uses his judo moves
to attack.]
[There they go!]
[Wow, even Jong Hyun...
is beaten by Gary's attack.]
[I'm... so cool...]
[Will Gary seriously be able to
eliminate them all on his own?]
[Theater Club's Woo Bin!]
[Gary barreling down!]
[Wow! Twists his body around
to push Gary into the water!]
Come out here, Suk Jin.
Min Hyo Rin, come out here.
[By requests from the others,
it's Suk Jin vs. Jae Suk.]
- Go up there.
- Then who's going to take Hyo Rin?
[Threatening him with his
lightening quick shadow boxing moves?]
We can't even see his moves!
Look at how fast you are!
[There they go!]
Nice!
[Without even having done anything...]
[What the heck...]
Come on!
[Athletic Club's Haroro!]
- Show him what you've got!
- Okay!
[Both trying to make their
build look bigger?]
[Huh? Why is he flopping around?]
Ha Ha, what are you doing?
[Gollum attack mode.]
[Just what kind of a strategy is this?]
I can't even think straight.
[Is he planning on pushing Jae Suk
off the platform like this?]
[Jae Suk barely manages to
keep himself on the platform!]
Nice going!
[Ultimately being reduced to fighting
like a couple of neighborhood kids?]
[It's time for me to step in.]
[Soo Ro's surprise attack!]
[Pushing off Kwang Soo and
Soo Ro as a pair?]
[Who is this?]
[Woo bin sees a chance and charges...]
[The scene that you just witnessed...]
[In his attempt to attack,
Mr. Capable just shoves him off.]
[Jae Suk and Hyo Rin are the only
survivors of the Theater Club!]
[Hyo Rin gathers up her courage
to rescue her teammate!]
[Complete chaos]
[May be too much for the Theater Club.]
[Mr. Capable lifting up Jae Suk
to throw him in the water.]
[But Jae Suk withstands his maneuver!]
[Jong Kook loses his grip!]
[How can this be?]
[Jong Kook is eliminated!]
[Jae Suk's unbelievable strength!]
[Using his strength to throw
Ha Ha in the water next!]
[And as for the sole survivor, Ji Hyo...]
[Theater Club wins!
Jae Suk pulls it off!]
Jae Suk is no joke!
[Nice going, Yoo Jae Suk!
With his determination to win!]
- Suk Jin and Kwang Soo next?
- No more breaks.
[Used up all his energy.]
I need to get rid of Jae Suk first.
I need to get rid of him first.
Move, move!
[There's a time and place
for everything...]
I'm just going to come
charging ahead.
- Watch out before you fall in.
- Ha Ha, get out!
[We told you not to get involved...]
Ha Ha... don't you think you're being
too much to your own teammates?
[Anyway, the third round of the
Aquatic Battle starts now!]
I have to attack his balance.
Give it your best shot.
[You've lost your own balance?]
[Battle of the wills from the two
team leaders continues!]
You deserved it!
Come out here right now.
[At last, Soo Ro steps up
to the front lines.]
[Soo Ro undoubtedly had a plan
when he stepped up to the front...]
[There he goes!]
[A blunt attack!]
[This is the true image of
Game Adversary Soo Ro!]
[Still unable to comprehend
what just happened.]
[The Game Adversary is back!]
[Second period, special activity...]
[Theater Club wins!]
[Arrives at school,
their final battleground.]
[Who will be the
ultimate club left remaining?]
[Theater Club confident with
the flag now in their possession.]
[Athletic Club also enters
the school hallway.]
This is your final mission.
Throughout this school,
you will find several flag poles.
What about it?
[There are five flag poles per club.]
[Athletic Club - White flag poles.
Theater Club - Blue flag poles.]
[Time on the clock to steal the flag:
30 minutes.]
[The team who's flag pole holds the flag at
the end of the allotted time is the winner.]
[But, if the flag is kept in the flagpole
for a minute at any time, it's also a win!]
If you can keep the flag in the flagpole
for a minute without having it stolen...
then you win the game.
So the important thing is to hide the flag
for now and find the flag post first?
But if the flag is found by the other team
while you have it hidden...
We're not going to hide it anywhere
where they can find it.
I'm Kim Soo Ro.
He just knocked off the other team
like a stack of bowling pins.
He just swept them off
like they're nothing.
We're going to start the game
in your own classroom.
All of the rooms are different.
Flagpole...
Flagstaff...
[Everyone's waiting in their own
classroom full of nervous energy.]
[Huh?]
[Jong Suk enjoying his moment
of relaxation.]
I really want to fight.
[Betrayal mania who wants to get the flag
in his hands as quickly as possible.]
I want to hang the flag in
our own flag post.
And now...
we will start our final race.
[The time has come...]
[Steal the flag - Race start!]
[Time on the clock: 30 minutes!]
[Theater Club vs. Athletic Club!
The final battle starts now!]
[Which of the Theater Club members
has the school flag?]
Don't you think Soo Ro would have it?
I'm positive that he'd have the flag.
[Blank Ji slowly on the move.]
There you go pretending
not to notice anything again!
When did I ever do that?
When?
- I know everything I need to know!
- I have no interest in you!
I don't have any interest
in you either!
- Look at you trying to look young...
- What?
Why are you wearing that weird hat
as if you were a kid?
- You really shouldn't be doing that!
- Seriously...
- Where did you hide it?
- We don't know either.
- Where is it? I don't see it.
- I don't know, but I don't have it.
Oh, there's a flagpole right here.
[Jong Kook and Ha Ha in the
auditorium on the second floor.]
[Discovers the flagpoles!]
If they try to hang the flag here,
we can just steal it from them.
Here it is.
[Woo Bin also discovers a flagpole
for his team on the fifth floor.]
- You scared me!
- You have it, don't you?
I don't have it.
I really don't have the flag.
- Are you sure?
- Yes.
[Running away for now?]
I really don't have it!
You scared me.
[Jae Suk's surprise attack.]
But I like being scared like this.
- Really?
- I'm a scaredy-mania.
Nice going.
Following around girls who are
younger than you like that.
- Follow around?
- Of course.
[Getting into a battle whenever
they run into each other.]
Did you not see me just trying
to carry out my mission?
What did you say?
I just said, did you not see me
just trying to carry out my mission.
- Carrying out your mission?
- That's right.
I don't think I saw that.
I'm trying to do my mission,
so don't talk to me anymore.
- Fine!
- Talk to my lawyer instead!
What did you say?
I told you, I don't have it.
So why do you keep doing this to me?
Why are you changing the
tone of your voice?
[Toning down right away with
Mr. Capable in front of him?]
[Where is the flag?]
There's a flagpole in there.
- You found one?
- Yeah, it's in the gym.
Soo Ro!
[Discovers Soo Ro who's the only one
that knows of where the flag is.]
Why is he running away from us?
[Seeing how he's running away,
does Soo Ro really have the flag?]
Help me!
Soo Ro has the flag.
[Surrounded!]
Athletic Club is after me!
[Could that really be the flag?]
[If that really is the flag,
then the Theater Club is in danger!]
- It's not me.
- Let us just check.
- Soo Ro...
- I said, it's not me.
[Four members of the Athletic Club
surrounding Soo Ro to block him in.]
- He has it.
- Jong Kook...
You know that I don't lie.
[Does he really have the flag
around his waist?]
That's not the flag.
[It's a fake!
They've been deceived!]
[Game Adversary fools
all four of them!]
[This one is a fake!]
[In that case, who has the real flag?]
I have to find it.
[Big-nosed Brother on his own
in search of the flagpole.]
There it is!
[What? The flag?]
[Discovers Jong Hyun with
the flag by pure luck!]
Jong Hyun... where's Jong Hyun?
Where did he go?
We can't have our flag stolen.
I already checked the fifth floor,
but he wasn't up there.
Then does that mean he
went downstairs?
You think he's hiding somewhere?
Didn't you say he's very good at hiding?
[Hiding? He's actually
being chased right now.]
The flag!
The flag is up on the fifth floor!
Fifth floor!
[Woo Bin appears out of nowhere
like a flash of lightening!]
- Hey! Fifth floor!
- Look at all those cars outside.
[Jong Hyun succeeds in seizing
that moment to successfully escape.]
[Hiding out for now behind all the lockers.]
Athletic Club!
How is it that the Theater Club
can run better than the Athletic Club?
Athletic Club, where are you?
Hey, Athletic Club!
[Other members of the Theater Club are
also in a frenzy searching for Jong Hyun.]
- The Athletic Club...
- I found one of the flagpoles.
- Have you seen Jong Hyun?
- I saw him.
- Where are you going, Suk Jin?
- Where are you going?
- Isn't that mine?
- Huh?
- That looks like mine.
Where in the world did he go?
[Finally discovers Jong Hyun!]
Stay in hiding.
Soo Ro... Jong Hyun is
hiding back there.
[Theater Club in an emergency meeting.]
Just be cool... don't make it obvious
because Jong Hyun is back there.
[Jong Hyun's been found
to be in possession of the flag.]
- I think we're going to have to switch.
- Woo Bin should take it.
Woo Bin, you take the flag this time.
[Theater Club making the switch to Woo Bin
to hold on to the flag?]
You can keep watch back here.
[Entrusting the flag with Woo Bin who's
already had many run-ins with the Athletic Club.]
How about the fifth floor?
Jong Hyun... take that and go
the other way.
[Jong Hyun is going in to
fake the others out.]
[I have the flag now!]
Where are they hiding?
[In search for the flag.]
Should we start searching from
the first floor again?
Kwang Soo and I'll go up to the
top floor and search down.
Okay.
[Is Woo Bin heading over to the flagpole
since he knows where one is?]
[Where could it be...]
[Hard to make his move with the
Athletic Team scattered everywhere.]
Lee Jong Suk.
[Just then...]
- Over there?
- Right there.
[Big-nose and Blank Ji discovers Woo Bin.]
I'm scared to death.
- That's it, isn't it?
- Wait...
- Let's go check it out.
- It's over there.
- There it is!
- Let's go.
- We found it!
- Lets go check it out.
[Woo Bin and Jong Suk at a loss
as to what they should do.]
We found it.
We found it!
[What do we do?]
I'm just going to take a quick look.
Let's take a look inside.
[The flag is caught in a mousetrap.]
It was around here somewhere.
[Attempting his escape!]
[Woo Bin breaks through!]
[On a full-out chase of the flag
after finally having discovered it!]
Third floor!
[Where did he go?]
[Totally caught!]
[Huh?]
[Gary just leaves without seeing him?]
I don't know where anyone is.
Where did the camera-man go?
[Over here!]
He's in there.
- He's in there?
- I'm positive.
[He didn't miss him!]
- Suk Jin!
- What?
[Gathering up all of
the Athletic Club members.]
Over here!
[Woo Bin and the flag are in
the music room!]
[Athletic Club blocking both doors!]
He's not in here.
Go towards the back door.
[Woo Bin and the flag trapped
with nowhere to run to!]
- I'm telling you, he's by the back door!
- Where?
- He's in there.
[Huh? Where did Woo Bin go?]
- Where are you talking about?
- He's right here!
Shut the door!
[Locking him in.]
- Hurry up and call the others!
- I don't have a phone!
Give me your phone.
[The other door isn't connected
to the back door.]
[Theater Club in extreme danger!]
Come up to the music room on the
fifth floor. Did he escape?
No, he's hiding in there.
Hurry up and get the others!
Come up to the music room on the fifth floor.
You sure he didn't escape?
- He did escape.
- The window's open.
[What? He escaped out the window?]
[Woo Bin fools them all and escapes
out the window like a thief in the night.]
[While everyone was searching
in the music room...]
[Woo bin makes his escape
through the window!]
[Pretty clever...]
I made a great escape,
but it wasn't captured on camera.
[He's worried about getting it
on screen in his situation?]
This is terrifying.
[Giraffe's surprise attack]
[The Theater Club is in danger
once again!]
Jong Kook!
[Jong Hyun and Jae Suk trying to
thwart Kwang Soo's attempts.]
[Passes the flag over to
Jong Hyun!]
Don't lose the flag!
[How flustered must he be to block
his own teammate, Jae Suk?]
Run away!
[Mr. Capable, Jong Kook!]
[Appearing out of nowhere
for the chase!]
Kim Jong Kook!
Help me!
[Athletic Club finally steals the flag!]
Where do I need to go?
[Makes his escape for now!]
[Haroro hiding away in the
storage room.]
[There you are...]
[Hello, Haroro!]
[Of all people,
to be caught by Soo Ro?]
[Easily takes over the flag!]
He's right here!
First floor!
[Desperate chase of
nonstop stealing.]
[Jong Suk now has the flag!]
- This isn't right!
- Who are you battling for?
Who is this battle being fought for?
[What is the importance of that flag
to fight so desperately...]
[That's the Theater Club's flagpole!]
[If they can keep the flag on the pole for
a full minute, then the Theater Club wins!]
[The flag has been hung.]
[Just then, Mr. Capable
makes his appearance!]
[Pulls it off the pole to
make his escape again!]
[Both teams are being so generous
about giving out hugs today.]
[Even though he was able to
escape Mr. Capable...]
[Climbing over a hill to
encounter another hill.]
[Ace Blank Ji]
[The flag is back in
Athletic Club's possession!]
Run!
Run away quickly!
[Passing it back to Blank Ji?]
[Only three minutes left on the clock!]
[Complete physical brawl]
- Ha Ha...
- Hurry!
[Exhausted Blank Ji]
[Passes it off to Haroro!]
[Back to the auditorium on the second floor
that he saw earlier!]
[What? Why is he heading to
that pole?]
[The blue flagpole belongs
to the Theater Club...]
Hurry up and shut the door.
[Hm...]
- Let's protect this with our lives.
- We're going to protect it.
We have to protect it no matter what!
No matter what!
[One minute warning on the clock!]
[Bodily blocking him from entering?]
[Tying it up nice and securely
to the other team's flagpole...]
Use your legs to keep it shut.
[No one is getting through here!]
[Running full speed towards the flag!]
[You can just leave it alone...]
[Seriously, just leave it alone...]
Jong Hyun!
That's the Theater Club pole.
That's our flagpole!
- Soo Ro, that's our flagpole!
- Please stop!
[Theater Club's exquisite opportunity
to win is dissipated!]
[The 30 minutes on the clock is up!]
[Only thing left to win the battle
is to hang the flag on the flagpole!]
[Quarterback Soo Ro's surprise pass!]
[Receiver Jong Suk catches the flag!]
He's got him again.
Stop hugging me!
It's annoying me to death!
[Heading towards the blue flagpole!]
[Unfolding the flag on his way in
preparation to hang it up on the pole.]
Done!
[Capture the flag: Theater Club wins!]
I am happy that the Theater Club won...
Even though all our guests get to go home,
I'll be back with these guys next week...
I have to face them again
next week.
- You were very aggressive today.
- We saw the glint you had in your eye.
That wildcat glint in your eye.
That traitorous look in your eye.
We're not filming into
tomorrow, are we?
[A rumor's been heard that the Athletic Club
broke up after this day...]
Subtitles by DramaFever
My name is Oh Soo...
'R' group that fell for the female lead
of Running Man mini-series.
[Scene one: Meets the student that works
at a coffee shop and also the heir to 'R' group.]
[Scene two: A couple overcomes challenges
in life to fall madly in love.]
[The love that seemed to
be everlasting...]
[However...]
[A shocking twist to the drama!]
[A tragic beginning to the story.
A real sibling amongst the group!]
[The family hidden secrets slowly
coming to the surface...]
[Find the siblings that were separated
long ago to become the heir of the fortune!]
[Love and betrayal,
conspiracy and conflict!]
[What will be the shocking
conclusion to this drama?]
[Running Man mini-series;
The winter storm is coming.]