[One fine day...]
[A young girl comes up to the writer.]
[And shyly hands over a fan letter
full of her love and encouragement.]
[Running Man will run today
for the love of that young fan girl.]
[An emotional surprise race they'll be
running for that one fan girl alone.]
[Find the young fan girl!]
Subtitles by DramaFever
[A gas station in Namyang- 7:30 a.m.]
[Who could it be?
A car is seen rolling up to the gas station.]
Hello.
- Hello.
- Here's your mission.
- Thank you.
[Hands over a mission.]
Today's mission.
Running Man's sign photo booth.
Pass the mission by handing out
30 of your own signatures.
30 of your own signatures?
If you look in front of you,
you'll see a picture sticker photo booth.
Inside, you'll find seven buttons
with all the members' pictures and names.
- Once the fans walk into the booth...
- So it's all about who's button they press?
The first person who gets
30 selections passes the mission?
[They can only give out their signature to
the fans who pressed their buttons.]
What are you going to come
up with next?
What kind of things do you guys
think of at the meetings?
This man, this man, and this man...
it's going to take a real long time for them.
[Not much hope for Suk Jin,
Kwang Soo and Ha Ha?]
30 signatures isn't going to
take much time at all.
I've been getting a lot of fans lately.
Yes, I don't think this is
going to take long at all.
So they can press any one
of the buttons?
That's why in a case where the crowd presses
someone else's button other than yours
you'll have to stamp a seal that says
'Out of stock' for the crowd.
This is a popularity contest, isn't it?
Then can I get my manager and
my stylist to do it too?
- Hey, guys...
- You can't get your family to vote for you.
[Time for them to sneak into the booth
without anyone else being aware of it.]
[Everyone's in!
RM signing booth is now in operation.]
Who's going to stop by
when this place is so remote?
[And in another location...]
[Another remote location.]
I should be in front of an elementary school.
Namyang is where Kwang Soo is from.
[Now that they think about it,
Namyang is Kwang Soo's hometown.]
Citizens of Namyang... Let's
show them what Namyang is made of!
We are as one.
What do I do?
I'm going to go out of my mind.
Who's going to come here?
My booth looks like it's been abandoned.
This is in the middle of nowhere.
I'm sorry, but this place...
This place is way too remote.
Take a look around this place.
We're in the middle of a
mountain out here.
This isn't going to work.
[Even Ji Hyo's booth in front of the
health building is devoid of any people.]
I want to sign for someone.
Someone please come and
get my signature.
I will give you my signature for free.
[Trying to lure people in by calling out
in a high pitched machine voice.]
Ma'am!
[Has Jae Suk already been selected,
and is about to give out his signature?]
[Ah... he's forcefully giving the PD
his signature as a gift?]
Tell them that this is a gift from me.
I always used to sign, 'Study hard', but
I changed it to, 'Do a good job of editing.'
I want him to do a good job of editing.
Here, you can have one too.
[Through this method, his VJ and the PD
already have ten of his signatures.]
[But, just then...]
[Oh?]
[Someone... came up to the booth!]
[After 40 long minutes...]
[A first customer for Kkuk?]
[Just leaves after a brief glance!]
[Ah...]
[Waiting...]
[Feeling defeated...]
[Falls asleep.]
Hello!
Is anyone out there?
I'm stuck in here.
My freedom has left me,
and I'm left in here to cry on my own.
Ah... my unattainable dream.
I'm suddenly reminded of a thought.
Something that a director
once said to me.
[Just then]
[Oh?]
[Someone is standing out in front
of Gary's booth!]
[What is this?]
[Please!]
[First customer of the day!
Will he choose Gary?]
[Ji Hyo is chosen!]
[Disappointment]
[Must give them a card with 'Out of stock'
stamp on it when someone else is chosen.]
Nothing happened.
[He leaves without even taking
the 'Out of stock' card.]
[Darn...]
Okay, Sam.
Make your move.
Sam, where are you going?
[Starting to talk to the bugs
out of his loneliness.]
Sam!
[Someone's here!]
[His first customer after
an hour of waiting!]
[Nervous anticipation.]
[Let's see here...]
[Will he... choose Ha Ha?]
Yoo Jae Suk.
[Ah... he chose Jae Suk.]
Out of stock?
Running Man?
Song Ji Hyo.
[Twice in a row.]
[That's out of stock too?]
Kim Jong Kook.
Why are they all out of stock?
[I want to cry.]
Thank you for your love and support
for Running Man.
Big-nose.
[Oh... Big-nose Brother's booth
finally gets his first customer!]
[Chooses Ji Hyo as soon as
he steps inside.]
Do you love Song Ji Hyo?
I'm sorry, but Song Ji Hyo
is out of stock.
What is this?
Then I'll pick Yoo Jae Suk.
Yoo Jae Suk is also out of stock.
[Doesn't seem to be interested in anyone else
other than Jae Suk and Ji Hyo.]
I like Ji Suk Jin.
Since all the booths seem to be lacking
in popularity and interest...
- I think ten would be plenty.
- Ten?
We've decided to settle for five.
Okay, let's go with five.
[A crumbling defeat for the booths.
New goal- Five signatures.]
Save me!
There's someone in here!
Anyone!
[Namyang's prodigy who has yet to see
a single customer in his booth.]
It's Running Man!
[Giraffe 1]
Wow! Running Man must be filming here!
[Giraffe 2]
Really? Where?
[You are doing okay in there, aren't you?]
Really?
Then should we check out the booth?
Wow, it's a Running Man booth!
Wow, that's so fascinating!
[Not a single customer for Kwang Soo...
Deciding to relocating the booth.]
Let's all stay focused and strong.
I have to get all the signatures
for the rest of you to be freed, too.
This is my final hope.
[Ultimately decides to move Kwang Soo's
booth next to the local supermarket.]
Hello, Ma'am.
- Hello.
- Oh my goodness. Hello!
I can't believe it's you.
That booth over there is where you can get
a signature from Running Man members.
- Will you please go use the booth?
- Could I?
Yes, please.
You just go in and press whomever you'd like.
Just disregard the fact that I'm in there.
You just step inside and press the picture of
the person who's signature you'd like to have.
Yes.
Please don't mind me, okay?
You just press whomever you'd like.
I think that she's so pretty.
- I think that she's so pretty.
- Excuse me?
[Can't you see that I'm in here?]
- Are you really disregarding me?
- I just pressed her button.
You pressed Ji Hyo's button, right?
Yes, I did.
[You should've just asked her
to press your button.]
[Maybe I should've pressed
Kwang Soo's button.]
There's a fly sitting on my face.
[Do you want me to ask you
for your signature?]
Can you hit the slate for me?
I've run out of tape.
How can you be out of tape?
You haven't even filmed anything.
How can you be out of tape
when you haven't even filmed anything?
[An hour has already gone by
without a single customer...]
[Just then]
[A male student can be seen
walking up to the booth!]
[He's in the booth!]
[Takes him by surprise in the midst
of switching out the tape.]
[Who will he choose?]
[Blank Ji is selected again!]
[Is someone back there?]
All the male students love Ji Hyo.
[Second customer for
Gary's booth at the gas station.]
[Ji Hyo again!]
Song Ji Hyo's out of stock?
It's because she's already mine!
Please!
Song Ji Hyo.
[All the men love Blank Ji!]
[Getting his revenge on the popular ones
by drawing on their faces.]
[A hot mess.]
[Everyone seems to be thinking
on the same wavelength.]
Someone's here.
[Three female guests at Blank Ji's booth!]
I think you should try pressing something.
Try pressing the button for Song Ji Hyo.
Kids in my class love Song Ji Hyo.
- Song Ji Hyo.
- Is this what I press?
Press it.
It says to press the button.
[Selects Blank Ji!]
[First member to succeed in
handing out her signature!]
- Wow!
- Oh my goodness!
Try Yoo Jae Suk.
[Unfortunately,
Yoo Jae Suk is out of stock.]
- Yoo Jae Suk is out of stock.
- What? What the heck!
[They select Jong Kook next!]
- He's out of stock too!
- What the heck!
[That's our ace!
The lone member to succeed!]
My name was the first button
they pressed.
[At the same time, a customer walks
into Jae Suk's signing booth.]
[Welcome]
Please choose the person
who's signature you wish to have.
You've selected Yoo Jae Suk's signature.
Please state your name.
Lee Mi Sun.
Mi. Sun.
Thank you very much.
[Jae Suk also succeeds in getting out
his first signature.]
Gary, Gary, Gary!
[But this customer chooses Jae Suk.]
Everyone either wants Yoo Jae Suk
or Song Ji Hyo.
[Just then.]
[Gary's picture is suddenly lit up?]
[Some male customer walks in
and chooses Gary!]
[Gary finally gets his chance
to hand out his signature!]
Me!
It's me!
[Ha Ha also succeeds in getting out
his first signature!]
[Ecstatic]
[And soon thereafter, Jong Kook succeeds
in getting his signature out.]
[Jae Suk is the first member to
get his second signature out.]
Is there something going on today?
[Ji Hyo follows immediately with
her second signature.]
[Thank you.]
[Jae Suk's popularity...]
[vs. Ji Hyo's popularity.]
[Five votes is their goal.
Jae Suk is currently on his fourth signature.]
[Ji Hyo also has
only one more signature to go.]
Sign!
We'll give you our signature.
Ji Suk Jin is recommended.
Press your selection.
Out of stock.
[Currently tied in first place.
Another guest walks into Jae Suk's booth.]
A guest walks into Ji Hyo's booth as well.]
[Only one signature left to go.]
[Let's see here...]
[Just which of the two will be the first
to get out all five of their signatures?]
[They both choose
the owner of their booth!]
[They simultaneously succeed
their mission!]
- Yoo Jae Suk.
- Yes?
- Congratulations, you've succeeded.
- Yes, thank you.
[Passes over a mission cellphone.]
Really?
I have a text message.
[Make your way over to Sudong Building
in Namyang District.]
[You will find your mission for the day
at that location.]
[You must find your own transportation to
get yourself there as quickly as possible.]
[They must find their own mode of
transportation for the rest of the day.]
Hello.
I have a place that I need to get to.
[Just which one of the two will be the first
to arrive at the mission location?]
There are a lot of those photo booths.
There's one over there too.
I guess whomever is in there
is still working at it.
[Jae Suk discovers
Suk Jin's booth on his way.]
Ji Suk Jin is so cute!
Free signature!
It's free!
[Jae Suk stops by on his way
to play a trick.]
Please make your selection.
[Jae Suk pretending to be a random
person off the streets.]
[And he selects Big-nosed Brother.]
[One man stays oblivious to what's going on
and is excited that he's finally chosen.]
Thank you!
[Ah... you cruel man.]
Have a great day.
[I want to return my signature.]
[What is this?]
Why is he giving it back?
You can have the signature for free.
You startled me.
What are you doing?
Sorry, that didn't count.
That was you?
- Are you done now?
- Yes, I'm done now.
- Seriously?
- Bye, I'll see you later.
- How many have you gotten so far?
- I think I've got two.
Seriously.
[Good-natured Big-nosed Brother
goes back to work.]
Ugh, seriously.
[Kkuk's busy photo booth.
Only has one more signature left to go.]
- Make your selection.
- What did it say?
- I said, make your selection.
- Make a selection?
[Chooses Kkuk.]
[Ecstatic]
[Kkuk also succeeds in handing out
five signatures.]
[This makes five for Gary as well.]
- Is someone back there?
- No, Sir.
[Gary succeeds the mission.]
Go to the address provided.
There, you will find your mission.
- It's close enough for you to run there.
- I can run over there?
I think I'm going to run over there.
[Deciding to run over to the address after
having asked the attendant for directions.]
I'm the first one here.
[Jae Suk finally arrives at the location
written on the mission statement.]
Song Ji Hyo!
I'm not the first one here?
I thought I was the first one to get here.
I was the first one to arrive here.
Even if you were the first one here...
How frustrating. I didn't know.
We're supposed to find our mission.
I even have a map here.
What's the mission?
You have to find
the mission for yourselves today.
It's somewhere at the address provided.
How are we supposed to find the mission?
You have to tell us.
- Hey, by the way...
- That address is your hint.
[The only clue that they're given is
the address provided by the writers.]
[No matter what the case,
it's quite close to their current location.]
It's showing that it's right around here.
It's somewhere in that direction.
[Because the other way
would just be a field...]
Why do you keep following me?
Follow your own map.
I'm following the map myself.
[Following the address they're given...]
[And they arrive at a furniture store?]
It's showing that it's around
here somewhere.
[First floor is the showroom.
Could the mission be somewhere in here?]
It's this way.
[After having completed his booth mission,
Kkuk also arrives at the furniture store.]
I can see Jae Suk in there.
This has to be the place.
I think this is the place.
I think this is the address.
- There has to be something in here.
- Yes.
[Springing into action already.
Kkuk starts off his investigation.]
- What are you looking at?
- Don't you even know the basics of a search?
I'm starting off with searching
all the little stuff.
We're here.
This is the place.
[After looking into it further,
this whole place encompasses the address.]
Hello everyone.
- Hello.
- Can we come in for a moment?
Yes, thank you.
I heard that you have a mission for us?
Can you tell us what the mission is?
- I just got here myself, so I'm not sure.
- Ah, I see.
Sir, do you happen to know
what our mission is?
Why are you listening in? I was
the one who asked them the question.
- I was just...
- Come on, Ji Hyo.
Please use the photo booth.
[Someone, please!]
[Just then, a male adult enters the booth.]
Please make your selection to
receive your signature.
[Please... I want to escape from here!]
I'll just go with Lee Kwang Soo.
- Lee Kwang Soo was your selection?
- Yes, he was.
[Wow- The Giraffe finally succeeds
in getting out all five of his signatures.]
[Giraffe succeeds the booth mission.]
- I've already searched everywhere.
- So you're here to pick out the furniture?
[Is Monday Couple here to pick out
their furniture for their newlywed house?]
Ji Hyo, pick out whatever you like.
- Is that the piece you like?
- Yes.
- Kang Gary.
- Yeah?
[Picks out something she likes as soon as
the words leave Gary's mouth.]
I like this piece over here.
I like the red chair.
That piece doesn't really suit you.
Don't buy that.
You can just sit on my lap.
[What a piece of work...]
Did you get a text?
It's Kwang Soo.
Hey, Kwang Soo.
What is it?
- Hi, Jae Suk.
- I'm filming right now. Call me back later.
Jae Suk!
I'm filming right now too.
- Hey, Suk Jin's here too.
- Seriously?
Yeah.
I'll be...
What is this?
But...
Hurry up and get here.
[This...]
[This is...]
Wait, I know this place.
What?
[What? He knows this place?]
[Just what is the mystery behind
this furniture factory?]
[It does seem like Kwang Soo
is familiar with this place...]
We're here.
This is the place.
Wait...
What is this?
What are we doing here?
I know this place very well.
I know this place very well!
[He knows the place well?
Could it be his favorite furniture store?]
[Why does he suddenly look so relaxed?]
Ji Hyo!
This is the place?
How did they know about this place?
Jae Suk!
Do you know what this place is?
- What?
- I asked if you knew what this place was.
Why?
What are we doing here?
- Why? What's going on?
- What's going on here?
Why?
What is it?
What?
What about this place?
- Is this a hidden camera?
- What?
- What is this?
- Why? What is it?
- What?
- What is it?
[Just... what is this place?]
This is my dad's place.
[This is Kwang Soo's father's place?]
- Get yourself together!
- I'm serious!
This really is my dad's work.
[Yoo Hyuk seems to have figured out
what's going on.]
- What are you doing?
- Seriously?
This is my dad's place of work.
[Could Kwang Soo's father be the mission?]
- Are we supposed to find your dad?
- Are you serious?
Why?
- Hey! Where is he?
- What are you guys doing?
Where are you going?
Jae Suk!
[Even though they don't know
what the mission is...]
[Their priority is to find
Kwang Soo's father!]
Who are you looking for?
Dad!
Where are you going?
[Everyone's suddenly in a rush
to find Kwang Soo's dad!]
- What's the mission?
- I don't know!
It's Kwang Soo's father.
Are you looking for my dad?
[The Giraffe finally figures out
what's going on.]
Why are you guys all getting so excited?
I used to work here when
I was a little kid.
- This is your father's factory?
- Yes.
- I used to work here a lot when I was a kid.
- Seriously?
- I used to...
- Hello!
[A face that all the workers
seem to know.]
Where's Kwang Soo's father?
Sir.
[Could this man...
be Kwang Soo's father?]
Sorry, you've got the wrong person.
[Even though there is some resemblance,
he is not Kwang Soo's father.]
- Where? Where is he?
- On the third floor of the across building.
[Third floor of the building across the way!]
[Yoo Hyuk finally figures out
where Kwang Soo's father is!]
- Did you find it?
- No!
Hello.
[At this rate, Jae Suk
will get to his own dad first!]
- Follow Kwang Soo!
- Why?
Dad!
Dad, where are you?
Third floor?
Don't open your door for anyone!
Lock the door and don't
open it for anyone!
I want you to lock the door!
[Yoo Hyuk is the first one to
arrive on the third floor.]
Hello.
By any chance... are you his father?
[Could this man...
be Kwang Soo's father?]
Are you by any chance,
Lee Kwang Soo's father?
- He just told me to lock the door.
- Are you by any chance...
He just asked me to lock the door.
[Jae Suk discovers Kwang Soo's father!]
Dad!
[His son is one step too late
in finding his own father.]
Dad!
- He's my dad!
- Father.
[Having gone through Kwang Soo's agency
to find Kwang Soo's father.]
His father?
Are you really Kwang Soo's father?
Yes.
[Son- Lee Kwang Soo and Father- Lee Jong Ho.
See the similarity?]
- But your father is so handsome!
- What are you talking about?
- Your father really is so good looking!
- This is an old picture of him.
Why are you showing him that picture?
[Such a cute little Giraffe...]
This is when Kwang Soo was little?
Your father is such a good looking man.
[Big-nose greeting Kwang Soo's father
for the first time.]
[Everyone arriving one by one after
having followed Kwang Soo into the office.]
Hello.
Hello, Father.
- This really is his father.
- Your father is so handsome, Kwang Soo.
- Why do you all keep saying that?
- Can you get me a sofa at cost?
[Taking his opportunity.]
[Just then, the Tiger makes his entrance.]
Dad!
This is the guy!
This is the guy who
picks on me all the time!
- This is the guy!
- You're in big trouble, Jong Kook.
- This is Kwang Soo's father!
This is the guy that torments me
all the time!
[Yoo Hyuk takes this opportunity
to tattle on Jong Kook.]
[His face is turning beet red!]
He hits me even when
the cameras aren't rolling!
I saw him hitting you
three to four times yesterday.
Just smack him across the face!
[His father never misses an episode
of his own son's show!]
You and Kwang Soo don't look
anything alike.
I think Kwang Soo's looks changed from
having been on Running Man for so long.
- That's right.
- So both your parents know how you are?
So you changed because of the environment.
It's all because of Running Man.
[Running Man DNA- Giraffe!]
Didn't Kwang Soo recently
move out of the house?
- Yes.
- You should go check out his new home.
There could be another reason
why he moved out.
Come on, this is my father!
- All the more reason why he should.
- He's not an actor, but he's my real father.
It's because you don't look
anything like your father.
I know.
He looks like he could be your brother.
Your father looks so young.
[Just then... one person that they all had
forgotten about makes his arrival.]
Wow... I can't believe that none of you
waited for me.
- Dong Hoon!
- Where in the world are we?
- Come say hello to Kwang Soo's father.
- What is going on here?
- This is Kwang Soo's father.
- Seriously? Hello.
[Immediately becoming docile after
being introduced to Kwang Soo's father.]
Then is Kwang Soo's father
going to give us our mission?
- Go ahead and ask him.
- What's the mission?
There are no other missions.
- Do you have something in your pocket?
- No, I didn't receive anything.
- You don't have anything?
- Then is there something around here?
I'm sure that there's something here.
We should search for it.
[Could the mission be somewhere
around father's desk?]
Could that picture he showed us
be the mission?
- It has to be around here somewhere.
- Why are you all snooping around?
We're not snooping.
We're just searching for a mission.
- You didn't receive anything?
- That's right. This is Namyang.
- This is Namyang.
- Here's a picture of Kwang Soo.
Father, you have a phone call.
[Kwang Soo's father receives a phone call?]
Wow, Kwang Soo.
Yes.
[The mission is to be transmitted to father
five minutes after he was discovered.]
- He just received something.
- It must've been about a mission.
There's a showroom on the first floor,
and the mission is on one of the beds.
[The mission can be found near a bed
in the showroom on the first floor!]
- Thank you, Father!
- Thank you!
[Saving the farewell greetings for later,
and off to find the mission!]
You should go too and
find the mission.
- I'll call you later, Dad.
- Thank you!
Where's the bed?
[The mission is near
a bed in the showroom!]
A bed?
[Today's mission is near one of these
countless number of beds!]
Please make sure
to be careful with the furniture.
- Watch what you're doing!
- Where is it?
Is this it?
[This is!]
[Ace, Ji Hyo, discovers something!]
- She's found something!
- What is it?
- She found it.
- Hey!
[Ji Hyo tries to run away
to look at the mission by herself.]
- Did you find something?
- What is it?
She really is something else.
Please have a seat, Princess.
[Thus, everyone gets to find out together
just what the mission is.]
- Let's all sit down and find out together.
- Yes, let's all look at it together.
[It appears to be a book.
What could it be?]
What could it be?
[Namyang race]
[Pass each mission via the pictures in the
book to find the person who made the book.]
[The person to attach a picture of themselves
with the author of the book is the winner.]
[A book sent in by a young fan girl
who lives in the city of Namyang.]
- What is this?
- It's a girl.
[Hello, it's such an honor
to meet you all like this.]
[My name is ___,
and I'm a huge fan of Running Man.]
[I currently live in Deokso,
which is two subway train stations
away from where
Lee Kwang Soo used to live.]
[The reason why I sent you this is because
I would love for Running Man to come here.]
[So I would like to give you a brief
introduction of my neighborhood.]
There's no mention of her name, her age,
or the name of the school she attends.
- We have to find the girl who wrote this.
- Look.
[I've gone to watch the filming of
Running Man in the past.]
[It was 'The Laws of the Jungle' episode.]
[I watch Running Man every week.]
What are you doing!
[Yoo Hyuk wanting to get closer to
the book of devotion sent in by the fan.]
[Everyone trying to get a little bit closer.]
- What are you all doing?
- Hang on a minute.
Let's all look at it together.
- Let's all look at it together.
- Okay, here.
[I have an older and a younger sister.]
[My older sister is a junior in high school,
and she's interested in broadcast journalism
and she's a huge fan of Running Man too.]
[We're planning on going to see a filming
of the show after she takes the SAT's.]
- Which means she's younger than a junior.
- That would make her younger.
[Whatever the case...]
[The book shows how much love and dedication
she poured into making this fan book.]
Place the picture of yourself with the
author of the book in this spot.
- We have to find the author of the book.
- We have to find this girl.
Our mission is to find her.
The fan girl came to the station herself
to give me that book.
- She really made this book herself?
- Yes, she gave it to me herself.
She made this book all by herself?
I'm really touched right now.
[One day in August of 2013.]
[A young fan girl disappears after
handing the book over to the writer.]
Do you see all those pictures
in that book?
She went to all of those places herself
to take those pictures
and she put them in that book along
with a description of each place.
But what you're going to be doing, is
filling the rest of the empty spaces.
Every time you finish a mission
you'll be given a picture
to put into that book.
And as you work on filling up
the rest of that book
you'll eventually get to meet
your fan.
Yes, that's right.
The person to meet that girl and
take a picture together
in order to complete that final page,
will be the ultimate winner for the day.
What's more important is that even though
we also got to meet Kwang Soo's father...
today's victory will not have
anything to do with Kwang Soo.
[We'll just assume that Kwang Soo
isn't going to be today's winner.]
- But he knows the area very well.
- We're just here by chance.
When a celebrity usually
visits their hometown...
they usually get a special episode
like this filmed in their honor.
Kwang Soo's father is watching us right now.
[He's watching...]
-  Kwang Soo is...
- He's the star of the show today.
You heard, right, Dad?
- Kwang Soo is the star of the show today!
- Did you hear that?
Lee Kwang Soo!
- Let's ride the wave!
- Okay.
One, two, three!
Dad, I'm working right now.
I'd like to add one more thing.
That fan girl has no idea
that this is happening right now.
- Seriously?
- No, she has no idea.
- This will be a total surprise to her.
- She'll be so shocked.
So we're going to have to find her.
There's a copy of the book
in these bags.
[Everyone to head on their own separate ways
with a copy of the book in their bags.]
There's also a camera in your bags.
- Okay, the camera is in here.
- Everything is in here.
Let's take this one.
What's this?
[These are the pictures that were
in the book the fan girl made.]
[Pictures of various
different locales in Namyang?]
What are you looking at?
What is this?
- Do we just pick one?
- Can we pick whichever one we want?
[First mission- Take public transportation
to get to the place within the picture.]
Han River Park.
Sampae Earth.
- Wabueup Office.
- Is it near here?
If I have to take public transportation,
does it mean that my dad can give me a ride?
That's such a great idea.
This looks like a library.
What is this place?
- Hello!
- Hello.
- Let's go together.
- What do you mean, go together?
- We're going to the same place anyway.
- Why would we go together?
- Pyungnae Library, please.
- Pyungnae Library?
- Do you know where it's at?
- Yes.
- Sir, do you know Han River Public Park?
- How about Sampae Earth?
- Dad, can you give me a ride?
- That's awesome.
- That's so awesome.
- Okay.
- Wow, what a good dad.
- Did he say he'll give you a ride?
- Yes, he is.
- Yes.
But since we have to take the VJ's,
I think only one of you'll be able to go.
- Hey, I'll carry your camera.
- Yeah, he can be your camera man.
[Thinking fast on his feet-
Haroro offers himself up for service.]
I've always wondered who Kwang Soo took
after for him to be so handsome and sexy.
But, now I see where he got it, Father.
[What kind of a girl could the fan girl be?]
She probably has no idea whatsoever
that we're on our way to find her right now.
I'm so thankful for what
she did, aren't you?
Father, you know how Kwang Soo is
making a pretty good living these days?
But what's really shocking is...
he bought you a new car last week.
- What a good son!
- He's such a filial son!
[Time to give Kwang Soo a bit
of a hard time.]
He also bought two designer
handbags for his mother.
- It's for you, Mother!
- For you!
[Kwang Soo's in big trouble.]
- He really loves surprising people.
- He does. Sorry for ruining it for you.
Congratulations, Sister-in-law!
Dong Hoon just told me that
he bought a house for you!
You're moving in there next month!
[Wabueup Office in Namyang]
- Thank you.
- Thank you, Father.
[The three having made it easily to their
destination, thanks to Kwang Soo's father.]
- Bye, Dad.
- Goodbye, Father.
[Thank you, Mr. Lee.]
- This place looks just like the picture.
- Let's go up to the second floor.
[Han River Park- Sampae Earth.]
[Monday Couple arrives at
their destination.]
Wow, this place is really nice.
Look!
Someone's flying a kite.
[Look at all those countless numbers
of kites flying in the sky!]
[What are those kites doing up in the sky?]
[Find a picture from the people who are flying
their kites to get to your next destination.]
- One of these people has the picture?
- Could the picture be attached to the kite?
[Could the picture be attached to the kite?]
[Meanwhile]
We're here. Does it
look like the place in the picture?
[Pyungnae Library]
Hello.
[Enters the children's library.]
This is a mission.
- We have to do something over here.
- What is it?
[In order to earn the picture you need
to get to your next destination
you have to find the book you need
within the library.]
[You have ten minutes.]
There is a book with the 'R' sticker
stuck on it somewhere within this library.
- We just need to find that one book?
- You first need to bring back the book.
- Yes, I understand.
- You have ten minutes to find it.
[Good idea-
Resorting to dirty plays and tricks.]
We're not supposed to be acting like this
inside of a library. I'm so sorry.
[A book with the 'R' sticker on it...]
[Discovers a copy of a traditional children's
fairytale with the 'R' sticker on it!]
[Big-nosed Brother having found
the book within no time at all.]
Of course, I found it.
What's so difficult about finding one?
A book with an 'R' sticker on it?
Hello.
[Hiding Suk Jin's shoes away.]
- The book that you brought back...
- Yes?
You need to study it.
- You're going to test me on this?
- Just study it.
I've read this before.
Having read it isn't what's important,
but you have to find the one with the sticker.
I've read quite a few books in here.
Ah, here's one.
[Finally discovers a copy of
'The Little Prince' with the sticker on it.]
The Little Prince.
Oh, Saint Exupery.
No, it's not.
Then is it... Saint Desibury?
No, Suk Jin.
You don't know your literature.
[You already got it right on the first try.]
- That's not it?
- Saint Taxabary?
- Saint... what was his name?
- I have to read this book?
With the time you've spent finding the book,
and the time you have for studying...
you've got six and a half minutes left.
But look at how thick my book is.
You took too long to find the book.
His book is only 13 pages long.
Suk Jin, can't you just read it
to yourself silently?
[Both of their voices are starting to
get louder and louder.]
You weren't a very good student,
were you?
- Yes, I was.
- No, you weren't.
- Okay, put your books down.
- Okay.
Pass your books forward.
Here you go.
[Return the books
that they were studying from.]
- I got this.
- I picked the wrong book.
I'll start by asking Suk Jin a question
since he seems to be so confident.
As I'm sure you already know
the first person to answer three questions
right gets to leave first with the picture.
- Of course.
- Yes, we understand.
I'm sorry, Jae Suk.
It looks like I'll be leaving first.
Okay.
Here's your first question.
In the book you just read,
'Kong-ji and Pat-ji'...
Yes?
How many butterflies were
on the cover of the book?
How many butterflies
were on the cover of the book?
I knew it was going to be like this.
These are the types of things
that we should've been looking at.
- That's the thing we needed to study.
- Seriously.
[Did you see the book?
How many butterflies were on the cover?]
[Correct answer- Four.]
- Five, four, three, two...
- 672.
[672 butterflies?]
- You know that's not right.
- I didn't see the butterflies.
If Yoo Jae Suk can answer it correctly,
we'll allow it.
- Seriously?
- Yes.
Five.
[Correct answer is four.
So close...]
Is it one?
Or is it two?
[You can check for yourselves.]
- Check for yourselves.
- Three, four? Ugh!
- How is there four? There's only one.
- One, two, three, four.
[Whatever the case,
the first question is now over.]
- Next up is, 'The Little Prince' question.
- Okay.
On page 23...
'The little Prince says
with a sad expression on his face.'
'You won't be able to get very far even if
you say you'll go straight from now on.'
- That's an excerpt from the book.
- Yes.
There's a picture of a pretty star
underneath that excerpt.
How many stars are in that drawing?
[How many stars are
in the picture on page 23?]
That's a good question.
Are you going to keep asking
these types of questions?
[Correct answer- Four.]
[It's a page that Jae Suk was
sure to have seen.]
Five!
The correct answer is... four.
[Jae Suk gets it wrong by one again.]
Second question from the book,
Kong-ji and Pat-ji.
- You read the book twice, right?
- Yes, I read it twice.
You have to know this answer, okay?
In the very last page of the book...
where is the place that Kong-ji
is seen standing with the officer?
That's an easy question.
- Where is this place?
- Is it an obvious place?
Yes, it is.
There would be no doubt about it.
- You read through it twice.
- I read through the book twice.
It's in front of an octagonal pavilion.
Or is it a hexagonal pavilion?
[Correct answer- On top of a bridge.]
[Big-nose Brother rewriting the
architectural history.]
- There is no such a thing!
- How many angles were there?
Octagonal pavilion?
[A chance is given to Jae Suk
to answer the question correctly.]
I didn't see the page,
so I have to guess the answer.
Please give me one more chance.
- I see a door...
- I see water.
And there's water.
Ms. Kong-ji... Ms. Kong-ji's house.
[What?]
What do you mean, Ms. Kong-ji?
Are you two friends?
[You must be on friendly terms with her.]
Do you know who she is personally?
She would be like my older sister.
She's been around for a long time.
- Is it a bridge?
- Yes, it is a bridge.
Oh my gosh! It is the bridge!
I got it right!
How could you not have
gotten that answer?
[Kong-ji and the officer are seen
standing on top of the bridge.]
Wabuep Office.
Beat the office's expert
to win your picture.
If you can't beat the stapler expert,
then you will move on to the next expert.
- Okay, we'll admit defeat when we're beat.
- Yes, we will.
I think we'll be able to do this.
[Huh? What are you trying to do?]
These pages are sticking together.
[He took the staples out of his stapler,
and swapped it out with the expert's!]
Let's do this.
Okay, let's start.
Three books of thirteen pages.
[Everyone's attacking the mission
with their own unique style.]
[Doing it with the style
of an expert at ease.]
[This is much more effective!]
[Stapling a stack with
the stapler he swapped.]
[Using his strength...]
[All the expert has left to do now
is to staple her stacks together.]
[There aren't any staples in there?]
[Expert steals Jong Kook's stapler.]
You can't use mine!
You can't use my stapler!
- You can't use my stapler!
- Done!
No, you can't use my stapler!
[Kwang Soo and Ha Ha
finish at the same time.]
What are you doing?
You can't use my stapler!
- Kwang Soo and I are finished.
- Kwang Soo took out her staples.
[The director verifies that
Kwang Soo cheated.]
- That's why she used mine.
- That's not such a huge deal.
- That's not such a bad thing.
- Disqualified.
[Kwang Soo is disqualified.
Ha Ha alone passes the mission.]
I need to take a look!
[Meanwhile, the Monday Couple is trying
to find their picture from the kite fliers.]
It's another dud.
Here you go. Thank you.
There are way too many kites.
[Ace Ji Hyo seems to have
discovered something.]
[Something on the kite being flown
by the man running around.]
Sir!
Just a minute.
[Finally having caught up to the
suspicious kite flier.]
Can I fly your kite for a minute?
[Is there really a picture on the kite?]
[It really is a picture!]
What is this?
[This is a picture that will bring
Ji Hyo one step closer to finding the girl!]
[This picture alone isn't enough to
guide her to where she needs to go.]
[Meanwhile...]
- Is this supposed to be Ann?
- Yeah.
[Next 'R' stickered book is,
'Redheaded Ann'.]
What's the book about?
It's a story about love.
She cut her hair off.
She cut her hair off?
Why cut it off?
It doesn't say
which salon she went to, does it?
No, it doesn't.
Come on! What are you doing?
- We just need to look at the pictures.
- Yeah, just the pictures.
There are two windows.
[They're only looking at the pictures now
after the last batch of questions.]
Who's the grandfather?
[An immature fight that breaks out
right before the exam starts.]
- Let me just take a quick look.
- No, you can't.
What does this say?
What is all this?
- What did it say?
- Lucimon.
Let me take a look.
[Time over]
This is all just going to be guesswork.
- You two just read the book, right?
- Yes, we read it.
- Yes, we really enjoyed the book.
- Do we really need to read it like this?
- This question is for the both of you.
- Okay.
The first person to shout out the answer
gets it, okay?
What is the name of
Ann's friend in the book?
What is the name of her
friend in the book?
Isn't there more to the question?
- Can you tell me the answer?
- It's not a picture question?
- We only looked at the pictures.
- We only studied the pictures.
We only looked at the pictures.
- What is the name of Anne's friend?
I just told you that we only
looked at the pictures.
You have to ask us about the flowers.
- There are four flowers.
- There's a page with 20 flowers on it too.
What are you doing?
There are only six characters
in the book.
Seriously.
[There aren't even that many characters,
but you only looked at the pictures...]
[You shouldn't have
just looked at the pictures.]
[Correct answer- Diana.]
[It's quite an easy answer to find.]
- Natasha?
- It's not Natasha.
[Her only friend is from Eastern Europe?]
Which country is that book from?
It's not from Russia?
In the book, 'Heunbujeon'...
This is a very easy question.
Where did the couple plant the seed
that the bird brought them?
Answer.
On the roof.
No, that's incorrect.
[Correct answer- By the fence.]
[Shutting Jae Suk's mouth out of fear
that he'll answer it correctly.]
I think you were about to
give the right answer.
What is it?
By the well.
Want to give the answer
that I was about to give?
- What the heck is that?
- You never know.
- Really? Back in those times?
- You never know what they could've had.
[Just what is the answer that he told you?]
By the faucet?
That isn't it.
[This is the Joseon times.
Faucets didn't exist.]
They needed to have pipes, and
where would they have gotten the faucet?
They could've had a faucet back then.
This isn't going right.
Just what is the correct answer?
- You looked like you had it. It's the fence.
- Ah, the fence!
You only have one chance
to answer the next question.
Just one chance?
Only one of us?
Okay.
- How many birds are on page 19?
- Answer!
[The correct answer is... four!]
[Jae Suk shouts out with confidence.]
Four.
If I get this right, then
Suk Jin has to buy our lunch, right?
But if I get it right,
then he has to buy, right?
Please.
[Jae Suk answers it correctly.]
[Jae Suk succeeds the book mission.]
Who would've ever thought that I'd lose
over the number of the birds?
- What is this place?
- What is it?
Is this where we need to go next?
Alpine Federation?
I think I saw this earlier.
[Ha Ha is already on his way to figuring out
where his next destination will be.]
What could this be?
It looks like some wall climbing place.
Sir.
Can I ask you a question?
Would you know where this place is?
[Will he know where this place is?]
Is this the Alpine Federation in Namyang?
It looks like some kind of a statue.
Can you tell me where this place is?
Nothing like this exists around here.
- You don't know?
- No, I don't.
- In Namyang? Ah!
- What?
- It's the athletic field.
- The athletic field?
- That's right.
- What's the place called?
- It's the Namyang Grand Athletic Field.
-  Namyang Grand Athletic Field?
Thank you so much.
Thank you!
[Succeeds in figuring out
his next destination!]
[Gary's also in the process of asking
where his next destination is.]
[Gary also figures out that he needs to go to
Namyang Grand Athletic Field.]
That's the rock climbing wall.
Ah, this is the rock climbing wall?
[Also figures out that it's a
rock climbing structure.]
Yes, you're right.
Thank you.
[Ji Hyo and Gary heading out together
to Namyang Grand Athletic Field.]
It has to be the place, right?
She wrote that it's a place that she'd
always walk by on her way to school.
[Referring back to the book in their bags.]
- I don't know anything about this area.
- It must be nice for Kwang Soo.
I bet he knows the area really well
since he grew up around here.
[And the prodigy of Namyang...]
[Is stuck and isn't able to budge
from being detained by the Tiger.]
[Giraffe is 70% topless,
trying to make his escape.]
Why are you taking off you shirt?
[Tiger attempting to skin the Giraffe.]
Thanks for lunch, Suk Jin.
- You have to pay the cab fare, okay?
- Don't even worry about it.
Let's not make bets like that anymore.
I don't even have any money for the cab fare.
[Jae Suk and Suk Jin approaching
Namyang Grand Athletic Field.]
I doubt anyone's there already.
- There it is. It's just like the picture.
- I see it too.
Isn't that a rock climbing wall?
Are you going to have to climb?
- No way.
- That's a rock climbing wall?
They're not expecting us
to climb up there, are they?
[Namyang Rock Climbing Wall.]
- This is it.
- It's the same thing.
It's exactly the same.
[A perfect match to the picture.]
[It's none other than a place where
the fan girl likes to exercise.]
[At the height of 15m, their
heads automatically tip back to see.]
Look at this.
[Their own personal equipment
is arranged next to one another.]
Oh my goodness.
Wow, seriously?
What do they expect us to do?
[Haroro also arrives.]
There's a balloon up there.
It's telling us that if we want a better
hint, we need to climb up higher.
['High' and 'Low' balloon.]
What are we expected to do here?
You'll find envelopes that contain a picture
behind those low, middle, and high balloons.
There's a huge difference between the
hints for those three pictures.
They're quite different.
Therefore, we encourage you to
go after the higher ones.
Can we go for something lower if we decide
that we can't go for the higher one?
Yes, but you have to get on a different line,
so you have to come back down first.
- We have to come back down?
- We have to decide before we go up.
- I'm going for the middle.
- I'm going for the middle too.
[They each select their hints to go after.]
- This is...
- Wow, this is seriously.
- Should I just go for the low one?
- Did you pick one?
- Maybe we should stretch out first.
- That won't do anything for me.
[Climb!]
[Suk Jin and Gary going for the 'High',
and Jae Suk and Ji Hyo going for the 'Mid'.]
- This is so scary!
- I don't think I can do this!
This is so scary!
This is absurd!
Hang on!
- Are you sure this won't fall off?
- It's not going to fall off.
How am I ever going to go up that high?
I think that I was being too greedy.
[Amazing-
A rock climbing grasshopper.]
Look at Jae Suk.
That's unbelievable.
[Almost there!]
[Climbing fearlessly up the wall!]
[Yoo-piderman!]
I'm so scared.
[Finds the envelope containing the hint.]
[The 'Mid' hint.]
Down!
Just take your hands off.
[Barely... makes his descent.]
[Beats his fear of heights to
be the first one to succeed.]
Hang on!
[His legs giving up on him.]
There's nothing for me to grab onto!
No!
I don't have anything to grab onto!
[Blank Ji making her way upward.]
[Arrives midway.]
I got it!
Descent!
Do you find that fun?
[Blank Ji lightly making her way down.]
How can she think that's fun?
Suk Jin!
Why did you pick the high one?
Wait!
Wait a minute!
[Oh... Gary!]
[Arrives at the highest hint.]
[Gae-piderman arrives at
the highest balloon.]
[Gets his hand on the highest hint.]
Descent!
Ji Hyo, you should've gone
for the high one.
[Easily makes his way back down.]
- Suk Jin!
- I'm so scared.
- Yeah?
- I brought a middle hint down.
Why don't you take my hint,
and I'll go for your high hint?
- Seriously?
- Yeah, you can take this one.
- Ji Hyo, I love you!
- Here you go!
[Fearless Ji Hyo offers to go back up
for Suk Jin's high hint.]
- What's there to be scared about?
- You don't find that scary?
Descent!
- Descent!
- Let go.
- Let go!
- I can't let go!
- Suk Jin, let go!
- I can't! I'll just go back down.
- No, you can't.
- I'll just come back down.
- Let go!
- You just need to let go!
I can't!
I don't trust that guy!
- Just let go!
- I can't let go!
- How can I let go!
Take your hands off of the wall!
Are you crazy?
- Grab the rope!
- I'll just come back down.
[Just keeps on insisting
that he'll come back down.]
Grab the rope in front of you!
- What if the rope breaks?
- It's not going to break.
Wait!
Wait, wait a minute!
- Seriously, Suk Jin.
- I understand what he must be feeling.
Okay, I've let go.
[After all the screaming...]
[Finally makes his way back down.]
You're doing it too fast.
Slow down.
Please slow it down.
Please.
[Finally back on the ground.]
- Where is it, Ji Hyo.
- Here you go.
- Thanks.
- You're really going back up there?
Don't you know how high up that is?
- Don't you have any fear?
- There is a difference between the hints?
- Yes, there's a huge difference.
- Really?
There is a tremendous difference.
I don't think I can do this.
I'm so terrified.
You can't look down.
I'm only able to say this because
I'm back down on the ground.
That's what I realized when I got back down.
What are you going to do?
Are you going to go up or down?
- Me?
- Yes.
Should I go for the low one?
Why are you even making us do this?
- Look at Song Ji Hyo up there.
- She's already almost there.
[Fearless Blank Ji steadily making
her way up to the top.]
- I feel like I'm going to fall off!
- Look at Song Ji Hyo climb up there.
Look at Song Ji Hyo up there.
- There's no spot for me to grab onto!
- Song Ji Hyo! What are you made of?
If you think you don't have anything to grab,
you should take a look at Song Ji Hyo.
- Song Ji Hyo, are you the Spiderman?
- Your left foot!
Hang on a second.
No!
You can't fall down!
- Don't give up!
- You're there!
[Wow... arrives at the highest balloon.]
She seriously is...
[Wins herself the high hint envelope.]
Ha Ha!
Look at what Ji Hyo's doing.
[Huh?
He's going for the low hint?]
- Why are you going for the low hint?
- That was really hard.
- Wow, this really was very hard.
- Ha Ha, you're seriously...
Descent!
Ji Hyo!
No, Ji Hyo!
I did it!
I'm satisfied with this.
I thought I was going to die up there.
I can't believe I did it!
[All in a day's work for Ji Hyo.]
[Yoo Hyuk checking his mid hint.]
[A park?
Someone filming something?]
I don't even know what it is with my hint,
so there's no way for you to know what it is.
But we can join our heads
and work together on this.
I think we can just follow the others
with the high hint.
Okay.
[Their plan is to follow the ones
who gained the high hint.]
[Gary checking his high hint.]
[An apartment building?]
[Is this where the fan girl lives?]
[My house.]
This is...
This hint is unbelievable.
- Isn't this a rock climbing wall?
- It's rock climbing.
Isn't that Jae Suk?
Maybe he just got here too.
[What do you mean, just got here?
He's about to leave.]
- Where is he going?
- Jae Suk!
- Jae Suk, where are you going?
- What took you guys so long?
- Where are you going?
- We're going to the next location.
- You're already done?
- Of course, we're done.
- How can you be finished already?
- Just go and do your mission.
- Don't go and just stay with us.
- Just go and do your thing.
- Why are you locking your door?
Once Gary gets in his taxi,
can you follow it?
[His plan is to follow Gary
to his next destination.]
There he is.
Please follow his taxi.
Thank you.
Sir.
I need to get to this building.
I don't know which apartment
building it is.
[At a closer look,
they can see some street signs.]
- I think I got it.
- You know where it is?
It looks like they're filming something.
- Could it be a drama shoot?
- I'm not sure.
This won't do.
He said there's a huge difference.
I think I should follow Ji Hyo's car
when she gets on the road.
[Only one mid and low hint are left.]
How are you so high up there already?
- Jong Kook.
- Yeah?
[Take that!]
- Why are you coming up my way?
- I have to get the mid hint.
You have to go after your own.
Are you already up there?
[Giraffe is almost to his mid hint.]
Then I'm just going to go back down.
Like this?
[Kkuk is making his way back down
from having no other choice.]
[Giraffe wins himself the mid hint.]
Help me!
I dropped my balloon!
Just let go of the wall
and grab the balloon.
You want me to let go?
How am I to let go?
[Frozen in his awkward stance.]
[Barely manages to rescue his balloon.]
Please.
Slow down!
[The envelope containing his hint!]
I'm all done.
What are you doing!
[Lucky enough to find the hint
that fell out of the sky.]
What are you doing?
Untie me!
- Help me!
- I'm all done here.
- Wait!
- I'm leaving!
- Thanks, Kwang Soo.
- Don't do this!
- Come on, Jong Kook.
Come on!
What are you doing!
See you later, Kwang Soo.
Call the police!
Wait!
[Bye, Giraffe.]
He shouldn't have beat me up there.
He should've waited for me.
There's still one low hint
left up there.
[One lonely low hint left up
on the wall.]
Fine, let's just do this.
[Blank Ji with her high hint.]
Building eight.
- I think that's in Deokso.
- In Deokso?
Are there a lot of apartment buildings
that look like this in Deokso?
Ji Hyo knows where she's going,
doesn't she?
I doubt she's just going aimlessly, right?
This is the real chase.
I feel like we're in a movie.
[Jae Suk is also secretly chasing after
Gary and his better hint.]
Wow, I can't believe the difference
between the hints.
Wow, she lives on the top floor,
which makes it easier for us to find her.
So that's where she lives.
[Born in July of 1998.]
Do you know which middle schools
are in that area?
- There's Shimsa Middle School.
- Is it for girls?
It's a school for both boys and girls.
[Born in July of 1998.
A student at a middle school in Deokso?]
[Lives in an apartment in
the Deokso area.]
[Kkuk checking out his mid hint.]
What is this?
[One of the hint pictures is
of a movie poster?]
Could it be a movie theater?
'Hide and go seek'...
'Do you like scary ghost stories?'
[Re-reading through her notes.]
[Could this be the place?]
Will you please take me to
Gildong Elementary School?
[But that's back in Seoul?]
[Where is he going?]
Those squares and circles on the roof...
Yes, I think this is the place.
[He seems to have made it to the
right apartment complex?]
Yes, this is the place.
[Discovers an apartment building that looks
identical to the one in the picture!]
That's it!
That's the house!
There it is!
That's the place!
Driver, we've found the place!
[A match!]
- Thank you.
- Yes, thank you very much.
[Gary is the first one to arrive.]
[Yoo Hyuk having followed
Gary all the way here.]
I think we're on our way to
the girl's house.
Or is this a location of a film shoot?
[Even though he followed him here,
he still has no idea where he's going.]
It's one of those buildings.
I think you can just drop me off here.
[Ji Hyo also arrives at the apartment.]
Okay, we're here.
How much is the fare?
[Big-nose Brother also arrives.]
[Which one is it?]
Here.
This is the place.
Okay, this is good.
I can see Suk Jin up there.
[Ro-Ro gets lucky and sees Suk Jin.]
- I'll show everyone the power of Namyang!
- Okay, fighting!
- Do you have a car?
- Yes.
Then can you give me a ride to this place?
I don't know where that place is.
- Okay, let's go.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
[But he's lucky enough to hitch a ride.]
Is there a school nearby this picture?
Would you know where this is?
If you keep on going a bit further,
there should be another school.
Jong Kook... you're going to get it.
Excuse me.
- Do you live here?
- Yes.
Can you help me out with something?
Would you happen to know
where this building is?
- This is the building right up front.
- Seriously?
That's the building right up there.
[Right nearby!]
- There it is!
- I think that's the building.
Thank you so much!
See this structure right here?
And this is the building that she indicated
as being her house.
[That's the place!]
I wonder which apartment number that is.
Hello. Ma'am, do you
know which number this is?
[Showing all the neighbors the hint picture.]
- That's apartment 101.
- That one?
[The next building!]
[Is this the place?]
[Gary and Blank Ji storm the
front entrance!]
Jae Suk.
Where are you, Kwang Soo?
We don't even need to drag this out.
Let's just meet up and talk.
Where are you right now?
I'm right by the apartment complex area.
[The exact same street
as the one in the picture!]
- I'm right by the complex.
- Me too.
- I'm right by the entrance.
- Wait for me there.
[He found his way to the right place?]
Kwang Soo made it here.
He found it with his low hint.
[Checking out the camera before he
meets with the fan girl at her home.]
Why isn't this working?
I've never used this before,
so I don't know how to work it.
[They arrive at the very top floor.]
[Checking if they're in the right place.]
Who is it?
Hello.
[Is this how you work it?]
By any chance...
Is there a girl who was born in
1998 that lives here?
[Could this be the girl's house?]
Hello.
Do you have an older sister at home?
Or how about a little sister?
- I don't have a little sister.
- Then an older sister?
Was your older sister born in
July of 1998?
- No, she wasn't.
- She wasn't?
Sorry.
[In that case...]
[Could this be the house?]
[Practicing a candid photo shot.]
Mine won't work.
[Yoo Hyuk having made
his way to the interior.]
This is... this must be the place!
This is the place.
[Having found the place
within the picture.]
This has to be it.
This is where the picture was taken.
[A perfect match
to the locale in the picture.]
This is it.
This is where the picture was taken.
[Got it... I found the place!]
- I know.
- Where did Ji Hyo go?
- Was the picture taken from the top?
- Yeah, from the top.
[Big-nosed Brother's mid hint photo.]
Did they come here to shoot
a film recently?
- Yes.
- Which movie?
- 'Hide and Go Seek'!
- That was shot here?
Yes!
[Bingo!
The movie which Son Hyun Joo was in.]
[The place where the movie, 'Hide and Go Seek'
with Moon Jung Hee and Jeon Mi Sun was shot.]
- Where? Right up here?
- No, back there!
- Where?
- Let's go!
- Over there!
- Where?
- Big-nosed Brother!
- That's me!
[That's why there was the
'Hide and Go Seek' hint...]
Hide and Go Seek?
[Away from everyone else on his own
just to stare at the picture...]
[If he would just search the movie,
the name of the apartment would pop up...]
This looks like the place where
the movie was shot.
- Who is it?
- Hello.
I'm sorry, but is there a girl who was born
in July of 1998 that lives here?
How old are you?
- I'm ten.
- I see. Do you have an older sister?
- Yes.
- Is your sister in middle school?
Yes.
[Her older sister is in middle school!]
-Hi!
- Hi!
Hi. You're so cute.
[Mother coming to the door to
greet them with a smile.]
- By any chance, did your sister...
- Is your sister in 3rd year of middle school?
Is your sister a third year in middle school?
She is!
[They found it!
The fan girl's house!]
She's not here?
- She's not here?
- She's not home right now.
- Then where did she go?
- She's at school.
- She's at school?
- Which school does she go to?
- Middle school.
- But which middle school?
- What's the name of her school?
[Adorable little sister knowing
how to play the variety game.]
She's at middle school.
- That's the place.
- That has to be it.
- That's it.
- That's the place.
[Correctly guesses the girl's home.]
- Run.
- Let's go.
[Countless number of Running Man pictures
in the girl's bedroom!]
[On top of it all,
she seems to like Kwang Soo!]
She's a fan of Kwang Soo.
[Kwang Soo related merchandise is
seen strewn all over the room.]
Hye Mi!
[Discovers the girl's name in
the signature from Kwang Soo!]
Your sister likes Kwang Soo?
Really?
Who do you like?
You.
You like me?
- Not this house, but the other one.
- I bet Ji Hyo's there right now!
- Thank you.
Is Ji Hyo already there?
Song Ji Hyo!
[Having discovered that
Ji Hyo has already been there.]
She's such a sly fox.
- Yes?
- This is the police.
- I think you've got the wrong house.
- Song Ji Hyo.
No, it's Gary, isn't it?
Gary?
A driver?
I didn't call for a driver.
I said, Gary, not Driver.
Seriously.
- Gary.
- Open the door, Gary.
I'm going to call the police
if you keep this up.
Don't open the door to them.
Why do you keep acting like that?
- You almost had me fooled.
- Gary.
- She's not here right now.
- What?
- She's not home right now.
- She's not?
[Kwang Soo walking into Hye Mi's room.]
[All over the room... is
proof of her love for the Giraffe.]
[Me... me?]
[This is what Hye Mi looks like!]
[His own signature is lovingly
framed in her room!]
What?
This place is full of giraffes!
She must be a fan of yours.
She even has your signature.
She has your signature in a frame.
Look at all the goosebumps on my arms.
I know her.
I know her name too.
There's her name.
[Her name can be seen written
inside the frame.]
Hye Mi.
Gary and Ji Hyo already saw
everything in this room.
Really?
[This is the middle school that she attends!]
[Name- Ahn Hye Mi.]
[School- Wabu Middle School.]
She has lessons from 6-9 p.m.
[Hye Mi's at school!]
[Hye Mi's school- Wabu Middle School.]
This is Wabu Middle School.
Hye Mi's notebook is hidden somewhere
in a classroom on the third floor.
The person to put Hye Mi's picture on the
last page of that notebook is the winner.
You must hurry.
Hello.
Is this the place?
Have you seen a notebook
around here?
[The original notebook is right here!]
[The rest of the members rush in
to find the original notebook.]
It has to be around here somewhere.
Is it okay if we look for it?
[Searching every other place except
for where the notebook is.]
[Gary walking in one step behind
everyone else.]
- Hello.
- Is this the only teacher's office?
- Really?
- Are there any other rooms?
[Discovers the real notebook!]
There are seven offices?
Where are you going, Gary?
[Did she not see it?]
I found it!
Is it okay if I open these drawers?
[Everyone else is searching
all the wrong places.]
I found it right away.
Hello.
Where are all the students right now?
[Gary's asking around to
locate Hye Mi.]
Sorry, what I did was wrong.
Please spank me with the whip.
[Must be reminded of his school days.]
Where's the notebook?
It's in here somewhere, right?
Guys, do you know who Hye Mi is?
Ahn Hye Mi?
Ahn Hye Mi.
She's a third year student.
- Do you know who Hye Mi is?
- Ahn Hye Mi?
- Yeah, Ahn Hye Mi.
- I think she's in classroom number five.
- Okay. Where's Hye Mi.
- Check room number five.
There's only one notebook?
There's only one?
What if someone's already found it?
No way.
Who's not in here?
Where did Gary go?
Did he find it already?
[Showing surprising deduction skills.]
[Find Hye Mi!]
Excuse me.
Where are all the students?
Have you seen Gary around?
[Gary is found!]
[Catch him!]
- You found it, didn't you?
- No, I haven't found it.
- I'm just trying to find Hye Mi first.
- Gary.
I know what Hye Mi looks like.
Gary.
- Did you find it?
- No, I didn't.
I'm trying to find Hye Mi first.
This isn't the real one.
- You found it, didn't you?
- No, I didn't.
- Gary.
- No.
[Gary ultimately gets caught in his lie.]
- Let's search for her together.
- I can see that you found it.
Everyone's looking for you.
You need to run away.
[The two iconic traitors surrounding Gary
with his authentic notebook.]
- Let us help you.
- Let me win something for once.
Okay, but you've won a lot
of individual missions in the past.
- Do you know what she looks like?
- Of course, I do.
- Good thing we found you first.
- Gary.
I think I really need to go find
Hye Mi first.
[Everyone is now convinced beyond doubt
that Gary has the notebook.]
Even if I do have the notebook,
it doesn't matter if I don't find Hye Mi.
- We have to find Hye Mi first.
- We have to find her and get her picture.
Finding Hye Mi should be our priority.
[Where could Hye Mi be?]
Hi, girls.
[Where could the third year students be?]
- Third year students?
- On the upper floor?
- Are you third year students?
- I could go with you.
- Okay, here?
- Come with us.
[Searching with the help of
other students.]
[Where are you, Hye Mi?]
[Could one of those girls be... Hye Mi?]
[Both Kwang Soo and the students
are in a state of shock.]
[He discovers Hye Mi whom
he's been so desperately searching for!]
[By following Hye Mi's book...]
[he finds Hye Mi.]
[Having ran all day in a race to find
the girl who showed them her love...]
[At last, Hye Mi is
right in front of his eyes.]
Hang on, Hye Mi.
Stay in hiding.
- Seriously.
What's the point of looking for her
when you don't even have the notebook?
We have to get the picture first before
we start worrying about the notebook.
Gary is looking for you,
so you have to stay in hiding.
Gary has your notebook.
Why are you going in there?
[Hyuk and Kkuk heading in Hye Mi's direction.]
Hye Mi!
You're making yourself too obvious!
I can totally see where you're hiding!
Where is she?
Is Hye Mi in there?
[Entering the classroom where
Hye Mi is hiding.]
Hi!
[Huh? They don't recognize Hye Mi
and just walks on by.]
Study hard, okay?
Wait!
[Wait...]
[Could that girl be...]
[the same Hye Mi we've been
searching for?]
Wait, I think...
I think...
[Darn!]
I think that's her.
[Hye Mi is unsure of what to do.]
[Kwang Soo feeling the pressure
asks for her picture right away.]
Wait.
Run, Hye Mi!
Don't take your picture with them!
Don't do it! Run!
Don't let them take your picture!
They're bad people!
Every man in this world is the same
except for me!
[Running away without knowing
the reason behind it.]
[Kwang Soo succeeds in
getting her picture.]
I just need to find Gary now.
I think that's her.
[Total chaos in Hye Mi's wake.]
There she is!
[Photo time with hard to find Hye Mi!]
Run!
- Run!
- Hye Mi!
Run away!
Hye Mi!
[Oh no!
Of all people, the Tiger?]
Why don't you want to take
a picture with me?
Okay, Hye Mi.
Just one picture.
- Hye Mi!
- Hye Mi, run!
[Trying to take a picture of himself with
her while on the chase.]
[Where's Hye Mi?]
[Gary with the real notebook...]
- We have to stop him.
- Hye Mi.
Hye Mi!
- I have one too.
- Let's take a picture together, Hye Mi.
[Taking the opportunity for a picture!]
Hye Mi!
[Gary is blocked out of the way.]
- Stop Gary.
- Hye Mi!
- Hi, Hye Mi.
- Stop him.
Look over here, Hye Mi.
[Gary succeeds in getting the picture!]
We have to stop Gary!
[Catch him!]
Why are you doing this to me!
My picture hasn't even developed yet!
What do I have to do in order
for Kwang Soo to win?
[In order for Kwang Soo to win...]
[He needs to get the authentic
notebook away from Gary.]
Lee Kwang Soo!
[The real notebook is now in
Ha Ha's hands!]
We can't lose him.
I'm going to drop it.
Don't come any closer.
[Right to Gary!]
[Darn!]
[As soon as Gary puts his picture of
Hye Mi on the very last page...]
[Big-nose's steal!]
[Big-nose Brother!]
I was about to stick it with my spit,
but I got the wrong page.
[Big-nose Brother is the winner!]
A round of applause!
Ji Suk Jin!
The sole winner!
- Ji Suk Jin!
- Sole winner for the first time ever!
[After 165 episodes...
A sole winner for the very first time!]
He was able to win today
all thanks to Hye Mi.
- I'm so sorry for what we did to your book.
- Sorry, but we kind of ruined your book.
- I'm sorry.
- You must be a huge fan of Kwang Soo's.
- Look at this here.
- I'm sorry, Hye Mi!
- Look at all these pictures of Kwang Soo.
- I was going to win for you today!
- I'm sorry!
- Why do you like Kwang Soo so much?
I saw him for the first time at
a movie opening.
When he walked onto the stage...
flowers were swirling around him.
[What? Swirling flowers?]
[The man who walked on stage amongst
a swirl of flowers?]
How could there have been swirling flowers
when Kwang Soo was walking?
[Thanks, Hye Mi.]
Anyway, all thanks to Hye Mi,
we were able to go around the city
and made a lot of nice new memories.
We even rock climbed the wall
all thanks to Hye Mi.
- Yes, we did.
- You're so knowledgeable about Namyang.
We did everything that Hye Mi
wanted us to do.
Yes, we did everything that
you took a picture of.
- That's so awesome.
- You know that picture of the library?
- Yes.
- We went there today.
We went there and had to
answer a lot of ridiculous questions.
This whole episode was possible
because of you, Hye Mi.
[Hye Mi was the creator
for this entire episode!]
- It was all thanks to you.
- That's so awesome!
This is what we went by.
- We all have a copy of this.
- We used your book to do our mission today.
- We went to all these places.
- Wow, that's awesome.
Thanks so much to Hye Mi for creating this
episode for Running Man.
This was Hye Mi's special episode.
And do you have anything to say to Kwang Soo?
[Anything she'd like to say to Kwang Soo?]
- Ask him for a hug.
- Why don't you shake his hand?
Yeah, give her a hug.
Okay.
[A hug to remember Kwang Soo by.]
Promise him that whenever you stop liking
him, that you'd still be cool with him.
That's the best thing you
can do for Hye Mi.
You're dead if you ever stop liking me!
Don't joke like that.
Let's take one last group shot
before we go.
Thanks, everyone!
[Thank you to Hye Mi's mother,
Hye Mi's sister, Hye Won for your cooperation
and to everyone else in the city for
all your help and participation.]
One, two, three!
Subtitles by DramaFever