[Brutal battle within the family.]
[The gold bars that they
worked so hard to earn.]
[But...]
[They were told that they would be given
the chance to earn more gold.]
[Mysterious kidnapping.]
[Where did all the gold that they worked
so hard to earn disappear off to?]
[An unidentified pirate ship above the sea.]
[As they stepped on the sea deck
the following morning...]
You already took away all
our gold yesterday.
[A suspicious band of people were
waiting for them on the deck...]
- Get up there.
- We have no money.
Can you let the people in the
top three rank go free?
[The identity of these people that have
taken Running Man members as hostages?]
[They are none other than...]
[Pirates of the Western Sea, Shinhwa.]
[No strangers to the variety world-
They make their return as pirates!]
- Hurry up and get up here!
- Are you seriously going to do this to us?
[Instead of a face-off with the pirates,
it feels more like a reunion of friends.]
Hello!
- Hello!
- We are the pirates!
No, you're not. You guys are Shinhwa.
What are you talking about?
We are... pirates!
[What a joke.]
Are you really going to do
this to me, Eric?
We are... pirates!
- What are you guys doing?
- Where's the other guy?
- Where's Dong Wan?
- Where did Dong Wan go?
- We dumped him in the ocean.
- How can you be pirates without Dong Wan?
- Why did you take our gold?
- Why would you guys take our gold?
- Where is it?
- We have it.
- We have the gold.
- We have it right here.
- We worked hard to get the gold.
- You want me to open it for you?
- Why can't you open it?
- Can you open it for me?
- Say, 'Can you open it for me, please'.
- What kind of a pirate are you?
- Let's open it on the count of three.
- One, two, three.
[All the gold bars that were
taken away from them...]
[What?]
[All of the gold bars transformed
into scrap metal?]
[All of those gold bars...]
[have been cursed out here
in the Western Sea...]
[and transformed into scrap metal.]
- What is this?
- What happened?
There was gold in there just
a little while ago.
- What happened?
- Someone took our gold.
There's a letter in here.
Can you read it for us?
[Instead of taking the lead,
the pirates are being led.]
We have to take the lead here.
If anything,
they're taking the lead here.
The curse of the tides.
- The tides again?
- Your treasure...
Your treasure has been cursed.
You will be given hints to lift the curse,
and to regain your treasure.
Winning team will be given a useful hint,
and the losing team an ambiguous one.
The first team to gather all the hints to
lift the curse will get to keep the treasure.
No!
Just give it a rest.
- Stop with that 'no'.
- What are you going to do about it then?
I'm tired of hearing you say that.
But there are only five of them on
Shinhwa's team, so what are we going to do?
- I know.
- I think five of them is more than enough.
- Why are you saying that?
- Actually, that's true.
I normally wouldn't say this,
but these guys...
- These guys are pretty competitive.
- We really like competition.
Seriously.
[Pirate Shinhwa's invasion on Running Man.]
They're practically flying around here.
[Just like the olden days,
their skills are still as sharp as ever.]
[Shinhwa- We have returned!]
But the problem is...
these guys are way too good.
- I know.
- But we're older too now.
[Even though they're the legendary Shinhwa,
with the passing of years...]
[The average age for
Shinhwa members are 34.3 years old.]
- Seriously?
- Yes.
When did you guys get so old?
- But you're older than us.
- We're still not as old as you are.
How old do you think we are?
Our average age is way too high.
You have no idea how strong
they are, do you?
- These guys used to be like machines.
- Machines?
[Their younger days when their skills were
comparable to that of a machine.]
Whenever these guys would play a game
it would be a given to eliminate all
the members of the opposing teams
and they would just start to
compete amongst themselves.
But Andy looks like
I may be able to handle him.
[Unfounded sense of confidence
towards Andy.]
- I think I can handle Andy.
- Don't anger Andy, Suk Jin.
- Seriously?
- You really have no idea.
If anything else,
Eric is our weakest player.
[Eric is the designated
weak player of Shinhwa?]
I'm feeling really seasick right now.
What is it, Kwang Soo?
Are you looking at Eric as your rival?
I think I can take him on.
There it is.
[A mysterious island of sand
in the middle of the ocean.]
[Island of sand that only appears
when the tide is low.]
This place is like a piece of art.
- I can't believe a place like this exists.
- This is normally under water, right?
[Team Shinhwa and Team Running Man
anchor on the island of sand.]
[The island stretches out for 5km
during the lowest tide.]
This island is an infamous landmark in
the Western Sea called, The Puldeung Island.
I'm really shocked to know
that a place like this even exists.
[The mystical island showing off
it's wondrous beauty.]
- It's amazing that a place like this exists.
- Ganjo.
- What is 'Ganjo'?
- A place that sinks underwater at times.
That's correct.
[He almost had it right.]
Gary is very smart.
As you can see,
there are little flags in front of you.
Are you all familiar with the movie,
'Far and Away'
where they claimed their land
by staking the ground with their flag?
Yes, we know that movie.
[The competition that is
about to take place...]
[is just like what took place in the movie,
'Far and Away'...]
[Claim your own land by staking
your flag into the ground.]
Choose the colored flag of your liking
and go out as far away as you can
on the stretch of this island
and stake your flag into the ground.
That is the concept of this game.
As you can see, there are ten flags.
That means that two of you
will be without flags.
These guys here are like champions
when it comes to stuff like this.
Do you know how hard
this is going to be for us?
Until you hear the sound of the whistle,
you can steal the flag from one another.
There's no way we'll be
able to take it from them.
- We won't be able to take it from them.
- Ah, we can steal their flags?
[Predicting a fierce battle
right from the start...]
- How are we even going to do this?
- How are we to compete with these athletes?
I don't think Eric would be much of a problem.
I think we'd be able to take him on.
- We have to do our best.
- We have no other choice.
- Eric is their weakness.
- Do you run or anything?
- I have bad knees.
- Is that right?
Sorry for clapping at that.
[Will it be the veteran Running Man Team...]
[Or will it be the infamous Shinhwa Team?]
This is going to be difficult.
[Ready!]
[Go!]
[Running towards the flags.]
[Blank Ji shoved aside by the rough men
and falls to the ground.]
Where do we go?
Let's go to the right.
[Giraffe took two flags as predicted,
and passes one off to Blank Ji.]
Go that way!
[Run as far as possible!]
Let's go off to the other side.
[Stake your flags into where
you're standing right now!]
Good job.
What the heck?
[What?
Jun Jin doesn't have a flag?]
- You don't have a flag?
- You didn't get a flag?
Jin didn't get a flag.
How is it that Jin...
Jin didn't get a flag?
What the heck?
[Even Blank Ji has a flag...]
Jun Jin... how could you not
have gotten a flag?
- Who's the other person?
- I think it's Jun Jin and Suk Jin.
[Jun Jin, Mr. Capable of Team Shinhwa
fails to procure a flag.]
[And on Team Running Man,
it is of course, Big-nose Brother...]
- My plan was to just get it from someone.
- Really? Our plan was to avoid you.
- You got the furthest distance.
- We beat Shinhwa!
- Hey, we won.
- We practically won this thing.
We won the first game.
Everyone, you will now be given
your real rules of the game.
- What is it?
- There are more rules?
- There's more stuff?
- As you can see, there is a boat out front.
Yes.
From that boat, a pirate captain will choose
one of the flags through a random drawing.
The person who crosses the finish line...
with the same colored flag that
the pirate chooses
in their hand will be
the ultimate winner of this game.
- So going out far wasn't a good thing.
- The person with the same colored flag...
must cross the finish line
with the flag in hand.
And those without that colored flag must
take that colored flag away from the person.
We have to protect our own members,
and take the flag away from our opposing team.
So this is going to be played
rugby style.
It's not good to go too far out.
Ready.
Take a good look.
Look to see what color the flag is.
[What colored flag will the pirate captain
lift up from the boat?]
[A blue flag!]
Who has the blue flag?
- Blue!
- Who? Who is it?
- Blue! Blue flag!
- Who? Who has it?
Run, Jae Suk!
[Right in front of Jae Suk!]
Blue!
The color is blue!
[Running towards the finish line
with the blue flag in hand.]
His shoe fell off!
[But that doesn't stop his chase!]
[Catch!]
[Nice catch!]
Get Kwang Soo!
Suk Jin!
[A dazzling play of passing game.]
Gary.
- No!
- Get it, Jae Suk.
[A tug-of-war over the flag.]
[Yoo Hyuk not letting go of the flag.]
Tickle him.
[Proposing that they play jump ball as in
a basketball game to determine who gets it.]
[Giant Giraffe is chosen to be the person
to toss up the flag.]
- Toss it towards the middle?
- Right there.
Ready?
[Shinhwa having exhausted themselves out
from the fierce physical competition.]
This is exhausting.
[It's between Yoo Hyuk and Min Woo.]
[Huh?]
[Figures...]
[Kwang Soo makes it!]
I can't believe he did that.
How could he do something like that?
[Experiencing firsthand what it is like
to be betrayed by the Giraffe.]
- We can't win unless we do that.
- No, we can't.
[His first taste of betrayal.]
We all knew that Kwang Soo would
run off with that flag.
Yeah, we all knew.
But you guys didn't know, did you?
That's why we asked him
to be the tosser.
- I can't believe these guys.
- Lee Kwang Soo passed the first round.
- Lee Kwang Soo may now step aside.
- Is he not participating anymore?
He's not participating anymore?
The first team to win
three rounds of the game wins.
Which means, Running Man needs to win
two more rounds of the game.
And the pirate team needs to win
three more rounds of the game.
These guys really have aged.
- Why would you trust Kwang Soo?
- Look at how we knew what to anticipate.
- We didn't know.
- They're so easy to scheme.
You can't trust Kwang Soo.
The reason why these guys are like this is
because no one betrayed anyone in the past.
- I didn't even fathom that happening.
- Betrayal didn't used to exist in games.
[The 'betrayal-nista',
leading a new trend in variety games.]
[Steal the flag- Round Two.]
[What color will it be this time?]
[A white flag!]
It's mine!
[Find the white flag that Blank Ji
staked into the ground!]
[Kkuk's dead run.]
Finish it, Jong Kook.
[Min Woo's quick body check.]
[Quick footed Min Woo gets the flag.]
[Heading towards the finish line.]
[Team Running Man's
concentrated defense line.]
[Eric is much quicker with
his actions than expected.]
[Team Shinhwa shows their
dazzling pass play.]
[Continuing their momentum with their
surprising work of relay teamwork.]
[Right in front of the finish line!]
[Eric makes a direct pass over to Jun Jin.]
[A fantastic pass.]
[Jun Jin makes the goal!]
These guys are way too good.
He's like a real football player.
He's literally flying around here.
We can't compete against these guys.
- Wow.
- You need to play better defense!
Why did you let Min Woo beat you?
- I got tired out.
- You lost to Min Woo.
- Listen to me.
- What are you going to say now?
Even though they played good teamwork,
they had themselves well positioned.
- They had themselves really well positioned.
- You should've grabbed the flag.
You should've took the flag
from the beginning.
- I can't believe you lost to him.
- What were you thinking?
[Team Shinhwa laughing over
their bickering.]
- The old feeling is starting to come back.
- I know.
You guys are finally starting to laugh.
Hye Sung is starting to laugh now.
[Doing the crab dance now that they're
starting to get the old feelings back?]
[Dancing the dance for the first time
in ten years?]
We have to get serious now.
- We have to get serious.
- We have to get this done.
Now that Shinhwa got their laughter back,
we've lost our ability to laugh.
- We have to take the flag.
- Ready!
[Now that Shinhwa's gotten their groove,
will they be able to win again?]
[Yellow!]
[Run!]
[Here's the yellow flag.]
It's over to the right.
[Hye Sung vs. Ha Ha.]
Ha Ha is so fast!
We have to defend him.
Someone needs to go.
[Ro-Ro gets the flag in his possession.]
Jong Kook.
[Escaped Hye Sung's attack
with a diversion.]
Nice move!
- Jong Kook!
- Hey!
[Oh no!
Jong Kook loses the flag to Min Woo.]
We have to stop him no matter what.
[A face off with quick footed Min Woo.]
To the front!
[A direct pass to Eric!]
[A scene right out of a martial arts movie.]
[Straight to the finish line!]
[The final line of defense
is Blank Ji by herself.]
[Big-nosed Brother's desperate interception.]
[Passing it off to another member.]
[Gary's ferocious tackle.]
[The finish line is right
in front of his nose!]
You did good.
Toss it up in the air.
Air toss?
[Suggests another round of air toss.]
- Let go.
- We can't trust them.
[Will it be a fair play this time?]
[Walking side by side.]
- I'll toss it since I'm out of the game now.
- No, we can't trust him.
[Refusing traitorous Giraffe's offer.]
Why don't you guys trust me?
I'm not going to do that anymore.
[Betrayal-nista Giraffe's excuses
not working on anyone.]
How about we have one of
the staff members toss it?
[Finally settling on Andy to throw the toss.]
How about this?
[Stakes the flag into the ground.]
[The moment the whistle sounds,
everyone scrambles to grab the flag.]
Let's have everyone turn around
with their backs to the flag.
I haven't seen a competition
like this in a very long time.
[Gary vs. Hye Sung.]
You may start as soon as
I blow the whistle.
[Grab the flag at the sound of the whistle!]
I can't reach.
[All the members to stay out of the way,
and stay on guard.]
- We have to stay on guard.
- I feel like we're playing football.
Let's go and win this thing.
[Personally guarding Min Woo.]
[Ready]
[The team that grabs the flag...]
[is the most likeliest to win the game.]
[Gary gets the flag!]
[He passes it off to Ji Hyo!]
[Blank Ji Hyo makes the touch down!]
He didn't have his hand behind his back.
[Team Shinhwa with their endless
litany of complaints.]
- He's mad he didn't win.
- He didn't have his hand behind his back.
Was I supposed to have
my hands behind my back?
I didn't know that.
- You guys are just too much.
- I don't think he knew he had to do that.
[Team Running Man - 2
Team Shinhwa- 1.]
[A fierce mental competition on the island.]
[Orange!]
- Off to the right over there!
- Is that it?
[Yoo-ruce Willis makes a dash for it.]
We have to block him.
Go run over there.
Over here!
There you go!
[A nice back pass?]
[A missed pass turns the whole game around.]
Grab him!
Get him!
You have to get him!
[Kkuk shoves him over to the finish line.]
[Min Woo passes.]
With Kim Jong Kook's assist...
Shinhwa wins!
[Back to an even score!
One last final round.]
You have to get yourselves together.
Let's have everyone come back in the game.
[Everyone come back in the game
for the final round?]
- That's a great idea.
- Why, are you afraid you'll lose?
- They're afraid that they'll lose.
- I doubt it.
[Then without the exception of Blank Ji,
Team Running Man- 6 vs. Team Shinhwa- 5.]
I haven't smelled the sweet smell of
manly sweat in a long time.
With Shinhwa here, the beast
inside of me is starting to wake up.
[The beastly instinct slowly
starting to make a comeback.]
[The fierce glint in their eyes are back.]
[Who is this wild beast?]
Since this is the final round,
we'll do one last cheer before we play.
Our opponents have finally noticed
that we've been going easy on them.
Let's not go easy on them anymore.
- Let's show them what we're made of.
- Okay, let's do this.
One, two, three.
Running Man!
[We're not going to go easy on you anymore!]
One, two, three.
Shinhwa!
[Shall we start playing for real?]
- I will shoot to start.
- Okay.
- Don't shoot us.
- You watch yourself, Jae Suk.
- I wouldn't put it past you.
Just shoot it.
Okay, ready!
One, two, three!
[Purple!]
[Find the purple flag!]
You have to run.
Is that it?
No, that's not it!
- Is that it?
- That's it.
[The purple flag way out in the distance.]
[Quick footed Min Woo getting
possession of the flag once again.]
Be careful.
[A strong break to the front of the line
with his quick speed.]
[Another brilliant show of teamwork.]
Throw it!
[Gary steals the flag!]
[A long pass into the air.]
[Hye Sung catches the pass!]
[And throws it directly over to Eric.]
[They make their way close to the
finish line within a blink of an eye.]
[Yoo Hyuk's desperate tackle.]
[Kkuk intercepts the pass.]
[Front of the finish line is
very densely populated.]
[Big-nosed Brother feebly
drops it to the ground.]
[Throws him down to the ground.]
[The flag is passed off to Haroro.]
[Giraffe misses the important pass.]
[Flag is back in Team Shinhwa's possession.]
Be careful and toss it.
[A straight breakthrough.]
[The finish line is right
in front of their nose!]
[What?]
[Goal]
[Wow...
to make it pass amidst all that chaos?]
Okay, the practice game is now over.
[Team Shinhwa wins.]
[Like a wild buffalo
breaking through the herd.]
Shinhwa's finally back.
We will now give a hint to Shinhwa
for having won this game.
You have to look only amongst
yourselves.
And Team Running Man will be given
an ambiguous hint.
You have to look secretly
amongst yourselves as well.
[Steal the shoe from the undead.]
The undead?
[Steal the shoe from the undead?]
[Steal the ___ from the undead.]
We'll never be able to
figure it out from that.
- Let's just go.
- You guys all played great.
[Happy with having played their best.]
No way!
[Curse or a blessing?
The existence of the undead...]
[Who is the undead?]
[The pirate restaurant.]
- I assume the both teams are very hungry?
- Yes, we are.
Yes, we're very hungry.
We will now start your meal.
[What price will the meal at the
Pirate Restaurant be?]
Do you see the menus that
are behind you?
- Can we order whatever we want?
- Let's order.
- Wow, I don't know what I want.
- Who stuck all those menu items up there?
The team that won the previous game may
first order what they'd like off the menu.
[Team Shinhwa gets to order first
for having won the previous game.]
We're going to have the spicy chicken soup.
[Team Shinhwa chooses a
spicy bowl of chicken soup.]
In order to be able to eat your meal...
you have to play a game and win.
[It's the food competition between
The Pirates and Running Man.]
- You never just let us eat.
- Can't you just let us eat?
- Can't we just eat our meal in peace?
- Why won't you just let us eat?
[Full of complaints.]
- All I got today was a mouthful of sand.
- Shouldn't you feed us at least one meal?
What is this?
Your spicy chicken menu game is...
Toe Competition.
- What?
- What is he talking about?
Each team has to pick one representative
to play the game
and it is essentially a form of
the thumb war, but played with your big toe.
Pick one member from your team whom
you think would be best for this game.
But, once a member plays a game, that person
is excluded from all the other games.
When it comes to toes,
isn't Kwang Soo the best?
You have to think very carefully about this.
If you play this game, then you
can't participate in the other games.
[But there are other games
to consider too...]
- We choose Kwang Soo.
- Kwang Soo!
[Shinhwa's representative is, Jun Jin.]
Jun Jin is very strong.
You have to watch yourself.
[Even his foot is extremely large...]
It's gross how big his foot is.
How can you say that my foot is gross?
- My shoe size is 290.
- Wow, that's gross.
Please intertwine your toes
with one another.
You know what to do, right, Kwang Soo?
You know what to do with your toes.
Just to let you know, Kwang Soo...
Jun Jin doesn't wash his feet very often.
Kwang Soo never washes his feet.
[A mental battle between them
over cleanliness and hygiene?]
- I'm starting to feel the sensation.
- Are you feeling the sensation?
I've never seen two men sitting around
with their toes intertwined like that before.
[Even though they're seeing it,
it's still a strange sight to behold.]
I feel really shy right now.
- What kind of a game is this?
- What are you making us do right now?
[Maybe a commemorative picture
of this moment?]
[This is probably the very first picture
ever taken of such a scene.]
Kwang Soo.
You have to hook line him first, okay?
I've never done this before,
so I'm not sure if I'm doing this right.
Do you think Jin's done this before?
Where would he ever have played this?
This is my first time too.
- You think it's first time just for you?
- I was just making a comment.
Can't you just cheer me on
instead of berating me?
So if Kwang Soo wins this round,
does it mean that we get the chicken soup?
- Yes, that's correct.
- Really?
- With just this one round?
- That's it.
[This one round will determine
who gets to eat the chicken!]
- Really?
- That's right.
Fighting!
[The spicy chicken soup making
everyone desperately cheer them on.]
Jun Jin!
I need you to cheer for me too.
Just hurry up and do it!
Kwang Soo!
[A jeer instead of a cheer?]
- Kwang Soo, you know what to do, right?
- Kwang Soo, do a good job.
Ready.
[The world's first ever toe competition.]
Wait, the other team is much closer.
['Mr. Kim-Just leave it'
butting in once again.]
- What are you doing?
- No, listen.
But look at how the starting line
on this thing isn't matching up with this.
- Yeah, you have to line it up like this.
- Kim Jong Kook!
- No, we have to line it up together.
- In a straight line.
- The line is right here.
- Their toes are turning blue! Just hurry.
You have to lean your body over this way
so that you have more strength in your toes.
But then I'll have my back towards
the camera.
- Who cares? Just around.
- It doesn't matter if you're not on camera.
- Just turn around.
- Why don't I turn this way then?
Can you still see me on camera?
There's a camera over there too.
[We're shooting from every angle.]
You have to find the center balance.
Jin has to come forward a bit more.
Move forward a little,
and you move back a bit more.
- Why do you want him to go backwards?
- Because your feet aren't centered.
[A strange claim of their feet
not being balanced.]
You have to come forward a bit more.
Come forward, and you go backward.
See? Your feet aren't balanced.
Can you get us a better referee?
Do you think I like sitting here with
your toes in my hands right now?
I don't want to be touching your toes!
I don't know what's going on here.
He doesn't like touching people's toes.
I've seen Jin a countless times before,
but this is my first time seeing his toes.
[Even though he's known him for a long time,
he's never seen his toes before.]
Ready.
Set, go!
You can do this.
[To all our children viewers-
Please don't follow in their footsteps.]
A little bit more!
[Invalid because the wall was knocked
down by dragging over his foot.]
[Pain in their toes?]
I can't do this anymore!
I really can't do this anymore!
[Sort of agony that he's never felt
in his life before..]
The person who's toes breaks off first
loses the game.
I'll put my second toe
on the line on this game!
How about we switch our feet?
[Agrees to switch feet.]
Don't allow Jong kook to wear
stuff like that anymore.
['Mr. Kim-leave it' in a white one piece.]
Why?
It's nice and cool.
Even Ji Hyo is all covered up here,
so why are you dressed like that?
- One piece?
- He's wearing a one piece right now.
[A re-match with their left feet.]
[A fierce competition with their left feet!]
[Jun Jin with his teeth gritted.]
[Giraffe enduring the pain
with his monstrous strength.]
[Giraffe's left foot is not easy to defeat.]
Spicy chicken soup!
[The spicy chicken soup bringing out
the monstrous strength in him.]
[The game may be coming to a close...]
[Ah, the foot slips again...]
I can't do it! I lose.
You win!
[Throwing in the towel?]
[Ouch...]
Did I win?
[Cooley gives up on the game.]
You pulled your foot back
from the pain, right?
I know you pulled
your foot back from the pain.
[Toe wrestle- Team Running Man wins!]
[Wins the spicy chicken soup.]
I think he pulled his foot back
because of the pain.
- He pulled his foot back from the pain.
- I've never felt that kind of pain before.
Team Running Man has gained
the spicy chicken soup on their lunch menu.
Spicy chicken soup!
I really wanted to have that for lunch.
What should we choose?
[It's Team Running Man's turn
to choose the menu.]
[Their menu of choosing is, rockfish sushi.]
The next game you'll be playing is,
'Pirate Disco King'.
How do we play?
All the team members will dance their
heart out with a pair of headphones on.
But, with the exception of one person,
no music will play on the headphones.
So to win the game, you have to find the
one person who actually is dancing to music.
[Find the one person who's actually
dancing along to the beat of music.]
We're good at things like this.
[Having a meeting first to determine
who will actually be listening to music.]
Only one person out of the group is actually
hearing music through their headphones.
The music is currently playing
through the headphones right now.
[Given time is one minute.
Find the music listener within that time.]
[Go!]
Andy.
[Too busy dancing to pay attention
to anything that they're saying.]
Yeah!
[Just which one of them is listening to
actual music being played? Can you guess?]
It's not Min Woo.
- I have no idea.
- I think it's Andy.
I want to say it's Andy.
No, Andy's always been really weird.
[Did he hear that comment?]
- It's not Andy.
- Hey, Andy.
- Can you hear us?
- He can hear us.
[Then could it be poker faced Jun Jin?]
- Min Woo's laughing too.
- He's laughing at our comment on Andy.
[Min Woo suddenly bursting out
in bouts of laughter.]
No, no.
No, it's not him.
- No, it's not him.
- Ten seconds left.
[Ten seconds left on the clock.]
Could it be Hye Sung?
- But the way that they're dancing...
- I don't think it's him.
I'm positive that it's not Andy or Hye Sung.
[Time over!]
- I have no idea.
- I think it's Jun Jin.
I really don't know.
[So confusing...]
And there's Eric to consider too.
I saw Min Woo laughing.
Andy heard everything that we've said.
You'll make your selection after watching
each of them dance separately.
- Am I first?
- Everyone stay still while Andy dances.
Ready, set, go.
- He really is...
- Look at Andy.
Andy's laughing already because
he knows we're going to say something.
[Keeping his eyes tightly shut.]
No, it's not Andy.
- It's not Andy.
- Should I go next?
- Yes.
[Next up is, Hye Sung.]
You have to turn the music on first.
Turn on the music.
[Huh?]
- It's not Hye Sung.
- Make sure to turn your music on.
You can stop.
You can stop pretending now.
He's always liked dancing to no music.
It's not Hye Sung.
Okay, it's Jun Jin's turn.
[Next up, Jun Jin.]
Jin's is really sly.
He's sly so you have to be cautious.
- I never know with Jun Jin.
- Is it you, Jun Jin?
[Jun Jin grooving on his own.]
Min Woo.
Let's see Min Woo next.
I already did it.
What?
You already did it?
[Too loud of a voice...]
If you press play,
you can hear the music playing.
If he was listening to music,
he would've spoken louder.
[Anyways, it's now time to dance.]
[Is it the dance to one of Shinhwa's songs?]
- Finally, Eric.
- Eric.
[Acting very unnatural for
some reason...]
No, it's okay.
We've made our decision.
[Mr. Cool taking off his headphones
in one smooth move.]
That's so funny.
Eric is so funny.
Eric is funny.
I never knew how funny Eric was.
- He's a very funny man.
- He's quite entertaining.
Eric is funny.
- Don't you think it's Jun Jin?
- I think it's Jin.
[Is it Jun Jin?
Or is it Min Woo?]
I think it's Jin.
I don't think it's Min Woo.
Five, four, three, two, one.
Jun Jin.
[Powerful dance moves.]
[Skilled dance moves
moving along to the beat.]
[Was Jun Jin listening to actual music?]
[Time to check for themselves.]
I don't think it's him.
Do I just press play?
It's playing.
It's playing, right?
- Do you hear music?
- Is music playing?
That's not it.
- It's not Jun Jin.
- Then who was it?
- It's not Jin.
- Was it Andy?
- Who was it?
- Then I bet it was Min Woo.
[Then could it be Min Woo?]
I bet it's Min Woo.
[Min Woo, the dancing machine.]
[Is dancing to no music
not a big deal for him?]
Set, go.
It's Min Woo.
[Min Woo was the one!]
[Dancing machine with acting skills to boot.]
[Team Shinhwa wins the rockfish sushi.]
It's Team Shinhwa's turn
to choose an item off the menu.
- Can we choose the sushi again?
- Yes, you may.
Rockfish sushi.
[Chooses to add an additional order
of rockfish sushi to their menu.]
Your next game is called,
'Pirates of the sails'.
One member of each team will come up front
and sit with their knees off the ground
and the person to scoot themselves on their
bottom to make a round wins the game.
- Like this?
- I think you should do it.
- I don't know if I can do this.
- You mean, scoot along like this?
Who wants to do this game?
[Anyone can play this game.]
- I think Jong Kook will be good for this.
- Okay, I'll do it.
Jong Kook's going to do this round?
Is some bodily contact allowed?
Of course. That's the only
way to play this sort of game.
Then I really want to do this game.
I think Hye Sung would be really quick
in a game like this one.
[Hye Sung may be the best candidate
from Team Shinhwa?]
- Come on.
- This won't be tough.
- We have to make this fun.
- How rough do you think I'm going to get?
You're asking me to do it because
you're pretty sure I'd lose, right?
If that was the case,
we'd be asking Eric to do it.
[Ask Eric to play if they want a sure win?]
Eric!
You now have to make your decision.
- Team Running Man?
- Kim Jong Kook.
Team Shinhwa?
[Team Shinhwa chooses
quick-footed Min Woo.]
Please come up to the front.
- Are you both ready?
- Yes.
Do we go down the room,
and turn around this way?
Or should we make a wide inward turn?
- Make the inward turn.
- Okay, we'll do that.
If we turn like that,
he'll be going around in the inner course.
['Mr. Kim-Leave it' and his attention
for even playing ground.]
We have to turn that way so that
we both have the same length of distance.
He never used to talk this much
back in the day when he first started.
[Having transformed into a
chatterbox since his earlier days?]
Suk Jin.
Can you sing us a song in cheer?
I know you're good at coming up
with things like that.
It doesn't even take him five seconds
to think up a song.
- Say something for us.
- One, two, three, four.
I love the thick arms on Jong Kook.
Thick arms, fighting!
[Comes up with the
'Thick arm song' out of nowhere.]
That was a good song.
The problem is that he himself is
embarrassed of what he just sang.
What's there to be embarrassed about?
Ready, set, go!
[Quick footed Min Woo vs.
Muscle Boy, Kkuk.]
Look at the expression on his face.
[Neck and neck speed!]
[Colliding into each other
at the halfway mark.]
Just turn around and avoid him.
[Go away!]
[The incident at the halfway mark
made a difference in the competition.]
[Goal!]
I love Jong Kook's thick arms.
[Team Running Man's Muscle Boy wins!]
Did you see how Jong Kook scooted
himself up there?
I really couldn't stand the sight of him.
Team Running Man just won themselves
an order of rockfish sushi.
[Team Running Man wins the rockfish sushi.]
[The final play-off game.]
- The thick noodle soup?
- Thick clamshell noodle soup.
[Their final menu item selection is,
clamshell thick noodle soup.]
The game you'll be playing for
clamshell thick noodle soup is...
the hand slap game.
[The final game- Hand slap game.]
This?
The team who gets in the most
number of slaps wins the game.
[The team that gets in the most number
of slaps wins the game.]
We want to be the one to
avoid the slaps first.
Why?
We just won the last game.
['Mr. Kim-Leave it' who just can't
let anything go easily.]
- What? I was making a comment.
- Let's decide with Rock, paper, scissors.
He's gotten so weird since
the last time we saw him.
I'll go first.
I'll go first with this.
[Team Shinhwa- Andy.]
Let's eat the clamshell thick noodle soup.
- Don't you have to have your hand out?
- I will once we start the game.
Okay, I'll say it.
Set, go.
It's really going to hurt if you get slapped.
[What they need is the right timing.]
He's not putting
his hands together close enough.
I am putting my hands together.
Suk Jin is going to go first.
[Huh?]
What are you doing?
[Getting annoyed with how long
Andy is taking.]
You're getting annoyed, aren't you?
[This is Team Shinhwa's plan-
To annoy to the point of exhaustion.]
Yes, until you're exhausted.
Suk Jin's speed will start to
slow down as the game drags on.
I can do this all night.
[A strategic win- Score one for Andy.]
One point for Andy.
[Big-nosed Brother
flabbergasted at his loss.]
[Yoo Hyuk taking it upon himself
to step into the game.]
- Set, go.
- You have to stay on your toes.
Set, go.
[Eyes wide open.]
Aren't I fast?
I can go even faster.
[Even with his fast hand movements,
his mouth doesn't know to slow down.]
You're losing your strength.
Take a quick break.
What are you doing?
[Casually relaxed.]
How long do I have to do this for?
That's their strategy.
What the heck?
[Loses to Andy again...]
What did I tell you?
[Andy- Two wins in a row.]
You're much worse than Kwang Soo
when it comes to taking cheap shots.
You have no right
to say anything to me anymore!
That's the first time I've done
something like that.
It's because I'm on the show.
I'm not normally like that.
Okay, Jong Kook.
[Muscle Boy, Kkuk's turn.]
[Playing mental games by showing off
how fast his hand moves are.]
No, I don't have to have my hands together
since we haven't started the game yet.
He even knows how to play
gonggi with those thick arms of his.
[King of sneak attack, Andy...
Will he be able to beat Kkuk as well?]
[Huh?]
[Unbelievable!]
What is he doing?
[Amazing speed.]
[Come on!]
[Hit me if you can!]
Come on!
Come on, and hit me.
My stomach hurts.
All this laughing is making my stomach hurt.
[Muscle Boy's slicing moves are
catching in popularity.]
He looks like the village idiot.
Hurry up and come on.
[Mr. One-piece lasting longer
than anyone else.]
Set, go.
[Come on!]
I love the expression on his face.
- One-piece!
- Okay, come on.
[He knows no exhaustion.]
Hey!
[Succeeds in his plan to annoy Jong Kook.]
Hey, are you going to do it or not?
[One-piece Muscle Boy on fire.]
- How is it that you're lasting that long?
- Your arms are all pumped up right now.
My arms are about to explode.
Look at how sweaty I am right now.
- You have one minute on the clock.
- One minute?
You're doing good, Jong Kook.
Set, go.
[Can't even see his hands...]
[Kkuk gritting down on his teeth.]
One minute.
You have 40 seconds to go.
[Fast hand movement to ensure
that he doesn't get slapped.]
[Starting to slow down...]
[Crazy pumping movements.]
What in the world are you doing right now?
- You didn't hit me!
- Yes, I did!
He didn't hit me!
Why don't you check on camera.
I swear that you didn't hit me.
[Sweat soaked.]
- You move so fast.
- That wasn't easy.
[Unable to make an accurate call.
Still 33 seconds left on the clock.]
[The longest minute in history.]
- Set, go.
- 33 seconds.
[Obsessive dusting of the hands.]
[Hand dusting movements
starting to slow down.]
15 seconds.
You've only got 15 seconds.
[Andy eyeing for his moment.]
Five, four, three, two...
[Pumping Kkuk wins!]
But it still feels like we've won.
That was a really nice effort.
- I can't even lift up my arms right now.
- You should make a fitness video.
This is a very good workout, everyone.
I'm serious. Do it as
fast as you can for a full minute.
[One minute on the clock-
Kkuk's hand dusting exercise.]
Director, can you produce a music video
for Jong Kook with his hand exercise?
- What did you say?
- This move... let's see it how it plays out.
Jong Kook's... music video!
[Jong Kook's music video- Start.]
[I love Jong Kook's thick arms- Music video.
Song about his never tiring muscles.]
- Yes!
- At last!
[Time to switch it up-
Team Running Man's turn to attack.]
One minute on the clock?
- What am I doing?
- You're doing the slapping.
[Attacker this time is,
Mr. Random Capable, Gary.]
- We need our noodle soup.
- I know.
- We need the noodle soup.
- I really want to eat it.
[Andy, now on the defense.]
Just leave him alone.
Just leave him.
Let him tire himself out.
[Slowly starting to show his exhaustion.]
It's okay.
Just let him go.
[Total concentration.]
How much time is left on the clock?
He's really annoying me.
[Whether he's on the offense or defense,
Andy is the King of annoyance.]
There's 20 second left on the clock.
[Humiliated-
Hand on fire, and face on fire.]
I think I dragged it out for too long.
It's Eric.
[Team Shinhwa's next player is,
their black hole, Eric.]
I can't believe how different they look from
one another when they're of the same origin.
[Weird looking man vs. Beautiful looking man.]
Fighting!
[Gary on the attack!]
[Huh?]
[Over before the first second is even up.]
Gary's too quick.
[As expected,
he coolly accepts the outcome.]
When I saw the glint in Eric's eyes,
I thought he was going to be really good.
But what's the deal, Eric?
But I really love how quick and cool
he is about accepting the outcome.
[The final round.]
[If Jun Jin avoids being slapped,
then it's Team Shinhwa's win.]
Let's eat the clamshell noodle soup.
- I'm going to do this.
- We can't lose to him.
He's reminding me of Jong Kook
right now.
[Unlike any other players thus far,
his movements are adding more nervousness.]
I can't believe Jong Kook
did that for five minutes.
[It's understandable why his arms are so big.]
[Ten seconds left on the clock!]
[Jun Jin on his own unusual rhythm.]
[Five seconds left on the clock!]
[The winner will be determined
within the next five seconds!]
[Who will be the victor of this game?]
[Gary fails at his attack!]
[Team Shinhwa wins the
Pirate Restaurant mission!]
[Shinhwa's still got it.]
What is it?
Team Shinhwa will win
the clamshell noodle soup.
Thank you for this wonderful meal.
[Spicy chicken soup to start off the meal.]
There's the clamshell noodle soup.
[Here's the clamshell noodle soup.]
This broth is amazing.
I really want some.
The spicy chicken is amazing.
I think this spicy chicken is the best.
Why is everything going over
to that other table?
It's the blue crab soup.
[Even the blue crab soup!]
- We'll take our hint now.
- We're getting the bad hint again?
[Team Shinhwa earns another solid hint.]
[Team Running Man wins themselves
another ambiguous hint.]
[Yellow parasol.]
[The undead?
A yellow parasol?]
['At the top of the roof _______.'
This is a hint?]
This hint is way too hard.
[Must find 'that place' on the rooftop.]
[The only solution to lifting the
secret of the curse is at 'that place'.]
[A quite beach- Shinhwa vs. Running Man.
What's the next game that awaits them?]
Okay, everyone.
Your next mission...
is the battle of strength.
[The battle of strength!]
This is a classic water game.
You'll be playing,
the Water Shoving Game.
[A classic water game-
Water Shoving Game.]
- Against Jong Kook?
- You guys are all strong and in good shape.
I think it's been about seven to eight years
since the last time we did this.
- Then give us one extra player.
- No, it's not going to be that bad.
[Five people vs. Seven people.]
- Since they have a woman on their team...
- What woman?
- Ji Hyo. Ji Hyo's a woman.
- I know how strong Ji Hyo is myself.
But you guys are beating us
two to zero right now.
Then let us take Ji Hyo and
we'll give you Eric.
- I agree with that suggestion.
- What did you say?
These guys are like professionals.
[Real battle of their strength!
Prepare yourselves for what's to come.]
This battle will be fought five against five.
[Water shove battle- Round one.
Five against five.]
- That's not going to be an even fight.
- How about Six against five?
[I guess they really are afraid of Shinhwa.]
If you want it to be six against five,
you have to get your opponents to agree.
It's not fair to us,
so let's just do it like that.
- Six against five.
- Okay, fine. We'll allow it.
- Okay, then you're agreeing to 6 against 5.
- Let's just get on with it.
[They're just happy with their decision.]
Since we're being nice to you guys,
invite us onto the show more often.
Of course.
You're invited to come anytime.
[Knows how to get along
with Running Man members?]
- Invite us on often.
- Guys from back in the day!
- First, I ask that you all play it safe.
- Yes, don't worry about that.
Even though it's six against five,
let's play like it's even and fair.
I understand.
[Pride of Running Man is on the line-
We have to win this battle!]
[We've been winning every mission!
We won't lose this time around either!]
[Water shoving match- Round one.]
[Andy is on the forefront for Team Shinhwa.]
Okay, I got it.
Don't push me.
Stop pushing me!
[The brotherly love of shoving one of their
members forward as a sacrificial lamb.]
[Andy attacks!]
[Gary changes his direction.]
[Andy's attack fails miserably.]
[Team Shinhwa's Andy- Out!]
[Oh my goodness...]
[Jun Jin also fails his attack against Gary!]
I can't believe that just happened.
- You're doing great, Gary!
- Suk Jin. Let Suk Jin show us what he's got.
Let me get out there. Their
physical strength is right at my level.
Let's do this while standing.
[Team Shinhwa's Min Woo vs.
Team Running Man's Big-nose.]
[Rest comfortably.]
[It's Kwang Soo to the front line this time.]
[A water slap to the face!]
[Team Running Man's Giraffe
is also eliminated.]
- Get in there, Jae Suk.
- Fighting.
[Team Shinhwa- Three people vs.
Team Running Man- Four people.]
Okay, here I come.
- Okay, come on then.
- Are you serious?
Because I really am coming.
[No way to take back his words now.]
One, two, three.
Why are you going by what they say?
[You're right, why am I doing that?]
[Almost fell for Team Shinhwa's plans.]
[I can't fall for their tricks.]
- One, two, three.
- Why are you listening to them?
- We'll just stay here.
- You can just come to us.
[Attack!]
[Total chaos.]
[Gary and Min Woo fall in simultaneously.]
[It's absolute chaos on the water float.]
[Ha Ha falls victim to chaos and
gets dumped in the water.]
[Jae Suk and Jong Kook vs. Eric and Hye Sung.
It's two against two!]
Jong Kook!
You have to beat them!
Jong Kook is like a raging bull!
He's a total bull!
[Scary bull, Kkuk
charging in on his opponents.]
Come with me, Jong Kook!
[Just then, Hye Sung and Jae Suk...]
[All four of them...]
[Simultaneously...]
[Round one- Invalid.]
- What happened?
- We won, right?
[Eric's surprising sneak attack.]
See? Even 6 against 5,
it's still an even fight.
Six against five is an even fight.
[Needs all six of them in the fight
for the fight to be an even match.]
You should've sacrificed yourself earlier.
Why would you stick it out instead?
- What are you talking about?
- I could shoved both of them in earlier!
But I wasn't able to do that
because you were in the way.
I was holding onto them for you
so that you could attack from behind.
When it's time for you to die,
just hurry up and die, okay?
Why do we always have to die for you?
[Yoo Hyuk and Big-nose always
in charge of sacrificing themselves?]
[Current score- 0:0.
Back to round one!]
Fighting.
The referee is really cute.
- Are you cheering for Shinhwa right now?
- Is it us or Shinhwa?
- I'm cheering for our team.
- Gary thinks that you're being really cute.
[The referee is totally my style.]
[Water shoving match- Round two.]
[Andy back to the front line.]
[This time, it's zombie style attack.]
[Checking each other out like a couple of
zombies to start off the round.]
Let's just attack him.
Get rid of them.
Just sacrifice Suk Jin.
- Sacrifice Suk Jin?
- How can you say that?
[Big-nosed Brother explodes in
hurt disappointment at his words.]
[What?]
[Jae Suk is uselessly eliminated.]
[Hye Sung takes advantage of the confusion
to spring an ambush attack.]
Now's the chance.
You have to get up there now!
[Jun Jin and Andy attacks simultaneously!]
[The whole group falls in together!]
[Min Woo, Hye Sung, Suk Jin, Gary, and
Kwang Soo all fall in the water together!]
I'm scared!
[Jun Jin decides to retreat for now.]
Ha Ha, you need to stop pushing me
whenever you feel like you're in danger.
- Why do you keep pushing me?
- Because I got scared.
You almost made me fall in the water.
[Jun Jin vs. Jong Kook.
A one on one face-off.]
Okay, our two warriors.
Let's see who wins this battle.
Why do you keep letting go?
Why do you keep letting go of my hand?
[The battle between The Bull and The Ox.]
[Jong Kook twists his body around
so that only Jun Jin is eliminated.]
[Min Woo and Eric have no other choice
but to join in on the attack.]
[Jong Kook still manages to eliminate
Min Woo in the midst of all the chaos!]
[Final survivors-
Eric vs. Jong Kook and Ha Ha.]
[Eric vs. Jong Kook-
Battle of their strengths.]
[Haroro]
[Becomes the victor
without doing any of the work!]
- He didn't even do anything.
- I did it!
I'm... the ultimate victor!
- All you did was just stand there.
- I shoved them in the water!
[Current score-
Team Shinhwa- 0: Team Running Man- 1.]
For the next round of the game,
it'll be five against five.
If Team Running Man wins this round,
that's the end of this game.
[Best out of three.
If Team RM wins, then it's game over.]
- Okay.
- This could be the last round!
- Okay!
- Okay, let's go!
- Let's go.
- Okay... set, go!
[Water shoving match- Round Three.]
You can't be sitting up there
with your legs crossed like that!
What are you doing?
How about Jong Kook and I?
Palm to palm shoving.
- Why me?
- That's a pretty good idea.
[Andy requesting a battle of strength
against the almighty Mr. Capable?]
- Do it.
- Show him what you're made of!
Jong kook's really good at that.
[A manly one on one battle?]
Okay, let's stand face to face.
[As expected!]
[Goodbye, Jong Kook!]
[Andy the cheater!]
[While everyone seems to be flustered...]
[Jun Jin springs an ambush attack!]
[Within a blink of an eye,
the situation turns into a total chaos!]
[Everyone is ultimately shoved
into the water simultaneously.]
[In the blink of an eye,
the winner of the round is determined!]
[Team Shinhwa wins!]
So you're going to cheat your
way to victory?
Hey, Lee Kwang Soo!
This is all your fault!
[Andy having learned his bad habits
from the traitorous Giraffe?]
[Submerges himself in the water
out of his happiness over their win.]
[Shinhwa's tactical deception that takes
even the traitorous Giraffe by surprise.]
- This is how you do it though.
- Okay, this is how we're going to play?
I don't know how, but my face
touched the ground when I fell in the water.
How in the world did that happen?
Look at all the sand on my face.
Okay, this will be five against five again.
We really have to win it this time.
This is the last round.
Yes, this will be the final competition.
Yes, this is the decisive round.
[Water shoving match-
The final decisive round.]
- You're the king of cheating!
- Get him, Kwang Soo.
[King of cheating, Andy starts to
take cheap shots right off the bat.]
We have to win this so we can earn the hint.
- We don't have a single hint.
- Shinhwa already has two good hints.
To be honest, the hints that we have
aren't all that great either.
Then how do you think we felt
with the hints that we have?
[That's true...]
Look how they're all posed together.
It's like they're posing for a picture.
- What are you saying over there?
- I said, you all look very picturesque.
[Now that they're thinking about it,
Shinhwa also gets into the pose mode.]
[The focus of their pose are
their arms that are sticking straight out!]
They are... Shinhwa!
[We are Shinhwa!]
I don't know why we were always sticking our
arms out like that during our days, right?
While staring at the camera like this.
[The popular idol pose of
back in their days.]
Bee, bee!
There's a bee, Jae Suk.
- It's okay.
- It's a bee!
[Frightened out of their minds.]
[All these manly men freaking out
over one single bee.]
We're going to make you
shake in your shoes!
[The two warriors of strength from each team
facing off with one another again.]
[Kkuk the Ox...]
[vs. Jun Jin the Bull.]
[A battle with the pride of these two
men laid out on the line.]
So that you can't grab my shirt.
[So that his shirt won't get grabbed...
strike a sexy off the shoulder pose instead?]
I really don't like to get my shirt grabbed.
- Just take off your shirt!
- Don't do that!
- Just take it off.
- Hey, don't do it.
[The two rivals from way back in the day.]
To be honest, just like Ha Ha just said,
you two are...
[Jun Jin's sudden attack!]
[They were stuck together...]
[Jun Jin and Kwang Soo's simultaneous
plunge into the water.]
[Once Kwang Soo and Jun Jin are gone,
the only challenge Team RM has left to face?]
- Jong Kook.
- Yeah?
- One on one.
- What a joke.
One on one like a man!
[Yoo Hyuk accepts the challenge
in Mr. Capable's place.]
[Nerve-wracking just like the real play-offs.]
[On my goodness...]
No!
[Wardrobe malfunction for Andy.]
[You dare do this to me?]
[Andy attacks bare chested!]
[Andy takes the plunge into the water
along with Ha Ha and Gary.]
[Min Woo immediately follows it up
with an attack on Jong Kook.]
[Team Running Man in danger!]
[Fantastic teamwork which brought the game
to an end in the blink of an eye!]
[Andy breaks up the pack,
and Min Woo finishes up the rest!]
[But what is he doing?]
[Hye Sung slides into the water by
himself once everything is already over.]
What are you doing?
[Team Shinhwa brings down the game!]
And thus... Team Shinhwa also wins
the water shoving match!
- Seriously!
- I'm sick and tired of losing.
[For the first time in history,
Team Running Man loses three games in a row.]
- This feels weird.
- But why did we lose this round?
Why did all three of you fall in like that?
I couldn't grab him to stop him
because he didn't have a shirt on.
[Bare-chested Andy's attack that
no one could've done anything to stop.]
- This is really annoying.
- This is the first time ever in history.
Is this going to be a one shot kill
by our guest?
- We've never had this happen to us before.
- This is the first time it's ever happened.
['G, D, P, O' Go away, invincible immortal!]
[Running Man's ambiguous hint.]
[Team Shinhwa's good hint- 'Gold power!
Go away, you invincible immortal!']
- Okay, let's go.
- Let's go on to our final destination.
[All the hints have now been given out.]
[Off to the final location where
the curse of the gold can be lifted.]
[Will they be able to lift
the pirate's curse...]
[And get their gold back in
their possession?]
[One quiet village in Seungbongdo.]
- Which is the first clue?
- I think I know what it is.
Steal the ___ from the undead.
What does that mean?
Steal the ___ from the undead,
and On top of the roof is _____.
Everyone,
when a person never dies...
don't you think that means that maybe one
of the guys on the other team is invincible?
Yes, I think you may be right.
[One of the Shinhwa members
could be the undead?]
Which would mean that one member from
our team would also be the undead for them.
G, D, P, O.
- What could that stand for?
- Could it be related to the pirate ship?
G, D, P, O...
[Meanwhile, Team Shinhwa is studying the
three good clues that they have gained.]
Is that like a chant we have to say out loud?
Do we go up to the rooftop
to say the chant?
- That's what I think too.
- We have to guess who the undead is, right?
- Jong Kook, you think?
- Yeah, I think he's the undead.
[There's no doubt in their mind that
Mr. Capable would be the undead?]
Maybe that's what they wants us to think.
That Jong Kook would be the undead.
But since their rank was pretty important
in the previous mission to this...
[Then could it be Ji Hyo, who's
in the first place after last week?]
- Let's just take them on.
- Yeah, that's a good idea.
[No matter, Team Shinhwa is at an advantage
for knowing all three of the hints.]
[Who will be the one to lift the curse,
and win the gold?]
[Put all the pieces of the hints together,
eliminate the name tag from the undead
and take the treasure chest
in order to lift the curse off the treasure.]
We will now choose one of you who will have
the 'undead' label under your name tag.
[One person from each team will be stuck with
the 'undead' label underneath their name tag.]
[But there's no way for any one of them
to know if they are the chosen person.]
So what is it that we know so far?
We have to take something from the undead.
Then we have to climb up onto
the rooftop to shout out the chant.
That's the way for us to oust them.
It's not just all about the name tag.
Yeah, I think you're right.
- What is it they're going to come after?
- We've really got nothing on us.
So they're going to have to take
something that we have on us away from us?
[Trying to figure out what it is that
they need to take from the undead.]
Shoes.
- Shoes?
- Ah, shoes.
- You may be right, it could be shoes.
- It's shoes.
One thing that we all have on us
would be either clothes, or shoes.
- I think shoes may be right.
- Either shoes or a hat.
- Shoes are the heart of Running Man.
- That's right.
- I think that's what it is.
- Let's all tie our shoelaces really tight.
How do we know which rooftop it is
with so many rooftops around here?
I wonder if their hint is easier than ours?
- Is it a person with the yellow parasol?
- I saw a yellow parasol earlier.
[Team Shinhwa's on their way to
find the yellow parasol.]
[So many parasols around...
but they find the yellow parasol!]
Look, there's the yellow one.
Now that I look around,
there's a parasol up there too.
- I see them over there too.
- I see them everywhere.
[A village with an unusually large
number of parasols on their rooftops.]
I see them all over the place.
[Oh... Team Running Man guesses that it's
a certain colored parasol on the rooftop.]
There's one over there too.
[Team Running Man splitting up to find
whatever it is that's up on the rooftop.]
I feel like something is going to
jump out on us.
I'm not falling for that.
They could be trying to lure us in.
I already used that trick on them
about two years ago.
[Sense of ease overflowing
from these two veteran chasers.]
I'll lure them over.
Where are you going?
[Min Woo appears on scene to
lure them in.]
Where are you going, Min Woo?
- The plums on the trees look delicious.
- Really?
- I'm positive he's trying to lure us.
- I know.
I bet they're all waiting for us
behind that wall over there.
And look, there's Hye Sung now.
[All the members of Shinhwa are
closing in on them as predicted.]
There's nothing difficult to figure out here.
You're trying to eliminate our name tag, right?
- Do we just rip it off?
- That's right.
[Andy's ambush attack!]
[Gary twists his body around to
get his hands on Andy's name tag!]
[Gary succeeds in his counterattack!]
[Andy loses to Running Man's
experienced counterattack moves instead!]
[Could Andy be the undead member?]
There's nothing.
[Andy isn't the undead!]
[Team Shinhwa's Andy- Out!]
Andy, out.
[Finding the undead is their priority!
Team Running Man into offense position!]
I feel like we're the ones
being chased after.
They scared me.
[Now that they've seen each other,
it's time for a face-off!]
Be careful.
- Should we go after Jae Suk first?
- Yes.
[Min Woo and Hye Sung surrounding
the two Running Man members.]
[Yoo Hyuk gets in a protective stance
of Blank Ji!]
[Danger!]
[Yoo Hyuk pulls a fast move to
escape from their dangerous moment.]
- Let's get them.
- Is this what we do?
[A ferocious two on two face-off.]
[Hye Sung showing his back off to them
to lure them into attacking him.]
[Just then!]
[Ace Ji Hyo eliminates
Hye Sung's name tag!]
[Could Hye Sung be the undead?]
[No, he isn't!]
I just got eliminated by a girl.
Why are you coming over to me?
[The neighborhood dog coming over
to offer comfort to Hye Sung.]
[Makes him feel even more pathetic...]
What are you doing over here?
[It's okay, Hye Sung.]
- Why is he coming over to me?
- Why are your guys just showing up now?
- Is Hye Sung ousted?
- Hye Sung's ousted.
Shin Hye Sung, out.
- Did Ji Hyo eliminate me?
- Yeah, Ji Hyo did it.
Can't we just say that Jae Suk did it?
[We're sorry, but we
can't magically edit that out.]
- You did it, Ji Hyo.
- You have to take your friend, Hye Sung.
- He keeps following me around.
- Just go play with him while you wait.
[Stop with all that chattering,
and just follow me!]
- Just follow him.
- Where is he taking me?
Just follow that dog to jail.
[Meanwhile]
[Eric starting to feel panicked once realizing
that two of his members have been ousted.]
[Let me think about this a moment...]
[Yellow parasol]
[A yellow parasol?
That would be that rooftop over there...]
[Get the shoes from the undead,
and head over to that rooftop?]
[I'm sure that something must be up there!]
[Gary having distanced himself
away from the pack.]
[Min Woo and Jun Jin
closing in on their prey.]
There's one over there.
[Gary discovers Jun Jin and
turns around to go the other way.]
[But Min Woo is waiting for him
on the other side!]
They've got me flanked on both sides.
[Gary is surrounded
with nowhere to run to!]
[Deflects the attack and escapes
his imminent danger!]
[But Min Woo and Jun Jin aren't
letting up on their attack!]
[Joined effort by the two ace players
from Team Shinhwa!]
[Min Woo eliminates Gary's name tag!]
That was so close!
[Could Gary be the undead?
No, he's not!]
It's not Gary?
Gary, out.
They're about to make an announcement.
- What? Gary's been ousted?
- By whom?
[Shocked at the announcement of
Running Man member's first elimination.]
I bet it was Jun Jin and someone else.
Gary's been ousted?
Darn.
[Min and Jin working in unison
and back on the prowl.]
[Discovers Jae Suk and Ha Ha off
in the distance.]
Jae Suk, I think we can take them on.
But what if Eric shows up too,
and there are three of them?
[Full of confidence.]
[Flustered at the sight of Shinhwa members
approaching them with such confidence.]
Come back here for now.
They look way too confident right now.
[To the left- Jun Jin.
To the right- Min Woo.]
- Watch out for Min Woo.
- What are you doing?
Hang on a second.
Already?
[What are you waiting for?
Fight!]
[A fierce battle breaks out
between Jun Jin and Jae Suk!]
[And over on this side, it's Min Woo and Ha Ha,
who are of the same age!]
[What?
Simultaneously?]
[Min Woo eliminates Ha Ha's name tag first!]
[Ha Ha... is not the undead!]
Ha Ha?
[Two against one!
Min Woo and Jun Jin attacks Jae Suk!]
[Jae Suk in extreme danger!]
[Could Jae Suk be the one?]
[The undead]
[Jae Suk is Team Running Man's undead!]
[Team Running Man's undead is,
the invincible Yoo-ruce Willis.]
I'm the undead?
[In that case...]
[Steal the shoes from the undead!]
- Then we need to take Jae Suk's shoes.
- What?
[Now they're after Jae Suk's shoes!]
We need his shoes.
[Jae Suk is about to lose his shoes
without even knowing the reason for it!]
[Jae Suk eliminates Min Woo's name tag!]
[Min Woo isn't the undead of Team Shinhwa!]
[Jun Jin trying with all his might
to get the shoes off of Jae Suk's feet!]
I'm the undead!
I'm going to eliminate you too.
But we already eliminated your name tag.
Are you allowed to be doing this?
[Jae Suk can't be killed even if his
name tag has been eliminated already.]
He's the undead.
[There's nothing for him to fear anymore.]
- Can I just have one of your shoes?
- Sorry, but you can't.
So the shoes have something
to do with it?
- It's the shoes?
- No, mine are just too sweaty.
[Jun Jin the Bull trying to get Jae Suk's
shoes no matter what he has to do!]
Come on!
[Just then, Team Running Man hears
the commotion and rushes in to help!]
- What took you guys so long?
- Jae Suk.
Don't walk around by yourself.
Have you been ousted?
[Members discovers Jae Suk's bare back
without his name tag!]
- Are you out?
- I was walking with Ha Ha...
- No, I'm the undead.
- Really?
It was you?
- That's not bad.
- I like that.
- That means that you can't die.
- Only Jin and Eric are still alive.
I bet it's Eric.
I don't think it's Jin.
I think we need to eliminate Eric
and verify the hunch that we have.
But what does it matter even if we do that?
We don't know what the incantation is.
Eliminating the undead from their team
is going to work to our disadvantage.
We're just letting them know who
the invincible immortal is on the team.
[That's correct... because the undead is
just going to attack Team RM ruthlessly.]
- But we still have to know what's going on.
- We need to capture one of them.
Do you think they know
what the incantation is?
- They have more hints than we do.
- They have all the good hints.
Jong Kook, I think you need to capture
one of them first
and we have no other choice but to
torture the answer out of them.
[Is there really a need to do all that?]
- You know I'm not that kind of a person.
- I know, but victory is on the line.
[They somehow need to find out what
the incantation is from Team Shinhwa.]
[The two survivors of Team Shinhwa,
Eric and Jun Jin meet up discreetly.]
Jin, we're the only two that are left.
We can't be seen together.
- It's Jae Suk.
- He's the undead?
[Alerting Eric to the fact that
Jae Suk is the undead of that team.]
[Now, they have to take Jae Suk's shoe
and take it up to the yellow parasol!]
[There's only one solution!
A face-off to steal Jae Suk's shoe!]
Why do they look so confident?
- They already saw us.
- How can they look so confident?
There they come.
Why do you look so confident, Jun Jin?
You're flustering me.
Do you know what the incantation is?
- Yes, of course.
- Of course, we know.
- How do you know?
- Then we're the ones at a disadvantage.
[A difficult situation to figure out no matter
how many survivors are left on Team RM.]
- The truth is, we're not afraid of you guys.
- Why not?
Because we know all the hints,
and one of us two is the undead.
[The tables have now turned.]
What is there to be afraid of
when one of us is invincible?
- Wait, but it could be Jun Jin too.
- We need to know what they want first.
[Proposing a trade in order for
each team to get what they want.]
We want to talk to Jae Suk alone
for a moment.
Why do you want to talk to him alone?
Just for a moment.
It won't take long.
Then are you going to let us know
what the hint says?
- Let us know what the incantation is?
- We'll give you a hint about the incantation.
We can't let you know what
the incantation is all at once.
You have to do as we say.
- Do you know what it is?
- We know everything.
You want us to tell you why it is
that you have to do as we say?
Do you want all five of us to
let you know the reason why?
[Okay then...]
We'll tell you what the first letter says.
[Team Running Man only knows what the
first initials of what each letter says.]
Then just leave us with two people to face,
and we'll let you know what the first word is.
- You want two people?
- Just two of you.
Jae Suk and Ji Hyo.
- You're being too much right now.
- Ji Hyo ousted Hye Sung!
Don't you even have a conscience?
Okay, then fine.
Since you're all veterans...
We want Jae Suk and Kwang Soo.
- Us two?
- Let's do it, Jae Suk.
- Okay, fine.
- The rest of you needs to leave.
- What about the hint?
- You have to let us know what the hint is.
- You have to tell us the hint.
- The first letter.
Gol.
- Gol.
- Gol?
- If you guys are lying about this...
- I promise you, we're not.
[Will Team Running Man be able to guess
that the incantation is, 'Gold power'?]
- The rest of you needs to leave.
- good luck, you guys.
- Fighting.
- This is seriously...
- We'll tell you one more letter.
- Okay.
Gol...
Gold.
- What?
- Gold.
[Gold?]
- Stop kidding us around.
- No, it's true.
- Gold?
- Really?
- Gold makes sense.
[Correct answer- Gold Power.
Will Running Man figure out the rest?]
We're not the ones at a
disadvantage here.
Gold pie?
Gold coin?
[Clueless]
I'm the undead.
[Team Running Man's Jae Suk and Kwang Soo
vs. Team Shinhwa's Jun Jin and Eric.]
[Kwang Soo eliminates Eric's name tag!]
[What will be found underneath
Eric's name tag?]
[The undead]
[Eric is the undead from Team Shinhwa!]
[Eric is invincible!]
[During the melee,
Jae Suk eliminates Jun Jin's name tag!]
[Eric takes advantage of this moment
to steal Jae Suk's shoe away from him!]
[The undead, Eric running away
with Jae Suk's shoe in hand!]
Hey!
My shoe!
It's the shoe!
Eric can't be caught.
We have to get him no matter what.
Kwang Soo!
Eric's shoe!
[In the meantime, Eric is racing towards the
yellow parasol with Jae Suk's shoe in hand!]
[Difficult to chase after Eric
with one shoe missing.]
- Just rest here for a moment.
- Can you give me a piggyback ride?
We have to get to our teammates.
Hurry up and give me a ride.
Hurry, Kwang Soo.
It's Eric.
[Emergency situation!
Team Running Man gathering for a meeting.]
- We had to eliminate their name tag.
- But now that we have...
[They need to figure out
what the incantation is...]
Hey, we can just follow Eric and
hear what the incantation is.
- Yeah! Hurry up and go.
- You're right.
[Follow Eric and listen in on
what the incantation is!]
Run faster!
[Eric arrives on the rooftop
with the yellow parasol.]
[Put the item of the undead in here,
and recite the incantation.]
[It's now time to recite the incantation.]
Gold power.
Go away, invincible immortal.
[Gold power is activated!]
[The shoe disappears and
in its place is a golden glove!]
[An old parchment inside the glove.]
[The only way to eliminate the undead is to
eliminate his name tag with this glove on.]
So that's the way to kill him?
[Gather the name tags from both undead and
place them on top of the treasure chest
to lift the curse off the gold,
and take the treasure.]
[All his needs to do now is eliminate
Jae Suk's name tag with the gloved hand!]
[Keeping the gold glove hidden
and out of sight for now.]
Let's make a deal, Jae Suk.
You have to take his shoe off.
What is that?
[Team Running Man discovers
Eric's golden glove!]
- We have to get that glove!
- Where's Jae Suk's shoe?
- What is that?
- Don't touch me!
Don't you dare try to touch me!
You'll all be dead if you do!
I'll eliminate all of you!
[Eric blatantly lies as he
senses that he's in danger.]
Don't do it!
- What?
- You have to take his shoe off!
- Go ahead and try it!
- What is that?
- Try it and take it!
- What is that!
- Hey!
- What is it?
[May not know what it is, but
Eric is doing a fine job of scaring them.]
You have to get his shoe off.
Get his shoe off his foot.
What are you doing?
Just get his shoe off of him!
[Team Running man attempting to get
Eric's shoe off of his foot.]
[vs. Eric trying to eliminate
Jae Suk's name tag.]
[The final battle!]
- Get his shoe off.
- We have to get his shoe.
[They did manage to get Eric's
shoe off for now...]
Where am I supposed to take the shoe?
- Go!
- Go where?
[Not sure where to go since she
doesn't know about the yellow parasol.]
[Just then]
[Eric attacks Jae Suk's name tag!]
[Eric eliminates Jae Suk's name tag!]
If the name tag of the undead is eliminated
with the golden gloved hand
then the undead can be eliminated.
[Eric gathers the two 'undead' name tags
with his gloved hand.]
Do I have to say, 'Gold Power' again?
Gold power!
Go away, undead... no, that's not it.
Undead... no, that's not it.
What was it?
What was it, Kwang Soo?
Gold power.
Go away, invincible immortal.
What are you doing?
Success!
Guys!
[Back to the ship where the
treasure chest with the gold awaits them!]
No matter the fact that
we outnumbered them...
there was just no way for us
to beat them.
[The two name tags of the 'undead'
in Eric's hand.]
[Shinhwa makes their comeback into the
world of variety by claiming victory!]
[Places the two name tags in front
of the treasure chest filled with gold.]
[The curse of the gold...]
[will now be lifted.]
[A new treasure chest appears
in front of their very own eyes?]
[All the gold that had turned into
scrap metal by the curse...]
[transformed back into priceless treasure
with the curse having been lifted!]
- Look at all that gold!
- Is it real gold?
Are you giving this to us?
Seriously?
You guys have to come back
on the show.
We've been losing to them all day.
[For the first time in history,
Running Man loses every single round.]
Today's victors... Shinhwa!
[Pirates of the Western Sea-
Shinhwa takes possession of the gold!]
Please invite us on more often.
It's been so fun having these guys on
who are more like my old friends.
[An enjoyable day for all!]
How are we as the boys from
back in the day?
There's a difference.
Subtitles by DramaFever
[That's why the idols of present day
have made their way to Running Man.]
[Just who are these idols to send
this big crowd into a state of frenzy?]
[A Pink]
[2PM]
[Girl's Day]
[Infinite]
[Sistar]
[Beast]
[MBLAQ]
[Greatest guest list in history- A fierce
competition amongst the hottest idols.]
[A ferocious battle to become
the ultimate idol of the pack.]
Which one?
You two look like a couple.
[Everyone cast in a glow of soft
pink light that only the idols can provide?]
[And the ultimate mission
that they have to face...]
One!
Two!
[Face your fear and conquer it!]
[Who will become the ultimate King of Idols?]
[Next Week's Running Man-
King of Idols.]