[An adventure into a fantastical land.]
[Dorothy and her brother...]
[Along with Running Man expeditioners.]
[On a journey in search of the Wizard of Oz.]
[Dorothy gets kidnapped!]
[The journey to find his sister!]
[A reckless journey to find Dorothy.]
[Wizard of Oz- Fellowship of Running Man.]
Subtitles by DramaFever
[One morning in October, 2013.]
- Where is this place?
- I don't know.
We were in Busan just moments ago,
Yoo Jung.
[Yoo Jung and TOP, who were in attendance at
the Busan International Film Festival...]
[How did they end up here?]
What brought us here to this
mysterious place?
[They've been brought here by some
unknown force of mystery.]
I feel like I've seen
this tree somewhere before.
You know this tree, don't you?
It's a pine tree.
[A pair of red heels and a capsule?]
What is this capsule?
[A letter inside the capsule...]
[To the children who have come
to this land from a different world...]
[From a different world?]
This place is a land that's far away
from the world that you're from.
It will be impossible for you to return to
where you came from on your own.
There's only one way.
You must find the wizard
and tell him what your wish is.
Scarecrows that are lacking
in their intelligence
the heartless tin woodmen,
and the cowardly lions.
Find them and have them join your
quest to find the wizard.
Only then, will you be able to
realize your true heart's desire.
[This is...]
The Wizard of Oz?
Then that means that you're...
Dorothy?
[Then Yoo Jung is Dorothy...]
Then you're...
[Huh?]
[I'm Toto?]
[Dorothy Yoo Jung, and Brother TOP get
on their bike in search of their friends...]
[But their bike seems to have
a mind of its own.]
I'm not scaring you with
how fast I'm going, am I?
Am I going too fast for you?
I think I see a doorway over there.
[A doorway into another world?]
Dorothy and her brother went off to find their
friends who can help them on their quest.
What is this that we're doing?
Wizard of Oz?
This is quite different than
how the actual story goes.
I can't go near any fireplaces.
[Oh my...]
Gary.
You look like a beekeeper.
[Beekeeper Gary bursts out in laughter.]
This is too small on my head.
He's a hip hop star.
He really isn't someone who should be
going around looking like this.
I really do experience all sorts of new things
on Mondays and Tuesdays.
- What is this I'm wearing?
- That looks like a funnel.
- That looks like a funnel on your head.
- Do I look okay?
Yeah, you look pretty good.
What's that?
A train?
[A train is headed their way?]
- Someone's riding on it.
- What?
What's that?
[Huh? Another tin woodman?]
Who's that riding on the train?
[A tin robot?]
Who are you?
[Wait... a name tag?]
[Yoon. Je. Moon?]
[The actor... Mr. Yoon Je Moon?]
It's Je Moon.
- I made a huge mistake.
- It's Yoon Je Moon.
- I didn't know.
- Je Moon! Hi!
[An actor who's at the top of his game,
Yoon Je Moon.]
I can't believe they made you
dress up in that costume.
I can't believe they made you wear this
metal pail on your head. That's going too far.
Don't you know what kind of
a man Je Moon is?
You've changed quite a bit.
You never used to laugh
quite so easily back in the day.
He's not someone you can
fool around with like that.
Je Moon isn't someone who
usually laughs so easily.
- Is it weird to see me laugh and smile?
- No, it's not that.
[A benign smile on his face.]
Wow... he really has changed a lot.
In moments...
You are aware of Dorothy in Wizard of Oz?
Dorothy and her brother...
They'll be coming here to ask you to join
them in their quest to find the Wizard of Oz.
Really?
[Dorothy and her friends leaving for
a world of adventure.]
[Just what awaits them
at the end of their adventure?]
What's going on with the weather here?
- What's going on here?
- What is this?
What are we supposed to be?
Street beggars?
We're not even scarecrows.
You have us standing here like beggars.
Scarecrow Ha Ha and Scarecrow Kwang Soo
did not possess any intelligence.
Their lack of any intelligence always
left them struggling.
You two are going to play a round of
the Blue Flag, White Flag game
to gain some intelligence
for yourselves.
Can't you do it in a nicer way?
[Ah... their arms...]
We're going to play 'Lift the flag' game
in order for you to gain your intelligence.
What do you think you should do if I say,
'Lift up the blue flag'?
Then you should probably lower
the white flag, don't you think?
Can't you ever make it simple?
If he tells you to raise your blue flag,
then you have to lower your white flag.
And what if I tell you to
raise your white flag?
Then you should probably lower
your blue flag, right?
This is hard.
Maybe I really don't have any intelligence.
Lower your blue flag.
Okay, then I raise it?
Lower your white flag.
[A hot mess.]
Raise your blue flag.
[Lack of intelligence made plainly obvious.]
Don't raise the blue flag,
but lower your white flag.
- What?
- Don't raise the blue flag, lower the white.
Don't lower the white flag,
but lower the blue flag.
Why do we have to do this!
Why do we have to do this?
As you can see for yourselves,
you don't have any intelligence.
What does this have anything
to do with intelligence?
Cowardly Lion Jong Kook and Lion Ji Hyo
on the other hand...
Even though they were very
afraid of the ax
they decided to try wood cutting
to earn courage.
I'm so scared of this ax.
I think you're slamming down
on that too hard.
- Get up.
- How am I to do it when you can't do it?
The cowardly lion.
[Cowardly lions' wood cutting show.]
You frighten me.
Why do I have to break these?
[Brick breaking this time?]
That's how you do it.
I feel so bad for these bricks.
I broke them all.
What to do?
The poor things.
I feel so bad for them.
Why are you making us do all this
so early in the morning?
I'm so scared.
[Trying to earn some intelligence by catching
the tissue that are flying in the air.]
Hey!
I caught it!
Scarecrow Ha Ha and Scarecrow Kwang Soo
did not possess any intelligence.
[As guesses, they possess no intelligence.]
[Follow the yellow brick road.]
[Dorothy Yoo Jung and Brother TOP in search
of their friends who could help them.]
I wonder how long it'll be
before we find any of them.
Where in the world are we?
[Friends... where are you?]
- Three times four is?
- Three, four!
Where are we?
- Scarecrows?
- It's scarecrows!
[Did they discover the two scarecrows?]
Scarecrows!
- Dorothy?
- We found them.
- It's TOP!
- It's TOP! It's TOP!
- Scarecrows!
- TOP! Hurry!
[They discover the scarecrows
on the field along the road.]
- Yoo Jung, you're Dorothy?
- Scarecrows!
- We've been searching for you everywhere!
- Hurry up and help us.
We've been waiting for you
for over an hour!
- Give us our intelligence!
- This is killing me!
What is going on here?
Hurry up and help us!
- How are we... just go like this?
- Just hurry!
- Get us out of this thing!
- We're freezing out here!
- We have to untie this?
- Free us from this thing.
- What took you guys so long!
- Hurry up and get us out of this.
What took you guys so long?
- We're free!
- Are we a team then?
- The four of us are a team?
No, but since you have no intelligence,
Dorothy and her brother...
He's not the brother.
Isn't he Toto? Toto, the dog?
Isn't he supposed to be the dog
for the day?
- No, he's her brother.
- Dorothy's brother?
- Since you're lacking intelligence...
- He's Toto.
They're going to take you to see the wizard
so that you can find your intelligence.
I really hope that it's someplace warm.
Okay, then we'll cast a spell for you.
A spell to turn that bike into a car.
[First... turn the bike into a car.]
- So that the bike can turn into a car.
- Bicycle... turn yourself into a car!
One, two, three!
Ta da!
It's been transformed into a car!
[Getting into the bicycle that they've
magically transformed into a car...]
- That's usually my spot.
- You can drive, Yoo Jung.
[How absurd... she's only 14 years old!]
Let's all pray for Yoo Jung to
get her license right now!
Let's all pray for it!
You will now be given a test to
control your heart.
The tin woodsmen who were in a quest to earn
their hearts cannot be surprised at any event.
[Bomb...]
Tin woodsman Je Moon, Tin woodsman Jae Suk,
and Tin woodsman Gary
started a competition amongst themselves in
order to learn how to control their hearts.
You have one minute on the clock.
[Heart control? One minute on the clock-
Play on the last letter of the word.]
Suk-tan. (Coal)
Tan-Kwang. (Coal mine)
Kwang-san. (Mine)
San-wool-lim. (Echo in the hills)
- Lim?
- You can play off of 'Im'.
Im-kkyukjeong.
[Unable to think of anything?]
Jung-boon.
[Huh?]
Boon-jang-sil.
Did you say, Jung-boon?
Sil-jang. (Mounting)
Jang?
Jang-bagu-ni. (Grocery bag)
Ni?
- Ni?
- Yes, 'Ni'.
Ni...
I have no idea what
you're going to come up with.
All I can think of is swear words.
- Ni-ce. (City in France)
- Nice?
Stock-holm.
[Holm?]
- Holm?
- Holm.
There's nothing.
You should just...
Why was the explosion so big?
Even Je Moon was really startled.
What do we do now?
Do we have to go get everyone else?
- We have to find the wizard, I think.
- Right?
[Must find the wizard...]
What about the Tiger?
Isn't there a cowardly lion?
You're right.
I think Jong Kook is the lion.
- The cowardly lion.
- And the tin robot.
Right, the tin robot.
Ah... so we all have to group together
and find our way to the wizard?
I guess we're going to have
to pick them up.
No matter how I look at it...
I think we have to go get them.
And I know that TOP...
he's quite the prankster.
What do you think we should do?
Just let them get in the car?
- No, we can't just let them in the car.
- Let's leave that up to TOP.
Since it's pretty cold outside...
We can't let them in the car
too easily.
[Wow... what a prankster.]
- Let's torment them as much as we can.
- You really are an awful person sometimes.
There's no room for sympathy.
[Absolutely no hint of intelligence.
Two scarecrows suit each other well.]
- What is this? They're here?
- What is this? This place is really cool.
[Jeonsun 'S' Exhibit.]
[An old coal cultural complex.]
- What the heck?
- What is that?
There are three of them?
Someone's coming.
[The three people are a sight to
laugh at even from a distance.]
I don't think all three of us are going
to be able to get in it.
What is this?
- What is this?
- What are you guys?
What are you guys?
Are you tin robots?
What are you supposed to be?
Sancho?
It's Yoo Jung and TOP.
[Fascinated by the sight of Dorothy Yoo Jung,
and her Brother TOP alighting from the car.]
- What are you guys dressed in?
- This is so embarrassing!
- This is seriously embarrassing.
- What are you doing here, Yoo Jung?
- What are you doing here?
- Yoo Jung is Dorothy.
- Yoo Jung is Dorothy?
- You can't cross these tracks.
- Why? Why not?
- No, you can't cross the tracks.
- It's very nice to meet you.
- Don't cross the tracks!
[Greeting each other happily with
the railroad tracks between them.]
How do you expect me to look like this
with TOP hanging around me?
What's going on here?
Yoo Jung looks so pretty.
You three look like a group of Idols
dressed in your stage costume from afar.
[Group name- Tin Woodsman Boys?]
How many of these three?
- One.
- Just one of you can get in that car.
And as for the other two...
[Woodman Je Moon thinking that he is
undoubtedly the person to get chosen.]
- You have to step back.
- This is unbelievable.
- Why do we have to get chosen by you guys?
- This is seriously ridiculous.
- This is absurd.
- They chose both of you?
- Yes.
- Why did you choose both of them?
- They chose both of us right away.
- Do you know how hard we had to work?
How hard do you think
we worked to win them over?
For them to choose both of us?
Those two over there...
You two are seriously getting on my nerves.
- I don't like either one of you.
- Did you just point your fingers at me?
- Did you?
- That's right! I did!
- You dare point your finger at me?
- I'm going to come and drag you over here.
You think you can do that to me?
- When I'm already over here?
- You're the only one who needs to get lost!
[Tin woodsman Jae Suk and Scarecrow Ha Ha-
Itching to tear each other apart.]
There's the dance portion, acrostic poem
and personal performance, right?
- They have to do all that, right?
- What kind of absurdity is that?
- You need to keep it down over there.
- Seriously.
You'd better be careful.
Je Moon has his eye on you right now.
- That's right.
- Got it?
Don't try to put ideas in his head!
If you do, we'll just take him right now!
- I'm going to come over there right now!
- You can't step over the tracks!
[Huh?]
You can't cross the tracks like that!
[Everyone seems to want to
cross the tracks.]
We're all like zombies!
[Zombies?]
- I don't even have a heart right now.
- We're zombies.
Let's start with the acrostic poem first.
We'll tell you what your word is.
Gary, your word is, 'Dong-chang-sang'.
- Je Moon's word is... 'Run-ning-man'.
- His word is Kim Yoo Jung.
Okay, his word can be Kim Yoo Jung.
And Jae Suk, we're not going to tell you.
This is ridiculous.
Absolutely ridiculous.
This is really ridiculous.
Seriously.
I'm getting so annoyed right now.
Why don't you start, Gary?
Remember, your word is, 'dong-chang-sang'.
[Gary to start the acrostic poem.]
- Dong!
- You are all animals! ('dong-mul'=animals.)
There you go.
You're doing great.
Chang!
I'm going to pierce you with this spear!
('chang'= spear.)
There you go.
You're doing great.
- Sang!
- I'm going to eat you alive!!
('sang'=alive).
You guys!
I'm going to eat you all alive!
Okay.
First of all... that wasn't too bad.
Okay, Kim Yoo Jung.
Kim!
Hey, Kim Yoo Jung!
- He startled me.
- Is he trying to copy what Gary did?
- What do you mean, copy?
- One, two, three. 'Yoo'!
Hey, Yoo Jung!
That's not bad, Je Moon.
That's pretty good.
[A new twist on the acrostic poem.]
Jung!
I hope you don't fall in love!
('Jung-boon"=affection, love.)
- What are you saying?
- She's only 15 years old right now.
- She's a teenager.
It's just that he used that word earlier
when we were playing our previous game.
How could you say that to her?
- Over!
- Okay.
For Jae Suk...
- You have to do whatever TOP tells you.
- Okay.
I'm confident I can do it.
Give me what you've got.
Come on.
- It could be a 15 syllable word.
- Try me.
[Overly confident Tin Woodman Jae Suk.]
- Fine, take it then.
- Give it to me.
- Do it. Give it to me.
- Then give it a try.
[Just what will TOP give out as his word?]
Top!
Top?
[One simple word... 'Top'.]
Top-cheo!
(A play on the word, 'shut up'.)
[He's telling them to shove it.]
- Listen you jerks! Just shut it!
- Jae Suk!
- You shut it right now!
- It's over! It's over for you!
- Over!
- I know that it's over for me!
That was such a sneaky play.
Top? That's what you had?
Forget it.
We've made our decision.
[Just who did they choose?]
Fine, make your decision!
- We're going to choose two people.
- What!
- Two people.
- We've had a sudden change of heart.
- You're going to choose two people?
- Then I know that he's out.
[Jae Suk is undoubtedly the one
to be disqualified?]
- Hey, you're choosing two people?
- You two did great!
Hey, Dorothy!
Hey!
- Hey!
- Bye! See you later.
- Bye.
- Woodsman Gae! You're leaving me here?
Hey, Dorothy! TOP!
You guys are just going to leave like this?
Hey!
Wow... unbelievable.
Fine!
This means war!
- This means war!
- This is war!
Look at the way he looks over there.
He really looks so pathetic.
I'm so pissed!
Ugh, I'm so pissed!
[Thus, the heartless Tin Woodsman Jae Suk
is left all alone steaming in his anger.]
[They ultimately allow Jae Suk to ride along,
and they're now headed elsewhere...]
But I haven't seen Suk Jin anywhere.
- What do you think Suk Jin is?
- I wonder if Suk Jin is the wizard.
- Why would Suk Jin be the wizard?
- You don't think?
You don't think we're filming this episode
without him, do you?
There they are.
[Jeongsun's 'D' forest lodge.]
But I bet they aren't that cold since
they're dressed in those furry costumes.
- They're dressed in furry costumes?
- Yeah.
Since they're lions.
Look, it's a tin man.
Why are there so many tin men?
- Scarecrows.
- They're scarecrows!
Why are there so many tin men?
Yoon Je Moon is the headmaster
for this traveling circus.
- Hello.
We came because we are in need of some
animals for our traveling circus act.
We can't be in a circus act.
We're too afraid.
- This is Dorothy.
- Dorothy!
- Hi, Dorothy! I can't believe it's Dorothy.
- This is Dorothy's brother.
- There is no brother!
- What did you say?
- She doesn't have a brother!
- Have you ever been over to Dorothy's house?
- Dorothy doesn't have a brother.
- He's a brother from a different relation.
- Does she just think of him as a brother?
- Dorothy's brother, 'Doto'.
- Doto. His name is Doto.
- Are you sure they're not just friends?
- Why are you holding onto an ax?
- We're cowardly lions.
- It's because we're afraid.
- We got that, so set down the ax.
That lioness looks like she just
woke up from a nap or something.
She looks like she's been sleeping.
Anyway, Dorothy and her brother, Doto...
- they can only take one of you with them.
- What did you say?
- Only one of you can come with us.
- Why?
The other one has to stay here forever.
The person that doesn't get picked
has to team up with Ji Suk Jin.
- In that case...
- Let's do an acrostic poem.
- Let's do the word, 'sa-ja' (lion)
- That's good.
Sa.
- Sa!
- Sa.
- I'm telling you to buy me. ('sa'=buy).
- Ja.
Ja!
('Ja'=here)
Buy me right now.
Buy!
Okay, next.
Blank Ji Hyo.
Sa!
- Ja.
- Ja! Ja!
- How much? How much will it be?
- Why are you copying me?
[Love-struck woodsman, Gary.
An immediate reaction to Blank Ji's poem.]
I have to buy while I have the chance.
[Dorothy and her expeditioners
are finally all gathered together.]
Suk Jin really is nowhere to be seen.
I see that you all are finally
gathered together.
The siblings who want to go back home,
intelligence seeking scarecrows
tin woodsmen in search for a heart,
and courage seeking lions.
Come find me if you have a wish
that you want to have come true.
If you succeed your group mission
you will win yourselves an item that will
help you in your quest to find the wizard.
Seriously?
You can change out of your clothes and
we will now start your mission for the quest.
- Okay.
- Let's go!
[Let's get started on
this world of adventure!]
They made you suffer for nothing when we all
just needed to get in that car together.
Je Moon is really angry right now.
You'd better watch yourself
right now.
[Just then...]
What is this? I came here by accident.
This is a radish field.
Ugh, seriously!
I keep making mistakes.
Oo-sa! Let's disappear.
Big-nose power!
[Target destination is right here.]
Ugh, seriously!
I keep making mistakes.
[Finally...]
I came to the right place this time!
[Come to me, Dorothy and friends...]
- Okay, let's get going.
- Let's go.
Is Suk Jin really the wizard?
- I wonder why Suk Jin is the wizard.
- What?
- Where are we going right now?
- I'm not sure.
[Where are they headed...]
We're supposed to go to
some restaurant.
This is the place.
We're here.
This isn't a restaurant.
[A place clouded in mysterious energy...]
[Will they be able to meet
Wizard Big-nose at this place?]
[Just then...]
[A message magically appears
on Jae Suk's cellphone.]
Welcome to your first adventure.
It's Suk Jin.
[Wizard Big-nose is watching Dorothy
and her friends through his magical portal.]
Don't get out of the car,
and look next to you
and you'll see another car
parked there.
I have placed a curse on that car
and you'll find that there are nine
magical canes stuck on that car.
Each and every one of you must
grab onto one of those canes
and every one of you must board
that car within your allotted time
and shut the car door behind you
for the curse to be lifted.
I will give you something that would be of
use if you can complete your mission on time.
You must do whatever it takes
to get past this hurdle.
What did he say?
What is that?
- What did he say? What is that?
- Is that it?
[Wizard Big-nose's first hurdle is revealed.]
[Magical plunger canes.]
[The same place, one hour ago.]
Magical car, appear!
Nine magical canes... appear!
Okay!
[His magic seems to be
working well for him today?]
Okay, my magical canes are ready.
Okay, Big-nose power!
Magical canes,
attach yourselves to the car!
Hey, hurry up and stick them on there.
[Magic apprentices are all suffering from
having met an incapable wizard master.]
Okay!
They're all on there now!
They are all really stuck on there!
They really are magical canes!
[These are...]
[Magical mission that Big-nose wizard
has prepared for them himself.]
Within 30 seconds...
all of you must get in the
car with a cane
and close the door behind you
in order for you to succeed your mission.
- Inside that car?
- Seriously.
- We're not getting in that car?
- No, we're getting back in this car.
- We're getting in this car?
- We have to get back in this car.
How are all nine of us to fit in that car?
No, you're getting in the other car.
You have to get in the white car.
- What did you say?
- You have to get in the white car.
- You want us to get in the other car?
- In that white car?
[The idea is so absurd
that all they can do is laugh.]
How are nine of us
supposed to get in that car?
We did a test trial with our staff,
and they succeeded in under 30 seconds.
- Is everyone ready?
- Yes. We have to move quickly, okay?
[There's no need for you
to be that serious...]
[The glint in his eyes alone is enough
to pull the plungers off the car.]
[Big-nose Wizard's first trial- Start!]
-You have to move faster!
- You have to hurry, Je Moon!
- What are you doing?
[Cold glint Je Moon's attempt at pulling the
plunger off isn't going as well as he hoped.]
I can't pull it off!
You have to pull it off the car!
Come on, Je Moon!
[No time for laughter! The next
person must hurry out for their turn!]
You have to move faster, Je Moon!
Like this!
[Yoo Hyuk pulls his off with one yank.]
[Huh?]
There's a door in the back!
Why are you getting in that way?
[Cold glint Je Moon insisting on making
things more difficult for himself.]
- There's a door in the back?
- Of course, there is!
[Kkuk also pulls it off on his first try.]
Come in this way.
Pull yourself in more.
Turn your body sideways.
There you go. Turn.
[Where did that glint in Je Moon's eyes
from earlier go?]
- Do I need to get in the back?
- Hurry!
- You have to get in the backseat.
- Hurry up and get in!
- Just get in!
- How am I supposed to get in there?
[Just cram in...]
Just fold yourself in.
[Already packed to the brim.]
[Blank Ji also gets it in one try.]
[Excited Dorothy Yoo Jung.]
Get in the front seat, Yoo Jung.
[They have to move quickly...]
Get in the driver's seat.
[Dorothy Yoo Jung burrowing her way into the
driver's seat with her tiny frame.]
[Gary is trying to follow her lead...]
- I can't close the door!
- You have to shut the door!
- I can't shut it!
- Shut it on yourself if you have to!
Your butt!
Your butt's in the way!
[Gary's butt is in the way of
closing the car door.]
- Your butt!
- The door is now shut!
[Everyone is in the car!]
Okay, your time is...
One minute and 41 seconds.
[One minute and 41 seconds!]
[The cold glint in his has completely
dissipated after a round of the first game.]
Je Moon!
You have to pull it off
on your first try, Je Moon.
[Je Moon seems to be the likely culprit
for their failure for the first attempt?]
It took you longer to pull off your plunger
than it took Yoo Jung.
Je Moon, there's a backdoor too.
[Je Moon...
he may be the new black hole.]
- We all have to rush out in succession.
- One right after another.
Je Moon has to be faster.
- I'm sorry, but you need to be faster.
- Okay, I got it. Fighting!
[Totally trying to override
Coach Kkuk's nagging.]
- I don't think he liked what I had to say.
- Je Moon doesn't like to be nagged.
- No, he doesn't seem to like that.
- Fighting!
You just wait and see. I'm positive
that he'll be much better now.
[Magical cane- Second attempt.]
Nice!
[Again!]
[Thrown on his back.]
Why does he keep doing that?
Why is he using his foot?
[But Je Moon still bounces right back up
to avoid being nagged at by Jong Kook.]
How am I supposed to
open the door in the back?
[Unable to open the backdoor again,
and tries to squeeze through the front.]
- I told you about the door earlier.
- I didn't see the door handle!
We have to squeeze in closer.
Scoot your body even more!
- A little more!
- Is this enough?
[Blank Ji easily pulls off the
magical cane from the car.]
[Wait! That's not the right door!]
Be careful when you shut the door!
[The mission will be complete as soon as
Blank Ji and Dorothy Yoo Jung gets in!]
Shut it!
Shut the door!
[All nine members are in!]
Open the door!
Open the door for us.
- Open the door.
- Save me! Please save me!
- How many seconds?
- Where's the door handle?
[First attempt was one minute 41 seconds.
This was faster than the first try...]
[Did they pass?]
52 seconds.
[Second attempt- 52 seconds. Fail.]
- Seriously, Je Moon.
- I told you earlier, Je Moon.
You told me that you knew!
The handle is right here.
- This is it?
- The door handle is right here.
- Why are you pulling it off with your foot?
- I can't pull it off with just my hands.
There's a dent in the car door.
[Je Moon's footprint.]
Je Moon did it.
- What?
- The car's a bit dented.
[Je Moon takes a closer look...]
- No, I didn't do that.
- What do you mean, you didn't?
What do you mean, you didn't?
That was definitely you!
You're the one who did it.
[Charismatic Je Moon.
A new cutie pie on the scene.]
- Seriously.
- I really want to succeed this time.
- What if we fail the mission?
- If we fail, then we won't get the hint.
- Seriously.
- Then do we just go home?
Are you trying to fail on purpose now?
[Is Je Moon activating his homing device?]
- I'm really trying to succeed.
- Okay.
[Yoo Hyuk positioning himself to be faster
even if it's by a mere second.]
My position is looking very
weird on camera.
- You're doing that on purpose, aren't you?
- No, I'm not!
- You love showing off your butt!
- Stop doing that.
He really loves to show off his butt.
Okay, let's do this.
We can do this!
- Ready.
- Fighting!
[The glint in his eye in back.]
[I will make sure that we
succeed this time!]
[Magical cane- Third attempt.]
[Black hole Je Moon's clean start.]
[He even gets the backdoor
opened correctly this time.]
[Lightning fast speed.]
[Must endure...]
[The tail end of the mission is
now left up to the ladies...]
Get in, get in!
Go!
[Lastly, even Dorothy Yoo Jung successfully
pulls off her magical cane off the car!]
Close the door!
[Dorothy and expeditioners-
Everyone makes their way in!]
The door is open.
[And their record is?]
- We were totally fast this time.
- We were really fast.
- We had to have succeeded this time.
- A new record.
- We got it. We got it this time.
If they tell us that we didn't make it again,
I don't know what I'm going to do.
I'm sure we made it this time.
If they tell us that we failed again, I'm
going to stick this plunger on the camera
and I can't guarantee what I'll
do after that.
20... maybe 26 seconds?
25.41 seconds.
[New record of 25.41 seconds.]
[Magical cane mission-
Passes with an astounding new record!]
[If someone saw their reaction,
they'd think they just won a gold medal.]
Je Moon just smiled!
I saw a smile on Je Moon's face!
Je Moon can't go home now!
We will now give you one magical hint.
Inside this magic envelope...
is a very useful tool that will help you
in your search for the wizard.
[Something crucial to help them find
Big-nosed Wizard inside the envelope...]
Even though I know that you're a team,
only one of you can have this envelope.
[The magical envelope containing the hint
will be given out to only one person.]
- Give it to either Je Moon or Yoo Jung.
- Why don't you decide, Yoo Jung?
- We all want that envelope.
- Am I not allowed to have that?
- No, you can have it too.
- You can have it too.
[The magical item's allure that even
Dorothy Yoo Jung can't seem to deny.]
Give it to Dorothy then.
[The unbelievable power of the magical envelope
will be revealed at the final race.]
[Just then...]
[A mysterious piece of paper
falls right out of the sky.]
- We just received some sort of a letter.
- What? A letter?
[What message is found on that paper?]
Come to the library in Sabuk
if you want to meet me.
[Second message from Big-nosed Wizard.]
- Let's go meet up with him.
- I don't particularly want to meet him.
If we don't meet up with him,
then Suk Jin won't be on this episode?
That's right.
Not if we don't meet up with him.
[Please come!]
You haven't been on many variety shows,
have you, Je Moon?
- You're new to this, right?
- This is my first time on a variety.
From what I saw earlier, I noticed
that you really like group games?
[Je Moon's eagerness showing through
right from the beginning.]
Do you want to know what he said to me
after the game was over?
He said, 'This is really fun'.
[Maybe he was made to be on
variety shows?]
[Sabuk's library.]
[Crash landing expert, Big-nosed Wizard
makes his landing on top of a bookcase.]
Why can't I get this right?
I can't get anything right because
I didn't graduate from the magic school.
Okay, this is the place.
[But what is he doing at the library?]
Okay.
[Magical powers activated.]
[Voting booth appears out of thin air!]
Since we're going to be
playing other games there too
if there's anyone in this car that you want
to hand that first envelope over to...
Jong Kook is basically telling you to
hand it over to him right now.
No, that's not it.
But... I think that you're the last person
who I should be giving this envelope to.
- That's right, Yoo Jung.
- That's smart of you, Yoo Jung.
Why don't you just give it to
whomever you want to give it to?
You can give it to me if you want.
- Here you go.
- Thanks.
- Look at how happy he is.
- We were told that we can't open it.
- Let's get out.
- Let's all get out of the car.
[Kind-hearted Dorothy Yoo Jung
conceding to her elder.]
Are we going to see Suk Jin in there?
[What will Dorothy and her expeditioners'
second adventure be?]
- Is Suk Jin not going to be in this episode?
- What is this?
What is this?
[Jae Suk discovers a mysterious booth.]
Welcome, everyone.
I have a huge surprise
in store for all of you.
You've all fallen for my trap.
- Look at all these books.
- What is this?
[Another piece of paper falls from the sky?]
I see that you've all passed your
first adventure safely.
He's talking to us in casual speech.
Ah, because he's older than all of us?
You will be given a magical envelope.
I will keep watching to see if you have
what it takes to catch up to me.
[Big-nosed Wizard...
What is he up to now?]
- Do you all see the voting booth?
- Yes.
You have to step into the booth and vote for
the person who you want to have the envelope.
Since Je Moon has the envelope,
I'm sure he won't vote for himself, right?
- Je Moon won't, right?
- I doubt that he will.
I can't have two envelopes?
[Well... of course, you can...]
You'll go on to the final mission location
after you're done voting.
- Already?
- What? Already?
When you make your move
to the final location
you will get in the numbered car
according to which of the two you pick.
I guess that determines which team
we're all going to be on.
[Car number one, and Car number two.]
- That must be the team we're on.
- Let's not vote for ourselves.
Should we make it a rule
not to vote for ourselves?
- Let's not vote for ourselves.
- We know that you're still going to do it.
[How did she know?
'Ha Ha'.]
[And picks to see which car
he'll be riding in.]
Be honest, and don't vote for yourself.
[And immediately board
the car that they chose.]
[Blank Ji votes for Dorothy Yoo Jung.]
[And picks Car number one,
just like Ha Ha did.]
Since he's playing my brother and all.
[Dorothy Yoo Jung votes for
her brother, TOP.]
[The car that Yoo Jung
will be riding in is...]
[Je Moon makes his way to Car number one
after voting for Yoo Jung.]
- Je Moon.
- We're all in this car?
[Gary, Ha Ha, and Ji Hyo are already
seated in Car number one.]
[There are four people already
in the first car?]
- I guess Yoo Jung's in the second car.
- Yes, she must be.
[Currently, Yoo Jung is the only one
who picked the second car.]
Hello.
- Is this Car number one?
- This is Car number one.
- How can this be?
- What is this? We're all here.
- Why are you getting in this car?
- Where's Jong Kook?
- I picked number one.
- Then Yoo Jung is the only one missing?
[Something strange is going on here...]
- Which one are you?
- Is he in this car too?
[Even Kwang Soo is headed to their car?]
[What's going on here?]
[And lastly, even Jong Kook
heads over to the same car.]
We're all number one.
Yoo Jung is the only one missing.
Dorothy is the only one
who isn't here.
[What... is going on here?]
Are they all riding in the other car?
Or are we all riding in our own cars?
[Car number two with only Dorothy Yoo Jung
as its passenger is already on the road.]
Am I just being driven there separately?
[Just then]
[A figure clad in black moves in
on Dorothy.]
[That's right...]
[This was Big-nose Wizard's plan all along.]
I'm taking your precious
Dorothy Yoo Jung with me.
[I'm taking Dorothy with me...]
If you want to get Dorothy back,
then come to the art mine.
No!
[You dare... take my sister?]
[Brother... save me...]
[Ten minutes ago when it was
Dorothy Yoo Jung's turn to vote.]
Is it finally Yoo Jung's turn?
[Big-nosed Wizard was hiding behind
the bookcase all along.]
[Switching out the ticketing ballot
right before Dorothy's turn.]
Change into Car number two.
Okay.
[Transformed all the papers into
number two for Yoo Jung's turn.]
[And places the box back in its place.]
[That's how Dorothy Yoo Jung alone was the
only person to have picked Car number two.]
- Aren't you scared about getting kidnapped?
- Where are you taking me?
There's no need for me to tell you
where you're being taken to.
You're being kidnapped right now.
You're my hostage.
I have big plans in the works
by using you as my bait.
You just need to do
whatever I tell you to do.
Do you understand?
- I can make all your wishes come true.
- Seriously?
With my magical wand.
What's your wish?
I'll grant you one wish.
I want to win today.
That may be a bit difficult.
- You said you'd grant me any wish I want!
- But I have to win today.
I have to win.
Anyway, my goal for the day is,
through the use of you...
- I'm going to win today.
- No, I'm going to win.
[The kidnapper and the hostage seem to
get along pretty well.]
[Through the magical portal...
they arrive at the steel mine.]
You're the hostage here.
You can't get out of the car first.
Come this way.
- Since you're the hostage...
- Please don't take me to jail.
- It's not a jail.
- But that looks like jail.
Open... portal!
[As the wizard chants out his spell...]
[The door to his magical home opens up!]
[An abandoned mine that's been turned into
an art gallery is the wizard's lair.]
Watch your step.
You're my hostage.
- I don't want to be your hostage.
- Do you take this wizard as a joke?
Aren't you even afraid of me?
When I've kidnapped you as my hostage?
Don't you realize what a serious
situation you're stuck in right now?
- I'm telling you that you're my hostage.
- This is fun.
My brother TOP is going to
come rescue me.
A wizard's lair needs to have a creepy feel
to it like this one.
Do you see that sign?
It says, 'Do not enter'.
[Taking his hostage, Dorothy to a place
where she can't be seen by others.]
Get in.
Get in!
This is my lair!
Couldn't you have picked someplace
warmer as your lair?
This is it.
[Wizard's mystical chair.]
- Is this where I sit?
- I've got security cameras.
No, this is your chair.
You're the hostage.
- Wow, security cameras.
- That's right. Security cameras.
[Security cameras displayed on the screen
where he can track other members' moves.]
Dorothy.
[It's time for things to start playing out
as Big-nosed Wizard had planned?]
All the other members will now start to
make their moves according to my orders.
Do you understand?
They're all in the palm of my hand!
- It's a bit cold in here, isn't it?
- Yes.
[In a few moments...]
This is closed off.
[The Running Man members arrive in
front of the closed magical portal.]
What is it barred off?
I see that you've all made it.
You all have to do as I tell you to do
if you want to get Dorothy Yoo Jung back.
Once the door opens,
everyone step in through the portal
and eliminate each other's
name tags.
[Eliminate... each other's name tags?]
Once two out of the eight of you have been
ousted and only six of you are left alive...
only then will you be able to move closer
to where Yoo Jung and I are hiding.
[When the second portal opens,
they will move on to the next stage.]
[The next door will open up only when they
follow Big-nosed wizard's instructions.]
[Then...
the portal to the final race will open!]
I will count to ten once the
portal opens...
so move quickly to situate yourself,
and start the name tag elimination.
Keep in mind that only when
two of you have been eliminated
that's when you'll be able to
see your precious Yoo Jung again!
[Eliminate their own friends in order
to rescue Dorothy?]
Before we go on...
One of you possesses a magical envelope that
you earned from the first mission, right?
Yes, Je Moon has it.
Please open the envelope now.
[Time to open up the envelope.]
[What is inside that magical envelope?]
A free pass?
A free pass through the first round.
Why do you look so happy about it?
First round... pass!
[First round- Pass.]
- Je Moon's disappeared.
- Where did he disappear off to?
He passed through the first round.
[As for the remaining seven members...
time to enter through the first portal.]
It has begun.
- We have to eliminate each other?
- We all have to scatter out on our own.
[Once two of them have been eliminated,
everyone moves on to Round Two.]
[The start of Big-nosed Wizard's countdown.]
I have to get situated first.
[All the Running Man members rush off
in a flurry of desperation.]
Race... start!
This is all going exactly
the way I planned.
[What will become of
Dorothy Yoo Jung's fate?]
[Even though they're feeling flustered,
the best thing to do for now is to hide.]
Please don't film me right now.
I'm just going to hide.
[They've all become masters
at hiding by this point.]
I think I'm going to hide right here.
Are these all individual rooms?
Are these dorm rooms?
[Dorm rooms where artists can stay
while working on their art pieces.]
What is all this?
This is an art gallery of sorts.
I know where Kwang Soo went.
A fight has to start somewhere so two can
get eliminated and we can move on.
- Okay, let's do that.
- We can't exhaust ourselves in Round One.
I feel... that I haven't been treating
you the best lately.
Why don't you keep going...
where you were going?
The only thing I can do at this point
is to stay in hiding.
[Jae Suk encounters Mr. Capable and Ace.]
This is a pure coincidence
that we're running into you like this.
Really?
We should just end this quickly.
Upstairs... Ha Ha and others are up there,
so let's just quickly...
You just wait here then.
Okay, thanks.
- See you later.
- Thanks!
- I'll just wait down here.
- Okay.
Please finish it off quickly.
I'll see you later.
- He's all the way down at the end.
- Down at the end?
[Meanwhile, oblivious Ha Ha...]
[Escapes into a guest room.]
[It's the Grim Reaper!]
No!
Why you of all people!
[Ha Ha in extreme danger!]
That's right, fight!
Rip him to shreds!
I said, rip him!
No!
Why does it have to be you of all people!
[Will Ha Ha become the first victim?]
Why!
[Jong Kook eliminates Ha Ha's name tag.]
[Ha Ha- Out!]
[Poor Ha Ha...]
Ha Ha, out.
I really love Jong Kook in
times like this.
He always keeps his word
if he says he's going to do something.
I really loves it when he does that.
He takes care of things.
There's only one elimination left.
Just one more person left to go.
[Jae Suk staying on Kwang Soo's trail.]
[Kwang Soo went that way!]
[Everyone seems to have decided on
getting rid of the icon of betrayal.]
- He went outside.
- Seriously?
[Kwang Soo's disappeared?]
[Rule- They cannot go outside...]
Hang on a second.
[A locked door...]
[Giraffe locked the door from the inside.]
[Seems to be asking the worker who's inside
the office for a favor of some sorts.]
- This door wasn't locked earlier.
- What is this? I thought you can't lock it.
Wait.
Wait a minute. Excuse me, Sir.
- No, you can't come in here.
- What do you mean, we can't?
- Wait a minute. Excuse me.
- You can't come in here.
- Excuse me?
- I said, you can't come in here.
Your voice seems to be trembling a lot.
Why is your voice trembling so much?
I'm sorry, but you sound nervous.
Excuse me, Sir.
Can you open the door for a moment?
[What do we do now?]
Let's just go for now.
[Huh?
Are they just going to leave like this?]
[They seem to be working
on some sort of a plan.]
- Let go! Let go of me!
- I'm going to get rid of you right now!
- Let me go!
- We're right here, Jong Kook!
Come help me!
Help me get him!
[Should I go, or not?
Go, or not?]
[All the members are in hiding for the
chance to ambush attack Kwang Soo.]
[Deceived by the silence,
and slowly opens the door.]
[Gary and Jae Suk's plan succeeds!]
Did you really feel the need to get
this nice man to lie to us like that?
We can't break any of the pieces in here,
so come outside right now.
- Come outside.
- Okay, I'll come outside.
- We can't break anything in here.
- Let's go outside.
[Agreeing to battle it out
in a more open spaced area.]
Okay, I've agreed to come out.
Let's do this man to man.
I don't want to do this like a coward.
Be careful. Let's go over
there as not to break anything.
- Let's go to an open space.
- Okay.
[Just then,
Gary moves in on Kwang Soo's back?]
[Sneaks up...
and eliminates Kwang Soo's name tag.]
I thought we were going to go
to a bigger open space.
I never said that myself.
This is what you always do to us.
That was no fun at all.
I'm having a blast right now.
Lee Kwang Soo, out.
- I thought we were going to go...
- I don't remember saying that.
Gary.
Gary!
[Kwang Soo- Out!]
[Eliminate two people in the first round...]
[Ha Ha and Kwang Soo- Out!]
[Everything's going according to my plan.]
- No one can eliminate my name tag.
- Yoo Jung.
Didn't you say that you wanted to win?
Want to try playing a name tag
elimination game just the two of us?
[Just the two of them playing a round of
name tag elimination game out of boredom?]
I'll cast a magic spell.
That you can't be eliminated even if
I rip off your name tag right now.
[Using magic to ensure that no one is ousted
even if the name tag gets ripped off?]
- I cannot get ousted!
- Yup!
Okay.
It won't be easy to rip my
name tag off.
Set, go.
Neither one of us will get ousted.
It'll be easier for me to rip your tag off
if you keep holding onto it
since you only have the use of one hand.
[First time contender, Dorothy Yoo Jung
vs. Weakest player, Big-nosed wizard.]
Wow, you're strong.
Wow!
She's really strong!
I'm serious!
Why are you so strong?
[Dorothy playing with the wizard
like her little toy.]
I'm serious.
I'm not joking about this.
[Big-nosed wizard is being
pushed around by little Dorothy.]
Hey, Yoo Jung.
[Dorothy and her monstrous strength!]
She's not an easy opponent.
I'm serious.
[Yoo Jung grabs onto his cape!]
Look at her!
[His cape may become his downfall!]
I can't let you beat me like this.
[The unbelievable power of
the 14 year old girl!]
[Yoo Jung eliminates Suk Jin's name tag!]
[Utter humiliation!]
I can't believe this.
[What will happen to sturdy Dorothy,
and the frail wizard?]
[Meanwhile, the remaining Running Man
members who have survived...]
[arrive at the second portal!]
- TOP, be careful.
- Okay.
There you are.
What took you guys so long?
- You sound so nice and calm.
- You want to know why we took so long?
You survived?
I bet you won't be smiling anymore
once we walk in there.
[Wait for the real Je Moon to
make his appearance...]
Seeing you guys tearing your friends apart
whom you've traveled with thus far...
It left a very memorable
impression on me.
He's such an awful actor.
I'll tell you the rules for
your next round.
Come and get me if you can!
[Come and get me!]
[Come catch... the wizard?]
[Big-nosed wizard challenging them
to come and get him.]
[What is he trying to do?]
[The countdown to the second round starts!]
Seven.
Six.
Five.
Four.
Three. Two. One!
Race... start!
[As predicted,
the glint in Je Moon's eyes changes!]
You startled me!
What are you doing over there?
- So I just attack?
- Yes.
Be careful, Je Moon.
[Continuing to follow... Gary's back.]
[The terrorizing sound of his laughter.]
[Locked on his target?
Continuing to follow Gary's back.]
He keeps on following us.
[The mounting terror as he casually
continues to stalk them.]
- What did the wizard say?
- Did he tell us to eliminate each other?
- I don't think that's what he said.
- What did he say then?
He didn't really tell us to
eliminate each other's name tag.
No, he didn't say that.
It could've been bad
if I ripped off your name tag.
What makes you think that
you could eliminate my name tag?
[I can do it like this.]
[TOP in front of the Monday Couple's path.]
[With Je Moon in in the rear of their path.]
[Stuck between a rock and a hard place.]
[There he goes with his
terrorizing laugh again.]
[In this case, the Monday Couple is...]
Why are you acting like Jong Kook?
The way I see it, hang on a second...
- Jae Suk, he didn't tell us to eliminate.
- He didn't say anything about elimination.
I think that we're
misunderstood right now.
[Monday Couple is still surrounded
on both sides.]
- Let's go that way.
- How about that way?
[Je Moon continues to prey on Gary!]
[Just then...]
[What!]
[Big-nosed wizard makes his appearance!]
[Je Moon's name tag!]
[Big-nosed wizard eliminates
Je Moon's name tag!]
[What is going on here!]
[Big-nosed wizard finally makes his
appearance in front of Running Man members!]
[Je Moon is still reeling from shock,
and doesn't even know what to say!]
Why is Suk Jin ripping off our name tags?
Are we not allowed to rip off
Suk Jin's name tag?
What was that noise?
What's going on?
[Big-nosed wizard is heading their way!]
[He approached them
and starts a conversation!]
- What are you, Suk Jin?
- Me?
- I'm the wizard.
- You're the wizard?
- What are you doing?
- I'm the wizard.
[All explanations aside, attack first!]
[Unlike other times, Big-nose
is acting aggressive and attacks!]
- What? What are you doing?
- Is he allowed to do that?
I thought we were just attacking
each other.
But he came out of nowhere.
- Why are you being like this?
- Because I want to win!
Because I want to win.
I'm going to win!
[Holding tightly onto
the wizard to keep him in place...]
I'm the wizard!
- Sit him down and make him talk.
- I'll tell you.
- Tell us what's going on.
- You're wondering about Yoo Jung, right?
Hey! You guys don't
know what's going on here.
- What's going on here?
- Why do you keep attacking us?
Hold onto him.
[Attacking at every chance he gets.]
I'm going to rip off your name tag
if you don't calm down.
[Everything will be over if
the wizard's name tag is ripped off...]
I'm going to rip off your name tag
if you don't calm down.
[He rips off the name tag...]
What is this?
[Reflect]
[Reflect!]
Only one more left to go now.
[He's disappeared!
What's going on here!]
- What did he mean by that?
- You shouldn't have ripped it off.
[He had no choice but to rip it off,
but what is going on here?]
Yoo Jae Suk, out.
[Ousted instead and the wizard disappears.
Just what is going on here?]
[Moments before Round Two started.]
[Wizard suggesting to welcome others
to throw them off their balance.]
- Okay.
- I promise that I'll do it.
- Don't make me laugh.
- I'm serious!
Avatar... go fight!
[Creates an image of the wizard himself...]
[The wizard that they've been battling
is only an image of the real wizard himself!]
- You're the wizard?
- What are you doing?
[That's why he was being more aggressive
about his attack on Running Man members!]
[The image eliminated the name tag...
and thus, Yoo Jae Suk is ousted.]
Then does that mean that I'm still alive?
[Je Moon is resurrected from having had
his name tag ripped off by the image.]
Since Jae Suk was ousted by
an image of me
one more person now needs to be ousted
before you can pass through the second round.
Then... I want the rest of you to
battle amongst yourselves
to oust one more person from the
five of you that are still left alive.
[Frightening Je Moon is
on the move once again!]
[As before, his target is still Gary!]
Then does it mean that Suk Jin isn't
going to be here for the last round either?
He's hiding out somewhere.
He has Yoo Jung in captivity.
He keeps on staring at me.
He won't take his eyes off of me.
[Is it time for me to rip off
Gary's name tag?]
[Since it's come down to this...]
[Let's just do this face to face.]
Gary's very good, Je Moon.
He has really good skills.
- But I'm a pretty good athlete too.
- Why don't you face him one on one?
[The big match- Start.]
[Grabbing onto Gary like an
experienced judo athlete.]
[And not letting go of his death grip!]
[How can this be?
Mr. Gary isn't able to make a move!]
What are they doing?
Dancing the traditional Korean dance?
This is fun.
[Spins him around and round...]
[Spins around again...]
[Je Moon eliminates Gary's name tag!]
Wow! I can't believe it!
It's almost impossible to do it like that.
Gary, out.
- Why did you target me like that?
- Sorry.
[Round two-
Jae Suk, and Gary- Out!]
- This stuff is really hard.
- Lose all your memories.
You won't be able to win.
Yup.
I'm going to win today.
You know what I'm like, don't you?
I don't go easy on anyone.
Not even on girl group members.
[Specialist on ousting female guests-
Cold hearted Big-nose.]
I'm the wizard.
[Whether he is or not,
all she wants to do is play.]
[Dorothy is all excited since she doesn't
seem to be fearing the wizard whatsoever.]
I'm going to win this episode
of Running Man.
I think it's that way.
[Off to the next portal.]
- Let's go.
- This is fun.
[The path that will lead them
through the third portal...]
[The eerie atmosphere to
perfectly match the wizard's lair.]
I think this is the way to go down
to the sub terrain floor.
[The path that used to lead down to the mine
is still left perfectly intact.]
- This place itself is like...
- It's like a museum.
Right?
[The third portal.]
[Opens]
[To the final location where they will
meet up with the wizard and Yoo Jung.]
That looks like our portal.
That looks like the same iron gate.
There are only four of you still left alive.
Soon, you'll be able to see
your Yoo Jung again.
You must eliminate your last two members,
so that only two of you are left alive!
[Eliminate two out of the four survivors!]
I heard some screaming,
then I heard that Je Moon was eliminated.
Then Suk Jin walks up to us,
and went crazy trying to eliminate me.
So what else could I do?
I eliminated him, and then I saw his tag.
Then I found out that Je Moon is still alive,
and I'm the only one that got ousted.
[No clue as to what Jae Suk is saying
from having been ousted so early on.]
- Bottom line is that you're here now.
- You're ousted now.
Seriously.
What is this all about today?
What are they thinking by ousting the
three main stars of the show here?
[Say what?]
- What kind words.
- What are they doing with this episode?
- You've got Brad Pitt over here...
- And Orlando Bloom over here.
He's Orlando Bloom,
and who do you want to be?
- Tom Cruise.
- He's Tom Cruise.
You've got all three of us here.
What are you going to do about this now?
What's this?
Did you get ousted?
- Who ousted you?
- Jong Kook.
Ugh, that Kim Jong Kook.
[Mr. Capable eliminates Ji Hyo
as soon as they step through the portal.]
Sorry, Ji Hyo.
[Everything was fine up to that point...]
[But Je Moon and TOP work together
to attack Mr. Capable!]
- Why are you doing this to me?
- One on one with him is impossible.
I shouldn't have ousted Ji Hyo.
I can see those two teaming up together.
Kim Jong Kook needs to get ousted.
[An unavoidable battle in an attempt
to rescue Dorothy.]
[Who will be the final member to be
eliminated in this third round?]
[Scary Je Moon vs. Mr. Capable Jong Kook.]
[The two powerhouses collide!]
[Just then...
TOP springs his attack on Jong Kook!]
That's right.
[TOP gets his hand on
Mr. Capable's name tag!]
[TOP eliminates Mr. Capable's name tag!]
Jong Kook is ousted.
That's right!
[Satisfied]
[The final two survivors-
Yoon Je Moon and TOP.]
[Dreaming of himself winning again.]
Okay, Yoo Jung.
There are only two of them left alive now.
It's time for us to finally step in.
- Let's go!
- I'm going to win.
I told you that you can't win.
Please remember that you're my hostage!
Seriously, Yoo Jung!
Why do you look so happy?
- I beat you earlier too.
- I told you that I gave you a break.
You're my hostage.
You have to remember that, okay?
[Oh... finally escapes confinement.]
Remember that you're a hostage.
- I'm going to win.
- You.
- I told you that you're a hostage.
- I'll eliminate everyone's name tag.
Open... portal!
The door's a little creaky, isn't it?
There they are.
There you guys are.
[Finally... faces off with the survivors.]
- Save me.
- Take a good look.
What is this that I have in my hand?
[Threatening them with her name tag
in his hand.]
I have Yoo Jung's name tag in my grasp.
TOP.
Don't you want to save your sister?
- Yes, I want to save her.
- Do you want to save her?
- We have to go back home.
- Right?
TOP, I'm going to give you an order.
Unless you want to lose your sister...
eliminate Yoon Je Moon right now.
[Eliminate Je Moon's name tag!]
Right now!
Or else, I'm ripping off her name tag!
[Dorothy is still excited.]
Wait, Suk Jin.
What if I eliminate him instead?
- If you do, then you'd win.
- Then why aren't you giving me that order?
[Ah... he didn't think that far ahead...]
Doto.
Come over here.
[An unavoidable battle in order
to rescue Dorothy.]
[Just who will be the final survivor that
will have to face off with the wizard?]
This is exciting.
Je Moon's got some moves.
[Doto TOP is immobilized!]
[But he won't be that easy
to take down...]
[Je Moon vs. TOP!
Who will be the victor?]
[Simultaneously grabs each
other's name tags...]
[But TOP is quicker!]
[As soon as the victor is determined,
wizard makes his move!]
[How did that happen?]
Let me put it back on first.
[Big-nosed Wizard really cramping
everyone's style.]
TOP can grab and hold onto Suk Jin,
and Yoo Jung can rip off the name tag.
[Easy prey Big-nose vs.
TOP and Dorothy siblings.]
This is my third year on Running Man.
Grab him.
Grab him by his clothes.
Grab his clothes,
grab his arms.
[TOP gets his hand on Big-nose's
name tag!]
[Big-nosed wizard eliminates
TOP's name tag instead!]
[A result that no one could've
predicted!]
This is the wisdom that comes from
three years of being on Running Man.
- I thought I had him.
- You thought you had me, didn't you?
Why don't you have a
seat over there?
[It's now Wizard Big-nose vs.
Dorothy Yoo Jung.]
It's down to you and I now.
[Acting like a brat in front of his opponent.]
- He's cheating with his clothes.
- It's his clothes.
- His cape makes it impossible to rip off.
- The cape constantly gets in the way.
You have no idea how bothersome this is.
It's hard having to hold onto it.
- Then just take it off.
- Can I borrow your jacket then?
- Lend me your jacket then.
- Then have a rematch with TOP.
- I can't do that.
- I'll lend you my jacket.
That's not right.
[Now's my chance!]
[Easy prey, Mr. Wizard...]
[Sorry!]
[Dorothy Yoo Jung takes his
cape away from him!]
[If she rips off his name tag...]
[How many times...
have I told you that the victory is mine!]
[Dorothy Yoo Jung eliminates
Big-nosed Wizard's name tag!]
[Dorothy siblings... finally... get it done!]
[After being had by Yoo Jung all day...]
You won?
Three rings?
Love, courage and wisdom.
[All three gold rings are given
to Dorothy for her victory!]
I have to find wisdom!
I'm just a scarecrow!
- I have to find my courage too.
- I can't live like an idiot like this forever!
- I have no courage.
- What are you going to do with the rings?
How don't the three of us split them?
[What a blatant request!]
- What's wrong with you?
- Why are you being so greedy?
[He ends up taking one...
to put it on his finger.]
It doesn't even fit you.
Give me mine.
[TOP's no different...]
We're all on the same boat anyway.
Did you see how Je Moon
isn't saying a word now?
First time he's been quite today.
He's not muttering a word.
[Thus, Dorothy and her friends
lived happily ever after.]
One.
One, two, three.
['L' Outlet in Chungcheon.]
There it is.
[Basketball mania, Haroro...
coming out in a baseball uniform?]
[Catcher is, Catcher Kwang-vatar.]
A special gift will be given to the person
who does the best opening ceremony act.
[Immediately jumps into the air.]
[Gets the crowd involved.]
[Running Man opening act contest.]
Fighting!
Don't I have to give you
some sort of a signal?
- You're supposed to do it first?
- I have to signal to you what to do.
[Exchanging signals like real
baseballs players do.]
[Not seeming to understand each other.]
[Finally explodes.]
What did I do!
[Going to signal exchange to
foot kicking exchange.]
I'm sorry.
[Please do it right this time...]
[Breaks out in a loud and
obnoxious scream.]
Go easy.
Please go easy.
[Catch... the ball!]
[Not a very good acting job.]
[The duo showing off their
perfectly harmonized act.]
- Hey!
- What!
How many hours is it going to
take you to throw that ball?
Do you know how many of us
are waiting back there?
Go away!
You guys can't even play baseball!
- Why are you suddenly making us pitch?
- Is our guest a baseball player?
- Ryu Hyun Jin?
- Is it Ryu Hyun Jin?
[Can it be... The infamous
'Korean Monster', Ryu Hyun Jin?]
- Could it be Ryu Hyun Jin?
- You think?
- What if it's Clara?
- Ryu Hyun Jin!
Please come on out!
Who is it?
[Hollywood?]
[Los Angeles?]
[Is it really Ryu Hyun Jin?]
See?
That's L.A.!
[L.A.- America.]
[It really is L.A.!]
[Oh!]
It's Hyun Jin!
[A clear view of his name
and his number.]
[Ryu Hyun Jin's L.A. home.]
See? He just pressed
the doorbell with his left hand!
- He could be just another big guy.
- Are we going to L.A.?
[Huh?
That's the real Ryu Hyun Jin!]
['Korean Monster', Ryu Hyun Jin!]
[A player for a major
American baseball league!]
[Korean Monster!]
[First debut season,
and came in at 14th place!]
[A major league player!
An astounding achievement!]
What are you doing here?
- It is Hyun Jin!
- It really is Ryu Hyun Jin!
- You too!
- Hyun Jin!
I don't know why I'm laughing.
This is your first mission.
You have to show me around
your house.
My house?
Why?
Because I came all the way
to America.
Okay.
Come on in.
[For the first time ever,
a peek inside Ryu Hyun Jin's L.A. life!]
Just go wherever you'd like to go.
In that case...
let's go into the living room first.
Please come this way.
[A first look into Ryu Hyun Jin's
L.A. home living room.]
This is my living room.
Who's that gentleman?
This is Ryu Hyun Soo.
He's actually my real brother.
- Hello.
- What are you doing!
Just until recently...
both my mom and dad were here too.
They went back to Korea recently,
and now it's just my brother and I.
It's just the two of us left here now.
Since the season is over now...
I'm thinking of returning back to
Korea pretty soon myself.
[The view is pretty nice...]
But if you see over here...
If you look into that distance,
it's the ocean.
And on a really clear day,
you can see all the way to the ocean.
So it's really nice.
What's that ball over there?
- That one over there.
- That ball?
That's the game ball from my
first game that I won in.
So I took that ball to remember
my first win in the major leagues.
And these bats...
When I played against Arizona...
This is the bat I used to hit
my winning hit.
So my clubhouse manager gave this
to me in commemoration.
This one is Shin Soo's bat.
Shin Soo signed it himself.
So I keep it as a keepsake.
Is that your family photo?
That one?
We took that last winter.
We took that picture last winter.
But I think we need a new picture.
- Why?
- I look too fat in it.
[What a loving family picture.]
He looks skinnier in that picture
than he looks in person.
- What are all these newspapers for?
- We don't really read them.
We don't really read them.
[He seems to like seeing himself
in the headlines?]
I do all the reading on the internet.
How do you feel when you see
your name in the papers?
I make sure to keep up with the news
when I'm doing well.
But I don't read the news
when I haven't played very well.
- On purpose?
- On purpose.
Since they're not going to say anything
nice when I lose, right?
- So I tend not to read it then.
- Do you normally care about those things?
No.
I'm not really like that.
But since so many people are watching...
I feel very blessed.
Especially with so many Koreans in L.A.
Do you see that white building
over there?
If you look right next to that building...
Do you see that light next to it?
It's a square shape.
That's our baseball field.
You can see the fireworks going off from
there after the game on Fridays.
That only happens on Fridays.
You can come over to my
house on Friday.
[The place they can see
from Ryu Hyun Jin's house.]
[L.A. Dodger's Stadium!]
Are you staying in town,
or are you going back to Korea?
- I'm going back next week.
- Next week?
- Have a good time. See you next year.
- Thank you.
- I can do at least that much.
- That was impressive.
That's the parking garage over there.
[A parking garage of immense size
once they enter the stadium!]
[Epic proportions!]
Sometimes they even run out
of parking spaces.
[Even with that size,
sometimes it's not enough!]
[As they cross over the parking lot...
they finally see the stadium in front!]
[Entering the player's parking lot.]
What's up?
- How are you?
- Good.
[Martin Kim- Dormitory Manager.]
[Time to enter the stadium!]
Look at my hair.
[Entering the players' locker room
inside the stadium.]
The locker room is completely empty.
The players' took their belongings home.
This is my spot.
Ryu.
Number 99.
[Korean Monster, Ryu Hyun Jin's locker.]
And this is our team's Ace,
Kershaw's locker.
Who else can I tell you about?
- How about someone you're friends with?
- Okay.
This is my friend, Uribe's locker.
Isn't his locker big?
Veteran player's lockers are bigger.
[Veteran players' lockers are bigger.]
This is Matt Kemp's locker.
What about over at the end there?
No, we don't have to go over there.
I want to give each of the
Running Man members a hat.
[Hyun Jin packs up the hats in the boxes.]
This is a woman's size.
Bye.
[Making sure to say his goodbyes to everyone
as he makes his way out.]
I'm just going to give the hat
to Ji Hyo only.
I think we're done with all
the introductions now.
What is it that I have to do now since
you came all the way to America?
There is a mission for you.
First...
- Isn't that for superpowers?
- It's a magical potion.
Once you drink this potion, you'll activate
your power to control Running Man members.
Really?
I can do that if I drink this?
Come on, Hyun Jin.
But you have to chant out a spell
once you finish drinking your potion.
That's the only way to activate
your powers.
Go away.
Get out of here.
Hurry up and go away.
[Getting rid of his brother because he's
too embarrassed to have him witness it?]
Why are you acting embarrassed about it?
- Having to chant out a spell like that.
- That's not easy to do.
I think I'd be too embarrassed to do it
in front of my own wife too.
[Now...]
The one who controls Running Man!
[Superpower activated!]
Then I'm now the king of Running Man?
Then can I do whatever I
want to do now?
For the next entire episode...
you have been given the ability to determine
the fates of Running Man members
however you see fit.
Seriously?
Look at how happy he is about it.
Then I will now give you a mission which will
determine the course of your fate.
I will be making a decision on several
different matters from this point on.
[What will Ryu Hyun Jin's selection be?]
Running Man members in Korea must guess
which decision it is that I have made
and make your move depending on
the correct guesses that you've made.
[Running Man members must guess
Hyun Jin's decision and make their move!]
Please do your best to complete the mission.
Fighting.
Let's go!
Run!
Quickly! Kim Jong Kook!
I'm coming to get you!
Subtitles by DramaFever
Ryu Hyun Jin's challenge!
[The one who controls Running Man,
Ryu Hyun Jin.]
[If they can't correctly guess at
Ryu Hyun Jin's decision...]
[They must pay a tough price for it.]
Will I eat jjamppong, or jjajangmyun?
[Seven level meat tower befitting
of Fat-Ryu's stature.]
[And an army of superstars
befitting of Ryu Hyun Jin.]
[The ultimate right handed pitcher,
Yoon Suk Min.]
[And Hallyu's newest Idol Group, EXO.]
[Next week's Running Man-
Korean Monster.]