Running Man
[He's finally here!]
[Ryu Hyun Jin]
[Korean Monster, Ryu Hyun Jin,
and Korea's First Love, Suzy.]
[Unbelievable missions with
these two guests.]
[Monster power-
I'll show you what I'm made of!]
[Ryu Hyun Jin's rosy hued confession-
What will Suzy's response be?]
[On the other hand- EXO and
Running Man's hide-and-go seek.]
[Current number of survivors-
EXO- 7 vs. Running Man- 5.]
[One minute before the exchange.]
EXO is right here!
[EXO's Suho and Tao trying to lure in
Running Man members before the exchange.]
[It'll be disastrous if the turn
changes from attack to defense.]
[Determined Jae Suk... it's do or die!]
[Not much time left for the attack!
Just what will come of the outcome?]
[With nowhere to run to,
Jae Suk desperately starts his attack.]
[With only three seconds left to go,
Jae Suk ousts two members of EXO!]
[Time over- Time for the exchange.]
[EXO's Suho and Tao- Out!]
[Current count of survivors-
Running Man- 5 vs. EXO- 5]
[EXO's turn to attack.]
I'm going to run out
as soon as the time is up.
[Giraffe, now in defense mode,
quietly sneaks in somewhere...]
[No way...]
[Pretending to be a mannequin?]
- Where are you?
- We don't have much time.
We don't have much time.
They're all on the first floor right now.
We have to get as many
as we can during this round.
I know that there's no one in there,
so don't go in there.
- There's no one in there?
- No.
[Nervous and itchy mannequin.]
I think I'm going to go check
my previous hiding spot.
I doubt anyone would be hiding
in here, right?
There's no way someone could
be hiding here.
[Yes, someone could be hiding there...]
Hey, do you need any help?
Let's look around here for a bit.
Do you see anyone?
I don't think anyone's here.
Ha Ha?
[Kai shoving the boxes into an
empty spot that he sees.]
[Right onto Big-nosed Brother's head.]
Suk Jin.
- Hello, Suk Jin.
- Hello!
[Kai calls in the rest of his
team members.]
- Okay, okay.
- I've watched you on the show a lot.
[Big-nosed Brother in danger.]
Please!
[In the end... Ji Suk Jin is out!]
[Ji Suk Jin, out.
Ji Suk Jin, out.]
There's more of them than
us right now.
They're getting good at
finding our hiding spots.
[Giving up on his mannequin plan.
Giraffe moving onto a different plan.]
[Giraffe's new plan- Imitating his VJ.]
[Kwang Soo VJ's unsteady camera work.]
I see Kwang Soo.
[Anyone can clearly see
that it's Lee Kwang Soo.]
[VJ imitation plan fails.]
Guys!
We need to stop!
I have to stop this, I've been caught!
I should've just stayed where I was!
- Where are you?
- Hurry up! I'm on the second floor!
[Giraffe has been discovered!
All the members rushing in to help.]
Hurry up!
[Three EXO members on the chase
after the Giraffe.]
- I'm sorry, Kwang Soo.
- How much time is there left?
- There's not much time left.
No!
Out!
[Giraffe is pathetically ousted.]
- Picture of proof.
- How did this happen?
['The day we ousted Kwang Soo'.]
Hello, it's nice to meet you.
See you next time!
How can they oust me so
cheerfully like that?
[Lee Kwang Soo, out.
Lee Kwang Soo, out.]
It's time to make the exchange.
[Current count of survivors:
EXO- 5 vs. Running Man- 3]
Start.
[Time for Running Man's attack.]
[He probably didn't see me, right?]
[As if he saw a fleeing shadow,
Jae Suk slowly enters the market.]
[EXO's Lay is totally caught!]
Can you let me go just this once?
I seriously am a huge fan of yours.
Lay, I really don't have any other choice.
I can't let you go right now.
[Even though Jae Suk's flattered
that he's a fan...]
[A win is a win.]
I really like you too.
However... however, I don't have a choice.
[EXO's Lay- Out!]
- It's nice to meet you.
This is our second time meeting.
- Thank you for your hard work, Jae Suk.
- Lay.
You're the coolest guy ever.
Thanking me for my hard work?
- Seriously though, I really am a huge fan.
- Really?
- I've been watching you since X-Man days.
- Since X-Man?
[It seems as though Lay really has been
a fan of Jae Suk's for a very long time.]
- I'll see you later, Lay.
- Okay.
[Meanwhile, another member is watching the
scene from a fast food joint's security room.]
[Sees Jae Suk is coming near.]
[Quickly ducks into the storage room.]
[Caught at a dead end.]
I'm sorry.
[EXO's Lu Han- Out!]
[EXO Chen's desperate flee.]
[Runs straight into Ha Ha's barricade.]
[EXO's Chen- Out!]
[Quickly running away after witnessing all
his other members getting ousted.]
[Immediately discovered by Ha Ha.]
I really am sorry.
[EXO's Sehun- Out!]
[Under the attack of experienced RM members,
four EXO members are ousted instantly.]
Ji Hyo and Jae Suk are still left.
If I'm to survive to take them out,
I think I need to hide for right now.
[Too unsure to hide here...
too nervous to hide there.]
[His hesitation leads him to
getting caught by Blank Ji.]
Jae Suk, he's right here!
What do I do?
- Jae Suk, he's right here!
- He's here?
- What do I do?
- Why?
[Jae Suk and Ji Hyo vs. EXO's Kai.]
[Jae Suk trying to take him on
with the use of his strength.]
I ousted Jong Kook with my own hands.
- Do you remember?
- Of course, I remember.
- We even danced together before.
- Of course, I know that.
- I'm sorry, Jae Suk.
- Kai.
- I'm sorry, Kai.
- Jae Suk.
I have no other choice.
There's no need to feel sorry for this.
- Kai.
- Yes?
[I have to do whatever I can
to escape out of here.]
[Caught!]
I'm sorry, Kai.
[Blank Ji's ambush attack succeeds.]
[EXO's last remaining survivor, Kai- Out!]
[Running Man... wins!]
[We sincerely thank the EXO members for
their surprise appearance on the show!]
[Running Man wins the final mission
given to them by Ryu Hyun Jin!]
How many balls have you collected
throughout the day today?
- Two.
Show by a raise of your hand
who has the balls right now.
[Ha Ha and Ji Hyo each have a ball?]
It's actually in my pocket.
[Suk Jin's original ball...]
[First stolen by Ha Ha in the restaurant...]
[Then stolen by Jong Kook.]
- You gave it to me earlier.
- You said you just wanted to see it.
But I held onto it this whole time,
and it's in my possession.
Isn't that stealing?
This place is like a cave full of thieves!
[Just what are these balls to be used for?]
Since you won the final mission,
you will be given two additional balls.
[From having won the hide-and-go-seek mission,
they are given two additional signed balls.]
- Can you give me one, Ji Hyo?
- Ji Hyo has two! Can I have one?
Give me one, Ji Hyo.
Since I have two balls,
do I have to give one to someone else?
I've been so happy to have spent
the day with Ji Hyo today.
Since Ha Ha had his ball earlier today,
I'm going to give one to Kang Gary.
[That's our Monday Couple!
Ji Hyo gives her extra ball to Gary.]
Tra-it-ors, Cross!
[And the Traitors Club
is back together again.]
The three of you have no options
since you don't have a ball.
As for the other four members with a ball,
please look behind you.
- You will see doors marked with 'A' and 'B'.
- Yes.
One by one, choose which door you'd like,
and you may step through the doorway.
- Who'd like to go first?
- I'll go first.
[Gary volunteers to choose first.]
- This is all about chance anyway, right?
- Of course.
[Just what is behind those two doors?]
If Gary goes through the 'A' door,
then should I go through the other door?
[Gary chooses door, 'B'.]
[Jae Suk chooses the 'A' door.]
[Ji Hyo...]
[Chooses door 'A' like Jae Suk.]
[The last possession of the ball, Jong Kook,
also chooses the 'A' door.]
[Seoul 'S' hotel.]
- What is this?
- Why are we stuck here?
- Move out of the way.
- Why are you doing this to us?
[Oh my goodness... so sorry.]
- What are you trying to do to us?
- Is this a hidden camera or something?
- Are you okay?
- We could've gotten hurt.
That was so careless of you guys.
Since none of you possessed a ball,
you don't have any rights.
- You just need to stand by and watch.
- But we can still win.
- Sure, go ahead and win.
- Trai-tors- Cross!
- We're seriously going to win.
- Door 'A', please come on out.
[Just then...]
[Jae Suk, Jong Kook, and Ji Hyo walking out
of the 'A' door that they chose earlier.]
I love doing things like that!
Can we try doing it too?
We'd be really good at that.
- Go ahead, then. Try it.
- Seriously... let us show you how it's done.
- We'll show you.
- I can't believe you guys can't do it.
One, two, three.
- What the heck?
- Why isn't the door opening?
[I'd like to see you try.]
I haven't even made my entrance yet!
Why are you opening my door!
- Why are you opening Gary's door?
- It was because we couldn't open ours.
I should've been able to make a
grand entrance like that.
- Go back behind the 'B' door.
- I have to go back?
- What is going on here?
- Why did you have to ruin it for me?
Why are you trying to
ruin everything, Kwang Soo?
Can't you tell by seeing how the three
of you guys are grouped together?
- Of course, we see! We're going to win.
- We know exactly what's going to happen.
- You think you guys are the stars of this?
- Yes, we do!
We're going to make sure to win.
You guys are nothing but comic relief while
the A and B teams take a little break time.
- You're like the seasoning on top.
- We're the seasoning?
- How can you say that we're seasoning?
- That really was uncalled for.
You three rightfully gained your own
signed ball, correct?
Rightfully? He practically stole it from me,
and he's saying that it's rightfully his?
So this is what you call, 'rightfully'?
- Seriously.
- You all passed through door 'A'.
- Yes, we did.
- You all chose to go through door 'A'.
I will now introduce you to someone
whom you need to meet.
[One person who's waiting for these three
that walked through door 'A'.]
[He's... finally here.]
[The return of our hero!]
[Korean Monster]
[Ryu Hyun Jin]
[Monster pitcher who led his team to 14 wins
during his first year in the major leagues.]
[The pride of Republic of Korea that's caught
the attention of everyone worldwide.]
[The cutie pie with the bright smile whom the
RM cast met for the first time last year.]
[He has now returned as a legend.]
[Korean Monster]
[Ryu Hyun Jin with Running Man.]
[Welcome back, Ryu.]
- Get out!
- Out of the way!
Ryu Hyun Jin!
[A forceful greeting of the superstar
by punching him in the mouth.]
- What are you doing?
- How dare you lay your hand on Hyun Jin?
Don't you know that he's a
world famous star?
- What are you doing?
- What are you doing to a world famous star?
- Get away from him!
- C team must get back to your stand.
Ryu Hyun Jin!
[And... one man who is still
unable to see him.]
- Ryu Hyun Jin!
- You should be thankful to us.
Gary's starting to get depressed
back there.
How about a round of applause
for Ryu Hyun Jin?
Can you say a greeting
to our viewers?
Hello, my name is Ryu Hyun Jin.
Are you seriously just
going to say 'hi'?
It's been a year since I was
last on the show.
- Well, and I...
- Why don't you say it in English?
Very, very happy.
[His sense of humor is still the same.]
Keep it down!
You keep it down back there!
You will be on the same team as Korea's Ace
Ryu Hyun Jin for choosing the door 'A'.
- Seriously?
- He's going to be on our team?
But as you can see from the number
of members in the Traitors Club...
there are only three members to a team.
So out of the three members that
walked through the door
Ryu Hyun Jin has to choose the two members
that he'd liked to be teamed up with.
- You have to be good to me.
- You'd better just come here, Jong Kook.
So he can just ditch one of the members.
- First, you need to put your arms down.
- Why does he have to do that?
- I don't feel as bad anymore!
- He has to pick two of us?
Ryu Hyun Jin must first pick one member
that he wants to be teamed up with.
Choose your first team member by giving
that person a gentle hug from the back.
- Look at how confident Jae Suk looks.
- Pick only one person for now.
[Trepidation]
- Pick your first member.
- Please, Hyun Jin.
[Just who will Hyun Jin choose?]
Oh, it's Ji Hyo!
[After teasing Jae Suk first...]
[He selects Blank Ji!]
- What are you doing!
- There it is!
[This is fun!]
- You're doing great, Ryu Hyun Jin!
- What did you just say to me?
- What are you doing?
- Okay, Song Ji Hyo.
Song Ji Hyo can now go stand
right next to Ryu Hyun Jin.
[One more person left to choose.]
Okay, now your other team member.
One, two, three!
[Wow! He chooses Kkuk!]
Don't you think that you're
being too harsh?
- Wow! This is awesome!
- You really are being too harsh!
- Seriously? Me?
- Do you know how much I cheered you on?
Go away!
Wow, Ryu Hyun Jin!
I've been waiting for a whole year for this!
[Thus, Hyun Jin, Jong Kook,
and Ji Hyo make up a team.]
Okay, it's time for the 'B' team.
Please come out through the door.
- Gary, come on out!
- I wonder who'll come through the door!
Come out?
[First official entrance after whole
20 minutes after the filming started.]
- Hey, Brother!
- What's up?
Yeah, I'm right here.
I'm right here.
Your English has gotten much better.
It's now time for Team B to meet
their other team member.
[Just who's waiting to become the final
team member with Gary and Jae Suk?]
[She... has returned.]
[The never changing nation's first love.]
[Miss A's Suzy.]
- She's gotten even prettier.
- Suzy! Suzy!
- Bae Suzy! Bae Suzy!
- Suzy!
Don't touch her!
Don't touch her.
[Suzy's innocent beauty that they can
never seem to get used to.]
Hyun Jin.
- Hello.
Hyun Jin really likes Suzy.
He's a huge fan of hers.
[Hyun Jin is a fan of Suzy's.]
Didn't you say that she's
your ideal type?
He likes her!
[A huge smile that he can't
manage to hide.]
[Getting his expression back under control.]
- What are you doing?
- Don't try to act all cool.
- Don't do that.
- That's so not like you.
[He doesn't have a serious expression on his
face even when he's on the baseball mound.]
[A handshake between the two?]
[Why are you doing that to me?]
- Try it again.
- It's nice to meet you.
He likes her!
- Suzy's here.
- It's really hot out here.
[This is a side of Ryu Hyun Jin
we've never seen before.]
As you may already know, Ryu Hyun Jin
brought you all a gift from LA.
[A gift that Hyun Jin brought back
all the way from LA.]
[LA Dodgers player hats.]
- These? They're authentic.
- Authentic players hats?
- Really?
- Wow.
You get the biggest one since you look
like you have the biggest head.
- They're all different?
- There are different sizes.
[Touched by his thoughtful gift
that he brought back for them.]
This is a little big.
And I have a game day hat for Suzy.
[And even more of a thoughtful gift
just for her.]
Don't you think that you're being
too obvious with your favorites?
- Wow, this is nice.
- This is so nice.
- You must be so happy, Suzy.
- You got the best one.
- Thank you.
- It matches your outfit too.
It matches your outfit perfectly.
I tried to wear something that would match.
- What is that?
- I brought a marker.
- Sign!
- Can you sign this?
[Everyone crowding around Hyun Jin to
get his autograph on their hats.]
- I want to get his signature too.
- Sign this.
- Is this Kwang Soo's?
- I already have one at home.
Why are you signing it!
- Why would you sign it!
- You don't want me to sign it?
- I thought you wanted me to sign it.
- You really are so weird.
- What is your name?
- Why would you do that?
- It's Kwang Soo.
- Why are you even answering that?
[And he actually answers the question...]
- Here you go.
- Give it back.
What the heck!
He really did sign it!
Okay, today's race is...
It's Running Man's Late Fall MT Race.
We're going on an MT!
(MT=Overnight field trip.)
Ryu Hyun Jin, who's come back to visit us
on Running Man after being overseas...
and Suzy, who could almost be the eighth
member of our show, Running Man...
You will all be playing several different
MT games throughout the day today.
And through the succession of each
of these games...
you will be earning yourselves
the money you need for the MT.
[Fees for the MT will be handed out in cash
depending on the number of survivors.]
More money you earn throughout the day,
more advantageous it will be for you.
I hope that you all work hard to do your best,
and make some good memories in the process.
Please change into your team uniforms,
and gather in front of your team vehicles.
- Go!
[Time to build some memories-
Off on their Running Man MT trip!]
- That happened so long ago.
- I'm not like that anymore.
- You three together is bad news.
- Which car are we supposed to take?
[Huh? Only two cars?]
[Team Hyun Jin and Team Suzy
are to share one car.]
- Let us come with you, Suzy!
- Close the door on them, Suzy.
[And Team Traitors Club who must go
on their lonely way by themselves.]
I locked the door.
[Let us come with you!]
What's going on in here?
You guys are all coupled off.
[Now that they take a look,
they're all coupled off in the back.]
Then what does that make Jong Kook and I?
The chaperons?
- Wow, seriously.
- I like where I'm sitting.
Hey, Hyun Jin.
This really does feel like an MT trip.
[Exciting start to their MT trip.]
- I've never been on an MT before.
- Seriously?
[Today is Suzy's first MT trip!]
- What do you do on an MT?
- You drink.
You drink and play some games.
- That's right, there are some games too.
- And there's some flirting too.
You've seen some of Hyun Jin's game too,
haven't you, Suzy?
- Me?
- Yeah, you.
Be honest, Suzy.
- Be honest with us.
- You haven't seen any, have you?
- I haven't seen too many.
- Do you even know who he is?
- You at least know who he is, right?
- Of course, I know him.
- Isn't he kind of chubby and cute?
- Well, yes.
But I wouldn't call him chubby.
Rather than calling him chubby...
- Am I fat? Just fat?
- I'd say that he's like a giant...
No, you're not fat either.
I don't think Hyun Jin should
be sitting there right now.
- Why?
- He's not really talking with Suzy there.
What is it about Suzy that you
like so much?
- Excuse me?
- What is it about her that you like?
Is it because she's pretty?
- Oh... that must be the reason.
- That's what I thought.
- Come on and tell us.
- Why aren't you saying anything?
There's no reason to be embarrassed.
Do you know why?
If you think about it, pretty much
all the men out there like her.
But seriously, Suzy...
He's really a great guy.
Hyun Jin really is a great guy.
- He's one of the best guys I know.
- He really is a great guy.
I feel like I'm out on a blind date.
- You didn't know?
- This is a blind date.
- You seriously didn't know?
- You weren't aware?
- We set you two up on a blind date.
- You didn't know?
- You really didn't know?
- You knew about it, right, Hyun Jin?
- Yes.
Yes.
[That's the Ryu sense of humor.]
So Suzy was the only one who didn't know?
Who cares if you didn't know?
- It's okay.
- I'll just have to get to know him then.
[Even she herself is surprised at
what she just said.]
What is it that you want to know?
What is it?
- I'm curious to know too.
- Where's the other car?
Team C.
Ah, Team C?
Who cares where that car is.
[That's right...
we forgot about Team C...]
[Were you talking about us?]
[These guys are slowly...]
[Ugh...]
There's something I'm curious
about, Hyun Jin.
People are always coming up to you
to say something when you're on the mound.
- What are they saying to you?
- Especially that player, Uribe?
Just that with all the bases loaded,
in case I'm getting tired out...
[Ah... they purposely come to talk to the
pitcher to buy him some time to rest.]
So when I just keep saying yes,
Uribe tells me to say his name.
So when I say his name, Uribe,
he just starts to nod his head.
That's what you guys do?
So that's what you guys are doing?
- Yes, yes.
- What is my name?
Uribe!
The thing is that all Koreans tend to have
a certain preconceived notion about Hyun Jin.
They all think that Hyun Jin never gets
fazed by anything or anyone.
- But to be honest, you get nervous, right?
- Of course! I bet it's no joke out there.
What comes to my mind is the third game
in the playoff series.
[Ryu Hyun Jin's first foray into the
National Major Leagues Playoff Games.]
How did you honestly feel then?
- At that moment... I really was very nervous.
- Yeah, I bet.
And I think that's the hardest I ever threw
in all the games I've played in my life.
[Seventh inning with all the
bases loaded...]
[He strikes out his opposing team.]
[Aggressive pitch that won the love
and fervor of all the fans in the crowd.]
Didn't you pitch 95-96 miles per hour?
That's what I heard you pitched.
I've never thrown a ball that clocked
that kind of speed in my life before.
[Ryu Hyun Jin having thrown the ball
with every fiber of his being.]
But it was actually pretty disappointing
from our standpoint.
If the Dodgers had made it to Game Seven,
you would've been standing on that mound.
If that's the case, then I really might die.
Remember all the ragging that Hyun Jin
used to receive earlier on during the season?
- Yes, I used to get ragged on all the time.
- I bet that must've been shocking to you.
But I didn't know that it was for me.
- I didn't know they were ragging me on.
- That's too funny.
- They love you when you play well, right?
- When I do, then they go ecstatic.
- I have seen the crowd going ecstatic.
- I've seen the crowd going wild for you.
But seriously though...
I know that Gary's mentioned it too
but you really are good at batting too.
You've already seen my batting skills
when we played psychic baseball last year.
So you're telling us that psychic baseball
was a huge help to you, right?
- Then we've pretty much raised you.
- That's not a joke, Gary.
We really did something great here.
Running Man's psychic baseball really
helped Hyun Jin with his batting skills.
- I even hit a homerun.
- That's right, I remember.
[His skills allow him to even hit a homerun.]
Even though I'm sure...
that you don't remember
every single game...
I bet you remember the
National Leagues Championship.
- You know the game I'm talking about?
- Game three?
That game and the first time
I got the shut out in the game.
- That's right, the shut out!
- That was so awesome.
[May, 29, 2013-
A game against Los Angeles Angels.]
[His first shutout in the major leagues
during the ninth inning.]
[Shut out?]
You don't know what 'Shut out' is, do you?
I don't think Suzy knows what it is.
- What is it? I can learn as I go.
- That's right.
- Explain to her what it is.
- Shut out is...
[Hyun Jin to explain it to her
directly himself.]
We'll lay down some background music
for you while you and Suzy talk.
- 'Introduction to Baseball.'
- That's perfect.
[Suzy's introduction to baseball.]
It's when one pitcher pitches the whole game
from first through the ninth inning.
And the opposing team doesn't
score a single point the whole game.
The opposing team scores nothing.
They don't score anything.
It's basically when the other team
is shut out from scoring anything.
- That's right.
- The other team is made a fool.
- I don't know too much about baseball.
- Yes, the terminology may be confusing.
The pitcher is always the star
of any baseball game.
You don't really know much about
baseball either, Jong Kook.
- Hey.
- He doesn't know much either.
What are you talking about?
I love baseball.
Are you taking Suzy's side right now?
What is going on here!
[Introduction to baseball only getting
deeper and deeper in next week's episode.]
[The girl who knew nothing about baseball...]
[Meeting him is opening up her eyes
to the world of baseball?]
[When are we ever going to get there?]
How was the car ride?
- It was the best.
- The car ride was great.
- The car ride was so much fun.
- Wasn't it a lot of fun?
- It was so much fun, I can't even tell you.
- You should've seen how much we had too.
I don't think any of your car ride is
going to make it on the broadcast.
I think they're pretty much only going to
show our car ride on the broadcast.
What is that?
I see a bunch of basins with water.
[What are those water basins for?]
- Why are you doing that?
- Why are you interrupting them like that?
[The Grasshopper keeps on getting in
between Suzy and Hyun Jin.]
- Stop walking in between them!
- Why?
It's because I'm close to both
Suzy and Hyun Jin!
Don't you have any common sense?
What's with those two back there?
- What are those two doing?
- What are they doing?
It must be nice for them to film a show
and date at the same time like that.
Did you hear what Suzy said about them?
About being able to film and date like that?
[This is what Monday Couple is all about.]
What is this?
Wait, that's...
- What is that?
- I'm not good at holding my breath.
[Nine water basins out on the field?]
- Is everyone in a good mood?
- Yes.
- What is all this?
- We were in a good mood until now.
All my team members, come over here.
We're going to play a game that
everyone likes to play on an MT trip.
If you do a good job on this game,
you can earn yourselves your MT fee.
- Really?
- Okay, let's do this.
Even if we were to die today,
we're going to die winning this.
[Making a vow of death?]
[The Traitors Club putting their lives
on the line to win the game?]
The game you'll all be playing is called,
'Noonchi Game'.
What is that?
- Is that where we count and watch each other?
- Gauging others' reactions?
[That's right, that's the game.]
You all will dunk your faces
in the basin full of water.
No one plays this game while
submerged under water like that.
[Kicking it up a notch
for the entertainment level.]
I swear this to you all right now,
but I'm going to win this game.
- I'm telling you right now that I'm going to.
- No, I'm going to win this game.
- You go ahead and try it.
- You can't say 'One', can you?
He just said that the best thing to do
is to last as long as you can underwater.
[Not seeming to really understand the rules.]
Suzy is going to explain the rules
of the game to Hyun Jin.
Go ahead and explain the
game rules for us.
- So we have to time when we lift our heads.
- You're doing this on purpose, aren't you?
[Giraffe not wanting to see things
blossom between Suzy and Hyun Jin.]
Suzy's talking right now!
[Giraffe not being able to pick up
what's going on between the two.]
- What are you saying?
- Can't you tell what's going on?
Don't you think that you're being
too harsh with your words right now?
So the first thing you do
is to dunk your head underwater.
- And once you do...
- Stare into his eyes while you talk to him.
Stare into his eyes while
you talk to him.
- Hyun Jin is looking at you right now.
- You're all embarrassing me.
[Learned how to make eye contact with
people during his stay in America.]
So the thing is...
[Wow... look at that guy!]
- Hey, go away!
- Stay out of this!
So what else?
We dunk our heads, and then what?
We have to dunk our heads,
and gauge what others are doing.
Then people start to lift their heads
one by one.
Two people can't lift up their heads
at the same time though.
[Clueless Hyuk cutting in front
of the camera screen again.]
So the team with a member who lasts
the longest underwater will win the game.
Suzy's not very good at
explaining things.
I didn't really get
what she was saying either.
We'll start at the sound of my whistle.
I'll blow the whistle once
everyone has their faces underwater.
Are we going on the count of one, or one?
[Huh?]
- Either way.
- It's the same thing!
One! One!
One, two, three!
I just wanted to clarify how he was
going to say 'one'.
There could be a lot of
confusion over that.
Let's just go on one, okay?
[Everyone preparing to submerge their heads
on the count of one.]
Ready.
You have to have your faces submerged
before I blow my whistle.
You have to put your face underwater.
- Your face has to be underwater.
- It is underwater!
- Gary's face isn't underwater.
- Just hurry up and blow!
- Why aren't you doing it?
- Let's all play honestly.
Let's all dunk our faces fairly.
I'll blow the whistle when you dunk your
faces and that's when the game will start.
Ready, set, go!
[Start!]
One!
[Big-nose and Ha Ha.]
Someone's out, right?
- Someone's out, right?
- Why?
[Two members of Traitors Club ousted
in the first round of the game.]
Ji Suk Jin and Ha Ha are out.
- What are you talking about?
- How can we be out already?
- Just give us one more chance!
- Please!
[Begging desperately.]
- Just give us one break.
- We can't be ousted already.
Why do we even have this team
on the show today?
[Traitors Team taking it upon themselves
to weed out all the bad seeds.]
- Okay, if Ryu Hyun Jin will allow it.
- Hyun Jin!
- Please let us off the hook just this once.
No, you can't do that.
You're out.
Rules are rules.
We didn't even say a single word to
each other in the car either!
Rules are meant to be broken!
- We want to be on the show too!
- Please just give us a break!
- Don't you even feel bad for us?
- Then beat Hyun Jin in rock-paper-scissors.
- Okay, fine. I'll beat him.
- You just have to beat him.
- Okay.
- Rock-paper-scissors.
Rock-paper-scissors!
[Big-nosed Brother loses.]
- What is this?
- Ha Ha too.
Rock-paper-scissors!
[Oh! Ha Ha wins!]
Thank you!
Okay, disqualified players
must go off to the left.
- I'm going to win, Suk Jin, so don't worry.
- Okay, win it!
Okay, everyone dunk your faces in.
Ready, set, go.
[Survivors must dunk their faces back in.]
[Noonchi game-Start.]
[Hyun Jin passes.]
- Two!
- Three!
[Oh no! Jae Suk and Gary
both shout out 'Three'!]
Yoo Jae Suk, and Kang Gary are out.
[Jae Suk and Gary ousted simultaneously.]
The person who said it first
should be disqualified.
- It should be the first person who said it.
- Suzy is left all on her own now.
No, both of you are disqualified. This is
a game that everyone knows how to play.
- But Ha Ha is still alive.
- Because he used the 'Hyun Jin' chance card.
- Then let Gary live.
- I'm using the Song Ji Hyo chance card.
Why are you saying my name
all of a sudden?
[At this rate, they're going to spout off
the names of everyone else that they know.]
- Just let Gary live.
- No, that's not right.
Then Ha Ha should be ousted too!
- Rules are rules!
- No, I escaped being eliminated.
[Everyone out! Disgruntled Jae Suk wanting
to drag everyone down.]
Why are you trying to drag me down too?
- I should've just stayed underwater.
- Everyone out!
[Jae Suk and Gary of Team Suzy are out!]
- No!
- That's too bad.
[Six players left remaining.]
- You have to do good, Suzy!
- Don't lift up your head, Kwang Soo.
- He says not to lift up his head.
- No, don't lift up your head.
You have to keep a close eye on Ha Ha.
[Both are disqualified.]
[What a pathetic pair...]
We have to go around and do it.
- I tried to do it.
- We have four people left.
[Start]
Have to say one.
- One!
- Two!
One! Two! Three!
Eliminated!
You're eliminated.
- You're out!
- Who was that?
Who was it?
Was it you?
- You're out.
- It was you.
You're still out.
So he's out!
Okay there are three people left.
This could be the definitive round.
The team of whoever is left wins.
Ready, go.
[Start!]
Suzy won!
- You won!
- Really?
Why did you do that?
You should have held it in.
Oh really.
Now for the second round.
The team who gets two points first wins.
- Sounds good.
- Fighting!
Fighting!
Ready, set, go!
Set, go!
One!
Two!
Okay, okay.
I did well, right?
- Sure he did...
- Five!
- Six!
- Okay!
It's six? Who did six?
Just let it go.
- One more time, and we're done.
- It's a relief. We almost got caught.
Let's do it like this. I'll call out one.
So don't call it out.
- Okay, okay.
- I'm going to call out one.
I'll do two.
So when I call out two,
we do two.
- I'm three. I'm three.
- I'm calling out two.
One, two, three.
You're a traitor.
It's not possible otherwise.
I told you guys. I'm doing one.
Okay, then let's try
to get these two out.
That's what I'm planning to do.
- Is everyone ready?
- Yes!
Okay. Ready, set, go!
- One! Two!
- Three!
Wait, I never blew the whistle.
Why did you do that?
That was good.
Then let's do two, three, four.
Sounds good.
Let's practice.
Set, go.
- One!
- Two, three!
Don't get nervous.
Ready. Get ready.
Go!
- One!
- Two! Ack!
They never blew the whistle!
We're sorry Hyun Jin.
We're really sorry.
You must have been very mad.
- This was too...
- So funny.
Ready...
Set, go!
One!
Hyun Jin.
Why aren't you getting mad?
It's okay, it's okay.
This is too much.
- I'm sorry.
- It happens.
- I'm sorry, sorry.
- Okay. Ready...
Set...
- One!
- Two!
Three!
- One!
- Two!
Three!
- One!
- Two!
Three!
Four!
Suk Jin and Hyun Jin eliminated!
Why am I eliminated?
You and Hyun Jin said four.
Hyun Jin, you and I think alike.
Okay, eliminate the blue team!
- Gary. Just go one, two, three.
- Okay, okay.
One, two, three.
- Sounds good.
- Okay!
- One at a time!
- I'm really going to shout out one!
Everyone get ready.
Start!
One!
Three!
[What the...]
One!
[Ah! Already one?]
Three!
Four!
Same time! They did it
at the same time!
- They did it at the same time.
- What are you guys doing?
Only one person has to die.
- Hey then...
- Jae Suk's team wins.
That was too easy.
- You were supposed to say one.
- You didn't either.
Hey, why can't you use your heads?
The rankings. Yellow team first place.
Red team second place. Blue team third place.
We'll do better the next game.
- We're going to do graded payment now.
- I understand.
We're going to move onto
the next game site.
Yes, I understand.
Let's go!
The team without a female member.
Lee Kwang Soo's team.
[A wig?]
This is rare hair.
- It's so you.
- You have to wear it.
Make up would suit you too.
[Transforms into Lady Kwang Ja]
Is this a punishment?
What do you mean punishment?
This is how I make my living!
Our next game is
Protect the Queen Dodgeball.
Queen.
- Let's go over there.
- Please take your positions.
If you stand there,
you can't see anything.
- Watch out for the legs.
- The biggest kid is after us.
- Gary you do the running.
- Watch out for Jong Kook.
Get ready.
Come stand here.
You did very well.
Lady Kwang Ja got the ball?
It's okay if we get hit, right?
At least one of us can get out.
Then it doesn't really matter.
- Is that our ball?
- It's our ball.
Okay.
[Hyun Jin has the ball!]
I almost forgot he was a
baseball player.
He throws up to 150km.
[Suk Jin is out!]
Your skills are amazing.
That arm.
He really is different.
Wow Hyun Jin. I almost forgot
you were a baseball player.
What is this?
He's out! Out, out, out!
Out, out, out!
The camera!
The camera doesn't matter right now.
[Steal!]
[Lady Kwang Ja in danger.]
[Member of the Traitor Club out!]
Get out, get out!
Red team, get out!
What's wrong with that guy?
Ryu Hyun Jin is amazing
with a ball!
You can't attack, but you can
pass from the outside.
Either catch it or avoid it.
Our team has to win.
I'm scared.
Pass it to me!
Very good, very good.
You're useless when
it comes to throwing!
You think you could have
done better?
Give us the ball.
I can choose who to give it to?
I've always been a fan of yours.
What a joke.
You're manipulating me.
I'm giving it to them!
What is this?
Give it to us!
[Gary out!]
- I can still attack.
- I did well, right?
It was strong, but accurate.
[Ryu Hyun Ji has the ball again.]
Hyun Jin, what are you doing?
[Penetrates Jae Suk's blocking.]
[Accurately hits Queen Suzy.]
[Worried right away.]
Are you okay?
- Seriously.
- Is this a love line or not?
You know that it's not possible.
This is a practice game.
- Blue team has won.
- You should have blocked it.
You should have blocked it.
He said it like a lead actor.
'Are you okay?'
Are you okay?
He was very cool.
- Hyun Jin is a beast.
- He's scary.
- Ryu Hyun Jin's the best with a ball.
- We haven't caught the ball.
This time, if a team gets out,
they can still attack.
But you can only help one team.
Get ready.
[Yoo Hyuk out!]
Seriously! I can still help,
so don't worry.
Hyun Jin. Let's get them out first.
They're unbeatable.
That's right.
That's right!
Kwang Soo got hit!
[Again passes through the guards
and gets to Lady Kwang Ja's leg.]
Kwang Soo got hit!
[The Traitors Club is out!]
- Why are you so scary?
- Hold on.
How did you hit me?
We're attacking this team!
- We were about to help you.
- We'll help.
- You guys are fine.
- But we're in last place.
But you're going to win.
- Hyun Jin is really...
- He's really scary.
This is not the dodgeball
we're used to.
What? What's wrong?
Good job.
If you guys make a ruckus,
I'll throw this way.
You guys will be dead.
You'll hit the camera!
He's really scary.
I'm scared.
What's wrong?
Come here, come here.
[Kkuk is out!]
He's a strong player though.
Block her, block her.
- Turn, turn!
- Kwang Soo!
[Kwang Ja attacks]
Your older sister will scold you!
Your older sister!
Good for you.
Hold on, time out.
- Ji Hyo, I'm sorry.
- Hyun Jin, you should have gone out first.
I can't see well because of the sun.
Gary come back!
He's rolling away!
Just throw it now.
Be gentle!
This is not the dodgeball we're used to.
Wow, he's really strong.
[Ji Hyo's in danger!]
What are you doing?
They're out?
[Suzy's team wins!]
Very good!
Good game, good game.
We'll help you out.
We can do it.
If either the blue or yellow
team wins, it's victory.
[Suzy's team is eventually all out]
Get out. What are you doing?
I said get out!
Hyun Jin, it's yours!
He's coming this way.
[Hits the target!]
[Hyun Jin's Amazing Attack!]
[Just one gap.]
[Makes it accurately through!]
[This is the power of
the nation's best pitcher.]
- What are you guys doing?
- That was amazing.
Those are amazing skills.
The winner of dodgeball
is the blue team.
Yellow team is second place.
Red team is third place.
It's not as bad as you think.
We're suggesting the next game
to be couple's dodgeball.
Ryu Hyun Jin and Suzy is one team.
- Gary and Ji Hyo is another pair.
- Hold on.
Wait, what about us?
Why? Just let them do it together.
Then put Kwang Ja
and Jae Suk together.
Us too. We'll be a team too, okay?
Let's do this!
Will bonus points be awarded?
We'll provide additional provisions.
We'll definitely win.
Hyun Jin, you have to protect her well.
It's not just about the ball.
I can't see anything.
Get ready.
Kwang Ja. Kwang Ja!
Why does the girl have the ball?
Kwang Ja!
Throw it over there.
I've got the ball!
Be careful!
Time out! Time, time, time!
What are you doing?
Why are you avoiding him?
Why are you running away?
Hyun Jin throws 150 km.
Kwang Ja couple. This is a warning.
- We understand.
- What are you doing?
[Who's protecting who?]
[I don't want to protect you.]
[You get hit by that dodgeball.]
Wait!
Wait, we were on the floor!
- Okay, it doesn't count?
- What do you mean? We're out!
We're out.
I don't love him enough
to risk my life to protect him.
Then why are you meeting me?
Give me all the designer
bags you bought me!
- Do you want to throw it?
- Hyun Jin, over here.
Hyun Jin, Jae Suk's right here.
Hold on, hold on.
I can't see anything.
That's it Kwang Ja.
Throw it!
- Throw it!
- What a joke.
Get out.
You useless man.
Get out!
Get lost.
- You throw it!
- Why? After all these years...
Kwang Ja...
Let's just break up
if you're going to be this way.
I'll go for that team.
If we go for this team,
we're over.
If you throw it, and we
catch it, you're out.
What are you doing?
[Hits the target!]
Are you okay?
You're okay, you're okay.
Lower your head more.
Jae Suk, I'm in danger.
What are you doing?
Why are you dragging
me towards him?
Jae Suk!
[Kwang Ja couple, out!]
Let's wrap up the game.
He's too fast.
You two!
It just ended up that way!
You don't have to be
hugging like that.
Why did he hold me like this...
- You don't have to hold each other.
- Why did you hold me like that?
You're the one who leaned in.
Hyun Jin, you're not good
at catching big balls.
Just good at catching small balls.
I hit her!
Kwang Ja's the best.
The love that Kwang Ja ended.
I'm sorry. I...
Kwang Ja, how could you end it?
I didn't mean to.
- Something's strange.
- What happened?
- What just happened?
- What did we just do?
The yellow team won the first game.
Red team gets second place.
Blue team gets third.
Blue team wins dodgeball.
It's money.
Yellow team is in second.
We'll give Ryu Hyun Jin and Kim Jong Kook
bonuses for couple dodgeball.
Wait hold on.
It's only W1000.
It's like chump change for
elementary school students.
- What are you giving us?
- I'm sorry.
- Hold onto this.
- This is W1000.
- Please give us W500.
- Just W100.
You all got your MT allowance.
Each team has to distribute
the money amongst themselves.
You can each have
W10,000 and W20,000.
Suzy gets a bit more.
Okay, now we'll go to have dinner.
[Hyun Jin's eyes change
at the mention of dinner.]
[Ryu-mes Bond Ryu Hyun Jin.]
Finish dinner and have everyone
at the dinner table.
[9 a.m. Seoul S Hotel]
[The PD seems to be looking
for someone inside.]
[Someone is still not awake.]
[It is... Ryu Hyun Jin?]
I have come to give you a command.
You will be shooting with the Running
Man members in an hour.
Yes.
By myself?
[Ryu Hyun Jin. You are a spy!]
[Secretly eliminate the Running Man team
and their special guest from dinner.]
Ryu Hyun Jin, today you are a spy.
It is you against the seven
Running Man members.
Including the special guest,
there are eight people you must eliminate.
The concept of today's race
will be a late fall MT.
The highlight of the MT is dinner time.
That is when you make your move.
Your special weapon...
Here you go.
Is it a water gun?
[Inside... as expected...
water guns!]
Wait. Is this a water gun too?
Choose one of these special solutions.
They will go into your water guns.
Pick the one you think
will stand out the least.
[The sky blue solution]
Now choose a water gun.
I'll do this one.
A turtle.
[A bit small for him...]
You have chosen the turtle
water gun and solution.
You must secretly shoot the Running Man
members' name tags to get them out.
[Best mission imaginable.]
- Are you confident?
- Yes.
I can always wear my poker face.
I can do this.
- You can't get caught.
- Of course. I won't.
[Can Ryu Hyun Jin do it?]
There's something you always
do with a water gun.
Strike a pose for the camera.
[Korean Monster.
His mission starts now.]
[5:30 p.m. Kyung Ki Do
Gwang Ju's 'H' Village]
Let's get out!
Is this a place to cook?
[A cooking set up awaits the members
on the front patio.]
Let's start.
I'm not bad at cooking.
It's okay. Jae Suk's good at cooking.
It's time for dinner.
It's the highlight of MT.
- You're hungry, right?
- Yes!
So we have prepared
the MT cooking battle.
A cooking battle?
The MT cooking battle.
There's going to be an MT cooking battle.
You have from when the battle starts
to when the eight finish and sit down to eat.
If you can get all of them
out by then, you win.
If the members catch you in the act
before then, the members win.
It's the MT cooking battle.
Is it really the highlight
of MT to cook?
Isn't a campfire the highlight?
A campfire?
When we did MT, we were
so tired we just ordered in.
We don't usually cook like this.
- We'll give you two hours.
- Who are the judges?
- We'll tell you.
- I'm sorry.
I'm hungry.
You will eat the food you cook.
Then you will vote and the dish with
the highest number of votes will win.
We could make mandoo.
We could fry the mandoo.
If you make mandoo,
you'll have to fold it from scratch.
You're kidding me!
If we're using cow, do we need
to catch it ourselves?
Let's catch it.
So we make the mandoo
wrap from scratch, too?
If we're making curry,
do we have to go to India?
- Do we?
- Let's go together.
- What are you saying?
- I thought she wanted to go together.
Curry would be nice.
[Everyone's laughing,
but he's keeping poker face.]
Jjajang would be nice.
Jjajang? They're making curry
so why bother?
Why are you over here?
Leave us alone.
You're annoying us.
We should talk about it.
Who's going to the market?
Jae Suk's going to the market?
But you have to write down
what we need.
Stay here and play with Suzy.
I'll go.
- No, no.
- I'll go.
[Nervous Hyun Jin.
Will he be able to do well?]
Thank you.
Hello.
Hurry let's get on.
- Hey kid!
- What?
You want to die?
Oink, oink, oink, oink.
Is the supermarket far?
[How will he shoot them
with the water gun?]
How to make curry deliciously.
Did you cook for yourself
when you were in America?
- You didn't?
- Hyun Jin always bought food.
But how did you have dinner?
My parents were there.
What do you want
to eat most? Curry?
I want to eat ddukbokgi,
soondae, and oh daeng.
[But I have something
more urgent to tend to...]
The sweet potatoes will be really good.
You could skewer them
and roast them.
Salted potatoes would
be really good too.
Oh my god.
Suzy have you had boppki?
(Korean sugar cookies)
Boppki?
I've made it before.
I made it in front of the school.
- You do things like that these days?
- Of course.
What do we do?
We need sugar for this.
We just need two of them.
It's all going to go in.
[Doubtful...]
You're a difficult child, aren't you?
She's fussy.
- Go over and help him.
- Nevermind.
[Meanwhile...]
I heard Puig is a real troublemaker.
He never stays still.
I think you're worse.
I heard Puig is really mischievous.
I learn all my mischievousness
from the other players.
All their arms are this big.
- Look at Puig's body.
- Steamed buns, mandoo...
Hyun Jin's body too.
What are you doing right now?
Steamed buns, mandoo...
[Must focus on spy mission.]
[Finally arrives at the market.]
- Let's skip the ddukbokgi.
- Sure, sure. Hyun Jin!
Let's eat this.
These are fishcakes!
Hello!
Ma'am. How much is this?
- Three for W1000.
- Oh, that's perfect.
- Can we have one?
- Of course, of course.
Are you paying for this Jae Suk?
Thanks Jae Suk.
Sure, it's on me.
Oh, it's so good!
Hyun Jin, are you getting
broth for us?
He has such good manners.
This warm broth is so nice.
It's the best.
Hyun Jin, don't you miss this?
You can't have stuff like this
in America.
Fishcake broth is perfect
for chilly weather.
Oh yeah. Suzy said she
wanted goldfish cake.
Did she?
- When we come back out.
- We'll wrap some up for her.
- I'll wrap it up for you.
- Thank you.
Thanks again ma'am.
- Where are you going?
- Hyun Jin where are you going?
To eat ddukbokgi.
We'll have that later.
We'll buy it. There are
stands everywhere.
Oh, here's what we need.
We need ricecake and pickled radish.
- Onions.
- Oh ddukbokkgi. Very good.
Do you have the meat
that goes into curry?
One piece is 600 grams?
Is that enough?
What are you doing?
- Curry.
- Of course.
We need tenderloin.
Beef tenderloin.
Beef tenderloin?
You don't have any?
Tenderloin.
Don't have any?
This, this. Give me this,
what is this?
Yes, this please.
This please.
[Target fixed!]
Yes, for ddukbokgi.
[He aimed well enough.]
[But he held it backwards
and shot his finger.]
It's for ddukbokgi.
[Spy Hyun Jin must be nervous!
What an error!]
[What do I do?]
- Onions.
- Are you already done?
No.
I shot it backwards.
Ma'am, where's the fish?
Ma'am, can I have some anchovy?
[One more time.]
Kimchi, kimchi.
Is this it?
- This is, this is fine.
- Which one? This one?
[Successfully hits Ha Ha's name tag.]
Jae Suk, do we need
to buy the onions?
Do we need these onions?
- Do onions go into curry?
- I'm trying to make it chunky.
You need the other onion.
[Spy Hyun Jin. Of all 8 members,
targets only Ha Ha.]
[Meanwhile...]
- Oh very good.
- Just like that.
This is it.
Put it here.
It's done, it's done!
- Put it here.
- It's boppki!
Put it here.
Wow! We did it!
Did you do it well?
- Wow, this is well done.
- Put it like this.
R for Running Man.
It's not working.
- Wow, the smell.
- This is awesome.
- Awesome!
- Hurry, we have to put it here.
You have to put it here.
- Did you make a rose?
- No I was just trying to get it off.
[Suk Jin's is a bit...]
[A pretty sugar cookie rose.]
Suk Jin, we can't eat this.
- We can eat it.
- You can't eat it.
- Eat it.
- Of course I can eat it.
Is it okay?
Hey, it's really good.
This is really good.
It's been a while since
I've had ddukbokgi like this.
I feel better.
- Good right?
- Really good.
Good, right Hyun Jin?
- But what do we do...
- How are you going to eat later?
I'm worried about that to.
- I'm really full.
- We won't be able to eat later.
[I still have to shoot Jae Suk.]
We're in big trouble.
I think I ate too much.
I'm full.
Thank you ma'am!
Goodbye.
Since Hyun Jin has to give
Suzy the goldfish cake...
Okay, you hold onto it.
You're going to eat more?
You said it was for Suzy.
But I really am full.
- What should we do?
- Wipe your mouth.
Wipe our mouths.
Seriously, where are they?
What are they doing?
- Why aren't they here?
- What have they been doing?
Stop eating.
What are you doing?
You're supposed to eat it bit by bit.
He put the whole thing in his mouth.
Just eat it all.
Wow. Is he an idiot?
- Where are they...
- Oh they're coming.
What took them so long
to get just that?
That's what took so long?
Let me inspect your mouths.
Let me smell your breath.
- There was a lot of traffic.
- Be honest.
You ate, right?
We bought stuff for us
to eat together.
- Come here.
- This is driving me crazy.
- Open your mouth.
- Really.
I can smell the grease from here.
Hyun Jin, come over here.
Let me go, let me go!
Ah, it hurts!
This is soondae?
Let's get dalgona ready for them.
- Let's get some Dalgona.
- Hyun Jin, come here.
Hyun Jin. Come here.
It's boppki.
Here you go.
He ate it all.
- What did you eat?
- I didn't have anything.
- It's all over your teeth.
- I really didn't have anything.
- There was no time.
- We can smell the grease.
- Yeah I smell the grease.
- What is that smell?
- Be honest.
- We had one goldfish cake.
We smell like grease because
we bought all this.
We were buying this.
You don't even eat so
why are you upset?
- Did you have fishcake?
- Yes!
We had fishcake broth.
Seriously.
- There's soda in here.
- He has something there.
He's hiding something there.
- What is it?
- It's Suzy's.
- Suzy, goldfish cakes.
- Get out of the way!
Get out of the way!
Do it again.
Oh, this warm moment.
What, what?
- What?
- You should get in the shot.
Should I put it back in?
Put it back in.
- Let's do it again.
- Okay, do over. No good.
Like it's the first time.
Suzy, make it happen.
Hey Hyun Jin, give it to her.
Suzy, I got you goldfish cakes.
Oh my...
Use the first version.
The first version.
This is really too much Suzy.
Suzy, such a player.
Suzy, you really always
ask for goldfish cake.
I really wanted some. Wow.
Wow.
- We need to have dinner, but you're eating.
- You set the table already?
Let me have some.
Do you eat fishcake?
There's a lot he doesn't eat.
This is great.
Everyone, it's not time to eat yet.
You've been told that this
is the MT cooking battle.
We have no desire
to do that kind of battle.
Why do we need to battle for dinner?
- This is just a snack.
- This right here is an MT.
Everyone gathers around and enjoys.
Seriously.
- Have some goldfish cake.
- I had some already.
No.
This is something you eat
when you're younger.
What are you saying?
- What did I say?
- Are you in your right mind?
Just wash one side, right?
[He'll have to slowly resume
his spy mission.]
Let's go the two of us.
[What a stroke of luck.]
[He can get Mr. Capable.]
Is this the only faucet?
There's another one.
- Where?
- It's in the back.
Then go over there.
Wow, it's water.
Do you know how to wash this?
But it doesn't matter if you
wash these carrots.
You still have to wash it.
What are you talking about?
Look at this.
Pre-washed carrots.
Really? I still think you
have to wash it.
If you bought it,
you should be telling me.
- Look. Pre-washed carrots.
- Okay, fine.
Over there.
Why do you use salt
for hard-boiled eggs?
Suzy, that's ours.
[No one's listening.]
We have to this well.
So that the shell peels well.
Thanks, you were listening.
Everyone, it seems no one
is listening to me, right?
But still...
Hey, it really seems like
an MT with you here.
It really seems like
an MT with Suzy here.
What are you doing?
[Meanwhile...]
Is this okay?
What are you doing here instead of
pitching for the Major Leagues?
Why? It's fun.
- I wanted to do things like this.
- Really?
Okay, that's fine.
Just one more left.
Did you peel this well?
You can peel this too.
I'll do the potatoes.
Be honest. What did
you eat with them?
What did you eat?
- Fishcakes.
- No really.
- Goldfish cakes.
- There's a reason I keep asking...
The reason I keep asking...
You should have bought more to eat.
And we needed more time to cook.
- And some more meat.
- There was nothing like that.
They would have given it to you.
They totally would have.
Just like this. Nice.
Jong Kook, we need to wrap up.
Very good Hyun Jin.
Why are you making me do everything?
You're closer to this than I am.
Very good. Don't spill it.
Let's go!
[Spy Hyun Jin hits two out of eight
Running Man members. Jong Kook hit!]
I'll cut the cabbage kind of big.
We're going to make ddukbokkgi broth.
- Why are you taking that?
- I'm just borrowing it.
- Let me just borrow it.
- We need that.
We're in the same boat here.
We're part of the same MT class.
- What class are you?
- Me?
- I'm the Broadcasting Entertainment class.
- Broadcasting entertainment.
I'm in the law school class.
What did you say?
- What's the first amendment?
- I'm not telling you.
I'm sorry, but are you
using all three fires?
That's right.
This is ridiculous.
Use that.
Wow, I really... I really
can't believe this.
Just like this.
This is going to turn out really well.
Oh, it's here.
- Jong Kook. Seriously!
- Why?
He keeps bossing me around.
What do you mean?
I did everything.
And did you wash the potatoes?
We need a big pot.
[Just six more left.]
- Let it boil.
- Why are you putting in so much dashima?
It's not that much.
Too fishy to eat.
How is this fishy?
- You put in too much.
- Put in more water.
[It does seem like there's too much.]
[Puts it into the Traitor team's pot.]
I put some dashima in.
I'll do it here.
- It's going to be so fishy.
- Just you taste it.
This smells amazing.
The broth is amazing.
This much will be perfect.
[Doesn't notice the added dashima.]
Can we pick it with our hands?
[Hyun Jin gets ready to attack.]
Don't we have to pick this well?
We can pick it well.
Thanks.
[Kwang Soo's name tag hit!]
[Spy Hyun Jin. Three out of the eight
Running Man members done. Kwang Soo hit!]
Where the onion?
There's the onion!
Where?
There are pumpkins here too.
[Acts as if he's joking around.]
Suzy, you said you need young radish.
- I want greens.
- Greens? What will you do with that?
I'll think of it later.
I just want to pick some for now.
You have no idea, huh?
What will you do with the onions?
- We're going to make ramen...
- That's so unimaginative.
You should be talking.
You didn't even hear me out.
It's a radish!
A young radish.
I was surprised.
I didn't know it looked like this.
It looks really pretty.
You want this, right Suzy?
How do you get young radish?
They're veggies.
- Get some greens.
- Are you going to do something with that?
You keep avoiding Suzy.
You have to leave for me
to play with Suzy.
- You want me to leave?
- Yeah.
So you're leaving?
I was going to leave anyway.
I don't think so.
There are no plump ones.
Young radish...
Where did you get the ones
from before?
- I didn't get it. Kwang Soo did.
- But how?
Suzy.
- Suzy.
- Yes?
We need more young radishes.
[Target fixed.]
Young radish?
[Suzy's name tag hit!]
[The special solution hit quite accurately.]
We need more young radishes.
Young radishes?
But that's another team?
No, we need it for everyone.
- We need more radishes.
- Why get more radishes?
We won't even eat it.
Seriously...
I'm just trying to feed you!
So frustrating!
He seems upset.
[Spy Hyung Jin. Four out of eight
Running Man members done. Suzy hit!]
How many potatoes do we need?
We're making ddukbokgi broth.
What are you doing here?
- It's ours to eat.
- It's that good.
Mister. Either eat it or put it back.
- Either eat it or not.
- Do you want some?
Seriously...
Be honest. It tastes good.
Good, right?
It's just that the fishcake is good.
There's a reason this broth is so good.
- Now Gary...
- Potatoes!
- Where were you?
- You have something for us?
Potatoes and onions.
Young radish and onions.
We picked it ourselves.
What should we do with all this?
Young radish bibimbap.
Young radish bibimbap?
With raw radish?
The red team said
they needed red pepper paste.
- There's some in the pantry.
- We're done.
So if anyone needs sauce....
please head out together.
- Where do we go?
- Get some for us.
Hey, just go with us.
Oh seriously.
- Just do it for us.
- Get it yourself.
[Silently follows as soon
as Suk Jin leaves.]
[One, two...]
[I'll be right back...]
Wow, this is totally...
This is just like ancient times.
Red pepper paste.
What kind of sauce do you need?
We need half-half.
Half red pepper paste, half samjang.
- What are you doing?
- What? Is it good?
Here you go. Have some.
Where's the samjang?
What are you making?
Are you making curry?
What is this?
[People will notice his vest.]
Okay! Let's go!
Wow, this is amazing.
What are you guys making?
Red pepper paste.
No, what are you making...
I said red pepper paste.
The red pepper paste is amazing!
[His vest is clean now.]
This should be enough.
[Spy Hyun Jin. Five out of eight
Running Man members done. Suk Jin hit!]
[All that's left is...]
[Gary]
[Ji Hyo]
[Jae Suk]
[He can't leave again.]
[What to do?]
Why are you adding packaged flavors?
It'll be amazing.
Just you try it.
- It'll be amazing.
- Seriously.
Hey Gary!
Come try this.
Wow, this is really awesome.
This is unbelievable.
Try some.
I told you!
This is amazing stuff.
[Secretly chomps on a boiled egg.]
[It's hot.]
So frustrating. Just eat it.
There! You greedy pig!
It's all ready.
It's boiling now.
Just watch it boil.
Do you need more eggs?
How many?
[Gary doesn't see it!]
[But too much water in the droplet.]
[If it drips he'll get caught.]
- It seems to be fine.
- Hey what's this?
[Looks like it will drip any time soon.]
Is this much okay?
Does it need more onions?
I only have one onion.
Should I put in more?
- I'll put in one more.
- Yeah one more is good.
[Spy Hyun Jin. Six out of eight
Running Man members done. Jae Suk hit!]
Where's the octopus?
[Two people left.]
[Gary]
[Ji Hyo]
[More nervous because
there's not much time left.]
Where's the octopus?
I don't know.
Gary.
Here it is.
Gary, bring it.
Put it all in?
Hold on.
[Changes scenes]
- Gary.
- Huh?
Why is this here?
[Gary's name tag hit!]
[Even though Ji Hyo is looking,
his body blocks the act.]
[Now only Ji Hyo is left.]
We're not cooking yet.
[He's happy...]
[All he needs to get is Ji Hyo
and his mission is complete!]
[Mission complete!]
What is that?
[Mission accomplished!]
What is it?
What did he do?
- It's mission accomplished.
- He shot something.
- What happened?
- What did you do fatso?
- What?
- What is it?
The winner of today's mission
is Ryu Hyun Jin!
Why?
What did he do?
But what did he do?
He shot something at your name tag.
- Me?
- There's nothing there.
Wait hold on.
- You have something.
- You do too.
The water gun is mine!
What are you doing?
[MT Allowance for Hyun Jin's
mission accomplished.]
The real mission wasn't the cooking
battle, but Hyun Jin's mission.
[Strong protest.]
You shot me when you were
eating ddukbokgi, right?
You had ddukbokgi?
- You had ddukbokgi?
- How could you?
Did you shoot me while we
were washing at the well?
Ha Ha was first at the market.
No wonder he kept following me around.
Let's see what the water gun looks like.
This is it.
This is it?
This is what you were shooting with?
- It's such a bright color.
- We didn't notice this?
How does this work?
It shoots well.
Why did you give this to Hyun Jin?
Let's take turns doing this.
One at a time. If we had just turned
around we would have caught him.
- That's true.
- If you had won, you would have gone to MT.
Hyun Jin put his arm around my shoulder
when we came back from the pastes.
He put his arm around my shoulder
so I thought we were a lot closer.
So this was the reason!
I shot it, but it got on your vest.
So I went...
I was so touched because
he put his arm around my shoulder.
I was really moved.
Suk Jin likes getting close
to famous people.
So that arm...
Didn't you have ddukbokgi earlier?
Yes, we did!
We had a lot of ddukbokgi
and five goldfish cakes!
We had 1.5 liters of fishcake broth.
I'm not hungry at all!
Then I'm going to eat this all.
[MT Cooking battle.
Spy Hyun Jin wins!]
Hyun Jin have some.
- It looks like the homeowner made this.
- Right?
- Good, right?
- It's no joke.
You should sell this.
This is like soup kalguksu.
I was so hungry.
Soup kalguksu.
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Next Week]
[After one year, supernatural
baseball returns!]
[Stronger than before!]
[Lee Byung Gyoo!]
[Kim Hyun Soo!]
[Shin Kyung Hyun!]
[Even better legendary magic baseball.]
[Upgraded supernatural baseball!]
Supernatural!