[Legendary fighter, Chu Sung Hoon.]
[The ultimate Amazon,
Lee Si Young.]
[They've come to annihilate Running Man!]
[The most powerful nemesis to date!]
[Running Man's nightmare!]
[Only possible in your imagination-
Running Man vs. The Fighters!]
Subtitles by DramaFever
[One day in January, 2013 - 4 a.m.]
[The sunrise is still hours away.]
[Incheon University's library.]
What is this going to be about today?
Please get your mikes on.
[What's the reason for gathering
Running Man members at this hour?]
Good morning.
Please get your mikes on.
[Still half-asleep.]
This isn't morning. This is still night.
You should say, 'Good night'.
[Even though their eyes are open...
their mentality still isn't present.]
As of now,
you can start entering one at a time.
[Huh? Each on their own?]
[Gary is the first to enter.]
[Huh? Clothes for the members?]
You can't seriously mean...
as soon as we start...
- It's a race?
- It's a race already?
- No, that can't be right.
- But we just...
What are you expecting from
us at 4 a.m.?
This is a hunt to eliminate each other's
name tag for a cash prize.
Money!
- You can enter right now.
- Yes, I understand.
First Running Man entering the arena.
You're expecting us to do a race
at 4 a.m. right now?
[Earliest in Running Man history!
A 4 a.m. chase?]
Right now?
[He said it was a cash race...]
Second Running Man entering the arena.
[Now that we take a look...
there's are cash prize wanted posters...]
I'm an expensive wanted suspect.
I'm wanted for 500 won.
Is this the cash prize?
800 won?
[Wanted posters that are put up on
the wall according to their skill level.]
How can it only be 800 won?
Suk Jin's only 100 won?
Even if you combine the three of us,
we're only worth 600 won.
Even if you eliminate all three of us,
it's still not as much as Song Ji Hyo.
How can I be worth only 300 won?
Make sure all your shoelaces
are tied tight.
[Giraffe exercising and
preparing for the chase.]
Name tag elimination hunt for
a cash prize?
- You may enter.
- Yes, I understand.
Fighting.
Seventh Running Man entering the arena.
What's going on here?
I haven't even done anything wrong,
but why is there a cash prize on my head?
I had a bad dream last night,
and it's making me nervous.
I really did have a weird dream last night.
I got two and a half hours of sleep...
You know those fantasies?
It was a black mountain where
goblins and monsters live...
In my dream, the moment they caught you,
you'd be dead immediately.
You know how you do this in your sleep?
Eighth Running Man entering the arena.
[Someone else is entering the arena?]
[Eighth Running Man...]
[The ultimate Amazon.]
[The ultimate Amazon?]
Hello.
[The ultimate Amazon...
Lee Si Young.]
[Fresh-faced adorable actress.]
[But in a ring, the ultimate fighter.]
[The strongest female guest to date!
She is here!]
[Still looking a bit bashful...]
[The ultimate Amazon...
Lee Si Young's entrance!]
Eighth Running Man, the ultimate Amazon,
Lee Si Young's entrance!
- Lee Si Young's entrance!
- Lee Si Young?
I'm so happy that Lee Si Young's here,
but... what do I do?
Are we going to be boxing
today then?
This is about name tag eliminating,
not about boxing, right?
I knew it was going to be like this.
My dreams...
Wow... Si Young's athletic abilities...
her boxing skills are just...
[Eight official wins out of nine competitions.
A runner up to a National Team Tryouts.]
[Undisputedly
the toughest female guest to date!]
Suk Jin's only worth 100 won?
But at least I'm worth 700 won.
Since this is early in the morning...
Lee Si Young would already be training in the
boxing ring, and she's here for the race...
This is a normal training hour for her.
[This is Si Young's
normal training schedule time...]
This isn't going to be easy.
Ninth Running Man...
The ultimate fighter...
[The ultimate fighter...]
[Si Young wasn't the end...
but there's a ninth Running Man?]
The ultimate fighter...
There's a ninth one?
[Ninth Running Man,
the ultimate fighter is...]
[To take over Running Man...]
The ninth Running Man...
[He is... here!]
[The ultimate fighter, Chu Sung Hoon.]
[Encompassing all sorts of martial arts,
and judo in his repertoire...]
[The toughest guest to ever appear
in history of Running Man!]
[Running Man... You're about
to meet the dominator today.]
[A superior expression on his face
as if he's about to enter the ring.]
- Welcome to Running Man. Please enter.
- Yes.
Do I have to put this on?
[This body...]
[is finally about to...]
[start...]
[the hunt!]
[Much more detailed than he looks.]
When I was on 'Family Outing'...
I did it kind of jokingly, but today...
I think I'm going to do it earnestly.
[If he does it earnestly,
then will anyone remain alive?]
[Running Man... you just wait!]
Chu Sung Hoon's entrance.
Ninth Running Man...
the ultimate fighter...
[How are they supposed to
accept this turn of events?]
Chu Sung Hoon's entrance.
Ninth Running Man, the ultimate fighter...
[Automatically starts to flee as
soon as he hears the name.]
Seriously?
[Can only laugh as she hears the
ultimate fighter's name being announced...]
How am I supposed to survive
to see the end of the day?
It's not THE Chu Sung Hoon, right?
Yes, it is him.
[Redesigning his jacket from it
being too tight around his thick biceps.]
Okay!
Can I start now?
[All the preparations are over...
Bounty hunting... starts now!]
I'm just going to go home.
What are you guys doing right now?
After calling us here at four in the morning?
I can't even do anything else but
laugh at the absurdity of it all right now.
Running Man members, welcome.
All nine members of Running Man
have now entered the arena.
I will now tell you about
your first mission of the day.
Your first mission...
Bounty hunt... name tag elimination.
[First mission:
Bounty hunt name tag elimination!]
The amount of bounty that's on the head of
the person you eliminate will become yours.
If anyone gets eliminated...
the bounty that they've
collected to that point...
will be lost without it being conveyed
to the person who eliminates them.
Only the person who survives to the end
can keep the bounty for themselves.
[Only the person who survives to the end
can keep the bounty for themselves.]
[Bounty hunt name tag elimination...
the imminent beginning.]
Are you going to stay with me
and follow me around all day now?
Are you a good runner?
- Yes.
- Okay, keep up with me.
I'll be running with all my might too.
- 100 won...
- Bounty hunt nametag elimination...
[With the amount of the bounty they're
worth stuck on their backs...]
Four... three...
Make sure to stick it on there tight.
Two... one...
Five... four... three... two... one...
Start!
[Bounty hunt - Start!]
[Size large having become a size small
due to the size of his muscles.]
Look at my jacket...
[Discovers the bounty posters!]
[Checking out how much each
person is worth.]
I'm worth the most!
[One poster that catches his eye...]
[The nemesis he faced a few years ago...]
[The one who resisted to the end!]
[Little brother... you are...]
[Going to face your end by me!]
I have to hide for now...
First, I need to hide.
Sung Hoon and Si Young...
I have to avoid those two for now.
[The bounty is everyone's goal!
Everyone is each other's enemy!]
- You've starting now? Is this starting?
- I was just getting a taste of it for now.
- Is this you starting?
- I was just getting a taste.
- How much is he? 200 won?
- I'm only worth 200 won.
I'm only worth 200 won.
What's the point of taking me now?
- Chu Sung Hoon is here... Chu Sung Hoon.
- We're in big trouble.
But Si Young's no joke either.
You know Si Young, don't you?
- She's an actual fighter in Incheon.
- Really?
She's a real boxing fighter.
Lee Si Young is a real fighter.
- She's an acknowledged fighter.
- Really?
I told you, I saw it for myself.
- Her skills are no joke.
- Hello...
Where are you going?
Si Young... it's Si Young!
[Just hearing Si Young's voice alone is
scaring the living daylights out of them!]
[The terror silently closing in on them...]
[Discovers Ha Ha!]
[Sung Hoon immediately starts to
chase after Ha Ha!]
Please!
Please! Sung Hoon... please!
Sung Hoon, it's nice to meet you!
It's nice to meet you!
[Easily spins him around a full circle.]
I'm sorry.
[Sung Hoon eliminates Ha Ha.]
[Even after being eliminated,
he's still out of sorts.]
Ha Ha, out.
Mommy... mommy!
[Ha Ha, out.
Ha Ha, out.]
What the heck...
he was right by me...
[Imagining the tragedy Ha Ha went through
by the horror he heard in his voice.]
I want my mommy!
- Ha Ha, I'm really sorry about that.
- You're so terrifying!
[First trauma of 2013.]
Thank you... oh my goodness.
[Sung Hoon wins 200 won
for eliminating Ha Ha!]
Why do you keep...
How much are you worth, Si Young?
- How much are you worth?
- What's the bounty on your head?
- Are you 500 won or 600 won?
- I'm worth 500 won.
I'm worth 700 won.
Your bounty is pretty high.
Can't we work together for now?
- Together?
- Yes.
[Is Si Young weaker than predicted?]
Help each other for now?
I'm pretty cheap anyways.
I'm only worth 500 won,
so no use eliminating me now.
[Deciding to join forces for now
to add strength to their team.]
Since I'm still a man,
maybe I could be of help.
[Gary decides to team up and protect
Si Young who looks so fragile and delicate.]
Then should I lure them in and you can...
[Discovers Chu Sung Hoon!]
Wait! Wait!
Where are you going?
Hello!
We were supposed to do this together!
Don't escape by yourself!
It's nice to meet you!
[This is his powerful first greeting!]
[Further escaping is a worthless effort!]
Si Young, make your escape!
Run for it, Si Young!
Hurry!
Don't do this!
I told you to run!
[Si Young eliminates Gary's name tag!]
500 won.
- I'll save the ladies for later.
- Thank you!
I was told...
that a man needs to be careful
about the woman he meets.
Gary, out!
[Upset about being fooled into thinking
that she was a frail woman.]
But at least my pride isn't wounded.
Since I was ousted by Lee Si Young...
[Si Young wins 500 won for
eliminating Gary!]
Gary, are you okay?
This is no joke, is it?
[The two kids running into each other
on their way to jail.]
- Hello.
- Hello, Sung Hoon.
- It's nice to meet you.
- Allow me to formally say hello.
May I have the honor of shaking
your hand?
He's like a dinosaur!
What happened to your arm?
You look like the incredible hulk.
- You sleeves are all ripped off.
- The sleeves were too small.
- You ripped them off?
- I cut them off.
[It would be like an
extra-large to these two...]
I can't believe how big he is.
Sung Hoon, please take care of Jong Kook!
Let him anticipate my arrival.
Jong Kook!
Wow... I think he's very
determined today.
[The wild beast having loosened up
his limbs.]
[Finally starts the real hunt!]
[Discovers the fighter!]
- Hello!
- What are you doing!
[Starts the chase after
politely greeting him first!]
Hello!
How was your new year?
I hope it was full of good fortune!
[Escaped from the fourth floor down
to the first floor in a span of one breath!]
[A dead end!]
Sung Hoon...
[Greeting each other first since they
haven't seen each other in a long time.]
[Grasshopper's life in danger!]
I'll let you live just this once.
- Thank you... thank you, Sung Hoon.
- I'll see you later.
[Jae Suk able to live for a little while
longer thanks to Sung Hoon's generosity.]
Sung Hoon... he really is no joke.
- Who? Who are you talking about?
- Sung Hoon!
What do we do, Jae Suk?
Sung Hoon wasn't giving me
a break earlier.
When Sung Hoon grabbed me
by my arms earlier...
he realized I'm not your
average opponent.
[Then he's saying Sung Hoon
ran away from him earlier?]
- One fighter recognized another.
- Then Jae Suk...
- You're going to go up against him?
- Don't worry about it.
Jae Suk, are you serious?
[The scent of Sung Hoon's cologne is...]
You really do have the nose
of a bloodhound!
[I'm positive he's nearby...]
[He really is!]
[He was just saying that he was going to
stand up to him if he saw him again...]
Who was it?
[Giraffe escapes in their direction too!]
[One person after another collapsing onto
the ground and saying they can't handle it.]
He's up on the sixth floor.
- Chu Sung Hoon and Lee Si Young...
- Jae Suk said Sung Hoon...
realized after grabbing him by the arms that
he's a frightening opponent and ran from him.
[Jae Suk starts to talk the game again after
having escaped from him for the second time.]
And then he just let me go.
He was taken aback by me.
He was basically saying that he wasn't
ready to take me on yet.
[How about you thanking him for
letting you live just minute ago?]
I hear someone coughing.
I think that's Sung Hoon again.
[But you said you could take him on and
beat him if you went up against him...]
[Si Young is right next to them!]
[Going somewhere?]
[The herbivores caught in total chaos!]
Ji Hyo... I can't live like this!
[Jae Suk and Ji Hyo having
breathlessly escaped.]
I told you, didn't I?
That I can smell Sung Hoon's scent?
He has a scent to him?
Like I always say...
The one that falls behind from the pack is
the one that gets eliminated in Serengeti.
Kwang Soo...
[The giraffe that fell behind
the rest of his herd.]
[Making his closing argument
to the fighter.]
You know that I'm not threat to you.
If I give you a break now,
it'll be my third time doing it.
I've already let two people go.
There's a Korean proverb that says,
'Best out of three'.
You sure do talk a lot.
[Oh look... there's the Giraffe...]
In that case...
[Pretending not to see her.]
Wait!
[Si Young eliminates the Giraffe!]
- She's really good... she's really good.
- Did you purposely not say anything to me?
No, I didn't see her either.
She totally snuck up on us!
[Giraffe, out! Kwang Soo's 500 won
bounty goes to Si Young!]
[Lee Kwang Soo, out.
Lee Kwang Soo, out!]
I told you, the one who falls behind
the herd is the one who dies.
[The chances are slim if one falls behind
their herbivore herd...]
[There he is again! The fighter!]
Wait... Jae Suk!
It's Sung Hoon again!
Hey! It's Sung Hoon!
Just how many
Chu Sung Hoon's are there?
[Ji Hyo barely escapes to her safety!]
And this way is Lee Si Young!
[A total dilemma!]
[Speeds up and catches him
within seconds.]
Why are you so strong?
[With a shockingly powerful grip...]
How much are you worth?
You... you haven't seen me in forever...
And the first thing you can say to me is,
'How much are you worth'?
[That's the first thing she says to him after
not having seem him in forever?]
[Yoo Jae Suk, out!
Yoo Jae Suk, out!]
It looks like everyone that should be
in jail will be here soon.
Of course, the sooner
they all get here, the better.
[But he still lasted longer
than expected...]
[Discovers Big-nosed Brother in hiding.]
- I used to practice judo.
- Judo?
[Easily takes over him by using the
judo skills his body is so used to.]
[Wins Suk Jin's bounty of 100 won!]
[Discovers Ace Ji Hyo!]
[Even though he's weak
when it comes to women...]
[He still knows to trip them over
with his foot!]
[Even Ace Ji Hyo is a piece of cake!]
- Good luck with the rest.
- Wait. Give me my 700 won.
[Win's Ji Hyo's bounty of 700 won!]
[Song Ji Hyo, out!
Song Ji Hyo, out!]
[Now...]
[It's time for me to step up...]
[I don't care how little the bounty is!]
[Now... there are only two
left remaining...]
- Sung Hoon!
- Hello.
It really has been a long time.
Why did you come on the show?
[A wild beast vs. A wild beast.]
How do you want to do this?
What do you mean,
how do I want to do this?
This is... Sung Hoon...
What are you doing?
Are you trying to fight me or something?
- That's what you do in the fighting ring!
- This is how I loosen up before I compete.
- Why are you being like this, Sung Hoon?
- You said I'm ignorant about my moves.
There's a rumor going around about you
saying that I'm ignorant about my moves!
- Who said that?
- I read it on Naver.
You can't believe everything
you read on Naver.
What are you doing?
What's wrong with you?
Why are you doing that?
Seriously?
[An unavoidable fateful showdown.]
- This is unavoidable, so let's just...
- I know, so let's do this.
[The fighter starting off
with light footwork.]
[Getting into the fighting stance!]
- Give me some time to prepare!
- What time?
[Sensing an opportunity,
Si Young makes her move.]
[A sandwich attack on Jong Kook?]
[Mr. Capable in extreme danger!]
- Si Young, why are you doing this to me?
- Si Young...
Why... why are you doing this?
Why are you doing this to me, Si Young?
[His leg?]
[Mr. Capable escapes a very close call!]
I think it's now time for us
to see this through.
[Si Young in a defense mode with
her back firmly attached to the wall.]
[After moving this way and that way,
Sung Hoon suddenly grabs Si Young?]
No!
[Grabs her within a blink of an eye!]
[Si Young - out!]
[Rule: The bounty she's collected
so far is no longer valid!]
[Sticks it back on?]
What are you doing?
Is it back on?
- Lee Si Young, out.
- No!
[Lee Si Young, out!]
[Wins Si Young's bounty of 700 won!]
Wow... 700 won?
Your bounty is worth 800 won, right?
[Now without having to worry
about anyone else...]
[It's now down to the two of them!]
[The real fight begins now!]
- You're my senior on this show.
- That's true.
[Anxiousness multiplied a hundred fold!
A battle of will!]
[Mr. Capable attacks first!]
[As predicted, doesn't
work too easily on Sung Hoon!]
[No words are exchanged.
Just the sound of their labored breathing.]
- Sorry!
- I'm fine.
This is fun!
How much do you work out?
Look at your arms!
- Your arms are the same.
- No, they're not!
[Mr. Capable, a rather equal opponent!]
Just give me my 800 won!
- Sung Hoon... Sung Hoon!
- I said, I want my 800 won!
- Why are you getting so worked up?
- I want my 800 won!
[Sung Hoon deflects by twisting his body!]
[Mr. Capable's repeated attack!]
[And Sung Hoon deflects it again!]
- What was that the last time...
- Family Outing?
You've gotten much stronger since then.
- We were just trying to be funny then.
- I know, but you're stronger now.
He's totally different!
[Each saying flattering words to
each other to prolong the rest period.]
You're very agile and quick.
- How old are you?
- I'm a year younger than you are.
[A perfectly matched pair of fighters'
battle of strength!]
[This is a real battle between the masters!]
This is really...
[Mr. Capable escapes with
an impressive reflex!]
[The two fighting with all their sincerity.]
No, that's fine.
Just don't rail me.
Sorry, Sung Hoon!
[Huh? Was he about to go in
for a knee kick?]
[The fiercest showdown
in the history of Running Man!]
[Just who will be the victor?]
[Sung Hoon grabs onto his sleeve
with his unbelievable strength!]
[Mr. Capable caught in a snare
and unable to move!]
[Wow! Sung Hoon's not letting go
of his grip on Jong Kook's clothes!]
[He has his hand on the name tag!]
[Sung Hoon succeeds in eliminating
Jong Kook!]
Ah... seriously!
[Wins Jong Kook's bounty of 800 won!]
[Chu Sung Hoon wins!
Wins a total bounty of 2,500 won!]
- Why does he look like that?
- I'm glad! You deserve it!
[Totally battered and mangled.]
- Look at you... you deserve it!
- Such a sweet payback.
Now what about the bounty?
[Hands out the bounty won to the winner.]
This money will become of
great use to you.
- How is that going to become useful?
- It literally is 2,500 won in change?
I will explain today's race to all of you.
Today's race is,
The Lord of Ddak-ji.
[The Lord of Ddak-ji.]
Yes! You just said, Ddak-ji, right?
There are too many leaders
in Ddak-ji that are emerging lately...
But I'm the master king.
[Last Chuseok, a huge reverse in the role!
The new ultimate Lord of Ddak-ji!]
You will be divided into three teams
to play the race today.
Each team will be able to win money for
their Ddak-ji's by passing their missions.
[Purchase their Ddak-ji's by using
all the money that they have earned...]
[And determine who the Lord of Ddak-ji is
by playing a round of Ddak-ji competition.]
Sung Hoon,
have you ever played Ddak-ji before?
Do you even know what a Ddak-ji is?
It's settled then!
We don't even need to worry.
- All he has is money. 2,500 won.
- He can get a good Ddak-ji though.
And the winner of the name tag elimination
is given the right to choose his own team.
Chu Sung Hoon can make up the team
however he likes.
- Take the Easy Brothers...
- Ha Ha.
- Thank you, Sung Hoon!
- Him? Are you serious?
Once my brother,
you'll always be my brother!
I feel so bad for ousting him so quickly
when we started the game...
No, Sung Hoon. I'm rather grateful to you
for straightening out my normally bad back!
Thank you, Brother!
He really is...
He's a total traitor though.
And for my other member...
[And his other team member is...]
Yoo Jae Suk.
[And his other choice is, Yoo Jae Suk.]
[Immediately bows down.]
[Birth of another traitor?]
- Why are you taking him?
- Sung Hoon...
[Did he just refer to Sung Hoon
as his older brother?]
What did you say?
Come on, now!
[You definitely said, 'My big brother!'...]
Who cares if I called him that?
Why is it important what I call him?
- Sung Hoon...
- Yes?
We're not traitors!
[The rising sun coming to find them after
their rousing round of the Bounty Hunt game.]
- What is this?
- What could that be?
[What is their next mission after
their first shocking mission of the day?]
[A seat cushion with each of
their names written on it?]
Why am I seated next to him?
[Annoyed with being seated
next to Sung Hoon?]
Si Young... fighting!
[Starting to break out the boxing jokes
in front of Si Young, the boxer?]
This is really fun.
Shadow boxing is a lot of fun.
[The birth of a new boxing couple gag.]
- Don't do it!
- I haven't see you joke like that in a while.
It's time for you to do the missions with
your team to win money to buy your Ddak-ji's.
Your first mission is...
Floor cushion quiz.
You have to roll over on your seats
up to the front
and be the first to place
the cushion on top of the coffee table
to gain the chance to
answer the question being asked.
Once the person answer a question correctly,
that person can now step out of the quiz.
The first team to answer the questions
correctly will be the winner.
- Suk Jin, you're good at this.
- Fighting.
[A great opportunity for
the weaker players!]
This is your best chance.
You have to do a good job.
You have to watch out for Si Young.
She may accidentally knock you out.
[Need to be careful of
Si Young's boxer moves.]
No, I'll never do that.
[Really?]
- Here comes your first question.
- Okay.
[First question.]
In the past...
It was said that if you bought this on the
night of New Year's Eve, you'd have good luck.
[A slugfest!]
[Screams heard from all directions.]
The cushion... the cushion!
You have to get it on the table!
[Si Young was faster!]
- What is her deal?
- Do you know the answer?
Is she allowed to hit people
with her elbow?
How could you...
- Si Young, don't you think that was harsh?
- What is it? What's the answer?
[Tell me...]
- What's your answer?
- You can't ask him for the answer!
- Five, four, three, two...
- The money pouch.
- That's right!
- No, that's not it.
Please go back to your places.
It's a silk pouch, isn't it?
A silk pouch?
Si Young was so forceful
making her way up to the front.
[Punching past people is just a given?]
On the night of New Year's Eve...
it was said that if you bought this,
it would bring you good fortune.
What is this tool which can
be used for rice?
[A given punch.]
Lee Si Young!
[A fierce battle of the cushions.]
[Sung Hoon gets to it first!]
- Chu Sung Hoon. It was Chu Sung Hoon.
- But I bet he doesn't know the answer.
[What will Sung Hoon's answer be?]
Your answer, Chu Sung Hoon?
Crayons.
[The tool used for the rice is crayons?]
[Did the Giraffe do something to
deserve getting hit?]
[You...]
[Right before the start...]
- Crayons... it's crayons.
- Crayons?
Ah... crayons.
[Playing a joke on Sung Hoon...
the fearless Giraffe...]
You can start as soon as
I sound my whistle.
What's the answer?
[Asking so innocently with
her sweet face...]
Okay, I know the answer.
[It seems as though a few know
what the answer is.]
[Ha Ha gets to it first by
the split of his hair!]
- Okay!
- Ha Ha!
- Bokjori! (Rice sieve)
- Yeah. That's the answer!
- Rice sieve!
- No... that can't be the answer!
- That's not the correct answer.
- That can't be the answer.
Correct answer.
[Correct answer.]
- It's the rice sieve!
- Is that really the answer?
- Rice sieve!
- Excuse me...
It's Bokjori, right?
But he said, Bokjjori.
[Wha... what?]
[Earnestly protesting the way
he pronounced the word.]
- You said we had to say it right.
- Bokjori.
- He's correct.
- That's not how he said it!
He said, 'Bokjjori'.
- What he said was right.
- What?
But if you're to enunciate each syllable,
it should be 'Bok-jo-ri'.
She's saying that he pronounced it wrong.
Listen, PD...
Can you do penalize Si Young
for her cheating?
Kwang Soo and I right now...
She's keeps punching us out!
[Another victim.]
Don't you think she's being
too rough?
[Jae Suk and Kwang Soo,
not even being able to get a real start.]
I can maybe understand the arm pulling,
but look at him over here.
Look at how red our necks are!
She grabbed me by the neck like this
so that I won't be able to move!
[Is that how she grabbed the neck?]
- No, I didn't...
- You have to do something about her!
I'm sorry, but she did it to help you
improve your blood circulation.
- Is that right?
- Yes!
- Really? Fine, fine!
- It's for the sake for your own health.
[Come on, let's just play...]
[Blue Team's Ha Ha succeeds!]
Didn't I say the silk pouch in the beginning?
- Yes.
- But I was thinking the sieve when I said it.
- I was thinking the sieve...
- That's what you may have thought...
If she argues that's what she was thinking,
how is this game going to be played?
That's why I'm acknowledging that
my answer was wrong.
I appreciate you acknowledging you were
wrong, but Kwang Soo and I...
It's not that we're being slow,
but we can't even get started on our way.
But you said it in the beginning that it was
okay for us to shove people out of our way?
- Yes, that doesn't matter.
- That's how the game is played.
- But she's the only one doing the hitting.
- Hit me, you can hit me.
[Huh?]
Hit me, you can hit me.
Hit me.
Don't be uncomfortable, and just hit me.
[What? Be comfortable and hit you?]
But that's the rule of the game.
Just hit and shove me out of the way.
- But how can we shove and hit you?
- It's okay!
- Really, it's okay!
- Isn't this all too much?
You can seriously just shove me off!
It really is fine!
I can't believe she's telling us
to shove her out of the way!
Okay, everyone...
here's your next question.
On New Year's day...
[Already?]
Lee Si Young.
Board jumping.
Don't you do that during Chuseok?
Isn't what we're doing right now
board jumping?
[Gary's morning show?]
She's jumping the board over here
and he's accepting her jumps.
I went because I thought of something.
Go ahead then.
[What is the answer Gary has thought of
before even hearing out the full question?]
- Answer the question and make us laugh
- Kang Gary.
Yut game.
(Stick throwing game.)
- Yut game.
- Seriously?
[Could it be?]
Okay, here's the question.
[She's coming out again?]
Lee Kwang Soo.
[Kwang Soo arrives first.]
Hwa-to.
(Korean card game.)
[What?]
What do you mean, Hwa-to?
That's not a traditional game
to be playing on New Year's day!
One of the games that's played on
New Year's Day...
Depending on how it's played, it can
be called throwing, hound dog, or loose.
Oh loose!
You're out way too far.
Why do you keep fidgeting like that?
[Sung Hoon continuously trying to
figure out his starting position.]
Three, two, one!
[Go!]
Sung Hoon, what are you doing!
[Ji Hyo arrives first!]
Song Ji Hyo.
- Song Ji Hyo!
- Song Ji Hyo.
Jaegi kick!
Wait, it's that thing.
[Huh?]
What is that thing? That...
What?
If you can't remember what it is,
just go back to your seat!
You know that thing...
the thing that starts with 'Chul'...
[The word that starts with 'Chul'?]
Jaegi Kick!
J-a-e-g-i, K-i-c-k. Right?
Why do we have to put up with this?
[Correctly spelling out 'Jaegi kick'.]
[Ji Hyo answers correctly!]
Si Young, you did good.
What was she talking about,
the word that starts with 'Chul'?
The word that starts with 'Chul'...
I'm sorry, but Sung Hoon doesn't
know any of these questions.
He doesn't know anything but he just
keeps getting in my way.
You have to do something about him.
I'm doing good right now.
This question has to do with food.
[Red Team's Jong Kook also answers
a question correctly and passes.]
Another name for this food is,
'Chumsaebyung'.
What dish is this referring to?
[Does Si Young even know what the answer
is as she's making her way up front?]
You're asking what the meaning is?
She needs to be humiliated once...
What is the dish that's at times
referred to as, 'Chumsaebyung'?
That... what was it called again?
Gyungdan!
[Huh? Gyungdan?]
I know you're my teammate,
but you're really something else.
Is that the whole question?
Chumsaebyung?
What is this dish that is at times called
'Chumsaebyung'? I'll give you a hint.
It's a New Year's food.
One, two, three!
[Oh... Gary!]
Kang Gary.
Rice cake soup.
(Dduk guk)
Double 'D' to the 'U'...
[Precisely spelling out the words.]
[Correct answer.]
- It was rice cake soup?
- It's the rice cake soup.
- You're the only one who needs to pass now.
- Kwang Soo!
This question is...
When you bow down to your parents
on New Year's Day...
which hand is placed on top
for the daughters?
[Jae Suk? What got into him?]
- It's a fifty-fifty chance.
- The left hand.
Which number with the left hand?
[Huh?]
- What is that supposed to mean?
- This is good!
- Nice going!
- What is that supposed to mean?
Second left hand?
It's the second right foot.
You answered incorrectly.
Sung Hoon, just guess the number.
- Yeah, just guess it!
- Sung Hoon!
Which hand does the daughter place on top
when she bows down to her parents?
Wait! Can he do this?
Wait!
[Utter chaos]
[Si Young's breakthrough
that knows no end.]
Si Young doesn't care about anything.
Third left hand.
Three times with the left hand?
Third left foot.
- Do you have it written down there?
- Yes, we have it written down.
[Maybe it's not the left hand
after all...]
Kwang Soo, we just need you to pass.
Three, two, one!
Si Young... Si Young!
Si Young! Get it!
[Kwang Soo's cushion having
made it through the melee.]
Your answer?
The fourth right hand.
Fourth.... fourth right arm.
[The fourth one is the right arm.]
Is this how you're supposed to
bow down?
[I'm sure that's not how it's done...]
It's the same thing with the right foot.
- Sung Hoon, stop moving around on it!
- He broke it.
[No thanks to Sung Hoon,
the chair is now damaged and broken.]
Look at how casually you're just
taking over my seat.
How many chairs are you
going to break?
- Are you ready?
- Yes.
[Which number is the right hand?]
[Jae Suk blocks Kwang Soo's cushion?]
[And immediately swipes Si Young's
cushion out of his way?]
Mine! My cushion!
[Kwang Soo's cushion hits the ledge
and bounces off the table...]
[And Jae Suk pushes it out of the way.]
[And Si Young's cushion immediately
follows by flying onto the table.]
[Si Young's chance!]
I can't acknowledge it when it's
shoved out of the way with the hand.
Which number did we get up to?
- And your answer is?
- Number six with the right hand.
- It's not six! We already said six.
[We already did six?]
- We've already gone up to number six.
- Aren't you on my team?
I'm letting you know that
we've already said that earlier.
- He already said number six earlier.
- No, he didn't!
- Why are you getting angry?
I was just telling her we
already said six.
I'll ignore what's been said so far,
and I'll accept what Si Young says now.
- Five, four, three...
- Number six, right hand.
Number six, right hand!
We told you, six has been said!
[Wasn't six already said?]
[What? Correct answer!]
- I guess number six wasn't said?
- I thought six was already said!
That's the correct answer.
Really?
- Six wasn't said?
- Wow, that's awesome.
- Six wasn't said.
- Really?
Okay, first place has been determined.
First place goes to the Red Team.
[Red Team takes first place in
the quiz game!]
- Here's your question.
- Do a better job, Kwang Soo!
- This is a very easy question.
- Okay.
[A really easy question?]
Yeah, I like questions like that.
This refers to new clothes or new shoes
that one wears on New Year's Day.
The parents...
[Green Team's last member, Kwang Soo
targets Jae Suk, who seems to know the answer.]
Sung Hoon, it's two words.
Your answer is?
[At a quick glance,
it may look like a steamy love scene.]
Your pants... your pants.
[Giving him a hint.]
[Getting even steamier.]
- Sweat suit.
- Excuse me?
Sweat suit.
[Sung Hoon's New Year's
outfit is a sweat suit.]
Okay!
[That's what I wear.]
What is it that you wear before you have the
memorial service on New Year's morning?
That's good, Jae Suk.
You have to get him.
[Chastising the Giraffe.]
I was wrong!
What I did was wrong!
[Broad forehead coming into view
for an easy mark.]
What did you just hit me with?
[Unable to believe that the force of that
hit came from just one finger.]
- No, it was just a flick of his finger.
- That wasn't just a flick of his finger!
Wait!
[Giraffe still hasn't learned his lesson,
and is trying to attack again?]
[Blocks him immediately with his skills.]
[That's why you need to be choosier about
who you pick your battles with...]
[Jae Suk succeeds in getting
a chance to answer?]
Yoo Jae Suk, your answer?
Seolbim.
Isn't it Kko-Kka?
[Is his own teammate sabotaging him?]
Isn't it Tae-tae ote?
- Five, four, three, two, one!
- Seolbim.
[Blue Team's Jae Suk passes!]
We got it!
[Now it's down to Blue Team's Sung Hoon,
and Green Team's Kwang Soo.]
- So I can use my skills then?
- Don't do it!
- Kwang Soo, don't do it!
- Are you out of your mind?
Okay, are you both ready?
- Sung Hoon, you can do it.
- Yes.
It was said, if this bird cried out on
New Year's Day, the year would be bountiful.
[Magpie!]
What's this auspicious bird species?
[Giraffe takes him on face to face.]
[Or... maybe not.]
[Save me!]
[Quiz or whatever, he's going
to see this through to the end!]
Sung Hoon!
You know what to do, right?
[Giraffe's attack coming out to show.]
[With every last drop of his strength...]
[However...]
[Sung Hoon escapes the hold,
and counterattacks!]
[His outstanding abilities to escape such a
disadvantageous position to counterattack!]
[Giraffe having met a
formidable match today.]
Kwang Soo, hurry!
Hurry!
[Ah... I bet that hurts.]
Your answer?
[Battered and mangled.]
Sung Hoon, relax!
And think carefully.
[If Sung Hoon answers correctly,
it's the end of this mission!]
That fish...
No, it's not a fish!
- Quiet! You can't say anything!
- Bird... it's a bird!
Tell me the name of the bird.
- Magpie?
- That's right!
Yes, it is a magpie,
but which number?
[Another multiple choice?]
Please just end it.
- I'll just give up.
- No, we can't do that.
[Feeling like death warmed over.]
- Three. Number three.
- Number three, magpie?
[Please, let it be number three...]
The way I see it, there's no
way Kwang Soo can make it out.
- Kwang Soo won't be able to make it out.
- No, he won't make it out.
[Even getting past the starting line
seems like an impossibility.]
Number three is pigeons.
So, your answer was incorrect.
Three, two, one!
[Breaks out into
another skirmish as predicted.]
[Did he just hit him?]
I'm so sorry!
[So easily caught because of
his long frame.]
[Tenacious Giraffe...]
[Makes his way to the table
in a blink of an eye!]
[Almost simultaneously!]
[Judging the cushions.]
[Sung Hoon's cushion is on the bottom!]
[By the split of a second...]
[Seriously has dirty, rotten luck.]
Look at how crestfallen Kwang Soo is.
- And you answer is?
- Number eight.
- There's no number eight.
Please just end it.
[Just desperately wishing for
this moment to just end...]
Kwang Soo seriously looks like a pile
of fallen leaves on the side of the road.
[His life is no different than some leaves
rolling around on the ground by the wind.]
Three, two, one!
[Sung Hoon with his monstrous strength
throws even the chair onto the table!]
No, I'm fine.
You're not angry, are you?
[Not many unbroken chairs
left to speak of.]
Lee Kwang Soo,
your correct answer is?
I'm going to answer, okay?
- Number seven, magpie.
- A little louder.
- You're dead if you're right.
[Green Team's Kwang Soo succeeds!]
[He almost had the game...]
I told you it was going to
be number seven.
[Keep that up,
and you'll be beaten up again...]
Good job, Kwang Soo!
[Anyways, with Kwang Soo's success,
this mission is now over.]
[Red Team wins 2,500 won
for coming in at first place.]
Okay, second place.
[Green Team wins 1,000 won
for coming in at second place.]
Kwang Soo, I bet your medical bills
are going to be more than what's in there.
Kwang Soo, your medical bills
[All my pain and suffering
is in that pouch...]
Sung Hoon, you really did great.
That was too bad, you were so close!
- All that matters is that I'm having fun.
- That's right.
[Go to Yongyoo seashore
and find Running Man's landmark.]
What are you looking at?
Seriously...
I have over 30 thousand ways
to tease someone.
My wish is to use them all
on Kwang Soo throughout my life.
Are you going on UFC this summer?
Yes, I'm planning on going
this summer.
Sung Hoon,
I'm sure this is a rhetorical question
but doesn't it seriously hurt?
Of course, it hurts.
And it's actually really exhausting.
If hurts more
once the competition is over, right?
It starts to hurt immediately
once the competition is over.
- Immediately.
- But you don't really notice during?
It really doesn't hurt then.
I don't notice the pain when I'm fighting.
But as soon as it's over, it's immediate.
But I bet that anticipation before you enter
the ring and the competition is no joke.
[The immeasurable amount of anxiety
right before the competition starts.]
And I don't think that kind of anxiety
can't be found anywhere else.
It's so physical. A body against
the body up against another body.
That's really...
People like us may just die from a heart
attack just from the anxiety alone.
Before the competition even really starts.
- Okay...
- Wow, we're in first place.
[Totally excited!]
[Singing a 'Si Young' song?]
Si Young...
I don't know if it's because I'm happy,
but the words are just flowing out.
It's just flowing out of you.
From the melody to the lyrics.
The 'jjuk-jjuk' part is the chorus.
I want you guys to sing it with me.
- I like that.
- Not bad, right?
Okay, we're here.
[Blue Team arrives at their destination.]
This is the place, Ha Ha.
Ha Ha, this is the place.
It's a tidal flat.
[Third mission location,
The tidal flats of terror!]
Since you're the first team to arrive,
you move up to the final round.
We are?
[Blue Team is chosen to move up to the
final round for being the first to arrive.]
- We're moving onto the final round.
- Really? That's awesome.
The Blue Team beat us here.
- We were too focused on singing.
- Did we get here too leisurely?
Do you think we're going to
have to wrestle?
I have a bad feeling
we're going to be wrestling.
[Bingo!]
We're getting harmonious now.
[Their unstopping song singing.]
[Coach Kkuk giving
a crash course in wrestling.]
Don't do it, don't do it!
He's watching everything.
You already know everything,
Sung Hoon. This is what you do.
- Look at you playing dumb.
- No, I'm being serious.
[A coy mental battle with the wrestling
match looming ahead of them?]
[In just a few moments...]
[Kim Jong Kook vs. Chu Sung Hoon.
The battle of a century is coming!]
[Battle of strength that's on
a whole different scale!]
[Incarnation of power, Mr. Capable!]
[Power of equal strength-
A real fighter, Chu Sung Hoon!]
[The shocking battle...]
[Coming soon:
The ultimate showdown of strength!]
Okay, this is the tidal flats wrestling.
A round of applause!
Why would we want to applaud this?
First things first,
Blue Team moves up to the final round.
[Blue Team is seeded to the final round
for having been the first to arrive.]
This round will be between the
Red Team and the Green Team.
And the first competition will be
Lee Si Young vs. Song Ji Hyo.
This is going to be quite the competition.
- Lee Si Young, fighting!
- Ji Hyo, you can do this!
[Strength for strength!
Skill for skill!]
[Undisputed Ace of Running Man, Blank Ji!]
[The actress with ultimate strength
who doesn't lack anything.]
[A real fighter with an innocent face,
a formidable powerhouse, Lee Si Young!]
- Ji Hyo and Si Young...
- This is going to be a good match.
No use of fists, okay?
Ji Hyo beat me the last time.
You can't take her lightly.
Here's the rule of the game.
It's an all-kill game where the winner will
keep going as far as they can go.
[All-kill game where the winner can keep on
playing as long as they keep winning!]
Si Young, just finish them all for us.
You can finish them all.
Everyone knows who
Lee Si Young is, right?
She runs three times a week,
for eight km at a time.
And you all know our Ji Hyo, right?
She eats about eight kg
of food a week...
Her jabs are just part of her
daily routine.
Why don't you give us a show?
- Stop it!
- Why do you keep shaking your hips?
- When Si Young plays...
- This is not what you do!
This is how we were taught
when I was little.
You just loosen up your arms,
and jab like this.
[Lightning fast fists!]
You always need to keep
your fists loose.
[Tidal front being an unknown factor,
can't predict what could happen!]
We can't pull our feet out.
- We can't predict what's going to happen.
- No, we can't predict it.
Nice grip.
That's a nice grip you've got on the tie.
Pull your feet out... pull your feet out.
[A showdown between two powerhouses.]
Please!
Ready...
[A face-off with an unpredictable outcome
that's happening right now in the tidal flats.]
What's she doing?
My feet keep sinking deeper!
[Her feet keep sinking lower, feeling
the pressure from her opponent...]
[Power vs. Power]
You got it!
[A competition between two women
where concession doesn't exist.]
You got it!
[Simultaneously?]
What happened?
[At the end of their fierce struggle...]
[Blank Ji's knee was first
to touch the ground!]
Her left knee touched the ground.
[Si Young wins!]
[A lightning fast win that happened
in the blink of an eye!]
Great job.
- I was wondering who was going to win.
- They both did a great job.
[In the next match against Gary,
Si Young also wins that match.]
[If she beats Kwang Soo too, then the
Red Team moves onto the final round!]
Kwang Soo...
Kwang Soo! Watch yourself
and be careful of her grips!
- Wait... wait... my foot.
- She's hanging onto you already.
Wait... it's not time yet.
[Loser wrestling rule: The person who's butt
touches the ground first is the winner.]
I can't even get my knee in there.
Were you just trying to kick me?
I could've sworn you were trying to
knee me somewhere just now!
[Third round of loser wrestling match: Start!]
[Ah... a kind of agony that words
fails to describe...]
[Men can sympathize 100%]
What to do?
[With the force of all her weight...
Si Young's unexpected attack.]
[Save a Giraffe's life...]
There's no penalty for this.
This was just...
[Giraffe losing his ability to breathe.]
[Anyways, the Green Team's
Kwang Soo wins!]
His legs are just so abnormally long...
Abnormally...
- Mr. 100 won?
- Oh, Mr. 200 won.
- No, I was 300 won. Please watch it.
- You were 300 won?
I apologize, Mr. 400 won.
Both of you, please keep it down.
I'm worth 400 won.
[A showdown between
the Easy Brothers!]
You have to grab the tie.
Why are you pinching his leg?
That hurts!
Why are you pinching me?
[Expecting a normal match between
the two is just impossible.]
Wait. My foot is stuck.
- Suk Jin, wait.
- Let's do this.
Suk Jin!
I asked you to wait!
[Immersing his sock clad feet
into the tidal flats.]
I said, hang on!
Hang on!
[A rather unbelievable wrestling match.]
[A total chaos before the real match
even starts!]
Okay, let's do this!
- Let's go!
- Put your socks back on.
[Designated as being in charge
of all the body gags.]
- This is what real tidal flats are about.
- Why does he keep falling lately?
It's finally starting now.
This is what tidal flats are all about.
You're all dead!
Okay, grab your opponents.
[Finally starts!]
[A real barefooted match.]
[Transformed into a combo
fighting event.]
[Immeasurable showdown between
the Easy Brothers.]
[Giraffe's knees touch down first!]
[Big-nosed Brother wins!]
[Red Team wins!]
- I won, right?
- Suk Jin wins!
- Kwang Soo, your knees touched down.
- Who's next? Come on!
[A final round between the
Blue Team and the Red Team.]
For this match, Blue Team's Haroro
will take the women's approach...
and will go up against
the Red Team's Si Young.
Ha Ha, don't get sucked into
her mind games, okay?
Lee Si Young, show yourself!
- Si Young, you can beat him.
- You dare laugh?
Do you think that
just because you're a girl...
[What just flew through
the air right now?]
Something just flew through the air.
[I'm scared...]
It seems you're not aware of the fact that I
specialize in leg tripping our lady guests.
We're going to go for the regular
kind of wrestling match for the win.
Do you accept?
The lady has the right to choose.
- Okay, let's do it.
- Seriously?
[A real face-off!]
Are you for real?
[It seems as though
Si Young is quite serious.]
Dong Hoon doesn't go easy
on the girls at all.
What am I supposed to do with this?
[Serious]
[Lady guests' leg tripping specialist, Haroro
vs. Actress/Boxer, Lee Si Young.]
[A surge of power.]
Wait, Si Young...
[Si Young attacking him full force
without any hesitation.]
[Si Young's foot...]
[Huh?]
[Taking her boot off to trip his inner leg.]
[Si Young wins!]
Lee Si Young!
[Si Young won...]
- Lee Si Young! Lee Si Young!
- No, that's not right! That was a mistake!
What happened was...
come on, this isn't right!
What are you doing?
That really wasn't right.
I'm serious!
What do you mean, it wasn't right?
Okay, Ha Ha lost that match.
Next.
What the heck is this?
Ha Ha, just come here.
You're the 100 won,
and I'm 200 won now.
Ha-100 won!
You are Ha-100 won.
Lee Si Young can choose to do
the losing wrestling this time.
Yes, she should choose the losing wrestling.
She can't do the winning wrestling.
I'm going to go for the
winning wrestling.
- How can she choose that with me?
- It's her choice!
You really shouldn't be
doing that with me, Si Young!
- Okay, Si Young!
- She says she's confident she can do it!
How can Si Young...
Come on, Judge!
How can she do that?
She should be picking the losing match!
- Si Young... you can do this!
- Si Young, I'm being serious.
[A real match with Jae Suk!]
I have no other choice then.
I'm just going to go for it.
- A winning wrestling match!
- But this is...
Her grip is no joke.
[A totally serious opponent, Si Young.]
Why is she so strong?
- Si Young, what are you doing?
- Let's just do this!
Okay, we're going to start!
I can't get my foot out!
- My foot is stuck and I can't get it out!
- Si Young, you can do this!
I said, my foot is stuck!
I couldn't move my feet!
I couldn't get my foot out!
[Si Young wins!]
- Lee Si Young!
- Wait... Judge!
- You can't do anything about nature!
- But my feet were stuck!
It's the call of nature!
I'm seriously about to go crazy.
Seriously!
My goal was Jong Kook, not Si Young!
I'll give you another chance
to do it barefoot.
- Then I'll do it barefoot.
- Me too!
- Not you, Ha Ha.
- I'm being serious!
Ha Ha, you legitimately lost!
Okay, I'm going to do this barefoot.
[Going in barefoot]
I feel like I can fly now!
I feel light as air now!
- We should've done this from the beginning.
- Si Young...
[A barefoot rematch]
Si Young, I'm really sorry about this.
- This is the real deal this time.
- Okay.
[Amazing... fifth match in a row
for Si Young.]
[A real barefoot match this time around!]
Si Young, don't give him any breaks!
Why is Si Young so strong?
Okay... wait, wait!
Okay, ready!
[Wow! She's bulldozing him!]
Si Young, what's wrong with you?
[Si Young completely bulldozing him
over with her power!]
How is this...
[Oh? A leg trip?]
[Jae Suk tries to leg trip her!]
[A flip!]
[But stands firm to withstand his maneuver...]
[And flips him over!]
[Si Young's perfect win!]
Lee Si Young!
[Lee Si Young wins!]
He really lost!
This footage is getting saved forever.
- No, this really isn't right.
- No, it's not right.
Actually, I lost once to Kyung Lim
back in the late nineties.
I don't think of things like this
as humiliation.
Don't you agree?
- I'm a little different.
- You legitimately lost to her!
Why don't we have a match later then?
[Anyways, Lee Si Young
really is something else!]
What if she beats Chu Sung Hoon too?
Okay, players from each team
please enter the ring.
- Can I do the losing game this time?
- Yes, you should.
You can choose, Lee Si Young.
[Whether it's a losing game or a winning game,
the choice is up to Si Young to make.]
- The losing one?
- The losing one's better.
- I'm going to go for the losing one.
- The losing game.
She chose the winning game with Ha Ha and I.
You're winning because of us, Sung Hoon.
The first person who's butt touches
the ground first is the winner.
[The first person to touch the ground
with their butt is the winner!]
Okay, Chu Sung Hoon is choosing to
take his shoes off too.
Hang on, I'll do it for you. Wait.
I can't get it past his ankles!
[Gary's tidal flats show.]
Why did you push me?
I didn't do anything.
[Gary's tidal flats show
coming out of nowhere.]
Okay, the losing game!
- Ready?
- Yes.
[Losing wrestling-
Chu Sung Hoon vs. Lee Si Young]
[As expected, extremely easily...]
All you needed was to touch with your butt,
but why fall all the way back?
Why did you ram her face
to the ground?
Why did you have to
shove her face in like that?
Why did you do that to her?
Chu Sung Hoon, come on!
Sung Hoon, can you do the move where
you lift him up and flip him over?
I'll save that one for the end.
What did you say?
- He keeps staring at Jong Kook.
- Sung Hoon...
- Go easy on him, okay?
- Ready?
[Blue Team's Sung Hoon vs.
Red Team's Suk Jin.]
Wait...
Are your legs planted
into the ground or something?
[Big-nosed Brother getting
slammed into the ground...]
He's still alive.
I can see him moving.
The tidal flats are still alive.
[Judge Gary doing emergency rescue.]
What just happened?
- It's okay. It was over quick.
- I'm still envious of Suk Jin.
At least he lost to Sung Hoon.
I wouldn't have minded losing
to Sung Hoon.
- Here's the main event.
- It's finally here.
Today's main event!
At last, we get to see the main event!
It's finally here!
A round of applause!
Chu Shin Soo and Kim Jong Kook...
Chu Shin Soo?
Can you each say a word about
how you're going to win this match?
What do you mean, how am I going
to win? I'll just be grateful if I win!
- What do you mean, how am I going to win?
- I'm going to flip you in the air.
Why are you trying to throw me?
You did that once already!
I beg of you both to show us
a really entertaining match.
That's the only way I can forget
the fact that I lost to Si Young.
The two of you need to show the two of us
a good game so we can move on.
I've already forgotten my experience
because of Sung Hoon, so it's okay.
No, you and I are going down together!
[The loss of these two
will forever be remembered...]
[At last... the meeting
of the two powerhouses!]
What do you think about
my thighs, Sung Hoon?
- Not bad.
- Not bad?
Sung Hoon, he used to wrestle.
[A one-time wrestler, Jong Kook
vs. Judo Champion, Sung Hoon.]
Are you ready?
[The ultimate powerhouse of
Running Man, Jong Kook...]
[Making everyone scream out
in pain during the Chuseok special...]
[The power of Mr. Capable, Jong Kook!]
[Even humiliating Jae Suk by
flipping him over upside down!]
[This is the power of Mr. Capable!]
[A showdown between the
ultimate powerhouses!]
This is going to be difficult...
[At last... the ultimate
tidal flats showdown!]
This is going to be fun to watch!
- This is going to be interesting.
- Look at Jong Kook's stance. He knows.
Don't flip your channels, viewers!
The real match has begun!
[Stay tuned and
watch the showdown of a century!]
Jong Kook said he's going to try
to flip Sung Hoon over.
[Anxiety ridden face-off
between these two.]
Even if Jong Kook lowers his stance
to start his attack...
his opponent Chu Sung Hoon is too familiar
with the judo moves to make it easy.
[Unbelievable amount of nervous energy
flowing through the competition ring.]
Even though they look like they're relaxed,
they're both exerting a lot of energy.
In another words,
it's a battle of their wills.
The moment one of them loses sight of it
for a second, the battle will be won.
I'm reminded of another match
that I saw back in the day.
- Chu Sung Hoon...
- They're both exerting a lot of energy!
I can see both of them trying to push
each other with their shoulders.
- This is 100% real!
- They're both doing whatever they can!
Let's give them both a
round of applause!
[Neither one of them able to
launch into a full attack mode...]
Both athletes are standing their ground!
Look at how much strength Sung Hoon
is exerting right now.
Chu Sung Hoon won the last round of
name tag elimination against Jong Kook.
[Will Jong Kook be able to pay him back for
the humiliation during name tag elimination?]
Chu Sung Hoon may be going into
his attack mode pretty soon.
He's changed his grip on him and
could be launching into an attack mode soon.
[Sung Hoon pulling his legs back
to get into defensive position.]
- He's moving his leg to the inner position!
- Jong Kook, think of Running Man!
[The imminent outcome...]
[Just who...]
[Sung Hoon slowing down momentarily.]
[Is now the chance?]
[One single attack that marked the end.]
[I won!]
That was amazing!
That was an unbelievable match!
[Amazing showdown of the century!]
That was amazing.
[Even though the real fighter,
Sung Hoon ultimately won...]
[Mr. Capable is actually a
ballad singer originally.]
I felt like I was watching the Olympics.
[A sincere hug between two men
congratulating the real victor.]
Even though I have seen countless wrestling
matches between celebrities...
this was by far the best I have ever seen!
After just testing out each other's
strength for five minutes...
at the moment when both their energies
combined and was about to combust...
they both used their skills,
but Chu Sung Hoon took that energy and...
And Lee Si Young took his energy
to use it during her matches, right?
- Excuse me?
- Lee Si Young took his energy for herself?
Lee Si Young just used her legitimate
skills to take you down flat.
I bet people are searching the internet now
for your loss against Lee Si Young.
And the search for Yoo Jae Suk's humiliation
against Lee Si Young is number one search.
[The long awaited
Ddak-ji competition location.]
[Incheon Metropolitan vehicle base.]
What is all this?
We have to buy it.
How are the Ddak-ji's?
[All different sorts of Ddak-ji's at
different prices all in one place!]
Hello and welcome to Luxury Ddak-ji Shop.
As you can see, I have all sorts from your
basic Ddak-ji to the highest grade Ddak-ji.
There's no exchanging or returning,
so be cautious about your selection.
- We can only choose one?
- Yes, only one per person.
- One per person?
- Look at this one.
- You touch it, you bought it.
Who would buy this ice Ddak-ji?
I think I like it.
I think I'm going to take the 'R' Ddak-ji.
Okay, since we don't have
a lot of money.
- How much is this one?
- 3,000 won.
[Shopping frugally to keep within
the budget of each team.]
- I'll go for the fashion Ddak-ji.
- I think I like this one.
- I'm definitely going to take this one.
- Then I'm going to take the water one.
- Do I get the water too?
- Yes, you'll get the charger with it too.
[Rule: One person at a time from each team.
The team with a surviving player wins!]
Why do I have to play against the girls?
[Green Team: Ji Hyo, Blue Team: Ha Ha,
and the Red Team: Si Young.]
[The Ddak-ji that Ha Ha chose was...]
[Fashion Ddak-ji made out of pages
from a fashion magazine.]
[Green Team Ji Hyo's normal Ddak-ji,
where normalcy is her weapon.]
My Ddak-ji that sticks to the ground...
Water Ddak-ji that can't be flipped over!
[Red Team Si Young's ultimate grip,
water Ddak-ji!]
- Ji Hyo, your honor is riding on this!
- You have to keep your honor!
[Fixed on Ha Ha's
fashion Ddak-ji as her target.]
- You have to hit it harder from the top.
- I understand what you're saying.
[Ha Ha from the Blue Team's
turn to attack!]
I'm putting my trust in you,
fashion Ddak-ji!
- Ha Ha, don't overdo it!
- That's good... good!
[Targeting on Ji Hyo's normal Ddak-ji.]
Good... good!
[You just wait and see!]
[It flipped over!]
That's it!
- It's okay. You did good.
- Ha Ha, that was it.
Ha Ha, you're on a roll.
- With his height...
- The power of sketchbook Ddak-ji!
I will show you its power!
- I'll show you its power!
- Just do it.
[Doesn't even budge...]
Nice, nice!
[Time for the water Ddak-ji from
Si Young of the Red Team.]
- Just hit it right in the middle.
- In the middle?
Hit it in the middle.
[Eliminates Kwang Soo's
sketchbook Ddak-ji.]
[Two people from the Green Team
are already eliminated.]
[Reaction befitting of
winning a national competition.]
That water Ddak-ji is awesome!
[Blue Team's Ha Ha starts
his attack on the water Ddak-ji!]
- You can't flip that thing over.
- That really can't be flipped over.
Okay, next up is Gary.
[Most recent King of Ddak-ji,
Gary enters the ring!]
My Ddak-ji is... the 'R' Ddak-ji.
[Green Team Gary's Ddak-ji
selection is the 'R' Ddak-ji.]
I'm going to go for this
persistent water Ddak-ji.
That water Ddak-ji really is...
You can't lose this, okay?
[Up in the air!]
[He flips it over!]
[I am... Kang Gary!]
Kang Gary!
[With his strength...
he really is Mr. Capable at times!]
Gary has a nice one.
His has some weight to it.
- Gary's Ddak-ji is pretty good.
- It has some weight to it.
- I think it's a really good one.
- He picked a good one.
[Full of confidence.]
I can't acknowledge your fashion.
[What's wrong with my fashion Ddak-ji!]
[Fashion Ddak-ji standing its ground!]
[Red Team's Suk Jin enters the ring.]
[Revenge for the water Ddak-ji?
'R' Ddak-ji is his target!]
- You have to get that one.
- Send that one out of here.
Stop it!
He's so bad...
[No kidding...]
[Red Team's Suk Jin...
The offensive Ddak-ji!]
You only get one chance to do this.
[His target is the Green Team's 'R' Ddak-ji.]
[Blue Team, Ha Ha's turn to attack!]
- Hey...
- Just hit it lightly.
[Easily flips it over!]
[Did you see that?]
Nice, nice!
[Blue Team's turn to attack!]
I should've flipped that one.
[Eliminates Green Team's 'R' Ddak-ji!]
[All three members of the Green Team
are now eliminated.]
I'm the King of Ddak-ji!
You did it with your 300 won Ddak-ji.
My worth is 200 won, and
this Ddak-ji is worth more than me!
This is my fashion Ddak-ji!
[None other than fashion Ddak-ji!]
The final player!
[If Jong Kook from the Red Team is
beaten, then the Blue Team wins!]
- Give me the chance...
- Fashion Ddak-ji!
[Ha Ha's fashion Ddak-ji vs.
Jong Kook's gold Ddak-ji.]
[Please...]
[Gold Ddak-ji not even budging.]
Jong Kook, show them all!
[The ultimate powerhouse of Ddak-ji,
Kim Jong Kook!]
- Take off your coat.
- Should I take it off?
[Coach Chu gets in the ring.]
Loosen up your shoulders.
This really is a Ddak-ji competition.
[If there was a Ddak-ji world championship,
this is what it would be like.]
- Fighting...
- Fighting!
Sung Hoon, you have to get down.
[Goodbye, fashion Ddak-ji.]
[It didn't flip over!]
[If the Blue Team succeeds with their attack,
then they win the competition!]
It's okay, you're doing good.
[Going right into Jong Kook's turn.]
- Jong Kook, hit it in the middle!
- I got this! I got this!
Here it goes!
Get it out of there!
Fashion... fashion!
- You did good...
- Get out!
Are you copying what Jong Kook did?
[Blue Team's Chu Sung Hoon's turn!]
[Complete attention]
Throw it down, Sung Hoon.
[Sung Hoon's Ddak-ji from the Blue Team, a
double Ddak-ji made up of two separate ones.]
[The flow of the victory could reverse
with this one game!]
- There he goes... there he goes!
- Here I go!
- Sung Hoon... concentrate.
- Yes.
[At last, it's Sung Hoon from
the Blue Team's turn to attack.]
Sung Hoon, be careful and concentrate.
No need to get greedy.
- Get revenge for my fashion Ddak-ji.
- One blow and you could end it.
- You can't do it, you can't do it!
- You can't do it, you're too nervous!
You can't do it, you can't do it!
You can do it, you can do it...
[Mr. Capable concentrating all his
energy into his Ddak-ji.]
You can do this, you can do this!
[He flips it over!]
[How... can this be?]
- Who's next?
- Come on out!
[Is it... my turn now?]
[I was the original King of Ddak-ji...
Do you remember?]
[But... one day...]
[I became the new King of Ddak-ji after
having flipped over the ultimate Ddak-ji.]
[I will reclaim my seat as
the King of Ddak-ji today...]
[Jae Suk's supreme Ddak-ji vs.
Jong Kook's gold Ddak-ji.]
- You're Kim Ddak-ji!
- Jong Kook, you're Kim Ddak-ji.
This is really making me nervous.
[Praying desperately...]
Just give me the chance...
You worked hard today, Jong Kook...
Just hurry up and do it!
[This moment is today's highlight.]
- Loosen up your shoulders.
- I'll just finish it here.
I'll just finish it and don't drag it out.
It needs to end for it to be fun.
- You can do it, you can do it...
- You'll get it...
God of variety shows, please...
[There he goes!]
Our moment has come!
[Who knew that a Ddak-ji game
could be this nerve-wrecking...]
You can't do it, you can't do it...
- You're too nervous, you're too nervous...
- Ddak-ji King! Ddak-ji King!
[It didn't even budge!]
Jae Suk, that's no joke.
[Gathering up his energy once more...]
That's heavy... that's a heavy Ddak-ji.
That's a heavy Ddak-ji.
- He can't do it.
- You're too nervous to do it!
[Jae Suk's Ddak-ji is turned over
in a disadvantageous position!]
You can do this!
[Can't even bare to watch.]
[Didn't flip over!]
[Even though it moved, it didn't flip over!]
- I'm seriously so nervous!
- Can we do this at the end of every race?
This is so much fun.
You saw what happened earlier, right?
In my opinion, it's going to flip this time.
I'm going to finish this.
Jong Kook... just another cm closer.
- Me? Closer?
- Yes, just another cm.
- Good?
- Yes.
Why is all this so important?
[Gets into attack mode again after
getting instructed by Si Young!]
[He flips it over!]
This is the happiest I've ever seen him in
the three years he's been on Running Man!
Si Young, here's your prize.
[Today's winning prize is a Hanwoo beef set.]
Subtitles by DramaFever