[The Asia Race that took them around
Asia in search of the nine daggers.]
[Landing in Macau...]
[Then after a trip around Hanoi...]
[Running Man expedition gets all
nine daggers in their possession.]
[And finds the legendary golden dagger
of mystery inside the golden turtle!]
[But even a greater mystery was cloaked
around that recovered golden dagger...]
[The legend of the golden dagger,
going back to the origin of that mystery.]
[The absolute power of the sword,
known as the Golden Sword.]
[The chaotic history that was caused
by the power of the absolute sword.]
[The secret of the nine daggers-
The legend of the golden dagger's origin.]
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Vietnam]
[Hanoi]
[Bustling of Vietnam citizens
early in the morning.]
[Running Man's dormitory-
Hanoi's 'L' Tower.]
[A peaceful sleepy morning...]
[Outside of the member's doors...]
[Costume and a letter?]
Good morning.
Vietnam... good morning.
Change into the outfit,
and read the letter.
What is this?
Change into the outfit,
and read the letter.
- Change into this?
- Yes.
Isn't this...
Isn't this Vietnam's traditional outfit?
Ao dai.
[Vietnam's traditional outfit meaning,
'Long gown'.]
This is my outfit?
I have to get dressed in this?
Are we going to be wearing this all day?
Good morning.
We need to get dressed in this today?
[Changing into the Ao dai style.]
[X-form...]
[How do I look?]
[Fashion is all about self-confidence.]
[Traditional samurai?]
[What a pretty picture!]
I've changed into it.
Isn't this pretty?
[Blank Ji dressed up in cheery,
yellow Ao dai.]
Does it look okay?
Does it look okay on me?
But still...
I feel embarrassed dressed in this.
I'm so embarrassed to be
dressed in this.
[Checking the letter...]
Episode zero of
the secret of the nine daggers...
[Secret of the nine daggers-
Episode zero?]
[First, head over to the helicopter airfield.]
[There, you will find three helicopters!]
So there are only three helicopters?
[A situation where getting there first
will definitely put you at an advantage!]
[Heading off to the helicopter airfield
once his hair is nicely brushed.]
We're taking the helicopter?
[Once we're in the helicopter,
where are we being taken off to?]
First, I need to find a taxi.
And get to the helicopter airfield.
Look at that waterfall...
Vietnam's waterfall.
[Passing by a refreshing
outdoor waterfall...]
That's a really tall building!
It's making me dizzy.
Hi, Vietnam.
I like trees.
And flowers.
And... Vietnam.
Wow, that's so tall!
[The height of the building making even
the giraffe crane his neck to stare up at it.]
Can you take me to the helicopter field?
The helicopter field.
[Giraffe-glish]
[Each heading on their way off
to the helicopter field.]
They're finally starting to know my name.
But they still don't have a
sign made up with my name on it.
I was told that it's more advantageous to
get there early, but I think I'm late.
[The reason for being at an advantage
to get to the helicopter field early is...]
[Passing through the city of Hanoi...]
So it's possible that not all of us
may be able to get in a helicopter?
Thank you.
[The taxi arrives on site.]
Am I the first one to arrive?
[Just who will be the first one to
get aboard one of the helicopters?]
Okay...
I'm finally about to board the helicopter.
You startled me!
[Morning prank to startle Ro-Ro.]
[Giraffe and Ro-Ro boarding
the helicopter right away.]
But it's kind of scary...
[Scared!]
[The helicopter lifting off the ground!]
[Where are they being taken to?]
[Frozen like a block of ice.]
I would like to say my greetings to
Vietnam, dressed in my Ao dai.
[The second helicopter is also
ready to take flight.]
I'm going to imitate what Jae Suk
is about to do.
[Making fun of Jae Suk.]
Here we go!
[Fly through the sky!]
[Clapping and cheering.]
[And frozen in his place.]
This is so much fun!
[But this man finds no fun in the ride...]
[Flying through the air of Hanoi...
and off to Trang An!]
[Even the last group finally takes flight.]
[And so, the helicopters
takes flight into the sky...]
[In a few moments...]
[Into the vortex that'll take them to a time
where the mystery of golden dagger awaits!]
[And in that place...]
[awaits the absolute power...]
[of the absolute golden dagger.]
[Secret of the nine daggers - The prequel.]
[Trang An]
Jae Suk, look down there.
It's so amazing!
[An area that used to be the capital
of the ancient kingdom...]
[The land of Halond Bay, Trang An.]
[Somewhere in this place...]
[Lies the absolute sword that
hold the absolute power!]
[Overwhelming beauty of nature
that captures their gaze.]
[The superb beauty with a hidden legend.]
[Golden sword expedition that
has brought them to a place of legend.]
Look!
It's the Running Man flag!
[The helicopter touches down in Trang An.]
[Now in order to find the legendary
golden sword...]
[Their journey is about to begin.]
[The place these two are heading towards
as soon as they're off the helicopter is...]
[Boats lined up side by side
on the calm river.]
[On the other side of the river
somewhere...]
[The absolute golden dagger
lies await in hiding.]
[Rushing is Running Man's nature.]
Wow, this place is seriously so beautiful!
I feel like a dragon is going to
pop out of here somewhere.
This won't go forward.
Ah! This is so frustrating!
Kwang Soo, what are you doing?
Ha Ha, wait for me!
[Giraffe's clumsy skills with the oars.]
How do I make this go forward?
This broke off!
My oar fell out of its place!
I said, my oar fell out of its place!
[How are you going to go find
the golden dagger that way?]
[On the other hand, Ro-Ro's boat
is nicely gliding ahead in its path.]
I've had experience paddling boats before.
How do I make this go in
the direction I want it to go in?
A helicopter is heading this way!
[Second helicopter about to
make its landing.]
We must be here.
[Golden dagger explorers
arriving one by one.]
Wow!
It's so beautiful!
[While taking in the breathtaking
beauty of his surroundings...]
[Ro-Ro heading the pack in the lead.]
[Wait... that place is?]
[A mysterious temple
floating on top of the river.]
[And there's the 'R' flag!]
[Is that the place?]
[Huh?]
[Who's the woman flagging him down?]
Okay!
[Ro-Ro touching ground
at the mysterious temple.]
Hi!
Hi.
[Confused]
What happened?
Gae-took, Gae-took (Keep going)...
['Gae-took'... only Vietnamese word he knows?]
No... Gae-took.
[I don't want to row anymore...]
In...
Huh? I have to go back again?
Go?
Move?
[Wanting him to go somewhere...]
Where are you going?
- Kwang Soo...
- Where are you going?
You have to meet one of
these ladies too.
Dong Hoon!
What is this place?
- Dong Hoon!
- We're not going in there, are we?
You're seriously going to go by yourself?
Are we going in there?
[Just where is he being taken to?]
[Huh? A hidden entrance next
to the temple?]
I feel like something is going to
jump out at me.
[The boat is gliding into the cave.]
This is scary.
[Scary... yet fascinating...]
This feels like something
out of a movie.
[Fascinating cave with narrow
and low ceiling passages.]
Even though I'm scared, it's still amazing.
How can a place like this exist?
[Nonstop mumbling from being frightened.]
I've never been to a place like this before.
What is...
Why is Running Man all of a sudden...
This feels like something out of a movie.
Isn't this terrifying?
Please drive safely.
[Kwang Soo follows Ha Ha's trail
into the cave.]
That's just a huge rock, isn't it?
In there?
We're going in there?
What is this?
Are you sure it's this way?
Where are we going?
In here... are you sure about this?
Are you sure this is a passageway?
This is no joke!
Those things up there
that look like icicles...
Sta... statics?
[You mean, stalactite?]
[Second group still rowing their boats.
Jae Suk, Dong Wook, and Blank Ji.]
Wow... how are we doing this?
Wow... this is hard.
Hey...
Dong Wook!
Why am I turning in circles?
Mine won't go forward!
Why can't anything be easy?
How am I supposed to do this?
[Going deeper into the cave...]
What is that?
[Inside the cave...]
[Is another small cave?]
[Scaredy cat Ro-Ro steps out
of the boat...]
What's this?
Is this the end?
[Discovers a hidden scroll!]
[When you possess the powerful
sword in hand...
powers greater than you can
ever imagine...]
[Once a powerful golden sword is in your
possession, you will gain amazing powers.]
[Use the amazing powers of the golden
sword to awaken the golden turtle...
[by giving it up as a sacrifice, and
gain the power to rule the earth.]
[Giraffe also arrives at the
secret cave's opening.]
Dong Hoon.
Dong Hoon!
What are you doing?
What is that?
You and I...
You and I can do this together.
[These two characters...]
I discovered this here.
- What?
- You were trying to hide this?
No, I was going to show it to you.
[The legend of the golden sword.]
- We have to do this together.
- It's a map.
[A map on the back of the scroll.]
Where is this place?
Is this where we're at right now?
[Does this mean outside the cave is where
the absolute golden sword lies in wait?]
- Dong Hoon... let's do it together.
- Kwang Soo, we're in this together.
Tr-ai-tors Cross!
Go, go, go!
Sword... the golden sword.
If I can just get that sword...
the whole world will become mine.
[Once the sword is in his possession,
the world will become his to rule!]
[Giraffe of the Traitors Club dreaming
the same dream and Ro-Ro.]
[That sword will be mine!]
[The last group finally getting
the oars in their hands.]
Why is this suddenly...
Oh, this is out of its place.
Jong Kook just broke the boat!
He broke the oar
because of his brute strength!
Seriously... he broke the oar!
Why did you have to jump in my boat
and making yourself suffer?
I don't know.
I should've just gotten a boat of my own.
[Suk Jin and Hye Jin's boat not looking
as though it's going to make any progress.]
When are we ever going to get there?
Where are we even going?
[Going backwards...]
Why does this thing keep circling around?
[On the other hand, inside the cave...]
Oh my...
It's so mystical...
the inside of the cave is so mystical.
For some reason, in place like this...
I feel like some mysterious treasure
would be hidden in here somewhere.
I feel like I'm treasure hunting.
[Finally heading back out of the cave?]
[Ro-Ro having reached the other
end of the cave.]
That's awesome.
That's seriously so awesome.
[Heading back out of the cave
just shown on the map.]
[Greeted with another grandiose
and spectacular sight.]
[On top of that hill...]
[A mysterious gateway!]
This feels like a magical island.
Kwang Soo...
Dong Hoon... I think that's the house
that was pictured on the map.
[The golden sword... must be up there!]
This is unbelievable.
[Heading towards the mysterious gateway.]
'The Mummy'... and 'Indiana Jones'...
[Keeping up with his nonstop chatter
from all the mysticism.]
Look at this place.
This is so amazing.
This is just like a work of art.
This is like a scene right out of a movie.
This is the Running Man movie.
[Giraffe following right in
Ro-Ro's footsteps.]
[Will the golden sword really be
found through that gateway?]
- I think we're heading in there.
- Yeah... I think we're heading in there.
The way we look right now...
It's like you're the rich Vietnamese man...
- and I'm the young trophy wife.
- The young trophy wife.
[The rich couple taking a
scenic tour of the cave.]
My wife... I will make you happy
for the rest of your life.
Rich, rich?
Rich, rich, rich?
I'm a rich man!
[The rich couple heading to the
inside of the cave.]
Are you sure that we're
supposed to go in here?
Are you sure we're allowed in here?
Is anyone here?
Is no one in here?
Wow... just where in the world
is this place?
[Jae Suk and Dong Wook having
exited from the other side of the cave.]
This is really...
[Discovers the mysterious gateway.]
Wow... I can't believe something
like that is up there.
Don't you think this is something
you'd see out of a martial arts movie?
Yeah, you'd totally see that.
[The gateway full of majestic air.]
Amazing.
This is unbelievable.
[Ro-Ro finally arrives at the entrance
of the gateway.]
[The mysterious gateway of Trang An.]
This is amazing.
Just amazing.
[The door that will lead you to Hoa Lu where
the legendary golden turtle awaits in slumber.]
[The door that leads to Hoa Lu?]
[Where could the golden sword be?]
[This is... the golden sword.]
[The power to give the beholder
an absolute power...]
[The legendary golden sword.]
The golden sword...
This is it.
[The sword... has finally been found!]
[The energy from the sword?]
[Now...]
[The sword is mine...]
[Is this... the secret of the golden sword?]
[Kwang Soo also finally arrives
at the entrance of the gateway.]
I've finally arrived.
When I was little...
this is the place where I mastered
my martial arts skills.
[Would you like to have a match with
a real martial arts master next time?]
- Kwang Soo...
- Dong Hoon!
Lee Kwang Soo... hurry up and get up here.
- Where are you?
- I can't do this alone.
Are you up there?
[Ro-Ro urging Kwang Soo to come up.]
Dong Hoon...
I'm so scared.
- The golden sword...
- Is this the place?
- Kwang Soo...
- Did you find the golden sword?
[Hiding the golden sword
behind his back?]
The golden sword is something
that we can't have.
- What are you talking about?
- I'll give it to you.
[Huh? You're going to give me the sword?]
- What's the golden sword?
- Kwang Soo...
I'm so scared.
- I'm so scared.
- Where's the golden sword?
It's right here.
[Is Ro-Ro really...]
I'll give this to you.
Here, take this.
- Okay?
- You're giving it to me?
I can't do it alone.
Kwang Soo...
- Please... save the world.
- Dong Hoon...
- Promise me.
- I promise...
For my master... and my father...
And for you...
I will get our revenge on the enemy!
Get down on one knee.
Kwang Soo...
Halt.
[Huh?]
[This is...]
What did you say?
[Time comes to a halt
for Kwang Soo.]
[Could this be the power
of the golden sword?]
- This sword...
- What is this?
This sword...
I can't do anything about
the control it has over me.
What is this?
[With the absolute golden sword in hand,
Ha Ha eliminates Kwang Soo's name tag!]
- Lee Kwang Soo, out.
- I'm out?
What?
I'm out?
[Just like this... is Kwang Soo
eliminated from the expedition?]
- Goodbye.
- Dong Hoon!
[The Traitor's Cross coming to
a shatter as predicted.]
[Is that... the power of
the ultimate golden sword?]
[Stop time?]
[So this is the power of the
ultimate golden sword!]
- Kwang Soo...
- Dong Hoon!
Lee Kwang Soo...
hurry up and get up here.
[The reason why he called Kwang Soo
to come up was...]
[Because he had planned on
eliminating Kwang Soo!]
[Oblivious to everything,
Giraffe walks on up the steps.]
Hurry.
[Ha Ha waiting for Kwang Soo while
keeping the power of the sword a secret.]
[And with that power,
he eliminates Kwang Soo!]
Now...
The world...
will be mine!
[The world is mine!]
[Must hurry to where
the golden turtle awaits.]
All of the Running Man members
that have disregarded me...
Shut... your mouths.
Be... be quiet!
Stand... stand still.
All Running Man members and viewers
that have disregarded me...
Today, you will see the true powers
of Haroro come to light.
[Behold my ultimate power as I possess
the ultimate golden sword in my hand.]
[Where the legendary golden turtle
lies in slumber...]
[The door that leads back to Hoa Lu!]
[Through the gateway in Trang An...]
[To Hoa Lu.]
[Hoa Lu: A historical site of an
ancient dynasty.]
[Ultimate golden sword...]
[Transforming back into Haroro mode...]
[This is fun!]
There are a lot of natives here.
[To protect the ultimate golden sword...]
[The legendary golden turtle
is said to be here in Hoa Lu.]
[On the other hand...]
[Jae Suk and Dong Wook heading
towards the mysterious gateway.]
Are we going to see the master
or something?
I've realized this while
filming Running Man...
there's no way you can gain weight
while being on this show.
[Arriving at the gateway entrance.]
Where do we need to go?
Can we just walk through?
Do we need to go up?
What the heck?
What is it?
Did you find something?
What is this?
[Kwang Soo's name tag!]
- Hey! Dong Wook!
- Yes, I'm on my way up.
Why is Kwang Soo's name tag up here?
There it is.
Someone already took the sword.
It's Ha Ha.
[That means Ha Ha...]
- It can't be.
- Wait...
[Since the race has started?]
Ha Ha found the sword and
eliminated Kwang Soo's name tag.
Kung Fu!
Doesn't it feel like we're making our way
up to a ultimate secret fighter's club?
Give it back.
- Let's go, Gary.
- Yes, Jong Kook.
Jong Kook...
I'll go first, and check it out.
- Jong Kook.
- Let's go together.
- Don't push yourself too hard, Jong Kook.
- Hey!
I'll go ahead first.
[So this is the door that leads
to Hoa Lu...]
[Ha Ha has the ultimate golden sword...]
Ha Ha found the sword and
eliminated Kwang Soo before he went.
Yes, he did.
Ha Ha...
[Huh?]
[Startling his VJ, Gwon Yeol.]
What are you doing?
That's the effect that you
see in movies!
When it flies through the air
and sticks right in front of the camera.
Why are you so afraid of it?
Seriously...
Are you here on a picnic or something?
I can't stay hidden because
you're dressed like that.
Look at how colorful the shirt is
that you're wearing.
Let's go.
[At last... off to Hoa Lu.]
We have to find Ha Ha.
[Ha Ha you scoundrel... where are you?]
- We have to take it from Ha Ha.
- Of course, that's a given.
I'm... going to win today!
- I'm going to win!
- Me!
[Gary and Ji Hyo also head
towards the gateway.]
[This door will lead you to Hoa Lu where the
legendary golden turtle awaits in slumber.]
[To Hoa Lu...]
[Running Man members arriving in
Hoa Lu one by one.]
[The final rich couple.]
[The rich couple's world
will come find them...]
[The rich couple falling into
each other's beat.]
Look at all that.
[This is Hoa Lu!]
[And...]
No!
[Giraffe being delivered to Hoa Lu
by the grim reapers.]
I'll get my revenge!
[Heads right over to jail.]
This is a lie.
This is all a lie!
First, they don't know the power
that I'm capable of.
I have the golden sword which
possesses the ultimate power.
While... being on
Running Man all this time...
the energy that I've received
from Suk Jin...
the sorrow of being the race starter...
I will get my revenge with today's race.
From this point on...
if I spot you in my sight...
or if I see you anywhere...
I will shout out for you to 'Halt'.
[I will shout out for you to 'Halt'.]
To start things off,
I need to eliminate one of them.
That way they'll know to fear me.
I think I'm slowly starting to go crazy.
[You get that too?]
Any moment...
I think I'm going to go insane at any moment.
I think something's invaded my body.
All the sorrow I've felt thus far...
I will get my revenge for it today.
[All the sorrow I've been given...
I will repay them today!]
[On the other hand...]
[Jae Suk and Dong Wook on the search
for Ha Ha who took the golden sword away.]
- Isn't that him?
- Over there.
Ha Ha!
[Discovers the owner of the golden sword
who's slowly on his way to insanity.]
He's totally into his character.
Hey...
[I will... show you my powers.]
Why did you...
you ousted Kwang Soo, didn't you?
Why do you have the golden sword?
I will give you until the count of three
to make your escape.
- One of you are going to die right now.
- Why?
By the time I count to three...
I suggest that one of you run away.
- You found the power, did you?
- Okay...
- One... one of you are really going to die.
- Really?
[Oh... so this is how you're going to play?]
My black grim reapers...
come this way, please.
I'm really going to do this.
One... two...
Three!
Come here!
One of you are going to die!
One of you are going to...
keep on running!
Keep on running!
Should I go left or to the right?
Let's go to the left!
One of you...  one of you!
Run faster, run faster, run faster!
I said, run faster!
- Here I go...
- What is this?
- I'll give you three more seconds to run.
- What are you doing?
Three seconds!
Don't ever show yourself
in front of me again.
Wow... this is awesome.
This is why I'm going insane.
The golden sword is what it's all about.
I wonder if that sword
allows him to do anything?
Hey!
Jae Suk!
If you're curious,
why don't you go check it out?
What's his deal?
- Why is he acting like that?
- What is the deal with him?
I think it has some sort of
special power.
- I think the knife gives you power.
- I think you're right.
- This is...
- Ah!
Those grim reapers were
following him around.
Do you think Ha Ha gets to order
them around like servants?
I think they do his bidding.
I think they do his bidding for him.
[Since they don't know the sword's power,
their terror is multiplied by two!]
[The feeling of having the whole world
in his control!]
Serves them right.
No matter who they may be...
As soon as they see me...
I will make them run away in fear.
Why is he being like that?
Just what in the world is going on?
- I don't know.
- What power does it have?
His character is totally different.
[frustrated and afraid from not knowing
the power the sword is capable of.]
- Then... is there no way around it?
- There he is.
See?
Look at that glint in his eyes.
Wow, you really are...
[What's wrong with him?]
Shall we do a little jogging?
- What's wrong with him?
- This time, Dong Wook...
[Unable to confront him,
so no other choice but to run!]
Why are you running?
Run, run!
What's the reason?
What's the reason for all this?
[With the golden sword in my hand...
everyone is in fear of me!]
This is so fun.
This is what it's all about.
Please remain my side forever.
[The sweetest of the power...
slowly going even more insane?]
Stay with me forever...
I love you.
I love you...
- Please be my eternal love.
- You think you're Gollum?
[Now that he mentions it,
Ha Ha's speech and behavior is slowly...]
[My precious...]
He really is a sight.
[That golden sword... how do I steal it?]
This really is a stab at my pride.
More than anyone else,
to be chased around by Ha Ha like that...
What is that?
Hey, Kwang Soo!
Hey, do you know what's going on?
I don't even know the game
that's being played today.
I saw your name tag that was left
up on the pedestal.
- Today we were...
- Yeah...
[Mr. Capable stops by their way
while on his way past them.]
- What happened to you?
- Right now...
He all of a sudden shouted out, 'Halt', and
I was grabbed so I couldn't move anymore.
- Who did? Who did that?
- The grim reapers.
- It was Ha Ha.
- Ha Ha?
Let me borrow your hat.
I have to disguise myself somehow.
How are you going to do that
when you're wearing that bright red outfit?
- I can at least hide my face.
- Did you only come for the hat?
Let me come with you!
- Can you keep an eye on my bag?
- What are you doing?
[With things borrowed...
and asking to keep an eye on things...]
What am I, the lost and found?
[Just then...]
[The owner of the golden sword
makes his appearance.]
My master's enemy.
You were once like a brother to me.
Do you know what happens if I use
this power on you one more time?
You'll get kicked out of here.
Watch closely...
as to what I'm about to do.
They all run from me
as soon as they see me.
A power like that has been given to me.
You have... no idea how much fun it is.
Like scared...
like scared little rats.
This sword was mine.
That's not true.
Say hello to my one and eternal love.
Call her 'Sister-in-law'.
Say hello to your Sister-in-law.
- If you don't, I'll kill you.
- Sister-in-law.
Sister-in-law...
Please be my eternal love.
Say hello.
I said, hello.
Aren't you going to do it?
Hello, Sister-in-law.
Kiss the top of my foot.
Do it!
- I won't do it.
- I said, do it!
I'll never do it!
Thanks for the laugh.
[Leaving after having toyed
with Kwang Soo.]
My precious...
I will grant Lee Kwang Soo his one wish.
Why?
Because I have the ultimate power.
Lee Kwang Soo...
All the memories you have of being laughed at
and disregarded since being on Running Man...
remember them all.
Any one person that you want...
I will eliminate for you.
In that case...
JK.
[JK= Jong Kook.]
JK...
I'll be leaving.
You cute little scoundrel.
Please don't do it.
I really think I'm truly going insane.
[Anyone with
the ultimate power in their hands...]
Kim Jong Kook!
[Will he truly be able to oust Mr. Capable?]
Dong Wook!
Who has the sword?
- Suk Jin, we're in trouble.
- Why?
It's no joke right now.
- Hey, Dong Wook...
- He's totally turned into Gollum.
He keeps holding onto the sword
and muttering about how much he loves it.
He's going around with the
grim reapers on his trail.
So when Ha Ha shouts out, 'Halt',
the reapers will take you away.
And Ha Ha can eliminate your
name tag that way.
[Finally understand how Ha Ha is using
the ultimate golden sword's power.]
So the three of us will have to face
the grim reapers...
and then one of us will have to grab
Ha Ha and take the sword away from him.
Kwang Soo's already been ousted.
- Kwang Soo's been ousted?
- Lets go.
Move as fast as you can to oust him.
- You can't, so we'll take down the reapers.
- No, I can't do that.
Kim Jong Kook!
- How are you going to get the reapers?
- Here he comes.
- What do we do? What do we do?
- Everyone has to move.
[Stop the reapers and get Ha Ha!]
I'll get them, so get Ha Ha.
[Ha Ha with his ultimate power
makes his entrance.]
- Get the reapers... get them.
- I'll get them.
Get the reapers... get them.
Ha Ha... you have to get Ha Ha.
Why are you running away?
Why are you running?
[Plan fails! Faced with fear,
the plan fails immediately.]
Why are you running?
Why are you running away?
[Ha Ha chasing after his target,
Mr. Capable.]
[Opening up the ultimate sword!]
[Ha Ha finally pulls out
the ultimate golden sword!]
Hey... you're really doing this to me?
To me?
Utilize me, Dong Hoon.
You can utilize me!
- You can use me like your reapers.
- I don't need to use you.
Because I have the ultimate power.
I have the golden sword.
Why me?
When there are plenty of others.
All members of Running Man,
gather around.
- Everyone, gather around!
- Come here!
- I said, come here!
- In order...
The first person to get here,
I will save you until the end to eliminate.
- What is it?
- Why me?
- Why?
- In order...
- I said, come on?
- What's going on here?
That looks like fun.
Today's race is really fun.
All the people who have neglected me and
despised me are now gathered in front of me.
- That's not me.
- Suk Jin...
- Go stand afar and watch what I do.
- Okay. Thanks!
Kwang Soo, thanks!
Kwang Soo?
No, stay right here.
No... you can't let him get away now.
Okay... everyone will say
one nice thing about me.
Each of you will now say
one good thing about me now.
If you can't say it within three seconds,
you're dead.
- Set, go.
- Dong Hoon...
All my little girl cousins
are fans of yours.
They said they love only you.
You're the best reggae
in our country.
- Reggae artist.
- You have nothing?
- He's taking too long.
- He's late.
Wait.
- You always make me jealous of you.
- Wait...
Is there even one time when
you felt envious of me?
Tell me when that moment was.
Tell me right now!
- I'm being serious.
- Dong Hoon...
What's the power that you really have?
- Can you just tell us that?
- The ability to take over your name tags.
- Just like that?
- Just like that.
- If you want it?
- Whenever you want?
[Saying one nice thing about Ha Ha...
now it's Mr. Capable's turn.]
You're the best husband in this country.
You're really all starting to bore me.
- You're the best husband in this country.
- That expression is really...
- That expression is making me feel too old!
- You're a sexy beast!
- Kim Jong Kook to the front!
- Go up front.
- Why me? Why me?
- Watch carefully.
- You will get to feel true fear.
- What's going to happen?
- Why is he standing like that?
- Why me? Why am I chosen?
Halt, Kim Jong Kook!
[The protectors of the sword,
captures Mr. Capable at Ha Ha's command!]
Once I rip this off...
if you don't run away within two seconds,
another one of you will be dead.
What the heck?
We were all supposed to do this together!
[Trembling in fear...
this is the order to halt?]
We were all supposed to
do this together!
- Three.
- Seriously?
[Mr. Capable, Out!]
[Shock]
[Terror]
[The gruesome public execution
taking place right in front of their eyes?]
[Unreal...
Mr. Capable getting eliminated so easily...]
What's going on?
[Crazed Haroro reigning his terror
upon all the people!]
[Used up two out of three chances
to stop time...]
[Just who will become his last target?]
The truth is, Lee Kwang Soo made a
request to Ha Ha to eliminate you.
What did you say?
He's just saying that because
he's jealous of our relationship.
- Hey... you seriously..
- You believe what he said?
- Have you lost your mind?
- Salute!
- Say hello to you sister-in-law.
- Hello, Sister-in-law!
Have a seat.
Okay... I've kept my promise to you
to fulfill your wish.
You asked me to bring Jong Kook to you.
I've fulfilled you your wish.
Now then... I hope the two of you
have a lovely time together.
Have you lost your mind?
- Wait... listen to me.
- What?
- I wanted you for myself.
I wanted to be with you.
You're really...
What is this?
Why does this hurt so badly?
Wait... what is this?
[A fascinating experience of making him
jump out of his seat with just two fingers.]
[Didn't realize to make an attempt at
attacking Mr. Capable's injured foot.]
Foot!
[But he fails even at that...]
Why are you like this to me?
- Jong Kook...
- You really...
I should've had the chance to do something
while we're at a place like this.
I don't even know what's
going on today.
Hey!
[Other members feeling even more
separated with Mr. Capable getting ousted.]
Kwang Soo and Jong Kook have been
ousted. There are grim reapers.
- The sword uses the grim reapers.
- The keepers of the sword?
[Relaying the power Ha Ha has with the
sword to Gary and Blank Ji.]
The reapers will grab you so you can't move
and Ha Ha will eliminate your name tag.
- Then that means...
- Then how is the game going to play out?
- I know.
- I'm sure there's a way to free it.
I'm sure there's a way for us
to stop that from being used...
It must be nice for you today.
You blend right in with everyone
walking around here today.
You should walk around with a hat on.
[Wait... now that she takes
a look around...]
[Everyone around here is
dressed in yellow.]
Suk Jin, should I blend myself in
to get rid of him?
[A surprising find of an opportunity!]
[Secretly approach Ha Ha to eliminate him
by utilizing her yellow clothing?]
- Since I'm dressed in the same clothing.
- You can't be told apart dressed like that.
Yeah... we have to oust him
anyway that we can.
- Suk Jin, I'll try it. I'll give it a try.
- He's out of control right now.
I'll give it a try.
Ji Hyo, be careful of your name tag.
Hye Jin... we're in trouble.
Let's do it together and
get rid of him.
- Let's work together to get rid of him.
- Listen to her talking that nonsense.
Why?
[Explaining things to her in detail since
she's only glimpsed at what's happened.]
They're doing whatever
Ha Ha commands them to?
Yeah, when Ha Ha just told them to stop
the cow from pooping, they did.]
[Loyal keepers of the sword who'll even
clean up the cow poop if they're told to.]
I'm scared.
Ha Ha's suddenly starting to
look more powerful.
[Wait... where did Ji Hyo go?]
I can't see Ji Hyo anywhere.
[They just parted a little while ago,
but she really is nowhere to be seen now.]
I can't see Ji Hyo anywhere.
Hurry... hurry.
[Ji Hyo used her time to gather others
of similar height and build around her.]
- Hello.
- Hello, Ji Hyo.
- You're not Korean, are you?
- No, we're Vietnamese.
Will you help me?
- Please take good care of me.
- Nice to meet you.
It's nice to meet you... nice to meet you.
First...
Just keep walking like this...
and when I give you the signal,
pair up in two's and walk around him.
Understand?
Walk in a group and first, then in two's.
And if Ha Dong Hoon is about to see me,
hide me by gathering around me.
But...
- We can't make it too obvious, okay?
- Yes.
Let's go.
[Ace Ji Hyo finally starts
her plan to infiltrate!]
Ha Dong Hoon... you're dead.
As for you two...
start searching for Kang Gary.
Once you find out his location,
alert me with a signal. Understood?
[Loyal keepers of the
ultimate golden sword.]
And you will act exactly as I do, understood?
Why aren't you following my lead?
You will follow my lead.
I'm not in the best mood
at the moment.
I'm sorry.
I'm sure you must be hot.
We will now search for Kang Gary.
Let's go.
Nobody knows how much of this
ultimate power I have left.
Even if I use the power now...
they're going to keep being afraid of me.
Let's eliminate Gary first.
He's heading this way.
[Hiding herself behind the tree...]
[Ji Hyo is starting to close in.]
Ha Dong Hoon... you're a dead man.
[Suk Jin is also secretly
making his approach.]
Suk Jin!
Suk Jin, come over here.
I promise that I'm not going to kill you.
I'm seriously not going to kill you,
so come here quickly.
Suk Jin... if you don't come in five seconds,
I'm only going to come chasing after you.
- Five, four, three...
- Hey, Dong Hoon...
- Two... one.
- I'm here.
Okay... I'm going to walk up to you.
I promise that I won't eliminate you.
- I promise.
- Okay, with your future on the line.
It's race start.
Do you understand?
Okay, here we go.
We are now on the same team.
- Thank you.
- Who's team are you on?
I'm on Master Ha Ha's team.
The one and only Ha Ha!
Ha Ha is the road to our salvation!
So they're sticking together?
[Ace Ji Hyo continuing to
move in on Ha Ha.]
[Monday Couple's Gary also completes
his plan to sneak attack!]
From this point on,
I'm going after Kang Gary.
- Yes, I will help you.
- Go over there and grab Kang Gary.
- Me?
- Then I will save you 'til last.
You want me to grab him and
hold onto him?
- I understand.
- I think I just saw him go that way.
While I'm...
Move quickly while I'm still
speaking to you in honorifics.
Quickly... while I'm still using honorifics,
and giving you respect.
I'm starting to get a little angry.
You're getting what?
Wait a minute...
I said, my loyalty to you is
getting stronger.
[Can't even say anything
because of the ultimate golden sword.]
Okay, this will be your test.
All the traitors really are alike.
I just really want to get rid of him.
[Where are you, Kang Gary?]
Halt!
[Ha Ha chants out, 'Halt'
as he pulls out the sword!]
Let go of me!
- Let go of me!
- I shall do this where others can see.
[Crazed Haroro is planning on making
a public execution this time as well.]
[What to do!]
What's going on?
What is that?
Is Gary getting ousted?
[Gary's been caught...
I can't just stand by and watch again!]
Let go of me!
Let go!
Just what is that sword... just what is it
for you to be doing this to me?
Okay... so that everyone
around here can see...
Get him down on his knees.
Good job.
You did good corralling him.
[Ji Hyo...
come quickly and save me...]
Let go of me!
- I said, let go of me!
- Everyone gather around.
[Hang on just a little bit longer...
I'm coming...]
I am...
Black... uh...
Black Knife...
how to do you say 'Lord' in English?
- King, King... let's just go with King.
- King!
[Just then!]
[Ace Ji Hyo completes moving in on Ha Ha!]
[She's here.]
Everyone look at me.
[Ace Ji Hyo's ambush fails!]
[This is their only chance!
Everyone move in on the attack!]
Suk Jin, hurry up and rip it off!
[How... can this be...]
[Now... the beholder of
the ultimate sword is about to change!]
I lost my chance to rip it off!
Jae Suk, I didn't get to rip it off,
and Suk Jin ended up ripping it off.
We're in trouble...
we're in trouble now.
- Let go of me... let go!
- My world is here!
My world is here!
Suk Jin!
How could you do this to me?
This is how the world goes round!
[The one who lusts after the sword...
gets destroyed by the sword...]
[The new owner of
the ultimate golden sword... Ji Suk Jin.]
[The power of the golden sword changes
depending on the owner.]
[What could be the sword's new power?]
[The grim reaper's hand]
[If your gloved hand touches the name tag
as you shout out 'Grim Reaper's hand'...]
[that person will be ousted even if
you don't rip off the name tag.]
As long as my hand touches it.
It means touch is out.
The grim reaper's hand.
[The power of the ultimate golden sword
changes depending on the beholder.]
The Grim Reaper's Hand!
[Will Suk Jin use the sword's power
to win the race?]
[Worried...]
I have no idea what's going on.
[Like a clueless young daughter of a family
who married and moved down to the country...]
[and getting caught in total chaos with
her brothers who are down for a rare visit.]
With her younger brother
Dong Wook in town...
My old husband now has
the ultimate power.
He's my rich husband.
[Rich husband?]
[What does she do about her
husband now?]
Hello, Jong Kook!
Kwang Soo... hi!
Come over here.
Why... me?
This kid... picked you out.
Now that the sword is gone...
that poisonous effect on me is gone.
[He's back to being nice
now that the sword is gone?]
Suk Jin now has the sword
after having betrayed me.
Suk Jin... I bet he'll be like me.
If anything, he'll be worse than me.
So stop being angry now.
Okay... I'll start behaving like
I've been taught by the textbook.
I'm sorry.
Jong Kook, that really hurts!
It's okay, my friend.
Thank you.
Big-nose power!
Big-nose... power!
I am Big-nose power!
Big-nose power... the moment
my hand touches you, you're out...
Big-nose power!
[Huh? A cow in the middle of the road?]
[Conversing with the man
through the song?]
[Look at him having fun...]
[It seems he's asking Suk Jin to ride the cow
and get a souvenir picture taken.]
[Since he's in a good mood anyways,
why not?]
[With the ultimate golden sword in his hand,
he's feeling like a triumphant general!]
Does he normally do that?
I'm sorry but he keeps
hitting me with his tail.
[Thinking more and more...
that he shouldn't have gotten on it.]
His back is so sharp
that it's poking into me.
[Triumphant General shouldn't have
been so jubilant...]
Hey, stop hitting me with your tail!
What a riot...
What an ultimate power he has.
From this point on,
this is the Big-nose's world!
Follow me!
Big-nose power!
The world of Big-nose!
- He's calling himself Big-nose?
- What's with Big-nose power?
- Big-nose power!
What is that?
What's Big-nose power?
[After only three minutes...]
[Time of Big-nose's reign
comes to an end.]
[We can't stand to listen to
Big-nose power!]
- Dong Wook...
- Did you think I'd let you keep it?
He didn't even get to do anything!
Wow... he really looks so pathetic.
Wait...
Why is he even riding the cow?
He should be rushing to oust people.
Wow, now Dong Wook has the sword?
[Nervousness escalating with
the sword now in Dong Wook's hand.]
When Suk Jin had it,
it was like a rest period.
You really throw fastballs
with the things you say.
You don't mince your words.
You really are a fast ball thrower.
[The spectators curious about his power
since they never got to see it in action.]
[The grim reaper's hand was a good power...
Just one touch on the name tag, and it's out.]
- It was awesome power.
- You should've used it.
Suk Jin... if you'd done it...
try it out on me.
Put your hand on my back
as if you're going to eliminate me.
- I'll do this...
- Okay, give it a try.
- See, I touched it.
- But it was your other hand.
[What's this?
You can't even budge?]
I would've given you a break
and not come after you.
[That's you giving him a break?]
[If it went the other way around,
he could've eliminated his own name tag?]
I would've targeted either
Hye Jin or Ji Hyo.
Big-nose's power only targets the girls?
[Golden sword's third owner, Dong Wook...
What will the power be this time?]
I need to check the power.
[If you shout out, 'Cloning power',
all the name tags of the remaining survivors...
will be swapped out
for a single person's name tag.]
[This power can only be used once.]
Wait...
In that case... if I for example...
If I shout out Han Hye Jin's name,
then everyone will have her name tag?
[If he shouts out Han Hye Jin's name,
everyone's name tag will be swapped out.]
Listen...
Some people get easy powers like
having to just say, 'Halt'...
What is this?
This is too hard...
Should I just try it now?
Can I shout it out from here?
[Why not think about it some more?
You only have one chance!]
[Think about when and
who you're going to use it for...]
I need a quiet place to think.
[What special power did he receive?]
[This is making me nervous...]
- Gary!
- You startled me.
- What are you doing here?
- I have no idea what's going on.
[Since they don't know the power Dong Wook
has, they're unable to approach him easily.]
For example...
If I shout out Gary's name,
and everyone gets Gary's name tag...
no matter who's back I rip it off of,
then Gary is ousted.
Let's give it a try.
Cloning power...
[Because he's not saying it loud enough,
the power isn't being activated!]
Cloning power!
Kang Gary!
Kang Gary?
He just called out my name!
Why is he doing that?
He just did something and
shouted out Kang Gary's name.
[Huh?]
[Ji Hyo's name tag... changed into 'Gary'!]
He's changing out all the name tags?
That means... wait...
- What happens to me then?
- That's not it.
It means that everyone's name tag
is becoming 'Gary'.
[Hye Jin's name tag also gets
cloned to Gary's name!]
- If Gary gets caught...
- Ah, then everyone becomes Kang Gary.
[And over here,
you have your Gary the grasshopper.]
[Ultimately, no matter who gets ripped off,
it's Gary getting ousted.]
I'm right here!
Over here!
I'm Gary!
- No! I'm Gary!
- I'm Gary.
[Service right to his doorsteps.
Everyone delivering their tags to him.]
What are they doing?
Wait... no matter who gets ousted,
I'm the one getting eliminated?
That's right! No matter who it is,
Kang Gary is the one eliminated!
[Right now, everyone's Gary.
No matter who's ripped off, Gary gets ousted!]
You can't!
I'm right here!
Kang Gary's right here!
[In front of Dong Wook are
two other Gary's already.]
- Gary, don't come here!
- I'm Gary!
I'm Gary...
I'm Gary!
- Why are you raising your hands?
- I'm Gary.
[Even the original Gary
arrives on the scene.]
Why are you all saying that you're me?
- I'm...
- I'm Gary.
I'm the one...
I'm the Gary that lives in Jamsil!
- Why are you doing this to me?
- Okay, okay...
- What are you talking about?
- I'm Kang Gary!
- Everyone...
- Why are you all imitating me?
[Blank Ji breaking down to do
Gary's signature dance.]
Look here...
only I can dance that dance!
I can do it too... I can do the dance too!
[Even Hye Jin is moving her leg.]
I can do it too!
- I'm Gary... I'm Gary too.
- Stop!
I'm the real Gary. Even though
you've all now become Gary...
in a few moments,
you can all become Song Ji Hyo!
And after that,
you can all become Yoo Jae Suk too.
- I'm Gary.
- I'm the real Gary!
[All the Gary's not able to communicate
with one another.]
I'm the real Gary!
- Don't be like this!
- Wait... everyone...
Why did you have to give me
such a useless power as this?
What is this?
What kind of a power is this?
Even when I bungee jumped,
I was left feeling unsatisfied.
And all I did since coming on Running Man
was lose weight.
- You're all shouting that you're Gary..
- I'm telling you, I'm Gary!
- Then why don't you be Gary too?
- I'm Gary too!
I'm Gary too!
[You wanted to be included too, huh?]
- I'm Gary too!
- We're all Gary!
[Five Gary group dance.]
[That aside, when is Gary going
to be ousted?]
Don't do that!
Why are you trying to rip that off?
[Gary protecting Jae Suk
so that he can survive.]
- You're trying to save me...
- I'm Gary!
Don't be like this!
What are you doing?
This is my choice.
This is so annoying.
Maybe I should change the name.
- Hurry up and rip off his name.
- Should I go with Yoo Jae Suk this time?
Yoo Jae Suk's right here!
I'm Yoo Jae Suk!
[Feeling in danger, Jae Suk
quickly eliminates Gary's name tag!]
[Gary, Out!]
[From having dragged out all that time,
Jae Suk ousts Gary instead of Dong Wook!]
Yoo Jae Suk is going to be next...
and after that will be Song Ji Hyo!
- Go away!
- I'm the real Gary!
[The ultimate power...
angry for never having even possessed it!]
- The sword now belongs to Yoo Jae Suk.
- Why?
[Dong Wook already used up all the power
that the sword had to offer him.]
[Since Jae Suk ousted Gary instead of
Dong Wook, he's now the new owner.]
You're saying... that the sword is mine?
[What luck is this!]
Hand it over.
[I should've been quicker to rip it off...]
Dong Wook...
The fool!
From this moment, in this place...
a bloody revenge is going to ensue.
[The new owner of the sword...]
[The time for Jae Suk's reign has begun.]
Unbelievable.
I'm the ruler of this land!
Prepare yourselves!
Summon the spirits?
[If you shout out 'summon the spirit',
one of the eliminated people can be
resurrected and will become
your servant to order around.
But they can't eliminate anyone for you,
and will disappear after a given time.]
[There's a time limit!
However, the time limit is for 20 minutes!]
It's not really summoning the spirits...
But since they have to be resurrected,
it's 'Aren't you happy?' that you'll shout.
What the heck is that?
[With the summoning spell being so long,
he may get ousted while saying it.]
That's what you'll have to recite.
Why is the summon so long?
From this moment...
[Anyways, pulls out the sword...]
I will...
show you my powers!
What was that summon again?
Let's hurry it along!
You'll soon see my powers.
Lee Dong Wook...
Han Hye Jin...
and Blank Ji Hyo...
You guys are...
soon going to witness my powers!
Hurry up and do it!
What's your power?
Okay!
I'll do it!
Hear me!
To be resurrected once again...
aren't you so happy?
[To be resurrected once again...
aren't you so happy?]
I summon the spirits!
[Summon of the spirits activated!]
[Just what does that power consist of?]
[Who from jail will be resurrected?]
Jong Kook is supposed to come.
What the heck?
Him?
[Summon of the spirits-
One of the prisoners are resurrected!]
Why is it Lee Kwang Soo?
Yoo Jae Suk!
All together!
Yoo Jae Suk! Yoo Jae Suk!
Yoo Jae Suk!
Louder!
[Ghost Giraffe excited about having
been let out of jail for the moment.]
Everyone...
How tired you must be from
having walked around all this time!
- Thank you.
- Now that I have the power...
I will oust everyone so that
I can send all of you home to rest!
I will make it so that you will
all return home shortly!
Yes... I'll do that.
I will promise you!
Not now, not now.
No now!
No now, no now...
Yes, yes...
- What... Yoo Jae Suk!
- Now's not the time for that.
What is going on over there?
Did someone get resurrected?
- So he has the power of resurrection?
- Yeah, he brought someone back.
[As mentioned, a power to resurrect!
Just how will he use that power?]
I think he's able to utilize someone.
- Are you ready?
- Yes, I'm ready.
If Yoo Jae Suk can oust someone
within 20 minutes...
- you can summon your next spirit.
- Really?
However... if you can't oust anyone
within that given time...
even Lee Kwang Soo's spirit
will be lost.
Then my life is the length of a fruit fly?
We only need three more.
Ha Ha... no, not Ha Ha.
Don't you think you have to
treat me well too?
- What did you say?
- Treat me well if you want to survive.
- Take that off.
- No, I didn't mean it.
I called you out here since you've had
nothing to do but sit around all day...
[How dare he after he was rescued from
having been in jail all day...]
Yoo Jae Suk!
- Let's go.
- Want to just keep sitting around in there?
No, Sir.
- Do you promise to do your best to serve me?
- Yes, I promise!
Okay.
From this point on...
I appoint you as my servant.
- Thank you.
- And if any gold is to be earned today...
- It will be yours!
- Thank you!
Go!
Don't walk in front of me.
[Seriously...]
Don't you think you're being too much?
- Take it off.
- Okay.
Please lead the way!
Don't step on my shadow either.
- Kwang Soo...
- Yes, Jae Suk?
Where's Dong Wook?
Wait.
I need to get up high...
and take a look to see where they're at.
- Up to the castle?
- Up on your shoulders.
- So I'm the high place?
- I have to get up high to see.
I have to take a look around
this wide open space...
so that I can see where they're at.
- Then why don't we climb up somewhere?
- Hurry up and lift me up.
Hurry.
I have to get up high to see.
This isn't what I'm supposed to be used for.
What is this?
Kwang Soo, where are they?
- How can I see?
- Take a look.
- Hurry up and get down.
- Lee Dong Wook is...
Right over there.
- Here he comes.
- Where?
Down, down... Kwang Soo, set me down.
[Target locked]
[Sets on his way with his spirit!]
[Kwang Soo and Jae Suk rush
to close in on Dong Wook!]
[Giraffe the ghost grabs Dong Wook!]
[The power of the sword- Making the
capturing easier with the spirit's help.]
[Right now... is the time to attack!]
[All the energy being drained
by the attack of these two.]
- I'm so exhausted.
- If I don't eliminate you...
I can't survive either.
[If I don't eliminate you,
I can't survive either!]
[Wait...]
[If Dong Wook's name tag gets ripped off,
then I have to head back to jail.]
[Every word out of his mouth
is a threat to fire him...]
If I don't eliminate you,
I can't survive either!
What are you doing?
[Why is Giraffe the ghost suddenly
grasping Jae Suk's hands?]
Rather than living this crappy life...
let's just die together instead!
[Giraffe the ghost betrays Jae Suk!]
Right now!
Do it now!
[And Hye Jin follows up by
eliminating Dong Wook's name tag!]
What have you done? Come here!
[Giraffe the ghost is already preparing
to offer up the sword to the new owner.]
- I'm the new owner.
- Dong Wook, you're out?
I ousted him.
What is this!
[The new owner of the ultimate
golden sword is Hye Jin!]
- Hey... I'm your owner...
- Owners can change!
Have you ever treated me right
as your spirit?
- You dare betray me?
- Wait... wait a minute.
- You think I'm one of your dogs?
- Wait, Hye Jin...
[This guy is angry at Hye Jin.]
I just wanted to rip off
someone's name tag.
- Between the guests...
- Seriously...
I'm just speechless.
He was supposed to be helping me.
- He wasn't supposed to help you.
- Why did he do that?
What is he saying that I've done?
- Seriously...
- Wow...
Master!
Okay.
- So an opportunity like this finds me too.
- Lee Kwang Soo is...
[Giraffe ghost was originally a power
that Jae Suk activated with his sword.]
[His usage time is 20 minutes!
Still has 13 minutes left until expiration.]
I can be referred to as
your guardian angel.
He's just a spirit.
[Kwang Soo is a ghost or a.k.a a spirit.]
I'm not a ghost...
[Must recite the summon again
to reactivate the spirit.]
To be resurrected again...
aren't you so happy!
I've heard this before somewhere else!
Master!
I'm your spirit.
I'm your bodyguard.
Okay.
Where did Song Ji Hyo go?
- I have to find Song Ji Hyo.
- You two are the only ones left?
Ji Hyo is the only one left.
In that case...
Spirit, go and find Ji Hyo.
[Even though he may have a new owner,
his tasks are still the same.]
[Two people on the opposing side,
while she's left all alone.]
[How can I win this?]
It's so confusing because
Ji Hyo's dressed in yellow too.
I know, but we don't have any time.
[Since it can be over in a blink of an eye,
every step is taken with caution.]
Seriously... how am I going to
fight them one against two?
How should I do this?
What do I do?
[Her opponent is Hye Jin with the ultimate
sword and Giraffe the ghost to boot.]
This is no good.
[Okay... there's only one way...]
[Blank Ji suddenly moving around in a rush.]
Come here.
Come on.
[Ah... Blank Ji gathering around
other women who are dressed in yellow.]
['Hide amongst the yellow dresses!'
The same plan she tried before?]
[Okay, this is it.]
[The garden suddenly full of yellow Ao dai
by Ji Hyo's request.]
- If I can only eliminate Ji Hyo...
- Master!
Walking around by yourself is dangerous!
Ji Hyo!
Song Ji Hyo!
You don't even acknowledge me
when I say something to you.
- Huh?
- I told you it's dangerous.
That's right.
You're under my service, right?
I'm not in your service,
but I'm just helping you out!
Song Ji Hyo!
Hurry up and find Ji Hyo.
Where... where's Ji Hyo?
- Where? There?
- Is she over there?
[Following the instruction,
and heading towards the garden!]
We have to go together!
- Oh yeah!
- Are you going to use me or not?
That's right...
I keep forgetting.
Ji Hyo!
[I need to hide for now.]
[Searching every corner
of the garden for Ji Hyo.]
[Blank Ji is disguised under the
help of others dressed in yellow.]
[Will her plan go the way she hopes?]
- You don't see her?
- I don't see her.
I was told she was around here.
[Find Blank Ji...]
[She has to be around here...
I can smell something fishy going on...]
[That's Blank Ji!]
You don't see her?
I was told that she was
in here somewhere.
[But she doesn't see her,
and just walks on by...]
It's like finding a venomous snake
among other serpents.
She really is the ace.
If we still can't find her after all this,
it means she's not here, right?
[She has to be around here somewhere...]
This is no good.
[The fierce competition...
Ji Hyo vs. Hye Jin.]
[Will she ambush first...
or will be she discovered first?]
[Grabs with the right hand...]
[But as Hye Jin turns her body around
to avoid the attack...]
[Eliminates it with her left hand!]
[With lightning fast speed!]
[Song Ji Hyo... our very own Ace!]
- Kwang Soo! What did you do...
- Why are you doing this to me?
- What have you even done?
- I was searching!
[Looking elsewhere at that
decisive moment.]
Master!
I pledge my undying loyalty to you!
[The final owner of the ultimate sword is...
Song Ji Hyo!]
[Giraffe the ghost who ultimately
proved to be of no use to Hye Jin.]
- I knew it would be you from the beginning.
- As your Master, I order you back to jail.
Go back immediately.
- Hurry up and go.
- Aren't we on the same team now?
- What do you mean, the same team?
- I was your ally from the beginning.
What? Why...
why are you leading me away?
What are you doing?
Ji Hyo!
I'm sorry, Hye Jin.
I'd like to see you try to stick that
sword into the turtle.
[The ultimate winner of Legend of the Sword,
Ace Ji Hyo!]
Where did Lee Kwang Soo the ghost go?
[This is... where the golden turtle
lies await in slumber.]
- Thank you. Thanks for all the hard work.
- Hye Jin, did you win?
- So Ji Hyo won?
- Ji Hyo won?
[The final owner of the golden sword-
Ace Ji Hyo makes her appearance!]
- Whenever we go overseas, she wins.
- As soon as the gold come back...
- Gold was the prize?
- As soon as the gold came back, she wins.
So gold was the prize?
The gold has been resurrected!
[As she pulls the half of the golden sword
out in front of the golden turtle...]
[It transforms it's shape
into a complete golden sword!]
It's a perfected sword.
It used to be only half the sword...
Hey... I should've been the winner.
It should've been me.
Shouldn't the sword be returned
to the turtle now?
- Yes, it should be returned.
- My golden sword...
I will return it to the turtle,
and restore peace upon the world.
Congratulations.
[This is the start of the legend...]
[The legend has it that once the
sword was returned...
the turtle disappeared
into the depths of the water.]
[And the ultimate sword that
brought out the greed in people...]
[Was broken down into nine daggers that
divided up the ultimate power...]
[and was scattered throughout
the land of Asia.]
[And several centuries later...]
[Running Man's Asia race will start
to find 'The secrets of the nine daggers.']
[Without knowing the secret
that is centuries old...]
[The nine members of Running Man set out
on an adventure to find the daggers.]
[Unraveling the secret of the golden turtle,
which has guarded the secret for ages...]
[And the golden sword ultimately
is brought back to humanity.]
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Once upon a time, King Go Dong
of Running Dynasty had three daughters.]
[Uee- The peaceful princess;
Ji Hyo- Blank Princess; Sa Yeon- Fat princess]
[Out of anger for his daughters,
The King marries off his daughters to idiots.]
[Now the princesses has to train the idiots
to become the best Generals in the country.]
[Next week's Running Man-
The idiot and the Princess.]