Case Number 157.
[Case of a smack to the head
in the dark room.]
[Confused Witnesses.]
I hereby indict them all as
co-conspirators of the crime.
- You're the one who hit me in the ear!
- Do you have proof of that?
- You saying I hit you?
- You did hit me!
- We deny all these charges.
- You guys are the culprits!
If you're lying, you're dead.
[The unknown truth.]
[Just who is the culprit?]
[12 hours before the trial.]
[Marina Center in Chungjoo.]
Subtitles by DramaFever
[In the waiting room
before recording started.]
That chili crab was really good.
[Relaxing before recording starts.]
[Giraffe arrives.]
[About to exchange greetings with the guests
since today's concept isn't a big secret.]
- Hello.
[Actor Jung Woong In.]
[Actors Kim Hee Won, and Ahn Gil Kang.]
[The hottest drama of late,
'I Hear Your Voice'.]
[Min Joon Gook/Jung Woong In enchanting the
audiences alike with his evil character role.]
[Kim Hee Won- Expert in playing all the
bad guy roles on screen.]
[Ahn Gil Kang- Stellar portrayals of evil roles
with the evil looks to boot.]
[Uncommon sight of greeting the guests
before the show starts.]
You really are very tall.
I see that the reaction has to
be exaggerated.
- Are we going to be playing games later?
- Yes.
[Only way to get to know this program
is to experience it for yourself.]
I feel like something really dramatic
is going to happen.
- What if there are helicopters and such?
- Maybe?
- Do you think that maybe...
- What's going on?
[A blackout?]
- What the heck?
- What's going on here?
Seriously!
What's going on here?
Someone just hit me...
Someone just hit me.
[The power comes back on...]
[Someone hit Big-nosed Brother
while the light was out?]
- Someone just hit me.
- Come on, don't be absurd.
I just got hit in the head!
I got hit here and here!
Two slaps!
There's not even a camera
around here...
Are you by any chance...
the one who hit me?
How can I reach over there?
I swear someone just hit me.
[A strange vibe in the room...]
- What the heck? Wait...
- What's going on here?
Something going on here, isn't there?
Something is definitely going on!
I'm telling you that someone just hit me!
I'm totally serious!
Is this what Running Man is like?
- You can't trust anyone.
- Is this part of the recording?
- Are you sure that someone hit you?
- I'm positive that someone just hit me.
- You are under arrest.
- What the heck?
[Arrest?]
- I think they must've been recording this.
- What the heck is this?
[A mysterious situation that seems
to have everyone in a state of confusion.]
Where are Jong Kook, Jae Suk,
and Ji Hyo?
[Suspect Jung Woong In is arrested.]
[Suspect Lee Kwang Soo is arrested.]
You're a suspect!
[Suspect Kim Hee Won is arrested.]
[Suspect Ahn Gil Kang is arrested.]
I'm going to file a lawsuit!
[Case Number 157-
Case of the head smack in the dark room.]
[A silent courtroom.]
[Defense Attorney Yoo.]
[The prosecution team entering
the courtroom.]
[Undermining each other
right from the get-go.]
What did you just say?
You're being too reckless with your words.
Please remain silent.
This isn't the first time I've taken on
cases such as this one.
What did you say?
[Please understand as the terms used for the
scene may be QUITE different than the norm.]
Sir.
You really shouldn't be doing this.
Lying about things that never even happened
is not a very nice thing to be doing.
Why?
Did you see what happened?
- Your speech is too casual!
- I'm telling you, someone hit me!
- Someone hit me in my ear!
- Stop talking! Don't give anything away.
- Seriously.
- Don't talk anymore about the case.
You really sounded authentic.
[Prosecutor Gae boosting up
the morale of the prosecution team.]
We'll find out the truth through the trial,
so you just sit there and remain patient.
Seriously.
It's those people over there!
They are the ones who hit me in my ear!
I'm positive that it's one of them.
One of them is the culprit!
I'm going to seek a
huge compensation amount.
Wow, look at the expression
on their faces.
[A fierce look on their faces...]
Who?
Who are you saying did it?
You know that you hit me!
You hit me in my ear!
- Who, me?
- That's right!
- When?
- Earlier!
You hit me in both of my ears!
Wham!
- Do you have any evidence?
- No, I don't!
Gil Kang, you need to just
remain cool.
[Chaos breaking out in the courtroom.]
- Prosecutor, please catch the culprit for me.
- Yes, don't you worry.
- In the name of justice!
- This isn't the first time I've seen this.
[Presiding Judge entering the court.]
- He's the Judge?
- Is that Beethoven?
- What's he doing now?
- Isn't that Mozart?
- He looks like Beethoven.
- He looks like a composer.
You need to address him in honorifics.
Case Number 157.
Case file,
'Smack to the head in the dark room'.
We will now start the trial.
[July, 22nd, 2013.
Estimated time- 2 P.M.]
[The waiting room is suddenly
plunged into darkness.]
What's going on here?
[And an incidence of violence
cloaked in mystery.]
- What the heck is going on here?
- Someone just hit me.
Someone just hit me.
- Who hit me?
- Come on, don't be absurd!
I'm telling you, someone hit me!
Twice on my head!
[Victim Ji Suk Jin full of resentment.]
[And the four suspects.]
Prosecution may make
their opening statement.
Yes, I understand.
July 21st, 2013.
I mean, 22nd, around 1400 hours.
[Prosecutor Kkuk bumbling around
with his opening statement.]
You don't even know the basic stuff.
Why are you bumbling your statement?
Why don't you wear some pants?
Get some pants on.
Is that any way to dress in
the courtroom?
- It's the latest trend!
- Don't you know the latest trend?
Don't you know that wearing shorts
these days helps to cool you down?
[Cool new business fashion that aids
in conserving energy and keeping cool.]
- This is the prosecutors' dress code.
- Sorry, but are the four of you in a choir?
[Singing in a choir would be better suited
for them than indicting someone?]
- Seriously... go on and speak.
- Okay.
Okay, this incident occurred in the waiting room
before the recording started around 2pm.
While Ji Suk Jin was conversing with
today's guests, Jung Woong In
Ahn Gil Kang, Kim Hee Won, along with
Lee Kwang Soo, Kang Gary, and Ha Ha
in the waiting room, he was hit in the back
of his head when the lights went out.
[The victim was assaulted in the head
while the room was immersed in the blackout.]
Why are you saying that we were the ones
who hit you in the head?
Please remain silent.
We are still talking.
It wasn't in the back of my head.
I was hit in my ears.
- Your ears?
- One, two.
I was hit twice like that.
The legal term for that would be,
'The Earmuff Assault'.
Yes, I understand.
The defendants Jung Woong In, Ahn Gil Kang,
Kim Hee Won, and Lee Kwang Soo
hit the victim, Ji Suk Jin in his occipitals
during the time of the blackout.
Also...
The situation in the waiting room...
who's phone is ringing!
Why are you getting angry
in the middle of the courtroom?
- Who keeps their phone on in the courtroom!
- No need for you to get so angry.
[Prosecutor Kkuk calms himself back down.]
It has been established that the four
defendants are guilty of co-conspiring.
- Therefore, the defendants...
- What are you talking about?
What?
Don't you know what co-conspiring is?
- Co-conspiring.
- You must've watched a lot of dramas.
Therefore, according to the
Criminal Procedural Act
Section 260, Article 1...
the prosecution indicts all four defendants
as the co-conspirators of the assault.
[Defendants- Indicted as
co-conspirators of the assault.]
- Defense may now make his statement.
- Okay.
My defendants deny their charge of being
co-conspirators of the assault.
- You can't do that!
- I was hit twice in my ears!
Honorable Judge.
These defendants did not hit
the victim, Ji Suk Jin in the head.
- Isn't that correct?
- Yes.
The victim is claiming that he was hit in
the head during the blackout
but the defendants was not aware
that there was going to be a blackout.
What did you say?
We were all shocked just like you!
- I was hit in both of my ears!
- And also...
The victim, Ji Suk Jin states that he was
the receiver of the Earmuffs Assault...
I was hit twice!
But the defendants weren't even aware
that he was hit in the head.
There was no need to follow Ji Suk Jin
and assault him in his ears like that
nor was there any reason to do that as
the prosecution stand is stating.
This charge of co-conspiracy
is an absurd accusation.
- What did you say?
- Do you even know what you're saying?
- You're a culprit too!
- What did you say?
Look at the goodness
radiating from these men!
How could you think that any one of us
could've assaulted him like that?
[Do you see...
the goodness radiating from me?]
I can't even look at defendant
number three in the eyes.
[Ahn Gil Kang with a fierce
glint in his eyes.]
Someone switch seats with me!
Silence!
Anymore outbursts, and everyone
will be kicked out of the courtroom.
[Anymore outbursts from the crowd,
and they'll be kicked out of the courtroom.]
Honorable Judge,
I'd like to question the four defendants.
Yes, you may start your line
of questioning.
Are the defendants aware of why
they're put on the stand today?
We don't even know why we're here.
What kind of an impression do
you believe that you normally portray?
I believe that we look very innocent.
I'd first like to question
defendant Jung Woong In.
What is the role that you play in the
recent drama, 'I Hear Your Voice'?
I play Min Joon Gook.
[Plays the role of Min Joon Gook in
'I Hear Your Voice'.]
[Killer extraordinaire, Min Joon Gook.]
[Bringing everyone to the edges of their seats
with his frightening and realistic portrayal.]
What kind of a character is
Min Joon Gook?
- He's a murderer.
- A murderer!
A murderer!
He's a murderer!
- I didn't hit you!
- You did hit me!
You hit me in both of my ears!
You told me that you're a killer
without even a change in your expression!
- He's not your average killer either.
- He really is scary.
I'm aware that there's a famous line
that your character says in the drama.
What is that saying?
Please tell everyone in this courtroom.
"I'm going to kill you if you tell anyone."
I told people earlier...
I told everyone about it earlier.
"I'm also going to kill the people
who you told it to."
[Let's not hear anything...]
- Ji Suk Jin.
- Yes?
If you lie, I'm going to kill you.
[Ice]
He just said that he's going to kill him!
He said the word 'kill' in the courtroom!
Honorable Judge, he was just describing
the character he plays in the drama.
Next.
Defendant Kim Hee Won.
- Listen to him.
- He really sounds like a prosecutor.
He really truly does look like
a psychopath.
[What?
He looks like a psychopath?]
- Most people that looks like him...
- He's too harsh with his words.
What do you mean,
he looks like a psychopath?
- Actor Kim Hee Won.
- Yes?
What do you consider to be the most
famous role you portrayed in a movie?
- 'The Man From Nowhere'.
- The movie, 'The Man From Nowhere'?
Ask him which role he thinks
that he's most famous for.
What is role that you portrayed
in the movie, 'The Man From Nowhere'?
The character's name was Man Suk.
[Played the character named Man Suk, the
villain in the movie, 'The Man From Nowhere'.]
What did your character
Man Suk do in the movie?
That was a scary character.
- The organs...
- Organs!
- What did he do with the organs?
- He meant he had an organ.
Organs?
What is it that you did with the organs?
I saw that movie!
He keeps badgering the defendants with
irrelevant questions
about characters that they played
in movies and dramas.
- I object.
- No, I will allow it.
Can you please show us the evil expression
your character was known for in the movie?
Show us what your character looked like in the
last scene as your younger sibling was dying.
You can re-act the scene for us by
using my name for the scene.
But since this is a variety show,
you can't swear in your reenactment.
'Ugh... Gary!'
Wasn't it something like that?
You're doing great!
Hey, Gary!
[The true face of evil.]
[Seriously...]
I think it was him!
- Look at his expression.
- No need to question any further.
Honorable Judge.
I believe that he is the culprit.
No further questions.
- It's the beautiful prosecutor's turn.
- Yes.
I will now start my line of questioning.
Show them what you've got.
The defendant that I will be questioning
is Ahn Gil Kang.
[Defendant Number Three, Ahn Gil Kang.]
I was hoping that she would be
the one to question me.
[Disappointed that he wasn't questioned
by Prosecutor Blank?]
[Asking to shake her hand?]
Don't shake his hand!
[Evil extraordinaire defendants vying for
the chance to greet the beautiful prosecutor.]
[Gil Kang joining in on the parade.]
What are you doing?
Don't even say hi to me.
Yes, Ahn Gil Kang.
What is it that you're most
well-known for?
- Expert in playing evil roles.
- That's correct.
[Actor Ahn Gil Kang having played
a variety of evil roles.]
And also, from my recollection...
you and I worked on the same project
together three years ago.
- What was it?
- What role did he play in the movie?
With that long sword in his hand...
he went around slaying people
throughout the movie.
What are you talking about right now?
She's just saying that he played
a role like that in one of his movies.
He went around slaying people
as if it was nothing.
- He slayed people?
- Yes, he rode around on the horse to do it.
- He slayed them like that.
- What do you mean, like that?
[A cruel and evil role.]
- I can't even look at him right now!
- Stop looking at us like that!
- This is a variety show!
- This is what I do for a living!
It is highly likely.
It is highly likely that he could've been
the one to hit the defendant in question.
[Highly likely that he is the culprit
that hit the defendant in question.]
I meant, the plaintiff.
('Plaintiff' sounds like 'One-go'.)
Two-go?
- Three-go!
- Stop!
[Legal terms are so hard...]
- Everyone, please calm down.
- Yes, I understand.
Next.
Lee Kwang Soo.
[Defendant Number Four,
Lee Kwang Soo.]
- This really is unfair.
- This is getting old, Lee Kwang Soo.
What is the nickname you've been
dubbed with on Running Man?
[Defendant Number Four's nickname?]
Traitorous Giraffe.
It's Slanderous Kwang Soo, isn't it?
Yes, I'm also known as
Slanderous Kwang Soo.
I remember how you tricked me during
the early days of Running Man.
- Don't you remember?
- What is this line of questioning about?
I told you not to say such absurd things!
Song Ji Hyo never caused a scene at the club!
That's enough!
I said, that's enough!
Did our Ji Hyo ever do anything
that deserves to have fingers pointed at?
I didn't know how much she loved
to go out doing things like that!
Ji Hyo quit her smoking!
- Please stop slandering her name!
- Congratulations.
It was a wise decision that you made
for the sake of your health.
[Defense Counsel Yoo hammering the final
nail with his slanderous remark.]
- That was a very smart decision you made.
- Hey, hey... please calm down.
- Okay then.
- What do you mean, 'hey, hey'?
[Getting everyone to calm down
and stop joking around.]
Okay, the prosecution team
may go back to their stand.
The defense counsel may now
start his line of questioning.
Then I will take a brief moment to
speak to each of the defendants.
You're currently in the drama,
'I Hear Your Voice', isn't that right?
Yes, I'm currently in that drama.
Weren't you in a comedy sitcom before you
took on the role of your current character?
I especially seem to remember a character
you played with his famous catch phrase?
That famous catch phrase.
Wasn't there one that became quite popular?
- What was it? It's been awhile.
- It's been so long since I've heard that.
'I think I got it.'
[He's still got it.]
- Everyone got a laugh out of that, right?
- No, we didn't.
- This is the type of person he is.
- I didn't think that was funny at all.
This is the type of character he played
before he started his current drama.
Okay? He brought big laughter
to everyone.
Do you have a special nickname
that you use for your girlfriend?
- Do I really have to say it?
- Come on, you can tell us!
- It's okay, you can tell us.
- Look! He can't even say it!
- I just call her, 'my baby'.
- 'My baby'?
Everyone heard, right?
A person who calls his girlfriend
'My baby'...
Could someone like that have hit Ji Suk Jin
and sit over there feigning ignorance?
Do you think?
- When's the last time you kissed her?
- What kind of a question is that?
Have you done it in the
past week or no?
- You have!
- Or you haven't?
You don't have to answer that question.
No need to answer that question.
I will now ask the defendant Ahn Gil Kang
one simple question.
[Just looking at him in the face
makes them quake in fear.]
Can you please tell us
how old your kids are?
They're five and seven years old.
- Five and seven years old?
- Yes.
Has your daughter ever said anything to you
when you told her you'd be on this show?
Did she tell you what she wanted
you to do on the show?
- No, she didn't say anything specific.
- She probably told you not to hit anyone.
You're being too loud, Mister!
What did you say?
How can you say that?
[Gil Kang exploding in anger.]
You guys are being too loud!
Let us talk too!
It's a very plausible statement.
- That's correct.
- Yes.
- Now, Lee Kwang Soo.
- Yes?
- Did you ever hit Ji Suk Jin in his ears?
- No, I haven't.
We need to check him out further.
What are you doing?
We're on the same side.
Okay, Lee Kwang Soo.
Is there anything that you'd like
to say to Ji Suk Jin?
No, there isn't.
I don't have anything to say either.
What are you doing?
- Is that all you've got to say?
- I can't help it if you get captured.
- Yes, I do have something to say!
- I thought that you didn't!
[He doesn't seem to want to be
Giraffe's defense counsel.]
[Defense counsel rests his case?]
Honorable Judge.
My defendants feel that this is very unfair.
Just because they've played
evil characters in their movies in the past
they've been framed for this
heinous crimes.
But these are very kind men who are being put
through a difficult time from that prejudice.
Then, Ji Suk Jin...
I feel that if anything, it's Ji Suk Jin
who fabricated this whole scenario.
I'm telling you that I really was hit!
What are you talking about right now?
Are you doing this to gain more attention?
What are you saying to our plaintiff?
- You can't doubt our own client!
- He does have a point.
I'm positive that I was hit
by someone.
Please quiet down.
Our country rules trials based on evidence,
and there hasn't been any evidence so far.
[We will now start a race to find
evidence to support this case.]
[The team that wins each of the game
will gain themselves a piece of evidence.]
[If the prosecution team wins, then
the defendants would be found guilty.]
[If the defense counsel team wins, then
the defendants will be found innocent.]
We will take a brief recess.
Please move on to your next location
for your first evidence gathering game.
- Yes, I understand.
- Let's see who wins.
[Prosecution Team vs. Defense Team.
Race to gather evidence- Start.]
[In moments- The closing arguments.]
[Evidence that they never knew existed
will be revealed to tell the true story.]
[A fierce battle between the Prosecution
and the Defense to argue their case.]
[Who is the culprit hiding behind
the mask of secrecy?]
[Where the 2013 world boat racing
championship will take place.]
- What is this?
- What are we going to be doing here?
- There's something shiny up there.
[What is the meaning of this red line?]
It's a little slippery over here.
You all know that you are here to play a game
that will give you a clue to the truth?
The first game you'll be playing for evidence
is the human 'Cola and Cider' game.
Human cola and cider game?
- Human cola and cider game.
- So we're going to be flung off this thing?
For the game we'll be playing now,
do you all see the red line over here?
- This red line is the line of truth.
- Okay, so?
The team that comes
closest to this line will win
and gain a piece of evidence.
- So we're going to be dumped in the water?
- Push too hard, and someone gets dumped?
So this is like a human curling game?
[Human cola and cider game-
The line of truth game- Start.]
[The prosecution team getting serious
about planning their game tactics.]
How are we supposed to play this?
- I think what we're supposed to do is...
- Look at how smiley these guys all are.
Look at the smiles on their faces.
[Who can point their fingers at these men
as they see these smiles on their faces?]
- Look at the angelic baby smiles!
- They're like baby angels over here.
- How are they like baby angels?
- What are you talking about?
Don't you mean the angels of evil?
No, baby angels, not evil angels.
Baby angels!
Instead of going through all this,
how about you let them all hit you once?
[Just let each of them hit him once
to see if he can recognize the slap?]
I think it would be a good idea to let them
hit you once to see who it is.
Do you have any idea how much it hurts?
[The team that gets closest
to this line wins!]
[First up for the Defense Team is,
Defendant Jung Woong In.]
[The glint in his eye transforms...]
If you tell anyone, I'm going to kill you.
[Bringing the dark energy he portrays
in the drama to this game?]
I'm going to get this evidence.
[Woong In flings himself
without any hesitation!]
[How close will he get to the
line of truth?]
[Went too far.]
Don't fling yourself too hard!
Not that hard!
- Seriously!
- Come on.
Get your food bowl.
No, I didn't mean to call that a food bowl.
- What do you mean, a food bowl?
- A food bowl of our variety world.
A food bowl for our variety world.
[Agrees that they can't use their foot as
a brake even if they're about to fall in.]
- No use of any brakes, okay?
- No brakes?
[Defense Team's Woong In is disqualified.]
[The first person up for the
Prosecution Team is Prosecutor Ha.]
Lift up your feet!
Lift your feet!
[A very close call, but he's safe.]
You have to stay there just like that.
[Next up for the Defense Team is
Defendant Kim Hee Won.]
[Expert in playing the evil roles with his
perfect mix of innocence and devilishness.]
You're not too athletic yourself, are you?
He's always ordering
others around in his movies.
He always has his minions
doing things for him.
Because he can't fight himself.
Hee Won doesn't know that hats like these
are usually worn in forests or the like.
Those hats are not suitable for
the water.
I really wasn't going to say this,
but I just couldn't help it.
Don't babies usually wear hats like this?
I usually see babies wearing them.
- Those hats are meant for babies.
- It's not like it's even all that sunny out.
I thought that it was going to be
really sunny outside.
I can't believe all the teasing he's getting
just because of the hat he's wearing.
Fighting.
[Defense Team's second defendant
Hee Won steps up to the challenge.]
[Heading in Prosecutor Ha's direction.]
[Falls into the water simultaneously.]
[Defendant Kim and Prosecutor Ha
are both ousted.]
[Struggling in the water with
his kid appropriate hat.]
Okay, Hee Won did well.
[Even though he fell in the water,
he still ousted a member of the other team.]
Move out of my way.
Why? Why are you speaking to
me like that?
[Victim Ji speaking with
some edge to his voice.]
What are you talking about?
Just get out of my way!
- I said, move!
- Don't do that. You have to gain sympathy.
[How close will Victim Ji
get to the line of truth?]
[A good looking start!]
There you go!
That looks good!
- Okay!
- That's actually the perfect spot.
- That's perfect.
- Victim Ji! Victim Ji!
[Defendant Team is formulating their plan
according to where Suk Jin is placed.]
To the side is better.
Kwang Soo, get over on his side.
[Giraffe from the Defense Team
gets ready to take his turn.]
- Fighting!
- Lee Kwang Soo is making me nervous.
[Will he push him out of the way,
or push himself out of the way?]
[Huh?]
[He's still not fully off?]
- I didn't fall off!
- You have to stay just like that.
[Slanderous Giraffe desperately
holding on with his one right foot.]
My foot is still up there.
Seriously... just get up here.
We will allow him to get back up there
if he can get up there by using his leg only.
If I get up there with the use
of my leg only?
[Will he be able to do it?]
What are you doing?
[Toad Kwang?]
You really are so ugly.
You're so ugly.
[Wow?]
[Unbelievable!
He succeeds in pulling himself up!]
Okay, we'll allow that.
That's very acceptable
behavior of a criminal.
- Let's go!
- Go!
[Prosecutor Gae from
the Prosecution Team takes his turn.]
[Attempted to push Kwang Soo into the
water by shoving Suk Jin into him.]
[He should've pushed him harder...]
I didn't even notice that he
bumped into me.
I thought that I pushed him pretty hard.
[Defendant Ahn Gil Kang's turn.]
- He's not very good at that.
- What are all those guys doing?
What are you doing?
I thought that you'd be better than that.
[His athletic abilities belies his looks.]
Who's in first place right now?
- Suk Jin's in first place right now.
- I'm in first place.
- For now.
- I'm in second place though!
[Prosecutor Beauty
gears herself up for her turn!]
[That's our Ace Ji Hyo!
Takes Kwang Soo into the water with her!]
[And thus, Prosecution Team
is in the lead!]
[Recent events throws both teams into
a state of frenzy to plan their attack.]
I'm going to push hard into you.
[Push me really hard,
and I'll eliminate them all.]
Okay, Jae Suk... fighting!
[The final runner for the Defense Team,
Attorney Yoo.]
[A powerful start with an
enthusiastic cry.]
[The domino effect!]
[A perfect success!]
[See that?]
[Defense Team seems to be celebrating
their certain victory.]
- We got this!
- We're going to win this!
[This prosecutor is on fire!
Jong Kook readies himself for his turn.]
[Those evil doers...]
[In the name of justice,
you will not be forgiven!]
I'm going to do this in the
name of justice.
- Okay! Don't worry.
- You have to endure his move.
[Prosecuting Team's last runner-
Prosecutor Kkuk.]
[Prepare yourself, you evil doers!]
[Hits himself directly into Attorney Yoo
and plunges him into the water.]
[But Gil Kang... withstood his attack.]
[Defendant Ahn flings himself backwards
to land directly on top of the line.]
That was like a car crash!
We did it!
We won the game!
[First round of Line of Truth game
is won by the Defense Team!]
I think he purposely made himself
fall backwards like that.
- I think he did that on purpose.
- You're being too loud again. Come on.
He did that on purpose, and
made himself fall like that on purpose.
He fell only because of
the way he was shoved like that.
- He fell because he was shoved.
- Look at his face!
[His face showing signs to back off?]
[Since problems are starting to rise,
his evil nature is starting to show itself?]
Are you going to call your minions now?
- He doesn't have any minions!
- How about only three people do it this time?
Let's stop all this talking and
just get on with the game.
You're flinging water at me.
[A fierce competition between the
two teams.]
[Agrees on having only three players
per team for the second round.]
- Pick your three criminals.
- Who are you calling criminals?
- How about you three?
- Yeah, let's have you three do it.
Why are you calling the three of us
culprits when you're on our side?
- No, they're not culprits.
- Do you know what Gil Kang just said?
He just agreed to the three
culprits doing it.
- Want to?
- Okay, the three culprits can do it.
[Is that a self-confession?]
Who are you calling culprits right now?
Culprit one, two, three over there.
- Who are you calling culprits?
- We did not do anything wrong.
Okay, let's do this.
[Line of Truth, Round Two-
Start.]
- Okay, kiddo. Hurry it up!
- Kiddo?
- It's better not to go too far out.
- I'm a prosecutor of this country!
A prosecutor?
You're a quality inspector?
[Quality inspector?
The word prosecutor also means, inspector.]
The fact that we're hanging out with these
culprits alone is just wrong.
[First runner up for the second round
is Prosecutor Ha.]
[This makes it too easy for the
opposing team to shove him out of the way.]
You wait right there.
- He's telling him to wait?
- You wait right there.
His killer instincts are starting to come out!
[Now that he sees his chance,
his killer instincts are starting to come out?]
You just wait right there!
[Gil Kang from
the Defense Team is on the move!]
[Gil Kang eliminates
Prosecutor Ha in leisure.]
- He used his shoulder too much!
- What do you mean, his shoulder?
[Prosecutor Kkuk is on fire!]
He can't use his shoulders like that!
[Second runner for the Prosecution Team
is Ace Ji Hyo.]
Isn't that life vest too small for you?
[On Prosecutor Kkuk,
the life vest looks like a kiddie size.]
Wait, hang on.
Seriously!
- What?
- Stop talking about it.
- Okay.
- Seriously.
- What is that? Your school bag?
- It looks adorable on him.
It looks way too small on you.
[Of all the vests to pick from,
he picks the smallest one...]
[Ace Ji Hyo-
Will she be able to get rid of Gil Kang?]
That's a great shove!
[Ji Hyo shoves herself off
of him instead.]
[Their trusted Ji Hyo
gets herself eliminated!]
[Huh?
What is he doing?]
Don't come back out.
Just stay down there!
[And what is he doing now?]
What are you guys doing?
[Easy Brothers showing their abilities
in physical gags.]
I told you not to come back out.
[Defense Team's Gil Kang staying
firmly put.]
- He's deeply rooted over there.
- Nice.
It's my turn now so you can just relax.
[Is it really okay for him to just relax?]
[Hee Won of the Defense Team
is on the move!]
He's so bad at this!
Nice!
Just stay right there!
[Amazing chance!
First and second winner position!]
[Final contestant from
the Prosecution Team is...]
[Fiery Prosecutor Kkuk!]
Why are you going so far back?
[Figuring out the direction
he's going to take.]
[I will prosecute in the name of justice!]
- In the name of justice!
- I will do this in the name of justice!
[Prosecutor Kkuk on the move!]
[Gil Kang disappearing from their sight!]
[Gil Kang is shoved in the water,
but what about Hee Won?]
[He survives the attack!]
[Shoves Gil Kang even closer to
the red line of truth!]
[Evil... no, the smile of a baby angel.]
Okay!
[Line of truth game- Defense Team wins again!]
[Defense Team wins two pieces of evidence
for having won the game.]
[Defense Team can use one of the evidence to
help their case during the closing argument.]
[Next piece of evidence
can be found in 'S' village.]
[Off to the next location in
search of the evidence!]
But... the three of you, actually four,
with Kwang Soo included...
You didn't really hit Suk Jin, did you?
He just made that up.
I really do think that
Suk Jin just made it up.
Really?
But how did his ears get so red?
- That's what I'm saying.
- His ears really were red.
His ears probably turned red
because he was lying about it.
I know I mentioned this earlier,
but it's because of the roles you've played.
What are you doing?
You're a very reckless driver.
- How should we handle this?
- Huh?
What do you mean,
how should we handle it?
- What are you saying?
- That was a very scary comment.
Seriously.
I can't believe you're saying that just
because I went over a couple speed bumps.
[Silence...]
Please talk or say something.
You three are too scary when you're quiet.
- They're most scary when they're laughing.
- Can the three of you say something?
[Choongchu in Choonchung District-
'S' village.]
[Defense Team arriving first
in their pursuit for more evidence.]
Please come this way.
What is this?
- Aren't you the Judge?
- The Judge is now a neighborhood watchman.
Everyone grab a flashlight over there.
A flashlight?
[What is the mission that awaits them
that requires the use of a flashlight?]
Sitting next to these three guys makes me
think that something big is about to happen.
[Three men with some grand plan
of doing something in the village?]
Disguising ourselves...
[Just like this?]
Just confess and end this charade.
[Prosecution Team without any evidence
finally arrives.]
- If you confess, this will all be over.
- Confess to what?
[ We told you that we didn't do it.]
What are we going to be doing here?
Okay, your next mission.
Your next mission is investigation
in the order of your arrival.
[Mission-
Investigation in the order of arrival.]
Find the mission relevant location that are
placed throughout the village
and clear the mission of that location.
- And come back to this starting line.
- Okay, we got it.
[Pass the mission in the
order of their arrival.]
I won first place the last time we played this
when Soo Hyun was guesting on the show.
- Who?
- Me.
It's going to be different today.
Suk Jin is feeling really competitive today.
He said that for once in a long time,
he feels he can take on our guests.
- These guys over here.
- Don't touch me.
[Upset at Big-nose's challenge?]
Your first mission is-
Put on the workpants.
[First round- Put on the workpants.]
You'll find that there are workpants hanging
on various hang lines throughout the village.
- Pants like these.
- Yes.
You have to put the pants on
without the use of your hands.
- Ah... with our feet?
- Simple, isn't it?
- Yes, it's simple.
- In the order of arrival.
I will accept two winners.
Go!
[Find the workpants in the village and
put them on without the use of your hands!]
These guys are slow!
[Looking all around for workpants.]
Here's one!
[Jae Suk is the first to find
a pair of workpants!]
[Two pairs of pants on the clothes line.
Kwang Soo takes the other remaining pair.]
- I have to get these on quickly.
- Let me help you.
[Yoo Hyuk and Giraffe
extremely out of sync.]
Why don't you just turn yourself in?
[Prosecutor Ha prompting him to
turn himself in at every chance he gets.]
- What are you talking about?
- I know that you hit him.
You need to take your
shoes off before you do that!
- You have to take your shoes off first!
- Should I?
Come on, don't you know anything about
playing these games?
How can you even think to
put on those pants with your shoes still on?
- Wow... there they are!
- Those are mine!
[Discovers a clothing line
in someone's front yard.]
- Okay.
- I don't think those are pants.
- Yes, they are.
- They're pants?
Yes, they're pants.
What?
No, they're not pants!
No, these aren't pants.
[That shirt actually belongs to
the grandmother who lives in that house.]
Ma'am, where are the other pair of pants?
Ah... seriously!
They're not all pants.
Just like that.
That's good!
Got it.
I got it!
[Yoo Hyuk somehow manages to
get his pants almost all the way on!]
You have to pull them up higher.
- Did I get it?
- You got it.
[Succeeds in putting the pants on
with Kwang Soo's help.]
- I'm going to get going first.
- What are you talking about?
- We're on the same team!
- What if I'm late for helping you?
[Yoo Hyuk wanting to abandon his
teammate Giraffe to go off on his own.]
Can't you be more gentle?
- Did we get it?
- Yes, we got it. Just need to pull them up.
Pull them up for me with your toes.
[Have to be more careful with
the placement of the toes...]
[These guys are fighting over
a single pair of pants.]
[Such funny young men.]
Want to help each other out?
Can you hike these up for me
with your feet?
I promise that I'll help you after this.
Okay, that's good.
Wow, you're good.
That's good.
Thank you, Hee Won.
- Thank you, Hee Won.
- What?
Thank you.
[Prosecutor Ha pulling a scheme
on the suspect.]
Let's go!
[Scary world of variety show where even
villain expertise like Hee Won can be had.]
I'm first!
[Yoo Hyuk is the first to arrive
after having abandoned the Giraffe.]
I'm really good at things like this.
First place!
What are you doing?
You have to get the pants all the way on!
- Your pants aren't properly on!
- Yes, they are!
[Woong In having borrowed the pair
of pants from the elderly grandmother.]
You look like the village idiot right now.
I can see your butt right now.
[Woong In is focused on coming in second
since the order of importance in this game.]
Here, I'll help you pull them up.
[Kwang Soo attempting to help
Woong In pull up his pants.]
[Ha Ha tries to seize that moment
to make his way past the finish line.]
[By the split of a hair,
Woong In crosses the finish line first.]
Okay, second place.
[Woong In happy with his win
like a little boy.]
I was able to win because
Kwang Soo helped.
Seriously.
Maybe I really should become a criminal.
[Hee Won left all by his lonesome
after being schemed by Ha Ha.]
[With his mouth?]
This is exhausting.
Just a little bit more.
[This it this way...
and try it that way...]
[One lonely suspect's attempt
on putting on the pants.]
What took you so long?
- You already got your pants on?
- Of course!
[You're nothing to be
impressed with.]
- You got them over your hips?
- You have to get someone to help you.
- Kwang Soo helped me.
- Really?
Hee Won actually helped me
get my pants on.
Really?
I got the pants on by myself.
Why did you do it by yourself?
We all had to find sharp corners to help pull
the pants up and it was just mess.
Why did you do it like that?
[Barefooted... village idiot?]
What the heck?
[Gil Kang running back out of anxiety.]
That's so funny.
Gil Kang seriously looks so funny.
What is this?
Everyone already got their pants on?
Of course, we did.
I couldn't get them over my hips.
You look like you've lived
in this village your whole life.
- I couldn't get them over my butt.
- You look like you've always lived here.
[This man... looks like he'll be here
doing this for the rest of his life.]
[One appearance on the variety show,
and it looks like he may never get to leave.]
[The awful pair of pants...]
- Hee Won is so nice.
- Then Jae Suk is the only one that succeeded?
[Since we said the first two to arrive wins,
wouldn't it be Jae Suk and Woong In?]
- I said, the first person to arrive.
- It's only one person, right?
- I said it was only the first person.
- That's what I thought you said.
[What did you say?]
That's what I remember you saying.
It's just the first person.
[A slip of the tongue on Dong Wan's part
at the beginning of the game.]
- That's what I thought he said.
- That's too bad for you, Woong In.
- You lost by the split of a hair.
- It's no fun having two people succeed.
You said it was the first two earlier.
- Woong In, it's just the first person.
- I'm the Judge here.
- I'm a very honest person.
- Take off that wig, and you're dead.
[Take off that wig, and you're dead!]
There's no need for a second place
winner in this world.
Are you going to kill the
first place winner?
So he did find a pair of pants to put on?
He did get those on.
What happened to you, Hee Won?
What happened to you?
[A total hot mess.]
I... helped Ha Ha because
he asked me to help him.
- Then he took off as soon as I helped him.
- Of course he would!
He's just way too nice.
No way are you the culprit.
I asked Gary to help me on my way
back here, and then he helped me.
And once I helped him,
he just took off on me.
[Quickly learning all the bad traits?]
You all have to do it over anyways
except for the first place winner.
- Who came in first?
- Jae Suk.
- Again?
- You all need to get up and get back to work.
But why are all the guests sweating
so profusely today?
Are you okay, Hee Won?
[Soaked in sweat.]
- I was so ticked off.
- You almost called your minions, right?
- What are you talking about right now?
- You wanted to call your guys, right?
[But this was just the beginning
of Hee Won's suffering...]
- Okay, your second mission.
- Yes.
Find the table tennis ball from the well.
- Aha!
- How are we going to find them?
You're going to find several wells
throughout the village.
You'll find the table tennis balls
inside the wells.
The person to come back with the plate with
the ball on it on their head wins this round.
The plate with the table tennis ball?
You have to come back to the starting line
with the plate balanced on your head.
So are you saying that the plate is
with the ball or not?
[Explosion of annoyance.]
He said it was the first two people
to cross the line earlier.
[Still angry at the mistake
Village Leader Go made earlier.]
Can Hee Won even handle going
back out there?
[Not sure...]
[Barefoot runner Gil Kang also
looks like he's bathed in his own sweat?]
I wonder if it's because I'm wearing
this long sleeved shirt?
This time, it's the first two people
to cross the finish line.
Two people, two people.
It's definitely the first two people.
- This is seriously...
- He says it's two people this time.
I heard him.
- Go!
- I'm going to stick close to Hee Won.
[Table tennis ball delivery- Start!]
Hee Won!
I want to help Hee Won.
It's the first two to cross
the finish line.
[In the lead are Kkuk and the Giraffe.]
[There's a well right here!]
[Passes right on by...]
You're really good at finding
things like that.
[Everyone working hard to find a well.]
I doubt they would've made
it too easy.
Isn't that a well up there?
[Kkuk and Giraffe discovers a well!]
[A ghost in the well!]
[Scared out of their wits.]
[Shot in the face with
the water out of nowhere!]
He said it's a dud.
[A ghost in the well
instead of a tennis table ball!]
[Woong In and Gil Kang also
shot with the water by the ghost!]
[A refreshing shower for Blank Ji as well.]
Give me my ball.
Give me my ball!
There it is!
[What will he find in this well?]
What is this!
What's going on here?
[A real well with the balls inside!]
[Carefully placing it on top of his head.]
[Will he make it back sometime today?]
Potatoes?
In the middle of the night like this?
Thank you so much.
[Village elder kindly bringing them an
evening snack of potatoes and watermelon.]
Wow... look at all these
potatoes and watermelon!
[Such a kind gesture by the elder!]
I'm giving it to you since you're the first
place winner, so enjoy.
- Yes, I will enjoy.
- You have to finish it, okay?
[Why act like he's the one being generous
when he wasn't even the one who brought it?]
What are you talking about?
I can't eat all this.
[Watermelon tasting as sweet as honey.]
[Hee Won cautiously heading back
with the ball balanced on top of his head.]
Are you heading back, Hee Won?
[Haroro having too much fun
teasing Hee Won.]
Get away from me!
[Rule- If the ball is dropped on the ground,
have to go back to the well and start over.]
[Trying to calm down and start over.]
Where are you going, Hee Won?
- Where are you going, Hee Won?
- Just get away from me!
It's the first two to cross the line.
I just need to make sure that
you're not one of them.
As long as it's not you... okay!
[Ro-Ro running away with
Hee Won's ball in hand.]
You have to give me back the ball.
Why do you keep bothering me?
Stop doing that.
I'll allow it if you make me drop the ball
without touching me in any way.
- Okay.
- But you can't touch me anymore.
- Okay. Shiny light in your eyes!
- You can't touch me though.
You can't touch me.
You just can't touch me.
Why don't you find yourself your own plate
and do the mission yourself?
- Hang on a minute.
- I'm not going to drop this.
- Really?
- Of course.
- I just can't touch your neck, right?
- No, you can't do that!
That's a really cheap shot.
Why are you doing this to me?
[These two attached together at the hip
right up to the finish line.]
[Oh no!
With the finish line right in front of him!]
Hee Won!
Hee Won, we've got watermelon over here!
Come on!
- You touched me!
- He's too nice to be in a variety show.
[Hee Won too nice to be on a
variety show?]
[Ha Ha trying to block Gil Kang this time?]
- Ha Ha... I love you.
- Hello.
I love you too, Gil Kang.
- Let me go just this once.
- Let you go just this once?
I love you, Gil Kang!
I love you so much, Gil Kang!
[Gil Kang ultimately drops his ball.]
- Where?
- Hurry up, Ji Hyo!
[Blank Ji taking the lead after
Gil Kang drops his ball.]
You dropped your ball!
I'm sorry, Gil Kang!
[Throwing the ball far off into
the distance somewhere.]
There's a dog over that way!
[Gary is somehow almost to
the finish line already!]
I'm almost there.
Almost made it.
I did it!
[Round two- Gary is the first
to get across the finish line!]
My arms are killing me!
[Only one spot left for the winner-
Hee Won and Blank Ji walking together.]
You still haven't made it to the finish line
even though you found the ball a while ago?
- I almost did make it there.
- But you dropped the ball?
Seriously.
You're not a very nice person.
- You're doing the same thing as I am.
- You're not a very nice person.
- Since I was here already...
- Hurry up, Ji Hyo!
[Only one spot left for the winner!]
[Hee Won drops his ball
right in front of the finish line!]
[How can this...]
- You still have a chance! Hurry!
- Two people already made it in.
[Gary and Blank Ji are the
two winners of this round.]
I can't believe that happened.
- What's wrong with you?
- Hee Won, are you crying?
- Are you crying?
- It's not my physical condition...
Are you crying?
What's wrong with you?
- It really isn't about my physical condition.
- Then what is it?
[Just what is it about?]
Tell us what you're upset about.
Why is he only bothering me?
[Nice Hee Won whom others can't help
but want to bother and interfere with.]
You kept tickling me and made me drop
the ball like three times.
I was just trying to show you how
much I like you. It wasn't done on purpose.
We just met for the first time today.
- What number am I?
- Is this all sweat?
[Woong In seen walking towards them
unaware of there already being winners.]
- What?
- It's already over.
- That's a lie.
- Don't  you see the people sitting here?
Don't you see everyone here?
Look at how many are here already.
I finally got the feel for it.
- You finally got it?
- Where did that come from?
- I said, I saw the potatoes.
- Ah, the potatoes?
[A play on words between 'potato'
and 'got the feel for it'.]
[Gil Kang having avoided the dog
and making it to the finish line.]
[Why are all the villains acting
so cute today?]
It's all over, so just hurry down here.
- We won, Jong Kook.
- Really?
[Monday Couple wins the second round.]
Woong In, Gil Kang, and Hee Won...
we have to win the next round.
If we lose again, then it's all over.
Okay, the third round is...
Speed corn eating.
- I really love corn!
- Me too!
Then you can go in my place.
[Hee Won exhausted after two rounds?]
You need to finish eating the corn,
and come cross the line with the cob.
This one is very easy.
It doesn't count if you come back without
the cob even if you finish the corn?
Why are you so crooked in
the way you think?
- You have to hold onto it.
- Since there are more of us...
[Hee Won's simple way of saying things.]
Since there's more of us,
let's each take one of them down.
Then why don't you take Jong Kook?
Let's just forget it then.
Why is it always me?
I'm too scared of Jong Kook.
Hee Won.
First two to cross the finish line!
Go!
[Corn speed eating- Go!]
[Where is the corn?]
[Nice and warm corn on the cob.]
[Mowing down on the corn.]
Hold him back!
There are only two up here.
[Members starting to feel the pressure.]
[Gil Kang discovers the corn.]
[Eating the corn at top speed!]
[Ha Ha trying to interfere with
Hee Won again.]
I'm going to beat you.
[Another love/hate couple over here.]
[Almost finished with the corn.]
[Village idiot brothers.]
[Rushing back to the finish line
with each other's corn cob in hand.]
[They both crossed the finish line...]
[I wonder if it was good corn.]
This one is Jong Kook, and that's mine.
Don't even joke!
I brought this one.
[Checking out Kwang Soo's corn cob first.]
[Hm...
there are still bits of some kernels left.]
Disqualified!
[Kwang Soo fails.]
[Time to check Kkuk's corn cob next.]
[You're dead!]
Fail!
There are guys like them every summer causing
trouble when they can't fall asleep.
Pick up your cob.
[Out of breath Gil Kang also arrives.]
- I see a kernel!
- Fail!
[One kernel left on the cob.]
[Ah... unfortunately fails.]
It's not easy to get with my braces.
You have to eat it clean.
[Kkuk's desperate attempts.]
Make your escape!
[Prosecutor Kkuk not allowing
Woong In to get through.]
Go!
Go, Gil Kang!
[Woong In passing off his cob
off to Gil Kang!]
[Go!
Run off to the finish line!]
[I will protect your empty cob!]
[Gil Kang...]
[Gil Kang passing the cob back
to Woong In.]
[Thanks, Gil Kang.]
[Wait, that is?]
No, that's just...
It's all done!
That's nothing but a...
Fail.
You have to eat it clean.
Please save me.
I can't do this again!
[The Traitors' Club all rushing in
together at this time.]
I have to check out your cob.
[Ha Ha's cob to be checked out first.]
You ate way too much.
I told you to only eat half.
Fail!
[Ha Ha fails from being
too greedy with this corn.]
- Please give me a break.
- Fail.
[Next up is Big-nosed Brother.]
It's clean.
Success.
[Big-nose from the
Prosecution Team passes.]
[Hee Won coming towards the finish line.]
[Ha Ha intercepts Hee Won's cob,
and gets rid of it.]
[Please...]
[Having to turn back around
at the finish line...]
Why did you let him take
that from you?
[Please just leave me alone...]
[Ha Ha returning his cob back to him.]
[Unable to stop himself from
teasing Hee Won.]
[You scoundrel!]
It's clean.
Success.
He succeeded?
[Nice Hee Won finally succeeds
after all his difficulties.]
Is it over then?
You're going to have to
work out some more, Hee Won.
You really are going to have to
start working out.
Look at how fit I am.
- Why are you looking so exhausted?
- But you didn't run around that much.
What do you mean, I didn't run enough?
I've been running around all day.
You haven't been running much today.
Suk Jin's never talked to
anyone like that before.
You really should start working out.
Want to have a wrestling match?
[Big-nosed Brother's challenge.]
- That would be interesting.
- Let's try arm wrestling.
Okay, let's do it.
[Okay, let's do this!]
[Big-nose continuing to act like a brat.]
- Even Suk Jin has a day like this?
- Suk Jin, seriously.
[First time seeing Suk Jin looking
so confidant and cocky like this.]
I guess he thinks I'm that
easy of a prey.
I've never seen Suk Jin like this.
This is the first time I've seen him act
so confidant like this against a man.
[The battle between the two men
with their pride on the line.]
Suk Jin, you have to make
the first attack.
- Are you right handed or left handed?
- Me?
I'll let you know after we do this.
[Hee Won waiting until after
the match to tell him.]
- You have to tell us which hand you use.
- Why is that important?
That's my choice.
You can do this, Hee Won.
If your elbow falls off the table,
you're out.
Wait, he already has his wrist bent.
[The two men acting very sensitive
before the match even starts.]
You have to loosen up.
Both of you need to relax your grip.
[Just who will be dubbed
as the weakest member?]
[Big-nosed Suk Jin vs. Nice Hee Won-
Arm wrestle battle!]
- What's going on?
- Seriously?
[Big-nose wins!]
[My goodness...]
[How can this be?]
[Today is just...]
[Celebration ceremony.]
Ahn Gil Kang, come out here.
Come out here, Ahn Gil Kang.
[Cocky Big-nosed Brother's challenge.]
- That's enough!
- Are you okay, Hee Won?
It's okay, it's no big deal.
- It's no big deal that you lost.
- I'm left handed.
He always loses to even the girls!
[But to lose to Big-nose...]
I even lost to Minzy.
Hee Won,
Ji Hyo's waiting for her turn.
[Big-nosed Suk Jin vs. Nice Hee Won-
Round two.]
Okay, then let's do it that way.
[No more excuses to give
if he loses this round too.]
If Hee Won loses this round too...
- This is really uncomfortable though.
- Relax your grip.
- I should sit like this.
- You can't do that.
[Extremely sensitive.]
- He's not doing anything wrong.
- Okay, ready...
- Relax.
- One, two...
[Round two-
Left handed arm wrestling.]
[How will it end this time?]
[Oh my goodness...]
[There's your answer.]
- He really is a strange one.
- What are we going to do about this?
- Stop making him do this now.
- Why did you make me do that?
- I just thought it would be fun.
- It's just because you're tired right now.
Yes, you're right.
Look at how sweaty I am right now.
- How about your lower body then?
- How about leg wrestling?
- You still have both your legs.
- Stop torturing him!
[Even the spectators don't know
how to react to the results.]
I don't think you're going to be able to
play anymore villainous roles.
[A damaging effect on his career?]
I don't think you're going to get anymore
offers on villain roles.
[We'll wait for your new,
kind character roles.]
- Winning isn't what's important.
- Let's just move on to the next game.
This wasn't part of the plan anyway.
I didn't know it was going to be like this.
Let's just move on to our next game.
- Didn't you pass the last game?
- Yes, you did.
That's right, I did pass!
[Losing his train of thought after
the arm wrestling match.]
[Everyone enthralled with
Hee Won's charming personality.]
He's so adorable.
[Kim Hee Won is now known for his cuteness
whom everyone wants to keep in their pockets.]
Your next mission is, fireworks mission.
[Fourth round- Fireworks mission.]
[Find the firecracker inside the
cake boxes.]
[Must return to the finish line
before the fire cracker goes out.]
Three people will succeed
in the order of their arrival.
Okay, okay.
Sorry.
[Ha Ha discovers a cake box!]
[Must return back to the starting line
before the fire cracker goes out!]
Where is it?
Is it this way?
[Gil Kang also heads on his way
after lighting up his firecracker.]
[Back at the finish line...]
[Hee Won wringing out his towel that's
been wet by the ice water.]
I bet my arms got all weak earlier
from wringing out my towel.
I've been wringing out my
towel all night.
- You're right.
- So that's why?
It takes a lot of strength
to wring out the towel like this.
[Ha Ha just needs to round this corner
to get to the finish line!]
No!
[Oh no! The firecracker went out!]
- Did it go out, Ha Ha?
- My firecracker went out.
- Okay, it's off!
- If it's out, then you have to go back.
- You have to go back then.
- You have to go back and get a new one.
Just get lost.
[Succeeds in getting his
petty revenge against Ha Ha.]
[Pocket-man, Hee Won.]
- He's so adorable.
- You have to hurry with that firecracker.
He's the nation's cutie mascot.
[Gil Kang's firecracker is still lit!]
[Ahn Gil Kang is the first
to cross the finish line!]
[By the split of a hair! The fire goes out
as soon as he crosses the line.]
[Complete exhaustion.]
Then our team is still missing
Kwang Soo...
- And Woong In.
- Woong In.
[Defendants' Team- Woong In and Kwang Soo
vs. Prosecution Team's Jong Kook and Ha Ha.]
[Defendant's Team has
Jong Kook surrounded.]
- Let me at least light it up.
- Sure, go ahead.
- Sure, light it and go.
- Let me light it up at least.
[Standing ready with
the water bottle in hand.]
[Kkuk unable to light up his match.]
You have to make sure to
stick close to him.
Here's another one in there.
[Woong In looking inside the cake box
in case another one can be found.]
[A lighter in the corner of the box
that Kkuk missed seeing!]
[Woong In secretly lights up his firecracker
and is on his way!]
[Ha Ha is also sprinting off
to the finish line!]
Is someone coming?
Who is it?
Is it Woong In?
[Woong In is the first to arrive
with the lighted firecracker in hand!]
We won.
[Succeeds the mission.]
- Did all your teammates make it in?
- No, there's still Kwang Soo.
[Ha Ha crosses the finish line
soon thereafter.]
[First three to cross the finish line-
Gil Kang, Woong In, and Ha Ha.]
- So there's only those two left?
- It feels good to have beat Jong Kook.
A friend of mine told me to make sure
that I beat Jong Kook at something.
Jong Kook's really bad at
games like these.
- Really?
- Yes.
That doesn't make me feel very
good to hear that.
But I think that the last competition
is going to be a very dirty fight.
[Last round-
The dirtiest round thus far?]
[Tiger and the Giraffe about to show
the true meaning of a dirty, bloody fight.]
Hurry up and tell us what
the next mission is.
You all might as well just rest.
This is going to take all night.
- Did you never get it lit?
- No.
- This next round is never going to end.
- Kwang Soo, you have to win this round.
- Okay.
- We have to win this, Jong Kook.
- It's a one on one.
The next mission is...
Tissue blowing mission.
- Tissue blowing mission!
- We have to do something more dynamic!
How much more dynamic do
you want to get?
[What?]
I will show you how dynamic
tissue blowing can be.
You have to win this, Kwang Soo.
Both of you have to blow on the tissue
and the one who keeps it afloat longer wins.
You just have to keep it afloat
longer than your opponent.
The team that the winner of this
round belongs to
will win themselves another
piece of evidence.
[The final battle with the evidence
to the trial hanging on the balance!]
- Fighting!
- You have to beat him!
I will show you that our team is innocent!
[Defendant Team's Kwang Soo.]
Hey, you have to win this no matter what.
[Let's find the culprit and
shed light to the truth!]
[Prosecution Team's Kkuk.]
There's only one chance.
Okay, the positioning looks good.
[The Tissue Blowing game with two pieces of
evidence on the line starts now!]
[Kkuk's tissue falls to the ground
as soon as the game starts!]
[What luck is this!]
[Defendant Team's Kwang Soo wins!]
[Victim Big-nose explodes.
Prosecution Team up in arms.]
It's because he's so tall
and he was able to blow it up high.
- We won.
- He's too tall.
[Village investigation mission-
Defendant Team wins!]
- We won two missions in a row.
- I can't believe it.
Red Team can follow me.
[Leading the team off to where the two
pieces of evidence are located.]
He's normally very good
at that game.
[Defendant Team can choose to use the evidence
that will be to their advantage at the end.]
- Here's the evidence.
- It's the evidence.
I can see the evidence here.
Okay, here's your evidence.
Here.
[Defendant Team wins
their two pieces of evidence!]
[Hee Won unable to trust
his own teammates now.]
Let's go.
[Who will these evidences point to?]
[Heading back towards the courthouse
for the closing argument...]
[First Round- Line of Truth.
Defendant Team wins!]
[Second Round- Village Investigation.
Defendant Team wins.]
[Third Round- Lie Detector Investigation.
Prosecution Team wins.]
[One advantageous, and one disadvantageous
pieces of evidence at each round.]
[Depending on the choices the team makes,
they may either win or lose their case.]
[Looking at the photo.]
[An image of someone receiving
their mission?]
[Must be smart about how they
use their pieces of evidence...]
[An x-ray image?]
What is this?
File of the incident?
[All the evidence has been checked.]
[July 22nd, 11:30 P.M.]
[Time for the closing argument.]
- Everyone stay firm, okay?
- Hello.
[Jury stands in the courtroom.]
We promise that we will catch the culprit.
We know who the culprit is.
Don't be persuaded otherwise,
and remember what we talked about.
- Yes.
- Yes, we know.
The culprit is definitely in this room.
Everyone stand.
[Presiding Judge enters the court.]
Let's take a seat.
Okay, Case Number 157.
Smack to the head in the Darkroom.
We will now reach our verdict.
This trial will now reconvene as
a trial by the jury.
The members of this jury consists of citizens
who are unbiased of this case
and they will judge the verdict based
only on the showing of the evidence.
I ask that the jury listens to each side,
and make a fair judgment call.
We will now start the final closing argument.
Please make your judgment based on the
showing of the gathered evidence.
Please make sure to show your evidence
in the order that they were won.
[I vow to catch the culprit who
committed the earmuff assault.]
[We're not the culprits.]
[Attorney Yoo to start off his argument.]
What is he thinking wearing a hat
inside the courtroom?
Seriously!
Honorable Judge.
And the members of the jury.
Ji Suk Jin, who claims that he was hit by one
of the defendants who you see up here...
I have evidence here in my hand which will
show just what type of a person he is!
[Evidence which will show just what
type of a person Ji Suk Jin normally is?]
This evidence in my hand!
I would like to submit this evidence
to the Honorable Judge.
I would like for everyone to take a look
at this conclusive piece of evidence.
I would like for the members of the jury
and the Honorable Judge to decide
just what kind of a person
Ji Suk Jin truly is.
The whole world needs to see this!
Okay, please show the evidence.
I'm a very nice and innocent person
who doesn't know how to lie.
Please take a look up at the screen.
[Easy Brothers' Spy Episode.]
I'm sure all of you know
when this is from.
This is the episode where Ji Suk Jin and
Lee Kwang Soo first became the leads.
[Looking extremely happy to be the
star of an episode for once.]
- What is this?
- Take a look at the next clip.
[Next up is the Sherlock Holmes Episode.]
Having shown some special favors after
making complaints to the writers.
This is a scene from our
last week's episode.
It's embarrassing for us to even watch.
Do you see how he shoved
his own team members?
[Killing off his own team members.]
Did you see that?
The greed!
Did you see his greedy he became?
- Greed!
- The greed!
[And the pathetic defeat.]
[That's a bad piece of
evidence against him...]
This is the evidence we have
to show thus far.
Ji Suk Jin's normal self...
You all know him, don't you?
There's no need to even say it.
- He's a bad person!
- What?
- What do you mean, a bad person?
- You are a bad person!
- I'm an innocent victim!
- Unsatisfied with his role...
He's always been greedy for
the role of being the show's star.
[Big-nose always having wanted to
become the star of the show.]
Even though any one of us
would like to be the star of the show
he is the only one who directly
approached the writers
to let them know that he would like to be
made the star of the show.
There aren't many other who would
have done what he did. However...
Our Ji Suk Jin...
he has approached countless numbers of
our writers and repeatedly pleaded his case
to ask for a special show written about him.
And just last week, he shoved Minzy
of 2NE1 off the water platform.
Yes, that was just last week.
You all saw that, right?
In order to stand in the limelight himself,
he shoved off all his own teammates.
He shoved Jong Kook and Blank Ji
off the water platform into the pool
and he even leg tripped Minzy who just
turned 20 years old, out of greed.
He showed us a very pathetic
and tacky side of himself!
I'm sure that even all the members of
the jury saw that clearly for themselves.
Therefore...
the incident in question...
is a fabricated story that the writers and
Ji Suk Jin wrote and came up with.
This is all just a fabrication!
I would like to clearly state and
make everyone see the truth behind that.
- No further statements.
- That's just absurd!
I was hit in my ears!
Ji Suk Jin cares for and cherishes his body
more than anything else.
That's correct!
- So?
- I wouldn't hit myself and hurt myself.
[He's not the type of person to hit
himself and bring himself that kind of pain.]
What if by hitting yourself,
you be made the star of the episode?
[Hm?]
[Prosecution Team keeping him
from saying anything.]
- Don't say anything!
- Don't respond to that!
Even the members of the jury know how much
Ji Suk Jin cares for his own body.
And Ji Suk Jin is known
for his inability to lie.
- Ji Suk Jin is a good liar.
- I can't lie.
I've seen you lie to your wife a countless
number of times in the past ten plus years.
That's something for the family court!
- This isn't the time for that!
- I saw him do it!
- This is not the setting for this!
- He lies to his wife all the time!
I only did that for the sake of
keeping the peace within my family.
This case is irrelevant to
those statements.
We will only hear the statements
that are relevant to this case.
If there are no further statements,
we will move on to the next piece of evidence.
- Okay, it's us.
- Prosecution may make their statement.
- Okay.
- Let's show them how to do this.
I don't think there's even a need for any
further evidence after this one.
[Conclusive piece of evidence?]
- I believe that you'll see the truth in it.
- I believe you'll know what it is.
It's a conclusive piece of evidence.
[It looks like a picture of some sort...]
Why don't we all take a look?
Please look up at the screen.
[A picture of Woong In?]
This picture was taken around
1 P.M. this afternoon.
This picture was taken in a location
nearby where the incident took place.
- Can you tell us who that is in the picture?
- It's me.
- Yes, it is.
- Yes.
- Who's the man that you're sitting with?
- It'd the PD who's sitting over there.
[None other than the PD in charge of the show
meeting with Defendant Woong In.]
Yes, it is.
In that case...
What were you talking about
with the chief PD?
I arrived a little earlier than
I thought I was going to be.
So I just sat down with him to thank him
for inviting me onto the show.
[Stating that they shared
a normal conversation...]
[The prosecution stand getting excited.]
Honorable Judge and
the members of the jury.
The defendant had a private meeting with
the PD in charge before the show started.
Yes, that's correct.
You need to look towards the camera.
It's because I have so much respect
for the presiding Judge!
Please give me your attention.
Arriving before any other members to meet
with the PD on the day of the recoding...
The meaning behind such a private and
secluded meeting like that...
What is this?
Am I the star of this episode?
[On average...]
[It's with the purpose of...]
[relaying special missions
such as this?]
- Whether to be told that you're the spy...
- That's correct!
- Or the star of that episode...
- Yes!
It's to receive a special order
such as that!
[Shows up early to receive a special
mission unbeknownst to others?]
That's the only reason why anyone would
have a private meeting with the PD!
- Take a look!
- It looks like a serious conversation.
He's intently listening to something.
Look at his serious expression.
That expression on his face isn't someone who's
casually thanking someone for the invite.
- This conversation here...
- He's such an amateur.
- He's such an amateur!
- Look at the secretive look on his face!
Look at the serious glint
in his eyes!
[Stating that his expression
looks too serious.]
- That's all.
- What was all that about?
- What were you even talking about?
- I'm saying that what Woong In said...
Get out here!
[Fit of rage in the courtroom?]
Please take a look at his behavior.
He's very violent.
Send him out.
He's not helping any.
He's going to make us lose our case.
- Judge.
- Yes?
- We have a witness.
- A witness!
- A witness?
- Its none other than our Prosecutor Gae.
[Calling Prosecutor Gae into the witness
stand for having been on scene.]
I was on the scene at the
time of the crime.
[About to explain the incident
at the time of the crime.]
[Attorney Yoo in charge of
defending the suspects.]
- Do you swear to only speak the truth?
- I swear.
- I swear to only speak the truth.
- Yes, thank you.
- If you lie on oath, you can be punished.
- Til the day I die.
This is how we were all seated
at the scene of the crime.
And the sofa was placed in the
U shape around the coffee table.
I ask that members of the jury
pay close attention to this.
Defendant Ahn Gil Kang was seated
to the left of me at the time.
And to the right of me
was Defendant Jung Woong In.
This is where I was seated in the beginning.
That's where I was seated at first.
But Jung Woong In kept insisting
on sitting where I was seated.
[Jung Woong In insisted on siting
where Ha Ha was seated?]
Ji Suk Jin was seated right
across from where I sat at first.
So he situated himself in the spot which
was the easiest spot for him to hit him.
I was shoved out of my seat
so that he could take over my spot.
And next to me sat Kim Hee Won.
[Prosecution Team lays out how
everyone was seated around the table.]
[The light went out for only five seconds.]
[The person who had the access to hit
Ji Suk Jin on his head was?]
It had to be either Ji Suk Jin,
or Lee Kwang Soo.
If the PD himself hit the victim, then he's
not even fit to be called a human being!
In which case, it has to be either
Lee Kwang Soo or Jung Woong In.
[Prosecution stand indicts Lee Kwang Soo
or Jung Woong In as the culprits.]
No! It's most likely
that he did it to himself!
[Self fabricated story?]
[He did it to himself?]
The most important fact to remember...
is that after the light went out...
and right before the light
came back on...
[Waiting room when it was
thrown into a pitch of darkness.]
I was seated in my seat.
And right before the lights
came back on...
I felt someone rushing back
to their seat just like that.
[He felt someone else rushing back
to take their seat?]
The difference between someone jumping
up from their seat and sitting back down
and the feeling of someone rushing back to
their seat to sit down is very different.
Unless I'm a total idiot,
I'd be able to feel something like that.
- Kang Gary can't lie.
- But you are an idiot.
[What?]
You have shown us your evidence,
and made your statements.
But one must remember that the act of
hitting someone is evidence in itself.
What Kang Gary just stated
isn't direct evidence in itself.
He didn't say that he saw the hit,
but that he felt someone move.
The image of Jung Woong In and
the PD having a conversation...
that's all just speculation of
what may have gone on.
It's all just speculation on their part.
Someone sitting next to Kang Gary
as he stated...
that's also just a speculation.
All of this is just
circumstantial speculation.
[These are nothing but
circumstantial evidence.]
What we need is solid evidence of someone
seeing a person get up from their seat
or the recording of someone moving
off their seats in the security camera.
Something for the members of the jury
that are sitting in the stand
or the Honorable Judge in his seat...
to be convinced of the who the culprit is...
some irrefutable evidence is needed.
Just because he's known for his
villain roles and circumstantial evidence...
That's correct!
[The defendants cannot be indicted as being
guilty just from circumstantial evidence.]
What you're doing isn't just!
- Another thing...
- That's a great point!
- What are you doing?
- I think that he has a valid point.
I'd like to say one more thing.
- Gary mentioned this himself.
- Yes?
Do you think that the PD hit you?
- That's what he said.
- Yes.
If...
If the PD in charge and
Ji Suk Jin really planned it...
and PD was the one who hit him?
Isn't that also just pure speculation?
That is all I have for now.
[Attorney Yoo could be right.]
[One of the pieces of evidence that
the Prosecution Team had earlier...]
[was a picture like this one.]
We will now move on to
the final piece of evidence.
Defense Team may present their evidence.
- You have another evidence?
- We...
We received a warrant to
confiscate Ji Suk Jin's cellphone.
We will now take a look through
Ji Suk Jin's cellphone.
- It's a warrant.
- This is injustice!
- Please hand over the phone.
- This could be the end of my family life.
Please unlock your cellphone.
There it is right away.
PD Jo.
[Call log and text messages from PD Jo?]
Every one of the jury and
Honorable Judge...
Please take a look at the correspondence
that took place between them up on the screen.
Okay.
Are you seeing this?
July 22nd, 12:22 P.M.
Do you see all the call logs?
There is a message right here.
12:25- 'Are you on the way?'
Response, 'I'm almost there'.
- 'Are you here?'
- 'Okay'
Scroll down.
This is the important one.
[The correspondence that
breeds suspicion.]
- 'You didn't tell the other members?'
- What did he say in response?
- 'Okay.'
Every one of the jury,
what time did we all meet today?
We were to meet at 1:30.
- 1:30.
- I got here at 1:50.
Then why did Ji Suk Jin arrive here
before the rest of us?
And also...
Ji Suk Jin and PD Jo never talks to each other
unless there's something special going on.
But...
[He's admitting to that point?]
He showed up half hour to an hour
before the rest of us
and exchanged those messages with
the PD. Why is that?
- Honorable Judge!
- I object!
- His questions are leading!
- Please wait.
What we just saw up on the screen...
is enough to show that these two talked about
something that we're not aware of.
That this episode...
is a show that was planned and made up
by PD Jo and Ji Suk Jin.
- No, that's absurd.
- Then Jung Woong In earlier...
[Then what of the picture that was taken
of Jung Woong In and the PD?]
I believe that the picture is a setup.
When it comes to that,
aren't you the expert in it?
I didn't take the picture.
Okay, that's enough.
Lee Kwang Soo is...
I don't want you to talk.
Aren't I allowed to say
anything at all?
Honorable Judge,
and the members of the jury.
I was hit twice in my ears.
He was once hit in the face
at a nightclub.
[What?]
[Breaking out into fits of laughter.]
He was acting up and got beat up
by all the big guys at the club.
Honorable Judge.
I ask that you find out
the truth for us.
It is time for the final closing statement.
[Prosecution's final closing statement.]
Victim Ji Suk Jin has been like an older
brother to all of us for the past three years
and he is always the first one ousted
and alerts us of the race starting.
And he's always been the one to raise
others up rather than himself.
And he has never once complained to others
about the position he's been in
or expressed any displeasure
to the writers on staff.
Why are you laughing?
And today, without any reason...
he was assaulted violently by someone.
And there are many circumstantial speculations
shown in the evidence today.
Therefore, I believe that it is unreasonable
to see this as fabricated story from Suk Jin.
However, the reason why we're stating that
Jung Woong In is the likeliest culprit
is because it's a very highly
likeable probability.
We, the prosecution, believe that there is
enough supporting evidence to back that up.
I ask that you make the right
and just verdict.
- I will now start my closing statement.
- Please take off your glasses.
Take them off.
[Taking off his classes to make
his serious closing statement.]
Honorable Judge and the members of the jury.
As I'm sure you've all seen already,
these men here are known for being villains.
I'm sorry.
I just received a complaint from
one of my defendants.
[Attorney Yoo receiving complaints about
the way he looks without his glasses.]
- The viewers may be uncomfortable too.
- Yes, I've received complaints about this.
- Yes, I understand.
- So I must put the glasses back on.
Thank you.
Because...
of their momentary frightening expressions
that's seen on their faces...
Because of the rough and villainous
roles that they've often played...
they are receiving this unfairly
based misunderstanding.
If the members of the jury could
switch your positions
and look at this from their perspective
how frustrated and upset would you be
from the injustice of it all?
[What have they ever done wrong besides
play villainous roles in movies?]
There is a saying that I'd like to mention.
'Even if you lose the catch
to capture the ten criminals...
you must not let even a single
innocent man suffer injustice.'
That infamous legal saying
was created for situation like this.
This is what I'd like to state
at this moment.
Even though I may not know who
is responsible for today's crime
please...
don't let these men suffer from injustice
for having played villainous roles.
That is all.
We will take a brief recess for
the jury to make their verdict.
[Just what will come of the verdict?]
One of them hit me in my ears!
On both sides.
- We're going to win this.
- It's at least a 20 year sentence.
I will show you what
a perfect crime looks like.
Ji Suk Jin has always dreamt of
being the star of this show.
The meaning behind meeting up with
the chief PD without anyone else knowing...
is to receive some sort of
secretive order.
[It's a premeditated crime.]
[It's a premeditated crime planned out
by Suk Jin and the PD?]
Why did he come an hour before
the rest of the members...
and exchange those messages
with the PD?
[Just... what is the truth?]
[The jury has reached a verdict.]
[The final verdict.]
- We have reached a verdict.
- I hope we get the innocent verdict.
- I believe in the members of the jury.
- Please.
- Please... please!
Case- Smack to the head in the dark.
The final verdict is...
The case claims that the victim Ji Suk Jin was
assaulted in the wait room during the blackout
but there aren't any eye witnesses who
can testify to the victim's claims.
From the evidence of the pictures that
the prosecution team has submitted
Jung Woong In met with the PD before the
recording started to receive the orders
to assault Ji Suk Jin in the dark.
And thus, it's highly possible that he did
assault the victim as ordered.
However...
if Ji Suk Jin was going after the spotlight
as the defense is stating that he did...
also the call logs and the text message
records from Ji Suk Jin's phone we've seen
could also indicate that this said incident
is an event that he fabricated
or committed to himself in order to
garner more attention.
This is also a possible scenario
that we cannot ignore.
Therefore...
this case does not prove to be an incident
without its share of reasonable doubts.
And thus, we the jury would like to
reveal the verdict that's been decided.
That verdict...
In a vote of four against one...
Per Criminal Procedural Law Article 325,
to the defendants standing this trial...
we declare the defendants innocent.
[We'd like to thank Attorney No Seung Hyoo,
and Gwon Yuri for their assistance.]
I'd like to appeal this verdict.
[No culprit has been confirmed.]
Justice has been served!
I'm going to appeal this verdict,
so you need to clear your schedules.
We're going to appeal this verdict.
- You have to come back next week.
- Thank you for all the hard work.
- You'll be punished for this!
- You're a bad man.
[Gil Kang finally feeling justified
after having been suspected of the crime.]
- Wow... seriously.
- Anyways, it's all over now.
Why don't we get a nice warm
bowl of soft tofu soup?
It's because of this incompetent
group of prosecutors.
I'm a little suspicious now.
Why did you do it?
[Huh? Why did he do it?]
Did you do it?
Did you really do it?
- Me?
- You did do it! That's what your face says!
This is driving me crazy!
Doesn't anybody believe me?
- Just go in for now...
- Go in where?
Why would I?
Why would I go to jail?
Seriously!
This is injustice!
[Two hours ago]
What is this?
[A tape?]
[Definitive CCTV camera footage.]
I'm going to pretend that I
didn't see that.
We have to ignore this.
[They decide to get rid of
this piece of the evidence.]
[The evidence that was thrown away...]
[The footage on the tape...]
[The footage that captured
the whole scene.]
[A man that headed towards Suk Jin
as soon as the lights went out...]
- What the heck?
- What? What happened?
[The truth of the Earmuffs Assault.]
[The culprit is none other than...]
Someone just hit me.
[Jung Woong In commits the
perfect crime.]
Subtitles by DramaFever