[Fate- A predetermined life
or situation.]
Subtitles by DramaFever
You're not scared, are you?
[One day...]
Let's look over here.
[An event...]
[That they weren't prepared for...]
I'm so sick and tired of this life.
- Please...
- I want to be done with this.
[An end that they so long for.]
- Jae Suk? He's still alive.
- Thank goodness!
[A mystery within the mirror?]
[Mirror, mirror...
Are we the fateful couple?]
- I have the 'Basic Instinct' movie.
- And I have 'Sunday Seoul'.
[A fateful couple?]
One, two, three. Mirror, mirror...
Are we the fateful couple?
One of you will die if you scream.
[However...]
[The mystery of the meaning of
the messages continues on.]
[Just why...]
- If more than three people gather...
- I think we're all going to die.
Let's all die together.
Let's just all die!
[The unavoidable twist of fate.]
[One of you will die if you
look behind you.]
I want to live!
I'm too scared to keep
doing Running Man.
[Their unavoidable fate.]
I saw who it was.
The two of you are not
the fateful couple.
[Had they known back then...]
[Five years ago at Running Man High School.]
So can we sit wherever we want?
[A rowdy group of junior year
high school students.]
- Hang on a second...
- There are eight seats here.
Morning announcement says
that we can sit wherever we want.
[Morning announcement-
Sit in any empty chair you wish.]
- I'm going to sit in this seat.
- I want to sit in the middle.
- All the cool kids can sit over here.
- Everyone give me your attention.
Are you the class leader?
- I'm the class leader.
- Why are you the class leader?
You're just a class giraffe
that our school is raising.
What are you talking about?
This seat is really comfortable.
- You always sat in the back, didn't you?
- Hang on a minute.
He always sits in the back.
- It's because he wants to nap in class.
- You should study more.
I know, and I block the teacher from
seeing him sleeping in the back.
- It's good to see you, Suk Jin.
- You still need to use formal speech with me.
[Asking for formalities to be kept
even during the role playing.]
Suk Jin, why are you the
same age as the teacher?
He's a year younger than me.
My wish is to finally
graduate from this school.
What's going on here today?
There aren't any girl students in here.
- One of those seats are Ji Hyo's.
- But only one of them are Ji Hyo's.
- But that still leaves one seat open.
- One of them is going to be Ji Hyo.
I bet it's a race to become a couple.
- This is an all-boys school.
- Hurry up and sit down in your seat.
- Hurry up and sit down.
- Don't you know what time it is?
Hey, be quiet.
She's the ruler of this school.
- I'm a new transfer student here.
- What did you say?
- I'm a new transfer student.
- No, you're not. We saw you last week.
- Guys, say 'hi' to the new student.
- Hey, I don't want you to say 'hi' to me.
- Go sit back down.
- Just come back here.
Don't talk to her.
- Know when to talk to her.
- Gauge Ji Hyo's mood before you talk to her.
- Are you the class leader?
- That's right.
- Then I have something to say to you.
- What is it?
What do you mean, get lost?
You can't tell the
class leader to get lost!
[Class leader Giraffe being treated
more like the neighborhood dog.]
- Are you going to keep being like that?
- Then be a better class leader!
- That was so funny.
- That's such an old trick.
I haven't had that trick
played on me in so long.
- And there's one more transfer student.
- What? Really?
[Another transfer student?]
[Another transfer student that will set
the hearts of male students racing.]
Come on in, friend.
- Who is it?
- Come on in!
- What nice manners.
- Come in.
[Who could it be?]
[The nation's first love, Suzy.]
[The class jumps to their feet.]
Suzy!
- Suzy!
Hi.
[Running Man High School's
male students in state of chaos.]
- My name is Suzy.
- I know!
I've seen you on TV!
- Please take good care of me.
- I saw you kissing Lee Seung Gi!
Look at her acting shy.
- But we still like you.
- Thanks.
[Bright and cheerful new
transfer student.]
- Is Suzy going to sit in this seat?
- She hasn't decided yet.
- Come here, Suzy.
- Where do you want to sit, Suzy?
[Which seat will these girls take?]
Come here, Suzy.
[Anticipation]
[Chooses the second group.]
Why?
[A mixture of joy and sorrow
in the classroom.]
- My name is Yoo Jae Suk.
- School no longer seems as fun.
What a pretty laugh she has.
- That's such nice laughter.
- Why don't you smile a little too?
- Hey!
- I told you not to talk to me.
- Quiet.
- Oh my goodness!
[Homeroom Teacher Go
makes his entrance.]
Why are you boys
so full of chatter this morning?
- Is he our teacher?
- Attention!
Quiet.
You're the loudest one of the bunch.
Okay.
Okay, roll call.
Hmm... I see that you're all here.
You're not up to anything, are you?
I'm not in the best mood today,
so we're only going to do the morning class.
- Teacher Go, who's your first love?
- Be quiet.
Okay, we are going to be playing
the Fourth Period Graduation Race today.
Once you complete your fourth period,
you can graduate.
- It'll be a great...
- Am I finally going to get to graduate?
- Wow, finally!
- Congratulations.
Every time you win a game,
you will be given a pair of running shoes.
The first team to cross the finish line
with everyone wearing the shoes will win.
Are we not going to be able to run the field
if we don't have running shoes on?
Okay, as for the field...
- Teacher, Go, I have a question.
- Ji Hyo has a question.
You have to answer the question.
- Why aren't you answering the question?
- It could be very important.
Your teams will be divided
in the group that you're in.
Group one will be one team.
And then group two will be a team.
- I knew that was going to happen.
- Pretty simple, right?
- I'm on the same team with Jae Suk?
- I like that Suzy's here, but Jong Kook?
[The two worst naggers, Jae Suk
and Jong Kook are on the same team.]
I'm stuck right in the middle of them.
[First period-
The Law of the Parabola.]
- What is this?
- What does that say?
[First period is outdoor phys ed.]
- The law of the parabola?
- What does that mean?
I think we're supposed to
put something in there.
Use the law of parabola to leverage
a 45 degree angle off the ground
to throw your slipper and land it
inside the shoe slot with your name on it.
[A scientific game utilizing
the law of parabola.]
What if we land the shoe in a slot
with someone else's name on it?
- Then it doesn't count.
- It doesn't count?
Suzy's name up there looks like
the name of some country.
- Isn't there a country with a similar name?
- No.
- Yes, there is.
- No, there isn't.
- I'm sure that there is.
- Then what about Lee Kwang Soo's name?
Lee Kwang Soo?
Some body of water?
Where do we have to stand?
Over here?
Who don't you go home and do it from there?
Then give me a camera!
I'll take a cameraman home and do it there.
- Why do you have to be like that?
- I hate being stuck between them.
Okay, Gary.
[Gary is the first to start.]
[Random Mr. Capable shows surprising skills
even though it was someone else's slot.]
- Gary's good at things like this.
- He's got the feel for it.
- You can't kick it off too high.
- You have to kick it low.
- Don't step on the line.
- The release time is important.
- You have to release it low to the ground.
- He's so loud.
You'd better be quiet before I kick my
shoe off and land it in your mouth.
It's going to head your way.
If you don't want to
go to this school anymore...
I'll make it so that you don't go to
this school anymore.
What did you say?
[Battle of wills between Kkuk and Yoo Hyuk
with no sign of concession from either side.]
You're going to graduate while
in a hospital bed.
I told you not to do that!
You needed to kick from this level.
Okay.
It's Suzy's turn!
- Suzy!
- You can't kick it off too high.
- That's what I said.
You should be able to do it since
you're good at martial arts.
[The shoe goes flying off her foot in
a straight and lightning fast manner.]
- That's the move, Suzy.
- That was it.
Show them what you've got, Kwang Soo.
Okay, I'll take my turn.
He doesn't look like he'd be
any good at it.
[Huh?]
No, I didn't do anything.
[Self-proclaimed class leader, Giraffe-
Instigating a fight with Kkuk.]
[Still eyes Kkuk as his target.]
- You're asking for death.
- He's starting to get mad.
- You really are asking for it.
- I wouldn't put it past him to do it.
Everyone except for Jong Kook sit down.
This could get dangerous.
[Giraffe warning every one
of his high kick.]
- Why don't you sit down, Gary?
- I already warned you guys.
This is just a game.
Enjoy it as a game.
No, I don't want to do that.
Challenge!
[Low kick?]
- I'm sorry, that was a mistake.
- Turn the cameras off.
- He asked for the cameras to be turned off.
- If they had, you'd really be in trouble.
Thank you, camera men.
Challenge.
- I think he's going to get it.
- Come on, Kwang Soo.
Kwang Soo!
[Flying above Suzy's head.]
What are you doing?
Are you out of your mind?
- You just almost hit Suzy.
- Suzy, I didn't hit you, did I?
Do you want to leave this earth?
[Looks as though his life may be
in danger after one wrong kick.]
This is harder than I thought.
[Big-nosed Brother's turn.]
[A perfect goal in!]
- I can't believe you made it in!
- I got it in there.
Hey, Gary!
We win if you get it in.
[If Random Mr. Capable, Gary succeeds...]
There you go!
[That was so close!]
- Okay, we can still do this.
- Watch out for the door hinges on it.
- Door hinge? Okay.
- You can do this.
You got it.
[Huh?]
[Ji Suk Jin]
[A newborn couple?]
- Confess your feelings for him.
- So it's been Suk Jin all along?
Is that why you've been acting the
way you have for the past three years?
- You have to kick your leg out straight.
- I know what I'm doing.
- This is nerve-wrecking.
- You have to kick it in the right direction.
This is the way you're supposed to kick.
[How will he do?]
[Fail]
[Bad enough for Suzy to condemn.]
There are three teams here today.
There's the Blue Team, White Team,
and Kim Jong Kook.
No, there are four teams here.
Team Yoo Jae Suk.
Just hurry up and do it.
It's not Team Yoo Jae Suk,
but it's Team Yoon Jae Suk and Suzy.
What did you say?
Don't you know Team Suzy and Ha Ha?
- We're a pretty well-known team.
- What did you say?
[Ha Ha taking his turn.]
[A perfect goal!]
You want to know how you do it?
Stand over here.
[Teaching a lesson to two Mr. Know-it-all's.]
- He just got lucky.
- One, two, three, kick. Try it.
- You have to know to be humble.
- You just got lucky.
What does being humble
have to do with anything?
The team hasn't won yet. Your
own personal win isn't what's important.
What do you mean, a personal win?
That was a win for the team.
[Kang Gary's turn once again.]
- Fighting!
- Ji Hyo usually cheers Gary on.
- He's on the opposing team, Suzy.
- That's what I'm saying.
It's okay, you can cheer me on.
Why don't you aim for the space
right below Ji Hyo's? That's right!
[A goal?]
[Success]
That's right!
[Random Mr. Capable!]
Gary! Gary!
I can't believe Gary made that.
[Thanks to Gary, Random Mr. Capable,
Group Two earns their pair of shoes!]
- Can we put them on right now?
- It's okay, we'll get the next one.
Second period is gym class.
Please move on to Room Three
for the junior class.
What's this?
I bet it's going to be arm wrestling.
- It's arm wrestling?
- It's gym class.
- Do you see what's written up there?
- Okay, it's couple arm wrestling.
You have to take care of this
for our team.
Finish this for us, Jong Kook.
You're our champion.
- Let's do this.
- Finish it.
Fighting, Kim Jong Kook!
Ji Hyo's really strong though.
- It's important for the girl to win this.
- The man with thighs for arms.
Ji Hyo's going to win this.
I'll tell you a sure way of
winning this game.
[Do it to me too.]
- I really like him at times like this.
- I love having him for things like this.
I like him a lot during games like this one
when he doesn't talk much.
Teamwork is what's important
when it comes to games like this.
- My thumb is stuck.
- This is a man with legs for arms.
- Look at how his arms looks like thighs.
- This man has four legs.
- What are you guys doing?
- I'm sorry.
Ready.
I can tell that this game is
already over.
[First round: Big-nose and Blank Ji
vs. Kkuk and Suzy.]
[Start]
- I don't know. It looks pretty close.
- He's smiling right now.
Suzy's the one doing all the
work right now.
- Let's do this, Suzy.
- You can do this, Ji Hyo.
They're holding up better than I thought.
Suk Jin has to stick his arm closer.
You have to stick your arm up
right next to Ji Hyo's.
See how your arms are spaced out?
You have to stick them up against each other.
There you go.
That way I can beat you guys.
[Ah... so he can beat them?]
[Kkuk's one man stage show.]
If they don't stick them together,
you can't push their arms down.
- Can't someone else do this instead of him?
- No, we can't.
- He's going to finish this for us.
- He's just too strong for us.
He's going to finish this game.
[Round Two: Gary and Blank Ji
vs. Kkuk and Suzy.]
You have to beat Jong Kook,
and you have to finish Ha Ha too.
Ready, set, go.
- That looks good. You can do this.
- This is a close call!
[Monday Couple power!]
[However...]
- Stick them together... that way I'll win.
- Their arms are sticking together.
[Even though they gave it their best...
still no chance of winning.]
- I'm not even needed in the game.
- It's all about the planning.
Kim Jong Kook is going to
finish this up.
Suzy's not even putting her
strength behind it.
[Will Kkuk be able to finish them
all off on his own?]
You can finish this.
[The last hope for Group Two-
Self-proclaimed class leader, Giraffe.]
It's like there's a building behind Suzy.
He's like the 63 building.
There's no way to beat him.
Once he wins this round,
it's an easy win after that.
- You can do this, Kwang Soo.
- Just look at Jong Kook in the eye.
[Their plan is to attack Jong Kook by playing
on Jong Kook's weakness towards women?]
Kim Jong Kook already has his wrist bent.
Look at this!
[A fierce protest.]
- I can't play like this!
- This isn't right!
[Protesting loudly at his bent wrist
before the competition even starts.]
Ji Hyo, I think you're being
too overly sensitive about this.
Look at how he had his wrist
already bent over like that!
[Extremely angry Blank Ji.]
- You seem very angry, Ji Hyo.
- Giraffe had his wrist bent over too.
[On the verge of Bully Ji Hyo
making her appearance.]
- But he already had his wrist bent over.
- Her alter ego is coming out in that uniform.
Okay, have a seat.
Okay, let's end this quickly.
Set, go.
- That looks good.
- Don't let him beat you.
- Put some strength into it.
- Just beat him.
[Giraffe and Blank Ji using every ounce of
energy they have into beating him.]
Here, get closer.
[Huh?]
That hurts!
[Giraffe going after Kkuk's shoulders.]
[But the 63 building isn't even budging.]
Come on, fall down.
Fall down!
Wait!
[Kkuk and Suzy win again!]
- Arm wrestling is the easiest to win!
- Suzy and Jong Kook wins!
[An easy win for Group One!]
- This really... there's no way to beat him.
- This isn't a fair game.
- There's no way to beat him in this.
- No way.
No way.
[She said that there's no way...]
[But this is still where she ends up.]
[Just how did this happen?]
[It's finally fourth period.]
- What's this?
- HR?
What's this?
[Personal belongings check.]
[Hide all your personal belongings.]
[Must find appropriate belonging
to oust the person.]
[The team to oust the most people
wins the game.]
What's this?
We have to find what the other person hid?
[Current count of the pairs of shoes won-
Group Two- 2 pairs, Group One- 3 pairs.]
[All of the students working hard to hide
each of their personal belongings.]
[Hiding them in secret so that
the other team can't find them.]
[Ten minute personal belonging
treasure hunt starts now.]
[Must find the personal belonging first
in order to eliminate their name tags.]
The 'R' sticker is stuck on the item.
['R' sticker and the name of the person whom
the item belongs to are affixed to the item.]
Could it be underneath the desk...
[Why is the self-proclaimed team leader
Giraffe staring at Suzy so intently?]
[A few moments ago.]
[Having found an unbelievably clever place
to hide his own personal item.]
[He thought no one would
ever find it...]
[What do I do?]
[Suzy fortunately only searches
through the lower racks?]
[Closes the door out of nervousness.]
Why is it so hard to find anything?
It can't be in a garbage can, right?
There are so many statues around.
Couldn't something be under one of these?
I know of a spot where there were tons of
bust statues that I saw earlier.
Here it is.
Here they are.
[Rushing over to the very same room.]
Seriously, what's with that guy?
[That's where Kwang Soo's item is!]
Jae Suk!
[Making desperate efforts to
divert his attention away.]
[Group Two made to feel anxious.]
[Giraffe ultimately walking into
the secret hiding room.]
What do you want?
What are you doing here?
[Ah...]
Run!
[Discovers Kwang Soo's item!]
Look at him running away!
Run away!
Lee Kwang Soo.
Lee Kwang Soo!
[Giraffe caught in the jar.]
[Kkuk and Yoo Hyuk working together
to oust the Giraffe.]
[Self-proclaimed Kwang Soo is out!]
What is he?
Is he a detective?
[But little Kkuk grows up to be
a singer instead.]
[Speechless]
[All of the students disperse to
find other people's personal items.]
Don't you think that
something would be in here?
[A room that's perfect for hiding.]
[Blank Ji searching through even
the smallest of containers.]
[Discovers Jong Kook's personal item!]
[Flustered Kkuk.]
Come here!
Gary, Suzy's by the front door!
[Kkuk and Suzy keeping both of the doors
securely shut.]
Dong Hoon.
Hurry up and find Gary's.
Where am I supposed to find Gary's?
[Group One's Kkuk is in danger!]
[Blank Ji sneaking up to the front door.]
Stop her, Suzy.
Keep Ji Hyo away from me.
Grab Ji Hyo!
Hurry up and grab Ji Hyo.
Get Ji Hyo!
Grab Ji Hyo!
[Must hurry and find Gary's item!]
Ji Hyo!
I'm sorry, Suzy!
I'm going to lose my mind.
[Kkuk holding out desperately.]
[This is where Gary's item is!]
[All four starting to exhaust
themselves of their strength.]
[Ha Ha is so close to where
Gary hid away his item.]
- Come here, Ji Hyo.
- Suzy...
I need you to move out of the way.
[Suzy getting shoved out of the way again.]
[Finally gets a hold of the name tag!]
[Jong Kook is finally ousted!]
Hurry up and find it.
Did he get ousted?
We have to hurry and find
Gary's item.
I can't believe she beat me
with her strength.
[Suzy's pride seems to be wounded after
having been shoved out of the way.]
I'm going to oust every one of them.
- Let's search through all this.
- Where's your report card?
- What about the comic book?
- The comic book?
[Finally finds Gary's item at last!]
[Carefully pulls it out...]
Kang Gary!
[Rushes off to catch Gary!]
- Kang Gary!
- Why? Did you find something?
Did you find something?
[Discovers Gary, the owner of the item!]
[Desperately tries to defend
his name tag.]
[Gary- Out!]
[Fourth period- Group One wins!]
Is it over?
[Class over]
Class is over now.
Since fourth period is over, you all
now get to graduate. Congratulations.
- Thank you.
- I finally get to graduate after 20 years.
Please pick a key of your choice.
[Several mysterious keys
laid out on the table...]
Which one are you going to pick?
Is Jae Suk picking the model student one?
- I want this one.
- What does the flower boy one mean?
That one is me.
I'm the only one who fits that.
[Yoo Hyuk chooses the game room key.]
- Should I choose the model student one?
- Then I'll take the last place one.
[Everyone picking a key of their choice.]
Hang on... I'll take this one.
[Gary who's confident with his looks
chooses the key for the flower boy room.]
Flower boy room?
That doesn't really fit you.
Isn't the young lady's room key
not really befitting for Ji Hyo?
- She may be a bit old for that.
- Which one did you pick?
Put your key inside the envelopes
that you see on the table in front of you
and write your name on
the envelope.
This is a letter that
you're writing to yourself.
And then you can put the letters in this
slow mailbox once you're done.
[Envelopes to be placed inside
the slow mailbox.]
- This letter is to your future selves.
- We put them in here?
[The letter is going to get delivered
to my future self?]
Then does this mean that I'm
going to become a flower boy?
That's right.
Gary's will become a flower boy.
[Without knowing what's going to
happen to them down the road...]
[they mail their keys to their
future selves.]
One, two, three.
[Thus they all got to graduate.]
[And the time passes...]
[Five years later.]
['O' University in Kyungido.]
Hey, Gary Kang.
- This... I remember this from five years ago.
- I remember this.
- Remember mailing the key five years ago?
- It's the mailbox from five years ago.
- Remember putting the key in here?
- That's right.
I forgot which room key I picked.
This is the first time you're seeing
each other since graduation five years ago.
- Have you been well?
- Hey, how you've been?
- You look the same as ever.
- I heard your baby's grown a lot.
He's already in the army.
[Exponential growth in five years?]
You all wrote a letter to
your future selves, didn't you?
- Yes, we did.
- I remember mailing the key.
Make sure to find your own key...
because you all have your own room that
has been prepared especially
for you for the five year reunion.
You'll find a note inside
each of your envelopes.
[A secret note inside the envelopes?]
- This is your future selves?
- Really? Just put them in here?
[Opening up the mailbox.]
This is mine.
- Kim Jong Kook.
- I can feel a letter in here.
- I do see a letter in mine too.
- You have to go read it in your room.
We can't show it to each other.
Please go to your own chamber of fate.
[Everyone off to their own chamber of fate.]
[What kind of events are awaiting these
friends after five years?]
[Class leader of five years ago, Kwang Soo
finds his Pioneer Room.]
[Items that are befitting of a leader
are found on the table.]
When I think about myself back then...
I don't know what was wrong with me.
Wait, this is...
This is what we hid away
five years ago.
[Different items are found in
each of their own secret rooms.]
Should I see what the letter inside says?
[What information do the letters contain?]
Even though you may not knowing it,
there's a fated couple amongst you
that's been predestined to be together.
Amongst you is a fateful couple
who's been destined to be together.
[Must find their fateful mate
whom they lost five years ago.]
Is there a clue as to who
the couple is?
Go find the person whom you think could be
your fate with one of these items in hand
and ask the magic mirror
the question.
Must get the correct pairing of the items
to know if you're the fated couple or not.
Each of these items you see has
a matching mate to it.
You'll be using your items to
find your potential fated mate.
Then do we carry
all these items around with us?
No, you can carry out
only one item at a time with you.
[Only one item at a time
may be carried out of the room!]
[The key is to meet up with as many people
as possible with a variety of items in hand.]
Where's the magical mirror?
You're going to have to find that
for yourself somewhere inside this building.
[Find out if you're a part of the fated couple
by standing in front of the magical mirror!]
This is going to have me running around
all over the place.
Ha Dong Hoon, where are you?
Suzy! Ji Hyo!
- Suzy!
- Wait right there, because I'm coming down.
- Hey, wait.
- Ji Hyo.
Stay right there, Ha Dong Hoon.
- Why are you looking for Ha Dong Hoon?
- What about it?
- What are you doing?
- What?
Which one is your room?
- Me? I'm in the Young Lady's Room.
- Young Lady's Room?
- Hey!
- Young Lady and Flower Boy goes together.
- You're the Flower Boy Room?
- That's right.
Why are you looking for Ha Dong Hoon?
It's because I have something
to discuss with Ha Dong Hoon.
[Could the Monday Couple be the fated couple
just like Gary wishes for them to be?]
- Hello.
- Suzy!
- Have you been well?
- Yeah, I have.
You're a young lady... and doesn't
a young lady and model student...
- Couldn't that be a link?
- You can't look at it like that.
- Couldn't it work that way?
- She'd be more fitting to go with a leader.
Romance usually take place more often
between a young lady and the model student.
- How can you think otherwise?
- But I'm Young Lady Number Two.
- Ah, you're number two?
- Yes, I'm number two.
Suzy is telling you that she doesn't
want to be involved with you.
Is Young Lady Two more
the playful type?
What do you mean,
is she more the playful type?
How can you say something so rude just
because she doesn't want to get involved?
[Who could she be fated to be with?]
- I brought the one thing that I'm sure of.
- What's that?
- Let's find the mirror room first.
- Okay.
It can only be activated when
two people are standing in front of it.
- Yeah, that's what I heard.
- What was it? The magical mirror?
- Yeah, the magical mirror.
- But where are we going to find it?
[Where in this vast space is
the magical mirror hidden away at?]
It's a little scary in here.
[Wait...]
[Places like that always...]
It's scary in here.
What is this?
Ha Ha! Ha Ha... Ha Ha!
- Ha Ha! Ha Ha... Ha Ha!
- What is it?
[Could this be the magical mirror?]
- I found it!
- Where is it?
- It's right there.
- How did you find it?
I came in here to check since you said
you were too scared to check it yourself.
I didn't see that even when
I peeked in here?
[The magical mirror... ]
[has finally been discovered.]
[Mirror, Mirror...
Are we the fated couple?]
[Ha Ha with a colored pencil,
and Ji Hyo with chocolate in her hand.]
Mirror, Mirror...
Are we the fated couple?
[Mirror, Mirror...
Are we the fated couple?]
- I guess we're not.
- These must not be the right items.
[Is it the items that are not matching,
or the people that are not matching?]
It wouldn't be Running Man if
it was this easy to find.
[On the other hand...]
[Kwang Soo and Jong Kook discover
another magical mirror!]
[But... wait...]
The mirror is cracked!
[Cracked mirrors cannot be activated.]
I'll put it back together.
I'll put the mirror back together!
There's a mirror.
But this one is cracked too.
[Cracked mirrors found all over
the place.]
I guess not all the mirrors work.
Did you bring that?
[Game Room Manager Jae Suk and
Last Place Ha Ha fighting over Suzy.]
You're seriously so pretty.
You're almost too scary.
It startled me to have such a
pretty face staring over at me.
Why are you so pretty?
- You're unbelievably pretty.
- Are you with Suzy again?
- What are you doing?
- Aren't you going to film this thing?
- We're filming right now.
- We've been filming this whole time.
- Have you found any mirrors?
- We found one upstairs.
My fated mate is either you or Jae Suk.
- It's you and me.
- He's been looking for Jong Kook.
I'm positive that it's you and me.
Want to go up and check?
- No, it's me.
- What?
- Don't go off with Jong Kook.
- Why does everyone think that it's me?
I'm from the Leader's Room.
Look at the spanking stick that you have.
- This is driving me crazy.
- I'm from the Leader's Room.
- You're from the Young Lady's Room?
- Yes.
Doesn't the young lady and
model student usually fit?
I thought you and Ha Ha went off together
earlier, so what happened to that?
- You think?
- We didn't work out.
It could be you and I then.
- What is it?
- Come with me.
- You're talking to Ha Ha?
- I think it's you and me.
- Why?
- Excuse me?
- Why are you going for his stick so suddenly?
- It's a little strange.
- She's acting very strange today.
- What are you up to?
- Which room did you say you were, Kwang Soo?
- I'm from the Leader's Room.
- Come here.
- Why?
- Why? Which room are you from?
- A leader...
[A whistle?]
[Suzy showing a strong reaction after
having seen the whistle.]
- Wait...
- Want to go to the mirror with me?
Are you going to ask that of
every single one of us?
- You have to just pick one of us.
- Don't you think that you're too aggressive?
- Go and see, Jae Suk.
- Hurry up and go.
[Why not do something about it
instead of just chattering on about it?]
- Do you want to come with me?
- Okay, let's go.
- Want to go try?
- Want to go?
Who?
Me?
- Are you asking me?
- Want to go?
Okay, then. Let's go.
You're going off with Suzy just because
she asked when you've already asked me to go?
- Suzy wants me to come with her.
- Just what am I to you?
- Let me just go with her first.
- You were supposed to go with me first.
What are you talking about?
I never told you that I'd go.
Just what do we mean to you?
You're just a Giraffe,
and you're just Haroro to me.
Let's go, Suzy.
That Grasshopper!
[Envious...]
- My item is a recorder.
- Really?
With your whistle...
isn't it a perfect match?
Everyone's going crazy over this.
- Isn't that it?
- That's it.
[Discovers an uncracked magical mirror!]
- This one isn't cracked.
- How are we supposed to do this?
We both have to stand in front of it,
and recite this chant.
Okay.
Set, go.
Mirror, Mirror...
Are we the fated couple?
[Mirror, Mirror...
Are we the fated couple?]
[Game Room Manager and the Young Lady...
Could they be the fateful couple?]
[You two are...]
- What is that? What does it mean?
- Are we the couple?
[not the fated couple.]
But just because we're not the couple...
why is the message written in blood?
It's really creepy.
[If four people or more including yourself
gathers together, someone will die.]
- Then that means...
- More than three people can't be together?
Then doesn't it mean if one more person joins
us, then one of us will die?
[Will accept only one question,
and the answer will either be a 'Yes' or 'No']
Then you ask your question first, Suzy.
We can only ask one question.
[Only one question can be asked.]
In that case...
Then does it mean if one more person comes,
then one of us here will die?
- Out?
- What?
[Jae Suk and Suzy are not
the ones it speaks of.]
- Then we don't have to worry about it.
- This is power for you and I.
Then who should we start with?
[If used wisely, someone can get ousted!]
[If three or more people including yourself
gathers around together, someone will die.]
If three or more people including yourself
gathers around together, someone will die.
Then something must have been triggered
by the magical mirror just now.
If three or more people including yourself
gathers around together, someone will die.
Someone will die?
[If three or more people including yourself
gathers around together, someone will die.]
Then we have to scatter ourselves.
This must have something to do
with the mirror.
[Is this the secret of the prophecy?]
If three or more people gets together,
then someone will be ousted?
Wow... that means even though
we don't know who it is
that's going to happen to one of us,
and even though I don't know what mine is...
there's something that's going to
get me ousted too.
- This is something really new.
- Today's concept is really new, isn't it?
[Scary, yet intriguing.]
This means that Suk Jin, you or I
also have a chance of winning this.
- Because it's not a name tag elimination.
- Hey, Kwang Soo!
- Run away!
[Escaping since it could be one of them that
dies when three or more gathers together.]
Hey!
- Hey, you dummies!
- Don't come any closer!
- Hey, listen to me.
- No!
It's not just me, but someone else can join
you and one of us three can be ousted.
Kwang Soo.
You can stay behind and talk to me.
There would only be the two of us.
Come on!
What if you're trying to take me with you
to see someone else?
Come on.
Hurry up, we don't have much time.
- Hurry up and come on.
- You acting like this means something is up.
No, I'm not trying to do anything.
The important thing right now is,
we have to go find a mirror.
I'm going to tell you something.
Suzy and I saw something in the mirror.
We saw this mission on the mirror.
If three or more people including yourself
gathers around together, someone will die.
And you can look in the mirror
and ask one question.
What was the question that you asked?
[One question can be asked of the mirror.]
I asked if either
Suzy or myself will be ousted.
And we were told 'no'.
Other than Suzy or myself,
it could be you, Ha Ha or Suk Jin.
If three or more people gets together,
one of you will get ousted.
[Then it means that you're safe?]
Do you still not trust me?
[I wish I could run away.]
Get away from me!
Please stop!
[Kwang Soo's screams are
suddenly heard?]
[Giraffe trying to run away
from Jae Suk!]
Get away from me!
Please stop!
[Giraffe afraid that if three or more people
gathers together, it'll be himself that dies.]
- Kwang Soo.
- I want to live!
Kwang Soo,
I'm not trying to oust you.
- You have to trust me.
- You're lying!
If I let you go right now...
I'm positive that you're going to go
somewhere else and try to come after me.
[No intention of letting the Giraffe go.]
I'll show you that I'm serious.
Just trust me on this.
[Everyone avoiding the situation of
more than three people gathering together.]
Run!
Have you seen Jong Kook?
[I don't want to die!]
[Suzy feeling at ease knowing that
she's excluded from the curse.]
Why are they running away
from me like that?
Hey, don't come any closer.
Get away from me!
[Telling each other to get away
as soon as they see each other.]
[Giraffe having made his escape
is heading this way.]
Jae Suk is headed this way.
[As soon as they make their way down...
Suzy meets up with them from below.]
[Model student and the Last place person
walking around in search of the mirror.]
- Is something in there?
- Is that one?
There it is.
[Found one!]
Okay, let's say it.
[Report card and a whipping stick-
What will be the mirror's answer?]
- I love you.
- I love you too.
- My brother.
- One, two, three.
Mirror, mirror...
Are we the fated couple?
[Mirror, mirror...
Are we the fated couple?]
[You two are...]
We are?
Why does the writing look so scary?
[not the fated couple.]
It's telling us that we're not.
- We're not, but there's something to this.
- We're not the couple.
But the writing was so scary.
Someone...
[Someone... will die if they turn around
and look behind them.]
Someone will die if they turn around
and look behind them.
[Rigid]
Someone will die if they turn around
and look behind them?
[I will accept only one question.]
[But the answer...]
[will be answered either a
'Yes' or a 'No'.]
We have to be careful with
what we ask.
Then let's ask if it's one of us since
the important thing is for us to survive.
Is that one person... one of us?
Is it one of us?
Either Kim Jong Kook or Ha Ha?
- It's a 'No'!
- We're all set!
- We're safe.
- We're not going to die from this.
Okay, Jong Kook.
Let's talk this out right now.
We have to figure this out.
One of us will die if three or more
people gathers together.
And there's another member who'll die if
that person turns around to look behind them.
That's the knowledge we gained by asking
the magical mirror our question.
But even if we look behind us...
we won't die.
- We won't die.
- We have to make others look behind them.
- That's right.
[Very excited about the prospect of
ousting the other members.]
But it could also mean that if someone walks
in here right now, one of us could die.
- We have to stop others from joining us.
- We could be the one to die from that.
[Sound of thunder suddenly being
heard off in the distance.]
Someone will die if they turn around
and look behind them.
Will die if they turn around to
look behind them?
[Someone will die if they turn around
and look behind them.]
What is this all about now?
Why are you seriously doing this?
You're not allowing us to
be able to do anything.
We can't get together or look behind us.
What are we supposed to do here?
[Making them more and more nervous
with each passing moment.]
But it may be referring to me.
It may not be me.
I'm too scared to keep doing
Running Man.
I'm so scared right now.
Give me back my leg.
(A famous line from an old horror legend.)
Running Man is too scary.
Is this a horror special?
We can walk around like this.
[Two middle aged men walking around
supporting each other.]
- Let's walk backwards.
- There's no need for us to do that.
- We can just go this way.
- Is it okay to walk like that?
- We can go this way.
- No, we can't.
[What are they doing?]
We'll be fine as long as
we don't look behind us.
- We just don't have to look behind us?
- We won't die if we go forward.
[Unable to comprehend.]
We can go this way and keep going
forward without looking behind us.
- Oh, so we can do it that way?
- What are you thinking?
[Making things even more difficult
with his lack of understanding.]
- You and Suzy are a team, aren't you?
- No, we're not.
- Tell me the truth.
- No, Suk Jin. I'm telling you the truth.
- Don't come this way!
[More than three is dangerous!
Everyone cautious of each other.]
- Running into Suzy like this is scary.
- Suzy, are you behind me?
Yes, I'm right behind you.
Don't turn around.
No, I'm not looking.
- There's nowhere for us to turn.
- Seriously.
- Do we have to make a P-turn?
- It's called a U-turn.
Let's make a U-turn over here.
[A necessary U-turn to go back
in the direction where they came from.]
[Behaving just like a car would.]
Why did they come up with
a rule like this?
Which one are you, Ji Hyo?
- What do you have, Suzy?
- Me?
I have a hairpin.
- I have a headband on.
- Seriously?
- This one up here.
- I have mine on too.
- Maybe we're the couple.
- Do you know where a mirror is?
- The mirror...
- Where could a mirror be?
- Let's look around here.
- Hurry up and get out of here!
Don't come this way!
We'll be fine as long as he stays away.
He's just so loud.
Hey, don't look!
Don't look behind you!
I'm walking behind you
so don't come any closer either.
- Go up to the fifth floor, Gary!
- Don't come this way!
- Don't come! No one come this way.
[Everyone in a state of chaos to ensure
that no more than three are gathered around.]
Just hurry up and go somewhere.
I want you to get away.
[What is that?]
[DIY neck brace.]
Let's go.
Please let it be us.
[The Easy Brothers-
Could they be the fateful couple?]
There it is!
This way, Suk Jin.
This is where I saw Jae Suk earlier.
It's still here!
[Working in sync together to
find the magical mirror.]
- I have 'Basic Instinct' movie.
- And I have 'Sunday Seoul'.
If this isn't a pair,
then what else could it be?
One, two, three. Mirror, mirror...
Are we the fated couple?
[Mirror, mirror...
Are we the fated couple?]
[The two of you are...]
- The two of you are...
[not the fated couple.]
[Disappointed...]
How can we not be?
Someone...
[Someone will die if they
scream out loud.]
Someone will die if they
scream out loud?
[Someone will die if they
scream out loud?]
[You may ask one question.]
- What do you want to ask?
- What should we ask?
Is that someone,
one of us standing here?
[Could the person who dies from screaming
be one of them standing there?]
Someone will die if they
scream out loud.
[Someone will die if they scream out loud.]
Someone will die if they
scream out loud.
scream out loud?
Someone will die if they
Then who was it that just screamed?
Wasn't that Kwang Soo's voice?
Doesn't this make you feel like something
scary is waiting for us today?
[The mood is turning scarier
with each passing moment.]
Someone will die if they turn around
to look behind them.
We have to walk around either alone,
or in pairs...
and now we can't scream out
loud either.
[They thought this was going to be a romance
with the game being called,' Fateful Couple'.]
[But this is just sheer terror.]
- Don't you think that this is really scary?
- Can you just eliminate me right now?
I think that jail will be the least
scariest place.
This is no joke right now.
What's even scarier is that I have yet to hear
the announcement of Suk Jin getting ousted.
I feel like something isn't quite right.
Jae Suk, let's try to figure this out.
[Getting back up to
look for the magical mirror.]
- Jae Suk.
- Yeah?
You keep trying to get me
to turn around.
You never know.
[Something is definitely up today...]
[Easy Brothers staying resilient
in their search for the mirror.]
Look at that.
I think Jae Suk tried this one.
It's still good.
If these two aren't a match,
then I don't know what is. One, two, three.
Mirror, mirror...
Are we the fated couple?
[No, you're not.]
No, you're not.
It's wrong again.
- Suk Jin, something else is coming up.
- There's another message?
[Someone will die if they
become uglier.]
- Someone will die if they become uglier?
- Poor Gary!
[You have no room to worry about others.]
- What are you going to do, Kwang Soo?
- What does this mean?
What kind of a prophecy is that?
Someone will die if they become uglier?
- You may ask one question.
- I really don't want this to be me.
- Anything else, but not this one.
- If it says yes, then it's you.
What are you talking about?
Is it... one of us two?
- It's a 'No'!
- Yes.
[Another roaring sound of thunder.]
Someone will die if they become uglier.
- Someone will die if they become uglier.
- Say what?
You're the only one that it applies to.
You always look so much uglier
when you take your glasses off.
You have to admit that it's true.
Could it be me?
Why don't you try taking off
your glasses?
Come on, just try it.
I doubt it'll make you that much uglier.
Just try it and take them off.
[Trying to ease away...]
[But there's no way that Jong Kook
will let him go.]
- There's no way.
- Just try it.
- No, then look behind you.
- I doubt that it means you.
- Then look behind you.
- It doesn't matter to me.
- What did you say?
- Turn around and look behind you.
- Try taking off your glasses.
- Turn around and then I'll take them off.
Turn around and look behind you.
Is it me?
I think I'm going to die.
No, I don't think that's what it means.
I think you have to make an ugly face.
Don't you think it means something
like that?
[I'm supposed to be the
flower boy today...]
- Ji Hyo.
- Hey.
[Practicing not turning around.]
Ji Hyo.
- Where are you?
Suzy.
No, don't come any closer.
Hey, don't come any closer.
Don't come!
[Oh no! The three of them
are gathered together!]
- Let's go.
- Suk Jin, let's go.
- Suzy...
- Suzy, why are you being so bold?
You won't die even if three people
gather together, will you?
- What?
- You and Jae Suk asked the question, right?
[Jae Suk and Suzy won't die even if
three or more people gather together.]
- Wait a second.
- I don't think it's either one of you.
[But all of them are still safe even though
there are three of them together?]
[We already knew that about Suzy.]
[Nothing's happening to either Suk Jin or
Kwang Soo even though they're all together.]
- Doesn't this mean that it's not us?
- What's going on here?
- Even when we're together like this?
- I don't think it's either one of you.
- Have you looked behind you yet?
- No.
- Let's go in the room.
- I may die if I looked behind me.
[The three of them going in the room to
test out their theory.]
- You look so natural walking around.
- Shut the door.
- This is really crazy.
- No, it's not one of you.
- Can one of you look behind you?
- One, two, three.
- It must not be us.
- If it's not you two...
[Still safe even though they're all
standing in the same room together.]
[Someone will die if three or more are
together, but the Easy Brothers are safe!]
Hang on.
Wait... it's not Jae Suk
or you two...
Then it's either Ha Ha, Gary, Jong Kook
or Ji Hyo.
[The person who'll die in the presence of
three or more are the other four.]
You really want to oust Jong Kook
right now, don't you?
I think it's him.
He's going around avoiding
everyone else right now.
I'm the only one that
he's not avoiding right now.
I think I'm the only one
who'll be able to do it.
[Jong Kook, want to take your pencil and come
to the mirror room with me? - Suzy.]
[Jong Kook discovers Suzy's
note for him.]
Are you by yourself?
[Suzy and Jong Kook meeting up
with a diary and a pencil in hand.]
[Suzy succeeds in luring Jong Kook in.]
[Suzy luring him into the mirror room.]
[Shutting the door tight for now.]
[Getting ready to recite the chant
in front of the mirror.]
[Now is the time!]
[Giraffe enters the room!]
What are you doing?
[Tiger senses sudden danger!]
What's going on here?
Suzy, did you lure me in here?
No, not at all.
Did you lure me in here?
[Time to counterattack!
Jong Kook making Kwang Soo's face uglier.]
I don't think it's you.
It must be Ha Ha.
[Jong Kook, Suzy, and Kwang Soo-
Thought that Jong Kook would get ousted.]
Then why don't you come in here?
[Suk Jin also enters to make it a group
of four just to make sure.]
[Just then]
What's that?
What is that?
- Something's happening, isn't it?
- Yes.
[If three or more including yourself is
gathered together, then someone will die.]
What's that?
I told you not to gather around
three people or more.
[I told you not to gather around
three people or more.]
[The grim reapers are
taking him away?]
[The one cursed with that prophecy,
Kim Jong Kook is out!]
I told you not to gather around
three people or more.
[I told you not to gather around
three people or more.]
Someone must've gotten in a
group of three or more.
- It means someone was in a group, right?
- Someone's just been ousted.
[I told you not to gather around
three people or more.]
This is scary.
Why does it have to be said like that?
Suzy is the best.
[What?]
You're the first one to get ousted?
You're not it, are you?
Is the mirror still good?
- What?
- Is the mirror still good?
- I don't know.
- Check and see if it's still good.
[What?]
[What's going on with these two?]
[There's something going on
with these two!]
[A little while ago.]
- Have you found a mate yet?
- Let's try the mirror room together.
- The mirror? Us two?
- Yeah, the mirror room.
- Yeah, us too. I have a hairpin.
- What? I have a headband.
[Ji Hyo and Suzy in possession of
a hairpin and a headband.]
Do you know where the mirror is?
[And that's how the two young girls
found themselves in front of the mirror.]
Mirror, mirror...
Are we the fated couple?
[You two are...]
[the fated couple.]
[These two are the fated couple?]
[It was us all along...
We're the fated couple!]
[Go to one of your supply rooms
immediately.]
Go to one of your supply rooms
immediately.
The two of us together?
Let's go.
Let's hurry up and go.
Suzy!
It's been us all along!
[A mysterious shipping bag in
one of the girl's room?]
Running Man High School
attendance record?
Graduation pictures?
[And even a Running Man High School
yearbook picture?]
Is that a cassette player?
[Even an old cassette tape that
they used to use back in the day.]
Huh?
We're not in this picture.
We're missing from this picture.
[Why are there only male students
in the group picture?]
We're not in this picture!
[It was a group picture that
they all took together five years ago...]
- Congratulations, guys!
- Congratulations!
[Just who are these two girls?]
Even though you two were sisters
with a very close relationship...
unfortunately you became ghosts.
[Unfortunately became ghosts.]
[Ghosts?]
[Five years ago.]
Quiet.
Why are you boys so
full of chatter this morning?
Why are you boys so full of chatter?
Teacher Go, can we not run out on the field
if we don't have running shoes on?
Okay, as for the field...
[Even though Ji Hyo asked a question...
the teacher was unable to hear her.]
In the way that you're seated already,
group one is one team.
[And it's because the two girls never even
existed at the Running High School.]
Once the Running High School friends
find out that you two are ghosts...
they're going to try to
eliminate you.
You two ghost sisters... must get rid of
all the Running High's male students.
[Get rid of them...]
[Notes are written in the attendance record
to show who's been cursed with what.]
[Loves to hang around with his friends.]
That's him perfectly.
[Even though three people were
initially gathered together...]
[Suzy being a ghost didn't count
in that mix.]
[And once Jong Kook felt reassured...]
[Suk Jin was finally brought
into the room.]
[With the gathering of Jong Kook, Suk Jin,
and Kwang Soo- Jong Kook is ousted!]
[Unbelievable plan of utilizing the fact that
she wouldn't count since she's only a ghost!]
Oh my goodness... what do we do?
[Ha Ha is usually quiet and
normally doesn't have much to say.]
[Kwang Soo never pays attention to class,
and is always looking behind him.]
That's totally him.
He'll die if he's made to look ugly.
Jae Suk only worries about his looks.
[Has more interested in his looks
rather than in his studies.]
Let's come take a look at this again
whenever someone gets ousted.
[Agreeing to come and recheck the list
whenever the mirror's curse is carried out.]
[The ghost sister's clever planning.]
[I'm sorry, guys...]
[But we're going to have to
eliminate you.]
[The ghost playing ghost?]
[Whips around again.]
[The older sibling ghost is trying to
sneak up on the Giraffe.]
[What was Kwang Soo's curse again?]
Instead of concentrating in class,
he's always turning around to look behind him.
That's totally him.
[So you'll die if you look behind you.]
- It's cracked?
- Yeah.
What are you doing?
Why are you doing that?
[Still not turning around to look behind him!]
Why are you doing this, Ji Hyo?
What are you doing?
Here it is.
[Suzy brings Ha Ha over to the mirror to
find out what the other curse is?]
Mirror, mirror...
Are we the fated couple?
[No, you're not.]
[I bet it's time for another curse
to be revealed!]
[Someone will die if they get wet.]
[Yes!
That's another curse revealed!]
Someone will die if they get wet
[Someone will die if they get wet.]
[Can be very sentimental
and loves rainy days.]
Are you by any chance...
Sorry to ask, but are you
trying to get me to turn around?
No, I'm not.
If I was trying to do that,
I would've made you do it already.
Where's the mirror...
[Older sister ghost coming up
behind him again.]
[Water?]
Let's just die together!
Let's just all die together!
[Giraffe's stress level explodes!]
Who needs the mirror?
Let's all just die together!
What's going on?
[Giraffe's screams heard
throughout the building.]
- That's Kwang Soo.
- Why is he screaming?
[This is it... this is my chance!]
He'll die if he becomes ugly.
Jae Suk only cares about his looks.
[I will make you look even uglier.]
[His glasses!]
[Jae Suk barely manages to
escape danger!]
- Suzy... you seriously are no joke.
- Seriously, Suzy.
[Little sister ghost unfortunately
fails her mission.]
- You're trying to make him uglier?
- Yeah, she is.
Are either of us ousted?
With us both soaking wet,
I don't think water is what'll oust us.
Let's go.
We're back to being partners.
Give me your hand.
[But no one...]
[Suspected the two girls of being ghosts.]
- Are you going to attack me?
- No, I'm not!
[I have to be cautious
about how I attack him.]
No, I'm not.
[Ha Ha and Suzy having returned
to the mirror room.]
Mirror, mirror...
Are we the fated couple?
[Older sister ghost is also back to the mirror
to find out what the last curse is.]
- I don't think we are. It's red lettering.
- But that's what it usually looks like.
- That's what it normally looks like.
- See? We're not it.
[Okay. Hurry up and
tell me what the curse is.]
[But... go search through the lockers.]
- Search through the lockers?
[It's not a curse?
What's this?]
I know where the lockers are.
- I know where the lockers are.
- You've seen the lockers?
- Let's go and check.
- Okay, let's go.
[Older sister ghost getting nervous
at the unexpected message.]
Gary.
- Let's keep what we just found a secret.
- Okay, I got it.
There must be at least
2,000 lockers in here.
[Somewhere amongst these countless
numbers of lockers...]
[Something wrapped in secrecy
is waiting to be found.]
[Ji Hyo searching through all the lockers
with a sense of nervous energy.]
[I'm getting a bad feeling about this.
Something's in one of these lockers.]
Suzy, it would be absolutely hilarious
if this turns out to be the one.
[Haroro returning with a cushion in hand.]
[Unable to shake his desire of
wanting to be a part of the fated couple.]
See how I'm leaning up on the cushion?
- Let's try them all.
- Let's try this one first.
If nothing else,
we may earn another hint.
One, two, three.
Mirror, mirror...
Are we the fated couple?
[Truly seems to be upset.]
- I'll see you later.
- Want to bring something else, Suzy?
- Me?
- Yeah.
[Wait...]
- Okay.
There's got to be something since the mirror
keeps giving us the chance to ask.
[Little sister Suzy slowly sneaks up on Ha Ha
who'll die if he screams out loud!]
This is my giraffe.
[Muttering to himself out of nervousness.]
It's like Kwang Soo.
[This is her chance!
If he screams, then he's out!]
[He screamed out loud!]
[Someone will die if they
scream out loud.]
[Ha Ha screams out loud at her
surprise attack!]
I'm sorry.
I told you not to scream.
[I told you not to scream.]
What... what was I?
I wasn't supposed to scream?
[You are to be taken out
for having screamed out loud.]
Suzy... seriously...
you could've been my fate.
[Cursed by the scream, Ha Ha is out!]
I told you not to scream.
I wonder if Ha Ha's been ousted?
I'm so scared of that voice.
[So Suzy pulled it off?]
[I have to make Kwang Soo turn around
and look behind him.]
[Someone will die if they turn around
to look back.]
What the heck?
[Smacked in the back of the head,
and fully turning to look behind him.]
What the heck?
[So sorry!]
[Even though it was a bit unconventional,
it was a very effective way to oust him!]
I haven't looked behind me even once
for the past five hours.
But did I really look back just because
you smacked me on the back of my head?
- I hit you too hard, didn't I?
- Did I look behind me?
You turned around and
looked at me.
Wait a minute.
That's me?
Wait!
- Wait!
- Kwang Soo, I'm so sorry.
Wait a minute.
Wait!
Let me hit her just once before I go!
[One very pissed off Giraffe!]
Do you know how badly I've been wanting
to look behind me all night?
I've been waiting all this time...
and couldn't even look behind me!
- Kwang Soo, I'm so sorry.
- You have no idea all that I've done!
I even wrapped a box
around my neck!
[Whatever the case, the older sister ghost
eliminates the Giraffe with one smooth smack.]
[The two ghosts exuberant hi-five.]
So this is how scary two women
working together can be?
This is seriously...
this is amazing teamwork between us.
The only ones left right now are
Jae Suk, Gary and Suk Jin.
- We only have three more left to get rid of.
- Three more to go.
The problem is that we still don't know
what Suk Jin is yet.
- So Gary is water?
- Gary's the water.
- He's very sentimental...
- And he likes to get wet in the rain.
He really is very sentimental.
[The men that are still left alive...]
Hey, Jae Suk.
- Can we look behind now?
- It doesn't matter anymore.
- I feel so much freer.
- That's so much better.
[Turning around to look behind them
for the first time in hours.]
[And screaming out as loud
as they want.]
So what happened?
Someone got ousted from screaming,
and someone got ousted from looking back.
- Ha Ha's got ousted from screaming.
- Really? It was Ha Ha?
- Really?
- Then what else is there?
- Being made ugly.
- Ji Hyo and Suzy are still left.
- Gary and myself...
- And Suk Jin.
So there are five of us still left?
But there aren't five curses left.
Then it means there's a couple
working together.
Amongst us?
- That's right.
- A pair?
Don't you think that a pair is
working together to oust all the others?
- A pair working together to oust others?
- Two people working together.
- That's possible.
- If there's a couple...
- Are you a couple?
- There could be a couple already.
- Is it you?
- No, it's not me.
That's what you always say.
- You're acting strange.
- You always tell us that it's not you.
- And you always scratch right here.
- Why are you scratching your neck?
It's not me.
Then the only thing that's left is getting
ousted from being ugly.
[So it's essential to find out what
other curses could still be left.]
[And wait... one more thing.
The lockers!]
What is it?
It's somewhere around here.
I haven't found anything yet.
I was here with Ha Ha earlier.
Set, go.
Mirror, mirror...
Are we the fated couple?
[Mirror, mirror...
Are we the fated couple?]
[No, you're not.]
Then who are the fated couple?
[Someone... will die if both of their feet
touches the ground at the same time.]
What is this all about?
[Someone... will die if both of their feet
touches the ground at the same time?]
Someone... will die if both of their feet
touches the ground at the same time.
So he has to keep standing
around like this?
Who does?
That can only be Suk Jin.
- Then I bet he has to do that now?
- So he has to walk around like this.
Then how are we going to do this?
Someone... will die if both of their feet
touches the ground at the same time.
[Automatically lifts his foot off the ground.]
There's a chair over there.
I can get around on the chair.
Okay, I got it.
I have a feeling that it's me.
[Little sister ghost chasing after Jae Suk!]
[Seems as though she's planning on taking
his glasses off to make him uglier!]
- Suk Jin.
- What is it?
Suzy's coming.
[Suzy discovers Big-nosed Brother
standing around on only one foot.]
Suzy scares me.
I think Suzy's trying to take off
my glasses right now.
Suzy!
Hurry!
[Gary works together with Suzy
to attack Suk Jin!]
- It's not you?
- No, it's not me!
[Suk Jin is ousted once both of his feet
touches the ground at the same time!]
[Desperately trying to avoid having both
of his feet touch the ground.]
[Little sister ghost Suzy accepting
the help offered by Gary.]
[Absolute and utter chaos.]
Just a little bit more!
[Stepping on one of his feet!]
[Both of his feet...
touched the ground at the same time!]
[Both of his feet make a touchdown!]
[Someone... will die if both of their feet
touches the ground at the same time.]
I'm still okay.
- Oh, it's Suk Jin!
- It's me. That's my curse.
- Are you seriously going to do this?
- I'm sorry, Suk Jin.
We have to end this game somehow.
[The curse of two feet...
Ji Suk Jin- Out!]
[After having eliminated Suk Jin,
Gary is back to searching the lockers.]
I have to remain calm
as to not to make any mistakes.
Search through these one by one.
[Just where is the locker that
the mirror told me to find?]
I wonder if Ji Hyo's found it
already by now.
Ji Hyo and I are the only ones
who know about that hint.
[Checking through all of the lockers!]
I found it.
[Stick this on the name tag of the deceased,
and the power will be activated.]
What's this?
[Stick it on the name tag of the deceased?]
Hang on, what's this?
I'm positive the girls were there before,
but both the girls have disappeared.
[Discovers the picture
with the girls missing in it!]
I'm positive that we all took
the picture together five years ago.
What happened?
[Not found in any other pictures either...]
What the heck is this?
They're ghosts?
Are they seriously haunted spirits?
They've been ghosts this whole time?
[They've been ghosts this whole time?]
[The girls were ghosts from
the beginning...]
- Jae Suk.
- Gary!
- Hurry up and come over here.
- Why?
- I'm scared to death right now.
- I have goosebumps all over my body.
- Why?
I found a hint earlier.
I was told to search the lockers,
and that's what I've been doing.
Remember how we were all there for
the group picture five years ago?
- Yeah, so?
- But the two are missing.
Then they're ghosts?
I'm so scared.
Look at all of my goosebumps.
- Those two are ghosts?
- Yes!
- Jae Suk...
- What's this?
- That's a different class.
- Oh, it's a different class?
That startled me.
- I noticed that Sa Yeon's our classmate too.
- You're right.
- Jin Young's in there too.
- Yeah, and Min Soo's our classmate too.
I think we can use casual speech with him
the next time we see him now.
- But this sticker...
- I have this too.
- You have one too?
- Ha Ha gave it to me.
[Ha Ha had one of the stickers?]
[Ha Ha having gone to the mirror room
along with Jae Suk.]
[No, you're not.]
Is there another message?
[But search through all of
the potted plants.]
[From one of the potted plants...
Ha Ha finds the sticker!]
[The exact same sticker that Gary
found in one of the lockers!]
What is this?
[Stick it on the name tag of the deceased,
and its powers will be activated.]
You got ousted from having screamed out loud?
What's this?
[Ha Ha hands his sticker off to Jae Suk!]
I think we're supposed to put these
stickers on the ghosts.
[Are they amulets that can stop the
ghosts if they're stuck on them?]
- Just like those Gangsi movies...
- So that's why we need two.
So then one of us is the ugly curse
while the other is the water curse?
- Let's go, Gary.
- Hang on. I'm so creeped out right now.
[Creeped out at the knowledge about
having been around ghosts all day.]
- This isn't going to be easy.
- Where are we supposed to stick this?
[Ghosts are going to know what's going on
as soon as they see the amulet.]
So they're ghosts?
- Hey, Suzy.
- Suzy!
- What are you doing up there?
- I'm just thirsty.
[A cup of water in her hand
that could kill Gary!]
- Where's Ji Hyo?
- Excuse me?
- Ji Hyo?
- Should I come down there?
- Okay.
- Should we go up there?
- We'll come up there.
- We'll come up.
- Okay.
We have to get it on the first try.
[Only one chance!
Each take one ghost to get rid of!]
Let's hope that we can
do it in one try.
Let's please end this in one try.
The more we drag it out...
Where did Suzy go?
Where's Ji Hyo?
[Suzy's going into some room?]
[Too afraid to get too close.]
[Even more terrifying because they
don't see the older sister ghost.]
- Do you want some water, Gary?
- Okay.
Here's some water.
- I've been drinking out of this cup though.
- It's okay.
- Why do you keep trying to give me the water?
- I just thought that you might be thirsty.
Rinse it off once before giving it to me.
[Something definitely is going on!]
Is someone back there?
[Of course... there is!]
[He avoided it?]
I didn't get any on me!
[This is my chance!]
[But... Suzy dumps her water on Gary!]
[Someone will die if they get wet.]
[Suzy dumps her cup of water on Gary!]
[Jae Suk attacks older sister ghost
with the amulet in hand!]
I have to stick this on you!
[The glasses!]
[No! That makes me ugly!]
[Someone will die if
they're made to look ugly.]
[He looks ugly...]
He looks ugly!
[Water cursed Gary is ousted
from having gotten wet.]
[Jae Suk is ousted from having been
cursed with the ugliness.]
I didn't know I was supposed to
stick this on her name tag.
Suzy, we won!
- Are you ousted too?
- My destiny!
I got doused with water.
[Ghost sisters Ji Hyo and Suzy succeed in
eliminating all of the members of Running Man.]
[The eerie story
that started five years ago...]
[The ghost sisters leave their side...]
[And who knows?
They could be next to you right now.]
Subtitles by DramaFever
[A mysterious UFO sighting in Korea!]
[A UFO touches down on earth!]
[Making their appearance
from their spaceship...]
[The four aliens overflowing with
their unique individuality!]
[Alien 2NE1]
[What's the reason for them
coming to earth?]
[Obtain water from earth and bring it back
to their planet with its short water supply.]
[Will they get their water,
or will they fall in the water?]
[The battle between
the aliens becoming fierce!]
[Youngest alien, Gong Min Ji...
about to be certified for being a bull?]
[Only those aliens that knows how
to party can obtain the water.]
[Treasuring every drop of water!]
[Who will be the one to obtain
the precious water to return a hero?]
[Next week's Running Man-
Aliens invade the earth.]