[SBS Office in Mokdong]
[One man walking into the building alone.]
[Handsome looking?]
[He's none other than... Jung Woo Sung.]
This is going to be fun.
[This is going to be fun, you say?]
Where is it?
[108 CCTV cameras.]
[He has his eyes on you.]
[The uncontrollable chase]
Come here!
[Running Man vs. The Grim Reaper,
Jung Woo Sung]
[S Marina in Yeouido]
[Summer is here!]
- This is great weather!
- It really is summer now.
It's the season for sunglasses.
[The season for sunglasses.]
I have some exciting guests
here for you today.
- It's female guests.
- At last!
- It's about time for some female guests.
Look!
A limousine is pulling up!
Remember Choi Ji Woo showed up
in a limousine last year?
- Do we need to get red carpet for them?
- Are we having a lot of guests on today?
- What is that?
- Isn't that big enough for twenty people?
- Where's the door?
- You two need to move back a little.
- Come back here.
- I'm getting ready to greet our guests.
[Just who are the guests
waiting in that limo?]
Is it a girl group?
The door's opening!
[Beastly Idol Group 2PM's Junho!]
It's Junho!
[And also...]
[It's the beautiful, Han Hyo Joo!]
- It's Hyo Joo!
- How beautiful!
How beautiful!
[The return of leg tripping goddess.]
[The beautiful Han Hyo Joo-
She has returned.]
- How beautiful!
How beautiful!
[Ro-Ro running out to her as soon as
he sees who it is.]
[Leg tripping her as soon as
he sees her?]
[She flips him instead?]
[You're not going to get me this time!]
- How beautiful! So beautiful!
- She's changed.
It's the return of a female guest who received
the coldest reception in Running Man history!
[Return of Han Hyo Joo, who has endured
rough treatment from the RM members.]
She was already ready for my attack
when I went to trip her over!
She withstood your leg trip maneuver.
Hyo Joo and Junho are our
guests for today?
They are here as our guests
for the day.
Especially since Han Hyo Joo was treated
so roughly the last time she was here...
- This past winter...
- With all the leg tripping.
She suffered a lot this past winter
when she was guesting on the show.
That's why we gave her the special
limousine service today.
Thank you.
- It's okay, but no more special treatment.
- You really are so beautiful.
It's time for Hyo Joo to get
dunked in the water now.
How do you feel about your second appearance?
Will you be okay with rough treatment again?
Yes, it's okay.
You can be as rough with me as you want.
Your skin is way too white.
Your skin needs to be burnt a little.
- She is very white, isn't she?
- Her skin is the color of opal.
Ugh, it's so hot!
There she is!
- There she is!
- And she's back.
It's back.
Her real personality is starting to surface.
- It's coming back.
- And we didn't even ask for it.
- Ugh, it's hot!
- Ugh, it's hot.
Okay, I will explain today's
mission to you.
Today's mission is...
It's the second round...
of the Survival Race.
[Second Round of the Survival Race.]
You will be voting for one person whom you'd
like to eliminate at the end of each game.
The person who receives the most
votes will be the one to get eliminated.
[Person to receive the most number of votes
gets eliminated immediately.]
The person that is eliminated cannot
participate in the games any longer.
Then what about Hyo Joo?
- What if Hyo Joo gets the most votes?
- She'll be treated the same, I'm sure.
- She won't have any options.
- She'll be treated like everyone else?
- Since when have you been so caring?
- What are you talking about?
Why are you acting like you're
such a caring person all of a sudden?
[Is he trying to start winning
points from Hyo Joo already?]
Let's get rid of him first!
- But Hyo Joo is...
- Let's get Yoo Jae Suk first!
I was just making sure that Hyo Joo
isn't excluded from the rules.
- Then you just get to go home?
- That could be the case if you're eliminated.
First through third place winners at each game
will be excluded from the elimination round.
They will be excluded from
the chances of being eliminated.
So I need to get in the top three
no matter what?
Yes, the top three in each of the games
will be safe from the elimination round.
[Second Round of the Survival Race- Start.]
Everyone can board the limousine to
move on to your next destination.
We can all ride in it together?
[Everyone into the limo!]
[Everyone starts on their way
with their matching summer outfits.]
[Everyone gets a chance to ride in
the limousine all thanks to Hyo Joo.]
- Mister...
- What?
You should let the lady get in first!
Don't you have any manners?
- Hurry up and get in.
- Seriously!
- This is so nice.
- Haven't you ever been in a limo before?
- Kwang Soo...
- Come sit back here.
Since the limo is long,
you can stretch out your neck that way.
Get in.
You just ride it like you would a subway.
What are you guys doing?
Are you taking a class picture?
- Why? What's wrong with it?
- Why don't one of you come back here?
I'm assuming you've never
ridden in a limo before?
- Have you?
- Have you ridden in one before?
[Anyways, off they go!]
- Driving sideways is making me feel carsick.
- How can you be carsick?
- The subway goes sideways too.
- We just got on the road.
- You're so sensitive to everything.
- Seriously though...
Hyo Joo and Ji Hyo...
Let's say that a boyfriend of yours
shows up at your house in a limo like this.
I'd absolutely hate that.
- I really would hate that.
- What about you, Hyo Joo?
I'd just walk past it and
pretend that I didn't even see him.
She's just going to walk past it.
And what if the guy started singing and
inserted Hyo Joo and Ji Hyo's name in it?
- What if the guy sang like that?
- Ugh, I'd really hate that.
Hyo Joo is going into convulsions.
[The Running Man members still
unaware of Woo Sung's presence.]
[Just what is he waiting for?]
[Arriving in Seochon,
where the history of Seoul breathes on.]
[The first mission-
Seochon, first come first serve game.]
First through ninth place will be determined
by playing this game all over the city.
And at the end of the game,
you will vote for the person to be eliminated.
[A tranquil city of Seochon,
where the history of Seoul breathes on.]
Go to the street where the traditional Korean
homes are and find the 'R' flag there. Go!
Hurry up, Junho.
- Where is it? Where do we go?
- Wait!
Wait!
- It's that way.
- That way?
Han Hyo Joo!
Stop right there!
She's so fast!
- Why is she so fast?
- How is she that fast?
Where is it?
[Beautiful Hyo Joo too focused on running,
and runs past the flag?]
We found the flag!
['R1'mission- In the order of their arrival.]
You're going to play
the 'Cola and Cider Game.'
If the cap you throw even grazes the line,
then you succeed this mission.
If the cap lands anywhere on the white line or
in the gap in between, you pass the mission.
- Wow.
- Is that even possible?
Of course, it is.
- Should we start?
- Hyo Joo can start.
This is so hard!
- That's right, Hyo Joo. Talk like that.
- It's so hard!
[There she is.
Screaming Hyo Joo is back.]
- Beautiful, Hyo Joo. Beautiful!
- It's so hard!
- She might get it. She might get it.
- Did she get it?
[Oh?]
[Ah... so close!]
[So close, yet fails the mission.]
It's so hard!
- Nice.
- Hyo Joo almost had it.
But I can see the possibilities.
[Backspin?]
I can't believe that it flipped backwards.
- Who slapped me on the butt? Who was it?
- I don't know.
It was Hyo Joo.
- No, it wasn't me.
- Use the wall, right?
[What?
Big-nosed Brother succeeds!]
- I succeeded!
- How did that happen?
It must've been pure luck.
- You can't just be wearing your underwear.
- These aren't my underwear.
[His shorts looking like underwear on him
with his extra-long legs.]
- How can you think they're underwear?
- Those aren't your panties?
How can you think that
they're panties?
- They're not panties?
- I took care choosing my outfit today.
Really?
I thought they were your panties.
I think the wall helps out.
Maybe I should utilize that.
[Moving over to the wall?]
What are you doing?
What do you think you're doing?
[What is he doing by the wall?]
I'm just trying to use different
methods to get it done.
Good luck with that.
It worked!
It actually worked!
[It worked?]
- It worked!
- Wow!
[Success...]
That's so annoying!
[You saw that, right?]
That is seriously so annoying.
[Unbelievable...]
- You can all do it that way then.
- You can't look where you're throwing it.
Move back even further.
That's how you do it.
- Is he imitating you?
- Yeah, that's the way you do it.
Watch him.
That's the way you have to do it.
- Wow! It worked!
- See?
[A nice try?
Very close to the line.]
You have to try out different methods.
- I got it now.
- There you go. You can't look at it.
[Hyo Joo also assumes the
peeper's position.]
Don't think anything of it,
and just throw it out there.
- It worked! Wow!
- I can't believe it!
What the heck!
What is it doing all the way back here?
- He's trying something different.
- That's a good plan.
[The street full of traditional Korean homes
being witness to all sorts of positions.]
- Look at how long his arm is.
- Look at his long legs.
- Look... look at this.
- Come on!
Did you see it?
You saw it, didn't you?
Why did you grab me by that?
- I hate things like that.
- You had number one written on your butt.
He seriously doesn't have any butt.
Miss Blank!
Wow, she got it!
[Wow!]
[That's our Blank Ji!
Success!]
She's really good at things like this.
Song Ji Hyo's always good,
but Lee Kwang Soo is always bad.
- Dong Hoon. It's Dong Hoon's turn.
- So annoying!
[What?
Ro-Ro also succeeds.]
[Succeeds from having thrown it
without thinking.]
- I wonder if I need to hit the wall.
- You have to not think about it.
- I didn't even think about it.
- Really?
- Don't think too much about it.
- Just throw it.
There you go!
[Hyo Joo also succeeds!]
- That's the way to do it.
- We have to move the game along.
- Just throw it.
- Don't think about it when you throw.
- Hurry up and throw it.
- Don't think about where you're throwing it.
[Wow!
Success!]
Hurry.
[Wow- Gary succeeds!]
[The Tiger and the Giraffe are
the only ones left now...]
Will it be the Giraffe or the Tiger?
[The ultimate face-off.
Will it be the Giraffe or the Tiger?]
For some reason...
I've got some dirty rotten luck.
What dirty rotten luck?
Will it be the Tiger or the Giraffe?
[Preparing the popular peeping tom method.]
- What is he doing?
- The Giraffe is taking his turn.
- There you go.
- Will it be the Giraffe?
[Not even a chance- Fail...]
I think that's the better way to do it.
[Oh?]
[So very close, yet fails!]
I don't know how many times
I've done this already!
[The win is still anyone's game.]
Just throw it.
There you go!
[Kwang Soo fails.]
[Oh...]
[Success!]
[Jong Kook survives.]
['R1'- Giraffe is eliminated...]
- The Tiger won!
- It suits you!
- The Tiger won.
- How does this always happen?
- Kwang Soo lost... Kwang Soo lost!
- Yes, Kwang Soo lost.
[Elimination really does suit this man.]
So he's going to be alone now?
- It's not like this is his first time.
- Where are you taking me?
[Kwang Soo is eliminated... for now.]
[However...]
[Do not fear being eliminated.]
[You will soon find out the
reason behind it.]
- The next location is...
- Yes?
[Ji Hyo gets eliminated at 'R2'
inside the bakery.]
- Start.
- Start!
[Heading over to 'R3' located in
the heart of the local street market.]
[Off to 'R3'!]
- Run! Run!
- Go! Go!
[Merchant Go Dong Wan awaits
their arrival at 'R3'.]
Pick one and you have to find the person
that is written on the slip of paper.
[Launching immediately into the mission
as they chooses their slip of paper?]
- With the camera?
- Find a couple on their first date?
[Jae Suk: Find someone carrying a camera.
Jong Kook: Find a foreigner.]
[Junho: Find a lady wearing a sun visor.]
[Ha Ha: Find a woman with a
bellyband around her waist.]
[Hyo Joo: Finish a whole order of ddukbokki
in place, and bring back the empty container.]
[Suk Jin: Find a couple at the market
who's out on a date.]
- Anyone here on a date?
- Where's ddukbokki?
- Ddukbokki!
- Date!
Are you two here on a date?
- Do you sell ddukbokki here?
- Are you two here on a date?
- Can I just have a small order?
- You are, aren't you?
This couple is here on a date.
- How long have you two been dating for?
- Just a small order.
- You two are boyfriend, girlfriend, right?
- Yes.
How long have you been together for?
- 250 days.
- Excuse me?
250 days!
Let's cheers to that. Look
towards the camera. One, two, three.
- Hurray!
- Why are you saying it?
- They just look so cute.
- I agree. You do look cute together.
- You two look beautiful together.
So beautiful!
Where do I have to go?
Where?
Right here?
Here.
She's a foreigner.
- She's from Thailand.
- Hello.
[Found someone from Thailand.]
We need to verify that you're a foreigner.
Please say a few words in Thai.
Did you understand that?
You didn't, did you?
- Thank you.
- Kim Jong Kook, pass.
Pass!
I really want some ddukbokki,
but I have no time to eat it right now.
[Find someone carrying a camera around.]
Anyone with a camera?
- I have to eat ddukbokki.
- I found my people.
- You're not a couple, are you?
- Yes, they are! What are you doing?
- I don't think they're a couple.
- What are you doing?
- Even though you may like each other...
- They are a couple.
- But you're not a couple, are you?
- You really aren't a couple, are you?
- This is their 250th day together. 250th day.
It may be your 250th day,
but you're not a couple, are you?
- They've been in love for 250 days so far.
- You may be in love, but are you a couple?
You can't be a couple, can you?
- His girlfriend is prettier than Hyo Joo.
- Do you by any chance have a camera?
- Do you have a camera?
- He doesn't have a camera.
[Yoo Hyuk's frustrating mission.]
You already found your people?
[Gary: Find a child who's out shopping
at the market with his/her mother.]
Take your time.
You have to finish that, Hyo Joo.
- Here, have some of this.
- Okay, I'll just have one.
Wow... this is unbelievable.
Ma'am, this is so good.
- This is so good.
- I have to get going.
- See you later, Hyo Joo.
- Bye.
[Big-nosed Brother and Hyo Joo get
on their way to complete their mission.]
Camera.
Do you have a camera?
Camera... camera.
Run, run!
[Finish an order of ddukbokki in place,
and bring back the empty container.]
- What is that?
- Hurry up and get up there.
- Over here.
- You don't have a camera, do you?
[Mission: Find someone with a camera.
But he's too busy having a photo session.]
- Mother, I have a mission to do.
- Hang on. I'll do it for you.
I'll do the mission for you.
- I'll do the mission.
- It's not that kind of a mission.
[All the ladies getting excited at the
appearance of Captain Running Man.]
Ma'am... I need to go find a camera.
- Ma'am... I have to get going.
- Just one more picture.
- Just a minute.
- Han Hyo Joo, you pass.
[Hyo Joo also passes.]
Find a couple out on a date at the market.
They've been together exactly 250 days.
I got it right, didn't I? How
many days have you been together?
- 250 days.
- 250 days. You two love each other, right?
- Yes.
- How about giving each other a hug?
Right?
- They're a couple, right?
- You're right. They are a couple.
- Thank you.
- A child out shopping with his/her mother.
His mother is over there.
Ma'am! Ma'am!
- Someone with a camera over here.
- Ma'am, hurry!
[VJ Gwon Yeol?]
Ma'am, hurry!
Ma'am!
- It's him. He's been carrying that all day.
- Ma'am, hurry!
He's been carrying the camera
around all day.
There are plenty of other people here
with their cameras!
I've got his mother here.
- Are you his mother?
- Yes, I'm his mother.
- Jae Suk's eliminated.
- Gary, pass.
[Gary passes!]
Yoo Jae Suk must stay behind
while everyone else can move on
to the next location.
This is driving me crazy.
Two people will be eliminated
at the next location.
[Two people to be eliminated at 'R4'!]
Where?
Where do we go?
- You have to tell us where to go!
- [All the survivors heading off to 'R4'.]
[Hyo Joo in the lead again.]
Wow... this is exhausting.
- Ha Ha, are you okay?
- Why are you being so slow?
You came determined today, didn't you?
Not exactly, but now that I'm here,
I can't seem to help it.
['R4' is at a very old bookstore.]
- Where is it?
- Is that it?
You can't push and shove
people like that.
How are you so fast?
- What?
- Han Hyo Joo...
Why am I getting so crazy over
these games?
[Usain Hyo Joo beating out all the guys.]
She keeps beating everyone to
all the locations.
Your next mission is...
an old bookstore quiz.
Once I read out the questions, you will each
have a chance to answer the question
in the order of your arrival.
From this mission...
two of you will be eliminated.
It's all luck of the draw.
- It all depends on the person's luck.
- Two.
Number two.
I will read out question number two.
- She was a good student too.
- Really?
I heard that Hyo Joo used to cry if
she even got one answer wrong.
- I'll read you your question.
- Didn't she even play a queen consort?
Maybe I should just say that I'm wrong,
and go back in line.
I bet she really is very smart.
[In the midst of all the burden...]
- In the fairytale, Peter Pan...
- I used to love Peter Pan!
What is the name of the world
that Peter Pan lives in?
- That's way too easy!
- She'll know that for sure!
- That's too easy of a question.
- Jamaica... it's Jamaica.
Here's your hint.
- It's ___ Land.
- Wow... that's just too easy.
Huh?
Oh, oh!
Wonderland!
- What?
- What did you say?
What did you say?
What did you say it was?
Did you say Wonderland?
Wonderland?
- Maybe she was talking about Disneyland.
- Anyone know the correct answer?
- Isn't it Neverland?
- Correct.
[Correct answer- Neverland.]
- You knew?
- Of course.
The way I see it, it's going to be between
Dong Hoon, Hyo Joo and myself eliminated.
[Next up is Big-nosed Brother's turn
to choose his question.]
In the novel,
'Rain shower' by Hwang Soon Won...
what is the color that the girl
in the novel likes?
- That's way too easy.
- You've got five seconds.
- One...
- Hot pink.
[Enough air shot in his face
to get his mind back together.]
- What color?
- That really got me.
The correct answer is, purple.
- Ah, purple?
- How do you not know that?
- Two of you are getting eliminated.
- Number 13.
- Someone has to get one right.
- This is an old proverb.
Old proverb?
I'm not good at those.
With the meaning that even though it's slow,
it's rather more trustworthy and dependable...
The way the proverb goes, it says,
'__ __ steps even if they're scattering steps'
What are the words that are missing
in the beginning of that proverb?
- _ _ steps even if they're scattered...
- _ _ steps even if they're scattered steps.
Sloth?
[What is the words missing from the proverb,
'_ _steps even if they're scattered steps?']
Strong pace?
[Unbelievable]
- What? They can walk like this.
- Strong? Strong steps in a proverb?
- What are you saying?
- This is a proverb they're asking.
- Strong steps...
- He failed very strongly.
- _ _ steps...
- A snail?
- Ant?
- Cow? Or a bull?
Bull steps?
Ah...
So it's a bull... did you even guess that?
The bull question was too easy.
Hyo Joo said 'ant'.
Number 19.
It's an English question.
No hints will be given.
Okay, English question.
In English,
a moon that's only half full...
- In English, a moon that's only half full...
- Half-moon?
It's called a half moon.
Then what do you call a moon
that's completely full?
- That's way too easy.
- That's too easy.
Full moon?
That's way too easy.
[Correct answer]
- That was too easy of a question.
- Of course, it's a full moon.
- Don't you think that was too easy?
- He just picked a good question.
[All you have to do is pick an easy question.
It's up to the luck of the draw.]
Okay, pass.
Don't give him any assessment questions.
- Okay, it's another English question.
- Oh my God.
- Since you're good with English...
- You can't tell him the answer.
Okay, don't worry.
DIY is an acronym used to describe
buying the raw material
to build a product or
an item yourself directly.
- What does DIY stand for?
- Come on, you have to know this!
[Blank...]
Come on, this is easy!
DIY?
Difficult!
I am Young!
[What in the world is he
talking about?]
I am Young!
- That's so funny.
- I am Young?
[Correct answer is: Do It Yourself.]
That's hilarious.
What will it be?
- Number 14.
- Question number 14.
Yep.
In the children's folklore,
'Sun and the Moon',
what did the tiger fall into when the
rotted rope he was climbing broke off?
- I know this one! I know!
- You have to know this one.
You have to know this question.
Yeouinaru.
(A city in Korea)
Baekrokdam!
(A caldera in Halla Mountain.)
- A millet field.
- Anyone know the answer?
- Millet field.
- Millet field is the correct answer.
[Hyo Joo guesses the correct answer.]
That's why the millet field is red.
Because the tiger fell on the field.
- His blood reddened the field, right?
- Yeah.
Number ten.
What did the creator of Pinocchio,
Geppetto do for his living?
He was a fund manager.
A carpenter?
- What did you say?
- A carpenter?
- Hyo Joo, a minister. (Play on words.)
- Carpenter?
[Correct answer- Carpenter.]
I'm so relieved!
What did you say for your answer?
[Two people to be eliminated with
only Jong Kook, Ha Ha and Gary left.]
Jong Kook, just answer the question
so that these two can get eliminated.
- In Hemingway's novel...
- Hemingway! He's my favorite!
- I love Hemingway.
- He's my favorite author.
- In the novel, 'Old Man and the Sea'...
- That's a great book!
- I really love that book.
- Reading books like that are hard for me.
What is the name of the country the old man
is said to go fishing in this novel?
I'm not sure.
Spain?
Germany!
You're stupid.
- I'll answer the question.
- Do you know the answer to this?
Isn't it Norway?
Ukraine!
The Netherlands?
- That's not it?
- Hey... I'll get it.
France!
Czechoslovakia.
- Maracay!
- America.
America.
Chile.
[They may name every single country
in the world at this rate.]
- Really?
- Yeah, it's nearby Chile.
[Got pretty close to the area.]
- It has to be a country by the ocean.
- The ocean?
- It's close to America.
- Close to there?
[A country close to America...]
- I know! I figured it out!
- I know it now.
- I totally got it figured out.
- I know!
Cuba!
[Correct answer]
- It's Cuba!
- It's next to Jamaica.
- Cuba.
- Thus...
The two kids... are eliminated.
[Two kids, Ha Ha and Gary are eliminated.]
[Surviving members head off
to the final location, 'R5'.]
- Hurry! Come on.
- Hey!
Why are you so fast?
- What place did you get?
- First place.
[What are the eliminated members
doing here?]
- What are you doing here?
- Is this the next game?
This is the lot of writer, Lee Sang's house.
[Writer, Lee Sang's house.]
This is called the six sided secret.
That's why you see the cube
sitting there before you.
You have to match one side of the cube
to pass this mission.
- How do you do this?
- How do we match this?
[So hard...]
- We tried this earlier.
- And?
- Don't try to match a side.
- If you try to match it, you won't get it.
- Really?
- You have to just start moving it around.
[Turn it...]
[And turn it some more.]
[No matter how hard they try
to match it...]
Seeing Suk Jin in the mix of the finalists
is really making this feel awkward.
Okay!
[Mr. Capable succeeds!]
[Big-nose Brother with his streak of luck
also succeeds!]
Okay, you're all set.
Wow, I did it.
One of you two are to
be eliminated.
I totally got that by fluke.
- Really?
- I really tried to get it matched.
- I really can't do these cubes.
- This reminds me of the 3x3 cubes.
I'm good at doing those 3x3 ones.
- But I get stuck with this instead.
- Look, you're getting there.
- How beautiful... so beautiful.
- I think she's almost getting it.
- Are you trying to match it?
- There's a way to do this.
But...
[Huh?]
[But he continues to keep spinning?]
- Why do you keep spinning when you have it?
- Why are you continuing to spin it around?
- You had it!
- You have to look at all the sides.
- You had the green side.
- You matched all the green!
- I can't believe you did that.
- You had it but you just kept on spinning.
You should've told me.
- I have no idea.
- Take a good look.
[One of the two will be
the final person to get eliminated.]
- That's right.
- You have to match up the white line.
- You have to match up that color.
- How?
He's close to getting it.
[Junho is first to succeed.]
This always happens to me.
After working so hard at it...
this always happens to me.
[And she ran harder than anyone else...]
This all seem so futile.
- This really seems so futile!
- Futile!
- You're no different than Kwang Soo.
- I know.
In the first come first serve game
Kim Jong Kook, Ji Suk Jin and Junho
are the last three remaining survivors.
Congratulations!
- Congratulations to the three of you.
- I really congratulate all of you.
- I'm one of the winners?
- Congratulations on your survival.
Wow... I wonder what happens now?
It is such an honor to be on
the same program as the three of you.
They're trying to take a little break,
so you need to get out of the way.
We have to get rid of all the untrustworthy
ones like those guys first.
- You can trust us.
- We have three votes between the three of us.
-These three are safe from elimination.
- Yes, that's right.
All nine of you have your own
vote to cast.
So all nine of you will vote to choose just
one of these six to eliminate and be rid of.
What are you saying to Hyo Joo now?
So we have to cast our votes by
writing down their name?
- It has to be one of these six members.
- I understand.
[Nervous two members with a
high probability of being eliminated.]
[Kwang Soo's vote]
- Let's do this together, Kwang Soo.
- Yes, Ha Ha.
[Ha Ha]
[After what he just said,
he votes for Ha Ha...]
[Blank Ji's vote is...]
[One vote for Kwang Soo.]
[Yoo Hyuk's vote goes to...]
[Kwang Soo!]
[Current standing-
Ha Ha:1 vs. Kwang Soo:2.]
[Gary's vote goes to Ha Ha.]
[You know, right?]
[Immediately votes for Kwang Soo.]
I have to survive.
Oh my, it's so hot.
[Current standing-
Ha Ha:2 vs. Kwang Soo:3.]
[Likely candidates to be eliminated
giving Hyo Joo the eye.]
It's going to be a fall out!
Fall out!
Cross!
Hyo Joo's made up her mind.
Leg tripping... Cross!
[Hyo Joo's vote...]
[Goes to Ha Ha!]
Squabble and Bicker Cross!
I've seen him betray one too many times.
[Junho also votes for Ha Ha!]
[Big-nosed Brother votes for Kwang Soo.]
[Current standing-
Ha Ha:4 vs. Kwang Soo:4.]
- Yours could be the deciding vote.
- Really?
[Kkuk's vote could be the
deciding factor!]
Okay, I'm finished!
[Who's name did he write down?]
[Ha Ha!]
Congratulations, Ha Ha!
Congratulations!
[Ha Ha is eliminated with five votes!]
This is definitely Hyo Joo's.
She wrote down your name.
[Eliminated Ha Ha gets flipped over again.]
[He really is being dragged away...]
I won't be killed off this easily!
[No... you won't die.]
[At the same time, in SBS Mokdong Office.]
[Jung Woo Sung finally makes his move?]
[He is... making his moves.]
[Jung Woo Sung's mission.]
You're the Grim Reaper of Revenge.
[In the order that the eliminated one wishes,
oust every member of Running Man in revenge.]
[You'll have the use of all 108 CCTV cameras
that are installed throughout the building.]
[This is... the surveillance room.]
There are a total of 108 CCTV cameras
installed throughout the SBS building
that you can use to locate the whereabouts
of each member of the Running Man team.
Use it well...
and you'll find it a very useful tool.
However...
Because Running Man members assume
that their positions are being exposed...
they will go around turning off
each of the CCTV cameras.
And once all the CCTV cameras
have been turned off
the members then come after you
to eliminate your name tag.
[Let's get started.]
[On the other hand, they're
conducting the second elimination.]
[Who will be the second member
to get eliminated?]
first vote is for Lee Kwang Soo.
Kwang Soo.
Lee Kwang Soo.
'Kwang Soo, I'm sorry.'
Kwang Soo, Kwang Soo, Kwang Soo.
[By a unanimous vote,
Kwang Soo is eliminated!]
- How did that happen?
- Is this even allowed?
Don't you think this is too much?
Seriously.
- Yeah...
- Ha Ha.
- I was so lonely here by myself.
- I can't believe it.
After what they just put me through,
isn't doing this again too much?
To be perfectly honest,
have you ever seen a traitor nicer than us?
And we're so docile too.
It's probably not good for us to be
as nice as we are.
Lee Kwang Soo has been eliminated
during the second round.
What's that?
What is that?
[Huh?]
[Death note?]
Do you feel unjust
from having been eliminated?
Don't you feel overwhelmed by rage?
In your answer is yes, then
who do you think is responsible for it?
[Write down the name of the person
that filled them with rage?]
Who's name tag do you want to eliminate
the most if you were able to?
Write down the names of today's
Running Man members that you
want to oust in the order that you want
to eliminate in this notebook.
[In the order that they want ousted?]
[Plan the order of members to be
eliminated in the death note!]
[The time is here...]
[SBS Mokdong Office]
[Van carrying the eliminated members
is the first to arrive.]
Why are you...
I have a death note in my hands.
But... wait, what's your name?
I'm writing it in my death note.
- Wait... but we've been brought back to life.
- This is the type of people we are.
This is really making me feel disappointed.
We're... we're not out of
this game yet.
The eliminated members are now
entering the building.
Why am I feeling so nervous?
You may open the door
and go on inside.
What's going on in there?
Wait, wait... wait a second.
Isn't that... Jung Woo Sung?
It is, isn't it?
- Did you see his profile?
- It could just be someone who resembles him.
It could be Dong Wan.
Dong Wan, is it you?
Hey, I think it is him.
Woo Sung... Is it you, Woo Sung?
[Everyone...]
[Hello!]
[The real Jung Woo Sung right
in front of their eyes!]
This is so amazing!
[Automatically slipping into
their fan mode.]
Seriously...
- You're so much better than Hyo Joo!
- Really?
- Yes.
I don't know what to do with myself!
Woo Sung... can I call you sometime?
No, don't call me.
[Overflowing with wit and charm
right from the get-go.]
- He refused right away.
- No, please don't call me.
- Wow... seriously.
- I feel like I'm in a movie right now!
- I saw this in his movie!
- 'The Beat'!
Where are you?
Where are you right now?
[Hit movie from 1997, 'Beat'...
Do you remember the movie?]
[Demonstrating it himself.]
You have to bend the neck like this.
[There you go trying to imitate him again...]
I do this more than the motorcycle
scene these days.
[Instead of the motorcycle,
it's the horse action these days.]
- Are you okay after that gunshot wound?
- Yes, I'm fine.
- I took out all the bullets.
- He says he got all the bullets.
I took out all the bullets,
and came back to life.
I came to life as another human being.
But I have to be more than
just a regular human being today.
- The way he talks is so cool.
- Really?
- Thank you.
- He asks if we're being serious!
I think he really likes hearing
things like that.
Yes, I really like it.
You should've been on
a variety show sooner.
- No, I've been too nervous to do that.
- This is your first time on a variety show?
I was so nervous to come on this show.
This is the first time that I've been nervous
enough for my heart to beat like this.
- Really?
- It gave me the flutters.
I've always heard so much about Running Man,
and it sounded like fun.
I thought it would be so fun and exciting
to meet all of you
but I wondered if I'd be good on the show.
Just the fact that you came on the show
is a great honor to us.
- What character are you playing today?
- Can you tell us?
I'm the death note problem solver.
[Jung Woo Sung,
he's the death note problem solver?]
In this SBS Mokdong office building...
there are a total of 108 CCTV cameras
starting from the parking garage
all the way up to the rooftop
where the helipad is.
[Total of 108 CCTV cameras placed
throughout SBS office building.]
[Three levels from the garage up to the roof
are all under constant surveillance!]
We can use those CCTV cameras to
find the Running Man members.
But if the Running Man members get rid of
all those 108 CCTV cameras
then Running Man members
can oust me.
So once all these cameras are out,
they can then start to attack you?
- Yes, that's correct.
- But if we eliminate them before that...
That's why we have to find them before
that happens and quickly eliminate them.
- We?
- Is the three of us are a team?
In exchange for me taking your lists in
the death notes to carry out your wish...
both of you need to join me
in carrying out this mission.
- We have a team uniform!
- I have a good feeling about this.
I feel like a Grim Reaper too.
I'm going to change into this right now.
- Wow...
- I love you, Jung Woo Sung!
Jung Woo Sung!
You've still got it, Jung Woo Sung!
- You have to do it with us.
- What? Together?
- We're a team. One, two, three, four!
- Okay.
You've still got it, Jung Woo Sung!
[Louder!]
I'm a member of his fan club,
Ha Dong Hoon.
- I'm the Chairman of his fan club.
- I'm the Chairman!
- No, I'm the Chairman!
- Then let's duke it out.
[A fight to take over
the fan club chairman position.]
[I can't believe I'm teamed up
with these guys...]
- Have you both completed your death notes?
- Yes.
You two need to discuss how
the order of the death note will go.
How should we do this?
So in a way, Woo Sung will have to do
as we order him to do?
No, no. Not order.
Choose your words wisely.
You're asking the Grim Reaper for a favor.
Right?
What did you say?
I have good hearing.
- He just said that we're your minions!
- No, I didn't!
He's lying to you right now.
- I'm the chairman of your fan club.
- No, I'm the chairman.
I have good hearing,
and I tend to be pretty petty.
- I'm going to keep my eye on you.
- I understand.
Think about this.
Remember when Jong Kook dragged out
ousting you awhile back?
That really was hell.
When I think about it,
I'm reminded of Jae Suk at the pool.
He kept coming after me and tormenting me
whenever he had anything in his hands.
- So these two people need to feel that pain.
- Be cruel and keep them alive to the end?
Let's be cruel about it.
We have to make them feel that fear.
- Scare them out of their skin?
- Yes.
We can do it because we
have Woo Sung here.
Then we'll start ousting people
starting with the nicest one
and as for the rest, make
them really know what real fear is.
And be very cruel about the way
you rip off their name tags.
Let's put Jae Suk at number seven.
[Yoo Jae Suk lands the last position
in the order of the hunt.]
Should we put Jong Kook at five or six?
Here's what I think.
- How about Hyo Joo?
- Okay.
Han Hyo Joo.
Remember what I told you about her?
I can't even attempt to
trip her anymore.
Have you and Hyo Joo ever played
lovers in a movie or anything?
- No, we haven't.
- You haven't.
- She's the enemy.
- The enemy?
[Hyo Joo lands the sixth position
without feeling any guilt or burden.]
Okay, next is Jong Kook.
Kim Jong Kook.
You have to be careful
about the fifth person.
And after that,
the order is no longer very important.
Who should we put in the first place
for the first one to get ousted?
- One, two, three.
- Ji Suk Jin!
- We really are of the same mind.
- Of course.
[The dignity of the race starter.]
He's like a fish in the pond.
You'll catch him the moment you
dip your fishing pole in the water.
Okay, Junho?
Since he is the guest, after all.
- Gary is strong too.
- Yeah, Gary is strong.
[The death note's order is
now complete!]
Since this is his first time
he needs to know what it's like
to rip off the name tag.
- Want to know what it's like to rip it off?
- If he rips it off, you're ousted!
No, it's okay for him to do this.
[In one swipe?]
- You got it.
- Did I do it right?
But I think you need to be more
snappy about it.
If you'll take a look,
see how I'm grabbing this corner?
When someone grabs ours like this,
do you know what our habitual reaction is?
We turn away like this.
[Demonstrating evasion skills that
are now embedded in their bodies.]
So when you want to rip it off,
lightly grab them and snap it off.
- See?
- So that they can't turn away.
[Point- Prohibit them from turning,
and snap off their name tag.]
Want to give it a try?
You sneak up on someone.
And next.
[Skilled enough for him
to jump right into action!]
What would you do if I grabbed
you right here?
That's right.
Grab him.
[Matrix?]
You're good.
You're ready for this.
- We...
Hang on a second.
I should be saying it first.
- I'm the Grim Reaper.
- Okay, I understand.
- Okay.
- We!
- We.
We Cross!
- How can I not laugh at that?
- Wow, it's so hot in here.
[Death note Grim Reaper.
His hunting starts now.]
[Running Man limousine arrives at
the SBS office soon thereafter.]
Our company.
Our company?
[Not even fathoming in their wildest dreams
that a Grim Reaper is awaiting their arrival.]
- This is where I became a victor.
- Stop talking about that.
How many times
are you going to talk about that?
- I haven't talked about it that much.
- That happened so long ago.
- What are you talking about?
- This is your final mission.
The survival games that
you've been playing thus far...
those games were played to determine
who was going to be eliminated.
The real survivor race starts now.
Your current locations...
are being exposed to Grim Reaper of Revenge,
who has a bell attached to his shoes.
Through the usage of 108 CCTV cameras
he is currently surveying
every move that you guys are making.
The Grim Reaper must follow the
order of revenge that's been designated
and must start ousting you one by one
in the order of that list.
- What do you mean?
- How was that order made?
Eliminated in an order?
- What have we done to deserve this?
- What have we done?
But you don't have to just sit back
and just be had by the Grim Reaper.
If you turn off all the 108 CCTV cameras
that are placed throughout the building...
- 108 cameras?
- What?
Starting in the lower garage level
going up to the twenty second floor.
How many would that make per person?
If you turn off all 108 of those cameras,
then the bell comes off of the Grim Reaper.
And that's when you can also start
attacking the Grim Reaper.
- We have to work together on this.
- Yes, we're not each other's enemy.
Let's each take a section then.
[Right before the mission is launched.]
[The Grim Reaper is also starting
to make his move!]
Woo Sung, let's win this race and
we can all spend the night at your house.
I like it. Let's have a garden party with
just us three at your house.
- You like going to someone else's home?
- Let's have a party.
Yes, I do.
Three, two, one.
You have no time. Get started.
- Do we know what the order of that list is?
- Do we just get going?
- Start!
- Hurry. Go, go, go!
Let us know right away when you
locate Suk Jin on the camera.
[One goes out to act as bait,
while the other stays behind to keep watch.]
- What floor are they starting off at?
- They're probably coming up from first.
[Only Woo Jung, the Grim Reaper has the
power to actually eliminate the name tag.]
Eighth floor is the level where the
two buildings connect with a walkway.
- Eighth floor.
- Okay, let's go to the eighth floor.
- These bells are no joke.
- Right? Aren't they nerve wrecking?
The people being chased are terrified
to hear the sound of those bells.
Where's Suk Jin?
Suk Jin...
Suk Jin.
Suk Jin, Suk Jin...
Where's Suk Jin?
Suk Jin...
All the members are now...
Oh, they're now just coming in.
Okay, first floor.
Okay, there's Suk Jin.
- How about the garage?
- We should check the helipad first.
I'm positive there's one up there.
They told us about it too.
Isn't that one?
[CCTV camera is discovered!]
- Isn't that one?
- I'll take care of the helipad.
There's one over here.
Look, one over here.
- There it is.
- I knew there would be one.
[Junho turns off the one behind
the information desk.]
- He got one
- Nice, Junho.
- Oh my God.
- You did good.
Junho's pretty good.
[One off]
- I'm going up to the seventh floor.
- I'll go up to the 21st.
Didn't he say earlier that there's an
order to the elimination?
There's one here.
- There's one here.
- You have to block it off.
Number 15.
[Second CCTV camera turned off.]
Okay, Suk Jin.
Suk Jin...
Suk Jin turned one off.
He's calling.
Yeah, Ha Ha.
Suk Jin just turned off a camera
down on the first floor.
- First floor.
- First floor?
He's going to be getting on an elevator
from the first floor.
- He's going to get on an elevator?
- Yes.
He's going to get on an elevator?
In that case, wait...
They've already turned off
two cameras on the first floor.
Okay, I got it.
I'm heading down to the first floor.
Can you tell me what he said?
Instead of going down, just wait a bit
since he's getting on the elevator.
- Tell me what he's saying.
- Okay.
I see you and Kwang Soo.
You're on the eighth floor?
Yeah, we're on the eighth floor.
Hang on a second.
I think they're all in the elevator.
I'll call you as soon as I spot them.
Oh, okay.
I'm so nervous!
Being here is a huge responsibility.
It's giving me a headache.
Okay, they were just on the first floor...
But what is that order exactly?
[Running Man members are clueless to
the order designated in the death note.]
- You can go up to the top level and...
- I'll go up to the 22nd floor.
Let's do that and we can all
start going down the floors.
There's one.
There's one right there.
I just need to turn it off, right?
Hello.
We need to turn off cameras
like these, right?
I see one over there.
[Turning off the ones they see
one by one.]
There's one.
They have it hidden everywhere.
Number 98.
Who's that?
Who's on the 21st floor?
Ah, it's Ji Hyo.
[Gary is making his rounds on
the 19th floor.]
It's Song Ji Hyo.
Song Ji Hyo's on the 21st floor.
I just need to find Suk Jin.
but I can't find him anywhere.
[They're finding the cameras
much faster than anticipated.]
I don't see him anywhere!
Where is Suk Jin?
Is he hiding somewhere?
[Big-nosed Brother finally arrives
on the 22nd floor.]
Ji Hyo.
Woo Sung, Ji Hyo...
[There he is!]
[First target, Suk Jin is discovered
on the 22nd floor!]
Ji Suk Jin is on 22nd floor.
- Ji Suk Jin is on 22nd floor.
- 22nd floor!
[Message received from the surveillance room.
Up to the 22nd floor!]
- What about me?
- 22nd floor. He's up on the 22nd floor!
You have to take me with you.
Ji Suk Jin is on 22nd floor.
Okay.
[Their second target, Ji Hyo
is on the 21st floor!]
Woo Sung, he's on the 22nd floor.
You can't go off by yourself!
They're turning off all of them.
This is a big problem.
You have to hurry.
And Song Ji Hyo's on the 21st floor.
- Song Ji Hyo is on the 21st floor?
- Yes.
So go one floor down as soon as
you oust Ji Suk Jin.
If it's taking too long, then use the stairs.
All the cameras are being shut off.
Hyo Joo's on the 19th floor,
and she's turning everything off.
- We're heading off to 22nd.
- Okay.
- Ten CCTV's are currently out.
- Ten? Already?
Ten CCTV's are currently out.
You're keeping me out of the loop.
He can't call both of us at the same time.
- That's why he just kept telling me.
- Okay.
I'm sure he wants to tell you too
as much as you want to hear it.
I'm sure he wants to tell you.
But let's first get Ji Suk Jin...
- Can we discuss it first?
- There's no time for that.
- And Song Ji Hyo's on the 21st floor.
- We can go down right after.
Bye.
I knew there would be one up here.
Jong Kook.
Jong Kook's up on the roof!
- 20 CCTV's are currently out.
- 20 of them already?
- Already?
You have no time for the elevator.
You have to run up there right now.
He says we have no time and
that we have to run up there.
Ha Ha, we've arrived on the 22nd floor.
- Stop taking so long!
- Where's Suk Jin?
You have to get up to the 22nd floor!
We just got to the 22nd floor.
Where on the 22nd floor?
[In the meantime, the Running Man members
are busy turning off all the cameras.]
Wow, these guys are
annihilating the cameras.
Wow, why do I feel so nervous?
I just don't know what's
going to happen.
[Not even guessing in his wildest dreams
that he's the first one to be ousted.]
Who's that?
[Death note Grim Reaper, Jung Woo Sung!]
[Their first target Ji Suk Jin
is within their sight!]
No!
Kwang Soo, what are you doing?
No, way, no way!
It's Jung Woo Sung!
- Stop!
- It's Jung Woo Sung!
Wait, wait.
[Eliminates the name tag
in the blink of an eye!]
[Grim Reaper Woo Sung succeeds at his
first hunt with lightning fast speed!]
You're out.
- Are you really going to be like this?
- Kwang Soo!
I've finally got my revenge!
I'm the first?
Ji Suk Jin, out.
It's finally starting.
It's starting.
[Running Man members unaware of
the reason behind the order.]
[Their anxiety level is growing
more and more.]
- Oh my goodness!
- You scared me!
- Gary, why was Suk Jin the first ousted?
- I don't know.
I'm so scared right now.
You have to keep a close eye on things.
But Suk Jin? How is that order working?
I have no idea myself.
- How do you think the order is going?
- Is it by age?
What?
In that case, I'm next.
- That would make me next.
- I'm scared to death right now.
[Who determined the order?]
[Grim Reaper off to hunt down
his second target, Ji Hyo.]
Call him.
Make sure Song Ji Hyo is on
the 21st floor.
I heard the bells ringing.
I heard the bells.
[Extreme level of anxiety after
having heard the bells ringing.]
I have to keep going down and
find the security cameras.
But I'm too scared to go down.
I hate being scared like this.
I think someone is already on
the 17th floor.
Someone already did this floor.
Sorry for taking off on you like that.
I ran too far ahead of you.
- Woo Sung, what happened?
- Ha Ha, we ousted Suk Jin.
Hey, sixth floor!
Song Ji Hyo's on the sixth floor!
- Hurry! Sixth floor!
- What floor?
- Sixth floor!
- Sixth floor?
Sixth floor.
She's on the sixth floor!
- Okay, sixth floor!
- Hurry up and run!
Hurry, hurry, hurry!
[Much of the camera screens have
already been shut off.]
Wow, I can't believe I saw Ji Hyo's
face like that.
[Ace Ji Hyo searching the sixth floor
for any hidden security cameras.]
[Easily finds one to shut off.]
[She's not the Ace for no reason!]
Look at Ji Hyo. Look at Ji Hyo over here.
This is driving me crazy.
Ji Hyo and Jae Suk are going around turning
off all the cameras. You have to move fast.
- Okay.
- We have no time.
Let's go this way.
Lets take the emergency stairs.
- You're going to run?
- Yeah.
[He's going to run down
ten flights of stairs?]
You should've waited for the elevator.
Kwang Soo, go back in there
and ride the elevator down.
- Down to the sixth floor?
- Yeah.
- Will you be alright by yourself?
This is too nerve wrecking,
and it's only the beginning.
- I'm on the 13th floor.
- 13? I told you to go down to the sixth!
- What are you doing?
- Woo Sung ran down to sixth on his own.
He kind of does what he wants.
What do you mean, does what he wants?
He's not even doing anything.
Ha Ha, I really...
have nothing to do here.
Ji Hyo's on the sixth floor.
Look, she's right there.
She's going around turning them all off.
Ji Hyo's shutting them all of on the sixth.
- I'm here.
- You have to move faster.
He hung up on me.
What kind of a Grim Reaper is this?
[Arriving on the sixth floor.
His search for Ji Hyo is on!]
[The sound of the bells ringing...]
[Succeeds at eliminating
his second target, Ji Hyo!]
Nice to see you.
[On my goodness!
Look who it is!]
I've got Song Ji Hyo.
Who's the third target?
Okay, Song Ji Hyo, out.
Okay, Gary.
Where's Gary?
[Find the third target, Gary!]
Where is he right now?
- Did you get any here?
- No, but I got everything on the 19th floor.
I wonder who ousted Suk Jin?
- I heard the bell sound.
- Really?
It was going after Kwang Soo.
Or was it not Kwang Soo?
I heard Kwang Soo's voice.
Ugh, that scared me!
That really scared me.
[Getting scared from having
seen their own VJ's.]
I'm going to go crazy.
[Pole dancing?]
- That really scared me.
- You said you saw Kwang Soo?
It was Kwang Soo's voice.
- Kwang Soo's wearing the bells?
- Kwang Soo's voice and the bell...
- I heard Kwang Soo's voice.
- Then the Grim Reaper...
- Then he's the Grim Reaper's minion.
- Kwang Soo is?
He's the spy.
Don't trust anyone.
Not anyone in this situation.
[Another ten years off her life.]
You have to be strong!
Stuff like this really scares me.
Song Ji Hyo, out.
- No breaks for the girls?
- No.
Remember they said that we're getting
ousted in order?
Suk Jin was first to get ousted,
and if Ji Hyo was next...
I wonder what the order is?
I think it would be better to start
our search from the first floor.
- Okay.
- That may throw them off.
What?
Not a bad plan.
[Sound of bells ringing...]
What's that sound?
Hey, it's Jung Woo Sung!
- Hey, it's Jung Woo Sung!
- Wait.
[Panic]
It's Jung Woo Sung!
What is this?
- What is this? What's going on?
- Wait, hand on.
- What are you doing? What's going on?
- Hang on. Just wait.
- You startled me.
- I'm the Grim Reaper of Death.
- What did you say?
Why are you the Grim Reaper of Death?
How are you the Grim Reaper of Death?
- Hang on a second and quiet down.
- Why?
Why are you doing this?
What are you doing here?
I'm on my mission.
You're on my side from now on.
- What?
- You're on my side from this moment on.
Why?
You have to be on my side from now on,
and help me oust the other members.
I can pick just one person
to join my side.
And you're my one person.
So you will be helping me
oust the other members from now on.
[What is he saying?]
- Since you have the best skills...
- Wait a second.
You're looking way too serious.
- You look so serious.
- We have to catch them.
- You have to lure them over to me.
- How?
But I have to go take care
of the CCTV cameras.
You have to lure the others over to me
while you go around taking care of the CCTV.
[Lying to him about luring
the other members over to him.]
- Then am I the spy?
- We have to separate for now.
- But, wait...
Hello?
Jung Woo Sung...
[Feeling as though he's been
swept through by a storm.]
This is driving me crazy.
Wait...
[So what is it that I'm supposed
to be doing?]
I'm not sure.
Everything happened so suddenly.
[Unsure about what's going on from
having things happen so suddenly.]
I think I'm going to go around
turning off the cameras for now.
There's one.
Here it is.
The way I see it,
it must not be my turn yet.
Seeing how he didn't eliminate me...
it must not have been my turn yet.
If that wasn't the case,
I'm sure Woo Sung would've ousted me.
[Clever deduction!]
I think... Ah!
Even though I'm not the spy...
Don't you think, Gwon Yeol?
That's it.
He told me that on purpose because it's
not my turn to be ousted yet.
So that's why he said I was a spy.
It doesn't make any sense otherwise.
How would I know where to take them without
even a way to communicate with him?
He can't even tell me where
to bring them.
He doesn't even have a way
of communicating with me.
That's it.
He totally almost had me with that
serious look in his eyes.
I really thought for a second I was a spy.
But that's not really the case.
No, that's not it.
No need to worry, Gwon Yeol.
Hey, there's no need to worry
whatsoever.
That's what I think.
I have to hurry
and turn all these off.
[Running Man members rushing around
to turn off all the CCTV cameras.]
So someone is watching me right now
as I'm doing this?
Who is?
Someone is.
Number two!
[Mr. Capable heads down to the garage
after completing the rooftop.]
That one was number three.
He's on the third lower level.
40 CCTV cameras are currently out.
Jong Kook is on the third lower level
and they're driving me crazy by
going around turning everything off.
Really?
Where did Gary go?
[Oh!]
Gary!
He's on the first floor!
[Discovers Gary on the first floor.]
Who is he on the phone with?
What do I do? He's on the first floor!
I just saw Gary.
Who's he on the phone with?
This is driving me crazy.
What the heck!
[Giraffe also spots their third target,
Gary on the first floor.]
[Calls Grim Reaper,
Woo Sung right away.]
Yeah, talk to me.
First floor.
He's on the first floor.
Gary and Hyo Joo are on the first floor.
- Okay, I'm coming down.
- Okay.
You don't have time for the elevator.
You have to run down here.
I really think that Kwang Soo is a spy.
You really have to be cautious of
Kwang Soo and Ha Ha at all times.
Are they leaving?
Are they going?
[Kwang Soo arrives on the first floor
in order to keep Gary captured.]
What is that?
- Huh?
- What is that?
[Surprised at seeing his
Jung Woo Sung fan club t-shirt.]
We have to gather up our strength.
I'm an impatient person to begin with,
but I've never felt this impatient before.
Let's go this way.
[The Grim Reaper has arrived!]
[Ambushes his third target, Gary!]
[Succeeds in hunting down his
third target, Gary.]
- What is this?
- Where's Hyo Joo?
Huh?
Where's Hyo Joo?
Wow, he's so good looking.
- Where's Hyo Joo?
- If you even casted a single vote against me!
- Kwang Soo, where's Hyo Joo?
- Hyo Joo's not next.
Hyo Joo's not next.
[His next target is Junho?]
[Grim Reaper chasing after his
sixth target, Hyo Joo?]
Hyo Joo's not next!
You have to go in order!
- Come here. Come here for a moment.
- Wait... he says I'm not next!
- I won't kill you. I'm not going to kill you.
- You can't oust her yet.
You can't eliminate her.
I'm going to propose something to you.
- I'll help you out.
- I'm so scared right now.
Okay, listen to me.
Junho... go get Junho for me.
- If you do, you'll become our teammate.
- Me?
You think she's going to fall for that?
That doesn't sound right.
I'm serious.
I'll seriously make you my spy.
- Wait a second...
- Then you'll become my spy.
[Lying through his teeth again
like he did to Jae Suk earlier.]
I'm serious.
You can trust me.
- I'll see you later.
- Wait...
[What is he talking about?]
Wow, I can't believe
Jung Woo Sung is here.
I saw him at Hyun Joon's wedding,
but he didn't mention coming on the show.
Oh my goodness!
[A quiet and gentle surprise.]
- Woo Sung...
- Do you really want me to oust you?
- I'm really going to rip it off.
- No, that's not it.
Do you really want me to tear it off?
- Woo Sung, please calm down.
- I really wanted to be calm about this.
- I wanted to be calm about it.
- Please don't get agitated.
You really caught me off guard right now.
- Woo Sung... that's not it.
- I asked you to get Gary for me.
- But I ousted Gary myself.
- You ousted him?
- I'll do better. I'm looking for others.
- You have to get the next one for me.
- Don't worry.
- Go get me the next person.
- We're on the same team. Don't worry.
And I'm going to give you a tip.
But Hyo Joo's also on our side.
- Really?
- Yes, Hyo Joo's on our side too.
I told Hyo Joo to find and bring
Junho to me.
- Hyo Joo as well?
- Yes.
So you have to bring Junho and
Kim Jong Kook over to me.
[Telling him to bring Junho and Jong Kook
over to him in that order.]
- So it's Junho then Jong Kook?
- You've got ten minutes.
Okay.
Fighting.
Wait...
This is a variety show,
but it feels too much like a movie.
Woo Sung.
I'm sorry.
[There's no need to be sorry...]
- We're on the same team now.
- Yes, I'm your spy.
Come on, we're on the same team.
So why are you doing that?
I'll see you later.
I'll bring them to you.
- And also...
- Yes?
Please stop turning off the
CCTV cameras now.
- But you told me to turn them off earlier.
- I...
I told you to turn them off earlier
because I didn't want them to be suspicious.
Okay.
I actually only turned off
about two cameras.
- I'm watching everything.
- You're watching everything?
- Me? How?
- My eyes are the CCTV cameras.
My eyes are CCTV cameras.
- What did you say?
- My eyes are the CCTV cameras.
Woo Sung, we're on the same team.
Of course, I'm with you.
- Hyo Joo too.
- Don't worry.
[Ten years off his life.]
See? He may scare me,
but he's not ousting me right now.
I don't know what the order is right now,
but it's not my turn right now.
I think I'm further down the list.
When is my turn?
When did he sneak up on me like that?
He startled me.
- Wow, today really is...
- I hear bells.
- I think it's going to be over soon.
- I'm sorry everyone.
[Visiting jail to greet everyone.]
Sorry for the late greetings.
Hello.
[Formally greeting one another since
they didn't have the chance to do it earlier.]
I know I should've greeted you first,
but I didn't get the chance.
I know.
But my mission had already started.
- And this building is so huge.
- So what's the order for the day?
The two people that were eliminated
gave me their death notes.
- So I was number one?
- Yes.
- They had a lot of grudge against you.
- Against me?
- Unbelievable. Against me?
- They were talking about you.
- About me?
- Yes.
- This is driving me crazy.
And they also have a lot of
grudge against you.
They said you're always disrespecting them.
- Me?
- Yes, they said you disrespected them.
- Then why me?
- They said you pay them no attention.
- Me?
- Yes.
They said you don't care what happens to them
and at least these two gives them attention.
They said that you have no
interest in them.
So they asked me to put you somewhere in
the middle of the list to oust you.
- That's what they said.
- I can't believe this.
I heard pretty much everything
that they had to say about you guys.
63 CCTV cameras are currently disabled.
Only 45 CCTV cameras left.
- So who's next on the list?
- You don't need to know that.
- Just rest easy over here.
- Woo Sung.
You have to keep this in mind. Ha Ha
and Kwang Soo will betray you for sure.
- Yes, okay.
- Be careful.
- You have to be careful of those two.
- Yes, I'll be careful.
- You have to be careful.
- Even his exit is cool.
- He's just so cool.
- The days of your motorcycle days...
So cool... I love you.
- Did you see how cool his exit was?
- When did I ever disrespect them?
Ha Dong Hoon!
- I can't believe it.
- At least you have a reason.
I just got ousted for no reason.
[On the other hand]
Nice.
There are so many.
[Junho searching through the radio
broadcasting room.]
Here's another one.
69 CCTV cameras currently disabled.
39 cameras left.
Jong Kook...
he's on the first lower level.
[Junho is searching through the garden
on the rooftop of the ninth floor.]
Okay.
Nice.
There he is again.
This is so frustrating!
I can't see anything!
[Amazing Running Man members.
Tirelessly finding and disabling the CCTV.]
Wait, isn't that Junho?
[Discovers the fourth target Junho
on the rooftop garden on the ninth floor.]
He's up in the garden.
- Ninth floor?
- Yes, on the ninth floor.
- Hey, but are you even doing your job right?
- Yes, I'm working really hard right now.
- I'm working really hard right now.
- Look at me right now.
I'm a totally different person now
than I was when I first left this room.
- You have to go oust him right now.
- Okay, I'll go oust him right now.
Just give me a minute.
I really want to oust him too right now.
I really want to oust him.
Do you have your name tag?
You're just going to wear that?
- Yeah, I'm just going to wear that.
- Woo Sung, ninth floor.
- Help me get this off.
- I got it, but help me get this off.
- Okay.
The person who eliminates him
gets this as a prize.
[A winning prize?
Woo Sung's sweat soaked shirt?]
You can have it.
- Ninth floor?
- Yes, ninth floor.
He turned everything off on the ninth floor.
But you should still go to the ninth floor.
- You have to run!
- Okay.
Ha Ha probably has no idea how much
I'm running around right now, does he?
This is scary. I don't know
why my heart's beating so fast.
Okay, I should head the other way.
I need to finish this up.
The weather is so nice.
It's so nice and cool.
Junho!
Junho.
- Junho.
- Yes, Woo Sung?
- Come here Junho, I have to talk to you.
- What are you doing here?
[Escaping back up onto the rooftop.]
[The chase is on!]
[A dead end!]
Junho.
- I have to talk to you.
- Excuse me?
[Grim Reaper also climbs up
onto the ledge.]
Come here.
[Nowhere to turn.]
- Please, Woo Sung, wait...
- Come here, Junho.
What's going on here?
[Succeeds at hunting down his
fourth target, Junho!]
That was totally scary.
Junho, out.
People still left are
Kim Jong Kook, Han Hyo Joo and Yoo Jae Suk.
No choice for Jong Kook either.
Kwang Soo has to go after him.
Lee Kwang Soo, what are you up to?
- Jong Kook.
- What are you up to?
[Tiger bothered my seeing
the Giraffe constantly walking around.]
- Who are you helping?
- I'm on your side!
- What?
- Kwang Soo.
Kwang Soo and Ha Ha are killing
the people that they have grudges against.
Did you hear that? I heard the bells.
Who is that?
[Mr. Capable still unaware of
who the Grim Reaper is.]
Up there... I see someone up there.
- I can hear the bells coming down.
- Jong Kook still doesn't know who it is?
- Jong Kook!
- Yeah?
Woo Sung is the Grim Reaper!
- Really?
- Yes.
- Seriously?
- Hi!
Hi!
[Grim Reaper Woo Sung beelines
for his fifth target, Jong Kook.]
[Mr. Capable fleeing with every ounce
of energy he has in his body.]
Woo Sung!
Why are you doing this to me?
Woo Sung, why are you doing this?
[Mr. Capable is quicker on the stairs!]
- Come here for a second.
- Why are you doing this?
- I'm a huge fan of yours!
- Wait.
- Hang on a second.
- I'm a huge fan of yours!
Ugh, this is so frustrating.
You know how in movies people are watching
from the surveillance room
and all the screens go out?
And while the main character doesn't know
what to do, he gets a sudden phone call?
'He's still alive!'
And everyone cheers?
I really want to try something like that.
What if all these screens go off?
Oh, I got a phone call.
Call Kwang Soo and ask him
where he is.
Kwang Soo is chasing after
Jong Kook right now.
If you find Kwang Soo,
you can find Jong Kook.
Jung Woo Sung!
Jong Kook!
Woo Sung!
Hurry!
Hello?
Woo Sung,
I'm chasing after Jong Kook right now.
Talk to me, Kwang Soo.
- Sixth floor. Sixth floor!
- Okay.
[Discovers Jong Kook off in the distance!]
[A Tiger that can't attack is no problem!]
[A huge help from the Giraffe's
relentless pursuit!]
[Succeeds in hunting down
his fifth target!]
You were my biggest hurdle.
[Kim Jong Kook- Out!]
Kim Jong Kook, out!
[Remaining Running Man members-
Hyo Joo and Jae Suk.]
Ha Ha and Lee Kwang Soo those scoundrels
are hell-bent on killing me.
This really is...
If I don't end this quickly, I'm dead.
I have to turn off all the CCTV cameras.
I think that's what my mission
is right now.
It's not like I can fight them off
with my own strength.
They're all so strong!
This is one of them, right?
It's so odd looking.
[Only cameras that are left now are the ones
hidden away in difficult spots.]
Ah... Jae Suk.
Don't you think I can get out
there too now?
Surveillance room is not much
help anymore.
It's coming from in there.
Hello.
Here's another one.
[Now heading off to where
Ha Ha's voice is coming from.]
Jae Suk is on the 13th floor.
Right here!
There you are.
- You startled me.
- What are you doing?
You're not supposed to be in here.
Hey, hang on a second.
You little scoundrels!
- You two wrote this, didn't you?
- That's right!
Yes, we wrote it.
What are you going to do about it?
- You deserve it!
- What is this?
- What are you guys doing?
- We're members of Jung Woo Sung's fan club!
Wait, you guys dare to write
my name in here?
Give it back!
Where did Kwang Soo go?
I don't know!
Where did he go?
First floor lower level.
Wait, where...
where is that right now?
- And where is that supposed to be?
- You can't be looking at that!
Hurry up and get out of here!
Get out!
Just get out of here.
[Chasing him out of the surveillance room.]
- You can't do that.
- Hey.
- Are you...
- You're last!
It would serve you to turn off
all the cameras quickly!
We wanted you to quake in fear.
You just wait and see.
You just wait.
- He's coming for you.
- You just wait.
Where was that spot?
It looked like it was underneath
a desk somewhere.
The other looked like a helipad.
Up on the rooftop somewhere.
I just saw it.
I saw one around something like this.
[Bingo]
Hey!
Are you watching this?
You're finished.
You'll soon be finished.
Jae Suk is up on the rooftop right now.
You're finished.
You'll soon be finished.
He just turned off the camera
up on the rooftop.
[Should've locked the door...]
He saw the screens in here.
[Hyo Joo turns off another one.]
100 cameras currently disabled.
8 left remaining.
[Only eight are left!]
She found another one.
One, two, three, four, five, six,
seven left.
[Will he finish the hunt first,
or will the CCTV's be disabled first?]
There.
There it is.
Ha Ha, are you watching?
You and Kwang Soo are finished.
What did you say?
What did you just say?
[Only six left remaining.]
There it is!
Ha Ha.
- Yes, Woo Sung?
- Where's Hyo Joo?
Hyo Joo?
I can't see Hyo Joo.
We've only got five cameras left.
[Difficult to locate them with
only five cameras left remaining.]
- Should I call her out?
- Try the second floor.
Yes.
- We have to scatter about.
- Okay.
The ones that are left are on 12th floor,
21st floor...
second, and sixth floor.
And Jae Suk found this room.
[12th, 21st, second and sixth floor!]
Sixth, sixth... let's go to sixth.
[Hyo Joo's already on the 12th floor.]
[Discovered!]
Wow, there it is.
[Jae Suk finally finds
the one on the sixth floor.]
Have a good day.
[Only two left!]
106 CCTV currently disabled.
Only two CCTV's left remaining.
That's really tricky.
- Its Jae Suk!
- This is the screen I saw earlier.
I was wondering where this one was.
[CCTV on the second floor is turned off!]
Woo Sung.
Second floor. He's on the second floor.
Second floor!
- Second floor?
- Yes, you have to get down there quickly.
107 CCTV currently disabled.
Only one CCTV's left remaining.
[Once all 108 cameras are shut off,
the Grim Reaper can also be hunted down!]
[Only one CCTV left!]
- Don't you think you're being too much?
- About what?
[No matter how angry Woo Sung is,
he still can't oust him out of order.]
- I'm guessing it's not my turn yet?
- I'll give you one last chance.
Chance at what?
- You'd better not let me catch you.
- Okay, I understand.
[Warning!
Do not get caught!]
Yes, I understand.
There's only one camera left.
- Then it's war.
- We'll see you later.
- We already are at war.
- But it'll start for real in a bit.
I understand.
But you'd better get Hyo Joo first.
Yes, I will.
- I'm going to get going now.
- Go ahead.
- Where are you going?
- I'm going to walk around.
I need to go catch Hyo Joo.
He scared me.
He really scared me.
I'm going to need Hyo Joo's help.
I don't think I can handle him on my own.
Jung Woo Sung is really strong.
- Jae Suk got everything.
- This is 21st floor!
The one that's left is up on the 21st floor.
[The last CCTV still left.]
It's all over once this one is shut off.
You can't even do anything then.
- Neither one of us can do anything.
- Okay, I'm going to call Woo Sung.
Since I saw Jung Woo Sung
down below earlier...
But I didn't see anything earlier
when I searched through this floor.
[Down to the 21st floor
where the last camera is located!]
Someone already got to this one.
They're all shut off already.
Finding the last one
is going to be really hard.
They're up here?
- I wonder if something's up here.
- Wait.
Something must be up here.
Something must be up here, isn't it?
Isn't that why you're up here?
[This is it!]
[Answer your phone, Woo Sung!]
Something must be in here.
Why isn't the call going through?
Why isn't he answering his phone?
Why?
He must be out of his mind!
[Find the last remaining CCTV camera!]
Why isn't Woo Sung answering
his phone?
- Here it is!
- No!
[Jae Suk discovers the last remaining CCTV!]
I found the last one!
[The last remaining CCTV is turned off!]
You're finished.
- Here it is! I found it!
- No!
What the heck?
He found the last one?
[108 CCTV cameras...
All are now shut off!]
Hello?
Where are you right now?
I just got down to the 13th floor,
but why weren't you answering your phone?
All the cameras have been shut off.
- All the cameras have been shut off?
- All of them. They're all shut off.
If they're all shut off,
you should tell me and come out here.
It was the last one
that was up on the 21st floor.
Okay, I got it.
You can just stay there.
What does that mean?
All the CCTV cameras are now off.
The Grim Reaper may now be hunted down.
[Running Man members are now allowed
to hunt down the Grim Reaper!]
You may now hunt down
the Grim Reaper.
Oh my goodness!
You scared me!
Hyo Joo, please...
I got the last one.
I turned off the last one.
All of them have been shut off.
We can eliminate Ha Ha now.
What?
You can oust me?
[Eliminated twosome are already ousted,
but she's just taking her anger out on them.]
- How dare you do this to us?
- I just got out here.
- Ha Ha!
- What?
I just got out here.
Do you know what Jung Woo Sung
is putting us through right now?
- Do you?
- Do you know how this all happened?
This is your punishment for
how you treat me.
All the CCTV cameras are now off.
[Jae Suk and Hyo Joo are now able to
attack Woo Sung now.]
But Woo Sung's so scary.
- We're in big trouble.
- He's so scary.
But Woo Sung has to eliminate Hyo Joo first
before he can eliminate me, right?
That's correct.
I walked down a flight of stairs and saw
Ha Ha walking around the 21st floor.
So I thought he was there to find the last
camera and that's when I found it.
[The Grim Reaper arrives.]
Hyo Joo.
They were just here.
[Grim Reaper's target is his
sixth target, Hyo Joo!]
Hyo Joo, get out that door right now.
- We have to stick together, Hyo Joo.
- Come on!
Out of the way, Ha Ha.
I'll go first.
How are we going to oust him?
How?
- Let's hide in here.
- Here, Hyo Joo.
[Hyo Joo seeking refuge in a small room.]
Woo Sung.
[Can't get Jae Suk now...]
You have to get Hyo Joo.
- Where's Hyo Joo?
- I know you can't get me right now.
[Jae Suk pushing Woo Sung away
from where Hyo Joo is hiding.]
I know you can't oust me right now.
I know it's useless for you to
oust me right now.
- But what I'm saying is...
- I got it.
[Maybe Jae Suk should just attack
the Grim Reaper now.]
Where are you going?
Where are you planning on going?
[Grim Reaper is in danger!]
- Okay.
- Wait a second.
Wait, you don't have to
use your strength on me now.
Where do you think you're going?
Where are you going?
Where?
Woo Sung!
- Is he gone?
- He's gone.
I thought I was dead.
Hyo Joo... if we work together,
we may be able to beat him.
I know.
We can't beat him by ourselves.
- There he is again.
- Hello.
I'm just an innocent bystander
just trying to get by.
What are you doing?
Wait.
[Ridding him of his headset and
the phone so that he can't call Woo Sung.]
You can't talk to him anymore.
- You were going to call him, right?
- I'm confiscating it.
I won't call him.
- Just get in there.
- Wait.
- What are you doing? Hang on.
- Come on, Ha Ha.
I just got out here.
- What are you doing? I'll just go.
- Just go in there.
Come on, guys!
Are you kidding me right now?
- Let go!
- Get in there!
You have to at least let my cameraman in.
Okay, come in.
[It's their nature to still worry about
their cameras in these situation.]
Just give me my phone.
Give me my phone back!
Seriously!
I'll grab him for you.
I can't rip it off myself.
Stay in hiding and when you see me with
a hold on Woo Sung, come out and rip it off.
Got it?
Okay.
I wonder where I should hide?
Let's go down to the 13th floor.
I didn't know it would be down to
a fight between life and death like this.
Every time you come on the show...
it happens every time you're on the show.
- I know, right?
- Every single time.
I don't know why I play
with such crazy determination.
- You really are something.
- What have I even got to earn by doing this?
It's just in your nature to do it.
[Having somehow escaped...]
Woo Sung.
Jae Suk is heading this way.
Woo Sung!
Jae Suk is coming! Come in here!
[Luring him in to another location.]
Stand here and block them off.
- Stay in hiding.
- Woo Sung.
- Like I told you earlier...
- I must've forgotten again.
I can't oust him before
Hyo Joo, right?
I must've forgotten already.
[Hiding to ambush him?]
I thought that maybe I could
oust you now.
[Right in front of her sight...]
[is Woo Sung's name tag!]
[But loses her chance with him
moving too far out of her reach.]
- Woo Sung.
- Why don't you go rest for now?
- Its almost over now.
- Yes, so go get some rest.
[Jae Suk, I'm over here!]
- Where are you going?
- Me?
- Yes.
- I have to go somewhere.
I have to tell you as another human being,
that you're really cool.
Yes, thank you.
- You're really handsome.
- What?
You're not only just handsome,
but you're really cool too.
But why are you so sweaty?
It's just because my t-shirt is really thick.
Where are you going?
Come on, let's just talk for a bit.
Okay, you can talk to me from over there.
[Staying alert since he doesn't know
where Hyo Joo will attack from.]
Come on!
Why is he running?
Did you see him bump into this?
- He bumped himself?
- Do you know what he just did here?
It was like a scene from an action film?
He opened like this.
There's no reason for him to do that.
Why did...
[Every move he makes is like a scene
out of an action film.]
He could've just opened it like this.
Seriously!
[Grim Reaper Woo Sung is staying
more cautious.]
[Grim Reaper Woo Sung is discovered!]
Where are you going?
- I'm looking for Han Hyo Joo.
- What?
- I have to find Han Hyo Joo.
- Why are you searching for Hyo Joo so much?
[Jae Suk distracting him with a conversation
to give Hyo Joo time to sneak up on Woo Sung.]
Why did you go through the door like you were
in an action film? What if you got hurt?
- Me?
- Yes.
[Hyo Joo springs her attack!]
[Grim Reaper is only attacking Hyo Joo!]
- Woo Sung... Woo Sung!
- Hang on.
[Fight off their attack while
attacking Hyo Joo simultaneously!]
[My goodness!
Fights off both at the same time!]
Hyo Joo!
[Hyo Joo in danger!]
- Wait!
- Sorry, Hyo Joo!
What are you doing!
[Just then!]
[Jae Sung attacks Woo Sung!]
I can't get it!
[Jae Suk and Hyo Joo at the same time!]
[Woo Sung lifts both of them up
off the ground!]
[While trying to lift them up...]
[The Grim Reaper gets ousted instead!]
We did it!
- We did it!
- What the heck is this?
I thought I was going to die!
I thought I was going to die.
Hyo Joo, are you okay?
Seriously... your strength!
Anyways, we won!
[Jae Suk and Hyo Joo are the
final survivors!]
Ugh, I lost!
For some reason, whenever we're in
SBS Mokdong office...
There's a special connection that
I have to this building.
It was a total movie.
Watch the episode when it airs.
He doesn't just open the door
like the rest of us.
[Action is his second nature.]
And I hate standing next to him more than
getting my name tag ripped off.
It's because he's way too good looking.
I'm sorry, but can you go
stand over there?
Please go stand over there next to them.
Stand right next to Jae Suk.
- He really looks so ugly.
- Look at how ugly Jae Suk looks!
[Total opposites]
[A world of difference]
As for the prize, all seven of the members
with the exception of the two in the back...
everyone including Junho and Hyo Joo
will each receive a prize for today's mission.
[Even though he lost,
Grim Reaper Jung Woo Sung was perfect!]
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Running Man running through the sky?]
[The one who faces their fear
will get to become one with the sky.]
[Jung Woo Sung in the sky.]
Did I get it?
[Who in the world he is?
This man lets it all go.]
[Introducing the real Jung Woo Sung
to the variety land.]
[Next Week on Running Man-
Comedian, Jung Woo Sung.]
[And...]
The worldwide superstar,
Park Ji Sung!
[Captain Park Ji Sung returns!]
[A man returning with a
shocking revelation!]
[SBS, I love you.]
- Say it to the camera.
- I love you.
[Park Ji Sung has changed!]
[Coming soon-
the Romantic Park Ji Sung]