Running Man
[Time- One chilly fall day.]
[Location- Arari Village in Kangwondo.]
[Arrival of the first target.]
Go into the village and find the flag
with your name on it.
[Order- Find the flag
with their own name on it.]
[Update on the situation-
Targets still unaware of the situation.]
[Target Number One: Yoo Hyuk.
Target Number Two: Big-nose.]
[Target Number Three: Gary.]
Go into the village and find the flag
with your name on it.
I have to hurry?
[All the members rush into the suspicious
park without even knowing the reason for it.]
Where am I supposed to go?
Where?
What a nice day.
[Update on the situation- The targets are
clueless about what's to happen.]
- Don't you think you're rushing too much?
- Where are these flags?
[Target locations are confirmed.]
There it is!
I see it!
[Target Number Five: Ha Ha.
Discovers his own flag.]
Hello.
[Picks up his flag...]
There it is!
[One by one, the members start to
discover their own flags.]
- I got it!
- There it is!
[However, their flag finding mission
scatters them away from one another.]
[Just then...]
[Helmet]
[Padlock]
Why are you putting this helmet on me?
Jae Suk!
- What are you doing?
- What are you doing? What is this?
[Everyone gets fitted with
their own helmets.]
- What are you doing?
- Ouch! My ear!
I just went and got my hair done
at the salon this morning!
[All seven members are fitted
with their own helmets.]
What is going on here?
Why are you putting this on me?
What is this?
Move on to the front lawn
of this village immediately.
To the front lawn?
Where's the front lawn?
- There.
- Over there?
[Off to the gathering location thanks to
the help from the kind helmet agent.]
What is this?
Isn't this the front lawn?
[Going to the location
where they're told to go...]
Hey... this is like that movie, 'Saw'.
[Just what is the purpose of these helmets
that they've been forced to wear?]
- What is this?
- Look at this thing.
Why are they making us
wear these helmets?
[A mysterious situation.
Just what is their mission?]
We're all here now.
So what is this all about?
[Now that everyone's been
gathered around...]
[Quite an adorable army of
rainbow helmet soldiers...]
- We have guests today.
- I see someone coming.
I can see someone coming this way.
[Huh?]
[Today's guests rolling up in
a stylish celebrity van.]
Hello.
[A warm and charismatic city man-
Today's hottest star, Joo Sang Wook.]
[But...]
[Huh?]
[Even the charismatic actor wasn't able to
avoid the colored helmet.]
He looks cute in his helmet.
The helmet feels a bit too tight
on my head.
[Having transformed into a cutie pie
in his sky blue helmet.]
[And...]
[There's one more guest!]
[Free spirited, Yang Dong Geun.]
[Charisma]
[But even he isn't able to
avoid the helmet.]
[Flustered]
[Finally able to get the helmet on him
after some struggling.]
I can't believe how good
he looks in his helmet.
This is the first time I've ever seen anyone
who looks better in a helmet than Gary does.
He's ruining everything for me today!
He's showing you up, Gary.
He looks better than you in the helmet.
[Dong Geun threatening
Gary's character on this show.]
I'm kind of regretting the fact
that I've become even better looking.
[Um... I don't think there's any
cause for worry there...]
What are we going to be doing today
with these helmets on?
What's the reason for even the guests
having to put these helmets on?
This helmet is really hurting my head.
[Just then...]
Your helmets...
[Hm? A moth?]
- What is it?
- I think that's a bee?
No, you really had something
on your head.
I'm serious, there really was something.
[Giraffe seizes his chance,
and attacks the Tiger on the head.]
I'm going to make sure to catch a bug,
and set it on top of your head today.
I promise you.
Today's race...
is titled, The Helmet Race.
[Today's mission-
Escape the helmet race.]
[The race will be performed with
the helmet locked on their heads.]
[Only the person who comes in at
first place in each of the missions...]
[will get the chance to choose a key to
try to unlock the helmet from their heads.]
I guess I won't even get to try then.
There will be a total of four missions today.
This is an individual race.
If the person that comes in at
first place during the first mission
happens to find their own key in their
first attempt to unlock the helmet...
Little butterfly...
- That looked like CG.
- The butterfly just flew away.
[The butterfly flies away... and
comes back to land on Giraffe's nose.]
[Oh ho...]
I really think that Kwang Soo has
the God of entertainment looking out for him.
- Are you okay?
- Jong Kook mentioned that he'd do that.
I'm so jealous.
I really am jealous that all the funny
stuff is always happening to you.
[Unbelievable that the butterfly would pick
that moment of all times to land on his nose.]
I can't believe that the butterfly would land
on Gary first, and go right to Kwang Soo.
['Gae-butterfly', then completes the flight
by becoming the Kwang-butterfly'.]
There will be a total of four missions.
If the person who comes in at first place
during the first of those four missions
happens to find their own key
right from the get go...
that person can take off their helmet on the
spot and move right to the final location.
That would be such a huge advantage!
[For the first time in Running Man history...]
[someone will be given
rest time during filming.]
But that person will be
losing out on screen time.
[Will it be the screen time... or rest time?]
But on the flipside,
if a person doesn't come in at first place
or even if they do, if they
don't manage to find their own key
that person will have no choice
but to film
all four missions with the helmet
on their heads throughout the whole day.
[The ever tightening helmet on their heads...
do you want to escape from it?]
[If so, then succeed your mission!]
[Escape the Helmet race- Start!]
[Today's race is an individual race.]
Is this it?
[To start off, everyone is given
a random key.]
[But no one knows who's helmet
that key belongs to.]
Am I the only one this is
being given to?
- No.
- Oh, everyone's getting one?
I guess... it makes sense
that everyone's getting one.
It wouldn't be fair if I was
the only person getting it.
Wow... it would be so awesome
if I were to find the key on my first try.
It's possible that this key could be
for my helmet, right?
[If their first key fits their own helmet then
they can escape before the race even starts.]
Seriously?
I can try?
[Could it be?]
You can't break it.
[All nine members are each given a key.]
All four of today's races will have
an option for you to choose from.
What is it?
- You have to choose one of these two.
- Okay.
- And you can go do the mission you choose.
- Really?
[Must choose one of the two mission cards
for each of their missions.]
What is this?
'Grab bare hands'?
Dead Run?
What is this?
- Have we ever told you what they are?
- You're not going to tell me?
Of course not.
I'll go with 'Grab bare hands' mission.
I'm unbeatable when it comes to
hands and feet.
Grab bare hands.
I have to choose one of these two?
[Which of the two missions
will Dong Geun choose?]
Bare hands mission.
Running is too exhausting.
Take your card and be on your way.
You each have your own car to take.
Okay. I will see you all later.
Have a great day.
Are you my VJ for the day?
It's nice to meet you.
I have a feeling that
it's going to be a tough day.
[Forming a good relationship
with his personal VJ for the day.]
I wonder where I'll be heading.
[Escape the helmet race- Start.]
I wonder what will happen today?
Rather than grabbing or catching something...
even though it may be tiring,
running is a better choice.
Kangwondo, seriously...
it's so beautiful here.
So pretty.
[Nature's true beauty that can be seen
outside their car windows.]
Hey, you have to film me too.
Stop just filming the scenery outside.
Even though the scenery is really nice,
I have to be on the show too.
Seriously... you really are
being too much.
To be honest, I'm not really sure about it.
They were talking about some keys?
But to be perfectly honest, I have
no idea what they were talking about.
Maybe I should try unlocking it
with this key.
No, I can't do that.
Because what if it actually unlocks it?
[Sang Wook is proving to be
quite the chatterbox.]
I'm starting to get a slight headache.
But I'm not sure what to do.
Should I get rid of this right away?
If I get the helmet off too quickly,
then I wouldn't be on the show much, right?
That wouldn't be good.
Here I am talking to myself,
and no one is even responding to me.
I need to get to the mission quickly.
Then I'd have someone to talk to.
[Charismatic Doctor Kim Do Han...]
[In actuality, he's a nonstop chatterbox?]
No.
It's over there.
[Jungsungun's 'G' village.
Jae Suk arrives at the 'Dead run' mission.]
What is this?
- Where is it?
- Do you see it over there?
What's that?
[Deep in the woods... a chicken farm?]
[Cock-a-doodle-doo!
Welcome!]
[You have to untie five ribbons that
are tied around the chickens' feet.]
You want me to untie those ribbons?
- I can't touch chickens.
- I'm too scared to touch chickens.
[Of all people, it has to be the two cowards
who are too afraid to touch chickens.]
- This is absurd.
- You know I can't touch chickens.
You only have to touch the ribbons
to untie them from their feet.
Those chickens aren't going to
allow us to just though their feet.
Don't you know how fast
those chickens are?
Had I known it was going to be like this,
I would've gone with the other mission.
[This is why the mission is called,
the 'Dead run' mission.]
[Meanwhile, the 'Bare hands' mission is...]
Bare hands?
[Kkuk is in the process of dressing
himself in the necessary gear.]
[Just what is this mission
going to be?]
You have to catch the fish
with your bare hands.
[Bare hands mission-
Catch three fish with your bare hands.]
You have to catch three fish with your
bare hands. Then you will be given a key.
Don't you know I used to be on Family Outing?
I'm good at things like this.
[Jungsun Namyun village's pride and joy,
Trout catching.]
Look at this.
[The water is so clear
that it's practically see-through.]
[Good luck catching me.]
I'm coming after you!
Your bright colored skin is making it
easy for me to spot you.
This isn't easy.
This is hard!
This is quite hard!
This is hard.
I'm in trouble. This is pretty hard.
What are you doing, Jong Kook?
- Are you fishing?
- I'm trying to catch these trouts.
- What?
- We have to catch these trouts.
- Goldfish?
[No, trouts are about a hundred times
faster than the goldfish.]
They're so fast!
And their colors are hard to see.
So it makes it hard for us to
see them in the water.
What do we have to catch?
Is it even possible to catch them?
- This is no joke.
- Should we corner them somewhere?
We have to corner them somewhere.
I want you to go stand over there.
It's so weird because when I looked from
up there, I saw a ton of fish in the water.
You should move slower.
We should just wait around until
Jong Kook tires out all the fish.
[Just then...]
[He catches one...
but loses it because of the Giraffe.]
- I had it!
- It's still right there.
[A tit for tat in their attempt.]
Run away!
Run away, little trout!
My hand just touched it!
[Loud screams that can be heard
from all over the woods.]
- Look at that one!
- Why?
- What is that thing doing?
- What is it doing?
Why is it doing that?
- It was attacking the other one's head.
- I can't believe I saw that.
[Totally freaked out.]
Did you see how it was pounding
on the head of the other one?
Did you see how that one chicken was
pounding the other one to the ground?
That's no joke.
[That is the power of the UFC league rooster.]
I don't think we can do five ribbons.
How are we supposed to do five ribbons?
Can you lower the number
of ribbons for us?
- I can't even touch them with my hands.
- Song Ji Hyo's really good at catching them.
Ji Hyo needs to come here.
We need her to come and help us.
[We miss you, Ji Hyo.]
[Just then, someone else arrives
on location.]
- Ji Hyo.
- Ji Hyo, is it you?
- Come and catch these chickens for us.
- Ji Hyo!
Is it Ji Hyo?
[Third member for the mission,
Chatterbox, Sang Wook.]
- Suk Jin.
- Are you good at catching chickens?
- What?
- Catch what?
- Chickens.
- Chickens?
- Yeah.
How are we supposed to catch chickens?
With our hands?
- Yeah.
- We have to catch them and undo the ribbon.
Can you catch these chickens or not?
I've never done it before.
- Seriously?
- No, I haven't.
- But you look like you're pretty confident.
- Grab these chickens by what?
- Is that how you're coming in?
- Is that not how I'm supposed to come in?
No, that's not how you're
supposed to come in.
- What are we supposed to catch again?
- Aren't you scared?
- I've never once in my life done this before.
- Hey!
Do you see that white chicken
over there?
That one held down another chicken with its
foot and pecked the other one to the ground.
These chickens don't mess around.
Isn't the owner of these
chickens around?
- You don't think you can catch them?
- No, I know I can do it.
I've never caught them before,
but do I just grab them by their necks?
No, you have to grab them
around their body.
- Ah, by the body?
- Yeah, the body.
That one over there looks like
it could even fly out of here.
I just told you.
That one over there is a fighter.
- That scared me.
- That one just flies around here.
You can't provoke those two chickens.
- I'll try catching this one first.
- Okay, try it.
[Chicken novice cautiously making
his approach towards a chicken.]
I'm too scared to touch them.
[Huh? He succeeds in his first attempt?]
- That chicken is really docile.
- This isn't too difficult.
Hey, stay still.
[Chatterbox Sang Wook
conversing with the chicken.]
Getting this ribbon off is actually
harder than catching the chicken.
- Yeah, that's hard.
- They shouldn't have tied it in a knot.
Hold still.
I'll let you go in a minute.
[Carefully working through his mission...
Good Doctor, Sang Wook.]
- Aren't you scared?
- What?
No, not really.
Okay, I got it.
[Sang Wook gets his first ribbon.]
Aren't you scared?
Aren't you scared at all?
To be honest, I am pretty scared.
[Only been screaming for
the past 30 minutes.]
I'm so annoyed!
- I caught one!
- You got it!
I got it!
[Now all he has to do is to put
the trout into his own basket...]
[Trout... breaks free.]
[Let me go...]
[Don't go...]
They're seriously so fast.
They're not even giving us a chance.
[Kkuk is still single-mindedly
chasing after the orange trout.]
[With only one hand!]
[Will the Giraffe disrupt him again?]
[But Mr. Capable has the trout in his
tight grasp and isn't letting go.]
[Kkuk succeeds in catching the first
of his three fishes.]
[Just then,
Dong Geun also arrives on location.]
Wow, look at how big they are.
- How many do we need to catch?
- It's really hard trying to catch them.
- Over there.
- Dong Geun won't be able to do this.
[Trout with torpedo-like speed.]
[Just then...]
[Mr. Capable gets the feel for it,
and catches his second trout!]
Wait, this isn't my basket!
[Darn...]
Who's basket is this?
It's my basket.
- One fish for Yang Dong Geun.
- This isn't fair!
[Kkuk's mistake from being too hasty.]
I worked so hard to catch that.
I'll help you to catch a fish.
[Dong Geun already has one fish in his basket
even though he just arrived, thanks to Kkuk.]
[Ro-Ro also arrives on location to catch
his share of the fish for the mission.]
I had a feeling this may be it,
but I didn't think I'd be doing it for real.
[Total concentration.]
[Dong Geun...
could he have caught one already?]
Don't move.
Don't you dare go anywhere.
You caught one!
[Succeeds in bare hand fishing
on his very first attempt!]
That's your second fish, Dong Geun.
- This one's mine, right?
- That's yours.
- That's not yours.
- No, this one is mine.
[Two trout already in his basket.]
Hey, we have to corral them towards
where we can see them.
- I caught one!
- How did you catch that?
[Giraffe finally succeeds
in catching his first trout.]
The shallow part of the water?
[Wait...]
[If Dong Geun catches one more fish,
then the mission is all over...]
[Giraffe seems to be up to something as he
makes his way towards Dong Geun's basket.]
[And then...]
[He pushes Dong Geun's basket over!]
Wow, they're so fast!
[The owner of the basket who is
oblivious to what just happened.]
[Giraffe's trickster DNA is
up to no good as always...]
[Sorry, Dong Geun.]
[Just then.]
I almost had it!
I got one!
[What in the world!
Scaredy cat Ro-Ro catches his first trout?]
You have to corral them to a corner.
I know how to catch them now.
I know what I have to do.
Look at this!
All of Dong Geun's fish are gone!
[Discovers Dong Geun's upturned basket.]
- Huh! What happened?
- I swear to you that I didn't do it.
- I swear, I didn't do it.
- What happened? Who did it?
- This one is mine.
- My basket!
- All your fish...
- Who did this?
- You lost both your fish.
- Maybe the current is too strong.
I think we should put some rocks
in our baskets to weigh it down.
[Gullible Dong Geun putting rocks in
his basket without a word.]
I think it's because the current
must be too strong.
That's too bad, Dong Geun.
[Just a lonely single rock in his basket...]
[Yes! I didn't get caught!]
[Just then...]
[Reverent...]
Look, he's praying.
The fighter of the wind.
[Seeking inner peace and solace out of
the shock from the basket incident?]
I'm sorry to say this
but if people were to see what you're doing,
they'd think you're filming a documentary.
[Human theater-
The transferor and the Trout.]
You look like a spiritual master.
[An ascetic arrives.]
[Blank Ji is the last member to arrive
on location for the 'Dead run' mission.]
- Ji Hyo!
- I'm so glad to see you!
- Come here, Ji Hyo!
- What's wrong?
- Ji Hyo, come here.
- We need you to catch these chickens for us.
- You're good at catching chicken.
- We need you to catch some chickens for us.
You're all standing around like that because
you're too afraid to catch some chickens?
Ji Hyo, please catch these chickens
for us. I'm begging you.
- Let's all do our own work, okay?
- Come on!
Come on, please!
Just catch one for me, Ji Hyo.
[Leaving the whiny cowardly brothers behind,
Ji Hyo forges ahead to do her mission.]
- Is this fun for you?
- Yes.
You don't think this is fun, Jae Suk?
How can you think this is fun?
I'm about to lose my mind right now.
Look at how she's laughing as she
goes after those chickens.
[Oh my goodness.]
I'm sorry, little chicken.
- She's starting, isn't she?
- I'm so sorry, chicken.
You see her, don't you?
Isn't she something else?
Look at her.
Do you see her?
Do things like that not even
scare you?
- I'm sorry, I'll take this off of you.
- Are you not even afraid of that thing?
What's scary about what I'm doing?
- I just feel bad for it.
- They're seriously so fast.
- They really are very fast.
- I don't want to touch them.
[Current ribbon count-
Jae Suk:0 Big-nose:0 Sang Wook:4 Ji Hyo:1]
- Look, this one laid an egg!
- Where?
- This one laid an egg.
- Seriously?
- It laid an egg.
- Wow!
[My goodness!]
It laid an egg before it ran away.
Look at that.
- It laid an egg?
- It laid an egg.
This one was born on the battlefield.
Here, try it.
- Try it while it's still warm.
- No, thank you.
- I can't believe it laid an egg like that.
- Are you going to try that?
Well, I am pretty thirsty.
[A fresh and warm egg...]
That's very good for your health.
- I can feel the energy coursing through me.
- I can't believe you did that.
I can't believe you ate the egg
that the chicken just laid.
Maybe I can win this race today.
[The two white roosters having shown
their pounding fighting skills.]
We will count it as two ribbons if you can
untie the ribbons wrapped around their feet.
I don't think I can even touch
those roosters.
Okay.
[I will channel the energy from the egg,
and catch those roosters!]
[Show me what you've got.]
[Egg powered Big-nose vs. UFC Rooster]
[Rooster's agile evasive moves.]
Let's see who can win this thing.
That chicken's muscles remind me
of Jong Kook's muscles.
[Oh! He caught it!]
[Infused by the energy from the egg,
Big-nose gets it done!]
I finally did it.
I won the battle.
[Whatever!
I just gave you a break.]
[Current Trout Count- Dong Geun:0, Gary:2,
Jong Kook:2, Kwang Soo:1, Ha Ha: 2]
[Dong Geun's luck having ran out ever since
Kwang Soo's dirty little trick.]
Are you the one who turned Dong Geun's
basket over earlier?
Me?
- No, it wasn't me.
- I have a feeling it was you.
- How could you do that to him?
- No, I didn't do that.
- What?
- I was just trying to catch my own fish.
- It was a total mistake.
- We've finally found the culprit.
[Kkuk's suspicions are confirmed,
and the culprit is revealed.]
Hey, Dong Geun is
the fighter of the wind.
Don't you know that
he's the fighter of the wind?
[So you're the culprit...]
It was an accident.
[Immediate punishment.]
It was an accident!
- Nice!
- It's the fighter!
[Is Dong Geun transforming into
a fighter of the wind?]
What should I do with him?
[I'm so sorry!]
[Kkuk's current count is at two.
This trout would make him the winner!]
Move.
Defense!
[Let's go!]
[Kkuk's ambush move!]
[Trout... goal in!]
Kim Jong Kook, first place.
[Bare hands mission- Kkuk wins!]
Bye, guys.
[Freeing the trout that they've caught.]
Dong Geun found himself a new pet.
I've never seen anyone treating a trout
like a pet before.
Look at the way he's petting that fish.
He really is like an ascetic.
You will be given your
first chance to free yourself.
[Kkuk is given his chance to find the key
to his helmet for coming in at first place.]
[Just who would have the key that could
unlock the helmet from Kkuk's head?]
For some reason,
I feel like Dong Geun would have it.
Give me yours!
[Jong Kook chooses Kwang Soo's key.]
Go on and try to unlock the lock.
I feel like it's going to fit.
[If this key is the right one,
Jong Kook can free himself and rest!]
Let me try to turn the key.
[Could it be?]
- Is it not working?
- That mustn't be it.
[It's not the right key.]
Lee Kwang Soo.
You have to go retrieve your key.
[Current ribbon count-
Jae Suk:0, Big-nose:2, Sang Wook:4, Ji Hyo:3]
- Would that kick back?
- Of course.
- Chickens do that?
- It would kick him in the face?
- Of course, it would.
Chickens do that?
What are you two doing?
[About to faint over.]
- Seriously!
- Why would you do that to us?
Seriously!
I'm done.
[Sang Wook succeeds his ribbon mission.]
- What would you like to do?
- Me?
[Dead run mission winner, Sang Wook.]
[Who's key will he select?]
I don't want it to open my lock.
Why do you keep thinking that
your lock is going to open?
- That's not going to happen.
- That would be next to impossible.
I'm going to try.
But I think it's a high probability.
- Is that the one you're choosing?
- Yes, I choose this one.
- You want me to do it for you?
- I'll turn the key for you.
[No way...]
- It opened! It opened.
- Seriously?
- You're lying.
- It didn't open.
Why are you lying to us like that?
- What's wrong with you?
- What are you doing?
- When did you learn to lie like that?
- Is the mission all over now?
- After getting the five ribbons?
- When did you turn into such a good liar?
[Lying Sang Wook also fails to
escape from his locked helmet.]
[Time to choose their second mission.]
Ah... a 'standup competition',
and 'lie down competition'?
['Standup competition' or
'Lie down competition'.]
[A simple method of choosing
for this former doctor.]
I didn't see what I chose.
[Sang Wook chooses the standup competition.]
I'm going to go with the
standup competition.
Lying down would be more comfortable
than remaining standing up, wouldn't it?
Okay, lie down competition.
I'm going to go with this one.
The lie down competition.
[Off to the second mission!]
[Meanwhile]
Master!
Excuse me, Elder!
What are you doing?
I feel so at peace out here.
[Filming forgotten,
Master Yang deep in self-meditation.]
He's so peculiar.
[Standup competition vs. Lie down competition.]
I really thought that once I won the mission,
the key I chose would've unlocked it.
[Sang Wook reverting back to his
chatter mode once back in the car.]
I was surprised when the lock didn't open.
It made me realize this is what
Sonogong used to feel back in the day.
[The originator of
the helmet fashion, Sonogong.]
[100% facial match!]
I really want to get a lot of screen time.
I wonder how Dong Geun is doing.
[This man is focusing all his
concentration on his driving.]
[Right]
[Straight]
[Left]
This must be it.
What is this now?
What are we doing here?
[Play tug of war, and the first person
to ring the bell with their head wins.]
- Ugh, seriously.
- We're in trouble if Jong Kook shows up.
Suk Jin, isn't it so pretty here?
[This is one chatter loving duo.]
I bet the scenery must be outstanding
once the leaves start changing colors.
[Falling in love with the beauty of the area.]
[The local scenery will soon turn
into a feast for the eyes in the fall.]
- Did you know that I was born here?
- This is your hometown?
- Yeah, this is my hometown.
- Kangwondo is your hometown?
Kangwondo, Jungsun-Gu, Dongyeon Hwa,
308-1.
Hello, Jungsun!
- I'm from Jungsun!
- Jungsun is the best!
Kangwondo, Jungsun-Gu, Dongyeon Hwa,
308-1.
- Jungsun, fighting!
- Fighting!
Another celebrity born from Jungsun.
Did you know that this was
Ji Suk Jin's hometown?
No, we didn't!
If you didn't know that,
it means that you don't really care?
I'm... a son of this city, Jungsun!
Look at the expression on their faces.
They're just glad you're not their son.
[Son of Jungsun not getting the warm
reception that he would've liked.]
- You're here.
- I'm here.
It's Dong Geun.
But wait... we'll be fine as long as
Kim Jong Kook doesn't show up here.
[Still no sighting of Jong Kook...]
[Have you been waiting for me?]
Why does he have to be here?
We're not meant to do this together with him.
He should be doing this all on his own.
I guess we can look at this as a competition
against three men?
Let's do this.
Let's pull it towards us first.
- We have to pull it towards us first.
- We have to work together first.
If we don't,
we won't even have a chance.
Just look at the way he's walking here.
He looks so smug and confident.
You figured out what
this is about, haven't you?
Why are you smirking like that?
That's very offensive.
You've got the fighter
of the wind by your side.
- You've got the fighter of the wind.
- No, I'm the windless fighter now.
- He was no joke when we were catching trout.
- Why?
I thought he was a saint or something.
[Having caught the trout like a master.]
[Preparing themselves for
a four way tug-of-war.]
Power of the egg!
Please help me beat
Kim Jong Kook just this once.
Ready.
This is driving me crazy.
Power of the egg!
Come to me!
Set!
[Jong Kook's force being felt
like a cast iron steel.]
What?
- I feel like we're tied up to a wall.
- What are you talking about?
- We have to join our strengths!
- Yeah, let's join our strength!
Set, go!
[Here I go!]
[Tiger power]
[Just as they predicted?
A three against one competition?]
- We have to work together!
- Come this way!
Come this way!
- You can't do this!
That's right!
Look at how Kim Jong Kook is being pulled!
[1 vs. 3?]
You can't do this!
Just a little bit more!
- My shoe is about to fall off!
- It's good! His shoe is about to fall off.
[Kkuk even loses his shoe!]
[The 3 vs. 1 plan is working
towards Yoo Hyuk's favor!]
- Dong Geun!
- Which way do I go?
If we keep this up,
Jae Suk could win this battle.
- Wait, in that case...
- We have to work together!
Why are you helping Jae Suk out?
[The coalition starting to fall apart...]
[Just a little bit more...]
[Time!]
My shoe!
[YDG doing everything he can.]
[Total exhaustion.]
[Kkuk almost has his shoe back on.]
Time!
- Can't I even call time?
- No, you can't call time.
[Even though he gave
his last spurt of strength...]
[Strength of Tiger is up!]
[The other three members
getting dragged along.]
[Tiger wins!]
Ugh, my stomach hurts.
Since Kim Jong Kook came in at first place,
please choose who's key you'd like to try.
[Kkuk gets the chance to find his key for
winning the four way tug-of-war.]
- I was going to choose Dong Geun's earlier.
- But you didn't? Then try it.
None of us knows who has our key.
Give it to me!
He didn't choose the right key
the last time.
[Decides to go with Jae Suk's key.]
- Ugh, I'm so pissed.
- This wasn't it?
[Big-nosed Brother telling Jong Kook that
Jae Suk's key didn't work for Sang Wook.]
You can't tell him.
That gives him a better chance.
- Really? I didn't know.
- Why would you tell him that?
I'm just happy to be back
in my hometown.
Why? Did it open?
- Did it go in?
- We'd be happy if you went to rest.
No, it didn't open.
Here.
[It's not the right key.]
I've been thinking of
Ji Hyo's key this whole time.
I've been waiting for Ji Hyo's.
If that key works, that would really...
- You two should just get married then.
- Okay, I'll do it for you.
She says she'll marry him.
I don't think that's such
a bad idea either.
- She said she'll just marry him.
- No, I said, I'll try the key for him.
[Trying out the key...]
- Put some strength into it and marry her.
- Could it be?
Ugh, I'm ruined!
Oh, wait!
- Oh, wait! It turned!
- Seriously?
- It opened!
[It opened?]
It opened!
[Seriously?]
Hurry up and open it for me.
[Gary escapes from his helmet.]
Freedom!
I can't believe that key worked for him.
- What the heck?
- Please give your own key to Song Ji Hyo.
- I'll go look for some wedding halls for us.
- What the heck?
Finish up here quickly, and come find me.
Okay?
- That's just unbelievable.
- Then Dong Geun must have my key.
- Dong Geun has my key. I knew it.
- Why?
[Seems to believe that there's a reason for
Dong Geun having his key.]
Even though this is nice, does
this mean that my screen time is over?
- Great work today, Gary.
- You can go to the final location and rest.
I don't feel very good about that.
[Gary's helmet- Off.]
[Happy meal time.]
That looks so good.
[Jungsun's signature dish- Gonderae rice.]
- That's really good.
- That is good.
[Appreciating the taste with their
helmets still on their heads.]
This is driving me crazy though.
I wish this helmet was off my head.
I agree. This would taste so much better
without the helmet.
What's this now?
- This is the Jungsun market.
- Okay.
[Jungsun's five day market where a huge
public market opens up every five days.]
[Even if it wasn't a famed five day market...]
[It's a place that always stays packed with
the best eats in town at all times.]
You will be starting your next mission,
which is the drama mission.
[Jae Suk chose the Drama Mission over the
Comedy Mission, thus having come here.]
[Starting with mission three, 1st and
2nd place winners get the key to try.]
[A lady with an apron.]
If it's a lady with an apron on,
I'm sure there will be plenty of them here.
[Moving into the center of the market in
search of a lady with an apron on.]
Hello.
Yes, hello.
Ma'am, I see that you have
an apron on?
[Found!]
Can you come with me for a moment?
- Do you have some time?
- Why?
Can you come with me for a moment?
I don't know what the mission is,
but can you come help me for a moment?
- Just come with me for a moment.
- I'm not very good at things like this.
I don't even know
what they're going to make us do.
Just come with me.
Hello.
- What are we doing? Hello.
- Hello.
- What are we going to be doing?
- Kwang Soo, you still have your helmet on?
- But Gary got rid of his helmet.
- Really?
Freedom!
[Feeling happy and energized
without the helmet on his head.]
Where is this place?
[Arrives at the final location where
he can just rest in peace and comfort.]
Combination?
[Getting his makeup touched up...]
[A huge plate of fresh fruit is served...]
[Helmet free world sure is a nice place...]
What's this?
[What could the mission be?]
Your drama is, a choice drama.
[Choice drama]
It's a choice drama.
You two will be acting out a drama.
[It's a scene from Sang Wook's
recent drama.]
[Must act out the scene with the ladies
that they chose to bring back with them.]
[Everyone is given five minutes to
memorize their lines.]
You are given five minutes to prepare.
[Sang Wook having shown the audience his
acting chops as a doctor in a recent drama.]
[Must reenact the scene in this market.]
I'm Doctor Kim in this scene.
- What's your name?
- My name is Lee Hyang Sook.
- Yang Sook.
- No, Lee Hyang Sook.
Hyang Sook... Hyang Sook?
Hyang Sook!
- You know who Moon Chae Won is, right?
- Yes.
You're going to have to act out
Moon Chae Won's character.
- Oh... I have to be Moon Chae Won?
- Yes.
- What's this? Sterilized operation?
[Spray water on the face three times
with a water sprayer.]
I know this is a drama, but...
I'm to spray your face with
the water, right?
So the situation is,
we're all at the hospital.
And we're all operating on a patient.
- I'm the doctor.
- The doctor?
You have to be cautious so that the Director
and his gallbladder doesn't get damaged.
Then you say,
'Doctor, his pressure is dropping'.
- 'Doctor, his pressure is dropping'.
- I have to say that line?
- If you get the line wrong, you're done.
- We got that.
- Are you all ready?
- Yes.
[Jae Suk couple is first
to take on the challenge.]
- Action.
- Doctor Cha.
Let's get ready for the operation.
[We need to start the operation.]
Why?
- Why?
- Jae Suk.
- What?
- You got the line wrong.
- It was, 'Let's start the operation'.
Move out of my way!
Your partner didn't even get to say anything
because Jae Suk got his line wrong.
It wasn't, 'Let's prepare for the operation'?
Okay, ready.
Pil!
What are you doing?
[All he was trying to do was say a cheer...]
[But she sprays him in the face
like it says on the script...]
- Why did you do that all of a sudden?
- Wrong!
Come back here.
You got it wrong.
[Then is it this one?]
[Utter confusion.]
- Okay, it's over.
- Why? I want to try.
[That couple...
Getting a bad feeling about those two...]
[Full of laughter and touching
even though they failed their attempt.]
Are you two out on a date or what?
[A new love blossoming at the market.]
She told me she just washed her hair,
and she's linking her arm with mine.
I want to hold tightly onto his hand.
- Okay, Sang Woo's turn.
- Seriously! What are you two doing?
- Can you take a picture of us?
- You're asking me to take a picture of you?
I'm a celebrity too.
- Come on, take a picture for her.
- Yeah, do it for her.
You're really pulling out all the stops.
[We're the Jungsun Couple.]
If we're going to do this,
let's all take a picture.
[Photo time out of nowhere
in the middle of doing their mission.]
One, two, three.
[Doctor Kim and Director's wife as well.]
Here, I'll take one of you too.
[All the couples gets a picture
taken of themselves.]
Let's move on to the mission now.
Okay, enough.
[A close up on her only?]
You have to take it of the both of us.
- Why are you leaving me out?
- You looked really pretty in that picture.
You remember your lines, right?
- Okay, we're ready.
- Let's go.
Ready.
Action.
Doctor Cha, let's start the operation.
Scalpel.
[Must break the wood on his head and say...]
Suction.
- I can't believe they already got that far.
- This is the difficult part.
- One shot, right?
[Hands over the cola.]
He ate a lot of
the blood sausage soup earlier.
We did it!
Why did you say that?
I'll call you back later.
[She took the time out of her
busy schedule to come and help...]
Her shop must be very busy right now.
- I'll put him on the phone.
- But I can't hear through my helmet.
[Passing the phone off to Yoo Hyuk to
explain the situation.]
She's helping me film our show right now.
I'm sorry for the trouble.
Yes.
Yes, I'm sorry.
She'll be back in a little bit.
Yes, thank you.
[He succeeds in getting her to stay.]
Action.
Scalpel.
Suction.
[Lessening the amount of cola.]
- You're dripping.
- You've dripped half of it!
You have to be cautious as not to cause
damage to the Director or his gallbladder.
Doctor Kim, his pressure is dropping.
[Says her line perfectly.]
Give me the balloon.
[Must blow up the balloon
within five seconds.]
[He succeeds the mission if he can
pop the balloon.]
[Must blow up the balloon
within five seconds.]
[I promise to do this right...]
[Will they succeed?]
[Could his drama mission be a success?]
[So close to succeeding...]
We were so close!
Seriously...
[She was so close to being freed...]
You were so close to going back home.
Ugh, that's disappointing.
Action.
[Jungsun's Giraffe couple.]
You have to be cautious as not to cause
damage to the Director or his gallbladder.
- Doctor, his pressure is dropping.
- Give me the balloon.
A really big balloon.
A bigger balloon.
[Will they succeed?]
Please!
No, that's too high.
Not up there, but we have to put it here.
[In her attempt to place the balloon
at her stomach level...]
[No, that's not what I meant...]
Where do you think
you're placing that balloon?
[Trying to work with the tall Giraffe
put her in an awkward situation.]
This field has completed
its harvesting of the crops
so we have prepared the field into an
arena for you to carry on your mission.
If you look over to the side,
you can see four wicker baskets.
You will find there are 50 potatoes
in each of those baskets.
Without the usage of any tools,
not the basket...
You have to transfer those potatoes to
the baskets sitting at the finish line.
- That's pretty simple.
- Simple, isn't it?
You have one minute to
complete the mission.
Okay!
[Starting off by making a little pouch
with the front of their shirts.]
What are you doing?
[Son of Jungsun trying to gain himself
an advantage at the starting line.]
- Have you lost your mind?
- What are you doing?
[Must pick up the potatoes
as fast as they can.]
[Turning themselves into
human kangaroos.]
[30 seconds left on the clock.]
[Dong Geun and Big-nosed Brother
getting on their way.]
[Being on his home ground is making Big-nose
act brash against Dong Geun.]
[Kkuk and Ji Hyo finally
get on their way as well.]
[Must be careful as not to
drop any of their potatoes.]
[Shoving Dong Geun out of their way.]
[Must hurry and dump their potatoes into
the baskets at the finish line.]
[Time's up!]
Please count the number of potatoes
that you've brought to the finish line.
Two, four, six, eight... I've got 24.
[Son of Jungsun has 24 potatoes.]
[Blank Ji has quite a stack of
potatoes in her basket.]
- Six...
- What are you doing back there?
- 24... 25.
- What are you doing?
[Blank Ji has 25 potatoes.]
[Dong Geun- Five.]
[Kkuk- 11.]
Song Ji Hyo wins first place.
- Okay.
- I got it.
[Time for Doctor Kim
to take on the challenge.]
Make sure to be cautious as not to cause
damage to the Director and his gallbladder.
Doctor Kim, his pressure is dropping.
Give me the balloon!
She's so cute.
[Will they be able to succeed the big finish?]
[Success]
- I can't believe they won.
- Thank you.
- Thank you, Ma'am.
- Congratulations, Ma'am.
- May I see your cellphone?
We're going to win second place.
- This one is going to be ours.
- Okay, on to the next scene.
- What?
[Changing to a new scene since
the previous scene is now complete.]
No, I like it.
I like having a new scene.
- What are you doing to us?
- You have three minutes, so hurry.
[The next drama scene is...]
[Sandglass]
[A top hit drama that swept the nation
in its wake in the early 90's.]
[Turns around and pulls her towards him...]
'It's not revenge! I just wanted you!'
[Hits Choi Min Soo with her gloved hand
as hard as she can on the head.]
'I thought that doing that meant I could
have you because you're my woman!'
'It's all over now.'
'It's not revenge! I just wanted you!'
[Ro-Ro couple's turn.]
[Pulls the woman towards him and says...]
'It's not revenge! I just wanted you!'
[A resounding smack to the head.]
'I thought that doing this meant
that I could have you.'
[Pulls the woman into his arms,
and sit and stand five times in a row.]
[Showing his strength?]
'Because you're my woman!'
- He needs to get beat some more.
- 'Because you're my woman!'
'Because you're my woman!'
[What is this during a romantic moment?]
After how many kids did you get like this?
How many?
I have three kids, and ever since my first...
- Okay, we're ready.
- Ready.
Action.
'It's not revenge! I just wanted you!'
[A lethal punch.]
[An automatic round of applause
for her passionate acting skills.]
'I thought that doing this meant
that I could have you.'
'Because you're my woman!'
[The last spurt of effort
to succeed the mission.]
[Will they succeed?]
[A lethal smack down to the head.]
[Jungsun market's energy maker,
Madame Ok.]
You have to say your line.
'It's all over now.'
[She has to say, 'It's all over now.']
I knew it would end like this.
What was my line again?
[Other teams are in a celebratory mood.]
- Why would you do that?
- 'I knew it would end like this.'
- What did you just say?
- It's all over now.
I just want to go home.
I don't think I can do this.
Where do you think you're going?
After you've already beaten me up.
We have to switch our roles and redo it.
Ma'am.
Thank you for your hard work.
[Thank you for the big laughter.]
Ready, action!
[Turns her around as it says in the script.]
'It wasn't revenge.
It was so I could have you.]
[Huh? A cute love punch?]
She has to hit you on the head.
No, everyone has their own style.
It's because she was trying to be cute.
You have to hit him as hard
as I got hit.
[Kwang Soo seems to be
holding some grudges.]
Why did you do that?
You could've hit me harder.
Ma'am, why did you do that?
Was it because you didn't want to hurt me?
You don't have to worry
about me so much.
[Ro-Ro couple's second attempt.]
'It wasn't revenge.
It was so that I could have you.'
'I thought doing that meant
that I could have you.'
'Because you're my woman!'
- Look at how his legs are shaking.
- 'Because you're my woman!'
'Because you're my woman!'
[His face looking worse for wear.]
[You are too much woman for me...]
[Wait... it was supposed to be the tray.]
Yes!
We got this, Ma'am.
[They were so close to succeeding...]
It's okay.
Ready.
Action.
'It's not revenge.
It was so that I could have you.'
She needed to have her
back towards you.
Because she didn't have
her back turned?
[Must have the staging correct too.]
- She had her back halfway turned.
- You have to do it accurately.
[Her face was turned directly
towards the camera.]
'It was so that I could have you.'
- She needs to be turned away from you.
- She wasn't turned around!
- She needs to have her staging right.
- It's because she's really shy.
But she was just...
why did you do that?
- Why didn't you have your back turned?
- I'm so sorry.
- Was it because you were feeling shy?
- Her back must be turned towards you.
Ready.
[Too much woman... Ro-Ro couple.]
'It wasn't revenge.
It was so that I could have you.'
[Acting getting better and better.]
'I thought doing that meant
that I could have you.'
'Because you're my woman!'
[The most difficult part of the script.]
Oh no... what to do.
[An exhausted feeling of emotion.]
[Now time for the final line...]
[The last line, 'It's all over now.']
'It's all over now.'
[Success]
We did it, Hyang Sook!
[Darn...]
Hyang Sook!
[Finishing off with a flying hug?]
[But why does she have him
in a headlock?]
Thus, Sang Wook passes in first place,
and Ha Ha also passes in second place.
[Sang Wook in first, and Ha Ha in second-
Earns a chance to try out a key.]
[Thank you to all the ladies
for your participation.]
- I've already tried Jae Suk's key.
- Yes, you did.
I'll go for the person that I have
absolutely nothing to do with.
[In that case, try out Ha Ha's key?]
- It would be crazy if the key fits.
- Here, try turning it.
It would be crazy if the key works!
[It doesn't seem like the key works...]
I guess your plan is working out though.
You said you wanted to keep staying.
I didn't try turning it the other way.
- Yes, you did. I saw you try.
- I did?
Yeah, you tried it.
[Ha Ha's selection is?]
Why don't you try mine?
- Okay, try it.
- Try it.
Mine?
[Selects Jae Suk's key.]
Okay, try turning it.
[Will it work?]
[Will the key fit?]
It worked!
See? It's opening.
[It opened!]
I felt it turn!
Awesome!
I'm freed!
[After eight long hours, he's
able to escape from his helmet.]
You can now move on to the final location.
The rest of you can move on to
the next mission site.
That seriously feels so good.
[Ha Ha succeeds in escaping
from his helmet.]
Oh my...
[Another helmet freed member arrives.]
- Come here and relax.
- This is amazing, Gary.
Have you been like this
the whole time?
I've had some coffee, fruit,
and fried chicken.
Here, have one.
[Even their own personal VJ's get lucky.]
[Huh? Is he getting ready to nap?]
[Napping in the midst of filming.
Something that's never happened before.]
[Meanwhile, the rest of the members are
moving onto their fourth mission.]
[An unbelievable scene unfolding in front
of their eyes inside the cavern.]
This is so unbelievable!
[An unbelievable sight of the
limestone cavern made by nature.]
- This is unbelievable.
- This is all made by nature.
- Is this a natural cave?
- It's completely natural.
[Mouths are gaped open in wonder.]
Wow, this is absolutely unbelievable.
[Climbing up the long flight of stairs...]
- What is this?
- What's this?
Walnuts?
[Walnuts?]
- We have to crack these with our heads?
- With our helmets?
How many?
Eight.
Set, go!
They're not cracking.
This is pretty hard.
[Walnuts aren't breaking so easily.]
- It's not working.
- This is hard.
[Human nutcrackers struggling to
crack their walnuts open.]
[Smashing down on their walnuts with
every ounce of energy that they have.]
Are you keeping count?
[Slowly getting the hang of it.]
[They're all doing pretty good.]
[Finally!]
[These nutcrackers are on fire!]
- Stop!
- I think I've got them all.
- I finally got it.
- Sang Wook is in first place.
To be honest...
I don't even want to come in at first place.
I've come in first at every mission.
[Even though he continues to come in first,
he still hasn't been able to find his key.]
What does it matter if I come in first?
I still haven't been able to find my key.
- Can I have your key?
- Mine?
[Sang Wook- First place. Jong Kook- Second,
Jae Suk- Third.]
[Sang Wook selects Jong Kook's key.]
- I just hope Jong Kook doesn't find his.
- Be quiet!
- I hope his helmet stays on his head.
- Now that I've had enough screen time...
[Now that he's had enough screen time...
it's time to escape from the helmet?]
[Will it work?]
- Got it.
- You got it?
[It worked!]
I can't believe that worked.
- Doesn't it feel really good?
- I can't look like this on screen though.
No, you look fine right now.
- Why are you taking a picture of yourself?
- What are you doing?
My hair looked kind of cute.
Everyone look over here and smile.
- What is he doing?
- It's not working.
[Third place winner Jae Suk
selects Ji Hyo's key.]
[The key turned in the lock?]
What?
What is it?
[It opened!]
[Gary's original key that Ji Hyo received
was the key to Jae Suk's helmet!]
Okay, give me your key.
[Jae Suk's key is then handed over to Ji Hyo.]
But Jong Kook has to continue
to wear his helmet, right?
- That's great.
- Okay, onto the next mission.
[Sang Wook and Jae Suk succeed in
escaping from their helmets.]
[Meanwhile, Dong Geun is the only one who
succeeds in escaping from his helmet.]
Wow, that feels so good.
I don't know what the final mission is,
but I have to do it with the helmet on.
That could mean trouble.
I have to escape from this helmet,
but I don't know who has my key.
[Just what is the final mission
that awaits them?]
[7:30 PM.- Jungsun's 'M' Resort.]
Hey, find it quickly.
If we don't, it's all over for us.
You just keep going.
I'll search around here.
[Helmet freed players
running around frantically...]
You members are the Defense Team
who have to remain on the run.
And the members who have not
successfully escaped from their helmets
are the members of the attack team
with bells on their shoes.
Why are we the ones being chased after when
we're the ones who escaped from our helmets?
Do they have to keep their helmets on
as they come after us?
- Yes, they still have their helmets on.
- As they keep getting even more aggravated?
They've all got their helmets,
and their bells on as well.
[The four helmeted members will be after them
to eliminate their name tags with bells on!]
[Even if the Defense Team rips off the
Attack Team's name tags, it's deemed useless.]
Your goal is to find the escape door and
make your way out before being eliminated.
There are buttons hidden throughout the
place which will open up your escape door.
Those buttons are hidden in boxes
that are locked up with a padlock.
If you press a total of five buttons,
you'll open up the escape door.
But you have to make sure to press
all five of the buttons.
This is really terrifying.
[If even just one of them escapes,
then then team succeeds the mission.]
[A locked box is discovered!]
You have to unlock the padlock with the keys
that you guys have in your possession...
This isn't opening.
Hey, there's a box in the gym
that's on the third floor.
- We have to try to open that box.
- Okay, let's all go down there.
- Let's all try it.
- Here's another one here.
Seriously!
Hey, there are a ton of these boxes.
[Find the correct five boxes
out of these countless number of boxes!]
Jae Suk!
We're all here.
Hey, there are a ton of these boxes.
There's one over there too,
so try opening it.
- Here's one too.
- Mine won't open.
[Neither of Jae Suk or
Sang Wook's keys are working.]
[Meanwhile, at the same time...]
My head is really itchy.
Can't you take this off?
I'm getting really annoyed right now.
- You don't have much time.
- We don't have much time?
Bell hide-and-go-seek?
We're the attack team!
[The four helmeted members
are the attack team!]
[Capture the members who have
freed themselves from their helmets.]
[You win the race if you eliminate all the
members who are freed from their helmets.]
This is good.
Okay, let's go!
Let's go eliminate them.
[Full of eager energy.]
I'm sure they've been having
a ball waiting for us.
[Full of desire to get revenge against the
Defense Team who are freed from their locks.]
Is it okay if I ram them with my head?
I don't think mine works at all.
Is my key a fake?
[Carelessly stepping onto the pebble ground.]
Ouch, that hurts!
[But he still has to try.]
I've found another one.
[Not the right one either!]
It's not working, is it?
[Gary's key not working on the box either.
How about Ha Ha's key?]
It's not working.
[It opened!]
- No, it opened.
- It opened!
[Ha Ha opens up the first box with his key!]
[One of the five escape buttons.]
[Pressing on the first of the five buttons.]
- I pressed it.
- We got it!
Here's another one.
[Just four more buttons in order
to open up the escape door!]
It was my key.
What's that?
The first button has been pressed.
- What is the first button?
- What does that mean?
They must've found something.
There's one advantage that you have
going for your team.
From the moment that
you press your third button
a member of the Attack Team will get
ousted one at a time.
From the moment that
you press your third button
a member of the Attack Team will get
ousted one at a time.
Which means, you have the chance to
eliminate three of your opponents.
In the instance that they find and press
their third button...
from that point on, one of you will start
being eliminated one by one.
- Play, rock-paper-scissors.
- Why?
To determine the order of
your elimination.
Wait, Suk Jin.
- Isn't it better if I remained to the end?
- That's right.
[It would be most useful for them if
Mr. Capable remains alive to the end...]
[Oh my!]
[Jong Kook is guaranteed to survive
until the end of the race.]
It's going just as he had hoped.
- Let's finish.
- Rock, paper, scissors.
[Oh my...]
Rock, paper, scissors.
- They're going to think this is planned.
- No!
[Giraffe is the very first to be eliminated
from the Attack Team.]
[Just as if they had planned
this out from the beginning...]
[Once the third button is pressed,
Giraffe will be jail bound.]
Rock, paper, scissors.
[Upon the pressing of the third button,
Kwang Soo is out.]
[Upon the pressing of the fourth button,
Ji Hyo is out.]
[Upon the pressing of the fifth button,
Suk Jin is out.]
[No time to waste!
Time to put their bells on!]
This is really exciting.
We haven't done the bell chase in a while.
There' no time to waste.
Let's go do this!
[One person is feeling extremely desperate
as the rest are feeling the excitement.]
Why are you so slow?
Did they already find their second button?
They must've found their second button.
The second button has been pressed.
No!
[Defense Team's Jae Suk unlocks a box
moments earlier.]
Hey, I got one!
[Jae Suk opens a box with his key.]
[Second of the five buttons to
the escape door is activated.]
The second button has been pressed.
- This isn't fair!
- Let's hurry.
[One more button,
and Giraffe of the Attack Team is out!]
This is so unfair.
[Three more escape buttons to go!]
No, no, no!
I have to capture at least one of them!
I have to get my revenge for
keeping me locked up.
For being stuck in this helmet all day.
I can't go to jail wearing this helmet.
- What if they find us?
- We'll be in big trouble if we're found.
[Must search every one
of the guest rooms as well.]
If they come, we have to hide.
Let's go find it.
I'm scared.
[Must hurry and find the buttons
before the bells could be heard.]
I think I'm going to go up a floor.
[The bells...]
The other way.
What do I do?
I hear the bells.
[Getting... closer...]
- Hurry!
- Hurry up and get in!
- Did you hear that?
- I heard it.
[Their hearts dropping to their feet at
the sound of the terrifying bells.]
I thought we were dead.
That was terrifying.
I don't have time on my side.
I will start this race!
[Desperation putting Giraffe on edge.]
- Check all the exit doors.
- There a lot of emergency exits.
I can't believe this.
- What is this?
What do I do?
What do I do about this?
[Sang Wook experiencing the terror
of the bells for the first time.]
How are we supposed to...
how many of them are there? Five?
They're like ghosts.
Kwang Soo. Did you check
the sauna on the second floor?
- Yes, but I didn't see anyone.
- Right?
I'm going to check the karaoke room.
Are the staff members walking around
with bells on their shoes to scare us?
[Attack Team carefully checking
each of the guest rooms.]
[The problem is that Giraffe may get ousted
before he can even oust anyone.]
- I may not even get to do anything.
- You have to check each of the rooms.
What are you doing?
I will show you what
a one man show looks like.
What do I do?
[The bells are near!]
There's no one.
This is the end of the hallway.
We should check downstairs.
I doubt they'll get in the elevator.
Check the emergency stairs.
I really hate this.
I really hate this feeling.
- What is this!
- There you are!
[Discovers Jae Suk of the Defense Team!]
[Mr. Capable is on the chase!]
[Escaping into a guest room after hearing
the frightening voice of Mr. Capable.]
[Mr. Capable on full speed!]
[This is where Gary went in to hide.]
[In the end... he's caught by Mr. Capable.]
Jong Kook.
[I don't even want to imagine it.]
Fifth floor.
- Yoo Jae Suk on the fifth floor.
- Jong Kook.
- Tell me where the others are.
Hurry up and tell me where
one of your other members are.
[Will Jae Suk sell out one of his members
to save himself from this danger?]
Let's see... tell me where Ha Ha is.
Ha Ha.
[He's looking for me!]
- Come on, give it up.
- Why did you have to be there?
Why would you ask me that?
I went because I smelled fear.
Why are you always in the same place
that I'm at?
[Continuing to listen in on the situation
through their walkie-talkie.]
Ha Ha... what floor are you on?
[The truth is, he's had the walkie-talkie on
the whole time to alert his teammates.]
- Why are you pressing the button?
- No, I wasn't'.
[And Mr. Capable caught onto his trick.]
[Dummy... hurry up and run away!]
Did Jae Suk do it purposely
so that I could hear what was going on?
Ha Ha.
Jae Suk, this is Sang Wook.
Where are you right now?
I've been captured by Jong Kook
on the third floor.
[Warning him not to
come up to the third floor.]
You've been captured?
[So that means I shouldn't go
to third floor.]
Hurry up and go!
Find the key and oust Jong Kook!
[The worst kind of hostage
who cannot be kept alive.]
Hurry up and rip it off.
Just rip it off.
You two...
[Defense Team's Jae Suk is eliminated.]
The hallways are way too long.
[Jae Suk- Out!]
Yoo Jae Suk, out.
I don't care if it's my teammate or my
opponent, but I just want to see someone.
This feels too lonely.
[Huh? He's answering the phone?]
Ah, Running Man Team's dinner?
Yes.
[Sang Wook takes the call to confirm dinner
reservation for after the filming is over.]
Yes, I understand.
Running Man filming is running late,
so it'll be between 8 and 9 o'clock.
- Yes, between 8 and 9 o'clock.
- Yes, thank you.
[Changes the dinner reservations himself.]
[Meanwhile, Dong Geun is still looking
for a box that would match his key.]
[There's a box over there...]
[Overly sensitized to even
the slightest sound?]
Hey!
[The chase is on for Yang Dong Geun!]
Yang Dong Geun is discovered!
Third floor!
Yang Dong Geun is on the third floor!
Hurry!
[At this rate, it'll be a frontal face-off!]
Come to the third floor!
Third floor!
[Fleeing as swift as a bird.]
[A much slower Big-nosed Brother...]
[Succeeds in fleeing down to the first floor
in a blink of an eye.]
Wow, that sound of the bell is terrifying.
I hate those bells.
[Okay... let's calm down.]
[Defense Team's Gary and Ha Ha meet up.]
You know that Jong Kook was just here, right?
- He was here with Jae Suk.
- Yeah.
- Did you find one?
- I found one in Room 557.
Room 557.
I think it was Room 557.
[There was a box that Ha Ha's key
wasn't able to open earlier...]
[The bells...]
I'm sure it was a lot of fun for them.
But it's all over now.
Don't contact me for the time being.
[The sound of the bells getting closer.]
[Kwang Soo enters the room!]
What's this?
[Discovers a VJ who didn't get
a chance to hide!]
What's this?
Once the door opens, I'm just
going to run out without you.
[Someone's definitely in here...]
Excuse me.
Oh my goodness!
[Gary is discovered!]
[Gary in extreme danger!]
[His chance at an escape... is now!]
[Just then!]
Lee Kwang Soo, Out.
The third button has been pressed.
[At such a crucial moment...
Attack Team's Giraffe is ousted!]
[Sang Wook discovers a box in
the moment of Gary's danger.]
[Sang Wook opens the box to
press the button.]
Okay, I've pressed the third button.
[Third button out of the five
has been activated.]
[What a crucial moment for this to happen!]
[Third button is activated,
and Kwang Soo is ousted.]
[Bad enough that he's first to get ousted,
but to get ousted like this...]
That was so scary!
Get away from me!
You're ousted!
Get away from me right now!
Hey... that was unbelievable timing.
[He thought he'd be eliminate one person
before he was ousted...]
[Ten years shaved off his life.]
[Gary's key doesn't seem to
work on this lock either.]
How could that have happened?
[Going back into hiding from a new
sound of someone else's bells approaching.]
[Going back into another closet.]
[This time, he takes the camera himself
so that his VJ doesn't get discovered.]
- Gae!
- Gae?
[His last dying message?
Screaming out 'Gae' as he's hauled away.]
[It must mean that Gae is near.]
Isn't this a box too?
[A box that the Defense Team is
seeking is discovered.]
- Isn't that one of the boxes?
- I think so.
- We have to find them quickly, Ji Hyo.
- I'll check this one.
[Mr. Capable and Ace agreeing to
separate and search on their own.]
If the box is here,
that means that someone is nearby.
I'm positive that someone is nearby.
[That's our Ace! Deducing that
Gary is in one of the rooms!]
[That's the room that Gary is hiding in!]
This room is different.
[Ace Ji Hyo searching every
nook and cranny.]
[The handsome face having gone gray.]
[Checking a different room this time.]
Peek-a-boo.
Who could this be?
[Ji Hyo discovers Gary!]
Kang Gary.
Please, Ji Hyo!
I'm too scared.
Why does it have to be you
of all people?
[Monday Couple's tragic fate?]
- Why does it have to be you of all people?
- I don't want it to be me either.
[Is the Monday Couple fighting?]
- Suk Jin.
- Yeah, it's me. Where are you?
- Gary's right here.
- Where?
- He's right there?
- In Room 505.
Gary.
Where is he?
You two want to do it yourselves,
or how do you want to do this?
I think this is the first time
I've seen you all day.
[This is the first time they're seeing
each other since the opening scene.]
- This seriously is the first time.
- I know it is.
- What do we do?
- We have to eliminate him.
You two stay in there.
I feel so bad, and I can't eliminate him.
What do you mean, you feel bad?
- What do we do?
- I'll grab him.
[This is a job for
heartless Big-nosed Brother.]
No, don't!
Ji Hyo!
Don't come to the fifth floor!
This is better than
Ji Hyo ousting you herself.
[Song Ji Hyo... you're one cold woman.]
Here it comes.
Over here.
Here, you can take this back.
[Food?]
If I'm already in jail,
isn't it all over now?
[Jail snack time.
Helmeted member can't partake.]
[That's my favorite!]
Wow... how did you get this?
I cant believe they'd think to get this.
Gary!
[Gary joining them in jail
after getting ousted.]
Who ousted you?
Ji Hyo and Suk Jin.
I know... she really is something.
That's my favorite ice cream.
[I'm sure it is...]
[Want some?]
Wait for it.
[Three escape buttons are now activated-
Defense Team-3; Attack Team- 3.]
[So many boxes...
but not many that open.]
There's a box in the karaoke room.
Here's another one.
In the restaurant.
[Everyone gathering at the restaurant
where Ha Ha discovers a box.]
[Everyone trying out their own keys.]
[But none of their keys are working.]
[The chase is closing in,
and they're running out of steam...]
Here's another one!
It's heavy.
[Will they find an escape button in this box?]
[Sang Wook's key isn't a match.]
[And Dong Geun's key...]
[At last!
Dong Geun's key unlocks a box!]
[Fourth escape button is discovered!]
[Fourth out of the five buttons
are now activated!]
Is Ji Hyo out?
- The fourth button has been pressed.
- No, Ji Hyo!
Song Ji Hyo, out.
[Attack Team loses their Ace!]
[Only one escape button to go!
Defense Team- 3, Attack Team- 2.]
[Now... only one
escape button to left to find!]
[Searching the rooms one more time.]
[Mr. Capable, Jong Kook.]
[They can forget about escaping
if they're caught!]
[Separate to improve their chances!]
[Jong Kook chooses to go after... Ha Ha!]
[Ha Ha- Out!]
Ha Ha, out.
But we just need to find one more
and it's all over, right?
Once the final button is found
and at least one member of the Defense
Team escapes through the door
then the Defense Team wins.
[Only one escape button left to go!
Defense Team- 2: Attack Team- 2.]
[Separate to search for the button.]
[Now they're using their brain!
Passing on the box because it's too light.]
[Here's another box!]
[Heavy]
[This must be the box for Gary's key.]
[Sang Wook with Gary's key is on his way!]
[If the button is in that box,
then the escape door will open!]
[The box is opened!]
Come on... we should've
been cooler about pressing it.
Why would you just press it
like that?
[All they have to do now is escape out
the door without getting caught!]
Come here, Kim Jong Kook!
Ji Suk Jin, out.
All the buttons have now been pressed.
The escape door will now be opened.
Ji Suk Jin, out.
All the buttons have now been pressed.
[That was so close...]
I lasted longer than I expected.
[All the buttons have been activated!
The escape door is now open.]
[If they can avoid Mr. Capable's chase,
and make it out the door, they win!]
- Oh my...
- Jong Kook.
[Dong Geun is hiding away secretly.]
- I didn't press it.
- You didn't press the button?
[Dong Geun must make his escape while
Sang Wook buys him some time.]
[Now's the time!]
[Go!]
[Dong Geun makes a dash for the escape door!
Mr. Capable is hot on his tail.]
[Will his escape
or elimination come first?]
Where is the door?
[Dong Geun arrives on the first floor
where the escape door is located.]
[Dong Geun discovers the open escape door.]
[Defense Team's Dong Geun...
the honor of escaping is his.]
[Defense Team-
Escape mission- Clear.]
[You did it, Master Yang.]
[Even after the race is over,
the helmets are still on their heads.]
Get away from me.
- Are they going to bed with these on?
- Shut your mouth!
- What's that?
- It must be our prizes.
[A table full of prizes for the winners.]
[Delicious and healthy combo set
of Kangwondo's specialties!]
Look and see if there's any gold in here.
[Hanwoo beef over gold!]
[Even a plethora of their infamous gonderae.]
After seeing that pile of gonderae,
even this looks like gonderae now.
[Now that they look at it,
Master Yang's beard looks like...]
Anyway... the no helmet team wins!
[A round of applause for the no helmet team!]
I'm so tired.
Laughing takes too much energy out of me,
and I don't have any energy left.
Honey, and Joon Suh.
I won the race.
Thank you to everyone for helping us
win our victory today.
Subtitles by DramaFever
[A fantastical adventure.]
[Thrown into the Land of Oz
by a swirl of wind.]
[TOP with his irrefutable charisma.]
[And the sweet and innocent, Yoo Jung.]
[TOP's fantastical adventure of finding
their road back home is about to start.]
[These special friends,
who will help them find their way...]
[Heartless tinman, Yoon Moon Jae.]
[But the evil wizard who will do
anything to get in their way...]
[Dorothy is then kidnapped!]
[Rescue Yoo Jung-Dorothy from
the evil wizard.]
[But the Running Man clan is about
to face frightening magic...]
[What will become of
Dorothy and her friends?]
[The Wizard of Oz.
The fantasy returns next week.]