[Dear Heirs]
[Defeat the temptation of the crown.]
[The young heirs-to-be:
Park Shin Hye, Kim Woo Bin, Choi Jin Hyuk.]
[And the troublemaking heirs of
Running Man.]
[The true heir of RM Group is me.]
[Win the votes of the
executive board members.]
[The merciless race for the inheritance.]
[Heirs- Defeat the pressure of the crown!]
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Mokdong, Seoul
RM Group Headquarters]
[A tall and handsome gentleman approaches.]
[And for some reason,
he is surrounded by flower petals.]
[RM Heir Lee Kwang Soo:
Chairman of RM Group Oil.]
[And his shorter brother in all white.]
[RM Heir Ha Dong Hoon
Director of Operations at RM Group Oil.]
Hello everyone!
Welcome to our garden party.
I have parties like this every
morning at home.
Am I doing this right?
[He's not used to being the rich guy.]
I'm supposed to be rich right now, right?
Hey! Wine!
Yes, Father.
I said no Father!
I don't need that useless building!
- Rich heirs! Rich heirs!
- Tell your father to pay us back!
What are you talking about?
He still hasn't paid us back!
- Didn't you see him last week--
- We'll seize your belongings!
Do you want us to put
re-po stickers all over your house?
You two work at the same company.
- It's nice to meet you.
- Hello.
- Your father doing well?
- Yes, yes.
I should visit him soon.
- I gave your father a call recently.
- So I heard.
- I should be pouring you--
- No it's okay.
You two are close childhood friends.
Really? Hey, it's so good to see you!
- You haven't changed at all!
- Let's have a drink!
- Yes, yes! Everyone doing well?
- Of course.
- Hi Jong Kook!
- They said we're all really close friends.
[Another heir, Director of RM Group Oil
Kim Jong Kook.]
[Since they are close childhood friends...]
What are you guys doing?
[Another heir,
Director of RM Oil, Ji Suk Jin]
- I thought you said we're all friends?
- Are all your businesses doing well?
Lee Kwang Soo! Come here.
[RM Group Heiress:
Director Song Ji Hyo.]
Hand.
- Aren't you also a heir Kwang Soo?
- Be quiet.
- Hello Ji Hyo!
- Hello Ha Ha.
I heard you found gold last week.
- Congratulations!
How is it everything you touch
turns to gold?
In just a bit, your rivals
from RM Fashion will be arriving.
Jae Suk is on the fashion team?
[Smooth]
[Sleek black suit]
[RM Fashion Heir,
Director Yoo Jae Suk.]
Caretaker! He's the caretaker!
Sebastian, get out of my way.
Who do you all think you are,
coming to my company?
This isn't your company!
This place is like my second home,
I used to come and play here all the time!
-What'd you say?
- Where? Where?
Hey boy! Come here!
[A free-spirited party animal.]
I heard there's a party here today!
[RM Group Fashion Heir
Director Kang Gary.]
You must stay right here.
You two will soon turn into squid.
Don't you know that if I'm
a squid you are a baby octopus?
How dare he says such things to me.
[We came to catch the squid.]
[Good looks that you can feel from
100 meters away.]
[Confidently walking over.]
[We are the true heirs!]
You're right,
they are in the fashion industry!
[Polite]
[Popular eye candy- Choi Jin Hyuk]
[Astonishing physique- Kim Woo Bin]
[Versatile chameleon- Park Shin Hye]
[The main characters of the
highly-anticipated drama 'Heirs'.]
That's enough.
You don't belong here as it is.
Our company executives!
[The best-looking individuals of
RM Group Fashion.]
Hello.
Shin Hye! What are you doing here?
- What do you mean?
- You should be on my team!
Jin Hyuk and everyone,
come over this way.
Please stand over here,
next to these two.
- Woo Bin you too!
- Where are you guys going?
I'm sorry but where are the
two squids that were standing here?
Two squids?
You're the baby octopus that's
standing next to them!
Where are the two squids
that were here?
- Honestly, I came here to work today.
- Gary, come over here.
As you can see...
these three are the heirs
to RM Fashion Group.
We are also all heirs!
Just take a bundle of squids
and be gone!
Stop calling me a squid!
Today's mission is the
Heirs' race to gain company shares.
Every time you win a mission,
you will receive a RM Group bankbook.
The more bankbooks you collect,
the better.
And only the team that wins the final mission
will have a chance to receive the inheritance.
If your team does not win, you
don't even have a chance to win alone.
So our team has to win for anyone
to even have a chance at winning?
So if your team does not win,
everyone on the team is immediately eliminated.
This will be a bloody battle.
Everyone will now change into
their team's uniform and get going.
[The search for the true heir!]
[Outfits perfectly suited for heirs-to-be.]
[Even sportswear looks good on them.]
I guess sportswear doesn't look
weird after all.
You all look so good in it.
Oh my...
Squids! You all really look like
a bunch of squids...
- We're expensive squids.
- We're amoeba.
Please go to the first floor lobby.
You will want to arrive there first.
Your departure time will be
decided based on who gets there first!
- Jin Hyuk, how old are you?
- I am 29 years old.
- Oh really?
- He's the same age as me!
- Yeah right!
- That joke is not even funny!
It's not like Jin Hyuk
looks that young for his age either!
He really doesn't look much younger!
Fear of heights!
- I screamed the first time I ever rode this.
- Really?
[Their destination is the
first floor lobby of RM Group.]
- Hurry! Hurry!
- Jae Suk! Jae Suk!
[The two handsome gentlemen
lead the way.]
[Where is it?]
[The entire team must arrive
in order to win.]
- Everyone is here!
Blue team wins!
You said whoever gets here first!
[This is only the beginning...]
Everyone, this is the lobby of
RM Group Headquarters.
What are you talking about?
This is the SBS building!
It says right there that it's RM Group.
At this time, as the employees
of RM Group arrive to work...
you will be enjoying
aristocratic sports here.
- Aristocratic?
- Is it something like horseback riding?
Polo? Polo?
As you live the life of an aristocrat,
you are often under a lot of pressure.
So the sports that only
the most prestigious enjoy...
Yes, I saw my grandfather playing!
So the name of the game is
Defeat the Pressure of the Inheritance.
[The team that removes all of
the plungers first, wins.]
Not like it's the weight of the throne...
This will be a timed mission so
someone will be taking down the time.
The Blue Team will decide
who goes first.
The squids can go first.
Stop calling us that!
[The battle of the RM Group divisions.]
- You think you're good looking?
- This team has never played these kinds of games.
The first round will be a
man-to-man battle.
One male squid, please step forward.
Then should the large king squid go first?
- Stop calling us squids!
- What do you mean large king squid?
Large king squid, premium squid,
cuttlefish, baby squid.
[Expert nickname-giver]
What kind of aristocrats play with
a bunch of plungers?
Do you want to receive the inheritance?
I do!
I will defeat the pressure!
The stress I've received
since I was young... the stress--
Just go!
I'm trying to pump myself up.
Ready!
[Defeat the pressure...]
[Start]
[Won't move even an inch...]
You really can't get it?
[Hold on...]
[An amazing reaction.]
What is this? Why is it like this?
- It's the pressure!
- Is it really that bad?
[The giraffe is exerting every
bit of energy from all the plants he ate.]
What's wrong with this?
- Don't joke around... stop it.
- That's enough.
Stop messing around!
Take this seriously now.
[Only the handle is moving...]
What is he supposed to do?
Is he being serious?
This hurts so much. Look!
It has been one minute!
He can't receive the inheritance!
He's not worthy.
[Taking out his frustrations on the plungers]
What are you doing right now?
How did anyone think to put
these on here?
- Seriously!
- You really can't take them off?
That's two! Two!
It doesn't work even when
you're holding it there?
[Three removed!]
All the pressure... since I was young!
[Was trying to help pick
up the one that dropped but...]
Oh wow...
Wow, this is no joke.
- It's really that hard?
- It's really hard.
- How are we supposed to get these off?
- Where are these from? Let me get one.
[The last one... success!]
[Giraffe's record= 2 minutes 54 seconds]
[The long but brief time
to overcome the pressure.]
The time is no different
than forfeiting.
I'm pretty sure it's not.
And from our team, Woo Bin will go.
- Good luck, Woo Bin!
- Let's go, Woo Bin!
Let's see how different he is!
Make it a clean and quick win.
Clean and quick.
Let's see whether or not
Woo Bin will become a squid.
[Start]
[Bitter laughter...]
Woo Bin the time is still going.
Really?
Woo Bin you must be tired already!
It's tough, isn't it?
- Woo Bin it's time for you to start.
- Let's go Woo Bin.
[Finally the first one!]
You know how to do it now!
[Mastered the technique?
Two in a row.]
[Dang...]
[He knows how to do it now.
Three in a row!]
He's not even grunting anymore!
[Success]
[Masculine?]
What the heck?
39.37 seconds!
- I'd like to try one more time!
- Yeah right!
So the Blue Team wins
the first round.
From now on, the opposing team
will put the plungers on.
What did you do? What did you do?
It was really hard for me.
[Jumping?]
You're going to put it all the way
up there?
Jin Hyuk, you don't look like
the type. What are you doing?
[His unknown competitive side
is surfacing.]
He's pretty competitive.
[What are you doing?]
[Looking around]
What are you two trying to do?
Neither of them wants to carry
the other person.
[In the end Woo Bin is on the bottom...]
Woo Bin! Why are you so weak?
Are you telling me I lost to him?
Get up both of you!
What's wrong with you guys?
Jin Hyuk, you're more fit.
Why do you keep trying to go on top?
You can carry Woo Bin instead!
Why are you getting involved
with our team again?
I'm just saying! Look!
He... he's younger than me.
[Even good-looking gentlemen
have respect for elders.]
[This time Woo Bin is on top.]
He's not that good at being
on top either...
[Just barely...]
You're not as perfect as you seem.
[The imperfect heir, Kim Woo Bin.]
I don't think it'll go up that far!
That's not that high!
- He's a bit ditzy...
- What are you doing?
It just fell off!
- Will it be better to jump and stick it on?
- Yeah, that will be better.
Give it to me, I'll do it.
[Now what are you doing...]
What are you two doing now? You
guys keep attempting to do things but...
We thought this would be quick
but it's taking a really long time!
What are you planning?
You're really falling apart on us today.
It's funnier when
good-looking people do this.
[Finally]
[Up he goes...]
What are you doing Jin Hyuk?
[These two do not let us down.]
It's like watching a circus act.
[Gary, showing an example
of what to do.]
Look at him!
That's what you should be doing!
Be careful.
[A selfless stunt simulation.]
[Not very high up.]
Two men, please step up for
the second round.
You have to hold on to the waist.
The waist?
Let's do it together.
You two will be a good combination.
This is a timed competition.
Are you two sure?
- Why?
- What are you trying to say?
[Who wouldn't be worried?]
I'm so humiliated I will
definitely take those plungers off!
Show them how it's done!
[Slip]
What are you guys doing?
I think this thing is crazy.
[They can do this all night]
[There's something black
on his face...]
Why is Suk Jin's face so dark?
Suk Jin, the black powder from
your head is all over your face.
- Really?
- It's all over you. Right here, right here.
[The secret to his dark hair
has been revealed.]
[Remnants of black powder everywhere.]
We are definitely from a wealthy family!
There is coal coming out of
my brother's head!
Why'd you take my hat off?
His stylist sprayed a lot on today.
[Focusing on the game to
distract everyone.]
[Switching places and trying again]
I saw her spraying more
than usual today.
- You got it! Do it again! Again!
- You grab it again this time.
One, two--
Last one! Last one!
One, two!
[Success...]
The squid ink brothers!
I saw this morning and your
stylist sprayed on way too much.
Ji Suk Coal.
[Coal mine heir, Ji Suk Jin.]
That was 1 minute 33 seconds.
Next two, please step up.
I'm a little nervous about this one...
- Jin Hyuk works out a lot so he'll be good.
- No, I don't.
[As usual, setting high expectations
for everyone.]
What are you two always planning?
They look so normal but act otherwise.
For the first time ever, we might
lose our Easy Brothers personalities today.
[Start]
- Wow!
[Powerful]
[As Kkuk predicted, Jin Hyuk is strong.]
Great job! You're doing a great job!
Woo Bin didn't do anything!
Kim Woo Bin and Choi Jin Hyuk-
7.81 seconds.
[Blue Team sweeps the first mission.]
We will now hand three bankbooks
to the Blue Team.
Okay!
- Really?
- There's a million won in here.
There's really money in there?
If you hold onto this throughout the
game, it will belong to whoever has it.
Say you do not earn
any bankbooks...
then that person loses all rights
to becoming an heir.
Now we will give one to
the losing team.
I'll hold onto it.
Please decide exactly who
will hold onto it.
Let's play Rock-Paper-Scissors for it.
Rock, paper, scissors!
Go away!
Why are you bothering us?
Why are you getting in the way?
Rock, paper, scissors!
- Seriously!
- Put that away!
Even I think he's being annoying.
Rock, paper, scissors!
Seriously!
Why are you teaching her
these things?
Rock, paper, scissors.
Scissors. Scissors. Scissors.
Ji Hyo got it! Ji Hyo won!
Why does Song Ji Hyo always...
What is this?
She's going to get it all.
Luck is always on her side.
We're off to a great start.
[Please go to S-Marina in Yeo Eui Do.]
Woo Bin put on my seat belt.
Woo Bin is actually like Mr. Bean.
[Potential iconic comedian, Kim Woo Bin.]
I almost spit out my drink.
I turned into a squid in
the back seat.
I'm so glad I'm not in that
picture back there.
Days like today
I really wish I was driving.
You have a very charismatic name.
My celebrity name?
Yes.
- Thank you.
- What does it mean?
My nickname in junior high
was 'Dog'...
- Adding the last syllable was a good choice.
- It was, wasn't it?
I thought a lot about what to
add at the end of my name.
What were some of the runner-ups?
At the time there was also Gaemi...
[Gaemi = ant]
Kang Gaemi!
So it's easy for people to remember, I see!
That would have been
really funny though.
Gaemi... Gaemi...
[S Marina]
- Let's go!
- Go! Go!
[Yeo Eui Do, S Marina]
Are we getting on the yacht?
[Enjoy a breathtaking yacht ride
along the Han River.]
We look like F4.
[F4 you say?]
[King of Coal + King of Gyms +
Vegetarian Animal + Queen of Gold]
Let's hurry up a bit.
This round is the
Bankbook Auction Game.
Just like the rich auction items
such as paintings, antiques and art.
Oh that kind of auction!
You will be able to receive a bankbook
that has money in the account.
There is a pre-determined one-on-one
game each round.
Please send in one person
from your team for each game.
- Okay! Got it!
- Sounds good!
The remaining team members
can fill up their water glass
based on how much they
believe their team member will win.
Please bring them in.
Sounds like a fun game!
Must we sweep you in
another game for you to quiet down...
And to the side you will see the water cups.
Each cup of water is worth
two bankbooks.
In the dramas, the wealthy
sometimes slap people or even get slapped.
Just in the dramas?
It happens here too.
They slapped someone with water
this morning!
Those cups are to
slap each other with water.
So when you win, you may
politely slap your opponent with water.
When you lose, you get slapped with
whatever water your team bet on you.
- Do you understand?
- Don't worry! Let's just get started!
Please just don't spray my hair.
The first game!
[Thumb Wrestling]
As much as there are
international competitions for this game
this is that much of a
widely-played game.
Please send out your players!
[- RM Fashion- Jin Hyuk
- RM Oil- Giraffe]
Great! You got this!
- Attack him first and hold him down!
- No matter what just win.
King squid! King squid!
This kid is not just tall.
His thumb is also really long.
His thumb is twice the length of mine.
Wow it's long...
Kwang Soo also has a long nose.
Why are you talking about my nose?
Blue team please decide
how many cups you want to bet.
Four cups!
We will bet four cups!
Six! We'll bet six!
Wow, it really is long.
Ready!
I'll show you Jin Hyuk
get drenched with water!
My fingers and toes rule!
His fingers are no joke.
I'll show you how it's done.
I thought that was your toe.
His are pretty long too.
Set, go!
What is he doing?
You're such a wimp.
This is my strategy.
Are you a mole or something?
- Very good.
- I got him!
I got him! I held him!
Hurry and call it!
It really is long.
He really is long.
It's too long.
My fingers and toes rule!
- Your toes are awesome.
- Bring it on!
Look at my toes!
- Hey Jin Hyuk.
- This isn't fair.
You can exercise your fingers more.
Since Kwang Soo won,
here you go.
I'll take these.
You're taking it all? Can't you be
grateful for all the support I gave you?
Get on your knees.
I'll hang onto it for you.
- You've got to be kidding.
- Why not? I'll just--
I fell for that with my mother
so many times!
Me first? Why did you
take your shirt off?
They said to take it off.
You'll struggle for 100 days.
- What did he say?
- I'll do it again.
- What kind of theater is this?
- One more time.
Ready, action!
You'll struggle for 100 days.
But eventually you...
- What did you say?
- Okay seriously one more time.
No, I can do it this time.
For 100 days, you'll want to be like me.
But in the end, you can't be me.
- So cool.
- Hey, he looks cooler than you.
Hey, I'm the winner.
I'm the lead actor.
Why am I overshadowed again?
Why am I overshadowed?
I'm the main!
Lead actors need a certain quality.
Wow, you must get a lot
of flack in dramas.
Why would I?
Hey. Look at me.
Pay attention.
I never liked you ever
since you were a kid.
- I don't...
- You're getting too into it.
Open your legs.
Open! More!
I never... I never liked you.
[Whispering into his ear]
Know that? Look into my eyes.
Do you know?
You're ugly!
Even though he's spread his legs,
he's still taller.
Very good!
We'll start the second game.
[Change clothes as fast as you can.]
One, two, three!
- You got this.
- You don't need to use your body for this.
I'm mad.
I get mad just looking at him.
Make Jae Suk get mad!
The clothes you were wearing
earlier are inside.
There is no necktie or vest.
- All in!
- That's right!
Let's go for it!
Please win. I beg of you.
Please let me splash water on his face.
- I want to drench this face...
- I'll win.
I will avenge Jin Hyuk.
Hold on.
I'm ready.
We'll begin soon.
Ready, set...
So erotic.
Just take it all off!
Dong Hoon sure is different.
You can beat Jae Suk!
You need to button up too right?
You need to button it all up.
- We won.
- Shoes, shoes.
[Barely has shoes on]
- We won, we won.
- Ha Ha wins!
We won! We won!
Congratulations. Here you go.
Who put socks in my shoes?
Why would you put this in here?
Seriously!
- These shoes...
- Come here, come here...
- Take off your glasses.
- What did you say?
Who do you think you're touching?
It's been a while, hasn't it?
I've worked under you for eight years.
This is infuriating.
- Don't be so stiff.
- Just splash me already.
Look at how he looks.
Really something.
You really look terrific.
- Just a moment.
- What?
I really can't stand you!
Infuriating!
Bend your legs.
Don't try to be cool.
- I'm going to get you for this.
- How will you do that?
- Here we go.
- I'll get you for this.
Should I do it this way
or that way? Here we go.
My father's enemy.
I'll get you for this.
I'll get you.
This is our third game.
[Blue Flag White Flag Spoons]
Gold is written on one spoon
while silver is written on the other.
Cover your eyes with both spoons.
And then uncover your eyes.
Choose your players.
- How much will you bet?
- We'll bet six.
- But I...
- Even Ji Hyo was like, 'Let's go with six.'
Six cups.
Let's go Eun Hye.
- What?
- I meant Shin Hye.
Eun Hye is Jong Kook's.
We miss you Eun Hye.
I would like to say hi as well.
You miss her, right?
I'm nervous.
Come to your senses!
Ji Hyo's not nervous.
She's already won.
- Why are your lips like that?
- Ji Hyo, you know which one's gold?
Why were you making your lips
all cute like that?
Like this?
Hurry up, it's hot!
Flip silver.
Flip gold.
Don't flip gold. Flip silver.
Flip gold and silver.
Don't flip gold and silver.
Flip silver. Flip gold.
Flip silver. Don't flip silver.
Flip gold!
Flip gold.
I can't hear what he's saying.
He said don't flip.
There's nothing we can do.
- Fix your pronunciation.
- Yes, I understand.
- Do it right.
- Yes, I'll do it again.
Did you only hear Gary's voice?
I was only looking at you, fool.
Flip silver. Flip gold.
Don't flip silver, flip gold.
Can't you even do it right?
Stop making Gary's heart flip.
- It's so frustrating.
- Good for you!
Don't flip gold.
Don't flip Gary's heart.
Don't do that.
Eun Hye...
We miss you.
I just miss her.
What's wrong with you?
- I just miss her is all.
- Do you still have feelings for her?
What? What's wrong with you?
You both are really good at this.
I'll start off slow.
Seeing her so focused makes
it seem like Ji Hyo was very studio.
Flip silver.
Don't flip silver. Flip gold.
Don't flip gold. Flip silver.
Flip gold. Flip gold.
Don't flip silver. Flip gold.
Flip silver.
Flip both.
Flip gold. Don't flip silver. Flip gold.
Don't flip silver. Flip gold.
Don't flip gold, flip silver.
Flip silver. Flip silver.
Don't flip gold. Flip both.
Don't flip any.
Flip silver.
Flip gold. Flip gold.
She was so happy to hear
Gary's voice she was smiling...
That voice...
No!
Hey do you like my voice that much?
- That's not it.
- It's not fair Gary.
Thank you.
We will start the next game right now.
[Rock Paper Scissors]
How many accounts do you
have so far?
- Five.
- We have six.
We mentioned there's a penalty
for the losing team.
You'll have to hand in half
of your accounts.
We have to win.
So it's the two of us?
Don't you remember Jong Kook
just throwing him across?
I just slipped.
- He just slipped.
- If he just slipped why did he fly off?
You just flew off.
Rock, paper, scissors!
What are you doing?
Rock, paper, scissor.
You wore your hat
more deeply this time.
Rock, paper, scissor!
You really went for it!
Put it up, put it up.
Woo Bin. Do well.
Rock, paper, scissor!
He's fast.
Fighting Jong Kook!
Rock, paper, scissor!
- That was good.
- It's a tie!
Keep your eye on the pot.
Woo Bin. What are you doing?
- This is the final round.
- What are you waging?
You're a weird kid.
Rock, paper, scissor!
Thank you.
He has six.
- Hand in half of them.
- We have a lot more games.
Of course.
Now it's time to splash water.
Let me take one.
[The ever so popular water]
- This is nice.
- Water is W100 each.
W100 is nothing.
As a bonus, we'll give you two cups.
What do you mean bonus?
I'll do what I want!
Stand up straight!
- You're too much.
- Stand up straight! Salute!
- Nice, nice.
- What are you doing?
- He's a mayfly.
- Why are you being so intimidating?
Seriously. You're being so scary.
This is so... ugh...
- Hey, give it to me.
- Oh really?
What are you two doing?
I raised money!
I still have my two accounts.
You had W500,000 and sold W1,000,000.
Seriously. Stupid fool!
Jin Hyuk, come over.
But he's really scary when
he exercises.
- He makes noises when he works out.
- When have I done that?
How does he work out?
He roars.
He makes the most noise.
Oh, I apologize.
- Should I make you scream?
- No, sir.
I've already done that. I lived
ten years screaming!
What do you mean you'll
make me scream?
I got some money.
What? I gave it to him, so what?
This is like a mental asylum.
Just splash him. It's fine Jin Hyuk.
I'll address you informally.
- Nice.
- Hey good timing.
Is this the last one?
I want to do it so bad.
What are you doing?
Hurry up and splash him.
Just take the water!
Just take it!
- Show me your face!
- Just take the water!
Hey, give this to me.
Hey, you! This is war.
Depart for Han River Citizen Park.
Jong Kook, you know why I did
what I did, right?
I didn't want to give the other
team a chance to splash you.
I would rather have splashed
you with my own hands.
All we have left is to
be held in water.
Shin Hye is really cute when she talks.
She does have that quality.
She's the type who burns a man up.
Do you want some?
Do you think Shin Hye...
[Arrival at the park]
Since there's no swimming pool,
they gathered all the water here.
They set up a pool here. Amazing.
They made it here.
I would do this in the winter too.
The next game is a mental one
between heirs.
Each player will go up and fight
only with their heads.
I was about to say that
just to be funny.
- We fight with our heads?
- That's really it.
You really must use your heads
and only your heads to fight.
We're going to start. Each time,
please push towards the middle.
When we count to three,
you can jump on the platform.
Who wants to do it?
One, two, three.
- You can come up.
- I'll go.
Where are you going?
So cold.
This is so much fun.
I have nothing to lose!
Me neither!
It's been a while.
Today will be your last day.
- I don't think so.
- Who says?
- I'm going to win.
- No I will.
You look like beasts.
Ah, this hurts.
It hurts.
Good for you Dong Hoon!
- Dong Hoon's impressive.
- It hurts!
It doesn't hurt me.
It doesn't hurt!
- I don't want to lose.
- I don't either.
I won't lose to you.
I feel no pain in my head.
Jae Suk fighting!
Next time...
[I'm impressive]
[What is he? A pro wrestler?]
Woo Bin, get in position.
Ready...
It hurts.
What the hell?
It hurts so much.
Okay again!
- Hey!
- You useless fool!
You think you can be an heir like this?
Be quiet!
- Good, very good.
- You were kind of loud Kwang Soo.
Just be quiet.
Then I'll be quiet.
You can't lose Woo Bin.
Think victorious Woo Bin.
- You're doing good.
- Hang in there.
It hurts! It hurts!
You went in like a squid.
It was like a squid sliding
off a cutting board.
How did he just go in like that?
Here goes Woo Bin again.
I said help me up! Help me up!
So help you up...
I will help you up.
Keep that image in your head!
Go on up.
Remember this feeling.
Remember it. Go up.
More, more!
Remember this feeling.
Jong Kook, remember this.
I really mean it.
Remember how he sent you flying.
Help him up!
Don't forget how he sent you flying.
He said he just slipped!
This is your chance for revenge.
You'll turn into a ninja turtle.
It doesn't hurt.
It doesn't hurt Jong Kook.
- Finish it off!
- Do it right!
He won, he won.
It doesn't hurt!
You're getting there.
Just keep going.
Hey what's going on?
What are you doing?
[Jong Kook wins!]
I'm Choo Sung Hoon!
I think I'm good at this.
I'm really good at this.
Shin Hye! We believe in you!
Shin Hye can't come out.
It's Shin Hye, not Eun Hye.
Jong Kook, how do you tie this?
Back or below?
Don't fall for her!
You can't fall for her Jong Kook.
Shin Hye's someone I really care about.
That's how my mom and
dad got together too!
I can't do it.
She can't do it.
What do you need to do?
- Don't fall for her!
- So you can look pretty?
Don't waver!
Don't do it! I said don't waver!
- Shin Hye don't forget to thank him.
- Thank you Jong Kook.
- Stuff her ears!
- Don't look into her eyes.
All she can do is be cute!
- That's good.
- Is it?
- Thanks Jong Kook.
- No problem.
[He's fallen for her]
This is the final round.
Losing to a girl is pathetic!
You better not lose to a girl!
Don't be that way Jong Kook!
- Put your heads together.
- Keep your eyes on the ground.
- It's so hard.
- What's so hard?
Of course his head would be hard.
Would it be soft?
Wait a minute!
- Wait, I'm not ready.
- Shin Hye shut your mouth!
What are you saying right now?
- Shin Hye!
- It hurts...
- I'm not doing anything.
- This is good.
Jong Kook!
- It's okay Shin Hye.
- I'm not doing anything.
Hold on, hold on.
Shin Hye. She's pretty strong.
Stronger than Woo Bin.
- She's stronger than Woo Bing.
- If you give up, he wins!
Seriously!
Really! She's really strong.
Shin Hye! She's for real!
I'm not kidding!
If you lose, it's over.
He's weak to women.
You can't do this.
Don't act like a pig Jong Kook.
They have ten already!
I don't know anymore!
[Tiger Jong Kook loses to a girl]
I'm not kidding. She's really strong.
Blue team wins.
Nice. There's nothing we can do.
As promised, here
are five new accounts.
Two accounts for everyone else.
You should have just won.
How could you have lost?
It's not even like it's Eun Hye.
Goodbye sister-in-law.
I can't stand being on his team!
He's so weak to women.
She totally ran away
with his heart.
He's Prince Charming. A real prince.
Let's not give any of our accounts.
Let's go! We don't need any of this.
Is today the day?
It's today, it really is.
Welcome back to RM Group.
Today you are going to meet
the shareholders who hold your stocks.
They are scattered throughout
this building.
I wonder what kind
of characters they will be.
They hold these documents
in their possession.
Collect these documents and make
your way to a room with five chairs.
All team members must have the documents
in their hands and sit on the chairs.
We each need to have it.
Which the most accounts so far?
- We do.
- You can have the first document.
- We can steal this from him.
- Sure you can.
We will reveal the shareholder identities.
[Lim Sung Hoon, Kultwo, Hong Rocky]
Wow, this is impressive.
They are all in the building.
They all have the documents with them.
Let's go together!
I know where they are.
Hurry up!
It's this way. It's not
a pre-recording. It's live!
[Shareholders Kultwo are
in the middle of recording]
[Walks straight into the studio]
Kultwo, Kultwo, Kultwo!
Welcome, welcome.
You know that I always listen
to Kultwo radio, right?
What brings you here?
[Gary and Shin Hye walk in]
No. We got here first.
We're going to see Mr. Lim Sung Hoon.
Is he in there?
[Seems they just finished recording]
What did you record?
Oh they were recording
What in the World.
Oh hello.
Hello.
Oh hello!
[Oh! Here's is shareholder
Lim Sung Hoon.]
It's been a while Mr. Yoo.
You brought such good-looking
young men with you.
You should be looking at me,
not at them.
[Her eyes naturally go this way.]
[Spots the document]
Oh I was thinking that...
Sir, is that your son?
[Television producer]
- It's been a while since I've seen him.
- You know him, right?
Yes, hello sir.
This is Miss Jae Soo.
[Announcer Kim Min Ji]
Sir, we're recording Running Man,
and I see that you have a document with you.
But this envelope belongs to me.
That can't be right.
But it's the same as the one we have.
It really is the same.
These Kultwo show hosts
are R&B music men.
We need to get a document from you.
- You need to give it to us.
- That's our mission.
We can't just give it to you.
You have to do something.
- Should we sing?
- Should we do a dance?
[An explosive response]
This is also a visible radio,
so you can see this.
Who wants to see Kim Jong Kook's abs?
Abs! Abs! Abs!
That's enough, that's enough.
We're really sorry about intruding...
Please choose a representative
to show how much you love Kultwo show.
Every time I release an album,
I come out on Kultwo show.
He writes songs for me.
The Kultwo theme song is in his hands.
We love Kultwo show.
Chan Young and Tae Gyoon.
What would we do if there
were no Kultwo radio? Kultwo!
That was pretty good.
Who are you giving it to?
We have to give it to
the team that showed up more.
That's right.
Also Jong Kook has always
been very supportive.
Kultwo! It's such a good show.
Okay, here you go.
- Yes!
- Thank you!
Goodbye.
[They get everyone's signatures]
Thank you.
Why are you acting like this?
So we just finished recording,
and you came.
Usually when we finish,
coffee comes out.
- Really?
- We usually get coffee.
- The four of us...
- Do you want iced coffee?
I like it warm.
- And you?
- I like iced Americano.
I like iced vanilla latte.
I like warm vanilla latte.
He's a really close friend of mine.
I don't want any. I change
my mind. I won't have any.
It's okay because I'm here.
Can I bring you my savings card?
Oh Jae Soo...
Hello!
- So nice to see you.
- Hello!
- Hello.
- Wait here.
Hello, it's so nice to meet you.
Oh Jae Soo.
I'll make sure to have
it punched for you.
- We're going to buy coffee.
- Jae Soo is really meticulous.
Hello. We're looking
for Hong Rocky.
There he is!
[DJ Rocky spotted in the middle
of live broadcast]
- You can go in?
- Yes! That's awesome!
- Hello.
- Hi!
Why hello!
This is live! This is live!
Hello everyone, we're Running Man!
Wait for the song to finish.
Let's dance!
As expected, Ha Ha's dance.
Changes mind after seeing Shin Hye.
[Song ends. Time for monologue.]
This is Hong Rocky. We have
a lot of guests in the studio.
We'll have our guests introduce
themselves one at a time.
Hello, this is Running Man's
Ji Suk Jin.
Hello, this is Running Man's Ha Ha.
Hello everyone.
I am guest Park Shin Hye.
Hello, this is Gary.
Nice to meet everyone.
- Why did you come?
- You're a shareholder.
Yes, I am RM Group's shareholder.
- We're here to get documents...
- That's right. From our shareholders.
One of the shareholders is Hong Rocky.
- Then I have to approve of you.
- Of course.
Then what's a good song?
A fun song for all...
'She was pretty.' Why don't
you all dance to this?
Change members.
Excuse me. We're in an emergency.
Could we pay later...
What would you like?
So we can do it?
We'll pay you as soon as we get down.
An iced Americano...
A hot Americano...
A warm vanilla latte.
An iced vanilla latte.
So four orders?
Could you punch this card?
- I'll follow Dr. So Hyun's decision.
- Why thank you.
- I need a boyfriend.
- I love you!
Please accept my love.
I love you!
I fell in love at first sight!
- Age doesn't matter to me.
- It matters to me.
[Jong Kook becomes impromptu guest]
Can I take your name tag?
- Sure.
- I always wanted to.
- My son wants it.
- One, two...
Son!
Let me put it back...
[Back here, still dancing]
Why is it just the guys?
Tired, right?
- Father...
- Dad!
- Dad...
- Jae Suk!
- What are you doing?
- What do you mean?
My co-worker's father
is also my father.
He's my father too.
He's my father!
- That's what I do in the morning.
- I never gave birth to a son like you.
- Woo Bin.
- Yes.
- Where's the coffee?
- It's on it's way.
In the meantime, this is proof.
You, you, you!
Thank you!
- Okay.
- We beg of you.
- Please give it to us.
- They have ten accounts, we have five.
But we still really need this.
Last challenge. One person from each
team should ask listeners to tune in.
Each person. Give
an impressive delivery.
Yes, everyone hello.
Hello Mr. Rocky!
The Running Man team is here today.
Please show Mr. Rocky some love.
Please support us until we
go up to number one.
Thank you everyone!
We love you!
Are you sick of your humdrum life?
We'll bring you all the love
and happiness you need.
Listen to our song and stay healthy.
- Thanks everyone!
- Thank you! Hello Mr. Rocky!
Rocky, rocky, rocky!
- Here it is.
- Thank you. We love you.
- We love you.
- I really missed you guys.
Here Shin Hye.
Hey you punk!
[Betrayal]
You were a lot better
with the last monologue.
Fighting!
- Shin Hye's no joke.
- Shin Hye was really good.
Okay, here we go.
Make sure to put it in
the envelope first.
Sir, this is too much.
He's always like that.
[Who will he hand it off to?]
We exchanged numbers during Chuseok.
Oh, you contacted him?
I'm so weak to good-looking guys.
We have a lot more troops.
You know who, right? We have
Jong Kook. He's good-looking.
[The Tiger arrives when he's called.]
Father.
[Here comes Jin Hyuk.]
Hey, why are you doing this?
What are you doing right now?
Who says you could get
away with this?
Let's make sure we keep in touch.
Whatever your decision, we accept it.
One, two, three!
Thank you.
- The four others have been revealed.
- Let's go, let's go.
- The rest of the four.
- It's all set?
Jong Kook. It's all set.
Let's go.
We'll let you know.
Okay, it's all been revealed.
Park Sun Young, Girl's Day, MIB.
Okay so it's announcer Park Sun Young,
Girl's Day, and MIB.
[Where will the rest of
the players be found?]
Sir, sir. Hello.
[They find out Announcer
Park Sun Young's whereabouts]
What is this?
MIB, Girl's Day!
Every day Girl's Day!
Girl's Day is going to give it
to Jae Suk no matter what!
Girl's Day. Girl's Day.
Minah, Minah.
How do we know where Girl's Day is?
Miss Park Sun Young...
Oh here she is.
- Oh hello.
- Hello.
Good evening ladies and gentlemen.
[An SBS Anchorwoman for Three Years]
- You are much prettier in person.
- Thank you.
Wow, so beautiful.
I thought you'd be coming
with the others.
There is no one else.
You can just give it.
- You can just give it to me.
- What is it that I give?
You're a shareholder.
Yes, I am. So shouldn't
you be more considerate to me?
- Are you telling me to hand it over?
- That's not it.
- You seem very impatient.
I'm just afraid the others will get here.
Then I want to wait.
There's MIB!
Hey, MIB!
Oh, there it is.
I'm thirsty.
First, let's get your signatures.
I really respect our shareholders.
She's coming, she's coming.
Hurry and sign.
Shin Hye! You can't! You can't!
Jong Kook! I want to see idols too!
- You want to see MIB?
- I want to see the idols!
First, just sign here.
Okay, MIB. I'll put it in here.
What is this?
Go help her. Come on.
Go help her. Hurry, go on.
Hurry and help her.
Okay, thanks!
How could you steal the document
from the shareholders?
MIB, you're the best!
Thanks!
You're the best! Thanks!
What can we do for you?
Ma'am, what can we do for you?
Announcer Park Sun Young...
And?
I have a present for you.
Go on.
I'll cheer you on forever.
- Your face gives too much away.
- Did you eat yet?
- No, not yet.
- Oh you didn't.
I love you!
I fell in love at first sight.
I was trying to win her over myself.
Leave them alone.
Their love is blooming.
Why are your eyes so smiley?
- Stop smiling with your eyes.
- So what if his eyes smile?
[Running Man's Jae Suk arrives]
Here he is, our savior.
Get out of the way.
- Oh so you were on the blue team.
- Sun Young. I'm going to get mad.
She won't flinch.
Park Sun Young is great.
You guys have no idea.
Let's go by whose eyes
are the most sincere.
Oh really? Who's the most sincere?
We're the sincere ones.
I hope you take this and win.
It was so great to see you.
This is really...
Thank you so much.
We go way back.
Please don't tell them.
- Thank you.
- Sure.
- I look forward to your dramas.
- We'll make sure to win.
SBS news rules!
- Thank you!
- Goodbye!
Good luck.
[Only Two More Left!]
Song Yong!
Shin Hye...
Hello.
Nice to meet you.
Please accept my greetings.
- It's been so long.
- We are enjoying your work.
He was complaining about
your work earlier.
He said it was so tasteless!
Sir, hello. We have a mutual friend.
Right, Ji Hyo as MC for Inkigayo.
While you catch up on Inki,
we'll move over there.
I come out as a beggar in
one of my dramas.
Sir!
Brother! Have you been well?
Your face looks so good, brother.
This is the first time he's met you.
- Have you been well?
- I've never met him before.
Get on my back.
Get on.
- We have to do something.
- I'll give you a piggyback ride.
In all my time of working with him,
I've never given him a piggyback ride.
Aren't you hot?
[Wait...]
[What's this?]
[I guess it's mine!]
[Giraffe acquires the document!]
Thank you sir!
Stop him! He took it!
- Wait did you do it?
- I signed it.
We'll see you next time!
Where did he go?
Shin Hye. Have you seen
Girl's Day anywhere?
What?
Shin Hye, have you seen Girl's Day?
[Shin Hye finds Girl's Day!]
- Hello.
- You're so pretty.
- You're even prettier.
No, you can't do this.
I really like your clutch bag.
Second floor!
Hurry up!
Shin Hye, why are you doing this?
Don't act like we're friends.
Every day... Girl's Day!
I really missed you all.
[What? He knows them?]
It's too crowded here so let's go
somewhere more open.
I shall escort you.
[Put it in the envelope]
- Jong Kook, when's your birthday?
- I'm Girl's Day!
When's your best day?
Of course it's Girl's Day!
Sing a Girl's Day song.
- Tell it to me... tell it...
- That's not it.
Tell... me it.
You call that a dance?
- Shin Hye, you're good.
- That's how you do it.
- You're really good.
- You're the best.
She usually likes to dance.
Just because you like it,
doesn't mean you can do it.
- How dare you!
- I'm older than you! Don't shout!
So the document you hold right
now is very important.
Just give it to who you want.
Wait a minute!
- Thank you!
- I'm not doing this!
Every day, Girl's Day!
Which way do I go?
Hey you can't run away!
Hey, where did she go?
Shin Hye, run! Run!
Hey, what are you doing?
Gary!
Bring it here.
- You...
- Let's take it all the way.
Suk Jin...
[They need to take his document
and sit down...]
Got it!
No!
A successor will now be
named from the blue team.
All of the accounts are different.
The person with the most left in their
account will be the winner.
I wonder how much will be left.
W500,000!
Plus W200,000 is W700,000!
Why does it say I can't use my account?
You put it in the wrong way.
What? How is this guy a successor?
Does someone know this is mine?
There's only W100.
How could there only be W100?
[An account that had W1,000,000
only has W100.]
- Then Gary your total...
- W200,600.
How much? Oh you have nothing.
She has W100, W500, and W100.
And W1,000.
It says there is no summary for my account.
Does that mean I have W1,000,000?
- You have W1,000,000.
- Right? Yes!
- What else do you have?
- W200,000.
W1,200,000.
Jin Hyuk's winning so far.
Woo Bin?
Nothing. Such variety.
W50.
- Wow W50.
- What is that?
- W1,000.
- Jin Hyuk. You practically won.
W50,000.
If he has enough in the next account...
W100,000!
[Woo Bin inherits W151,050]
Our Running Man successor!
Choi Jin Hyuk!
It's gold.
We had such a great time with our heirs
Jin Hyuk, Shin Hye, and Woo Bin.
The winner and heir of
today is Choi Jin Hyuk!
That was amazing.
Subtitles by DramaFever
How could you hit me?
What is this?
They're coming. It's Jung Myung.
Chung Jung Myung.
Pretty flirt Kim Min Jung.
- They this is our turf.
- Be quiet.
- Oh that guy is more childish than we are...
- Kwang Soo...
He's scary.
I'm a girl...
[A free-for-all without rules]
I can't do it because of him!
Subtitles by DramaFever