Jae Yoo Jae Suk's minions.
Come out here!
[Variety show newbie, Jung Woo Sung.]
[Variety show's rookie, Jung Woo Sung-
He shows us how it's done?]
[Early vacation that they're
learning to enjoy with their whole bodies.]
[Will Jung Woo Sung become a fixture in
variety land only after two shows?]
[We are the rulers of variety land!]
[And...]
[The eternal captain... Park Ji Sung!]
[I love you, SBS?]
How about a video message?
[Tough video message.]
- Where did you guys meet?
- Is she a good cook?
What was it about her
that made you fall for her?
[And...]
Do you have any interest in coming back?
[It all starts now.]
Subtitles by DramaFever
[One bright summer morning-
At a busy gas station.]
[Yoo Hyuk dressed in blue floral shirt.]
Hello.
- What's going on today?
- Please wait for the other members.
Ah... seriously. Why is he
wearing sunglasses on a cloudy day?
Come on, seriously.
- What are you doing?
- What?
- Why are you walking like that?
- Because I'm in a good mood.
- Why are you in a good mood?
- Isn't it nice to be outdoors again?
How nice is it to be working out here?
Why do you have your shirt
opened up like that?
- Don't you know what this look is?
- What is it?
This is like what he looked like
in 'City of the Rising Sun'.
This is what Jung Woo Sung dressed like
in the movie, 'City of the Rising Sun.'
[Is he making a comparison?
This is the original look...]
- As you can see from your clothes...
- We're on opposing teams.
I like being on different teams.
Your teams will be divided up depending on
the color of the shirt that they're wearing.
- Really?
- I wonder who'll be on my team.
[Mr. Gary in a blue floral shirt.]
- Gary!
- I think he's on your team.
Hello.
- It's Kwang Soo. Ugh...
- Ugh...
[And 2PM's Junho rejoining the gang
after his appearance last week.]
[New hope for the
otherwise dismal Red Team.]
Junho, why are you dressed in red?
[Excited Haroro arrives for the fun getaway.]
- The teams are divided up already?
- Hi, Ha Ha.
- Come here. Come join us.
- I'm stuck with the nagger?
- Come here.
- Is this it?
Both the teams are led by naggers.
Our situation is no better than yours.
I bet that the teams are
divided up like this on purpose.
- Why?
- Think of Woo Sung on your team.
It would be just as funny no matter
who's team he's on.
- You'd look so funny standing next to him.
- That goes without saying.
I don't envy you guys.
You guys look like Junho's entourage.
The entertainment firm's president
with his manager,
and you as the coordinator.
- That's hilarious.
- You're the coordinator.
[A rare sight of a muscle bound coordinator.]
- I see someone else coming.
- Where? Oh, it's Song Ji Hyo.
[Blank Ji dressed in a blue floral shirt.]
Good morning!
- Why are you angry, Ji Hyo? You look angry.
- I feel like it's my wife coming home.
It puts me in a bad mood when Kwang Soo
greets me so happily first thing in the morning.
- It puts you in a bad mood?
- What's that supposed to mean?
Why would I put you in a bad mood?
Stop greeting me so happily
in the morning from now on.
- It puts me in a bad mood.
- That's so funny.
- What the heck?
- Don't greet her happily anymore.
From now on, don't greet me
so happily in the mornings.
- Don't say hi to her.
- Just don't even greet me anymore.
I haven't greeted you.
I didn't want to put you in a bad mood.
- Hyo Joo's here. Hyo Joo's here!
- Where?
Hi, Hyo Joo!
- Hello!
- Hi, Hyo Joo!
- You're on our team!
- You're as lively as ever.
- Don't act so lively in the mornings.
- Hi, Hyo Joo.
Seeing you so lively puts us in a bad mood.
- You look so pretty.
- Don't even greet us.
[And...]
[The floral shirt legend,
Jung Woo Sung makes his appearance.]
I don't think I've ever seen
Woo Sung in a hat before.
- Hello.
- Hello, Woo Sung!
Hello.
It's 'City of the Rising Sun'!
'City of the Rising Sun'!
Wow, we get to see it in person.
I'm going to look so ugly
standing next to him.
- Wow, that's too hilarious.
- Doesn't this look so funny?
So this is our team?
Woo Sung's on our team?
See? Real stars don't wear sunglasses.
But you're always wearing your sunglasses.
- I was just about to take off my sunglasses.
- They think they're too cool for the cameras.
Take a good look.
The real stars don't wear sunglasses.
Look at how the real stars don't
even wear their sunglasses.
You will be divided up into
these two teams today.
Today's race is, Early Vacation Race.
[Today's race-
Early Vacation Race.]
- What is this?
- Is it Dong Wan?
- How long have you been back there for?
- When did you get here?
What you see in front of you right now
are your prizes for the day.
[From a TV to a tent,
12 generous different vacation giveaways.]
What you see behind you
is the giveaway number board.
As you probably know already,
you can't just take those with you.
The two teams will be combating each other
in a series of different games.
And at the end of each game
the team that won the game will get to choose
two numbers from the numbers board.
The winning team gets to pick their first two
and then the loser team picks their two.
So the team that chooses the prize behind
the number chosen wins that prize for now.
And at the end of the very
final competition
the winning team of that final competition
gets to win all of the prizes.
You look cool just standing there
and listening to the explanation of the rules.
[Even cool about how he
listens to the explanation.]
I thought he was shooting a
beer commercial.
I'm going to follow and copy him
with everything that he does today.
Yeah, it's funnier if you copy him.
That would be funnier.
That really is a comic show.
[A definite world of difference.]
- Why aren't you talking, Hyo Joo?
- What's wrong?
Was yesterday too tough on you?
Are you upset?
You look like you're upset.
No, not at all.
I'm going to try to be more gentle today.
What a joke. You think
that suits you on Running Man?
- What are you talking about?
- Why is she trying to be more gentle?
[She's not falling for it!
An automatic reflex by now.]
- She's so strong with it now.
- She's comfortable with it now.
She's more forceful with it.
[Ah... I was trying to be more gentle today.]
Let's all get going.
- Let's go.
- Yes, let's go!
[Early Vacation Race- Starts now!]
- Everyone needs to put on their seatbelts.
- Okay.
[Early Vacation Race]
[Go to Jeondongri and
find the Running Man landmark.]
- Okay, Jeongdongri?
- Yes.
- We're on our way.
- This is so nice!
[Everyone on their way with excitement
to their first vacation of the summer!]
- Wow!
- Jeongdongri? Not Jungdongji, right?
You two are friends, right?
Since Jae Suk is friends with Jung Jae,
and you're friends with Jung Jae
does mean that the two of you
are friends?
- No, it doesn't really work that way.
- The reason being...
He was born in '72, and I was born in '73.
- Really?
- So us being friends would complicate things.
I don't think befriending a friend of a friend
and mixing it up like that is a good idea.
- You think so?
- Then Jae Suk would be your 'older brother'?
Of course.
Jung Jae and I are friends because
we were in the army together.
But Woo Sung and Jung Jae still use
honorifics towards one another, don't you?
- Yeah.
- To each other?
- Really?
- Yes.
- Even after being friends all these years.
- Why?
That's what we're comfortable with.
That's how we show respect to
each other as fellow actors.
- Really?
- Yes.
That's so cool.
- Mr. Ha Ha!
- Yes, Mr. Gary?
- Hope you have a wonderful day today.
- Thank you, Sir.
- Let's have a meal together sometime.
- Yes, of course.
Even though we're not really stiff about it,
we do like to use honorifics.
- What are we going to be doing today?
- I had no idea you guys did that.
- Wow...
- They're like a happily married couple.
I think with how they treat each other,
they probably never fight.
- Yes, you're right. We've never fought.
- I bet you're right.
- To be so polite to your friend like that...
- I had no idea.
Since it makes us reconsider our actions
to one another before doing them
we find that we don't really
do anything offensive to one another.
- So we've never fought.
- Wow, that's amazing.
No casual speech to actresses either?
I don't really lower
my speech with them at first.
But once some time passes,
and we get to know each other better...
There was a time when the director yelled
cut during the filming of 'Love Story'
and when I asked if she was okay,
using honorifics then felt rather greasy.
- That didn't feel right.
- You're right.
It's actually better to be
more casual in times like that.
You okay?
[Mr. Gary showing us how it's done.]
- What about Ji Hyo?
- Ask Ji Hyo if she's okay.
Ji Hyo, are you okay?
So that's how it's done!
Nice... that was pretty good.
- He said it differently than you.
- But she's different.
- Why?
- As soon as I saw her yesterday...
I ran in on her and eliminated her
without even saying anything to her.
- He was the Grim Reaper yesterday.
- I thought your eyes were shooting out fire.
They were shooting out flames of fire.
[Last week...]
[Jung Woo Sung, who turned a variety show
into a scene out of an action movie.]
[But today, he's being
transformed into a comedian?]
- Don't you know that this is a variety show?
- Watch and learn.
[A promising variety newbie.]
[Running Man Vacation Plans.]
[Farming field snack game.]
There... there it is.
[Arriving at the first
Early Vacation Race location.]
Wait, this is like the last time
when Hyo Joo was here...
You can each choose one that you like
and change into it.
Woo Sung, you have to choose
one for yourself.
- Seriously?
- You can choose first.
- I think I'm going to go with this one.
- You sure that's not too fashionable for you?
I think I'll go with this grey one.
Kwang Soo loves the animal prints.
You're right.
Kwang Soo does like the animal prints.
But I can't forsake
my preference for him either.
Yes, you're right.
You go with the one you want.
But those pants on you...
- What the heck?
- It's taking on a European feel.
That's not how they're supposed to look.
[Even the work pants
takes on a fashionable look.]
[The man who turned a farming field
into an instant runway.]
Should I change my pants to match
the rest of my team?
Yes, change into this one.
- Okay, I'll do it for the team.
- See? You're supposed to look like Gary.
[The correct way the work-pants
are supposed to look.]
They're supposed to look like the way
they look on Gary right now.
[His body was made to wear the work-pants.]
[So that's what it is...
The body made for a variety show...]
- Then should we switch our pants?
- Want to try switching?
Yes, try switching with him.
It could be the pants.
- Yes, it could be the pants.
- I want to look like Gary.
These pants are very special to me,
but I will still give them to you.
- I think you're getting there.
- That's not it either.
[What?
But those are the same pants!]
How did those pants all of a sudden
turn into shorts?
They look like nice shorts on him.
[They look like three quarter length
work-pants on him.]
They should be pulled over
your bellybutton.
But even those pants look the way they're
supposed to look on Gary.
[No matter what bachelor Gae wears...]
It's the perfect length on him.
[The perfect fit all the way from
his bellybutton right down to his ankles.]
- That's the way they're supposed to fit.
- That's the correct fit.
There's nothing we can do about it.
Kwang Soo... yours is right here.
Thank you, Jae Suk!
- It's the giraffe print.
- Not the giraffe print, but a leopard print.
[Zebra or a leopard print...]
- Do you remember this, Hyo Joo?
- Yes. I'm all too familiar with this.
[All too familiar work-pants to Hyo Joo.]
- You get to wear the pants again.
- This is a familiar sight.
- They look like a stage costume on Junho.
- They look good on Junho too.
[They look like a stage costume for Junho!]
- They look the best on Gary.
- Isn't it perfect on Gary?
You look like you were born
to wear those pants.
I actually gave my original
pair of pants to Woo Sung.
I really wanted his pants.
Okay, everyone.
The name of the first game of the
Early Vacation Race is...
Watermelon loyalty game.
[Watermelon loyalty eating game.]
Watermelon is supposed to be the
specialty in this region.
They're supposed to be very delicious.
- Does anyone know what the loyalty game is?
- Isn't it like a relay?
The last person left has to eat
the remainder of the watermelon?
The members of the team will run around
the course in a relay
and have to eat a whole watermelon
in order to finish the relay.
- The whole watermelon?
- Yes, the whole thing.
This really is a watermelon eating contest.
The game will be played best out of three.
[One whole watermelon has been cut up
in several pieces of various different sizes.]
- You go first, and he'll be the second.
- I think that would be best.
You'll be first, he'll be second, you third,
I'll be the fourth and Hyo Joo the last.
But it's possible that all the watermelon
will be gone with the second person.
- Really? You think he'll do that?
- Yes, I'm serious.
No matter how you guys decide,
you'll have to go by what Jong Kook says.
Why don't you just tell us what to do?
Tell us what the order is going to be.
- Why even bother discussing it?
- No kidding.
- Suk Jin...
- Just do whatever you want then.
We're all just standing around here
waiting for him to make the decision.
- What are you talking about?
- You have two guests on your team.
What are you doing?
[With the two guests on the team,
all are waiting for Captain Kkuk to decide.]
Why don't we all gather around
and say a cheer?
- Fighting.
- Whatever.
[Forcing them into a cheer.]
- Come on.
- How many times do we have to cheer?
[His bulldozer-like leadership skills
are starting to surface.]
Do you want so trade places with me
so you can see what it's like, Woo Sung?
- No, that's okay.
- Seriously.
Why are you forcing us into this?
[All the teammates full of displeasure.]
- Jong Kook is starting to use his hands.
- Come on, let's go.
[Watermelon loyalty eating contest-
Round One.]
You want the small piece or
the big piece?
[First runners up- Jong Kook of the Red Team
and Woo Sung of the Blue Team.]
Nice, Woo Sung!
[The two alpha males giving a proper
watermelon eating show.]
That's unbelievable.
- Jong Kook's really fast too.
- Come on, Warrior!
Warrior?
Jong Kook, did you hear?
She's calling for her warrior!
- Show me what you're capable of!
- What a joke!
Do you want a leg flip?
Look at Woo Sung go!
[Big eater number one.]
[The two men scarfing it down
without any hesitation.]
Jong Kook, eat three more!
You can pass it off to the next, Woo Sung.
Pass it off to the next!
- Great job!
- There you go!
[Woo Sung heads off to 'R2'.]
- Nice. Come on, Ha Ha.
- Pass it over to me.
[Captain Kkuk also stands to pass them off
after eating four huge pieces.]
Eat all the big pieces!
['R2'- Giraffe and Ro-Ro.]
Wow, I'm so full.
Squish it down with your teeth and
get all the juices out!
Press it down!
[Instructing him to eat like
a Spartan would.]
- There you go!
- Kwang Soo...
Wow, you really do look so ugly.
- He really looks like a Super Mario’s Brother.
- He's Waluigi.
- Kwang Soo!
- Save me!
- Slow down. Take it easy.
- Someone please save me!
- You're doing great, Kwang Soo!
- That's good. You're doing good!
- That's good, that's good.
- You need to finish that.
[Ha Ha finishes his portion.]
- Go.
- Nice. You're doing great!
There you go.
You're doing great.
Nice, nice, nice.
There you go. Keep going.
- You can do one more.
- Are you okay?
One more.
I can help him.
[The inexhaustible eater.]
[Scarfing down without any hesitation.]
No, Kwang Soo already ate most of it.
- How many are there left?
- More!
Suck it down.
There you go. More!
There you go.
[Wow... he finished almost all of it!]
[And one more to cleanse his palate.]
Chew while you run!
- Run!
- Here he comes!
[Finally running off to pass it on.]
- They're almost gone?
- It's all over now!
I can't believe he ate it all!
That's amazing.
What the heck!
- Here.
- Shove more in your mouth.
[Red Team heads off to final 'R5' in ease.]
Hand it to Hyo Joo.
[Taking her time to finish
one tiny piece of the watermelon.]
What the heck is this?
Kwang Soo looks like he's
about to get sick.
- You did great.
- I told you Kwang Soo would finish it.
[Red Team Wins!]
Great job.
We won. Great job.
That wasn't so bad, was it?
- Are you okay?
- Look at what you've done to this kid.
This just made me realize
what I'm capable of.
I told you that he can do it.
That's too bad.
We could've won that round.
Why don't I start this time?
Okay, you can go first.
- Then Woo Sung...
- You should go last.
[Entrusting the crucial
'R5' role to Woo Sung?]
- I'll trust in you then.
- Yes, please take care of it.
- Are you guys still not ready yet?
- We're ready.
- We are ready.
- If you are, then let's hurry up and do this.
- Can't you speak in nicer tones?
- That's what I'd like to say to you.
- That's what I'd like to say to you!
- The way you said it was rude!
Why are you spitting
all over our watermelon?
Seriously...
- Your pants are on backwards.
- So what? They're my pants.
- These are my pants.
- Your pockets are on the back.
- Can't you speak nicer?
- Why would I need to do that? These are mine.
- Can't you speak in a nicer tone?
My pants are fine.
This is a fashion statement.
- Okay, let's go!
- Yes, let's go.
Everyone to their positions.
- You're the fourth.
- Okay.
- This is...
- The first person has to eat a lot.
- Okay!
- Okay, I can do that.
- Ha Ha!
- You have to eat as much as you can!
- Jae Suk
- Yes?
- Eat three more pieces than Kwang Soo.
- Don't you worry!
- I'll eat five more than him!
- That's my boy!
Kwang Soo, don't think of it as eating.
You have to squish it down with your
mouth and drink it.
How can you drink a watermelon?
He can't stop with the instructions.
Seriously.
[Round two-
Ro-Ro vs. Hyo Joo.]
Hyo Joo, if you're too full to eat anymore,
pass it off to the next person.
- Fighting!
- There they go.
- Be careful not to trip and fall.
- Ha Ha! You have to eat a lot!
Ha Ha!
Eat as much as you can, Hyo Joo!
- Squish it down, Hyo Joo!
- Hurry! There you go!
Hyo Joo!
Savor the flavor!
- Ha Ha, you have to eat a lot!
- I'm so full!
- You have to eat as fast as you can!
- Just eat!
Don't laugh!
There's no time for laughing!
Be quiet!
Why is she always just yelling at me?
- Don't provoke her, Kwang Soo.
- I didn't even say anything to her.
You have to eat as much as you can, Ha Ha.
Why don't you just...
[Filled to the brim.]
- Okay, that's fine.
- Come pass it off. Come on!
You have to eat more!
Don't stop!
You can't stop right now.
Keep up the pace!
Don't do that to yourself, Dong Hoon!
Just pass it off!
- Why is this thing so heavy?
- I couldn't eat anymore.
Take your time.
Take your time running.
Take your time running, Ha Ha.
['R2'- Blank Ji vs. Big-nosed Brother.]
How many are there left?
About 48?
Eat some bigger pieces, Suk Jin!
He's eating the smallest pieces
he can find.
[Nibbling away at the smallest pieces.]
He's choosing the smallest pieces and
leaving the larger ones for others.
What are you doing?
[Blank Ji showing her eating skills.]
[Blank Ji sure is a good eater...]
You're doing great, Ji Hyo!
Ji Hyo is doing really great.
[Giant bites vs. Tiny bites.]
Suk Jin ate about 15 pieces
that are this size.
- What?
- What is he doing!
- That's all he's doing.
- Why aren't you eating bigger pieces?
- I think I ate about eight pieces!
- You're amazing!
- I'm so full!
- You're doing great!
- Ji Hyo, you're doing great!
- Junho, it's going to be up to you!
- You're already done?
- That's so weak!
- Why are there still so many left?
- This is too much.
You did great!
- Gary, I'm so full!
- Okay, hand me a piece!
This is for you, Ji Hyo!
- Gary's looking good.
- Good, good. He's quick.
[Gary's eating show.]
- Gary's doing great.
- Great job.
Okay, Gary!
Gary's really...
he seriously looks like he's taking a break
from doing field work to have a snack.
- You must like watermelons.
- Yes, watermelons are great.
- How often do you eat it?
- I have watermelon three times a day.
- Gary's really good.
- He's in his element.
Here, have another one.
[And he and Blank Ji are so in sync.]
[Eating whatever is handed to him.]
Stop talking and just eat.
Just know that I'm not coming
home tonight.
I don't think this is working.
Finish that one and go to the next person.
- You can stop eating too.
- Here they come.
They're coming.
They're both coming right now.
[The teams at a similar level.]
You did good, Junho.
[Giraffe and Yoo Hyuk's turn.]
Come on, Jae Suk!
Eat!
What is he doing?
[Huh?]
Hey!
- Take your time.
- Hey!
Hey!
[Choosing to pass it off to 'R5' after
barely eating half a piece.]
You!
I'm going to...
Don't lose your pace because of him!
Don't lose your pace!
[Yoo Hyuk still eating as well as he came.]
[Still a lot of watermelon left
for the Red Team.]
- Are you out of your mind?
- Jae Suk is eating really fast!
- How is he supposed to eat all that?
- Jong Kook can do it!
[Giraffe getting his revenge.]
Fighting!
He's so fast!
He such a fast eater.
[Will they be able to win again like
the last round?]
If you're slowing down, pass it off to me.
Hurry up!
Hurry, hurry!
Jong Kook is working really fast on it.
Nice, nice, nice!
- There you go!
- That's the way to eat it!
- Hurry! We have to hurry!
- Okay, there you go!
[The Blue Team ups their speed
and passes it off to 'R5'.]
Let's go!
[Passes off to handsome Woo Sung.]
They don't have many left.
You have to eat faster!
[A huge difference between
the two teams.]
- How did you eat all that, Jae Suk?
- We're going to lose this.
- It's not over yet.
- Let's cheer Kim Jong Kook on!
- Kim Jong Kook! Kim Jong Kook!
- There's no way they'll finish that.
[The last spurt of gorging.]
[Woo Sung eating two pieces at a time!]
- What is he doing?
- He's not kidding around!
[He's one serious eater.]
You can set that one down now.
Okay, set that down.
[Great teamwork with Blank Ji.]
Nice!
[Captain Kkuk also taking on
two pieces at once.]
Woo Sung is almost done.
[As if grinding down with a mixer.]
Look at him grinding that down!
Grind that down!
[The ace with fire in his eyes.]
[Guinness World Book of Records?
Eating five pieces all at the same time.]
Nice!
Great job, Jung Woo Sung!
He's already done with it!
Wow, he's done!
Just think of it as
eating a hamburger.
[That's just absurd.]
Come on, eat!
You said you can do it.
You said grind it down like a mixer
and drink it up!
So do it like you said.
Let's see how well you
can grind it down.
Come on, grind it down!
That's hilarious!
[Eating with some ease...]
We're done, we're done.
Wow, Jung Woo Sung is
such a good eater!
- He's no joke.
- He's like a food fighter.
He really is a food fighter.
Jung Woo Sung, the food fighter.
Why is he being so serious about it?
This is a variety show.
Why are you being so serious about it?
I'm a variety rookie.
I've got a definite feel for it now.
Did you see his expression?
He looked like he did in his movie, 'Beat'!
- That's what he's always like.
- We won!
Okay!
- Okay.
- Let's go.
[Blue Team having finished their pile.]
Look at Jong Kook.
[You're dead!]
Seriously... I'm so full.
[Blue Team Wins!]
[Blue Team having shown
their great teamwork skills.]
Do you even want to win?
- You only ate one before you passed it off.
- Sorry, I'm sorry.
I guess I expected too much
from Jong Kook.
What the heck did you just say?
- This is the last round.
- The last round.
- This is the deciding round.
- How much do we have to eat now?
This is all you have.
[Final round only consists of five pieces.]
One person can't eat all of them, right?
Everyone has to eat one.
- You can't have any left in the mouth either.
- How about whistle blowing?
That's up to you guys.
The reason being,
did you see how Kwang Soo ate his?
He went off to the next person with
his mouth still full of watermelon.
When did I do that?
You really like to exaggerate things.
Just like how a squirrel stuffs his mouth
full of acorn nuts?
He's basically saying that he's angry.
- What's wrong with him?
- Why are you so competitive?
I'm not being competitive,
but games should be played fair and square.
[Rookie's opinion on game playing-
Games should be played fair and square.]
- Woo Sung is a real chatterbox.
- Yes, I see that.
He really likes to talk.
[Woo Sung finally opening up and
talking out on the field?]
I have good hearing, a small heart,
and I chatter nonstop.
- That's what I'm saying.
- So you're similar to me.
No, you and I are not similar.
[Variety rookie Woo Sung drawing a
clear line on what is and what isn't.]
- Let's win it this time!
- Okay, let's win!
Okay, fighting!
[Hyo Joo and Ro-Ro starting
the round off again.]
Ha Ha, Ha Ha!
- Take your time, take your time! Don't rush.
- You have to run!
- Just one. You just need to eat one.
- Just eat one and hurry!
- Hyo Joo, what are you doing?
- It's okay!
- Hyo Joo, hurry!
- Take your time.
Nice, nice!
- Swallow it.
- Cover Ha Ha's mouth.
He whistled!
[Entertainer Hyo Joo
resorting to physical force.]
What are they doing?
[Off to 'R2']
- Ji Hyo, Ji Hyo!
- Come on, Ji Hyo!
[No one beats Blank Ji
when it comes to eating.]
You can do this!
We have to win this.
- Is she finished?
- Let's win this thing, Ji Hyo!
- Nice, nice.
- Whistle, Junho!
Nice!
[Arriving at 'R3' almost simultaneously.]
You have to sit down and eat.
You have to sit down and eat, Suk Jin.
Suk Jin, you have to sit down.
- Hurry! Hurry up and get going.
- Come on!
Suk Jin!
Come on, Suk Jin!
[Blue Team ahead by a small distance.]
Fighting, Gary!
Eat faster!
[The final 'R5'!]
[The watermelon falls to the ground...]
Hey!
[In the meantime,
he's already done with his piece.]
- That's good. That's good enough.
- You're good.
We won!
[Blue Team wins!]
How could you have dropped it!
- How could you have dropped that!
- I'm sorry!
[Giraffe of misfortune
losing for the team yet again.]
- Good job.
- You did good.
Good job.
- Can we do that round one more time?
- No.
You did great.
Hyo Joo is beating up Kwang Soo right now.
What are you doing?
What did you do that for?
I can't believe Kwang Soo dropped that.
The winning team of the
first watermelon eating game is...
The Blue Team!
[Watermelon eating game-
Blue Team Wins!]
The Blue Team gets the chance
to pick first.
- This?
- Gary and Ji Hyo, you each pick one.
- I'll take number one.
- Okay, number one.
[Gary chooses number one.]
[Digital camera]
That's nothing special.
I have one at home.
I don't care about that.
- That's not even a good pick.
- He is just so spiteful.
I'll just give you mine from home.
I can just get another one.
Number eleven.
[Ji Hyo chooses number eleven.]
- Come on, sunscreen?
- It's okay, I need some sunscreen.
I like getting a tan.
I don't use any sunscreen.
Wow, this is great.
It's our turn now.
- Hyo Joo, why don't you pick one?
- You can pick it, Hyo Joo.
- How about number two?
- Number two!
[Read Team's Hyo Joo chooses number two.]
- An ice box? I need one of those.
- Those are heavy to carry around.
- I need one of those.
- What for? You already have a fridge.
Why don't you pick one yourself?
- How about you pick one?
- You can pick it.
- You pick it, Jong Kook.
- Yes, pick one.
- Okay, number six.
- Number six.
[Oh my...]
Everyone...
[How can that be?]
Why does it feel like we're the losers
when I know we won the game?
Just because we lost doesn't
necessarily mean it's a bad thing.
No thanks to you, I have to listen to
Jong Kook even more now!
I'll pledge to do even better
from now on!
Listening to me isn't such a bad thing.
- He really is Mr. Capable.
- Isn't he?
Let's get going to the next location.
I didn't even think of picking number six.
- But it comes down to the end anyway.
- That's true.
Just tell them to take it all then.
- I can't believe you chose the TV.
- I know.
- I couldn't believe when I saw that up there.
- I somehow got lucky with the pick.
That's why we have no choice
but to listen to you.
What I'd like to tell you all is...
listening to me isn't such a bad thing.
- It could be beneficial to listen to me.
- I realized it the last time I was here too.
I really thought that you had
some special skills and powers or something.
But I always feel like I'm getting scolded.
I don't usually hesitate,
and I try to look at the odds.
Even though it pisses me off,
he does bring good results.
And once the filming is over...
I go home and sleep for
two days straight.
- Oh my God!
- What? What is it?
Look at that.
Is something going to
fall off that thing?
[Choongnam's water reservoir.]
[Something large has been set up
in the reservoir...]
- Look at what those guys are wearing.
- I'm getting a bad feeling about this.
- What could this be for?
- What are we going to be doing?
I really am getting a nervous feeling.
Why are there helmets?
What are these for?
This is the Blob Jump, which was the costliest
to set up in all 152 episodes we've done.
[Welcome to Blob Jump]
- Blob Jumps are synonymous with vacations.
- What did you say?
This is a water sport that is enjoyed
by people all around the world.
[Currently hot trending world sport.]
[Blob Jump having started over in Europe
makes its way over to Running Man!]
[Early Vacation Race's second course-
Blob Jump Competition.]
This is a record competition.
The team that scores the
highest jump wins.
[Three members per team will jump,
and the team with the highest record wins!]
The specialists behind you will first
demonstrate how it's done.
[Blob Jump's demonstration to start.]
The specialists will get a high record.
- And you guys will do what you're shown.
- We're actually going to do this?
[Step One- One person to place themselves
in front of the tube.]
So the guy jumping right now doesn't
determine the score?
[Oh!]
- Are you sure that he's a specialist?
- Does he know what he's doing?
- What's he doing?
- What was that?
- You don't have to be cool about it.
- That was about two flips in the air.
- Are you sure he's not an entertainer?
- You did that on purpose, right?
He almost fell down to the water.
Are you sure he's not a specialist
on Running Man?
So once the other person falls,
I'm sure it makes the first one fly.
[Step Two- The other three people
then jump onto the back of the tube.]
Okay, take a close look.
These are specialists of the sport.
They're going to show you their jump.
Everyone take a close look.
One, two, three!
[Flies high into the air and dives into
the water after midair acrobatic moves.]
Wow, awesome!
You really are a specialist!
[Mistake that he made a minute ago
has all been forgiven!]
- I didn't know he'd fly so high into the air!
- What the heck is that?
How can a person fly so high
into the air like that?
- It needs to be a lighter person up front.
- Hyo Joo, you do it. You're perfect for it.
- That's no joke.
- How is that any different from bungee?
Just fall on your butt.
You just need to bend your back
while looking out into the distance.
Because you'll be shot
straight into the air like that.
Thank you so much.
That was very cool.
- That was really cool.
- That was awesome!
[That looks like fun.]
Jong Kook, why don't you
show us how it's done?
Since you've been telling us how good you are,
show us how it's done.
There's no real reason for me
to do all that.
- I was just explaining things to you.
- Since you explained it all to us...
Why don't you show us in action
how you're really supposed to do it.
And the three of us will jump.
- Which one of us will do it?
- It can't be a heavy person.
[Important for the three people jumping
on the back to be in sync.]
We have to land on our butt.
- I think we need to lift up one of our legs.
- Yes, that's right.
We need to land on our back as
we lift up one of our legs.
And we have to focus on that red point
as our target when we jump.
Just think of it as lying on your back
as you jump off the platform.
- This isn't your team.
- Just think of landing on your back.
You just go home and lay down.
If you lift just one leg,
your body may tilt too much to the side.
So as you lift up your leg,
you have to tilt your body backwards.
Are you a bully of this reservoir?
What's wrong with you?
- Why are you coming to bother us?
- No, I'm not doing that.
Seriously.
[Playing Paper-Rock-Scissors to decide
which team will be the one to go first.]
Paper-Rock-Scissors!
[Win - Lose]
Don't make me do
Paper-Rock-Scissors.
- Can you do it with someone else?
- Paper-Rock-Scissors. I won.
- I just won again.
- Thanks.
Paper-Rock-Scissors.
[Wins again!]
- Let's try it again.
- Paper-Rock-Scissors.
Come on, isn't that enough?
How many do I have to win?
- You're going to win again.
- Paper-Rock-Scissors. Paper-Rock-Scissors.
I'm going to say it.
- I'm going to say it. Paper-Rock-Scissors.
- Fine, do it.
Paper-Rock-Scissors.
[All- Kill!
Suk Jin wins five in a row!]
[Big-nosed Brother truly is
a Paper-Rock-Scissors genius?]
- How did that happen?
- It's because I was standing next to you.
- Is that why I did so well?
- Of course.
- Seriously...
- See? I'm a winning charm.
Turning my Paper-Rock-Scissors winnings...
Hurry up and get up there.
Okay, Blue Team first.
- Me.
- You're going to jump?
[First jumper for the Blue Team-
Jung Woo Sung.]
[He'll be the first to challenge
the Blob Jump in Running Man history!]
[That's... high...]
Remember how even the specialist
rolled backwards earlier?
- He almost rolled off that thing.
- He was rolling off of it.
It's not an easy thing to do.
- Fighting!
- Okay.
The Blue Team's... first human bullet.
Just call me the human rifle.
Okay, I'm going to jump.
- He's so full of gusto.
- Gusto!
- Don't try to be too cool about it.
- Woo Sung!
[Cooley shaking the hands of
his comrades in a greeting.]
- Is it really high up there?
- No, it's nice up here.
- It's high, isn't it?
- It's not bad once you're up here.
- It's not high up there?
- Your face is white as a ghost.
- You look like you're scared.
- Are you nervous?
- You know what he said earlier?
He said he actually is scared, but he doesn't
want to show it since it's a variety show.
No, that's not what I said.
But that since this is a variety show,
it is okay to show that I'm scared.
- Since this is my first time doing it.
- Of course.
- No! You have to look cool.
- Really?
You have to always look cool.
Shall we get started?
- He's scared right now.
- You can see his hesitation.
- Okay, the human bullet is going to jump.
- Okay.
It would actually be weirder
if he wasn't scared.
[First human bullet, Jang Woo Sung
is locked and loaded!]
[The fear is only momentary...]
[In this moment, I am free...]
[Into the water?]
[And in that crevice of all places?]
That was such a bad show.
That was awful.
He fell in the water!
- He fell in the water.
- That was hilarious.
What are you doing, Woo Sung?
[The power of the Blob Jump turns even
the coolest man in Korea into a comedian.]
[Instantly transforming him into someone who's
more like friend from your neighborhood.]
That's not at all the image I've seen of him
portrayed in his movies.
I was shocked for a moment thinking
that you weren't wearing any pants.
[Assuming his cool demeanor once again
no matter what the others are saying.]
Don't pretend to be cool now.
It's already too late.
We've seen what you're really like.
This is entertainment.
- Is that what you call it?
- He's good.
[Belatedly realizing how funny he can be.]
- That's really high up.
- Woo Sung.
- Don't you feel confident about it now?
- It's no longer scary, right?
- Not scary, right? It's no big deal.
- Yes, you're right.
But why did you fall in the water?
There's a little gap between that thing.
- There's a gap.
- Are you okay?
They should've told us that
there's a gap.
I'm sorry, but if you fall again,
we'll go after that.
If you feel bad about saying it,
then don't say it at all.
- We want to take our turn.
- Woo Sung's good at physical gags.
[And it's twice as funny seeing someone who's
normally so cool doing funny gags.]
If Woo Sung does it again this time,
you guys can take your turn.
Yes, okay.
- You're no longer nervous, right?
- Yes, of course.
[There was a deep meaning behind all this?
So that they'd shed their nervous energy?]
- We really did shed our nervous energy.
- That was too funny.
- This is your last chance.
Of all the male guests we've had thus far,
he is the funniest with physical gags.
[Funniest physical gags out of all the
male guests they've had so far.]
Fighting!
But I... no, okay.
- If you have something to say, then say it.
- He lost his desire to speak.
- Let him concentrate.
- Okay, here I go.
[Woo Sung's second attempt at
becoming the human bullet.]
[Again?]
[Two physical gags in a row.]
Jung Woo Sung really is so funny.
Why is he just doing his first variety show?
Jung Woo Sung is the best of
all physical gag do-ers.
[Even the national MC is impressed with
his ability to make others laugh.]
You're hilarious!
I can't believe how funny he is.
I keep wanting to make you guys laugh.
What are you doing?
[Even bigger laughs from his attempt
at trying to explain his reasoning.]
[The ultimate actor, Jung Woo Sung...
And now, the ultimate bringer of laughter!]
Okay, we're going to start
doing this seriously now.
Okay, Red Team's turn to go up.
- This isn't easy.
- I feel like I'm boarding a plane.
[Coach Kkuk is the first jumper
for the Red Team.]
- It doesn't look that high up from here.
- I know.
I know that people say that Running Man
is all about extreme games and sports...
But it's all about the eating games.
I ate all the watermelon, and now the water.
- We're all about eating.
- Eating contests.
- Fighting!
I can understand what
you were feeling now, Woo Sung.
Jump further than you think you should.
[Red Team's Coach Kkuk is
locked and loaded, and ready to go!]
[Oh!]
[Oh! He gets himself situated!]
But isn't he... oh, okay.
- Suk Jin, you fall for longer than you think.
- What?
- Really?
- Yeah.
- This is scary.
- This looks scary.
- It's pretty high up there.
- You have to jump all at once.
- Challenge.
- Challenge!
[Will they be able to
jump together simultaneously?]
- Let's go!
- Let's do this!
- Fighting!
- Look straight ahead!
One... two... three!
Three!
- Why are you jumping?
- Hey!
Do it right!
- Do it right!
- Cheer us on, Hyo Joo!
- Fighting!
- You can do this!
[Will they do it this time?]
One, two, three!
[There they go!]
[A pretty high jump!]
[Coach Kkuk of the Red Team
succeeds at the Blob Jump!]
- We did it!
- Did you see that?
- That was a pretty good jump.
It's fun!
It's fun.
- That wasn't so bad at all!
- That's how you do it.
- It really hurt my butt when we fell through.
It really stung my hips.
Here's the record for Kim Jong Kook
and the Red Team.
Kim Jong Kook's record is, 5m 70cm.
[Coach Kkuk of the Red Team's
Blob Jump record- 5m 70cm.]
[Nice, Coach Kkuk!]
- Nice, that was great.
- Hold hands when you jump.
- Hold hands and stay close when you jump.
- Stick close together.
Okay, we can take care of it ourselves.
We'll do it ourselves.
- We can do this.
- You should listen and learn from us.
But even if you teach this team a lesson,
they don't have me.
But we have Jung Woo Sung.
We're actually happier because
you're not on our team.
[Blue Team's Jung Woo Sung
takes another attempt at the jump.]
- Are you not scared anymore?
- It's not scary anymore.
- It's only scary right before you jump.
- You flew so high up in the air.
- This is really scary.
- This is no joke.
- Should I go in the middle?
- Yeah, you go in the middle.
Jung Woo Sung, fighting!
- One, two...
- Then we land like this.
- We're all set. We're going to win this.
- We're good.
- You can trust us, Woo Sung.
- Okay.
- Here I go.
- Okay. You can do it.
- Stop worrying about us.
- This parts harder than you'd think.
I'm even more concerned about
making the same mistake again.
I'm more concerned about falling
through the cracks again.
- I know.
- Show them how to do it.
[What if I fall in the water again?]
- They're going to think you're scared.
- It's not because I'm scared.
- He did it.
- He did it this time.
[He does it this time!]
- Nice job, Woo Sung!
- You're so happy about it!
I've succeeded my mission now.
Am I finished?
- No? Do I need to go up further?
- You have to go up to the front.
You have to go up
to the front point of the tube.
- Don't be scared and jump, okay?
- But you looked scared right now.
- No, I'm okay to jump.
- Look at him.
- The three scaredy cats are up there.
- This is going to be fun.
[Will they be able to jump?]
This is funny.
This is way fun.
Trust in each other
and jump on the count of three.
[That's easier said than done...]
Okay, I'm ready.
Let's all do this with our legs.
[None of the three look like
they want to jump on the tube.]
- Woo Sung, are you ready?
- I'm ready!
[Moments before Jung Woo Sung's
first Blob Jump!]
- Two...
- Let us count.
It's up to us to count.
You can't count for us.
- Don't be scared.
- We'll do it.
- We can't get scared.
- We have to do this for the jump.
- This is fun!
- Let's do this quickly.
[Pathetic...]
Hurry up and jump!
- All together.
- Set, go.
One, two, three!
[Jump]
There you go!
[Jung Woo Sung's blob jump... Success!]
[Even though he's flailing around
in the air...]
[He falls into the water with flair!]
- We did it.
- That was a nice job done.
[Satisfied]
- He didn't fly up too high.
- No, that wasn't very high up.
[What's the record for
Blue Team's Woo Sung?]
[Woo Sung finally succeeds
on his third attempt.]
- No, you did get some height.
- Is it fun?
It really is fun. But I wanted to turn my
body but I couldn't get it to do that.
Good, that was a good job.
[The highest record thus far is
Jong Kook's at 5m 70cm.]
- Blue Team's is, 5m...
- Is it more than 5m?
[Woo Sung of the Blue Team's record...
5m... 10cm.]
- Okay, we did it.
- You were off sync and fell after us.
- I think a lighter person needs to do it.
- It's all about the weight.
We're warning you right now,
we're going to beat our previous record.
Junho is going to take the challenge
and be the jumper this time.
Junho's already jumping?
He's the ace of that team.
Are we supposed to be scared
of that warning right now?
At least be nervous about it.
- You're not scared?
- No, I'm not scared.
I think jumping together in sync is
the most important thing.
[As predicted, the most important thing is
for the three back jumpers to be in sync.]
Do you know what you guys looked like?
Instead of you guys hearing each other,
you all had the same blank look on your face.
- Like this.
- We were all thinking about something else.
Yeah, we were thinking about
something else.
But it really is scary up there.
You have to break all the records.
You're our ace.
[Second jumper for the Red Team- Junho!]
- Let's fly!
- Make it so they can't even attempt it.
- Be quick like we were!
- Can I go now?
It's not as easy as it looks.
[Jumps without any hesitation
and falls on the tube safely.]
- That's our ace!
- He's our ace!
- That's good.
- You're going to get the best record.
This is tough.
Even though our record may be low,
no one can be funnier than us!
[No one can even come close.]
And not just once, but twice!
- Kick up your leg and lean on your back.
- Jump at once?
- Lay on your back or stare out front?
- You have to stare out front.
[Why are they talking so much
when all they need to do is jump?]
Okay, ready?
- Okay, ready?
- Jump on three.
- Am I good to trust you?
- Here we go!
This is fun!
This is really enjoyable!
- Okay, I'll do it.
- No hesitating, okay?
- We have to jump, okay?
- Jump all at once.
Here we go!
One, two, three!
[Look straight ahead... and jump!]
We're going to lose.
[This is...
what you call acrobatic diving.]
[Junho of the Red Team succeeds
the blob jump with flair!]
How did it turn out?
- Was it good?
- That was awesome!
- That was great!
- The Red Team's record...
The record is, 6m 36cm.
- How was it, Hyo Joo!
- You guys were so cool!
- Why are you looking at us like that?
- What's with the expression, Ji Hyo?
- We can do better.
- Trust us.
- Woo Sung's going to be in the middle now.
- Don't you worry!
- I'll do it this time.
- That was so cool.
I really wasn't thinking of anything,
but when I was lifted up into the air...
- When that happened, my mind went blank.
- Really?
- How does it feel up in the air?
- You have your legs spread apart in the air
so when you're up there, your body is flailing
and you're unable to control your body.
Is there a need for us to dissect
and pull it apart detail by detail like this?
- I'm just telling you how it is.
- Lets just be happy about it.
Let's just enjoy this moment.
[Second jumper for the Red Team-
Yoo Jae Suk.]
[Hates anything up high,
and hates jumping off of it even more!]
[But I still have to jump!]
Keep your eyes straight ahead!
Okay, here I go!
[After a nice fall... kerplunk.]
[No one beats this guy
in the comedy department...]
- But I had a nice fall!
- That was too funny.
[Seeing him trying so hard not to fall
in the water is even funnier.]
- Did you hear him while he was falling?
- Hey!
I'm going to have to do that again!
Once that happens,
that's all you're concerned about.
This is driving me nuts.
I can't believe that happened.
- Jung Woo Sung had to do it twice.
- You have to jump towards the middle.
- How did I jump?
- I'm not sure either.
- You can't let Woo Sung beat you.
- You know what the important thing is?
I bet Woo Sung's feeling much better
about himself right now.
[Junior in the gag reel department
feeling slightly better now.]
Now that someone else besides
himself did what he did.
That is really tiring though.
Okay, here I go again.
[Jae Suk, locked and loaded!]
[Smack dab in the middle this time.]
Ugh, that was scary.
I seriously feel like I'm going to die.
It's simple. Land on your butt.
It won't hurt on your butt.
[It's time for the three to jump again.]
- Set your right foot over here.
- Fighting!
- Okay.
- Okay, one, two, three.
There you go!
Awesome!
Wow, that was good!
[Flying... straight up in the air!]
That was awesome!
[Even at a quick glance,
it's sure to be a great record!]
You did it!
- That was good.
- That was higher than mine?
[My goodness... Jae Suk did that?]
The Blue Team's record is...
7m 28cm.
[Jae Suk of the Blue Team's record is-
7m 28cm!]
Awesome!
[The welcome party?]
I saw him screaming in terror as he was
lifted up into the air.
[Flailing as a grasshopper would
leaping through the air.]
But it wasn't as bad as I thought.
Up to this point.
- To where?
- You have to keep your head up not to turn.
Relax your body, sit up
and don't be tense about it.
- Okay.
- So you're listening to me now?
- Listen to me, and I'll tell you about it.
- I don't think he's right for it.
Woo Sung was a better jumper.
You have to relax your body
and don't be tense.
[But they were just saying the three jumpers
in the back did a good job...]
Listen to me after you listen
to Woo Sung.
- Listen and learn!
- You weigh a lot, right, Woo Sung?
No, no.
This is all about being in sync.
- How much do you weigh?
- You have to be in sync.
- Just tell us how much you weigh.
- Why, how much do you weigh?
- How much do you think I weigh?
- 85 kg?
- Are we going to do this or not?
- I weigh 80kg.
- 80?
- Don't lie to us.
- But I weigh 78kg.
- I'm serious.
- Why did you get so fat? Lose some weight.
- What did you say?
- How am I heavy?
- How much do you all weigh?
- Lose some weight!
- I weigh 78kg.
- That's not too heavy.
- We did a good job with our jump.
- Yeah, you did really good.
- I got that feeling.
- Why are you standing like that?
- I'm just hanging my fingers.
Because it's comfortable?
[What's wrong with you...]
- What's wrong with you?
- Is it your first time?
Just pretend you didn't see that.
Like we didn't see it?
[Current highest record-
Jae Suk of the Blue Team's 7m 28cm.]
[Blue Team's final jumper is Ace Ji Hyo!]
There you go!
- You're doing good.
- Did you see her do that?
That's how you do it, Hyo Joo.
[The three back jumpers are-
Woo Sung, Jae Suk and Ha Ha.]
We need to do it quickly
once Ji Hyo is ready.
Let's see what you can do, Song Ji Hyo!
[We'll help Ace Ji Hyo fly into the air!]
- Okay, here we go.
- Okay!
[Here we go!]
[Ji Hyo is airborne!]
[Unbelievable height!]
[Even though it's just for a little while,
it's like flying through the air!]
How was Ji Hyo?
[Our fearless ace!]
[Totally psyched up!]
- That was so much fun!
- Are you okay, Ji Hyo?
- It's fun?
- She says that was fun!
- That was no joke!
- I bet she got at least 9m!
I feel like she got 10m on that.
[She's not our ace for nothing!]
[Blue Team's mood is definitely uplifted!]
- Ji Hyo, you're the best!
- That was awesome!
Okay, the record is...
She scored the highest record.
- Yes!
- 7m 86cm!
[Ace Ji Hyo of the Blue Team's record-
7m 86cm!]
That was awesome.
What happened to Ji Hyo?
Woo Sung was very good to lead.
- No, it was all teamwork.
- When I was up in the air...
When I saw the water below me...
that was amazing!
That was so much fun.
I could see all the water beneath me.
[This may have to become Running Man's
new repertoire for our Blank Ji.]
I saw her face when she
was up in the air.
She had the biggest grin on her face.
[Ace Ji Hyo with a huge grin on her face
in the middle of the air.]
But my butt really hurts right now.
Your butt hurts?
Let me see.
I guess I can't do anything for her.
That was the most fun ever.
The Red Team has to beat their record of
7m 86cm.
I think Hyo Joo is going to fly really high.
If you beat this,
your next movie is going to be a hit.
Challenge!
- Challenge!
- I can't believe how that got her.
[Will Hyo Joo of the Red Team be able to
beat the record of 7m 86cm?]
[Hyo Joo following Ji Hyo's method.]
- You're doing great!
- That was good, Hyo Joo.
Let's break the 8m record.
Hyo Joo.... fighting!
Let's win this thing.
8m, okay?
There's nothing to this, guys.
Let's practice our timing.
One, two, three.
Okay?
Just keep your eyes straight ahead.
Hyo Joo!
Look up into the sky.
[Sky...]
Hey, Han Hyo Joo!
What are you doing?
- I think she's scared.
- No, she's just ready for you guys.
Okay, here we go!
- Let's practice one more time.
- Just jump!
One, two, three.
Okay.
They don't care about Hyo Joo at all.
[Sky...]
[Will she beat Ji Hyo's record for the win?]
Here we go.
One, two, three!
[She's flying!]
[Flying up into the air
at an incredible height!]
[Hyo Joo flying beautifully into the air...]
[What will the Red Team's
Hyo Joo's record be?]
That hurts!
That really hurts your butt.
[Does it really hurt?]
Yes, I'm fine.
You scared us for a moment.
- Come here, Kwang Soo.
- It's another amazing record.
[It's finally time for Hyo Joo of
the Red Team's record to be revealed!]
[If she beats Ji Hyo's record of 7m 86cm,
they win the game!]
- Let's win this!
- You need it for your next movie!
- Okay, good luck.
- You win this and your next film is a hit!
- Let's do this!
- Red Team's record is...
8m...
- Minus...
- What the heck?
His personality keeps on getting worse.
It's above 7m 50cm.
So her record is...
7m...
72cm.
[Blue Team's Ji Hyo- 7m 86cm.
Red Team's Hyo Joo- 7m 72cm.]
[Ji Hyo has the highest record!
Blue Team wins the blob jump race!]
[So close...]
- That was so close.
- That was a close call.
[Since Woo Sung is her co-star in the movie,
he's sure to see the success as well!]
The Blue Team will now choose their two
prize numbers for having won the game.
- Okay.
- Blue Team first?
- I'll choose one.
- Okay, pick.
- I've been wanting to pick, number 12.
- Number 12!
[Luxury picnic mat]
I can sit on the picnic mat after
I slather myself with the sunscreen.
You must be happy.
Okay, I'll pick this time.
- Number seven.
- He's not going to get anything.
- He's picking next to the TV.
- Number seven.
Number seven isn't going to be anything.
[Fan]
I can sit on the picnic mat with the fan
once I put the sunscreen on.
- That's not bad.
- That's a pretty good idea.
[That sounds like a good summer activity.]
- Okay, our turn?
- How about Junho pick one?
- Okay.
- Number four looks good.
- I want number eight.
- I said, number four.
[Luxury tent]
[Perfect for camping!]
- Tent is perfect!
- Why do I feel like we lost again?
- Number four?
- Four?
That was Suk Jin's pick.
- Number four!
- Coffee.
[Rice]
- We have to eat!
- Don't pretend you're happy about it.
[It is nice, but for a vacation,
it's a little...]
[Lunch time]
[Nice and plump grilled eel]
[Even the local specialty, Hanwoo beef!]
[A table worthy enough to make
their mouths water.]
Wow, that's so good.
- That really tastes fresh.
- It is delicious.
Wow, this is so good!
[The deliciousness of the beef makes
everyone forget what they were going to say.]
- That's really good.
- Better than you expected, right?
- Beef... eel...
- Beef?
Eel too?
That's awesome!
- Can we just eat?
- I'm so happy!
Here, sit down over here.
You didn't have this specially prepared
for us, did you, Woo Sung?
No, not at all.
[Everyone's astounded by the delicious
taste of the grilled beef.]
That really is good.
I feel so much better to be eating.
You look like you're feeling alive again.
You're starting to talk again.
It's raining.
[Everything else is nice, but
raindrops are suddenly starting to fall.]
You can just stay seated.
Why are you being so nice to us?
What are you doing?
What are you going to do to us?
Why are you doing this?
- Only Kwang Soo's not covered.
- Don't you think you're going too far?
[Kwang Soo's the only one
not covered under the canopy...]
[Giraffe of misfortune.
Having picked that seat of all places...]
[Nice breeze from the water...]
[Having finished their lunch under
the elegant canopy setting.]
Yes, it was delicious.
[A traditional wrestling ring
next to the ferry dock.]
Next up is the wrestling match.
[The third course of the Vacation Race-
Riverside All-Kill wrestling match.]
- We'll just stay in this order.
- Song Ji Hyo, you think you can take me on?
Of course!
We're all set.
Okay, then first up is
Gary and Lee Kwang Soo.
[First match- Blue Team's Gary
vs. Red Team's Kwang Soo.]
Fighting, Gary!
[The winner will keep on
staying in the battle.]
Finish it, Kwang Soo.
[The two men grabbing each other by
their ties in the sandy ring.]
Wait, it's not going in.
Hang on.
Hang on! Where do
you think you're going with that?
- I'm not doing anything!
- What are you doing?
I just got my tailbone to stop stinging.
Hang on.
Wait, I'm not ready!
[Giraffe trying to overpower Gary
with his height.]
Nice, Gary.
[Start match]
[New attack method?
Giraffe lifting Gary up above the ground?]
What is he doing?
[He was just going to flip him over,
but Gary is holding on for his dear life.]
[Gary sticking to him like glue
and not letting go.]
[Red Team's Giraffe wins!]
- Lee Kwang Soo!
- Make it an All-Kill.
- Kill them all.
- Kwang Soo... is like an insect.
What do you mean, an insect?
I'm a human being!
- That really hurts my pride.
- It's okay.
- Who's next?
It's me.
- It really hurts my pride.
- Come on, Ji Hyo.
[Giraffe catcher,
Blank Ji makes her entrance.]
- Her, she's the trickiest.
- Watch yourself, Kwang Soo.
Remember that I'm a girl,
so this is a loser wrestle game.
- Get Gary's revenge.
- Crush him, Ji Hyo.
Take them all down, Kwang Soo!
[Round Two- Blue Team's Blank Ji
vs. Red Team's Kwang Soo]
- It's all you, Ji Hyo.
- I'm doing this for real.
- Yes, you should do that.
- I'm going to treat you like a guy.
Fighting.
[Match Start]
[Blank Ji taking both her feet off the ground
as soon as the match starts.]
Kick him in the butt!
- Kick him in the butt.
- Kick him.
[Knee kicks!]
[Just then!]
[Kwang Soo using the weight of his body
to flip his body around.]
[However!]
[Blank Ji's knee touches the ground first!]
[Blue Team's Blank Ji wins!]
Song Ji Hyo won?
[My goodness...]
- Good job! That's out Song Ji Hyo.
- Ji Hyo doesn't mess around.
[Ace Ji Hyo not going easy on the men!]
- Ji Hyo, just go with the regular way.
- It's Suk Jin, you can take him.
What are you doing?
[Blank Ji provoking easy prey,
Big-nosed Brother.]
Nice, Ji Hyo!
Show us what you did.
- Nice!
- I know Ji Hyo's played around!
I knew it.
I knew she's played around a bit.
- Win or lose?
- What would you like?
I'll do whichever one you want.
- She asks him what he wants to do.
- What the heck is that?
- That really is a wound to my pride.
- Do the loser wrestle and take her down.
- Let's go with the losing one.
- Losing wrestling game?
- Okay.
- Ji Hyo, do the regular one.
- The regular way?
- No!
I want to go with the losing way.
It's a stab to my pride.
I'm going to go with the losing one.
I really need to win this.
[Need to try whatever he can to
maintain his pride...]
- That's so funny.
- Song Ji Hyo, fighting!
[Ultimately going with the regular wrestle-
Match start!]
- Nice, Ji Hyo.
- Why is she so strong?
Ji Hyo's really strong.
[Attacking Big-nosed Brother?]
She's really doing it!
[Big-nosed Brother doing whatever
he can to win the match!]
He's really trying hard!
- He's really using his strength!
- Of course!
You have to use your strength in wrestling!
Flip him over, Ji Hyo!
As you may know,
Ji Hyo even went up against Sung Hoon.
[This is the same Blank Ji who's even
gone up against Chu Sung Hoon.]
This is the battle of strength.
[That's why...
Suk Jin is at a disadvantage.]
[Oh? Just then!]
[Big-nosed Brother starts his attack!]
[Ji Hyo avoids that attack!]
[Ace Ji Hyo gets his inner leg!]
[She gets him in just the right position!]
Get his inner leg!
There you go!
Awesome!
[By tripping his inner leg...
she flips Big-nosed Brother over!]
[Blue Team's Ace Ji Hyo wins again!]
I won!
[Wins fair and square
at the regular wrestling match!]
[Best record at the blob jump,
and now wrestling... the power of the ace!]
I can't believe you won that.
Suk Jin, just go stare at the river.
- What?
- Go take a moment by the river.
Get away from me.
[Getting angry even after he loses.]
[So embarrassing...]
- Be a good sport, Mister!
- Han Hyo Joo is next.
[Next up for the Red Team is, Han Hyo Joo.]
- Fighting.
- Hyo Joo's practiced leg tripping a lot.
You have to be careful, Ji Hyo.
I tried leg tripping her,
and she can't be beat.
[Now that we take a look,
it's woman against woman.]
[Ace, who can't be taken lightly...]
[The invincible Song Ji Hyo]
[She fell for it the first time...]
[But no longer!]
[The woman who's eyes have been
opened, Han Hyo Joo!]
- Ji Hyo, fighting!
- You can beat her, Hyo Joo!
[A real battle between the two women!]
- This is going to be a good match.
- You have to win this.
Wow, Hyo Joo's not taking this lightly.
[Hyo Joo with a different glint in her eye.]
[Ji Hyo with some of her strength
sapped out of her after three rounds.]
They're so serious.
This is nerve-wrecking.
- This is giving me anxiety.
- Look at Hyo Joo's eyes.
[Match start]
- Nice.
- This is...
This is a fierce battle!
[Battle between the masters?
Starting off with a fierce battle of wills.]
She's thinking of flipping her
over right now.
I'm sure Jong Kook taught her something.
Hyo Joo's positioning
is really stable right now.
It's not just Hyo Joo, but you too.
Both of you are very stable right now.
- That's something else.
- Look at you guys right now.
[Pretty much what the pros
would look like?]
They really are no joke.
[Hyo Joo slowly starting to
make her moves.]
- She's making her moves.
- She's moving in.
You've already done well enough,
so don't feel pressured.
You've already won two rounds for us.
Hyo Joo has a really nice grip on the ties.
- You're fresh and energized, Hyo Joo.
- Make your move, Hyo Joo!
- Make you move!
- You have to make your move.
[Starting her attack!]
[Hyo Joo attacks Ji Hyo's leg!]
[Trips her leg, and bam!]
Are you okay?
[Red Team's Hyo Joo wins!]
Her leg flip...
- Her leg flip!
- I'm so sorry!
[Han Hyo Joo ultimately wins by
tripping her over!]
She got me good.
- She's discovered the leg flip maneuver.
- Are you okay?
[Beautiful Han Hyo Joo is
the new master of the leg flips!]
[At last...]
[The time... has come!]
[Final players-
Jung Woo Sung vs. Kim Jong Kook]
[Two men with
very serious looks in their eyes.]
This is not your average match.
[They've only got their grips on each other,
but the energy already...]
It's like the tiger against the dragon.
[It's like watching a battle between
the tiger and the dragon!]
Wow, you feel... so solid.
[This match is the highlight of
today's wrestling match.]
But this is the first time Woo Sung
has wrestled anyone.
This is more about the skill
rather than the strength.
[An unbelievable battle of will.]
But Woo Sung is really strong himself.
Wow, Woo Sung is no joke.
- This is nerve wrecking.
- It's going to be down to one blow.
[Woo Sung moves in like lightening
to trip Jong Kook by the leg!]
[This could be the deciding moment!
Will it be victory or defeat?]
[He trips him by the leg!
However...]
[How can this be!]
[Jong Kook withstands the attack,
and counterattacks in return!]
He counterattacked!
Ugh...
Did we win?
[Red Team wins the wrestling battle!]
You're so strong.
[Mr. Capable pulls it off!]
- He even attacked first.
- Wasn't it a close call?
That was such a close call.
Red Team wins.
[First victory of the day for the Red Team!]
I should've gone up against Jong Kook.
I don't feel happy with this.
I really don't feel good about this.
You're going to be
all fired up for the next mission.
[You just wait and see
until the next mission...]
- Calm him down.
- No, I'm going to let him just go.
You just lost.
[His rage-o-meter is climbing!]
- You getting fired up is different from me.
- Be quiet!
Losing for me has a greater
lasting effect.
No, losing doesn't suit you.
- A bigger effect...
- Red Team can choose first.
[Red Team to choose first for having
won the wrestling battle.]
- Hyo Joo, how about...
- Number nine.
We choose number nine.
[Grill]
[A necessary item to cook the meat
when away on a vacation!]
- Grill.
- Grill is perfect.
- We choose number ten!
- Nice!
[Espresso machine]
Didn't I tell you?
Number ten.
[Espresso machine
that Hyo Joo's been wanting!]
- They took all the good stuff.
- There's nothing left now.
- The bicycle is still left.
- What else is there?
- Number five.
- We choose number five.
[Bicycle]
Number three.
[Top grade hanwoo beef]
We will now be heading to the final location.
But there's something you must do in the car
on your way to the final location.
- What is it?
- Each team has chosen six prizes.
You will each have to choose a prize and
keep it with you under your name tag.
And one person will keep two prizes
on their person.
[The team that stays alive to the end
will take all the prizes!]
[Go to the Baekjae Cultural Center
and find the Running Man Landmark.]
- This is the final game.
- Baekjae Cultural Center.
[A bloody battle with
all the prizes on the line.]
- What is it that everyone wants?
- What should we do?
Well... I'm sure we all want the TV.
Can I have the tent
if someone else gets the TV?
- Really?
- And you can have the TV.
- Then Junho can protect the tent.
- I'll hang onto the tent.
I think we need to give all the
nicer ones to Woo Sung.
Even though I'm sure they'll think Woo Sung
will have the nicer items
they won't be reckless about
attacking him.
So how about you keep the
digital camera and the bicycle?
- Woo Sung can keep these.
- How about the beef over the camera?
Beef?
No, give the beef to Ji Hyo.
[Keep the prize race]
[Baekjae Cultural Center in Choongnam]
[A place where the history
is alive and breathing...]
[The site of their final battle.]
[The keeper of each prize items.]
We will now start the game.
Five, four...
[The final battle- Name tag elimination.]
One!
[Game Start]
[The battle begins now!]
This is such a huge place.
[It is a large space...]
[But jumping right into the battle!]
[It's Mr. Capable!]
We have to hurry up and find them.
Come on.
[The Tiger and the Giraffe
working together.]
Follow me.
Come on.
[I need to hurry and find my teammates!]
[Luckily it's Woo Sung that he meets!]
[Blue Team's Woo Sung and Ro-Ro
working together!]
[Junho running around at a quick pace.]
[Joining the Tiger and the Giraffe]
Woo Sung and Ha Ha.
- Down there?
- Yes, down over there.
[Red Team already having gathered
three of their members together.]
Ji Suk Jin, out.
He's already out?
He's been eliminated.
[A few minutes ago]
- Suk Jin...
- It hasn't even been a minute.
- You know what's going to happen.
- I'll give you inside information.
- What information?
- Then you need to run.
- Get out of here right now.
- Really?
[Giving him a break?]
Eight, seven, six...
Ice box.
- He had the ice box.
- You're out?
[This is how Big-nosed Brother
started off the race.]
He's been eliminated already?
[Rustling up the battlefield
in less than a minute.]
That's just unbelievable.
It's Kim Jong Kook.
Jong Kook is coming.
Do you know where you're going?
[Suk Jin- Out!]
Hyo Joo!
Where did she go?
Kwang Soo!
- He's already eliminated?
- Where have you been?
- We've been searching for you everywhere.
- We're in trouble.
Did you hear Suk Jin getting ousted?
I've been waiting here this whole time
thinking you guys were coming.
- They're headed this way right now.
- This is the tallest point here.
Let's move in.
- Let's get them all.
- Let's battle it out.
- They're heading this way right now?
- Yeah.
[Both teams heading towards
the same direction.]
There they are.
Should we call them out one at a time?
- Wow, this is kind of cool.
- It's like a siege.
[Feels like a siege warfare.]
- Should we call them out one at a time?
- Hey!
This is our castle!
One of you, come out!
One of you come in here!
You cowards!
One of you come out here!
What did you say?
[General Giraffe being easily provoked.]
- Don't fall for it, Lee Kwang Soo!
- Don't fall for it!
Don't fall for it!
- Let's go for a round.
- That's what I want too.
- No, Kwang Soo.
- You're too far out. Step back quickly.
- Really?
You're too far out.
Look at the way you're retreating.
He's just trying to provoke you.
It's just a provocation.
- Why you little!
- He's just provoking you.
[Provocation, a success...]
- Come here, beanpole.
- Let me just say one thing.
Your luxury ice box
is already in our possession.
Lee Kwang Soo.
Are you rice?
- Why do you assume that I'm the rice?
- Look at how angry you are.
- Come out here.
- No!
- No, don't go.
- Why do you assume that I'm the rice?
Come out here.
[Me?]
- Go get rid of that kiddo.
- Kiddo!
[General Kiddo continuing to provoke
General Giraffe.]
Get out here!
- Man to man!
- Let's do this one on one!
[A real man to man battle atop
the wooden bridge.]
On top of this wooden bridge...
[Kiddo warrior who's special skill
is to verbally attack...]
[vs. Warrior Giraffe who's specialty
is to betray.]
[The two experts in betrayals are
meeting atop the wooden bridge.]
[Huh?]
[Kiddo breaking out his strange
martial arts moves.]
- Ugh, this is so aggravating!
- I don't think this is going to work.
- Ugh!
- This isn't going to work.
You hit me twice!
- I saw you gripping your fist.
- No, you didn't!
You're shorter than me!
I feel like I'm watching an
entertaining show.
[Finally facing each other off
in battle of strength?]
[Ambush?
Making their moves into the castle?]
Move in!
[A live face to face battle!]
[Blue Team breaks through the gate!]
[Imminent danger!]
[Just then... it's Kwang Soo vs. Gary!]
[Both with their hands on
each other's name tags!]
I got it!
[Simultaneously!]
[Gary and Kwang Soo-
Simultaneously out!]
[Darn!]
[The Red Team backed up into a corner.]
[Junho keeping his eyes on Jae Suk.]
[Woo Sung vs. Jong Kook]
[Woo Sung moving in on the divine
Mr. Capable without any hesitation.]
- You got him!
- It's okay.
[There they go!]
[His hand is...]
[Just who...]
[Wow, Woo Sung gets him first!]
[Jong Kook- Out!]
[Everyone shocked at Woo Sung's victory!]
See what Jong Kook had.
Rice.
[On Jong Kook's back is... rice.]
[Let's get out of here!]
[Outnumbered...
only method now is to ambush!]
[As predicted, not falling for the trap!]
Junho.
Yesterday's humiliation...
[If you want a face-off,
that's what you'll get!]
[Speedy Junho proving to be
a formidable opponent.]
[The name tag!]
[Junho's formidable speed!]
[The name tag is in his grip!]
[Junho grabs it at the same time!]
[Junho- Out!]
And thus,
today's victory goes to the Blue Team.
[Blue Team- Final Winners.]
You can divide up the prizes
however you'd like except for the picnic mat.
So except for the picnic mat?
Why don't you give it to Ji Hyo and Gary
for the wedding dowry?
- Really?
- That's a great idea.
- If they get married, then okay.
- Then is that tent our home?
[Starting their newly married life
in the cozy tent?]
Hang on. Hyo Joo's really been
wanting the espresso machine.
- Really?
- Yes.
What about you, Woo Sung?
Tell us if there's anything you need.
As for me...
I'd like Hyo Joo's espresso machine.
- You're saying you want it for yourself?
- Yes.
- He's so greedy!
- He's hilarious!
- Take the TV.
- In that case...
I'll take the espresso machine
and the TV.
How beautiful!
[Woo Sung's beautiful entertaining
challenge is over for now...]
[And...]
[The day of the big event...]
[June, 19th, 2013- Incheon Songdo.]
Have you seen this?
- But before Park Ji Sung comes out...
- Is she coming?
No, no.
Other guests who will be joining us
will come out to join us.
- There's another guest?
- Not who we're thinking?
I see someone coming.
It's a girl.
She's really pale.
[White dress of purity.]
- Who is it?
- She's really pretty.
[She is none other than...]
[Sulli of f(x)]
- It's Sulli?
- That's Sulli?
- Hi Sulli!
- Sulli!
- It's Sulli!
- She's a woman now!
- She's all grown up!
- She's a young woman!
- Sulli!
- Hi!
- When did you grow into a young woman?
[Wow...]
[Young woman of innocence, Sulli!]
You look so pretty!
- Come here, Sulli.
- Yes.
Get out of the way, Kwang Soo!
- Get out of the way.
- You crazy? Get out!
- Get out of the way!
- Move!
[Kwang Soo kicked off to the corner.]
- Sulli!
- You look so pretty!
[Giraffe forbidden from high-fiving Sulli
by Hyuk and Kkuk.]
Sulli will be joining our show today,
and you know our next guest very well.
[He is coming!]
My brother!
- Seriously.
- Ji Sung!
- Captain Park!
[Having turned the world upside down
earlier this morning!]
[He is here.]
[The eternal captain, Park Ji Sung!]
[Last June...
Causing a riot with his guest appearance]
[Captain Park having shown us his other
great talents other than just soccer.]
[Running Man ran in the world famous
soccer field with the captain.]
[Joining us once again this year!]
- It's been a year!
- The heat of Korea.
- Thank you for joining us again.
- The eternal captain.
Now that Ji Sung is here,
earlier this morning...
- It's chaotic today.
- Yes, it's a big day.
But he still wants us to know he'll do
his best and that we shouldn't worry.
Whenever we're having a tough time,
Ji Sung's always cheered us on.
[Running Man's oxygen tank?]
Please greet our Running Man viewers.
Hello, my name is Park Ji Sung.
- It's been a year.
- I'm glad to be back this year again.
- And since today...
- What about today?
Why don't you send her
a video message?
I will run my hardest for my
special woman.
It's okay, so just say it.
I have had something exciting
happen to me.
[An exciting event in the life of
the world star, Park Ji Sung!]
Athlete Park Ji Sung and
SBS' Announcer Kim Min Ji
news of them dating has turned the world
upside down on its head this morning.
The news of your dating
has broken out.
- I see.
- How did it happen?
Well... it just happened that way.
- Congratulations!
You're a member of our SBS family now.
SBS, I love you.
[He's still sensible as ever!]
[He's still got it!]
Sulli will also be joining us today.
- Thank you.
- Hello.
Please take good care of me.
No, he wouldn't be
interested in you now!
- He doesn't even notice other girls.
- It doesn't matter who's standing there!
I can understand that.
Now that we're all standing here,
who did you miss the most?
- Including Sulli.
No pressure.
- Person I missed the most?
- Yes, who is it?
I don't really have one.
[Yup, he's still got it.]
But still... how can you say that?
I'm sure there's only one person
that he misses right now!
- That's good.
- That's our Ji Sung.
You ate chicken a couple of
days ago, right?
Yes, I really enjoyed it.
[All the details will be shared
next week...]
[This is one of the teams headed by
the Asian Dream Cup's Park Ji Sung.]
And the other captain to head the
opposing team...
There's someone else?
[A strapping physique]
[Broad shoulders]
- Who is it?
- It's none other than...
Okay, let's ask him out.
Please come out here!
- Who is it?
- It can't just be your average guy.
[Soccer player, Gu Ja Chul.]
- It's Gu Ja Chul!
- Wow!
It's Gu Ja Chul!
[The new captain, Gu Ja Chul.
He is here!]
[The amazing mid-fielder with
amazing skills!]
[The new captain who's already shown us
his amazing skills!]
[His fearless spirit!]
[He is the other captain for the day!]
- Gu Ja Chul!
- It's Gu Ja Chul!
Gu Ja Chul!
[Extreme welcome!]
I'm sorry, but hang on a second.
It's really Gu Ja Chul?
Get away from him!
[The crowd gathering around
the other captain!]
- Wow, look at how tall he is!
- We left Ji Sung all alone.
You get out of here!
[Forcibly blocking his approach]
Are you betraying me to go there?
[Amazed at the appearance of his guest.]
- This is amazing.
- I can't believe he's here.
Ja Chul... it's really great to have you.
Don't cross this line.
You're blocking my camera.
Sorry, but you're blocking my camera.
[Such unbelievable sense.]
Just keep your attention on Ji Sung!
I'm sorry.
We'll take care of Ja Chul ourselves.
Wow, Ji Sung's really good
on the show.
[Of course... this is MC Park.]
- Please say hello to the viewers.
- Greet our viewers.
Hello, my name is Gu Ja Chul.
Gu Ja Chul!
As you may already all know,
the reason why he's here in a year is...
The Asian Cup is upon us
once again.
[Asian Dream Cup taking place
in China this year...]
- Will we be able to participate again?
- That's why you're all here today.
[Even Running Man members will be
able to participate!]
I really want to stand as part of the
starting lineup.
- I really want to run.
- I want to be a part of it!
[Everyone filled with eager energy
and anticipation.]
[And thus... we stand on
the dream ground once again.]
Subtitles by DramaFever
What am I going to do with this kid?
[Captain Park vs. Captain Gu]
[The fierce battle of pride
is about to start!]
[Will it be the spirit of
the new generation's captain...]
[or the expert ease of the eternal captain?]
[The training fete held
for the Asian Dream Cup!]
[Team Park Ji Sung vs. Team Gu Ja Chul-
Who'll get the honor of the Dream Cup?]
[And... the location of the Dream Cup-
Shanghai!]
[The day of the battle!
The superstar who's come to cheer on the team]
[The world's ultimate left field defender,
Evra!
[The world's most famous soccer player...
shows his show talent!]
[Park Ji Sung vs. Evra-
A fierce battle between best friends!]
[And...]
[One man standing alone on the field...]
['Everyone in the stadium had
their eyes on my feet.']
[Next Week's Running Man-
Dream a New Dream.]