Subtitles by DramaFever
[June 2013- Republic of Korea]
[Their own identities... that they
weren't even aware of themselves.]
[Today...]
[The ultimate hero will be resurrected.]
[The world of superheroes...]
[That they've only dreamt of.]
[Just wait for what's in store
ahead of you.]
[Their shocking abilities will amaze you!]
[Superheroes]
[Running Man Avengers]
[8 hours before this historic
event took place.]
Up to the second floor?
Hello.
[What?
Delivering water?]
[Nice, Water delivery boy,
Yoo Hyuk. Age- 42.]
Who's that?
Why is he wearing a leather coat
on a hot day like this?
I'm here with the water delivery.
[The mysterious man who has been
waiting for his arrival.]
[Profile: Name- Dong Fury.
Job- Head of the Running Man Avengers.
[Special skills- Uses all weapons,
strong charisma and leadership skills.]
I knew it was going to be you.
- Have you been well?
- 'Have you been well?'
Is that the way you greet
someone who's older than you?
Sit down over here.
What is all this?
What is that?
[And the arrival of another person.]
[Intimidating plumber,
Kim Jong Kook. Age- 38.]
- Who called?
- What did you say?
I'm here from
'Can get through any clogs' services.
Look at those veins.
Ugh! I can't even stand looking at you!
- What?
- Be quiet and have a seat.
[Director Dong Fury.
Why did he call them here?]
What are you?
Water delivery boy?
I just delivered
that jug of water over there.
You have to go put it in
the water stand.
How many times did you roll
your sleeve over?
- What are you doing?
- What do you mean, roll over?
- Why don't you go around shirtless instead?
- It's because the sleeves are too long.
Seriously.
- Director Yoo Jae Suk.
- What did you say?
- Captain Yoo Jae Suk.
- Huh?
Director one minute, then Captain the next.
What's going on here?
Why do you keep going
back and forth like that?
- Captain Yoo and Captain Kim.
- What's going on now?
I'm Director Dong Fury.
- What did you say?
- He says he's Director Dong Fury.
- Dong Fury?
- What's Director Dong Fury?
Thanks for keeping quiet about
your identities all this time.
There are superheroes living their day to day
lives without knowing their true identities.
[Superhero comrades living their lives
unaware of their real identities?]
[Running Man Avengers...]
[Has the time come for them
to gather together again?]
Today... is the day for you to decide
who the ultimate superhero is.
This is the information on the
current whereabouts of your comrades.
- What? What is this?
- Do we have to go get them?
Working fast to get as many teammates as
possible will prove to be most advantageous.
[Captain to gather the most teammates
will have a bigger advantage.]
I remember HaHa tricking me
the last time we did something like this.
Gather up your teammates and
come to the hills in Geumsanri.
- Geumsanri Hills?
- You should both get on your way.
What's the deal with the hills?
- Hang on. I should call them first.
- Wait for me!
[The day of summoning
for all the superheroes.]
[Just then... a mysterious man who
has just witness the whole event.]
[A feeling of a formidable opponent.]
What kind of an illness brought
you here?
- The leg is broken.
- The leg?
[Doctor Giraffe is in the process
of healing another giraffe?]
How did it ever get into this condition?
Are you out of your mind or what?
[Tries to revive the patient
with every ounce of his energy.]
Someone help me!
Scalpel! Scalpel!
Perform mouth to mouth on my patient.
Hurry!
[Head Nurse bursting into fits of laughter.]
Have you been well?
I really love this vibrating plate on my chest.
I feel so much more at ease
with this on my chest.
[Coffee shop vibrating plate mania?
Rich kiddo, Ha Dong Hoon- Age 35.]
I'm back from delivery!
No, you could get hurt.
[Pizza delivery boy, Kang Gary.
Age- 36.]
Your pizza is here.
There you go.
[The customer takes a picture of Gary
as proof of him delivering the pizza.]
[On the other side of town,
a rock band is rocking out to their music.]
[Popular rock back vocalist,
Blank Ji Hyo. Age- 33.]
How long... how long am I
going to have to run for?
Let's stop running now.
[And something unusual
is going on at this location.]
I'm going to make the ultimate potion!
Yes, there it is.
[The tragic scientist, Ji Suk Jin.
Age- 48.]
It's another failure!
Am I not going to be able to become
a professor again this year?
But I can't stop now.
Because I'm the best scientist
in this world!
[Bogus scientist who's on the brink
of losing his sanity.]
If this succeeds,
I'll be able to become a professor.
[Members of the Avengers who've been living
their lives unaware of their true identities.]
My brother!
Hurry, hurry.
I'm out here waiting for you.
[Captain Yoo and Captain Kkuk
working fast to call their members.]
I'm working at my part time
job right now.
You're at your part-time job?
- My brother!
- Why are you calling me?
- What did you say?
- How long has it been, my brother?
[Captain Yoo arrives at
one of the member's locations.]
[His first stop is to
the Veterinarian Giraffe?]
- You're my first stop, Kwang Soo.
- Jae Suk...
- Kwang Soo.
- What is that getup that you're wearing?
- Hang on a minute.
Just get in.
Just get your foot in the car.
[Captain Yoo forces Doctor Kwang in
by tucking his body into the car.]
Hello.
- Everyone!
- Come on, Kwang Soo.
Someone please help me!
Help me!
- Someone!
- We have to hurry and get out of here.
- Kwang Soo...
- Someone!
Even though you are very precious to me,
Jong Kook has already abandoned you.
Do you get what I'm saying?
If you needed money, I would
be more than glad to lend it to you.
Good boy, good boy.
Who's next?
Who's closest to here?
- Gary and Suk Jin are at the same place.
- Really?
- They're both very close to here.
- Let's call Suk Jin and Gary right now.
Someone's here.
[Captain Yoo's team rushing over like
a bolt of thunder to get Gary.]
[Captain Kkuk finally arriving to
pick up HaHa.]
- I can't believe I'm first!
- We're totally ruined right now.
Look at this. Look at the map.
Look at where you're at.
[Where HaHa is all by himself in comparison
to where the rest of the members are at.]
Where are you right now?
[In the meantime, Captain Yoo and his team
are on the phone with Rock girl, Blank Ji.]
I'm coming to get you right now, Ji Hyo!
We're not far from where you're at.
Gary is throwing a fit about
going to pick you up right now.
- Kang Gary.
- What? What is it?
What is she doing?
Is she about to confess her feelings?
- What is she doing?
- No, Ji Hyo! You're on speaker! Be careful!
[Captain Yoo's team already has three people!
Even picked up Big-nosed Brother nearby!]
Yes, Jong Kook.
Put me on speaker
so that everyone can hear me.
Yes, you're on speaker right now.
- Okay, Kwang Soo.
- Yes, Jong Kook?
You should think about this.
Just how strong we're going to be.
The teams are too uneven.
What is he talking about?
When have the teams ever been even?
The teams have never been even.
Does he want to get smacked?
So you want to do it like this?
Fine, then let's just do this!
[It's war!]
I'm going to call up all my friends!
You're all dead!
- Fine, we got it!
- You're all dead! Hear me?
Let's take this to the end!
[Rushing to get the
sole female superhero, Blank Ji.]
Is this the place?
- Look, it says music.
- There it is. The drums.
What is she doing?
[Still rocking out with her band?]
I think she's asking me out right now.
[What is she doing?]
[Oh... A Leessang song!]
[Passing on the rap portion of the song.]
[The original singer of the song, Gary
with the mic in his hand.]
[He's doing great!]
[Suddenly turning into Leessang's stage.]
[Yeah, Monday Theater!]
What is it?
- Wow, I can't stand him.
- Isn't that a picture of his arm?
[A warning?
A frightening picture of Kkuk's biceps.]
- I think what he's trying to do is...
- Why did he send us that picture?
- I think I know what he's doing.
- What?
- He's saying he'll pull up the car...
- And he wants you all to get in?
- He wants all of us to get in his car.
- He sent me a text too.
- He sent me one too.
- I bet he sent it to everyone.
I can't believe he's doing that.
[Captain Kkuk's team feeling nervous
from lack of team members.]
[Captain Yoo and his teammates caught
walking out by Captain Kkuk.]
- Is he here?
- It's Kim Jong Kook.
- My doors are unlocked.
- What did you say?
I want you to know
that my doors are unlocked.
What?
You said your doors are unlocked?
We'll pull over right there
and park the car.
- You're blocking the traffic.
- You guys decide what you want to do.
What are you all doing?
Get in the car.
- Hurry up and get in.
- Give us a minute.
[All the members starting to doubt
upon seeing Tiger's appearance.]
- Song Ji Hyo.
- This is going to be tough.
Don't forget that I came all the way
here just to pick you up.
Hey, you were the first person
I picked up.
Come on, get in the car.
Suk Jin, just get in the car.
What are you hesitating about?
[Captain Yoo starts to feel desperate and
pushes his teammates to get in the car.]
Ji Hyo, get in.
Hurry up and get in.
- This is a tough call.
- Just get in.
Just get in.
- Just get in, Suk Jin.
- I feel bad for him.
Kwang Soo!
[Huh?]
[Monday Couple dashing over
to Captain Kkuk's team?]
You made the right decision!
Okay, you made the right decision.
[Darn...]
- What the...
- Just get in the car.
Seriously!
Come on, Suk Jin.
Kwang Soo!
[Everyone trying to flee from the team?]
- Just put your seatbelt on.
- Who's your brother?
- Come on, let's not do this.
- Tell me who your brother is.
- Suk Jin.
- Who's your beloved brother?
- My beloved brother, Suk Jin.
- What's my name again?
- And my beloved brother, Kwang Soo.
- Jae Suk.
Promise me that you'll never make
another reference to my butt again.
Pil!
Chok, Chok, Cross!
- What's 'Pil- Chok- Chok'?
- Let's just get going.
Gary, you made the right decision.
Monday Couple is the best!
- Yes!
- You did the right thing.
- That was a nice move.
- Ji Hyo gave me a look.
She gave me a look that said
she wanted to come over to this team.
- That's a smart move.
- Good. We're all set!
- We're set.
- Our team is all set.
What are we going to do now?
Our team has all of a sudden become pathetic.
When Gary was sitting back there earlier,
I felt really reassured about our team.
And also with Kwang Soo
sitting right here too.
You know that feeling of a cold draft blowing
through the window during winter time?
Especially from this side.
This side over here.
- I feel a cold draft from over here.
- Stop the car.
- I feel like we're all heroes of some sorts.
- That's right.
- But the other team...
- They're heroes of betrayal.
When I was at the coffee shop earlier,
you know those vibrating discs?
I had one of those vibrating discs
sitting on top of my chest.
- Seriously?
- That's Iron Man.
[Could HaHa be becoming that hero
that flies through the skies?]
- Then you're Iron Man!
- Yeah, you are.
Remember that Iron Man hat you wore?
He's Iron Man.
- I need turning!
- Yes, turning!
[A movie scene parody that everyone in
Korea broke out into fits of laughter over.]
[That Gary...]
- I wonder who I'm going to be?
- Right?
I'm curious about
who you're going to become too.
What is this place?
This really is a nice spot for a big battle.
[The gathering location-
Arrives at Geumsanri Hills.]
- What is that?
- Isn't that Samuel L. Jackson?
[I'm Director Dong Fury.]
- It's Dong Wan!
- You look so awesome, Dong Wan!
Don't you think he looks just like him?
What is this?
Is this war?
- What is it?
- Is it war?
You traitor, Song Ji Hyo!
And you, Kang Gary.
Oh my goodness!
Oh my! That surprised me!
I thought Gil came.
I really thought Gil came on the show.
I had no idea that it was Dong Wan.
Soldiers, it's nice to see
you all here.
Today is the day of Running Man Avengers to
determine who the ultimate superhero is.
- Oh yeah!
- We're the Avengers?
[That's right!
We're the superheroes!]
I'm your director, Director Dong Fury.
But he has hard enough time
walking around on his own two feet.
Soldiers, I need you to stay quiet.
- You're acting has really improved.
- That was impressive.
Let's move on.
Since none of you are heroes yet, you
need to earn your superhero memberships.
So we're not heroes yet?
In order to earn your superhero memberships,
you have to pass very rigorous training.
Aren't you hot?
I'm sure you're hot in that coat.
Okay, here's your first mission.
It's paintball survival mission between
Captain Yoo Jae Suk and
Captain Kim Jong Kook's team.
[Superhero membership course-
First mission: Survival challenge.]
- This is a sure win for us.
- This is in our favor.
But this really isn't good
with our odds.
The team that wins this mission will
receive their membership cards right away.
And if you fail, you will continue to follow
my instructions to perform further missions.
Okay, future heroes.
This is war.
Your acting skills have really improved.
- Don't you think this is too unfair?
- What's unfair?
- We're short a person.
- That doesn't matter.
If it doesn't matter,
then give us one person.
What did you say?
Your first mission.
We're going to determine the
offense and defense team.
As you can see,
there's an 'R' flag up there.
If the defense team can protect that flag,
then you succeed your mission.
And if the offense team can steal that flag,
then you'll succeed your mission.
[Offense Team- Captain Kkuk and members
Blank Ji, Jong Kook, HaHa, Gary.]
[Defense Team- Captain Yoo and members
Yoo Hyuk, Big-nose, and Giraffe.]
[Rule: If the name tag on their back is hit by
the opposing team's paint, they're out!]
[Survival Game- Start.]
[Captain Kkuk and his team approaching
the flag without any hesitation.]
- Still too far away.
- I see Jae Suk coming down there.
Left, left. Go to the left.
Approach from their behind.
- Where?
- To the left. Someone go over to the left.
- To the right over that way.
- Are you keeping a close eye, Kwang Soo?
- Yes, Jae Suk.
- Dong Hoon is on his way.
- Where? Which way is he coming from?
[There he is!]
[An opening?
Why is he standing up?]
[The paintball hits the mark!]
- That scaredy cat!
- He hit me!
- Are you hit?
- No, he hit the can.
I'll shoot towards Kwang Soo!
- Gary, I'll shoot towards Kwang Soo!
- No! Don't shoot!
I'll throw down my weapon!
[Blank Ji's undercover fire!]
[Just then]
[Gary being too careless.]
What's wrong?
[Wow!
Right on target!]
Are you hit?
Where?
Where did you get hit?
- I shot him.
- Let's see.
- Where did Gary get hit?
- Gary's out?
- Where did he get hit?
- Jae Suk, I shot him!
- How did that happen?
- Great job.
[Wow... what got into Kwang Soo?]
- We can't lose Gary!
- Good. Now, it's three against three!
Move forward!
[Giraffe shouting out a battle cry to
move forward out of his excitement.]
[You scoundrel!]
[Why is the defense continuing
to advance?]
Let's go get HaHa!
- Kim Jong Kook's coming!
- Where?
[Captain Kkuk racing towards the flag!]
Where is he?
I almost got hit.
Ji Suk Jin!
It's three against three!
We can each take down one of them!
Come on out, Song Ji Hyo!
[Big-nose challenges Blank Ji
as expected?]
Come out here, Suk Jin!
Stop hiding like a coward!
Make sure that they don't
sneak up here!
[Kkuk having moved
pretty close towards the flag.]
Don't be reckless, Dong Hoon!
- Dong Hoon's headed over there!
- I'm watching!
[Giraffe being reckless with his moves.]
- Be careful, Kwang Soo!
- Where's Jong Kook?
Hey!
Kim Jong Kook is over there.
- Kim Jong Kook is over there.
- Where is Jong Kook?
[Running so well through
the showering of the paintball shots.]
- Where is he?
- Hey, Ji Hyo! I see Suk Jin over there.
- Where's Jong Kook?
- You go to the left and I'll go to the right.
- Okay, let's go.
- Let's go!
Get out here, Song Ji Hyo!
Where did she go?
[Locks down on target.]
[Chance at a sniper shot on Suk Jin.]
[Unfortunately misses!]
- Be careful!
- What the heck?
[Too bad!]
- Kwang Soo, watch out for Jong Kook!
- What are you doing there?
- Suk Jin, you have to block Ji Hyo!
- I am blocking her.
Jong Kook is firing on Jae Suk!
[Captain Kkuk's team
showering them with fire.]
Be careful!
We have to remain alive!
Suk Jin!
- Does it hurt?
- No, it doesn't hurt.
Keep your eye on Song Ji Hyo.
Hold your fire.
Don't shoot.
[Blank Ji eyeing her target once again!]
[This time, it's the Giraffe with
his back exposed!]
What was that?
Who is it? Who is it?
It's Song Ji Hyo!
[Terrified out of his wits.]
You have to block her!
[Desperately makes his escape up the hill.]
- You have to get up there, Dong Hoon!
- What was that?
- You have to get up here right now!
- Cover me.
[Offense team closing in on
the defense team.]
[This is big trouble.]
- Hey, watch out on your left.
- Suk Jin!
- They're already closing in.
- You have to take care of Ji Hyo.
- Take care of Ji Hyo.
- You have to stop Ji Hyo!
I've got Ji Hyo covered.
What do you mean, you've got her covered?
You're just standing there.
- What are you watching, Kwang Soo?
- I'm watching you right now, Jae Suk.
Why are you watching me?
You have to watch the other team!
[Extreme state of nervousness
to the point of explosion.]
Hey, Kim Jong Kook!
[Captain Kkuk having made his way
even higher up the hill!]
HaHa is right up there.
[Will the defense team have
to surrender?]
I can see her right now!
- Where's Ji Hyo? Ji Hyo!
- Yeah?
You just need to take care of Suk Jin!
- I'm holding him off right now!
- Kwang Soo's heading your way!
I almost got hit!
Kwang Soo's trying to
lock in on you, Jong Kook.
And Jae Suk is targeting me.
Don't do anything until we get
a clear idea of what's going on.
[Giraffe racing down the hill.]
[HaHa shot in the bulls eye!]
Are you okay?
Song Ji Hyo, out!
[Ji Hyo shocked at seeing HaHa
getting shot.]
[Big-nose Brother seizes the moment
to shoot Blank Ji!]
[HaHa and Ji Hyo- Out!]
I did it!
I ousted Song Ji Hyo!
Dong Hoon!
Give me your gun.
Quickly!
[Oh no!
Captain Kkuk is out of bullets!]
- Kim Jong Kook is out of bullets.
- Shoot him!
No!
Don't shoot!
I said, don't shoot!
- He's out of bullets!
- Don't shoot!
I'm out of bullets.
- Hey, hang on.
- Do you have any bullets?
We have to shoot him!
- Bullets! I need bullets!
- I have bullets.
[All he needs to win is to
steal their flag away from them.]
Kim Jong Kook is out of bullets.
[Ruthless shooting.]
[Captain Kkuk- Out!]
Why did you keep shooting when
I said I was surrendering?
- We won!
[Captain Yoo's team wins!]
[Right at that same time...]
[With their eyes on the Running Man Avengers,
they make an emergency trip back to Korea.]
[These two mysterious men...]
[Seoul's Action School.]
- I thought you had your sunglasses on.
- You really do look scary.
- You're getting better at this.
- What are we going to be doing now?
Oh my God!
- Are you guys following us?
- So what if we are?
What are you getting mad at us for?
- We're waiting for our hellish training.
- I forgot you have to receive training.
Director... where are we going?
- Training hell is waiting for you.
- Training hell?
Look.
There are mats on the floor.
- This is going to be a sight.
- What is it?
[What kind of hellish training
awaits them here?]
[The nervousness and the anxiety makes it
difficult for them to even breath out loud.]
What is it?
[Just what is going to be
happening in here?]
- Wow.
- What is it?
[A drop fall.]
[Powerful yet elegant, like that of a crane.]
[The overwhelming power of the troupe!]
[Flinging his body through the air
without even a moment of hesitation!]
[This is what you call an action star!]
What are they doing?
[Fly like a butterfly]
[And sting like a bee!]
Fighting is not the solution!
[Precise movements.]
[A scene from an action movie
unfolding in front of their very own eyes.]
[Nonstop high octane action!]
[Seven aerial turns in the blink
of an eye!]
[Amazing swordsmanship!]
What is it?
What are they doing?
What are you doing?
[A deadfall.]
Wonder woman, fighting!
[Moving with more agility and
power than anyone else!]
[What?
The referee?]
No, not there!
[Finishing him off in
true Running Man style.]
Why don't you give it a try?
You can do it.
[The loud crying of a mosquito.]
Your training hell starts now.
If you pass through the three courses of
training, everyone will receive a membership.
However, if you can clear the mission
before those three courses
we will stop the training, and
give out the membership immediately.
- Okay!
- Then what do we do?
- You can rest comfortably.
- Yes!
You can tease them to your
heart's content.
Okay, your first mission is...
Killer Dodge ball.
Killer Dodge ball?
How can you tell us to play Killer Dodge ball
after what you've just shown us?
- We're not playing against them, are we?
- I think you're playing against those guys.
Training agents... come on out.
[As guessed...]
[The action stars running out
in full force.]
What are we going to do?
It's over.
It's so over.
- Wait, wait!
- There are too many of them!
- How are we going to do this?
- There are too many of them.
[Threatening.]
If even one of you are left standing at the
end of two minutes, you succeed your mission.
Finish them within 30 seconds!
- What is this?
- What is this? You can't do this to us.
Fighting!
[Mission- Start!]
[Blasts Gary!]
Hang on.
Are you okay?
[Gary having difficulty breathing.]
- Think about your mom.
- Did you hear that thud?
Okay, let's do this!
It's Jong Kook!
[The lightning speed
making them feel on edge.]
Make sure that you're careful,
and watch out for the ball.
This is terrifying!
[All hell's breaking loose!]
- Those guys are angry!
- They can't be doing this!
- A minute.
- We've only got a minute left. It's okay.
Jong Kook's not good at everything.
I'm sorry.
Wow, this is tough.
They might be able to pull this off.
Why are you going easy on Ji Hyo?
Look at how easy they're throwing
the ball at Ji Hyo.
- Who gets it?
- Not that side.
[Blank Ji with the ball.]
[A fight for the ball?]
- Hurry up and give it to someone.
- You have to tell us who you're giving it to.
You're giving the ball
to the good looking guy?
No, it didn't hit him.
[Captain Kkuk doing a good job
of avoiding the ball.]
[However...]
[It's a bulls eye on Ro-Ro!]
[Then Captain Kkuk immediately following!]
It's a double hitter!
Wait, wait!
[Blank Ji is the only one left!]
Why don't you try to act cute
for them?
[Action stars' toughness having
gone soft.]
[Blank Ji- Out!]
[Captain Kkuk's Team-
Fails the first mission!]
- You're going to have to do the next mission.
- Our Gary is level eight in martial arts!
- You know what a flying kick is?
- Forget it. I'm hurting right now.
[A demonstration by membership
carrying Captain Yoo's team?]
Do we have to show you how it's done?
- Seriously.
- What were you guys even doing out there?
- How frustrating.
- We need to show them how it's done.
- Why can't you get it done?
- Can we loosen up a little?
- Seriously.
- Let's show them.
I can't believe you couldn't
last those two minutes.
Let's show them what
real heroes are capable of.
Let's show them what we're capable of.
Don't go easy on us.
Let's do this right.
Where's the ball?
- Watch yourself, Kwang Soo.
- You've got one minute.
Wait... what are you doing to me?
[What are you all doing
standing in a line?]
What are you guys doing?
Wait.
[To be called a superhero when
you're acting like that...]
[Kwang Soo in danger!]
[Oh, nice escape!]
[Nice catch of the ball flying
at lightning speed!
[Could he have gone through a transformation
now that he's got his superhero membership?]
Let's run around.
Let's run around in a circle.
[That's more like it.]
[Knows to oust himself.]
[And just at the same time.]
[Another person arriving at
the airport.]
Jong Kook... you just wait.
Okay, your second mission is...
Loyal Sit-ups.
While an action star does
the sit-ups for a minute
your team will do the sit-ups
in a relay.
Action star, please make your entrance.
[Always making their entrance
with spirited shouts.]
I bet they'll do like 80 sit-ups
in a minute.
They look like they'd be swift.
[Starting the full minute of sit-ups.]
- Two, three, four, five, six...
- How can they do it so fast?
- His back isn't touching the ground.
- The back doesn't have to touch.
- Make him touch his knees with his elbows.
- 11, 12, 13, 14...
[Not showing any signs
of slowing down.]
- 21, 22, 23, 24, 25, 26...
- He's like a machine.
[Performing more like a machine.]
[Breaking through 64...]
I can see the whites of his eyes.
[The minute is ticking down to an end...]
One more, do one more!
[70!]
Is the time up?
[Wow!
71 sit-ups in a minute!]
- That's amazing!
- 71 sit-ups within a minute in a relay.
[Team Kkuk's team must perform
71 sit-ups in a minute in a relay.]
- Wow, this is...
- I'm ready.
- One, two, three, four...
- He's fast.
[Wow!
He's fast!]
- Seven, eight, nine...
- He's pretty fast.
[Amazing speed!
A fighting master, Gary!]
13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20...
He's not slowing down yet.
- Are you okay?
- Okay, we can do this.
[29 for Gary!]
30, 31, 32, 33...
[Blank Ji attempting the challenge
with her teeth tightly clenched!]
- 35, 36, 37...
- Come on, you can do this!
- 38, 39, 40!
- Stop!
[Broke through 40!
Now down to HaHa!]
- 43, 44, 45, 16, 47, 48...
- Hold on tight.
49, 50, 51...
[Now only need 20 more!]
[Last turn- Mr. Capable!]
[Powerful sit-ups!]
59, 60, 61, 62, 63, 64... 69...
69...
[Wow... that was so close!]
Wow... just two short!
Wow, they just needed two more.
Wow, that was so close!
- How about Jae Suk?
- Let's see the hero team's demonstration.
- Come on, we don't need to do that.
- Show us how it's done.
Let's show them why we're the heroes.
- No, we can show them.
- Okay, let's show them.
- Okay, then I'll go first.
- Let's show them! Let's do this!
- Let's show them what we're capable of!
- We're heroes!
Watch and see how sit-ups are done.
- Ready?
- Let's go.
Ugh, you're so ugly.
You startled me with your ugliness.
[Startled after seeing his face?]
You have to touch your knees
with your elbows.
How can you be so ugly?
Ugh, you scare me.
I can't believe you look like that.
[It already seems as though breaking
the record is going to be an impossibility.]
You can't stop now.
- Next.
- He's even uglier.
- This one is even uglier.
- You guys can't do this.
He really is like a giraffe
with that neck of his!
This really is the ugly team.
Wow, he really is ugly.
- Pass it over to the next person.
- Next.
- Kwang Soo, you did good.
- It's like watching the slow video.
What are you doing, Suk Jin?
Suk Jin!
You have to come up further.
[A fascinating method- Smacking
the back of the head to get moving.]
[Show us why you're the superheroes?]
You want us to hit it for you?
[Fail]
- Are you kidding?
- What was that?
What are you guys doing?
I don't know what happened.
We can easily handle that.
- Really.
- That really was too bad.
- Let's do this.
- Let's get it done this time.
Just do one and pass it over
to the next person, okay, Ji Hyo?
[Last chance!
Ji Hyo only to do one and pass it on?]
- Okay.
- We're ready.
[If they fail again this round,
it's off to course three of training hell.]
One!
[Ji Hyo only does one and immediately
passes over to Captain Kkuk.]
5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11...
- Wow, he's something else.
- He really is a machine too.
13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18... 22...
[Doing the sit-ups with
every fiber of his being.]
26, 17, 28, 19, 30!
[Already 30 sit-ups in the bag!]
32, 33, 34, 35... 43...
[A serious side of Ro-Ro
that we're not used to seeing.]
46, 47, 48, 49, 50!
[50 already finished!]
[Last person to take his turn is Gary!]
- You can do it.
- You can do this, Gary.
You can do this!
Just think that it's Ji Hyo
in front of you.
You can do it!
64, 65, 66, 67, 68...
[Just five more!]
70, 71, 72...
[72!]
- They did it?
- Did we succeed?
- Did they succeed?
- Success!
[Passes at the second course
of the training hell.]
Wow... we're prettier than you guys.
I didn't think that you'd pass
at the second course.
You will now be awarded your memberships.
[Captain Kkuk and his teammates are
also rewarded with their memberships.]
Gather up the strength of
thunder and lightning!
[Running Man Avengers]
[The ultimate superhero
will be determined today.]
[Incheon Mall's 'S' Shopping Mall-
Superheroes final destination.]
[Starting with Captain Yoo's entrance.]
Where?
Right here?
[Without knowing what
their true identities are...]
[they start boarding the
mysterious trailer.]
What is this?
[This is...]
[Running Man Avengers]
[The last person left standing through the
name tag elimination will become a superhero.]
[You're Captain Running Man.]
[Enlarge your opponent's name tag by shooting
them with the water gun inside your shield.]
[Captain Running Man.
Ability: Can enlarge opponent's name tags.]
[The superhero that used to
be the star of our dreams...]
[Today, that dream becomes a reality.]
[I am...]
[Captain Running Man.]
[Entering the venue with a heroic resolve
with shouts of welcome from the crowd.]
[Full of commanding manner.]
[A serious leader! Await what's
to come from Captain Running Man.]
[The second superhero
to make their entrance.]
[What kind of a hero
will Kwang Soo become?]
Isn't this Hawkeye's outfit?
[Hawkeye's outfit from the movie?]
You are the 'Giraffe Eye'.
[Superhero, Giraffe Eye.]
Can't I just be the Hawkeye?
I'm the Giraffe Eye.
[Giraffe Eye.]
[Ability: Bring misfortune to the opponent
by shooting them with his arrow.]
[Icon of misfortune-
Spreading misfortune even as a hero!]
[Girin Eye a.k.a. Giraffe Eye.]
[Girin Eye.]
(Girin=Giraffe)
You're the Hulk!
The Hulk?
[Big-nose is the superhero
with ultimate strength?]
[Doctor Zhee.]
[Ability: Transform into the Hulk if he's
angered and his heartbeat increases.]
[Dr. Zhee]
[Fourth superhero's entrance.]
[I'm the God of Thunder!]
[Kkuk Thor]
[Ability: Obstruct the opponent's sight by
striking down the hammer and saying a spell.]
The spell I have to say is,
with the powers of thunder and lightning.
[Kkuk Thor]
[And Running Avengers' most cutting edge
and high tech superhero costume of all.]
Wow!
Wow, this is so awesome!
This is awesome.
Iron Man!
Awesome!
Wow!
[Iron Ha]
[Ability: Fly into the air, fire weapons, and
the ultimate tools to locate your opponents.]
This is game over!
How will they be able to catch me
when I can fly into the air?
[Haroro is beyond excited over
his high-tech gadgets and tools.]
[I'm sorry.]
[Iron Ha]
[And the only heroine of
Running Man Avengers' Team.]
My name is... Black Blank.
[Black Blank]
[Ability: Steal the ability of another
superhero by leaving a mark on them.]
[But the superhero who's power she took
must be ousted before using their power.]
Must oust them before using
their powers.
[Black Meong a.k.a. Black Blank.]
[And...]
[Running Man Avengers' final superhero.]
[Spider Gary]
- Say what?
- Kang Gary!
[Spider Gary]
[Ability: Shoots out spider webs.
And his ability cloaked in mystery is?]
[Spider Gary]
[Running Man Presents]
[Running Man Avengers]
[Their superhuman abilities
are awakened back to life.]
[The ultimate superhero
will be determined today!]
Are you a primitive man?
What did you say?
What did you say that I was?
- What are you supposed to be?
- What are you dressed up as?
Can't you tell who I am?
Don't you know who I am?
I'm Thor!
- I'm Thor!
- Don't you know who I am?
- What are you supposed to be?
- I can fling this thing.
If I fling this around and throw it,
I can fly over to where you're at.
I'll make you fly out of here
with this shield of mine.
- Wow... you really are...
- This seriously is something.
I feel so cool right now.
[Giraffe Eye seeming to be
satisfied with his costume.]
Kwang Soo.
[Everyone who sees Captain Running Man's
costume bursts out in laughter.]
This is so frustrating.
- Don't you feel stuffy in that?
- It does feel stuffy.
- What are you supposed to be? Pororo?
- What do you mean, Pororo?
What's this?
I didn't even think about my armpit hair.
Now it's going to bother me all day.
I bet you won't even be able to shoot because
you'll be so worried about that.
- You really do look like superheroes.
- Why are you Dr. Zhee?
- What?
- What are you supposed to be?
[Dr. Zhee not looking like any heroes
by the looks of his costume alone.]
- I'm not going to tell you.
- Suk Jin.
- You have some special powers?
- Of course!
I have amazing superpowers.
You're the arrow shooting guy?
Yes, I am. I'm the Hawkeye,
but call me Giraffe Eye.
- What's your shield for?
- Hang on a second.
Are you the Hulk?
What are you even going to do
when you make your transformation?
Don't make me angry.
What is he doing?
[Since he's already been caught...
Trying to get his heartbeat going.]
- You don't need to know what I'm doing.
- Suk Jin is the Hulk.
But what's the point if you're the Hulk?
It's not like he can even do anything.
It's still going to be you
even if you do make a transformation.
[You're going to chap your lips
if you keep that up.]
[A secret room-
Iron Ha's gear room.]
Awesome!
Wow, I have already exerted myself.
I'm going to need to rest for a moment.
[Locator and other weapons as such,
full of high-tech gadgets for his use.]
[What power does the mysterious
robot glove hold?]
Let's just utilize this for now.
[Iron Ha- Putting his robot glove to work.]
[Black Blank with something held
tightly in her grip.]
Steal an opponent's superhero powers
by leaving a mark on them
and you will be able to use
their powers as your own.
However, the powers of the hero who's power
you took must be ousted first before usage.
[Steal the powers of another superhero and
use it as her own by leaving a mark on them.]
Anyone who's touched by me...
I will take your powers away from you.
[Who's power shall I steal?]
[Just then, she runs into Spider Gary.]
Can you really shoot out spider webs?
Let me see.
[Casually approaching him,
pretending to ask questions.]
Of course, there is something.
Keep your distance.
- Okay, let's just walk over there together.
- Where?
- It's boring to walk around alone.
- Okay.
- Don't think of doing anything foolish.
- Of course not.
You can't get Suk Jin angry, okay?
We really have to love Suk Jin.
- We have to be really good to him.
- Can you yell at me and call me stupid?
No, Suk Jin.
Don't you know how much I like you?
Aren't you going to tease me about
the way I look?
Why would I say that?
That hat looks great on you.
Aren't you going to ask me why
I'm dressed like this?
Why would I say anything like that?
You look great.
- You really do look great.
- Just act like you normally do!
What do you mean?
This is how I normally am with you.
This is driving me nuts.
Don't be upset.
You've got something on you
right here.
[Black Blank is making her attempt to
steal Dr. Zhee's superpower!]
- You've got something right here.
- Where?
[A clear black mark!]
[Black Blank is able to use Dr. Zhee's power
once he is ousted!]
- You've got something right here.
- Where?
Where?
Just slap it away instead
of stroking it away!
Me?
Slap you?
Suk Jin, I love you.
This is so frustrating.
Does being frustrated work?
How about being frustrated?
[Moves in on Gary to make an attempt
on his power as well!]
[Will she succeed again this time
without getting caught?]
- What do you mean by that?
- What do you mean, what do I mean?
[Black Blank easily steals
Spider Gary's power away from him!]
- What do you mean, what do I mean?
- Why are you doing that?
Why are you touching me
all of a sudden?
[A clear black mark!]
[How simple can this be?]
Kwang Soo.
[Giraffe Eye fires at Kkuk Thor
but misses his shot.]
You were trying to hit me
with your arrow.
- Did you just avoid it?
- No.
But I definitely shot it in
your direction.
Why would you suddenly
try shooting me with that thing?
[Unfortunate Giraffe still unable to do
anything even after becoming a superhero.]
Seriously.
Are you going to keep doing that?
You can't try to shoot your spider webs
pathetically like you did the last time, okay?
I'm the Spiderman.
- I'm the Spiderman today.
- Yes, you are.
[Just then]
[Sound of music suddenly
ringing throughout the mall.]
- Do you hear that music?
- What is that?
Is the Hulk making his transformation?
[What is the identity of that sound?]
[Someone else has arrived!]
[Wait, these two are...]
[2PM's Taecyeon and Chansung.]
[2PM Twins!]
Unless their name tag says 'Out'
you can't eliminate them no matter how many
times you rip off their name tags.
If the person with the 'Out' name tag gets
eliminated, both of you will be eliminated!
[If the person with the 'Out' name tag is
eliminated, then they are both eliminated.]
[They are of one body!
The Invincible Twins make their entrance!]
See? What did I tell you?
We have evil enemies!
[Unexpected turn of events.
Running Man Avengers Team put on edge.]
What is going on?
Hey, we need to have a meeting.
What is all this commotion?
[Just then]
[Music is heard again!]
[This music is...]
- No way!
- Is this what I think it is?
This is the music they play when
Athlete Chu Sung Hoon makes his entrance.
[The unforgettable melody...]
[He has arrived.]
[The ultimate warrior coming to
catch the Running Man Avengers.]
[The Fighter's ability]
[Shout out the name of the opponent in front
of you to fight one on one in a special ring.]
[Chu Sung Hoon- The Fighter.]
[Three chances to use his superpower
to lock his opponent in the ring.]
Okay.
[Shall we get started on
hunting down the heroes?]
Jae Suk.
Chu Sung Hoon is here.
Why does Sung Hoon always show up
around four o'clock in the morning?
Jae Suk.
[Even more anxious than
they were a minute ago.]
- We're going to be demolished.
- I know. We should gather our powers.
Make me get angry if we're
put in danger by our enemies.
How are we supposed to anger you?
Like this?
- That's not enough to get me angry.
- What's important here is...
Shouldn't we tell each other what
our own special powers are?
[Too strong of enemies for
Running Man Avengers Team to face!]
We can't get separated from each other.
We have to somehow take care of them first.
Down there.
Look down there.
- It's Sung Hoon!
- I told you!
- What are you doing here?
- Look at him dressed all in black.
- He's dressed in his ring gear.
- Why are you here dressed like that again?
What are you doing here?
What are you doing here, Sung Hoon?
I came to torment Jong Kook a bit.
Why me?
- I came here to torment Jong Kook.
- Why me?
Why did you come for me?
Are you back here because you lost
the Ddak-ji game to me the last time?
[Back to get his revenge after losing
the Ddak-ji battle to Kkuk the last time?]
- Let's go easy, okay?
- Okay.
You just stay there and wait for me.
- What is this song?
- Isn't this 'Kung Fu Fighting?'
Is someone else here?
Does it mean someone else is here?
Who else could be here?
[Intermission dance time from
the Beastly Idol group.]
[Who else is here?
Even The Fighter seems confused.]
[The final rival arriving to
get the Running Man Avengers.]
[The man of martial arts, Jung Doo Hong.]
['The Fighter of the Wind',
'The Good, The Bad,  and the Weird' and such.]
[Korea's representative martial arts director
of a countless number of films!]
[Master Jung's superpower]
[Ability: Can get through
any superheroes powers.]
[Master Jung]
Where am I supposed to go now?
Not sure what I'm supposed to do.
Can I just go anywhere?
[Heroes, you better stay alert.]
- Who could it be?
- Who do you think it is?
- What are we supposed to do?
Should we come up with a plan?
Even though we're not a team, we
have to become a team in this situation.
Who could... wait!
- Who could... wait!
- What? What is it?
- Hang on, Gary! Your neck!
- There's something on your neck.
- Do I have something on my neck too?
- No, nothing.
[Discovers Black Blank's black mark
on Spider Gary's neck!]
I know what it is!
It's the mark of a spider bite.
- Right?
- He got bit by a spider?
You touched my neck earlier!
[Discovers the black marker
in Black Blank's hand!]
- What is this?
- What is that?
- Song Ji Hyo, what are you doing?
- What are you doing?
- What is she doing?
- We have to erase this mark.
What is she doing?
- I don't have any on me.
- You have it too, Suk Jin.
- I have it too?
- Do I have it?
- Let's see.
- What about you?
- I don't have it.
It sounds like a neighborhood
fight has broken out.
- Do I have it?
- No.
[Just as they were to start working together,
they start to suspect each other instead.]
[In that case...]
[Should I start making my moves?]
You're Captain Running Man.
Enlarge your opponent's name tag by
shooting it with the water gun in your shield.
- No, I didn't do anything. Seriously.
- What have you done?
[Shoots Giraffe Eye's name tag!]
[Fleeing from his post immediately
after what he's done.]
[Captain Running Man's water gun mark.]
[It's... bigger!]
Is that my name tag that I see
out of the corner of my eye?
[How unfortunate...]
What is this?
[When it comes to water guns...]
- I'm so nervous.
- My anxiety level is skyrocketing.
- Why do you keep following me?
- Let's go together.
[Kkuk Thor's name tag is
now in front of him!]
[Bullseye!]
[Flees again after what he's done.]
[Captain Running Man's
superpower takes effect!]
[Kkuk Thor's name tag is supersized!]
What is this?
What am I supposed to do with this?
[Nice!]
- Oh!
- Hello, Kwang Soo.
- Hello, Sir.
- Hello.
- Have you been well?
- I'm a huge fan of yours!
- Excuse me?
- I'm a huge fan of yours.
Look at how big my name tag is!
- I'm weak.
- Have you been shot by the water gun?
[That's right! The Master
knows of everyone's powers!]
All my favorite men are here.
- What's your role in this?
- I have no powers.
- Come on.
- You can't be.
[You expect us to believe that?]
I really don't have any powers.
[Wow... Dr. Zhee's courageous moves?]
You're going to get hit
if you keep provoking him.
[Dr. Zhee trying to provoke him
into angering him.]
- Hey. You need to be more careful.
- Why? What did I do?
I'm getting so angry all of a sudden!
- You can't anger him, Jong Kook.
- Yes, I'm aware of that.
- You know?
- You know what all our powers are?
I have my own theory about it.
- I guessed his powers.
- What is Jong Kook's power?
My power really isn't anything.
My name tag got bigger after
you hit it with your hammer.
No, it wasn't me.
Someone else did that to you.
[Men in black coming onto scene
with something held in their hands.]
- Let's get out of here.
- Let's move.
[Running Man Avengers
flee the scene for now!]
[Master Jung walks around in ease
with the knowledge of what's going on.]
The given motto of Running Man members
is to betray.
They have no sides or loyalty.
[Their conclusion is that Avengers will not
remain loyal to one another.]
[Discovers Spider Gary!]
[Starting the chase!]
[Is it time to show them my
web powers?]
What are you doing?
Don't come any closer!
[Spider Gary fires his superpower web!]
[Taecyeon avoids it!]
[Flustered]
- Spiderman is in danger!
- Let's go help him!
[Spider Gary in danger!]
Hey!
Hey, wait!
[Spider Gary's name tag has
been eliminated!]
- Hello.
- Yeah, hi.
- You know who's here, right?
- Yes, we know.
- Chu Sung Hoon is here.
- We're waiting to see him too.
[Is Gary Running Man Avengers'
first victim?]
- What were you doing with that?
- This is my superpower.
- You're Spiderman?
- Yeah.
Okay, good luck to you guys.
[Wishing 2PM luck on their mission,
and sends them away.]
Those guys...
[I'm Spider Gary!]
[You can't kill me that easily.]
Those two guys got me.
[Huh?]
[His name tag is attached to
a spider web?]
No one knew my little secret.
[Spider Gary's name tag is attached
to a spider web!]
[As long as that string doesn't get severed,
the name tag can be re-attached!]
A secret that no one was aware of.
[Spider Gary is brought back to life!]
Hello!
Don't come any closer,
or I'll shoot you.
I really will shoot you.
Don't come any closer.
Fine, want a go?
What should we do?
[One of Iron Ha's superpowers-
Flying through the air!]
- What is he doing?
- Wow!
[Moving effortlessly through the sky.]
[This is the power of Iron Ha's
superpowers through his gadgets.]
[I'm envious of HaHa's powers.]
Gary!
Why are you still here?
- Why are you running from us?
- Me?
Because I'm scared.
Sung Hoon's right over there.
Why are you scared?
But we eliminated your...
oh, it's back on there.
- His name tag is still there.
- Why? Didn't we rip it off?
Behind you!
- We really are easy to fool.
- We're too easy to fool.
We really are too easy to fool, aren't we?
[Making his escape before
he's chased after again.]
[Just then, The Fighter starts
to chase after Spider Gary!]
Help me!
- Gary!
- Yes?
Let's go for a round!
[The Fighter's superpower is activated!]
Sung Hoon!
You can't do this!
- Fight! Fight!
- Why do you want to see a fight?
[Spider Gary locked up in the ring
for the next minute with The Fighter.]
This is what they were carrying.
- What is that?
- It's a real ring.
Don't forget that I'm Spiderman.
[Acting as though something
super powerful is hidden in the bag.]
I... I have my superpowers.
- What? What do you have in the bag?
- It's something. I have my own tricks.
- And what is that?
- What do you think it is?
[The Fighter hesitating with his attack.]
Ugh, this is so annoying!
What is it?
What do you have in there?
Don't make me do it!
Don't make me take it out of the bag!
- You got ten seconds left.
- Ten seconds?
[The Fighter's minute
in the ring is almost up!]
Don't come near me!
You really will get yourself into trouble!
[Time's up!]
Sung Hoon!
I'm out of here!
[Spider Gary bluffs his way
out of danger.]
Who are those people going around in pairs?
Those guys dressed in suits?
That's Chu Sung Hoon's powers.
- His ring...
- What? I have no powers!
Why are you trying to hide it
when we've already seen it?
- He has a ring?
- You don't want him to catch up to you.
- Sung Hoon.
- Yes?
You have to move faster and
eliminate Gary and Jong Kook.
- Where's Jong Kook?
- What?
I haven't seen Jong Kook at all.
Jong Kook's going around saying that
he's going to destroy you this time.
- Jong Kook is going around saying...
- Where is he?
He says that he gave you a break ever since
he won that wrestling match against you.
Seriously?
Jong Kook!
Yeah, go get Jong Kook!
[Gentle Fighter really getting fired up
after hearing their comments.]
[Right then, Kkuk Thor is...]
I can't believe my name tag got enlarged
like this as soon as the game started.
I can't even do anything now.
[Dr. Zhee on the other hand is trying to raise
his heartbeat to make his transformation.]
[Able to make his transformation once
his heart rate reaches 170!]
- This is my chance.
- What are you doing?
Kwang Soo.
Kwang Soo!
- Kick me in the behind. Hurry.
- Want me to shoot you with my arrow?
No, just kick me with your foot.
Seriously.
Hey, hey.
[Giraffe Eye shoots Dr. Zhee
with his arrow of misfortune!]
Is it making you angry?
Why?
Are you getting angry?
Yeah, I'm angry.
I'm still not there?
What?
What is it?
What? What is it?
What's happening to me, Kwang Soo?
[Being taken somewhere after being
hit by Giraffe Eye's arrow of misfortune.]
- What have you done to me?
- What?
I'm so angry.
Seriously.
I was so close!
I seriously barely managed to get it up.
I was so close to hitting it.
[Misfortune: To lower his heart rate, he must
stay in the meditation room for 10 minutes.]
[The effects of the meditation room-
Heart rate is dropping at a steady decline.]
[Working hard again to bring
his heartbeat up to 170.]
[What kind of transformation will
take place after all his efforts?]
[Exercising like he has never done before!]
Let's make the transformation.
Please, just this once!
Please.
Please!
If your heart rate climbs over 170...
[If his heart rate climbs over 170...]
A truly frightening power
will be activated.
[His truly frightening power
will come to life!]
[The nature of the beast that has been
hidden deep inside of Dr. Zhee!]
[Awaken the power!]
[Heart rate breaks through 170!]
[Dr. Zhee completes his transformation
into a wild beast!]
[Kim Dong Hyun]
[The ultimate fighting champion
representing Korea!]
[Kim Dong Hyun!]
[Dr. Zhee's superpower-
He is the Hulk!]
[He is on the move!]
It's Kim Dong Hyun!
- What? What is it?
- It's The Hulk!
- Run!
- Who is that?
He keeps coming after us!
Please stop following us!
What the heck?
Hey, Dong Hyun!
- What are you doing?
- Come here, Sung Hoon!
What did you say?
[The Fighter flees the scene!]
Why are you here?
I guess I should be quieter.
Everyone is running away from me.
[Discovers his target!]
[Spider Gary!]
Wait!
[Monster vs. Human Spider.]
I don't know how to speak Korean.
Wait a minute.
Do you even know what I have in here?
No, I don't know.
- Wait! Don't you know what's in here?
- What? What is it?
[Spider Gary trying to
bluff his way out again!]
You can end up regretting this.
Why don't we shake hands first?
It's been a while.
- Yes.
- Let's shake with our right hand.
I'll put my fist down first.
Wait!
You're squeezing my hand!
Dong Hyun!
Wait!
[Spider Gary trying to use
his web once again?]
[Starts his spider web attack!]
- What is it?
- Stop coming after me!
[But his spider web is
extremely tangled in his bag.]
[Immediate chaos!]
[The Hulk starts his attack on Gary!]
What are you guys doing?
[But his spider web is still fortunately
stuck to the name tag!]
[What?
It's been severed!]
[Spider Gary- Out!]
I'm really out?
He severed my web?
He really severed my web?
[Can't believe it's been severed.]
What the heck is this?
How is this web supposed to
work on anyone?
Who was I ever supposed to catch
with a web like this?
- It's been five minutes, so the power is up.
- Okay.
[Five minutes is up.
The Hulk is back to being Dr. Zhee.]
[Pathetic, Running Man Avengers.]
This is total chaos.
Total chaos!
- What is going on here?
- Gary, out. Gary, out.
He's out?
[What do I do?]
[The Fighter's ambush attack!]
[Captain Running Man drops
his weapon!]
- Sung Hoon.
- Yoo Jae Suk!
Let's go for a round!
[The Fighter's power is activated!
A ring match for a full minute!]
What is this?
- What is your power?
- What?
- What's your power?
- My power is...
You can't be reckless with
your attack on me.
I doubt you'll be able to eliminate
my name tag so easily.
If you make a mistake...
it could be you getting ousted.
Why do you think I keep
appearing in front of you?
- Here, rip it off.
- Seriously!
[Dummy...]
Here, rip it off.
- Sung Hoon! Come on!
- Seriously!
- Go on and rip it off.
- What the heck!
- Rip it off, Sung Hoon.
- What the heck is that?
No, you can't.
[Iron Ha is seen headed in their direction.]
[Fires a shot from his glove weapon.]
What?
What is that?
[An ideal suit to chase his enemies away.]
- What is he doing?
- What is that?
What was that?
- I'll shoot again if you come any closer.
- Chansung.
What was that?
- What is that?
- What is going on here?
Hasn't it been a minute already?
- Okay.
- Where did he go?
[The Fighter's time in the ring
is over already.]
- Not me! It's not me!
- No, Sung Hoon!
Through the strength of
thunder and lightning!
[Releasing the power of thunder
in Kkuk Thor's zone.]
[Both of them showing off their powers.]
What is he doing?
[Thunders and lightening.
Kid hero Iron Ha acting recklessly.]
Hello, Master.
Up! Up!
Up!
[Almost gets caught by Master Jung
from all his reckless behavior.]
Why?
Aren't you on our side?
[Huh?]
[The Fighter making an appearance!]
Get down. I have to get down.
Sung Hoon is up here.
Get me down!
Wait, wait.
I have to get back down.
[Mouse caught in the barrel.
The Fighter above, Master Jung down below.]
I have to stay up here for now.
Stop!
Don't put me down!
I have to stay up here!
This position is perfect.
Jong Kook.
What are you doing here by yourself while
everyone else is getting caught?
Shouldn't you come out and face
some of our enemies?
- Come on out here.
- What did you say?
I think we'll be put in danger
if we were to step in there.
- We have to get rid of him, Jae Suk.
- What are you doing?
What are you doing?
What's your power?
With the power...
You're dead if you even
step foot in here.
Iron Ha having too much fun
with his gadgets.]
Seriously!
The fire is out!
Iron Man!
Fly into the air!
Let go of me.
Let go! I'm the Iron Man!
- What is that?
- What do you think it is?
- Why? What is it?
- Come in here if you're that curious.
With the power...
[The Fighter eliminates
Kkuk Thor's name tag!]
With the power...
With the power of what?
Do you know who made
his name tag so big like that?
Your power, my butt!
[Kkuk Thor and Iron Ha- Out!]
I haven't been able to set
foot out of here.
What have you been doing
inside there all night?
[Every single one of them is pathetic.]
[Dr. Zhee dreaming of transforming
once more.]
Please.
I don't want to live as me.
I want to live as The Hulk.
Please!
I'm The Hulk!
[His true nature starting to
move inside him once again.]
[So close to breaking 170!]
[Eliminated by The Fighter
right before his transformation!]
I was right about to transform!
No more Hulk from now on!
I was just about to transform.
I can't believe you did that.
[Dr. Zhee- Out!]
Thank you.
Thank you!
Thank you for your efforts.
[I'm sorry, Dong Hyun.]
2PM...
Have you seen Chansung and Taecyeon?
- You can't try to shoot me again.
- I only have one shot left.
I have to make sure that I hit my target.
Ouch, my hand!
Do you know what's going on?
We have to work together.
- We're the only Running Man members left.
- There's still Ji Hyo too.
- Let's stay together.
- Give me my arrow.
I can't give you your arrow.
- I know you'll shoot me with it.
- I'm not going to shoot you.
Who's the first person that
got into your car today?
I'm the one who picked you up.
They do say that people are different
before and after their trip to the bathroom.
Give me the arrow.
I'll shoot it when we're in danger.
[The deadly chase continues even
amongst the guest members!]
[Master Jung's target is the 2PM Twins.]
You guys made me run too much.
[Which one of Chansung and Taecyeon has
the 'Out' sign on their back?]
[The older men's frightening joint attack.]
[Not letting the name tag
out of his grip!]
No!
[An invincible talisman on
Taecyeon's back!]
[Only the elimination of Chansung will
oust the 2PM Twins!]
What are you doing, Ji Hyo?
- Isn't that Gary's bag?
- What do you want?
Kwang Soo!
[In order to face those monsters...]
[I only have one choice.]
Jae Suk, behind you!
[A full on open hunt
of the Running Man Avengers!]
[If only the Running Man Avengers can
somehow gather up their strength together...]
Are you chasing after me?
- We're on the same team.
- What?
[The Fighter and Captain Running Man
working together?]
Hang on!
[Captain Running Man and The Fighter
joining their efforts to capture Giraffe Eye!]
Wait!
You can't do this!
Wait a second.
What's going on here?
[Running Man Avengers Team splitting
like a piece of glass yet again.]
I almost had Jae Suk's name tag!
[Running Man Avengers unable to work
together like they had agreed to earlier...]
Huh?
Isn't that Dong Hyun?
I thought Dong Hyun was dead.
Isn't he?
Don Hyun...
I thought I just saw Dong Hyun.
What?
- Who?
- Kim Dong Hyun.
What do you mean, Kim Dong Hyun?
I saw him earlier.
[Captain Running Man is the only person
who didn't see Dong Hyun earlier.]
- Kim Dong Hyun.
- UFC Champion, Kim Dong Hyun?
No way.
- You didn't see him? I saw him.
- Saw who?
I saw Dong Hyun.
- He was screaming and running around.
- I think I just saw...
- Green. He's in green.
- Yeah!
- That's him.
- That's Kim Dong Hyun?
Are you kidding me right now?
With Sung Hoon right there and
Master Jung... what are you doing?
And Taecyeon and Chansung too!
And you're now telling me that
Kim Dong Hyun is here too?
[Unaware that ousted Dr. Zhee's power has
been transferred over to Black Blank.]
But I know that Suk Jin is ousted.
I know.
I ousted him.
Look!
Look over there!
[The monster makes his appearance.]
Kim Dong Hyun...
that's Kim Dong Hyun!
[Champion Kim Dong Hyun
makes another appearance.]
[Here he comes!]
[Running away at the speed of light!]
I thought you were dead!
What's going on here?
[Dr. Zhee was definitely ousted...]
It's me, Ji Hyo.
- Ji Hyo?
- Yes, I'm Ji Hyo.
[Transfer of power!
Black Blank transformed into The Hulk!]
- There. Over there
- What?
He's hiding in there.
- He's hiding in there.
- In there?
You're going to attack my back
when I go after him, aren't you?
No, I'm not.
Just go.
- I think I need a cup of coffee.
- Oh my goodness.
Please... why do you have
Ji Hyo's name?
Come on!
Don't you think this is too much?
Seriously!
Taecyeon!
Hey, Taecyeon.
What's going on here?
- Me? I'm still alive.
- Are you on his team?
What is going on?
Long time no see, Dong Hyun.
- What are you doing?
- It's me, Ji Hyo.
- What?
- I'm Song Ji Hyo.
What are you saying right now?
- What do you mean, you're Ji Hyo?
- You're Ji Hyo?
Why are you Ji Hyo?
Aren't you... you're not on my team?
Hey, Taecyeon!
Don't just stand there!
After all these years of knowing each other,
how can you just stand there?
Come here and do something.
- Come on.
- Do you want me to help you?
- What?
You need to be helping with him,
not with me.
- You want my help with him?
- Yeah.
- Then you'll rip off his name tag?
- I have a bad feeling about this!
Where's my water gun?
Come on!
Why are you all surrounding me?
[Now that the tiger is gone,
the den is full of lions.]
Hey, Taecyeon.
[Master Jung and 2PM's Taecyeon's
joint attack!]
Don't you think this is too unfair?
Come on.
What am I supposed to do here?
I manage to escape from
the tiger just to...
[Discovers 2PM Twin, Chansung.]
- Are you trying to get me?
- I just want to shake your hand.
I feel like shaking your hand
will be the end of me.
Where are you going?
Seriously...
come on, seriously!
[The Hulk attacks 2PM's Chansung!]
We just have to rip off your
name tag, right?
- I won't die even if you rip off my name tag.
- You won't?
Why can't you be ousted?
[A battle of two against one.
Captain Running Man mustering up his strength.]
But I won't die.
Why... why can't you get ousted?
You have to find my other half.
You need to oust my other half.
Taecyeon!
Seriously!
[2PM Twins- Taecyeon is invincible!
Chansung must be ousted and eliminate both!]
[Chansung with life or death on his shoulders
is being chased after by The Hulk!]
Seriously! How am I supposed to
beat your strength?
Right?
So just come on.
[The monster's attack!]
Taecyeon!
I'm fine!
- No, I'm not.
- I'm fine!
I'm really not okay.
Please!
You have to find my other half.
- You have to find my other half.
- You want to go out like this?
You want to get beat one on one
or one against two?
What's the difference between the two?
I'm exhausted!
[2PM Twins- Out!]
I didn't even get to do anything!
Wow... you ever given any thought
to trying out for UFC?
Wow... you're so strong!
Thank you.
Thanks for your effort.
I think Ji Hyo's going to win.
This... this was a battle
that I could never have won.
I could never have won that.
[Captain Running Man- Out!]
[2PM- Out.
2PM- Out.]
You're going to oust me like this
as I'm standing here drinking water?
- What happened?
- Chansung got both of us ousted.
Really?
[Chansung got us eliminated...]
Okay, since we don't know what'll happen,
can we first shake hands?
I don't want to.
Your hands are too dirty.
[Master Jung fully aware of
Black Blank's powers.]
How can a woman's hands
be so dirty?
[And not even giving Black Blank any time
to transform into The Hulk.]
What are you going to do about Sung Hoon?
He's worse than Jong Kook.
[If they go by strength alone,
The Fighter has the best chance of winning.]
I think we should first oust the girl...
I'm not going to say anything about that.
He said that so seriously.
I think we should do something
about the lady first.
[Asking her to step out of a man's fight?]
[First up is the battle between
Black Blank and The Fighter.]
Let's squarely face off with one another.
But no one can be upset
from getting ousted, okay?
Okay.
[Does that mean she thinks
she can win?]
You can't be upset, okay?
If I could've just had some time
to activate my powers...
Can't we do it with one of
Sung Hoon's hands tied behind his back?
[Is Black Blank really going to do this?]
Can't we seriously do this with one
of his hands tied behind his back?
- Okay, let's do it that way.
- With one hand tied behind your back.
- Okay.
- Seriously?
[A real battle with one of his
hands tied behind his back?]
Like this.
- Will that be enough?
- It'll be fine.
- Really?
- Even if I die, I want to die with dignity.
[The final surviving member
of Running Man Avengers.]
I don't want to go down without a fight
just because I'm a girl.
[Ji Hyo steps into the battle with
Running Man and Ace's pride on the line!]
[Black Blank and one-armed Fighter.]
[Ace Ji Hyo escaping his clutches!]
Why are you so strong?
[Black Blank, no, Ace Ji Hyo!
Faces off in a real battle!]
[Her name tag is within his grip!]
[Ji Hyo's crucial attack!]
You're good.
She's really good!
[The Fighter with a new glint
in his eye!]
[He grabs it again!]
No, it won't rip off!
I can't get it off her back!
I can't get it off!
- Are you okay?
- Yes, I'm fine.
[Black Blank- Out!]
[She may have lost the battle,
but she is our eternal Ace!]
[And The Fighter who fought with only
one arm just as he promised...]
[Now!]
[The ultimate martial arts director...]
[And the strongest fighter.]
Let's go for a round!
[The ultimate battle between the two men
with their pride on the line.]
- It's an honor.
- No, the honor is mine.
[Once the cordial greeting
is out of the way...]
Okay!
[The two dragons will
face off with each other in this ring!]
[Real life fighter, Chu Sung Hoon.]
[VS. Action Master, Jung Doo Hong.]
[The two of Korea's biggest legends
faces each other in this ring!]
[When it comes to strength,
The Fighter is unbeatable.]
[But Master Jung
easily escapes his clutches.]
[Each fighting with their own styles.
Who will win the battle?]
[Master Jung attacks with
lightning fast speed.]
As expected...
[Battle getting fiercer and fiercer.]
[The Fighter moves in on
Master Jung's back!]
[Fighter moves in first to grab
Master Jung by his back!]
[And eliminates Master Jung's
name tag!]
Yes!
[The ultimate winner,
The Fighter, Chu Sung Hoon!]
- Thank you.
[And thus...]
[Running Man Avengers were defeated.]
[Several days later...]
[Giraffe Eye called into
an unidentifiable room.]
[Taking his rage out on the bow.]
What is this?
Team Avengers?
What right do you think you have?
[The one called him in is none other
than Director Dong Fury.]
Director Nick Fury!
No, it's Dong Fury.
It's Team Avengers
performance evaluation.
Performance evaluation?
- This is all our performance evaluation?
- Captain Running Man.
Team Leader.
Wasn't able to lead the team as a leader,
and was too focused on his own win
which led to joining hands
and working together with the enemy.
That's correct.
He's the one who ousted me!
Unsuitable!
- What does 'Unsuitable' mean?
- Thor, the God of Thunder.
Even with his strength and
excellent physical abilities
he failed to protect his own
team members.
He hid out of his concern for his own safety,
and fell to his own demise.
That's correct.
That's an accurate description.
Unsuitable!
- What's 'Unsuitable'?
- Iron Man.
Classic narcissistic personality.
Unsuitable.
The Hulk.
Out of control.
Unsuitable.
Spiderman.
Lacks in ability to understand. Unsuitable.
You can't find him unsuitable for that.
That's just how he normally is.
Giraffe Eye.
I never just think of myself,
but I always put everyone first.
- Unsuitable.
- No, wait!
Black Blank.
She was the last sole survivor
of the Avenger's Team.
She's a total wildcat.
She only cares for her own survival.
Extreme improvisational skills,
outstanding ability to overcome danger.
Passed as the ultimate member
of the Avengers Team.
What the heck does that mean?
She really passed?
You mean you evaluated all of us?
What is this?
There's not much time left.
Time?
There's no time?
But aren't the Avengers over?
A war is approaching.
Prepare yourself.
Another battle is approaching us?
Director Dong Fury!
What does that mean?
Dong Fury!
Subtitles by DramaFever
[2013. 06. 10.
Rooftop of SBS Mokdong Building.]
Just what is going on?
[108 eyes are following
every move Running Man makes!]
You can use all 108 of the
security cameras.
[The one who escapes,
will meet the man...]
[The man with 108 eyes,
Grim Reaper, Jung Woo Sung.]
Why are you doing this?
I really am a huge fan of yours.
[The only road to survival
is to blind his eyes!]
[Appearance of the ultimate chaser!]
[Running Man vs. The Grim Reaper.
Who will be the winner to escape the dark?]
[Next Week's Running Man-
The Grim Reaper Race with Jung Woo Sung.]