Running Man
2013 end of the year special episode,
Men's Popularity Race.
The man you'd want to date the most
if you were to be born again.
[Who would you want to date
if you were to be born again?]
[A race of popularity between the men
who caused the biggest stir in 2013.]
[Just who will be the most popular man
to woo the hearts of all these women?]
[1,000 Korean women between their
teens and fifties were asked.]
[Who would you like to date?]
[December, 2013 in Yeoui-do.]
2013 end of the year Running Man
special episode, Men's Popularity Race.
Then shall we get started?
Contestants, please come on out.
[First contestant- Yoo Jae Suk.]
[Portrayed roles such as Yoo Hyuk,
Yoo-ames Bond, and Yoo-ruce Willis in 2013.]
[Iconic for his dancing, and stirred up the
hearts of women by showing off his derriere.]
[Second contestant- Lee Kwang Soo.]
[Modelesque Giraffe- Showed off his nature
of being the Giraffe of betrayal once again.]
[New trend setting man who brought us
Kwang-vatar, Kwang-Toad, and Kwang-triever.]
Third contestant, please come on out!
[Third contestant- Ji Suk Jin.]
That's not how you're supposed to do it!
[Contestant number three- Ji Suk Jin.]
[A man you can't help but like even if
he does tend to be high maintenance.]
[A romantic man who is most popular
with women of his age.]
[Contestant number four- Ha Ha.]
[Crooked dislocated hip strut?]
[A representative of children of all ages,
Haroro.]
[The world's cutest daddy who swept many
women off their feet with his leg tripping.]
Fifth contestant, please come on out!
[Contestant number five- Gary.]
[Looking like a real hip hop artist
for once in a long time.]
Gary, are you drunk?
[The man we all want to have, Gary-
Hero of all unattractive men worldwide.]
Our sixth contestant, please come on out.
[Final Running Man contestant.]
[Did the music stop?]
[Contestant number six- Kim Jong Kook.]
What is this?
Why is he the only one getting this song?
[Everyone's disgruntled at the special
treatment that Kkuk is receiving.]
[Was an icon of romance at one time,
but has been redubbed as chatty muscle boy.]
I used to think that you were the strong
and silent type back then.
[He really did used to be cool...]
I used to think that he was cool.
I miss you, Eun Hye!
All the Running Man members
have now made their entrance.
- We will now meet the other contestants.
- Other contestants?
- This year's biggest trendsetting men.
- Trendsetting?
Our first trendsetting man.
Please come on out.
[Contestant number seven- Lee Juck.]
He used to be in Panic.
[All the men of Running Man are sent into a
state of panic by his unexpected entrance.]
- Don't pay him any attention.
- What is he doing here?
[A popular ballad singer who can steal a
woman's heart with his sweet lyrics.]
- He looks so cool all dressed up like that.
- Why are you wearing rain boots?
- Why are you sitting in front of the piano?
- Are you going to play the piano?
[A man who can play the piano,
which no women can resist.]
You definitely need to sit in front
of a piano at all times.
He looks so cool.
If glasses are what defines me,
then piano is what defines Lee Juck.
He needs to have
that piano attached to his hip.
[A man who should never be
without his piano.]
[Beautiful piano melody,
and his beautiful voice...]
He's so cool.
[No matter what anyone has to say,
his charm by the piano is undeniable.]
I need to learn how to play the piano.
No, don't get up, don't get up!
Stay seated right there!
- Stay right by the piano!
- That was really cool.
Contestant number eight,
please come on out.
- Who is it?
- It's Kwang Gyu!
[Contestant number eight- Kim Kwang Gyu]
You're not here to shoot a commercial.
He's so weird.
[Breaking out in dance out of the blue.]
[A man with an endless limit of magnetism.
A free spirited man with high energy.]
Contestant number nine,
please come on out.
[Contestant number nine- Jang Ki Ha]
[So handsome...]
[A man who knows how to enjoy the simplest--
as well as life's biggest luxuries.]
[Huh? SHINee?]
[Showing off his level of lower class.]
[His unique charm that no one can deny-
Specialty: Dubbed 'The Lucifer'.]
[Is that Jo Yong Pil?]
[Muzy- A man who can make any woman laugh
with a knack for musical abilities.]
[These five are the top
trendsetting men of 2013?]
How is this a popularity special episode?
Today's guests and Running Man members
will participate in a race.
It's a race to determine which
of the men is most popular.
We have asked a thousand women
from their teens to their fifties.
This race will determine which one of you
is the most popular of all.
What we asked them was,
if you were to be born again...
To clarify, if all of you and the women who
were asked, were to be born again
in that case, which one of you men
would they like to date?
[Which one of these men would they like to
date if they were to be born again?]
I bet they picked me.
[A man to represent these 1,000 women
as the one they'd most likely want to date.]
[A question that delves deep into
the heart of these women.]
[If you were to be born again...]
[Which one of these men
would you like to date?]
[Through this detailed research,
their ranking from 1-11 will be determined!]
There is a total of 11 of you
as the men to represent year 2013.
And you will be competing against
our writers in this competition.
Which means, after you complete all
four levels of your missions
to arrive at the final location
with your final results...
If you guess all 11 ranks correctly
without getting a single guess wrong...
then you guys will win this race.
If you don't, then you all will face
some sort of a penalty altogether.
If you all end up winning this race,
then you will all receive a gold prize.
[If all the men end up winning the race,
then everyone will receive a gold prize.]
- We can all do this.
- Let's work together and do this.
[Today's group mission-
Teamwork is of utmost importance.]
[Traveling to several different locales
that represents a woman's heart.]
[Win a good hint if you succeed the mission,
and an ambiguous hint if you fail.]
[Must learn to understand women
in order to win the race.]
[If you were to be born again...
which of these men would you want to date?]
[Popularity Men Race- Start!]
Stop glaring at the lower rank.
It's not right to make the actual low rank
holders to sit in the lower ranked seats.
Then are you saying that your side is the
upper rank, and the other is the lower rank?
- No, this is just where we're sitting.
- There was nowhere else to sit.
To be honest though,
these two are untouchable right now.
[Is Ha Ha admitting that Jae Suk and
Gary are upper rank holders?]
The public's opinion never changes.
It's always Yoo Jae Suk.
No, you don't know that.
Listen, there's no need to even discuss that.
We're all on the same team today.
We just need to guess the ranks correctly,
and go our own separate ways with our gold.
- Yes, you're right.
- Let's play it cool.
- Play it cool, and say our goodbyes.
- Okay, I got it.
We can all say our goodbyes
and go our separate ways.
But I still don't want to be labeled
as being lower class rank.
I'm not quite sure where I stand
in the public's opinion.
We've got a lot of smooth talkers here,
and with this many good people here
there's a good chance that some of you
may not get a chance to get to talk.
So let's all make sure that everyone
gets their chance to talk as well.
Muzy sitting in the front seat
by himself could feel frustrated.
So let's all make sure to include him
in our conversations.
And let's all make sure to laugh
at each other's jokes too.
[Everyone agreeing to laugh and
appraise each other's jokes and stunts.]
- It's not a loss to laugh at other's jokes.
- Let's laugh at the guests' jokes.
Don't leave me out.
[Good timing]
That was good timing.
That was perfect timing,
with the perfect one liner.
- Is Muzy...
- It's not 'Muzy'.
[It's not 'Muzy', but it's 'Muzy'.]
I went to some rural town recently
and one grandmother thought that
my name was 'Myoji'.
[Myoji=Cemetery, graveyard.]
- That's not your real name, is it?
- Lee Hong Li.
- Who names their kid, Muzy?
- Then is that your nickname?
['Nickname' is the term used
on the internet.]
I have an internet nickname too.
It's 'Ramses'.
- Why is your nickname, 'Ramses'?
- Don't you know Ramses, the son of the sun?
You?
You're the son of the sun?
That's right, that's me!
Ah!
I get it now!
[Ramses, Kwang Gyu.]
[The men's first point of attack.]
[Where women come to work on their figure-
The dance studio.]
Can you move a little faster?
What took you so long to get here?
[There's always one person who lags behind-
Ramses Kwang Gyu.]
- I thought that you went home.
- What are you doing?
[45 year old Kwang Gyu-
Another high maintenance man.]
What are you doing?
You need someone to do everything for you.
You're the first person we've seen who's
even higher maintenance than Suk Jin.
[Even more high maintenance
than Big-nosed Brother.]
By any chance, do you know a game
called, 'Dari-Dari'?
I have very bad legs.
(Dari= Legs)
Why doesn't that surprise me?
- All of you need to work together...
- Yes?
To pick the number of legs...
I mean, guess the number of legs...
Let's try to read correctly on
the first try.
MC Blank.
- You used to MC on a live show.
- I know, but this isn't a live show.
Choose a number and work together to stand on
the same number of legs as the number chosen.
- I see.
- So you have to lift your legs?
[A mission that requires a sense of balance.]
We get a hint if we succeed this, right?
[If they succeed within three tries,
they'll earn themselves a hint.]
- Is there a time limit?
- 30 seconds.
- Yes, you must do it within 30 seconds.
- 30 seconds is plenty for a game like this.
[Excuse me?]
What kind of a rule is that?
There are certain sets of rules that
all variety show hosts and players
in the world meet up
every four years to decide on.
It's a set of rules determined by
all the variety show hosts.
- These rules are determined every four years.
- Let's expand it to 35 seconds next time.
We can all discuss if that's what we
want to do at the next meeting.
You must finish within 30 seconds,
and must stay in that position for 5 seconds.
Okay, let's do this and
guess the correct rank of popularity.
Then, we can win this race against the writers
and all win our own individual gold prize.
Then we can all say goodbye
and go our separate ways.
[Let's play it cool.]
- Are we going to start now?
- Yes, you come in.
- What is this?
- Come in.
- What's coming in?
- What is he doing?
What is that?
[The game must be played on top
of the acupuncture mat.]
No way!
We should agree to eliminate the use of
acupuncture mats at the next meeting.
Is this being sponsored or something?
[No, this acupuncture mat is more precious
to a variety show than any sponsorship.]
- This is driving me crazy.
- This is really painful.
Even if you have the popularity,
it's of no use without your health.
- Just stay quiet and don't say anything.
- Seriously, just be quiet!
But this really is good for your health.
There are a ton of other things that are
good for your health than this.
[But other things aren't as entertaining...]
Everyone must take off their socks.
Ugh, this mat really hurts.
[Preparing to face the acupuncture mat
without their socks.]
We need to pick the number first,
so someone must step up and do that.
[Kwang Gyu steps up for the group,
and picks the numbered card.]
- Please, please.
- Show your number to the camera.
- What is it?
- It's not a two or a three, is it?
[Picks the number 'Two'.]
[How are 11 people to stand
on only two legs?]
What if we all stand on our heads,
and lean our feet on the one person standing?
- Everyone stand upside down but one person?
- Like a bridge?
- That's good.
- That plan could work.
How about two people stand on one foot each,
and the rest stand upside down on their heads?
- That's sound good.
- I think that's a great idea.
Why doesn't Ki Ha be one and
hold one of the lines steady?
- We can do it in a double line.
- Then let's figure out who'll do what.
- Then everyone else go behind Ki Ha.
- It's a good plan, but don't get angry.
I'm not getting angry at all.
I'm scared.
[Loud voiced coaching making some of
the first time guests nervous.]
- Just talk more calmly.
- We're just strategizing right now.
Ki and to Suk Jin will be the first line.
Jong Kook to Kwang Gyu
will be the second line.
Everyone get yourselves together!
Let's all quiet down!
[Icon of intellect finally explodes.]
- Scream out loud, Ki Ha!
- I really am sorry for this.
Make some noise, you fool!
[Even Ki Ha is starting to loosen up,
and get into the spirit of things.]
Look at how Hyun Moo looks like he's aged
some already before the game even started.
[Hyun Moo having aged noticeably since
before their strategizing started.]
- This is how we normally talk.
- You've got a five o'clock shadow too.
[His five o'clock shadow is darkening
right before our very own eyes.]
- This is just the beginning.
- We've got the whole day ahead of us.
Okay, we will start with your
first attempt.
[Heavier the weight of the legs,
the heavier the pain of agony.]
[Where in the world am I?]
[Almost seems to have it...]
[Then Kwang Gyu's legs give out on him.]
What's wrong with you?
[Not much time left on the clock!]
Put your legs up!
[Oh... he's got it!]
[Now they must stay in this position for
five full seconds in order to succeed!]
[Will they succeed?]
Success!
[Succeeds in withstanding five seconds
on only two legs!]
[Screams of agony heard from everyone.]
Stop coming up with these sort of games!
We did it, everyone.
[A success earned through
their harmonious teamwork.]
I applaud you on your great teamwork,
and you've earned yourselves a hint.
[Earned themselves a hint on the
order of popularity rank.]
It had better be a good hint.
I've got indentations all over my hands.
You just need your fingertips to
play the piano, so you'll be fine.
How am I supposed to play with my fingertips
without the use of my hands?
[So the hands just get in the way?]
I would like to propose something here.
You've already earned yourselves
your first hint.
- But by increasing the level of difficulty...
- No, forget it.
How can it get more difficult
than two legs?
Doing it on one leg.
[Offering two additional hints if they can
do it only on one leg.]
You're right.
We could do it in the shape of a 'V'.
Like we've done before, the person at the end
would have to lift up one of his leg.
You only get one chance.
And we don't have to lift up both of
our legs right from the get-go.
Since we're all playing in a group race,
how about you lower your voice a bit?
- I'm sorry.
- You sound like you're angry at me.
Let's ask others for their opinion.
What do you think of this, Hyun Moo?
- Excuse me?
- Next person if you don't have an opinion.
- No, that's not what I was saying.
- He said he'll be back in 60 seconds.
That's not my line.
[That line belongs to this man.]
[Hyun Moo's line is,
'We'll be back after these messages.']
- What are your thoughts, Kwang Gyu?
- Me?
He said he'll just go along
with the crowd.
- When we do this...
- We heard you!
[Ah, the stress!]
Okay, we're going to start.
[MC Blank stepping up to put
all the men back in line.]
Hey!
You, be quiet!
- Be quiet and let me talk!
- Sorry.
[Live broadcast specialist,
MC Blank explodes.]
- Our MC is very angry right now.
- Yes, I'm sorry.
[What am I doing here?]
Are you done strategizing?
One, two, three!
Start!
[One legged challenge-  Start!]
[The plan is to get in a v-shaped formation,
then put their weight on Kkuk's shoulders.]
Hurry it up!
[Everyone's already starting to quake.]
[They're building and getting into formation
much faster than the previous time.]
[It's now up to Mr. Capable and
his ability to endure their weight...]
Put them up!
[All the men lift up
the other remaining legs...]
[Mr. Capable must endure the weight of
all ten men on just one foot.]
[Only one foot left grounded!]
[Must endure this position for five seconds.]
[Just one more second...]
Success!
[They did it!]
[Point of collapsing.]
[You'd think they won first place in
some world competition.]
[An ocean of tears.]
[An emotional victory.]
You've won yourselves a total
of three hints.
You may choose three hints
out of this container.
- How about Ki Ha?
- Pick one, Ki Ha.
[Ki Ha to pick the first hint.]
Please show your hint to the camera.
- A child drawing hint?
- What's a 'child drawing hint'?
- Kwang Gyu can pick the next one.
- Go on and pick.
- No, Hyun Moo can pick.
- No, the father can pick.
How am I your father?
I just picked one.
[Yoo Hyuk steals their chance while
they were bickering.]
- Intermediate hint.
- First one is a child's drawing.
[First hint is a child's drawing of five
different people.]
[The people in these drawings are of those
in 7th through 11th ranking positions.]
We're going to move on to
the next location.
Do you by any chance have any
medicated patches?
[Discussing the drawing in the car.]
I think you're right.
I think it's Kwang Gyu.
[They're sure that this one is Kwang Gyu?]
- Look at the hair.
- It's a cute drawing.
[And mysterious brown colored hair.]
- Could it be Hyun Moo?
- It looks like Hyun Moo.
Or is it, Ki Ha?
- But the hair is colored.
- I've never colored my hair.
He says he's never colored his hair,
but I've colored my hair before.
- This is 100% Muzy.
- Why is that one Muzy?
[Anyone can see that this one is Muzy.]
What's the other hint in
the envelope?
[They also received two intermediate hints
in an envelope.]
[Lee Juck is one rank above
Kim Jong Kook.]
I beat Kim Jong Kook!
[No Way]
There's another one.
[3rd, 6th, and 10th place holders
were born in the 80's.]
- Who all were born in the 80's?
- Raise your hands.
[Muzy- '81; Ki Ha- '82; Kwang Soo- '85.]
- Tenth place.
- No, it's not him.
- I don't think it's him.
- I think I'm in tenth place.
The reason being, Muzy's one of the
pictures that the kids drew.
[Muzy's picture was one of the drawings
that the children drew...]
[Then Muzy is the 10th place holder?]
What about this one?
What kind of clothing is this?
[And another picture that may be
indicating Big-nosed Brother.]
- That does look like you though.
- But look at how fat the face is.
You are chubby, Suk Jin.
Aren't there any pictures of you
during a chubby phase?
This hint says that this person is
one rank above Kim Jong Kook.
Which means that if that person is drawn,
then Jong Kook has to be one of these too.
- That's right.
- But we all agree that Jong Kook's not here.
[Since there's no picture of Jong Kook, then
Lee Juck and Jong Kook are higher in rank.]
Which means that I have to be in
the top four ranking positions.
According to these clues.
Since I'm one rank above Jong Kook,
then it means I'm one of the top four.
You have to think about winning the game,
not gloating that you're above me in rank.
[Winning the game aside, Lee Juck
is just happy to have beaten Jong Kook]
Never mind all that.
We're all on the same team.
[Will the true ranking of their popularity
be the same as their guesses?]
[Their second target location is...]
[The place where all beauty begins!
A beauty salon.]
[Huh? Could this be a quiz
of some sorts?]
[Seoul University graduate, Lee Juck and Ki Ha
with Hyun Moo, a graduate from Y University.]
Hyun Moo told me that he has never
failed a single exam in his life.
- Is everyone seated?
- Yes.
Here's your second mission.
[Popularity Race- Second mission!]
Even though looks are very important,
intelligence is just as important.
- Yes, of course it is.
- That's why we've prepared this mission.
Running Academic Quiz.
[Running Academic Quiz!]
Do you all see the board with different
categories and values in front of you?
You all will be taking turns to
answer the questions on this board.
The total number of points earned with
all eleven members playing
must be at least 30 points.
[Each of them must participate in the quiz
to get 30 points or more to succeed.]
Ha Ha's good at nonsense and
entertainment questions.
- Jae Suk's good with common sense questions.
- Gary's good with women's feelings.
Yeah, Gary's good with women's feelings.
Now that I look at the different categories,
I realize that we need to work together on it.
- Which category are you good at, Kwang Gyu?
- Me?
Women's feelings?
[Kwang Gyu's category of expertise-
Women's feelings?]
- What about you, Muzy?
- Relationship?
- You're good with relationships?
- Yes, relationships.
How about you?
- Ah, you mean, Lee Juck?
- Yes, Lee Juck.
- How about SAT questions?
- Okay, SAT questions!
You can take the SAT questions.
- I'm of the academic testing era.
- What about Ki Ha?
['82 born Ki Ha to take charge of
the SAT questions.]
- Can't I do 'Women's feelings'?
- No, you take the SAT questions.
Why is everyone trying to take
the Women's Feelings category?
Hyun Moo can help with the SAT category.
You can do that, right?
[Hyun Moo guaranteeing that he could
sweep the Entertainment category.]
If you have scored more than 30 points
by the end of the first round...
you can earn yourselves
a total of three hints.
We understand.
- Decide who will go first.
- We'll just go in the order we're sitting.
- No, not in that order.
- I'll go first.
[First one up- Jang Ki Ha.]
[He looks as though he's eyeing
the high score questions from off the bat.]
Which question would you like?
You really want me to go for
the SAT questions?
[He's really going for the five point
SAT question?]
SAT question for five points.
Jang Ki Ha, fighting!
[Jang Ki Ha, fighting!]
- We really need to get this.
- Five point questions are going to be hard.
You have chosen an SAT question
for five points.
Just the fact that he can even go for that
question makes me feel envious.
From the 2011 college entrance exam.
This is a question right out
of the 2011 entrance exam.
It's an English listening evaluation
question.
- We're going to get those five points!
- He's good at speaking English, isn't he?
I wasn't in KATUSA,
but I was an interpreter.
[Wow! He was an interpreter for the army?
A position which requires fluency in English?]
- We're going to win those five points!
- It's already in the bag!
[The anxiety level is even higher.]
- If anyone from the back gives any hints...
- That is not going to happen.
- You don't have to worry about that!
- All I know is, 'Yes' or 'No'.
I get nauseous just from thinking
about speaking English.
[How is that even possible?]
Listen to the following conversation.
From the price of the item that
the man orders...
Figure out how much his monthly payment
will be and tell us what that amount is.
- That's a tough question.
- How is he going to figure that out?
- Let me read it to you again.
- I didn't get what he said.
I don't even understand what
the question is.
Listen to the following conversation.
From the price of the item that
the man orders...
Figure out how much his monthly payment
will be and tell us what that amount is.
Figure out the amount of the monthly payment
from the price of the item the man orders.
- Monthly?
- Amount of the monthly payment.
I'll play the recording now.
Everyone must remain quiet.
Listen carefully.
It's a phone call.
Hello?
Roger's office supplies.
Would you like to place an order?
Yes, I'd like to order a fax machine.
- May I have the model number please?
- It's FX1000.
Alright.
That model is $150.
And I'd also like to order a scanner.
That's $250.
Would you like to order anything else?
No, that's all for today.
Then your total comes to $400.
Do you have any discount coupons?
Yes, I have a special
10% discount coupon.
Okay, we'll apply that to your order.
Would you like to take advantage of our
three or six month installment payment plan?
It's interest free.
I'll pay using
the three month installment plan.
- That was really long.
- That was long.
I recognized five of the words.
The English portion was hard enough,
but I was lost after the math portion.
- It's a combination of English and math.
- That's really tough.
[Just what is the dollar amount of
the man's monthly payment?]
Here's the question one more time.
You've listened to the conversation, right?
What is the monthly payment amount
for the items that the man ordered?
- I think I know the answer.
- Hyun Moo says he knows.
You have five seconds to answer.
Five, four...
$120.
[Ki Ha's answer is, $120.
Did he get the right answer?]
[Correct answer]
[SAT question for five points-
Jang Ki Ha gets the correct answer!]
[That was so cool.]
[Gets the national hero treatment.]
[Can only be envious...]
- That was pretty sexy.
- How did you come up with $120?
I added up the two items that were worth
$150, and $250 respectively.
Then he used his 10% coupon,
which brought it down to $360.
Then he got three month installment at
no interest, which made it $120.
[That's how the answer came to be $120.]
- I thought it was going to be $125.
- That's amazing.
[Whatever...]
That was a three point question in the foreign
language portion of 2011 entrance exam.
[A high score question from
2011 college entrance exam!]
[He just earned themselves five points
for their total of 30 points!]
- He totally earned my respect just now.
- Now that we've earned five points...
- Go with another hard one!
- Go for another five pointer!
[Jae Suk is riding the winning streak,
and going for the common sense category.]
- Just keep riding this wave.
- Okay, a five point question!
- I should've had that question.
- Don't blame me even if I get it wrong.
- Let's just keep going for the five pointers.
- I'll try my best to get it right.
[If Jae Suk gets it right too, then
that's ten points from only two people!]
Let's go.
This question...
is a terminology question.
- Terminology.
- He's really good at things like that.
- Jae Suk reads the newspaper every morning.
- Come on, Jae Suk.
I've even seen him reading
ancient Korean text.
Come on, Yoo Jae Suk.
Let's make some headlines!
- How is this going to make any headlines?
- You never know.
Come on, Yoo Jae Suk.
Let's see what you can do.
- Let's do this!
- Here's your question.
Let's see how deep his knowledge is.
- What is there that Yoo Jae Suk doesn't know?
- A man with an endless wealth of knowledge.
- Yoo Jae Suk's intelligence.
- Keep it down!
Here's your question.
In a stock market...
That's my question!
I should've had that question!
Seriously!
If the stock takes a sudden plunge,
or a sudden surge in value...
What do you call the system that puts a
halt on stock sales in those instances?
- You know that one, right?
- I know this one!
- Please, get it right!
- Come on, I know this one.
- You know this.
- I'm a little unsure about my answer.
The answer is...
- Please!
- Think about it coming to a stop.
I think... it's called 'The circuit break'.
- Is that right?
- Is that the answer?
- That's right, isn't it?
- Circuit break?
[Jae Suk is saying that it's called,
Circuit break...]
Circuit break.
That was good pronunciation.
That was for five points.
[Correct answer]
[Hooray!]
[Yoo Jae Suk gets the correct answer!]
He's good at everything he does.
'Circuit breaker' and
'Circuit break' are both very similar.
So we've decided to give you a break,
and count it as being a correct answer.
[Already at ten points!]
- How about Lee Juck takes his turn?
- Okay, Lee Juck.
[Time for Lee Juck to take the hot seat!]
How about 'People' for three points?
- Should I go with 'People'?
- Go for the four pointer.
- People for four points?
- People for four points.
[People for four points!]
- I feel so confident about this.
- We've been doing so well!
This really feels like
some sort of a quiz show.
[Both the questions and the contestants make
this mission feel like a real quiz show!]
The keyword is... Economics.
- You can do this, Lee Juck!
- It's got to be an economist.
[They're predicting that it's about
some economist.]
As the founding father of
principles of economy...
This man said that the nation is an invisible
hand in the economic market.
- You can't see his hand?
- You know this, right?
You know this, right, Lee Juck?
You have five seconds.
- Five, four, three...
- Adam Smith!
Adam Smith!
[Correct answer]
[Lee Juck gets the correct answer!]
[A very simple question for Lee Juck!]
- Adam Smith!
- How did you get that answer?
[The team has already
earned themselves 14 points!]
Why doesn't Suk Jin go next,
and I'll go after him?
- Okay, Suk Jin.
- Go with something that you're sure about.
Go with 'History', Suk Jin.
Take History.
- Suk Jin's good at this.
- Gam-oh-kyung-jang, 1894!
[What?
How can this be?]
[Even though we don't know if it's right,
he shouted out the answer with confidence!]
- Ji Suk Jin!
- History for five points.
Go for the five pointer!
Go with history for five points.
- I'll take history for five points.
- I think that's going to be too hard.
- You can do this, Suk Jin.
- A round of applause!
- He's won the Star Golden Bell before.
- You're right, he has.
- Really?
- Yes, he's won the Golden Bell before.
[Now that we think about it,
he's done that for six years in a row!]
The keyword for your question is...
- Person?
- Our country's beginning.
- He likes things like that.
- This is good.
- He likes questions like this.
- You know your history, don't you?
Here's your question.
Our country's very first book of poems
written in the Korean language...
- You know this one, Suk Jin.
- That's an easy one!
Is that the question?
Was 'The Legend of Hong Gil Dong'.
- I didn't know that.
- I knew that one.
Then what is the first book of poetry written
in Chinese characters from our country?
- I don't know this one.
- I have no idea what it is.
I'll give you a hint.
- It's three words, right?
- No, it's four words.
It's four words?
Then it's not what I'm thinking.
Can't we just attach the word, 'Jeon'
behind a three word answer?
Hoon-min-jung-eum?
[Kwang Gyu hasn't been any help
ever since their first 'Dari-Dari' mission.]
Hoon-min-jung-eum?
The very first book of poetry
written in Chinese characters?
Wait a minute.
Can Lee Kwang Soo answer for him?
He's got this sudden
glint in his eye right now.
He just told me that he knows the answer.
Five points if he gets it right,
but minus three points if he's wrong.
- Come on!
- Fine, then we won't do it.
- He really does have this look in his eye.
- No, we're not doing it.
- No, don't do it.
- Let's let him do it.
- Suk Jin doesn't know it anyway.
- Kwang Soo, are you sure of the answer?
- I know the answer.
- Then send him in!
[First time seeing him like this-
Could Kwang Soo really have the answer?]
Then I'll go with the answer
that I'm thinking of.
Okay, let me reiterate this.
Five points if he gets it right,
but minus three points if he's wrong.
- Are you sure of your answer?
- Okay, I understand.
[Can Kwang Soo come up with
the right answer?]
[What is the first ever book of poetry
that Kwang Soo is thinking of?]
Hakwon Byeolkok!
[What?]
[What about 'Hakwon Byeolkok'?]
[Answer wrong,
then you get the windy hairdryer!]
[He was given the benefit of the doubt,
but as always...]
[Three points are subtracted as agreed upon,
so they're down to 11 points.]
Isn't that a name of a song?
[Ah... now that they think about it...]
[That was a 1997 debut song
by Sechs Kies.]
He said he knew the answer.
[Shifting the blame on each other.]
[How could he have lost them the three points
that they worked so hard to earn?]
Ji Suk Jin forgoes his turn, so
you may go back to your seat now.
- Who did you think came up with that?
- Sechs Kies.
Give it back.
Give me the three points back.
How can I give it back?
[What's the correct answer?]
- The name of the poet is, Kim Si Seup.
- I know the answer!
It's Geum-Ho-Shin-Hwa!
[Kim Si Seup's Geum-Ho-Shin-Hwa.]
- Ah, Geum-Ho-Shin-Hwa?
- Geum-Ho-Shin-Hwa!
Hey, it's wasn't Sechs Kies,
but it's Shinhwa!
[Oh my goodness...]
[Thus starts the trials and ordeals
for these men...]
Who is the German philosopher who
advocated the idea of Nihilism?
It's the man who said that
the God was dead.
Hegel.
[Wrong answer]
[Correct answer is, Nietzsche.
Jun Hyun Moo gets it wrong.]
It's not God, who's dead, but it's you.
Come back to your seat.
[Followed by Kwang Gyu's incorrect answer
to Women's Feelings for three points.]
[Kwang Soo inevitably gets the wrong answer
for Fashion for four points.]
[Parade of wrong answers.]
Even if they don't get
any more points...
[Even if they don't get any
more points?]
That's good!
How many points do we have so far?
- 11 points.
- How many of us are left?
- It's all over already.
- Let's forget everything and start over.
[Since it's impossible to win the first round,
they suggest starting over from scratch.]
That was a practice round!
[They're calling that a practice round
because they're at a disadvantage?]
Okay, then here's the new deal. If
you score more than 30 points this time...
then we'll give you three
separate hints.
And if you score more than 20 points,
then we'll give you two separate points.
- That sounds good.
- I like that deal.
[A deal that everyone
seems to be happy about.]
Lastly, we'll give you one hint
if you score more than ten points.
[One hint for every ten points earned.]
Yes, let's do that.
- Gary can go next.
- Gary, then Muzy.
[Random Mr. Capable is up
as the first player up.]
- Which one are you doing, Gary?
- Why don't you go with sports?
- Sports for two points.
- Muzy can do the relationship category.
Here's your sports question.
This is making me nervous.
It's burdensome.
The keyword is... Ball games.
- Okay, ball games.
- You like this stuff.
Here's your ball game question.
What is a French ball game with the name
that translates into, 'Catch it'?
- What?
- Catch it?
- A French game?
- Think of a game where you have to catch.
- What's 'Catch it' in French?
- What game requires you to catch?
This is really hard.
It's a ball game of sorts?
Is it a world famous sport?
You can't keep asking all those
sorts of questions.
I'll give you one hint.
- Ask him the size of the ball.
- It's a ball game of sorts?
Ask him for the size of the ball.
- How big is the ball?
- It's big enough.
- Gary.
- If you take a look at the ball...
The ball isn't all that big.
- You have five seconds. Five, four, three...
- Should I just answer it?
- Just answer it.
- Two, one.
Tennis.
[Gary's answer is, tennis.]
I think he's right.
[Gary answers correctly!]
[How did he know that?]
I just went with my gut feeling.
I really had no idea.
[This is why he's dubbed,
Random Mr. Capable.]
Isn't there like
Wimbledon Tennis Tournament?
Yes, the term 'Tennis' itself
is a name of sorts.
Isn't Wimbledon in France?
[It definitely was a random guess.]
- That was amazing.
- That was awesome.
Hey, how did you know that
it was tennis?
I've always been good at guessing.
[Two points gained right from the start.]
You've earned yourselves two points
thanks to Kang Gary.
This feels like he just earned five points.
- This is no different than earning 5 points.
- You did a great job.
- Muzy, you're up!
- These questions are hard.
[Next player up is, Muzy.]
I had no idea what the answer was.
- I'll go with the relationship category.
- Relationship!
Relationship for two points.
The keyword is, Neologisms.
- Neologisms.
- Wow, that's crazy.
Muzy, Muzy...
If you don't get this right,
then you'll be disgraced.
- Neologisms?
- Here's your question.
What is the neologism used to coin someone
like Kwang Soo who falls in love easily?
That's way too easy.
- That's too easy, Muzy.
- The answer is already obvious.
You can't look behind you.
- Can you say that again?
- Everyone must keep quiet.
What is the neologism used to coin someone
like Kwang Soo who falls in love easily?
- You have to know this.
- You have five seconds.
Neologism...
- Four, three, two, one!
- What could it be?
Hopeful?
[Wrong]
- What is it?
- Geum-Sa-Ppa! (Falls easily)
[Geum-Sa-Ppa:
A person who falls in love easily.]
[Muzy unfortunately fails at
earning the team any points.]
You've only earned yourselves
two points so far.
Jang Ki Ha!
[The return of their hero?]
Go for a five pointer!
Jang Ki Ha, fighting!
Which question would you like?
- A five pointer?
- History!
Go for the history category.
- Go for the SAT category.
- Not economics, I don't know that.
- I'll go with History.
- History!
History for five points.
- This is going to be a tough one.
- I'm nervous for him.
The keyword is... order.
- This is going to be tough.
- Order?
- You can do this one.
- An order of historical events?
This should be my question!
Gap-oh-kyung-jang, 1894!
- Stop saying that.
- Enough with that.
[History? Order? What kind
of a tough question would it be?]
Jeongyujaeran.
I'm ruined.
Dynamic movement.
Hunminjeongeum hangul.
Completion of Suwon.
Four events.
Please put them in chronological order.
- First was Jeongyujaeran.
- Jeongyujaeran.
Next was Dynamic movement.
Completion of Suwon.
- No way is he going to get this.
- I don't know.
This is a Golden Bell level question.
- This is really hard.
- What's the last one?
If Ki Ha answers this right...
- He's thinking right now.
- I think he's going to get this.
- No shame in getting it wrong.
- No, I know Ki Ha can do this.
- Ki Ha can do this.
- He looks so cool from the back.
- I feel so much confidence in him.
- I know that he can do this.
Ki Ha looks really dashing when he's
trying to figure out the quiz questions.
He almost looks sexy.
- What if I get it wrong?
- You'd be so sexy if you get it right.
- I'm going to take a guess.
- He's ready with the answer.
He's about to answer.
Hunminjeongeum hangul is first.
Really?
- He won't be wrong from the start, right?
- Let us know if it's wrong.
He must be right.
Dynamic movement is last.
- Really?
- I wouldn't have known.
What are the other two that are left?
Completion of Suwon.
- I feel like I've heard it before.
- What's 'Jeongyujaeran'?
Jeongyujaeran is second, and
Completion of Suwon is third.
- I think Jeongyujaeran is right.
- I think he's got it right.
Jeongyujaeran is second, and
Completion of Suwon is third.
[Would he have answered this five point
question correctly?]
[Correct]
[Jan Ki Ha gets the correct answer!]
[Jeongyujaeran-
A war during the Joseon era.]
[Everyone is impressed by
Ki Ha's sexy intellectual mind.]
[Tears of envy over something that these
guys can never even hope to have...]
Ki Ha is a genius.
[Ki Ha's impressive intellectual skills.]
[Five additional points!
A total of seven points earned.]
Jang Ki Ha!
Don't do anything else on Running Man today.
Just keep doing the quiz, Ki Ha.
[Answering these quiz questions
is more than plenty for them.]
[Has been dubbed
'The Quiz King of Running Man.']
Can we just keep playing this quiz game
for the next four weeks of our show?
- This is fun.
- This is way too fun.
- I feel like I'm getting so much smarter.
- I really like this game.
Can we make this one of our staple games?
This game is a lot of fun.
This game makes me even more nervous
than the name tag elimination game.
This game really is nerve-wrecking.
- And I feel like I'm learning something.
- Me too.
[Also gaining a sense of camaraderie
from having to work together.]
I'm sorry, but my schedule is too busy.
[Sorry, but no need to invite me
to any more of these quiz games...]
Chung-rok-pa!
[Lee Juck- 4 points, Jun Hyun Moo- 5 points,
and now, Yoo Jae Suk- 4 points.]
[A total of 20 points earned so far.]
- Let's go for 30 points.
- We already have 20 points, right?
- We have 20 points.
- You're doing great. You have 20 points.
We've already got two hints.
- Then let's play the rest with ease.
- No need to be nervous.
- No, we need to get all three hints.
- Take history for four points.
- That's the last of the four point question.
- Ha Ha won't be able to get it.
We need a five point question.
Can you give us two more five pointers?
Okay, this is what I'll do then.
I'll answer your proposal with one of my own.
We'll go with two five point questions.
But if you get it wrong,
you'll be docked one point.
- Ha Ha's not very credible.
- I don't know if he'll get it.
[Must risk the danger for it to be possible
for them to get the 30 points.]
You can choose whichever category you'd like.
- You can do this.
- Nonsense for five points?
- Go for Nonsense for five points.
- Yeah, you can do that.
- Nonsense for five points.
- There you go!
[This is the toughest question Ha Ha
has ever taken on in a quiz game.]
- I'm really nervous right now.
- This is like an SAT level question.
This feels like
the final Golden Bell question.
You'll be docked one point if your get it
wrong like agreed upon.
Nonsense for five points.
Here's your question.
What is the world's simplest number?
[It seems as though
they're reminded of something...]
You can't look behind you.
- Ten, nine, eight...
- This is really easy!
Number, a number...
- Six, five, four, three...
- Think about it.
Two, one...
One!
[Wrong]
[What is the world's simplest number?]
- It's either 19, or 50, isn't it?
- Or is it 20?
- It's 19!
- The correct answer is...
190,000.
(Sound of the number means, 'Very easy'.]
[Correct answer- 19,000.]
[Ah...]
- What did you say your answer was?
- Did you say, one?
I was so flustered, so I said, one.
That nonsense question was really hard.
- That was really hard.
- I'm so mad at myself right now.
The rest of this game all depends on you.
You currently have 19 points.
Depends on whether you lose the point or not.
[Answer it right to earn two hints,
or lose a point to earn only one hint.]
- Should I go with the SAT question?
- No way!
- Stop joking around.
- Relationship for one point.
Just go with people category instead.
- People?
- Okay, people for two points.
- People is a good category to choose.
- I don't even notice the time passing.
- Seriously.
- Let's do a bit of this every week.
[Requests to bring this game back
since it's so fun.]
This question will determine whether
we'll get two hints, or only one hint.
[A very important question that will
determine how many hints they'll get.]
[People for two points.]
- People for two points.
- Yes, please.
The keyword is... The beginning.
- The beginning?
- The beginning.
This should be easy.
What is the name of the astronaut who was
the first man ever to step on the moon
in year 1969 by flying into space
on a spaceship named, Apollo 11?
- Don't let yourself get confused.
- Let's get this!
The first man to step foot on the moon?
- Yes.
- It's not the rabbit, okay?
It's not someone from our country!
[A riot is about to break loose
behind the old man's back.]
- The first man to land on the moon, right?
- That's correct.
You were already born at the time.
- I was already born by then, right?
- You saw the event, didn't you?
- Do you need the full name?
- He knows. that means that he knows.
I think he knows.
[It seems as though everyone else knows.
The correct answer is, Neil Armstrong.]
[Will he get the correct answer?]
Will Armstrong.
[Will?]
[Wrong]
Will Armstrong.
[Who's 'Will Armstrong'?]
[Kim Kwang Gyu answers incorrectly.]
How could you say, Will?
- It's 'Neil'!
- Don't you even know?
- It's 'Neil'?
- Are you kidding me right now?
[To miss such an easy question...]
We were telling you not to get
Neil confused with Louis Armstrong.
- We told you not to get confused.
- If anything, you guys confused me more!
You guys confused me.
You only gained yourselves a single hint
for having answered, Will Armstrong.
[Gained one hint from having
earned 18 points.]
[No more attempts are allowed.]
Thus, you guys have
earned yourselves one hint total.
This was really fun.
Let's do this every week.
I feel like I'm getting smarter.
Mr. Will Armstrong can choose the hint.
Okay, I'll pick.
This is really disappointing, MC Blank.
[Rap hint?]
We will sing you the rank standing
in chronological order.
- You're going to rap it?
- It's going to be rapped.
- I bet I know what they're going to do.
- It's going to be twice the speed.
- Twice the speed?
- Listen very carefully.
You'll only be given one chance,
so you must listen very carefully.
- How many times will you play it for us?
- Just once.
- Where is the speaker?
This is what we spent the past two hours
working ourselves up for?
[Enraged at the hint that
they couldn't even understand.]
[Giving them one more chance to listen from
the level of their unhappiness.]
I couldn't even hear anything.
Let's try and see if we can at least
figure out the first and the last.
[Listen carefully]
[Listening again wasn't much help...]
- Yoo Jae Suk.
- Yoo Jae Suk was first.
[Did they hear something?]
No, it was Lee Juck.
[First place is Yoo Jae Suk, or Lee Juck?]
From what I heard,
first place is Lee Hwi Jae.
[Is he hearing things now?]
- What are you saying?
- And eighth place was Jung Won Gwan.
[Jung Won Gwan in eighth place?]
Okay, we're going to move on
to the next location.
[Time to move on to the next location!]
[Splitting into two cars befitting
of their ranking status?]
- Thank you.
- Goodbye.
People who thinks they're in the upper ranks
can get in the 'Upper rank' car.
- Let Ki Ha ride in the upper rank car.
- Come, Ki Ha.
[Ki Ha gets to ride in the upper rank car
for being the hero of the day?]
Get in the car.
Kwang Gyu doesn't even have to think.
He can go on to the lower rank car.
- Where is Jong Kook going to go?
- How could you have said, Will Armstrong?
[Sad Mr. Will Armstrong.]
[Kwang Soo is being shoved towards
the lower rank car without hesitation.]
- You didn't have to shove me.
- Okay, but just keep walking.
Okay, let's go.
You know that last rapping hint?
I didn't really get to hear the words.
First place is either Jae Suk or Lee Juck.
[The rap hints alludes that first place
is either Jae Suk or Lee Juck?]
- It's either Jae Suk or Lee Juck.
- I really didn't hear anything.
- It was at twice the speed.
- I think I heard Kwang Soo in third place.
Lee Kwang Soo in third place?
Since Lee Juck is known for his heartfelt
songs such as 'It's a relief'...
- You're so right.
- Because he sings all romantic songs...
The type of man whom the women think would
sing those types of songs for them?
Since the question is about which man
the women would like to date?
I can't believe you just talked about
yourself like that.
Come on, think about this.
Jong Kook wasn't one of the kids' drawings.
And the other hint said that I'm one rank
higher up than Jong Kook.
And third and sixth place holders
are already known.
Meaning, 1st and 2nd place, or
4th and 5th place are the only possibilities.
That sounds about right.
1st and 2nd place or 4th and 5th place
are the only possible answers for us.
You're right.
That sounds right.
I think everyone does need some
brain power.
[A brainy character that has never been
one of the mainstays on Running Man.]
We need to make sure to win
this final hint.
First place is Jae Suk, second is Gary,
then Kwang Soo in third place...
Fourth place is Lee Juck,
and Jong Kook is in fifth place.
- Jong Kook in fifth.
- Sixth place is... Ki Ha.
Then seventh, eighth, and ninth would be
me, Hyun Moo...
- The drawing with big eyes is Hyun Moo.
- And he also used to have red hair.
So seventh, eighth, and ninth would be
Hyun Moo, myself, and... who else is there?
[Possible candidates for 7th, 8th, and 9th-
Hyun Moo, Suk Jin and Ha Ha?]
[A shocking turnabout in the ranking position
will soon be revealed.]
[Seoul 'E' Women's university.]
We have arrived at a women's college where
we'll get to find out how popular you are.
[The next mission on campus...]
Even though Gary may be very unattractive,
there's something very enigmatic about him.
- The way he treats Song Ji Hyo is adorable.
- I love you, Gary.
- Jong Kook is so handsome.
- I love you, Ha Ha.
Jang Ki Ha is the best.
[Wow... Gary?]
Here's your final mission.
- This is our last mission.
- We're finished if we don't get this.
Yoo Jae Suk,
you may get out of the car.
- What is the next mission?
- Scoot over a bit.
[Mission aside, Big-nosed Brother is just glad
to have a bigger space to sit in.]
You need to go find the 'R' marked flag.
'R' marked flag?
I've got a soft spot for this place.
[Second runner- Lee Juck.]
Do you have bad memories of
women's universities or something?
I used to be the designated on-campus
singer for this university back in the day.
But that all changed once Sung Si Kyung
came onto the scene.
You need to go find the 'R2' marked flag.
Wow, there are so many people here.
Hello, everyone.
Hello.
I need to go find the 'R1' marked flag.
'R2' marked flag.
Hello.
- You know who I am?
- I know your new song, 'Lies'!
Lies, lies, lies!
[Fervent popularity from
countless number of female students.]
Yes, thank you.
Yes, thank you so much.
I can't believe this.
Smart Jang Ki Ha.
- Go out, and you'll see an 'R1' marked flag.
- An 'R1' marked flag?
Yes, you need to go find the flag.
[Brainy Ki Ha gets on his way!]
Go out the door and find your way
over to 'R2' flag.
- 'R2'?
- Yes.
What is this?
[Find and bring back one female student
within five minutes.]
[Win 5 hints by each of the men bringing back
a student with all different surnames.]
- Each of you will bring back a student.
- Okay.
And if you all bring back someone with
different surnames, then you'll get a hint.
That's just absurd.
So all 11 of us needs to bring back a student
with all different surnames to succeed?
So it's all about chance when we're
all gathered together?
- Anyone with a unique surname?
- What's your surname?
[All 11 of them must find students
with different surnames.]
Excuse me.
I just need one student.
I need help from one of you.
What's your surname?
- It's 'Han'!
- 'Han'?
'Han'?
'Kim'?
We need some unique last names.
- What's your last name?
- It's 'Kim'.
We need to gather a total of 11 students
from this campus.
And all 11 of these students
must have different last names.
- What's your last name?
- Excuse me?
- It's 'Lee'.
- What's your last name?
- 'Park'.
['Kim', 'Lee', 'Park'...
Most are very common surnames...]
[He's about to ask the surnames of
every single student on campus.]
[An endless stream of 'Kim', 'Lee', 'Park'.]
[No one has a clue as to which last name
each other will bring back to the group.]
I just need one person.
- What's your last name?
- It's 'Na'.
'Na'?
[Oh... not a very common surname!]
[Rule- Must be a student of this university.]
[Ah... she's a student
from another university.]
[Rule-
Must be a current student of this school.]
Are there any foreign students here
who have been naturalized?
[What?]
Excuse me, are you a student
of this school?
- What's your last name?
- It's 'Park'.
'Park' isn't going to work.
What's your last name?
- Do you have a student ID?
- Yes.
Can you show it to me?
- Can you make an appearance on Running Man?
- Excuse me?
- Appearance on Running Man?
- Do it!
You can come with me right now.
We don't have much time.
Okay, lets run.
There it is.
I think we're going to be good.
What?
'Hyun'?
That's good. That's a good one.
Do you have a student ID?
Let me see it.
That's great!
Let's go.
- We're good.
- No 'Kim', 'Lee', 'Park' for now.
I think everyone else
is thinking the same thing.
[But... what if no one brings back
any of those common surnames?]
Welcome.
[Jae Suk arrives at the meeting destination.]
- You left after me?
- Hello.
- You found a unique surname, right?
- Of course, I did.
[Will there really be no doubles of
any of the eleven surnames?]
[Worried that they may be disrupting
their busy schedule.]
- Where were you heading to?
- Me?
- I was meeting people for drinks.
- A drinking date.
- You'll have lots to talk about later then.
- You start drinking on Tuesdays?
I was going out drinking because
I failed my interview.
[Ah...]
I'm sorry.
I had no idea when I asked you that.
You were going out for drinks
because you were feeling down?
- But you applied at other places too, right?
- Yes.
[Principles of happiness-
Good things will soon come your way!]
I thought that you were going to
cause some sort of a stampede.
- Everyone was just so welcoming.
- I didn't cause any sort of a stampede.
- I walked around in ease and comfort.
- Really?
Maybe we were walking around
different school campuses.
- I was greeted with such fervent welcome.
- Really?
I was greeted with some welcome,
and everyone parted their way for me.
As if they wanted me to pass by quickly.
All the surnames have to be different.
I have a feeling you two will be different.
[Will all their surnames be different?]
I'm sure they'll be different.
Everyone is either 'Kim' or 'Lee'.
I didn't know there were so many of them.
[What is the surname of this student
that Ki Ha chose?]
I don't have a single friend who has
the same last name as I do.
I wonder if there won't be any
'Lee' or 'Kim' from other members.
[Worrying that others wouldn't have brought
anyone with the common last name.]
I wonder if anything else,
no one would've brought a common last name.
We should've done a better job of figuring out
what the other may have brought.
We should've found a way to communicate
with each other through telepathy.
[It seems as though they all brought girls
with a very unique last name.]
[Will they be able to succeed without
a single doubling of the same surname?]
You'd have to assume that the people who went
out first would've brought an easier name.
[Sixth member, Ki Ha also arrives.]
- Have a seat over here.
- Have a seat.
- What's your major?
- I'm in Video Media Relations.
Everyone has a different major.
That's so unique too.
[Now that there are six gathered here,
time to find out which surnames they've found]
- Can we ask them their surnames?
- Yes.
- Tell us what your name is.
- My name is...
My name is, Joo Jin Young.
- Your last name is Joo?
- Okay!
[All the members brightens up at
the revelation of the first surname.]
Even though she was heading out to have
drinks from having failed an interview...
She's still keeping high hopes
for tomorrow.
She failed her first interview today.
[That's already a part of the past.
But she still has high hopes for tomorrow!]
She says she has another interview
tomorrow.
[What could her surname be?]
My name is, Yoon Seul Bi.
Miss Yoon Seul Bi.
Okay, tell us what your name is.
My name is...
[Next student.]
My name is, Hyun Yoo Rim.
[Everyone's in a great mood!]
Okay, good.
Hyun Yoo Rim.
- Your neighbor in Namyangjoo.
- She lives in the next building.
- Then you guys are neighbors?
- Did you know Kwang Soo was your neighbor?
- Yes.
- What kind of a reputation does he have?
- Just that he's on Running Man.
- That's it?
When Kwang Soo grabbed her shoulder,
she flinched like she was about to get hit.
[Flinching from being afraid that
she was about to get hit?]
Just that he's on Running Man.
[Giraffe's threatening front paws?]
What kind of a reputation do you have
in your neighborhood?
They wanted to know what kind of a reputation
I have in our neighborhood.
You must have a bad reputation
amongst your neighbors.
- What's your last name?
- My name is...
[What is the name of Giraffe's neighbor?]
- Ra Ha Jung.
- Ra Ha Jung!
Ra Ha Jung!
Her last name is, 'Ra'.
'Ra' as in 'Ramyun'!
- That's a good last name. 'Ra' is good.
- Unreal, right?
- And she also lives in your neighborhood.
- Yes.
My student came from Suji.
- Tell us your last name.
- Suji, where Ehwa Woman's University is?
Her last name is very unique.
My name is, Sung Yoo Mi.
- Sung Yoo Mi.
- Ah! Sung Yoo Mi!
[All five of them so far have
different surnames!]
[Still in a good mood...]
- No one has the same surnames.
- Yes, you're right.
Okay, Jun Hyun Moo,
please step out of the car.
Go out this door and find your way
to 'R1' flag.
- 'R1' flag?
- Yes.
Thank you.
'R' what?
Was it 'R1'?
[Kkuk also gets started on his mission.]
[Finally getting to find out what
his new mission is.]
[Find and bring back a student
within the next five minutes.]
[All 11 members must bring back a student
with different surname in order to succeed.]
- You've got five minutes to do your mission.
- Five minutes?
Anyone with the last name, 'Nam'?
Seriously?
Is it really 'Nam'?
This is seriously...
any unique surnames?
Anyone with the surname, 'Sun' or 'Woo'?
How about, 'Jo'?
There has to be one of you here.
- How about, 'Gil'?
- 'Gil'?
'Kang'?
I'm 'Kang' too.
- Your nationality is?
- I'm American.
American?
Sorry.
- I'm Korean.
- What? Korean?
But you're not a girl.
- You're not a girl, right?
- I'm Korean.
- You're Korean? What's your name?
- Jung Ahn Na.
- 'Jung' is too common.
- Me!
Ki Ha's really been stepping up
to the plate today.
- Congratulations.
- You've been doing great.
She works in media broadcasting
department on campus.
- Are you an announcer?
No, I do this.
(camera man)
- Can you tell us your name?
- Which one of these members do you like?
- Yoo Jae Suk.
- That's obvious.
I'm so sick of hearing that.
I cried when you got married.
Why would you cry over such
a happy occasion?
That is just absolutely absurd.
Do you want me to make you really sad?
What's your last name?
[Her name is...]
My name is, Na Hyung Jung.
- 'Na'.
- Oh, 'Na'!
[Not 'Ra', but 'Na'.]
[Was a close call, but all six still maintain
their unique last names.]
All six of them so far
have a different last name.
- We're going to be okay.
- We've got six of them confirmed now.
We'll be okay if someone brings either
'Kim' or 'Lee' now.
- More common names will be okay now.
- There's Suk Jin.
All six of the women we've brought
all have different surnames so far.
[All six of them currently have
different surnames.]
I don't think any of the ladies that are here
will already have this last name.
What is your last name?
Ji Jung Eun.
[An immediate celebration.]
Your name is Ji Jung Eun?
Is it the same 'Ji'?
Yes, it's the same 'Ji'.
I had a feeling that there wouldn't
be any other 'Ji'.
If anything else, I feel like we're not
going to have any 'Kim' or 'Lee'.
[No 'Kim', 'Lee', 'Park', 'Choi' so far.]
- We don't have any 'Choi' either.
- We just won ourselves a hint.
[Seven successful surnames means that
they've earned themselves a hint.]
- I can hear Jong Kook's voice.
- Kim Jong Kook is coming.
- You can't tell them yet, okay?
- He's coaching the woman already?
There he goes commanding someone again.
Is it a unique surname, or a common one?
None of these seven women have
the same last names so far.
- Really?
- Really.
- They all have different surnames.
- What is your last name?
- Can I say my name?
- Is it okay to say it?
- Yes, you can say it now.
- It starts with a 'K'.
That's good!
We should be okay!
Is it, 'Kwak'?
- What is it?
- Tell them.
It's, 'Kham'.
[Oh... 'Kham'!]
[All eight of them have succeeded so far.]
We don't have any 'Kim', 'Lee', or
'Park' so far.
I was thinking that everyone would've
went for the unique
and if anything else,
common last names would be missing.
That's what I thought you'd do.
You're so disappointing.
Why would you feel disappointed when
I've brought the surname, 'Kham'?
- That's the most unique name so far.
- Kwang Gyu's here.
Did you bring your daughter or something?
[A sweet father and daughter duo
entering the room?]
Is your daughter graduating?
[What could be the last name of the student
whom Kwang Gyu brought back?]
All the students here so far
has different last names.
- They're different?
- Yes.
[Looking pretty confident.]
Is it a very common last name,
or is it a very unique last name?
- It's a common last name.
- No, that's okay!
- We're okay as long as it's not 'Yoon'.
- What is your last name?
[What is the common last name that this
student supposedly has?]
- Yang Hee Kyung.
- 'Yang'!
[Succeeds again!]
[All nine of them currently have
a different last name!]
Yang Hee Kyung!
Wow, this is amazing.
- How is this even possible?
- What are you majoring in?
- Architecture.
- Architecture!
- Architecture major!
- They're all different.
[Even all their majors are different!]
[All of the male contestants seem to
be in perfect sync with one another.]
[Time to switch out the tape-
A brief time for some rest.]
- Are we taking a break?
- Yes, we're taking a brief break.
You're going to put makeup on?
Why are you putting makeup on?
- I didn't realize I'd be on TV.
- Your skin looks great right now!
- Just put something on your lips.
- No, I need some makeup on my face.
- Okay, then put it on.
- Put it on and we'll do a visual comparison.
What does your father do?
Your father's an architect?
Ah, I see.
Your skin is starting to look brighter.
- Now that she has it on her face...
- How is it? Is it better?
She needs to put the eyeliner on too.
Just hang on a minute.
[Needs a little bit more time.]
Her eyes have gotten bigger!
[A woman's transformation that still
fascinates men every time.]
She would like to know if
you could lend her your eyeliner.
- She's all done.
- Wow, Jung Eun.
Her lip color is different too.
Why are you all staring at her like that?
Why are you all staring at her?
Let me see.
You look very pretty.
- You should show them.
- You did a good job.
[I should check too.]
Our 'Ji' family line.
Doesn't she look different?
Doesn't she look nice?
She looks more fierce.
- I didn't put any B.B cream on.
- You don't have what on?
- B.B.
- So I don't have as good of a coverage.
You did good.
- We're missing Gary and Hyun Moo?
- Yes, Gary and Hyun Moo are still left.
Anyone with a unique surname?
- 'Park'!
- You've got one minute left.
Anyone with a unique last name?
[There's not much time left on the clock.]
[Hyun Moo finally seems to have
found something?]
Here it is!
I've found it!
Come on.
We need to hurry!
[Gary seems to have found one too?]
[What are the surnames that these two will
break through the crowd to bring back?]
Hyun Moo's here!
[Gary arrives soon after Hyun Moo.]
- Please.
- Gary.
Is it a common last name,
or a unique last name?
[Totally curious.]
- That could be more dangerous.
- Very uncommon name in our country.
I don't think I've heard her surname
in the past six years or so.
- Seriously?
- Yes.
I personally don't know a single person
with the same surname that she has.
- Really?
- Me neither.
All nine of the ladies so far
have different last names.
They're all different.
First of all, we'd like to thank all our
students for participating in our game.
[Thank you for taking the time out of your
precious schedule to help us out!]
Everyone prior to Jun Hyun Moo currently
all have different surnames.
[Everyone has a different surname.]
[Even their majors are all different!]
- It's time to check the last two.
- These final two ladies...
[Time to check the last two surnames.]
If the last two ladies are different and
all 11 of the ladies have a different surname
then we win a total of five hints.
[A total of five hints if the final two
women have a different last names!]
We're all in such total sync.
- Why don't we start with Gary?
- Why me?
[Starting with Gary's student.]
Her surname is two hyphenated names.
[Predicting a success?]
- Please tell us your name.
- I'm a third year student...
I'm a math major,
and my name is, Jae-Gal Da Eun.
My name is, Jae-Gal Da Eun.
[Easily succeeds.]
That's so unique.
[Confirms with her student ID.]
That is such a unique last name.
Okay, time to revel the final surname.
[One final person left remaining.]
Since Da Eun was a success too,
then do we currently have four hints?
We'll have five hints as long as
the last student's name is different too?
[If Hyun Moo's student also has a different
surname, then they win a total of five hints!]
Her surname starts with an 'O'.
- 'O'?
- What could it be?
We already have a 'Yoon' and a 'Yang'.
- 'Eom'? Or 'Wong'?
- There are plenty of other possibilities.
Her name is Eun Kyung.
Everyone...
[What could her surname be?]
Yook Eun Kyung!
[Mission is a success!]
We'd like to thank all of you once again
for your participation.
- Thank you.
My name is Yook Eun Kyung,
and I'm a Western Art Painting Major.
[Everyone succeeded in bringing back
students with different surnames!]
Why don't you explain to these students
what kind of a race we're doing today?
We have to earn hints by succeeding
various different missions.
A question was asked of women from
their teens to their fifties.
- If they were to date someone...
- After being reborn.
Which one of us would you want to date
if you were to be born again?
- In order of the rank.
- And we have to guess the order of rank.
We'd like to ask all of you here.
[Since they're here already,
how about asking them the same question?]
Just tell us the person you'd most
and least want to date.
This is making me nervous.
No need to worry about naming people because
we're all very cool about things like this.
- It's okay, you won't offend us.
- Everyone has their own preference.
- Is his name, Kim Kwang Goo?
- No, it's Kim Kwang Gyu.
[His name...]
What does your father do?
- What does your father do?
- Calm down.
She could've meant that you're
in first place with her.
We'll just go down the line,
and quickly name people
and we'll all say our goodbyes
after a big round of applause.
Since we don't know what's about to happen,
let's all take a quick picture first.
[Time for some pictures first?]
Okay, take your pictures.
All the women stay seated where you are,
and the men will go around to different seats.
[A new picture taking method?]
We'll just go around clockwise, okay?
[A revolving photo booth.]
And if you don't want a picture of
the person standing behind you
then just shout out, 'Pass'.
[Shout out, 'Pass', if they don't like
whomever is behind them.]
Okay, here we go.
[Time to take some pictures!]
Okay, next!
[Move on to the right
after a picture is taken.]
Keep on moving!
We don't have much time!
Stick your face forward, and stop winking!
[Being overtly cute is prohibited.]
Why are you doing this?
[Rotating pictures are now complete.]
How about a group photo now?
[A full service.]
Everyone gather closer!
Okay, one more picture.
[Still acting overtly cute.]
Everyone, smile!
[11 female students and
popularity contestants.]
[Time to answer the question of
who they would like to be reborn to date.]
Get your bags ready and get ready to go
after you answer the question.
Don't forget your drinks either.
Thank you everyone once again for your
help and be careful on your way out.
This show will be broadcasted
in two weeks.
[Even kindly letting them know
of the broadcasting schedule.]
Okay, we're going to start now.
The person you'd want to date the most
if you were to be born again.
- Yoo Jae Suk.
- Person in last place.
Person I'd least want to date, Jun Hyun Moo.
Jun Hyun Moo.
[Answers the question...
and coolly leaves the room.]
[Bye!]
[She really left without even
a single glance backward.]
You can't glance back.
- You can't glance back.
- Just keep going.
[Next student.]
- First place.
- Yoo Jae Suk.
- Last place.
- Muzy.
[One vote for Muzy.]
Stop her!
- First place.
- Lee Juck.
- Last place.
- Kim Kwang Gyu.
What does your father do!
[Grief of coming in at last place.]
Go wait for me outside!
[Not a single one of them has
glanced back.]
I love how cool they are.
- First place.
- Lee Kwang Soo.
- Last place.
- Jun Hyun Moo.
[Two votes for Jun Hyun Moo.]
I'll see you back home!
Okay, here we go!
- First place.
- Yoo Jae Suk.
- Last place.
- Kim Kwang Gyu.
[Two votes for Kim Kwang Gyu.]
- Person you'd want to date the most.
- Yoo Jae Suk.
- Last place.
- Kim Kwang Gyu.
[Three votes for Kim Kwang Gyu.]
[A bloody battle for the last place.]
- First place?
- Yoo Jae Suk.
Last place?
[Who will she pick for the last place?]
Kim Kwang Gyu.
[Happy?]
Look at how happy Hyun Moo is.
[Battle for the last place-
Kim Kwang Gyu- 4 vs Jung Hyun Moo- 2.]
- First place?
- Gary.
- Last place?
- Jun Hyun Moo.
Jun Hyun Moo.
[A fight for the last place.]
[Kim Kwang Gyu- 4 vs Jung Hyun Moo- 3.
Only one vote difference.]
- First place?
- Jang Ki Ha.
Last place?
[Last place...]
Jun Hyun Moo.
[The student staying loyal to her 'father'.]
[4:4- a tie.]
[A fierce battle comparable to that of
a World Cup game.]
[Please...]
[Current score is, 4:4.
Only two people left.]
- You've made up your mind, right?
- No one's even interested in first place.
- First place.
- Ha Ha.
Last place?
[Who will she pick to be in the last place?]
Jun Hyun Moo.
[A reversal!]
[Already in celebration mode.]
[All worked up.]
I was the one who brought you here!
[Having been given the last place vote
by the student he brought himself.]
I brought you here!
Miss Yook!
[Miss Yook, staying true to her feelings.]
- I brought you here.
- He's the one who brought her here.
I was the one who brought her here,
and I liked her too!
How she must've hated being
dragged here by him.
- This is so funny.
- Okay, step up to the front.
[Kwang Gyu- 4 vs. Hyun Moo-5.
One final vote left.]
The person that just walked out of here
is the student that Hyun Moo brought.
[Voted by the student that he,
himself brought.]
She must've come here to see me.
This vote will determine whether you'll tie
or solidify Hyun Moo's status.
[Will they be in last place together,
or will Hyun Moo stand alone?]
- First place?
- Gary.
It's because Gary brought her.
Last place?
[Who will come in at last place?]
Jun Hyun Moo.
[His status is solidified.]
This place is on fire right now!
[Same atmosphere as when
Team Korea won the World Cup.]
Thanks to all the students and everyone else
who came out to see us, and joined us today!
Today's last place winner that you
helped choose yourselves.
Jun Hyun Moo!
[Jun Hyun Moo- Last place holder that
the 11 students chose themselves.]
This is the first time I've ever been made
to tear up while doing a variety show.
Since all 11 of those students were
brought here by different members
and the mission was a success,
you've won a total of five hints.
[Gained five hints from having
succeeded the mission.]
Hyun Moo can pick all five hints.
Hyun Moo was given five votes.
Since he's lost so much today.
- Intermediate hint 7.
- That's not bad.
[Hyun Moo appears to be more
down than usual?]
Why don't you do it while doing
a SHINee dance?
- Have some fun.
- You're all so cruel.
You could be making the viewers think
that you're really upset or something.
I am upset.
[The music is already playing...]
[Immediately starts to dance!]
You have to shout it out.
[Premiere hint 4.]
[His special dance to chase
all the sadness away.]
[It's back!
The flashy footsteps!]
[And finishes it off with a cute pose.]
Isn't it so much easier to take
the pictures like that?
- That was hilarious, Jae Suk.
- That was much easier on those students.
I think we're going to know our answers
for sure once we see the other hints.
But seeing those 11 female students earlier,
I can see how I came in at last place.
- You shouldn't let that bother you.
- That was just a joke.
I knew that I may come in at last place
and I just accepted the fact.
[Hyun Moo having sacrificed himself
for the sake of his teammates.]
- I predict I'll come in at last place.
- Me too.
What are you saying?
That you agree with him?
Then I think I'll come in at 9th place.
- I'm most curious about the last place.
- Me too.
- After what just happened to Hyun Moo.
- I couldn't believe that happened.
- After what just happened...
- I wonder if Hyun Moo's really sad?
[Seoul Mok-Dong.
SBS Broadcasting Station.]
[Only the moment of the final decision is left.]
- It's the water drop?
- What?
- It's the water dump!
- The water.
[Eleven water bombs.]
Two low hints, one intermediate hint,
and two top hints.
The top five ranking positions.
There are a lot of singers in those ranks.
How about all the singers raise their hands?
I think the two of us will be up there.
- Not you.
- I don't think it'll be you.
So if there are three singers of the five,
then it's the correct count.
Then Gary has to be in second place.
[Gary seems to be in second place?]
[There are two guest members amongst
the first five ranking positions.]
[Two guest members
in the five upper ranking positions.]
- I'm in fourth place.
- What about after that?
Then Ki Ha must be in third place.
[Ki Ha in third place?]
[Possible third place contestant is feeling
saddened by this new development?]
He thought that he was
going to be in third place.
It's possible that I'm not in first place.
[People in 2nd, 4th, 9th, and 10th
are known by their stage names.]
Then this just confirmed that
Muzy is in 10th place.
[Muzy's in 10th place?]
- Second place is Gary.
- Lee Juck is in fourth place?
Lee Juck is in fourth place.
Then Jong Kook must be in fifth place.
- Then 9th place must be...
- It's me, Ha Ha.
- Then Muzy really is in 10th place.
- That's right.
You're in 9th place?
- Third place is Jang Ki Ha.
- Yes, that must be Ki Ha.
It could be Jun Hyun Moo.
Let's see the top level hint.
[Time to reveal the top hint.]
[Ha Ha, Jang Ki Ha, Ji Suk Jin, Jun Hyun Moo,
and Kim Jong Kook are in odd numbered spot.]
[Ha Ha's spot in 9th position is solidified?]
[Ki Ha's position in 3rd spot also
seems to be solidified.]
- Then am I in 11th place?
- No, you're in 7th.
- Write your name down in there for now.
- Why am I so high up in rank?
Ji Suk Jin and Jun Hyun Moo could both
be in either the 7th or the 11th position.
[Confusing 7th and 11th spot.]
Erase your name out of there.
Erase it for now since
we're not sure of it right now.
[Kwang Gyu's position in
8th position is solidified.]
I lost out to Kwang Gyu?
[An unforeseen circumstance.]
Hyun Moo and I are both candidates for
both 7th and 11th position.
I could be in 1st place.
Why are you all reacting like that?
I think this is my spot,
and Hyun Moo's in the last position.
[Key to winning this race is to figure out
which spot Hyun Moo and Suk Jin are in.]
[The fate rides on their one single decision.]
We just need to figure out
Hyun Moo and Suk Jin's positions.
- I don't know what to do.
- If Hyun Moo is put in the last spot...
If you're in last spot and we get drenched,
then it's a good thing for you.
- You should be happy about that happening.
- I don't know which is better.
- I think it's a toss-up.
- Best I'll be is 7th place.
You're complaining?
That's a huge difference from my spot.
- Look at the place that I'm in.
- Okay, Hyun Moo is going to move down.
[Then everyone is agreeing that Hyun Moo
should move down to last place?]
You're sacrificing yourself for the team.
You're being very gracious right now.
This is you being gracious.
I don't know if we're going to get
the water dumped on us or not...
- Our teamwork was amazing.
- Our teamwork was great, and it was a blast.
[Results aside, their teamwork today
was something to be very proud of.]
[Time to head up to the final judging stage.]
[Would they have gotten
the correct answer?]
[Their nervousness is compounded tenfold
once they're on the stage.]
It's time to make your final decisions.
Is this your final decision?
[7th and 11th place that
the team isn't too sure of.]
What are you going to do?
Are you sure that Suk Jin is in 11th place?
If we hadn't done that impromptu voting
at the school earlier...
- If we hadn't done that earlier...
- Then it would've been different.
I think the impromptu voting we did earlier
gave us a very useful insight to this answer.
I'm the least popular with single,
unwed women in their twenties.
I'm the least popular with them.
I'm serious.
Older women really love me.
[Big-nosed Brother keeping his faith
in the middle aged women?]
I think we've got the right order though.
Listen, no matter what the answer,
I do feel pretty pathetic right now.
I can't believe I got pushed down
to the very last spot.
[For the sake of the team's victory...]
No matter what, this still means that we're the
top 11 most popular men in all of Korea.
[That's Ha Ha's way of comforting Hyun Moo.]
[With an emphasis on his own image.]
I think Hyun Moo should be
moved over to 7th place.
[Hyun Moo and Suk Jin to ultimately
switch out their spots?]
No, this isn't right!
[Hyun Moo's rival vehemently
opposing this switch?]
We're going to get started now.
Five, four, three, two...
Make your final decision!
- The lights have been turned on.
- We've had great teamwork today.
[Since they've had such great teamwork
all day today...]
Final decision!
[This is their final decision.]
We will start with the first place.
First place.
[If the light on the number turns blue,
then it's the correct answer.]
[First place prediction- Yoo Jae Suk.]
[Correct]
Onto second place.
Second place.
[Second place prediction- Gary.]
[Correct]
Third place.
[Giraffe is still upset about
having lost his spot in third place?]
It's not you!
Why are you getting mad over that?
[Third place prediction- Jang Ki Ha.]
[Correct]
[Disappointed?]
We will now reveal the fourth place.
[Fourth place prediction- Lee Juck.]
[Correct]
Then I must be in the correct spot.
I'm in the right spot.
- Fifth place.
- He's in the right spot.
[Fifth place is also correct.]
Sixth place.
[Sixth place is also correct.]
[It's now time for the fateful
seventh place.]
Since we don't know the seventh place yet,
we'll first move on to the eighth place.
[MC Blank is doing a great job.]
I'm really nervous about this too.
Kim Kwang Gyu in eighth place.
[Correct answer]
Ninth place.
That is also correct.
[Tenth place is also correct.]
[Now it's down to 7th and 11th place.]
[Will their answer be correct?]
[They can't stop chattering from
their nervous energy.]
Keep it down!
[MC Blank explodes
from their chaotic chatter.]
- You know what this feels like too!
- I know, but keep it down some.
How old are you?
Anyway... MC Blank.
Let's just keep going
even if we don't get this.
[Their motto for the day?]
I will now announce the
7th and 11th place.
[Time...]
[To reveal the final results.]
Show us the results!
[This will determine whether they'll
come out victors or losers.]
[Just what will the results reveal?]
[Did they guess correctly?]
Please show us the results!
[Jun Hyun Moo is 7th place?]
[With Ji Suk Jin in 11th place?]
[Correct]
[Succeeds in guessing the correct answer!]
I'm not happy!
[Automatically breaking out in applause.]
It was fantastic team play today.
[Fantastic teamwork that they won't
soon be able to forget.]
Let's all stay cool and say goodbye.
As we mentioned earlier, we thank everyone
who participated in our show today.
[Thank you to everyone
for their participation.]
What are you still doing here
instead of going home?
Subtitles by DramaFever
I want to get out of here!
Gary, no!
[A mysterious kidnapping...]
[A keyword to help identify
the kidnapper...]
[The kidnapper is amongst us.]
[Mysterious people that may be involved
with Gary's kidnapping.]
Why did he get kidnapped?
Where is he?
[Running Man members are on the run
to find Gary's whereabouts!]
[Next week's Running Man-
A Christmas Nightmare.]