Running Man
[Winter 2013]
They're not going to ask us
to cross the Han River, are they?
- How can they expect us to do that?
- Do we have to do something at Han River?
[A mission that no one
could have even fathomed.]
[The game that went down
in Running Man history...]
[It'll happen once again on the Han River.]
[Fast flowing water currents...
and the time that flows just as fast...]
[Having kept up the breathless pace
for the past three and a half years.]
[This time, they're taking on
the Han River challenge.]
[The battle...]
[of Running Man against the Han River...]
[What result will come of it?]
[Earlier this morning.]
[Huh?]
Let's protest!
[Cast of Running Man on strike?]
We're going to have some words today.
Please. No more bungee jumps.
Let's stop those.
No more water games!
I refuse to play them anymore!
[A variety of different conditions.]
This is a negotiation table.
[A negotiation table that's been prepared
for their end of the year meeting.]
We need to have them take all these into
consideration for the year 2014.
- We need to change up the games.
- Yes, you're right.
- I think we've done enough.
- I change my underwear 3 times in the summer.
Do you know how much laundry
I have to do at home?
No matter how many times I wash my clothes,
I still find dirt on them.
Even my stylist isn't happy with this.
We've played a total of 24 water games
during this past year.
That's too much.
24 water games?
That's unbelievable.
A total of five acupuncture mat games.
Remember when Seung Gi came onto
our show in the middle of the winter?
Remember that water spray game
we had to play at the carwash?
[Seung Gi was given an ice cold
shower in the middle of the winter.]
Remember when Shin Yang was on?
[Even the gentlest Park Shin Yang blew up
during the ice cold water game.]
[The muddy rice paddy mission that even
the fashionista, GD, couldn't escape.]
- And the bungee jumps are getting too crazy.
- Yes, it is.
Ji Hyo actually had to fly through the sky.
Even though I never said anything,
but back when Big Bang came on the show...
I can tell you now that our own team members
really stunk like frogs during the missions.
They all smelled like the mucky water,
and smelled like frogs too.
How can us humans be made to smell
like the amphibians?
I'm starting to grow weeds
under my armpits.
- Why did you have to say that?
- I'm serious, they're growing under there!
Gary's not saying anything wrong.
But just because you feel that way,
we can't totally stop playing water games.
- I know that we can't completely stop...
- But we're asking to use more discretion.
Let's only play those games
until the fall starts.
Here's our point.
We understand that we could fall into
the water while playing some of the games.
We have no problems with playing games that
may have us fall into the water at times.
But we're asking to abstain from going into
the water specifically to play these games.
Wow, you're being so agreeable.
Okay, this meeting was organized to take in
your suggestions and comments
into consideration as part of
our 2013 year end closing.
- Have you made all your points?
- That was the jist of it.
Then I'd like to make a proposal.
How about we play a game today...
to determine how we're going to close out
this 2013 year end meeting?
One determining game?
That's why today's mission has been titled,
Running Man vs The Writers Year End Race.
[Today's mission- War against the writers!
Running Man vs The Writers Year End Race.]
What's the race?
So you're saying that our conditions will be
met if we win against the writers?
I can't even imagine what kind of
a tough game you have prepared for this.
- Let's play the name tag elimination game!
- Sounds good to me!
- That sounds good to me!
- Let's take this to the acupuncture mat!
- How about the water?
- Let's go to the rice paddy!
Let's play the name tag elimination game
on top of the acupuncture mat!
How about the cat and mouse game
with the bells?
What we have prepared is a group mission.
[Must pass the group mission that the writers
have come up with...]
[To win the running ball depending on
the end results of the group mission.]
So the better you do at these missions,
the more running balls you can collect.
The running balls you'll win will come to play
an extremely vital role at the final mission.
Your most hated water related punishment
awaits if you fail at your final mission.
However, since this is a race
against the writers...
depending on who wins or loses
today's race...
seven members of the writing staff
can also be punished equally.
- Seriously?
- You're actually being agreeable for once.
- We have to win no matter what.
- Can we choose the staff members?
- Can we pick?
- We want to be able to pick the members.
Who would you like to pick?
- I'd first like to choose PD Jo Hyo Jin.
- I'd like to choose PD Myuk.
- I want Joo Hyung.
- I want Hyung Taek.
- We need Min Soo too.
- Yes, Min Soo.
- How about Ji Min?
- Min Soo really embarrassed me yesterday.
If we play this right, and do a good job,
we can see the writers get crushed.
- Let's do this.
- We've never done anything like this before.
- Let's show them what it's like.
- Writers' first time getting soaked.
We've even prepared our own
team uniform.
[Even the writers are outfitted with
their own team uniform.]
Let's play the name tag elimination.
I bet we can eliminate all your name tags
within the first five minutes.
I'm confident I can do it
even while blindfolded.
- Then do you accept the proposal?
- Yes, of course.
[Running Man vs The Writers-
The battle is on!]
[Then off to the first mission location!]
- Let's do this!
- Let's really win this thing today.
I'm going to bet everything I have.
I'm going to bet my whole life's fortune.
Everyone must forget about
playing as an individual.
[Starting the mental coaching of the members
just like he has done every other day.]
[A never before seen cheer for victory.]
[Running Man vs The Writers-
Start!]
They're not going to make us play any
water games on a day like today, are they?
[There is something special
we've got prepared...]
- Let's win!
- We can win as a team!
- Today is the day.
- You're right. Today is the day.
It's really comforting to know that there
won't be any betrayals going on today.
He could still betray us in an effort
to look good in front of the writers.
Kwang Soo could make some sort
of a deal with them or something.
[They can't let down their guards
when it comes to the Giraffe.]
I noticed that Suk Jin didn't come across
too strong with the writers earlier.
[Suk Jin seemed too tame with the writers?]
I'm going to keep my eye on you.
This is our last show of the year.
Let's make it a good one for us.
[Everyone to work well together,
and have a nice day together?]
- That's what I'd like too.
- The emergency underwear we all brought...
- Let's all wear them at home tomorrow.
- Let's do that!
- Yes, lets wear them tomorrow!
- Nice and dry!
Let's stay nice and dry!
Let's stay nice and dry today.
[Big-nose lyrical machine that's activated
whenever a keyword is given.]
Let's stay nice and dry today.
Let's not get wet,
and stay nice and dry today.
- Let's win!
- Yes, let's beat them!
What is this?
- What is it?
- What is this?
Is this what I think it is?
[Jenga?]
[A gigantic Jenga.]
- It's a Jenga.
- It's a giant sized Jenga.
- What is this?
- It really is Jenga.
- You all know that it won't be easy today?
- Of course. We're prepared.
This is the 2013 Running Man Year End Game,
The Human Jenga.
One person will have to climb up to the top.
[One person to climb up
to the top of the Jenga tower.]
The remaining six of you will pull out
the Jenga pieces from the set.
If you can all pull out the pieces without
crumbling it, then you succeed the mission.
There are a total of 15 running balls
that are riding on this mission.
Wow, that's a lot of balls at stake.
The remaining six members have to pull out
four pieces each in order to succeed.
[Running Man vs The Writers-
A total of three rounds of group missions.]
[The writers will gain a total of ten balls
with each game that they play.]
Yes, since we've created these games,
we'll gain ten balls per game outright.
Don't you think that's being too cocky?
So if you succeed each round,
then you'll win a total of 45 balls.
[Succeed all three rounds,
and win up to a total of 45 running balls.]
This isn't going to be easy.
- If this Jinga crumbles...
- It's 'Jenga'.
It's 'Jenga', not 'Jinga'.
[Already worrying about it crumbling...]
We've prepared a wire, so
there's no need to worry about falling.
However, the remaining six members on
the ground will have to hurry out of the way.
Yes, we understand.
Is that why you gave us
these heavily padded coats today?
- That's going overboard.
- They really are reaching for it today.
[They haven't even started the race,
and the atmosphere is already frightening.]
[Then you're not going to
get out of the way?]
We'll show you what
water punishments feels like.
You each have to pull out four pieces,
totaling in 24 pieces.
- 24 pieces is a lot.
- There are a total of 60 Jenga pieces.
That's not even half the Jenga set.
- Have you tried this?
- Yes, we've tried it all.
- How many pieces did you pull out?
- We pulled out a lot.
- Decide which one of you will go up.
- Ji Hyo. Ji Hyo will go up.
[Everyone shouts out
Ji Hyo's name in unison.]
It's because I'm light, right?
Not because you're scared?
Come on, Ji Hyo.
Why would we be scared of that height?
- Then why don't you go up, Jae Suk?
- I would, but I have to pull out the pieces.
- Ha Ha should go up there instead.
- They're not pulling her up by the string?
Is it high up there?
- That looks safer than I expected.
- It's high.
- That looks pretty safe though.
- No, it's really high up here.
[A gigantic sized Jenga tower that
reaches a total height of 7m.]
No matter what we say,
she's the bravest one of us all.
- Isn't that shaky?
- I can see it shaking.
- She's seriously like a superwoman.
- This is a lot shakier than I had thought.
- Really?
- How can you say that so casually?
[Light Ji Hyo is now perched
on top of the Jenga tower.]
Let's pull out the highest piece
that we can first.
- Okay.
- Let's move quickly.
- Okay, let's start.
- Nice and dry!
[Singing the Dry Song to cheer themselves on.]
I think Kwang Soo needs to boost us up.
[Human Jenga- Mission Start]
[Planning on pulling out the highest piece
they can by utilizing the Giraffe's height.]
- You're our human ladder.
- Step onto his shoulders.
It's nice to have the Giraffe on our team.
Grab my ankles.
Should I pull this one out?
[The first piece is the most crucial piece.]
- Can you pull out the one next to it?
- Anything higher?
Just pull it!
Just pull it out!
- Okay, I'll pull this one out.
- Pull it!
[The Jenga pieces are too large
to pull out in just one attempt.]
[To the other side?]
[Human ladder, Giraffe,
screaming out in pain.]
You can just pull it out now.
- What role am I playing today?
- You're our step-ladder.
What are we going to do about
Kwang Soo later?
[They're still working on their first piece-
Coming around to the back of the set...]
Climb back up onto his shoulders.
Be careful!
[Blank Ji is flattening her body down
to keep the tower as steady as possible.]
- Get the one down there.
- You really look like a monkey with that on.
[Fly, little monkey!]
Okay, I got it.
- Okay, I got it.
- You can't knock it down.
- Can I stand now?
- Stand up. One, two, three.
We have to support Kwang Soo.
- We're going to keep nice and dry today.
- Let's win this thing today.
- Hurry!
- Let's go around.
- You can't get it in one try?
- No, we can't. Sit down, Gary.
Can we get a stick or something?
- Can't we get some sort of a tool?
- This is too much.
[Having to go back and forth every time
they have to pull out a block.]
We can't topple the Jenga tower over.
We should be more worried about
toppling one of us over.
[Jenga has all of a sudden become
more important than a human being.]
Even if you end up getting up,
we can't hurt this Jenga tower.
- We should be more worried about the people.
- We can't have Kwang Soo getting hurt.
[Slowly moving over to the other side.]
Make sure to fall backwards
if you feel like you're going to fall.
We got a lot of it out.
- Okay, pull it out.
- There you go.
Okay!
[Managed to successfully pull
two of them out.]
I feel like there's so much love
between us right now.
Let's use this at least.
It's too hard doing this without anything.
- Let's push it all the way out with this.
- Come on, let us use this at least.
[Coolly allows the use of the stick.]
I think Dong Hoon can do this one.
You can do this one, right?
[Kkuk is transformed into a nagging teacher
as soon as he gets the stick in his hand.]
- Dong Hoon can do this one.
- Are you the site manager or something?
- I'm just trying to set a plan for us.
- Seriously.
Why are you all listening to him
so intently?
- Come on, seriously.
- Do you want to get beat?
- I don't think I should have to do this.
- Yes, you need to do this.
[The Giraffe is continuing to play his role
of being the human ladder.]
You've really gained a lot of weight.
[The Running Man members are given special
permission to use the stick as their tool.]
- Hang on, wait a second.
- Dong Hoon's gotten really heavy.
[Much easier now with their tool.]
[Three down!]
[Working much faster
with the use of their stick.]
[Combination of the Giraffe's neck and
the stick has given wings to their speed.]
We got it!
[Really?]
[Hm...]
- You think I'd be okay with a lower one?
- Let's get this done!
A couple of you need to stand on either side
of Kwang Soo and help support him.
[Manager Kkuk tries to pull out a piece
high up in the tower.]
- Which one of you is pulling down my pants?
- I'm just grabbing you by the waist.
- What's the point of grabbing my pants?
- You don't like it?
- Why are you holding onto my pants?
- I'm not so sure about this one.
You're about to pull the one out at the edge.
Be careful how you pull it out.
- No, Jong Kook. You can't do that one.
- You're knocking it off the center.
- Don't touch it anymore.
- No, Jong Kook.
- It's twisted sideways.
- You're making it crooked.
- Hang on a minute.
- Is it okay now?
Hit it in the middle.
[Isn't budging no matter how hard
he tries to push it out.]
- Lift him up higher.
- It's shaking.
[The tower is starting to
lose its center of balance.]
We're just going to give up!
Just prepare a water game for next week.
Jong Kook! Would it be easier
to pull it from the other side?
- Go around where?
- The edge is already sticking out.
- Where do you think we're going?
- It's already sticking out.
- Just endure it a little bit longer.
- Just hold on a little bit longer.
Okay, I'm going to try going
to the other side.
When I reach for a higher piece,
none of you can help support my back, right?
So without that support on my back,
I can't put any strength into my pushing.
You can just go up and do it that way.
There's no need for you to explain it to us.
- I'm trying to tell you that...
- Just go up there and do a good job!
Can't you see how we're all suffering
down here because of you?
[Crying out a protest for
the human stepladder?]
Just go up there and get your job done!
- Stop lecturing us, and just do it!
- What is going on here right now?
Okay, let me just go up there for now.
- Find your balance.
- Support him on either side.
Grab his feet, and support Kwang Soo.
- Okay, we just have to succeed now.
- Pull it out.
- Down push, or shove it.
- Stop talking and just do it!
- Grab my ankles!
- I'm about to start crying here.
- Just pull it out.
- I don't think it's lose enough to pull out.
- I think we need to go back around.
- No.
Stop talking so much back there,
and come over here and help us!
- We have to go back around.
- Someone hand me the stick.
- Jae Suk is the only one on that side.
- Hurry up and hand me the stick.
Can't we go for a different piece?
Why is he doing?
What is he doing up there now?
What are you doing?
What's this falling on my head?
[Something is falling down on their heads...]
What are you doing?
- Merry Christmas!
- Happy New Year!
- What is this?
- What's he doing?
What is he doing up there?
I almost got it.
- I think I got it.
- There's a heavy snowfall warning.
The snow is starting to gather
on the ground.
Don't make me laugh.
Stop making me laugh!
Jong Kook... I'm about to freeze to death
from all that snow down here.
I feel like I'm going to freeze to death.
It's a winter storm.
Escape and find shelter.
[A project with no end in sight?]
[The human ladder is nearing the end
of his strength level.]
My shoulders are about to break!
I can't do this anymore!
[Manager Kkuk continues to shower down the
snow without any intention of stepping down.]
Are you carving a sculpture up there?
- Half of it is out.
- I'm about to break.
Jong Kook struggling that much means that
it's really starting to get hard.
[The tower top is twisting around!]
[Extreme state of nervousness.]
I think you've got it.
[Careful... will he be able to pull it out?]
Just pull it out!
[Please...]
[At last!]
[After all that work,
succeeds in freeing their 8th block!]
[Just the fact that they're still breathing
is agonizing enough for them.]
[Time to work on the mid to lower level,
and give themselves a little break.]
[Still only helping with overseeing others?]
[Onlooker Big-nose continues to nag them on
with his arms crossed over his chest.]
When I asked him why he has his arms crossed,
he told me it's because he's cold.
- How can you be cold?
- The rest of us are covered in sweat!
[Everyone else is covered in sweat...]
- You're sweating? Why?
- We're all sweating!
Be careful, Kwang Soo.
[Their goal is to get 24,
and they currently have 20.]
[Working on their 21st block.]
I got it!
[Hm...]
Wow, I can't believe we're going to
succeed this mission.
- This one is going to be easy as pie.
- That's going to be so easy!
That's going to be cake!
[Current count- 24 blocks,
including the piece of cake block!]
[The writers are starting to
show their nervousness.]
The writers' faces are getting red!
[Running Man members are already
in their celebration mode.]
Go on and keep taunting them.
I can see them getting annoyed!
[Succeeds pulling out
their 23rd block with ease.]
The writers are having an emergency meeting!
[The writers are having
an emergency meeting?]
They're having a meeting!
Having a meeting!
Having a meeting.
We're not having a meeting, we're discussing
how we can get you more running balls.
- Kwang Soo is up.
- You want this one, or the one up there?
I think this one is going to be really tough.
There's a lot of pressure on this one.
- Which one should I go for?
- I think the one up there will be better.
- The one up there?
- Go for the one on the left.
- You can do this, Kwang Soo.
- It's all over if we fail this.
- This is all riding on you.
- We're not going to fail this.
We're going for the riskier one up there
to make it better for the writers.
- You guys do whatever you want.
- You're leaving it up to us?
Then why is your face getting all red?
- Your face is getting really red.
- You look very upset right now.
The writers are pretending to be okay!
You don't think...
[Could the entertainment god be smiling
down upon Kwang Soo during this mission too?]
Don't get greedy with this.
Just do what you need to do.
Don't get all greedy and
try to be overly entertaining.
- Lee Kwang Soo!
- Hey, whose side are you on?
All the writers are
chanting your name right now.
[The success of their mission is
riding on Kwang Soo.]
Just pull this one out by tapping it lightly.
- Let's get this done.
- 15 running balls are riding on this.
[The fate of 15 running balls are riding on
Kwang Soo's shoulders.]
- Grab my hand.
- Grab his hand and do what he needs.
- Don't do anything funny.
- I'm going to stand up now.
[Will it be victory?
Or will be it pure comedy?]
- He's already up.
- I'm going to stand up now.
- Up a little bit more.
- Are you okay, Jong Kook?
Will you be okay?
I need you to move up a little bit.
- You think this one is okay?
- That's really high up there.
[Going for their targeted Jenga piece.]
- No, no!
- I don't have a good feeling about this.
[Everyone is extremely nervous.]
- Is it not going to work?
- Why are you touching that?
- Pull it out or not?
- Hurry.
- I think it's going to work.
- I think he can do it.
[Just what will be the results?]
[Succeeds the Jenga mission!
All 24 blocks are removed.]
[Darn...]
- I can't believe we did it.
- All of our hard work paid off!
That was a pretty easy mission.
- Let's play another round.
- No, forget it.
[Immediately proposes
another round of the mission.]
I propose that we play another round with
20 balls on the line this time.
- If you fail, you only get ten balls...
- No, we're not doing it then.
Why would we even do it then?
There's not enough in it for us.
Okay, then here's what we propose.
Pulling out five more blocks from
the way things currently stand.
We'll count it as a win if you can
pull out just five more right now.
Then if we were to fail,
then we get 12?
[Taking it upon himself
to knock off a few balls?]
- What are you saying?
- Let's make it more entertaining.
We have to consider the writers' positions,
and try to make it interesting at least.
- That's too much.
- We may not even get to go home tonight.
- Then how about we go for ten?
- Ten is a bit too much.
I'll take the ten, and I offer nine.
- I'll go down to 13.
- Okay, we'll take that.
13 if you fail, but 20 if you succeed.
[Take out five more blocks, and win 20,
or go down to 13.]
Hey, she's sleeping up there.
I can't believe she fell asleep up there.
[Blank Ji fell asleep while the rest were
negotiating the game.]
Don't you think that we could call
'How Can This Be' for something like this?
[Took off the helmet to use as a pillow,
and sleeping like she's in her own home.]
- That's unbelievable.
- No matter how tired she is, how could she?
[Strong heart, Blank Ji.]
It's not even a solid tower,
but it's a tower missing its blocks.
How can she sleep on something like that?
- She really is something.
- Song Ji Hyo.
- She's not waking up.
- Then just leave her alone.
Song Ji Hyo.
Did you sleep well?
- We're going to do this without the wire?
- Don't pretend you weren't asleep.
Look at how unashamed she's acting.
- You saw?
- What are you doing up there?
Let's just go on.
No need to drag this on anymore.
- We can do this.
- One, two, three. Challenge!
- Who wants to go first?
- I'll go first.
I'm going to kick it out.
- That's not easy.
- That's kind of stuck down there.
- Be careful.
- Let us know when it starts to shake.
Okay, we got it!
- Okay, I'm going next.
- Four more to go!
- How are you going to do that one?
- You have to punch it with all your might.
Hey, careful.
[Everyone is starting to freak out as
the tower starts to shake.]
- Hey, you have to come this way.
- Be careful.
[The Jenga piece is stuck on tight...]
[Will they be able to free up the piece?]
- Just pull it out.
- Pull it out.
[The whole tower sways!]
- Don't try to push it!
- Lift a little as you pull it out.
[Even more carefully.]
[Could've been big trouble!]
- It's really stuck on tight.
- Just pull it out quickly.
- Just pull it out.
- Just ease it out of there.
[Haroro is focusing all his
concentration on the piece.]
We can go home nice and dry.
Sing me the song, Suk Jin.
I feel nervous about this.
[With them cheering him on... he succeeds!]
[Three left to go of their bonus round.]
[Manager Kkuk's turn,
who's been born to play Human Jenga.]
[Kkuk chooses to go for
the very bottom level of the tower.]
Careful.
- Okay, that's good.
- That's a very safe piece.
Okay, that looks good.
- Two more to go!
- Okay! We can do this!
- Which one are we going for now?
- The right one doesn't really matter.
The last person to go has to make sure
to be really cautious.
[High up in the tower...]
- He can't even reach up there.
- This is bad.
[Actually climbing up the Jenga tower!]
Lift up my right foot.
- Are you okay?
- Be careful.
- Make sure to hold onto me.
- Tap it out of there.
[Carefully tapping the Jenga piece
out of its spot.]
[Blank Ji awaits with her breath held
on top of the Jenga tower.]
[Pulled a good portion of the piece out.]
Carefully.
Go to the side.
[Moving carefully around to knock
the rest of the piece out.]
- You just need to knock it out of there.
- Be careful.
- Keep it balanced, Ji Hyo.
- Grab tighter onto my feet.
[Ji Hyo's role is becoming ever more crucial
as the number of the pieces lessens.]
[It's almost out of there.]
- It's okay.
- Just tap it out.
Okay!
[Finally knocks it out of there!]
- I'm so scared.
- We've got you, you're okay.
The writers are starting to get
scowls on their faces.
- I think that we're amazing.
- Which piece should I go for?
Go for this piece.
Come over to the right a bit, Ji Hyo.
[Ji Hyo needs to help find
the tower's balance first.]
- Okay, let's do this.
- And be careful.
Take the stick up there with you
just in case.
Take it with you,
and if it seems really stuck
then dig a small space on the bottom
to make a handle to pull it out by.
- Okay, take this with you.
- That stick is our hope.
- Okay, stand up carefully.
- Am I good?
- This is all in your hands.
- Do I need to go on my tiptoe?
[That's the target piece!]
I need the stick.
- Dig a groove?
- Yeah, you have to stab it.
[Ready to start making some snow.]
Okay, you're getting it.
- Try putting your finger in there.
- Can you fit your finger in there?
[Completely covered up in snow.]
- Are you sure that this is how I do it?
- Yeah, just pull it out now.
[Finally attempts to remove the piece.]
- I think this is going to work.
- Ji Hyo!
- You have to keep the balance!
- Okay, that looks good.
- To the right a bit.
- Ji Hyo has to keep the balance.
[Sticking his finger in
the self-made handle...]
[Just a little bit more...]
[Will they get it?]
[Will they pull out the final piece without
making the tower crumble down in pieces?]
[He did it!]
[The tower must stand for five seconds
after Kwang Soo is back on the ground.]
[Succeeds the bonus mission!]
You did great!
[A round of applause for Ji Hyo as well for
doing a great job up on the tower.]
Thank you.
You sure 20 isn't too many?
[20 running balls as promised.]
- Aren't you scared up there, Ji Hyo?
- Are you not even scared?
- Does not that even scare you?
- How is she okay with that?
Okay, let's go.
I don't know what the writers have in store
for us on such a cold day as this.
We're off to a really good start.
- Great job, everyone!
- We're awesome when we work together.
When we work as a team,
we all know what our own specific roles are.
We're like the earth.
[Like different elements of the earth?]
[Like the water, like the cloud,
like the wind...]
Then I'm the star.
I wonder what they have in store for us now.
- Is that our van?
- I see the cameras.
[A camera on top of the bridge?]
[Hm... the next mission looks
pretty challenging as well?]
I wonder why they're standing out there
on top of the bridge.
[The fact that they're on
top of the bridge...]
- What is this?
- Isn't this the Han River?
[Not a very good feeling about this...]
[Location- Han River Observation Deck.]
What are we doing here at Han River?
- I see a stage.
- I see some sort of a stage.
Are we going in the water?
- What is that?
- It's boxes!
[Box, tape, tools-
They can't be serious...]
They're not expecting us to cross
the Han River, are they?
Come on, no way!
- That's ridiculous.
- This is just absurd.
[Entering the stage with apprehension.]
Didn't you see the cameras
on top of the bridge earlier?
[The cameras... They can't really mean...]
They really expect us to cross
the Han River?
[Their worst nightmare come true.]
[What is the fate that awaits them?]
- Are we doing something on the Han River?
- This is absurd.
It's time for you to cross the Han River
on board your paper boat.
You have to cross the Han River
in the paper boat.
[Reacts vehemently as soon as
they hear their next mission.]
- You have to cross the Han River.
- Han River is ridiculous.
- We did a simulation this morning.
- Look at how strong the currents are.
Since there are seven of you,
you can divide into groups of four and three.
You'll be given 30 minutes.
If both the boats can cross the river
within 30 minutes
then you'll be given 15 running balls.
But if only one of the two boats makes it
in that 30 minutes, then you only get ten.
If even one boat makes it across past the
time limit, then you get five balls.
If both boats capsizes, then you get nothing.
There's another option.
If even a single boat makes it across within
25 minutes, then you'll get 20 balls.
We said we didn't want water games,
so why are we doing a water game?
But if we make our boat like Jung Chi and
Jung In did, then we may be able to make it.
But I really want to recommend that
just a plain raft is the way to go.
But if we make a boat like Jae Suk did,
then we're going to capsize for sure.
[If they make it like Jae Suk
and Kwang Gyu did...]
We've learned a few tricks since our last time,
so we may be able to do this well.
We've even prepared some snacks
for all of you to enjoy as well.
Enjoy your snacks while you work.
We should listen to Gary's advice
about the raft.
[Building the boats aside,
they're focusing on eating first?]
- We're going to eat first.
- Your clock starts now.
- What? Are you serious?
- Can't you give us time to eat first?
[How are they going to make two boats to fit
three and four within an hour?]
Look at that current.
That current is no joke.
[Will their boats be able to cut through by
the knife-like winds and the strong currents?]
Look over it to make sure that they
didn't put any holes in the boxes.
[You really think that
the writers would do that?]
We have to remain alert.
Let's look at this one first.
[The four person boat to carry-
Jae Suk, Jong Kook, Gary, and Kwang Soo.]
That should be big enough
for all four of us to sit down, right?
You don't' think that's too wide?
[Maybe they can build it within 25 minutes.
These aces seem to know their stuff.]
- The size of Gary's shadow.
- Then that's simple. Just pull it up.
Yeah, that sounds good.
[As for this team, we can only hope-
The three person boat's strategizing time.]
What if we did something like this?
This is the side view of the boat.
[A former marine-
Big nosed Brother's blueprint.]
Think of how this will look
once the sides are stood up.
This won't take too long to build.
[Will they be able to build it like this?]
- We need to tape it on this side too.
- And get it on this side as well.
[Meanwhile, the Cruise Line Ship Team
seems to know exactly what they're doing.]
And tape it like this.
You see this gap over here?
We should overlap these sides
so that there aren't any gaps.
So that no water leaks in.
- Okay, I get it.
- And we're going to add another piece.
We're going to add another one there.
You know what I'm saying, right?
Yes.
- Wait...
- What?
- What is it?
- I'm a member of this team too.
- I never said that you weren't.
- This isn't some dictatorship over here.
- I'm just making sure that we do it right.
- Seriously.
They are we done with shaping it?
Is this how the boat is going to look?
- There's no need for it to look pretty.
- How it looks isn't important.
- I believe that how it looks is important.
- We have to make it really waterproof.
If looks are so important to you,
then what's wrong with your face?
- How can you say something like that?
- Can you scold him for me?
[Is the Cruise Line Ship Team in danger
of in-house fighting?]
- Teamwork is very important here.
- I know that.
- I want to let you know...
- Look at our teamwork.
Look at how well we're working together.
- What are you guys doing?
- What are you drawing down there?
This is how Ji Hyo and I ended up making
our raft boat the last time.
- Because we were crunched for time.
- But remember what's important here.
This team needs to make it across
without sinking for us to succeed.
- I made the model.
- Just go with the raft idea.
But this cardboard is too thin
for you to be able to do that.
- See? This looks like a boat.
- But you're forcing that into shape.
I'm telling you that this is going to work.
- See? It's perfect.
- Okay, let's start making it.
[They've agreed to go along with
Big-nosed Brother's plan...]
Let's fold it and see if it fits.
- Why does it have to look like a boat?
- I don't know why either!
What do you mean, overlap it?
The boat has a huge hole in it!
- Why not just go for a plain box instead?
- Or how about a turtle boat?
- How are you going to build it?
- We're ruined!
- No, this could work.
- This isn't what I had in mind.
[Big-nosed Brother in the end agrees to
try out Ha Ha's idea...]
Fold up the sides over here.
Are your legs okay?
See? Look at this.
Look at how simple this idea is.
[It's already taking on the shape
of a boat...]
Look at this, Suk Jin!
Suk Jin!
I said, take a look at this!
[They're already pretty much finished with
the boat as they go with Ha Ha's idea.]
- How is it being built so quickly?
- Just hold it like this.
This looks better than my idea.
There won't be any leaks either.
- Get to work!
- Just hurry up and get to work!
- It feels really sturdy.
- Right?
[Really starting to take shape.
Time to build it strong.]
I'm getting a really good feeling about this.
Have yourselves a hot cup of coffee
while you work.
Is there any caramel macchiato?
- Come hold this! Gary!
- Yes, Sir!
[Even the Giraffe is taking out the time
to take a sip of his coffee.]
- Kwang Soo.
- I said, grab this part!
- Kwang Soo!
- Grab it!
This is really hot!
You don't think we're thirsty either?
You want a drink of the Han River?
[A stern warning.]
- I'm sorry!
- This is looking pretty good.
[A nice wrapping job to make sure
that there won't be any leaks.]
[Planning to build onto the boat to help
increase its buoyancy.]
Then you want us to put something
inside the box?
Okay, I got it.
[The boat building project
is really starting to pick up speed.]
[Will they be able to safely cross
the river in those boats?]
[Only 13 minutes left on the clock.]
Get out of the way!
[Great idea- Attaching the box under the boat
to help increase its buoyancy.]
Wow, this is a real workout.
- Yes, we'd appreciate that.
- We just want someone to help with taping.
- But you have to adhere to the time limit.
- Yes, of course.
Grab it down here.
Wow, that's unbelievable.
[Finishes it up within a blink of an eye
with the help from a crewmember.]
Just keep going.
We have to make sure
that it's really taped well.
Well, this is really on there.
[Well-made buoyancy boat.]
Are we really going to be
able to cross the Han River?
If this won't get us across,
then nothing will.
I was just joking about it, but I
can't believe we're really doing this.
I know that I've seen someone crossing
the Han River on TV years ago
but I never knew that I'd be the one
to attempt it too.
[Just who will be the ones to really
cross this giant expanse of the river?]
Okay, let's lift it up.
Wrap it around like this.
We're going to build a raft and attach
our boat to the raft.
[Plan is to attach
two separate boats together.]
Can you lend us a pair of hands since
Ji Hyo's not strong enough to do all this?
Can one of the staff members come help?
[Ji Hyo's strong manager steps in to help.]
I'm fine.
Just help them with that.
[They're picking up speed on their project.]
- Make sure there's no room for leaks.
- Don't give up. We can do this.
We can make this float.
[The three member team that had some trouble
in their designing phase, will they make it?]
Are you making cotton candy or something?
- How are you going to get in that?
- Is that a coffin?
- What is that?
- Suk Jin did it.
- What are you doing?
- How are you going to get in that thing?
There's not much time.
This is ridiculous.
[The more they build,
the more ridiculous it's becoming.]
This really is absurd.
How are you going to cross the Han River?
That's no small creek to cross.
[The idea of crossing the Han River
in a boat like that...]
[It'll be a shock to just see it float on top
of the water from a quick glance at the boat.]
Just keep wrapping it.
This looks like a battle ship.
[The four person boat is complete!]
[The team's hope may have to
ride on these four men.]
[Time's up!]
[Time to face the river...]
Let's try sitting in it first.
Ji Hyo, I just want you to go from side
to side and keep the boat balanced.
If it seems it's leaning too much one way,
then you paddle from the opposite side.
[They have to make sure to be in sync to
battle the strong winds and the current.]
We need to think of the water
like it's the sand.
[The four men team must paddle in sync!]
To be honest... we should
leave the speed to the other team.
We should just focus on finishing the race.
I don't know if I can even lift this.
[Time to make history!]
[They're going to attempt to cross the river!]
[The four person boat is proving to be
quite heavy in its weight.]
Fighting!
- Cross all the way to the other side?
- Is that even possible?
Is it even possible to cross?
[Will they be able to cross...
the whole river in their boats?]
[Yoo Hyuk, Mr. Capable, Giraffe, Mr. Gary.]
[F4?
Four men Running Boat.]
[And another team.]
[Big-nose, Ace, Haroro.]
[Three person... life raft?]
[Must cross the Han River to
earn your next set of running balls!]
[Their start is looming.]
- Fighting!
[Everyone's cheering each other on.]
[Must pull the finish flag on the other side
of the river to succeed the mission.]
- We have to paddle in sync.
- I hope we don't sink right away.
[Will their boat even float?]
[Even the slightest move off balance
might capsize the boat.]
[Both teams are now ready... Go!]
[It's floating!]
[Wow- It's actually floating!]
Okay, let's go!
[The three person boat is floating
lightly on the water.]
Off to the right a bit.
Okay, here we go.
Paddle to the right.
[Off on the Han River... with confidence!]
[The two boats have to be extra cautious
as they start off on their adventure!]
One, two!
[Cross the river in 25 minutes or less,
and win 25 running balls!]
[The two boats are finally headed
into the heart of the Han river!]
[Kwang Soo's boat.]
[The crew of these two boats are keeping their
focus to steadily make their way forward!]
- Row on the right side, Suk Jin.
- Help row to the right, Ji Hyo.
[The boat is starting to drift away!
Ha Ha gives out emergency instructions.]
[Even though the pace may be slow,
the boats are definitely moving forward!]
We're going to earn our balls.
This is unbelievable.
[The tough challenge that seemed
impossible in the beginning...]
[Not a single person who can help,
or a single person for them to lean on.]
[Only the comrades that they're with.]
[Both boats are headed
towards the finish line.]
[The four person boats forges ahead
under the direction of Yoo Hyuk.]
Paddle to the right.
[With the strong and icy winter winds...]
[The boat keeps swerving in other direction
no matter how straight they try to row it.]
We can do this.
Don't give up.
[Even the three person boat with all
their early troubles seems to be doing well.]
Paddle deep.
[On the other hand, the other boat is
forging ahead like a well-built tank.]
[Captain Yoo Hyuk instructs them to change
the direction of their paddling.]
Careful.
No!
No way!
[F4 is in danger of capsizing!]
[Will they be able to right the boat again?]
[F4 members overboard!]
They fell in the water.
The boat capsized.
[They lost their balance while trying to
change the direction of their rowing.]
No!
No way!
[How can this be...]
[The unbelievably cold temperature of
the December waters!]
[Automatically screams out
in pain from the icy waters.]
[The rescue crew on standby
comes to their aid.]
[The boat is completely flipped over.]
[Calmly fishing out one person at a time.]
[All members are safely
pulled aboard the rescue raft.]
Are you okay?
[Is this the end of the F4's capsized boat?]
[Meanwhile]
[The other boat is shockingly still afloat
and forging on ahead.]
[Captain Ha Ha is remaining focused,
and forging his team ahead.]
[This small boat is the Running Man Team's
only remaining hope.]
This is unbelievable, Suk Jin.
We're the aces of the team.
[Is he serious?]
[If they can only make it across
without capsizing the boat...]
[The F4 members make it safely back
to shore on their rescue boat.]
[They thought they could succeed
without even a doubt in their minds.]
I told you that we should make it wider.
You should've listened to me!
But having the boat sit up that high
was tough for us to keep our balance.
That really took me by surprise.
And that water is shockingly cold!
[The water is colder than they had
ever even anticipated.]
[But... will they be able to take
that boat back out into the water?]
Ten minutes and ten seconds
have currently passed.
Do you want try going across
in this boat again
or do you want to drive across to the
other side and cheer the other team on?
You have to make your decision right now.
[The decision is up to these four men!]
[Will they make another attempt in this boat,
or give up going across the river?]
Let's try it again.
[F4 suggests making another attempt
at crossing the river!]
One, two, three!
[In the boat they worked so hard to build...
they will make another attempt!]
[But what kind of a condition
will their capsized boat be in?]
[The boat seems to be completely ruined
from having been capsized in the water.]
How about we rip out the top part,
and go on just the raft alone?
[Rip off the top portion,
and just go on the bottom raft portion.]
- Let's just go on the bottom part.
- Should we just go on the bottom portion?
- Let's make one more attempt.
- You think it'll be okay?
- Should we just go change out pants?
- I'm not sure that you have the time for it.
- Let's just go.
- If we fall in the water again...
[There's nothing left to lose!
One last attempt to make it across!]
[Meanwhile]
[The other boat is still steadily
making its way across the river.]
[Hardworking and focused Captain Haroro.]
[The earlier scene of them bickering
while building the boat is long gone.]
[Even though they've still got a ways to go,
they're full of their fighting spirit!]
Out boat is so sturdy and strong.
I'm proud of us.
Let's finish this race.
I know it's exhausting, but
keep your focus.
- Keep your eyes ahead.
- Let's finish this.
We're almost there.
[Captain Haroro is continuing
to cheer on his team members.]
[Will this boat be able to last
across to the finish line?]
Let's try it.
Let's cheer up and see if we can make it.
My guess is...
88% guaranteed that we'll sink.
I can't fall back in that water again.
[They now know what it's like to
fall into that icy water.]
[Making another attempt without the top part,
and just on the life raft portion.]
[Just seeing the water alone is enough
to make them quake in fear.]
Okay, let's go.
Let's remain strong.
So cold!
Okay, we're good.
We're steadier than we were before.
[Another gauntlet is thrown at the river.]
[Deep and strong paddles.]
[And move forward.]
[Even though their boat may be ruined,
their will is stronger than ever!]
[Their teamwork is rowing the boat
is even stronger than before.]
[The voyage of F4 starts now!]
This is good.
A little bit to the right.
[Keep up this pace, and their only problem
would be the matter of time.]
Look at that wave!
It's coming our way.
[Wave?]
[Wave!]
[A giant wave is headed their way!]
- Loosen up your limbs.
- Don't tighten up your bodies!
[They already fell in the water earlier...
Fall again, and they're done for!]
[Here it comes!]
[Extreme state of nervousness.]
Let's go again!
Here we go!
[Head off again once the wave passes.]
Let's go!
Please!
Running Man!
Going on four years now!
Even though we've been ignored
and disrespected all this time...
but we've endured all those years
to show them this moment.
We're not traitors.
We're married men now!
Can you get me some water, Ji Hyo?
[They're all like one big family
in their little boat.]
Suk Jin. Let's think of this as being our
only means of seeing our family again.
I'm going to be a father
that my baby can be proud of!
Dream!
Daddy is coming!
Hyun Woo!
Dad is coming!
Uncle is coming too!
I love you, mom and dad!
Let's have another baby, honey!
Let's have a second baby too, honey!
[Crossing the Han River with their
determination to get back to their families.]
[F4 members are struggling even more
ever since having fallen in the water.]
Who would've ever thought that I'd be
trying to cross the Han river like this?
Everyone... you're all tired, aren't you?
- Are you okay?
- Yes.
We could pull you the rest of the way
if you just want to give up.
No, we're going to finish ourselves.
[Insisting on crossing the river themselves.]
We're going to finish this ourselves!
- We love everyone!
- Let's stay strong.
[The other team is already near
the water fountain.]
We're going to finish this.
We can finish this in five minutes.
Let's stay determined and finish this!
[Picking up the speed to forge
full speed ahead!]
[Even though they're exhausted,
their teamwork is better than ever!]
We're moving at a good speed!
[Perfectly in sync.]
We'll show them that we're not the bottom,
but that we're the foundation of this team!
We're almost there!
Stay focused!
[Their strength is diminishing...]
[It really is down to
the final spurt of energy!]
Let's pick up the speed.
We have to pull the flag.
[The shore... really is
right in front of their eyes now.]
[About to land!]
[Pulling out the flag
is the most crucial part!]
[Ace Ji Hyo runs full speed ahead
towards the flag!]
[And their time?
And how many balls will they earn?]
[Succeeds in crossing the Han River
in their paper boat!]
[The time is still unknown...]
Wow, we really did it.
[Really did cross the river
in their paper boat.]
- We'll reveal your finish time.
- Get up, Dong Hoon.
[Haroro stepped up to the plate
as the captain of their boat.]
I'm really impressed by what we did.
[A moment where no words are necessary.]
Okay, everyone.
Here's your time.
I told you that you'll earn ten balls
if one boat arrives within 30 minutes.
One boat did succeed in making it to shore
within 30 minutes.
[One boats succeeds in landing in 30 minutes-
Ten running balls are earned.]
[Made their way across the whole river
in that flimsy boat.]
[If even one boat makes it within 25 minutes,
then 20 balls are won as a bonus.]
[Their finish time is...]
20 minutes and 39 seconds!
[Unbelievable!
20 minutes and 39 seconds!]
[Under 20 minutes!
20 running balls are earned!]
- We made it in 20 minutes!
- Unreal!
[Emotional over their huge success.]
You saw that, right?
You saw that?
[Well deserved after
all their unyielding hard work.]
[Emotional from succeeding
this almost impossible mission.]
- Unbelievable.
- This is amazing.
Let's take a picture.
[Everyone thought that they'd fail...]
[Picture of proof-
20 minutes and 39 seconds.]
[Succeeds in crossing the Han River!]
We did it!
This means our skills have improved greatly
without us even realizing it.
[No one even fathomed that they'd be able to
cross the river this quickly.]
- I love you, mom and dad!
- We did it!
- We love you!
- What a great start to 2014!
I love you, my son!
This is what you call real action!
This is the first time I've ever
teared up like this during a show.
This is unbelievable.
I'm so emotional right now.
I love the fact that it was the
three of us that got it done.
He's the designer.
[It's now time to cheer on the others.]
[Not giving up to the end.]
[These men, enjoying this moment
of their challenge...]
[These men, who know that giving up
is the real loss of the game...]
I can't believe how close we are
to the water fountain.
[The fountain that they've only seen from
atop the bridge is right in front of them.]
[With fierce determination...]
[With their trust only in each other...]
[Just like this one moment...]
- They ripped off the top portion.
- They're crossing on the raft.
- You guys are awesome!
- You're so awesome!
You can do it!
Just a little bit more!
- One! Two!
- This is really amazing.
In a paper boat... A paper boat that
we made. It's unbelievable.
You're almost there!
It's right in front of you now!
You guys are awesome!
I'm proud of you guys!
[Cheering each other on.]
You're almost there.
You're really almost there.
- One, two!
- Running Man, fighting!
[They're almost at shore...]
You guys ripped off the top
of your boat.
[After rowing for so long,
their exhaustion can be seen in their faces.]
[The finish line is right
in front of their eyes.]
Run!
[Yoo Hyuk never gave up to the very end.]
[Even though they don't know
how much time has passed...]
[They still run over to the finish line...]
[All the members sincerely cheering
each other on with all their hearts.]
[Chilled down to their bones,
but kept warm with their own fervor.]
[Running Man Han River Boat Challenge-
Success!]
I can't help but be impressed by the
fighting spirit that you've all just shown.
We're all shocked right now by
the fact that you've all succeeded.
[Both boats succeeded in their mission-
What is F4's finishing time?]
47 minutes and 32 seconds.
[The fact that they kept on rowing that
whole time without ever giving up...]
The first team made it
in 20 minutes and 39 seconds.
[20 minutes and 39 seconds-
20 running balls earned!]
We all did it!
[No matter who actually did it,
they all accomplished it together.]
Please come this way.
It's almost time for PD Myuk to
take a little plunge in the water.
I can't believe I'm about to witness this
in my lifetime.
When we were dumped in the river...
I really wasn't going to say this.
- But he really is no joke.
- Why?
Look at the picture that he uploaded.
Why would you upload a picture
of a cup of coffee?
I got really bored while waiting
for you guys to get to the finish line.
You really are something else.
I really want to see him
get plunged in the water.
- I brought an extra set of underwear today.
- Seriously?
We always bring extra with us since
we never know what'll happen.
We already had to
change our underwear once.
We're about to start our last round of games.
All of you have worked really hard today.
Even though we don't know
what the results will be
the beauty of seeing how hard you're
working in the challenge against us
- I'd like to see...
- Did you say that this is our challenge?
Your final mission is...
Hongdae's Rhythmic Gymnastics.
- Hongdae's Rhythmic Gymnastics.
- What's that?
If you'll look outside,
you'll see a special set for the mission.
Rhythmic gymnastics?
[The area is already full of spectators.]
[Seven Running Man members must do seven
different predetermined categories...]
[And complete the series of categories
within seven minutes to win.]
Seven minutes is going to be tough.
We've prepared a set of nice and warm
gymnastics outfits for all of you.
You call this nice?
You'll do the mission in a relay method
to complete it within seven minutes.
If you succeed with three attempts,
then you'll earn 15 running balls.
If you succeed within four attempts,
then you'll win 10 running balls.
But if you succeed within two attempts,
then we'll give you 20 balls.
We have to be very serious about this.
Can you give us just
three minutes to practice?
- Since we've never done this before?
- That's an excellent suggestion, Ji Hyo.
If you'll give me two running balls...
I'm going to step outside
and think about the decision.
Can someone else take over for him?
- Send someone else in.
- Let's get PD Myuk today!
- Yes, let's do that.
- Let's seriously win today.
One, two, three.
Challenge.
[Hongdae's Rhythmic Gymnastics-
Challenge accepted.]
- Fighting.
- Fighting!
I'll go do it and be right back.
- I think she'll do really good.
- She's good at everything.
Ten hoola hoop jumps.
[Blank Ji- Ten jumps through the hoola hoop.]
[Oh... she's a good jumper!]
[She's doing so great!]
Ten!
[Success!]
[Back to the second player!]
Okay, Gary.
Get it done.
[Second player, Gary,
is off to their special stage.]
[But their stomachs are feeling
a bit too full...]
Where?
Where do I go?
[That's hard...]
What's wrong with this!
- You have to go up a bit more.
- Up a bit?
[Will he catch it this time?]
[Ah... so close!]
[Finally succeeds!]
He got it!
- Jong Kook.
- That's our Gary!
Good job.
[Complete exhaustion.]
[Third player- Kkuk.]
[The spectators burst out in laughter from
seeing how tight the uniform is on him.]
[Everyone starting to grumble
now that the Tiger is out of the den.]
- Left to right?
- You have to stay within the boundaries.
If your foot leaves that little mark,
then you fail the mission.
[Turn once to the left and once to the right
on one foot while twirling the ribbon.]
I got it, right?
How did I fail?
- You can't hop around.
- What!
There he goes getting angry again.
Why did he have to keep on insisting
to do that category?
- Why did he keep insisting on that one?
- I told him to do the dribble.
Okay, here I go.
[Second attempt.]
You're stepping on the ribbon!
[Fail]
[Failed thanks to a spectator
pointing out his mistake.]
There he goes getting angry again.
[That's one circle.]
[Back to the right now.]
[Success]
- Okay!
- Here I go.
[Time for Ha Ha's turn.]
You got that, right?
[Throw the three hoops and
jump over them in succession.]
[The hoop isn't rolling very well
on top of the mat.]
[Endures the painful agony...]
- Fighting!
He has to throw it further this time.
[He throws it far,
but success still eludes him.]
Why isn't this working?
Why!
[Yoo Hyuk- Bounce the table tennis ball
ten times on top of the club.]
Stay calm.
I'm trying to remain calm,
but it's not really working.
[The unpredictable table tennis ball.]
Ugh!
This is so frustrating!
This is seriously so frustrating!
[Big-nosed Brother's turn.]
[Bounce the ball five times on his shoulder.]
How am I supposed to do this?
I think he'll only succeed once
his shoulders stiffen up.
A round of applause!
I did it!
[Five shoulder bounces- Success!]
I did it.
[Time for Kwang Soo's turn.]
- I did it.
- I think today really is the day.
My long johns are really
keeping me warm.
[Throw the clubs into the air,
and catch it after two turns.]
- That's hard. That's really hard.
- Even a single spin is hard.
[Why is he stepping forward?]
[Ultimately ends up taking out his anger
out on PD Myuk.]
[First attempt- Fail.]
[Full of complaints over nitpicky judging.]
This is absurd.
I'm taking a very athletic approach
to this mission.
I don't think we'll be able to
succeed this mission.
[Unable to see the possibility
of them succeeding this mission.]
If you'll give me three running balls...
[Will adjust the most difficult category
at the cost of three running balls.]
Then reduce Kwang Soo's mission
to only a single spin.
[Asking to adjust Kwang Soo's mission
to only one singular spin.]
[Mr. Capable is easily able to
jump over the hoops.]
[Jong Kook and Ha Ha exchanging
their categories?]
Then you're going to give me
three of your running balls?
Yes, we will.
- Okay, fine.
- Then we'll do that.
If you succeed at your second attempt,
then you'll earn 20 running balls.
[20 balls if they succeed this time.]
One, two, three.
Challenge.
[Start]
[Blank Ji succeeded her part in one try
during their first attempt.]
[Doing it just as well this time around.]
Seven, eight, nine, ten!
[Success]
[Succeeds again in one attempt.]
- She successful at everything.
- I know.
[Time for the second runner.]
- Okay.
- Good job, Ji Hyo. You really are our ace.
You really are amazing.
[A definite chance at succeeding.]
[Will he succeed?]
[Success]
- Thank you.
- Good job, Jong Kook.
[Haroro waits for his turn.]
- I did it.
- Good job.
- You got it done very quickly.
- You did a great job.
[Ribbon category
that he took over from Jong Kook.]
[One turn in each direction from
the same spot while twirling the ribbon.]
You're doing great!
[Second attempt only clad in his sock.]
[Success]
[Only four people left to go.]
[Bounce the ball ten times with the club.]
[Nine!]
[Wow!
Succeeds in bouncing it ten times!]
Okay, that's ten!
I got it!
[First of the four players
all passed their categories.]
[Getting a good feeling about this!]
[Four minutes left to go!]
[Time for Kwang Soo's turn with
his newly adjusted category.]
[He only needs to turn a singular turn
before he catches the clubs.]
[Success!]
He did it!
[Suk Jin's turn.]
- I feel so antsy.
- Fighting!
[Will he be able to succeed again this time?]
He looks like he's fencing.
[Oh?]
I did it, right?
[Another success!]
[Succeeding at a much quicker pace
than anticipated!]
[Only Gary is left to
succeed his category now.]
Our day is here.
I bet your wife and Hyun Woo
are really happy right now.
[Will Gary be able to succeed too?]
[So close!]
[20 running balls on the line!
Everyone's on the edge of their seats.]
[Oh?]
[The ball bounces out again...]
[He caught it!]
[Gary also succeeds!]
[The time he arrives back on the second floor
is their completion time!]
[Did they succeed within seven minutes?]
Your time is...
[Time is...]
Five minutes and 56 seconds.
[Time- Five minutes and 56 seconds.]
[Hongdae's Rhythmic Gymnastics-
Succeeds at second attempt.]
[Earns themselves 20 running balls.]
[Now the only thing that's left
is the final verdict.]
[Who will have to face the water blast?]
[Running Man vs The Writers.]
[The results will soon be revealed.]
[Calm before the storm,
but they're still feeling at ease.]
[SA long as they're at the ice cream shop...
Time to grab some ice cream!]
Why are things going so well today?
Things are going so well today.
If some other company asks us to compete
in some kind of a competition...
I'd bet that we'd pretty much win it.
[It's clear that RM members would have the
advantage from playing over 1,000 games.]
[What is that enormous set?]
Hwan is here again.
Go get us our running balls.
Min Soo, Hwan Jin, Dong Hwan...
[All the writers are present.]
What's going on here?
[Announcer Kim Hwan is here as
a special guest MC.]
[Even the writers have changed into sweat suits
just in case they end up getting wet.]
- What's going on here?
- We will now...
We will now hear the final verdict on 2013
year-end Running Man negotiations.
We will now start the verdict.
- You have 57 balls in your possession?
- Yes, that's correct.
- Please hand it over here.
- Yes, Sir.
[Team Running Man- A total of 57 balls.]
I don't know if the container's even
big enough for all those balls.
[Team Running Man with
a huge stash of balls.]
We have even more than that, don't we?
Just to assure fairness of the draw,
I will be making the draw myself.
I will proceed as I do every Saturday.
If the ball I draw is the Running Man ball,
then Team Running Man will win.
But if the Team Writers ball is drawn...
- Is it just going to be a single draw?
- One ball will determine who gets punished.
- We have twice the chance of winning.
- We have a pretty good chance.
[It's all left up to chance.
It's up to the luck of the draw.]
We will now start the final verdict.
[2013 Year End Final Verdict]
I really don't want to get wet!
We'll get started as soon as
everyone's up on the platform.
[The biggest water bomb that they ever faced
is hanging right above their heads.]
How about we stand facing each other?
[Wanting to look at each other's face as
one team is soaked by the water bomb.]
- Staring at each other's a good idea.
- It's nice, isn't it?
[Linking arms with one another to endure
the force of the water bomb.]
- Happy New Year, everyone!
- Happy New Year to all our viewers!
[Wishing everyone a Happy New Year
before the bomb is dropped on their heads.]
Thank you for all the love you've shown
us this past year.
- Thank you!
- We'll work even harder next year!
Thank you!
This is going to be very interesting!
[A face-off with their writers
to close out the year 2013!]
[The final results of that competition
awaits them right in front of their eyes!]
We will now start the final verdict for
Running Man Year End Competition.
I will start by putting all these balls
into the drawing machine.
If we lose right now, everything
we've done today was for nothing.
But we do have the advantage since
our team has more balls.
We do have the advantage,
but you know that it's still all about luck.
- Can't you put them in there faster?
- All the balls are now in.
[All 87 of the running balls are in.]
We will now start the running ball draw.
[Time to start the draw!]
So the ball that comes out
indicates who won, right?
- Ball that comes out is the winner?
- You win if it's your ball that comes out.
The team whose ball is not drawn will get
the water bomb dumped on them right away.
2013 year end draw.
[Today's harsh missions that were
harder than any other day...]
[We will claim victory over
our final competition of 2013!]
[Which of the two teams will win?]
[The ball is drawn!]
I have the ball in my hand.
[The winning team's ball is in
Announcer Kim Hwan's hand.]
Year 2013...
Running Man's Year End Competition.
The final running ball draw...
The ultimate winning team is...
[Running Man?]
[The Writers?]
It's Team Writers!
[Team Writers win!]
[What... happened?]
[Team Running Man is supposed to be
the ones to get wet!]
[What is this feeling?]
[We won, so why are we...]
[In complete celebration mode!]
[Rushing off the platform just in case
they water gets dumped on them too.]
[Who cares what had happened?
As long as we're not wet!]
[Happiest they've
ever looked in the past year.]
[Still clueless as to what happened.]
The ball says the 'writers'.
Team Writers won the draw.
[How did Team Writers get soaked
when they clearly won the draw?]
Thank you!
What kind of luck is this?
You know what PD Myuk would say to this?
'Nothing we can do about it'.
[PD Myuk's usual response-
'Nothing we can do about it'.]
We're the ones who should've gotten wet.
But they made the mistake,
and got themselves soaked instead.
There's nothing that can be done.
It was their own mistake.
There must have been
some slight misunderstanding.
[A learned mistake on their part.]
This is Running Man's
last episode of the year.
[The machine operates a little too late.]
- It must've been a mechanical error.
- That's why they got wet instead.
So no more water games
during the cold weather, right?
[Even though the writers got soaked,
they still technically won.]
Anyway... we will see you next week.
We will you all a very happy new year!
[Happy New Year!]
Thank you!
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Thank you for all your love and support.
We will work even harder in the new year!]
Your first mission of 2014 is,
The Running Man Cooking Battle.
[2014 Running Man Cooking Battle.]
[First week of the New Year's dinner table.]
[A fierce cooking battle.]
[The true taste of the food that
is unparalleled.]
[Find the ultimate cooking master.]
[Cooking secrets that will be passed
down to these members.]
[For the ultimate dinner table...]
[Just who will be crowned
The Chef King of Running Man?]
[Cooking Competition.]