Subtitles by DramaFever
[Couples]
[Gold]
[1% friendship]
[One scorching summer day...]
[Four beautifully set tables.]
- What is this?
- I'm so sleepy.
- What's going on here today?
- It looks like a party.
I feel like all the Girls Generation girls
may show up on the show today, right?
It's a celebration.
Is someone coming on the show today?
Special guests?
- How many guests, do you think?
- The number of settings will let us know.
Yes?
Today's race will be a Couple Race where
people will be paired up in teams of two.
It's a couple race!
- There's going to be two per team?
- Yes.
A very special couple will be your
guide for this race.
- I want to see my tuna sister on the show.
- Is the tuna sister here?
What is that?
[A suspicious couple is
seen walking in sideways.]
- Welcome to the couples party.
- Are you a couple too?
[Huh?]
- What the heck?
- They look so much alike!
- They look exactly alike!
- There are two of them?
- They look exactly alike.
- They really do look a lot alike.
Where did you find him?
[FD Jae Chul from the
Tuesday evening show, Hwasin.]
- Do all the FD's look alike?
- How can they look so much alike?
- Are all the couples going to look alike?
- What if they all look like us?
- Then Han Ki Bum must be here.
- He looks just like you.
Our first guest for the day is...
- Yoo Jae Suk's partner.
- My partner?
[Jae Suk's partner is the first
to make their entrance.]
- I need to go greet my partner.
- Please ask your partner to come out.
- Who is it?
- We all have assigned partners?
- Please come on out.
- Guest, please come on out.
[Who could it be?]
[Self-proclaimed master of the variety world,
Kim Kwang Gyu.]
It's Kwang Gyu.
- It's Kwang Gyu.
- That's his partner?
Why are you seriously doing
this to me?
[The party atmosphere
taking major downturn.]
- Kwang Gyu?
- That's a nice partner you've got there!
- What's with the dour atmosphere?
- It's nice to see you.
It's because of you!
I thought that Suk Jin
was going to be my partner.
- So that you could be the young blood?
- I thought I'd be the younger of the two.
What are you saying?
You're saying you're the young blood?
[Bright and shiny as the sun?]
- You're not that much younger than me!
- I could pass for much younger than you!
[Self-proclaimed master of variety
showing his greed for Suk Jin's spot.]
This is going to drive me crazy.
He thinks he looks younger than me.
It's time for a trade.
It's time for Suk Jin to take a rest.
- Next, we'll welcome Ha Ha's partner.
- Ha Ha.
- Already?
- You just wait, Ha Ha.
[With the way this is going,
will it really be the tuna sister?]
Who is it?
- Who is it?
- Is that Sa Yuri?
[Woman with a 4 dimensional personality,
Sa Yuri.]
- This is a sad bunch of guests today.
- What is going on here?
Hey, Sa Yuri!
Look at the way she's walking!
She's already walking like this!
Watch your steps.
- Yuri, are you two friends?
- Yes, we're friends. We're the same age.
- Really?
- Yes.
Even though Yuri has been paired up
with Ha Ha on this episode
is there anyone else that you wanted
to be paired up with instead of Ha Ha?
- Yes, there is!
- Who?
- Kim Jong Kook.
- Why?
I really like him.
Everything about him is just so loveable.
- Why?
- I don't know, but he's just so delectable.
- He's delectable?
- Yes.
- What are you talking about?
- Ha Ha, you should step aside and concede.
- Is it my turn now?
- Seeing who our guests have been so far...
- It's time for a pretty girl guest.
- What if it's someone from a girl group?
It's so hard to predict who it could be.
[Full of anticipation.
Please... come on out.]
[Peek-a-boo!]
[Heavyweight actor, Park Sang Myun.]
It's Myun Sang.
Look, it's Myun Sang.
What is this?
Sang Myun is my partner?
It's Myun Sang.
Park Myun Sang!
[Looking dapper for the party?]
[As a continuation from the last time,
partnering up with his friend again?]
Why do we keep getting partnered up
when we don't even like each other?
- It's nice to meet you.
- How do you and Kwang Gyu know each other?
We both made our debuts
in the same movie a long time ago.
[They made their debuts in the same movie?]
Look at how happy he is with that comment.
He really likes that.
- Look at how happy he is.
- I thought that he was older than me.
I thought that he was older than me.
But I came to find out...
he and I are the same age.
He just looks older than his age.
- You two are the same age?
- Yeah, we're the same age.
- But he's younger than me.
- Yeah, he's a year younger than you.
- But you and I are friends?
- How that works is...
- Have you been deceiving me this whole time?
- It's because of our birthdays.
- Get down on your knees!
- But my birthday is very early.
I'm just going to go home.
- So how old are you then?
- I think I've gained too much weight.
[Changing the subject...]
[Avoiding the sensitive topic.]
Look at how nervous he's become
since they started discussing their age.
Next, we'll welcome
Lee Kwang Soo's partner.
[Asian Prince, Kwang Soo's partner.]
It's possible that his partner will be a girl.
[Seeing how the guests are of similar age,
he could have a younger girl partner?]
- Kwang Soo's partner is going to be a girl.
- Come on out.
[Who could it be?]
It's a very tall person.
[The rising star of variety, John Park.]
[The rising star garnering much attention
since having debuted in the audition show.]
[A singer with boyish good looks
and heartfelt voice.]
- It's John Park!
- John Park?
- It's another Kwang Soo!
- They're very similar.
John park is the newest rising star
in the variety world!
- He's so tall.
- Hello.
I feel like I'm looking at another
Kwang Soo.
[The two look-alikes greet one another.]
John Park is pretty quirky himself.
- I wanted to be Kwang Soo's partner.
- Why?
- I felt like we'd really get along well.
- Why do you think that?
Why?
Is it wrong of me to think that?
[Oddball John Park...]
- Kwang Soo's done for today.
- I think today's going to be fun.
I can't wait to see who's going to
be the weirder one today.
- I don't want to lose to him.
- You have to bring out your A game.
Then there's only Ji Hyo
and one other person left.
- I'm sure Gary will be with Ji Hyo.
- I'm excited to see who it'll be myself.
- Get out there and greet your partner.
- Who do you think it'll be?
This one is for you!
I knew this was going to happen!
Ji Hyo is the best of the lot here!
[Miss Blank makes her entrance.]
Ji Hyo is the best out of the lot today.
- Ji Hyo really is the best today.
- Ji Hyo is the best of the lot today.
You need to feel honored.
I'm still saving you like this
even though today is Tuesday.
- You two look good together.
- You guys look really good together.
- They really look good together.
- Why do I feel like I'm being led?
Next up is Kim Jong Kook's partner.
[Then who's going to be Kkuk's partner?]
Who could it be?
[Who... who is that?]
[All Right- Kim Ye Rim.]
[Having garnered much attention on the
show with her dream-like voice.]
[New rising star, Kim Ye Rim,
having made a recent solo debut.]
- How did you get so lucky?
- Hello.
Why is Jong Kook the only one?
- Why did Jong Kook get Ye Rim?
- Why are you doing this to us?
- Are they friends?
- All right!
- Hello.
What the heck is this?
They have similar hair color.
- What are you talking about?
- They actually look good together.
- I can't believe Ye Rim is here.
- Hello.
- Look at him. There he goes again.
- Why are you taking your sunglasses off?
- Why are you taking off your sunglasses?
- We have to be able to see each other.
- Seriously!
- She's here as my partner.
- There's someone else waiting in the back.
- There are more guests?
You're saying we have more guests
waiting to come out?
Who is it?
[Jo Jung Chi and Jung In!]
- What is this?
- Jo Jung Chi?
- Jo Jung Chi and Jung In are here?
- What are those two doing here?
Aren't they a real life couple?
What is Jung Chi wearing?
What's with that jacket?
Why don't you two hold
each other's hands?
Going on various variety shows
are their usual dates.
Why don't you help her out?
She's having trouble walking in her heels!
- Why don't you give her some support?
- It's hard enough for me to walk myself.
Why don't you hold onto her
and give her some support?
[Anyway, welcome to the show.]
- Why are we being partnered up again?
- Why?
[Jung In unhappy with her partner?]
- You want someone else here as your partner?
- Yes.
Kwang Soo.
- He's mine.
- Why am I yours?
- You should feel honored.
- This is really...
- This is a very strange setting today.
At this rate, I wouldn't be surprised if
Jo Gap Gyung and Hong Seo Beom came out.
This really feels like...
This feels really surreal today.
[A surreal combination...]
What's going on today?
We're going to have a couple race today where
you will be paired off in teams of two.
The title of today's race is...
'Couple, 1% of friendship.'
[Couple, 1% of friendship.]
You'll find out for yourself why today's race
is titled, 'Couple, 1% of friendship.'
First, I need one member of each team to step
forward and receive an item from me.
What are we getting?
- Isn't that gold?
- Oh, it's gold.
It's gold.
- Is it a cellphone?
- No, it's real gold!
Is it real?
Wow, it's real gold!
It's real gold.
- Are you giving this to us?
- This is real?
- You're in a better mood now, aren't you?
- Yeah, I like it!
This is my first time seeing
gold like this.
- This is your first time?
- This is real gold.
- I've never seen a gold bar.
- Awesome.
If you come in at the top in each
of your missions
you'll then receive additional gold bars.
In other words, you'll get a chance to take
your opponent's gold bars away from them.
The team that has the most number of
gold bars at the final mission
will receive an unbelievable advantage
for their team.
The first place winner can't have
their gold taken away from them.
I ask for each team to place their love
and friendship on the line and do their best.
And also, you will all be responsible
for the care of your own gold bars.
No one can help you if you lose, or have
your gold stolen from you along the way.
So if you lose it, then it's gone for good.
We will not keep it for you.
Each team will be
responsible for their own gold.
Even when you win yourselves
additional gold bars
you need to discuss with your partner
about who will take possession of the gold
and make sure to keep the bars safe
with you until the final mission.
[Each team putting their gold bars
in a pouch for safe keeping.]
- Did you both agree?
- Yes.
Okay, everyone to their cars.
[1% of friendship- The unlikely couples'
adventures are about to start.]
[Go to 'S' chicken soup restaurant.]
- This isn't it, right?
- No, it's in Sangshi.
Sangshi.
These two are riding with us because
neither one of them has a license.
- Really?
- Thank you.
Kwang Gyu looked at Ye Rim so warmly
when he greeted her earlier.
- He did?
- The way he greeted her was different.
No, that's not what happened!
It was Jung Chi who did that!
Ye Rim has become a mainstay
at our company, so everyone is...
That's right. Ye Rim is making
all the money for Jong Shin lately.
Really?
I'm the main bread winner for
my company too.
- You are?
- Yeah.
I guess they don't require much
to live then.
I think this is going to be
good today.
- Me too.
- I think it's going to be so much fun.
A lot of people have been calling me
an idiot these days too.
Hey!
Did you just call me an idiot?
No, that's not what I was saying.
[The subdued Idiot Couple,
Kwang and Park.]
- You pretty much just called me an idiot.
- But aren't you kind of like that?
[Hitting it on the mark?]
- Goofy.
- Goofy can be cute though.
- Yes.
- Then don't refer to yourself as an idiot.
- We're not idiots.
We're just a little different from others.
That's all.
- Kwang!
- Park!
- Cross!
I really want to win.
I'll make sure you do.
Let's win.
If we don't win,
let's not even keep in touch.
How can you say that?
- Sa Sa.
- Yeah, Ha Ha.
- When are you going to get married?
- I want to get married within the next year.
- Do you have a boyfriend?
- No, I don't.
- Anyone you're interested in?
- Kim Jong Kook.
- Want me to set you up with Jong Kook?
- I need you to really make it happen.
I'll give you a tip. The type
of women that Jong Kook likes is...
He likes women who are modest,
and feminine.
You know those women who
laugh like this?
[Learning how to be modest.]
[Meanwhile...]
[Jong Kook is currently getting to know
another modest woman.]
- I heard that you're really young?
- I was born in 1994.
- '94?
- Yes.
I made my debut in '95.
[The age difference is...]
Is that it?
We're here.
- Wow... look at that. Wow.
- Wow, look at that stream.
[Refreshing water stream.]
[And in there, is a
delicious chicken soup restaurant.]
We're the first to arrive!
[Ha Ha and Yuri also arrive.]
Chicken soup!
- I'm so hungry.
- Me too.
[While listening to the refreshing sound
of the water in the stream...]
[Chicken soup with all its nutrients...]
[Jae Suk, Kwang Gyu,
Jung Chi and Jung In also arrive.]
I need to get out too.
I'm so sorry.
[Real life couple's
consideration for each other.]
What are you doing?
Let's go.
Where do we have to go?
- Go into the room.
- In our own individual rooms?
What are we going to do in the room?
[Why...]
- Do we have to go in there too?
- Are we all going in here together?
Really?
[Everyone into the first room.]
- Come on in.
- We're all going in here?
- Everyone in the same room?
- What's going on in here?
Aren't we going to get our own
individual rooms?
He looks like duck restaurant owner.
[Shop owner with good humor.]
- Can we get three orders of the duck?
- Sure, whatever you want.
- Your duck...
- Your duck looks nice and plump.
[Feels like they're away
on a summer vacation...]
[Setting up thick mattresses
outside of their door?]
What did John Park and Kwang Soo
talk about in the car?
Even though John's very good looking,
his stare is still very much like Kwang Soo's.
[The idiot brothers?
Very similar vibe from the two...]
- He's the good looking idiot.
- And this one is the real idiot.
What?
I'm the real idiot?
[A lot of commotion going on
outside their door.]
During our drive here, Yuri and I
talked a lot about marriage.
We're going to pair her up with someone
in this room today.
- Are you older than me?
- Yes, I am.
I thought that Yuri was still
quite young.
I thought that she was
younger than me.
I'm being very sincere right now.
She really is a very good girl.
Want to share
some chicken breast together?
'Want to share
some chicken breast together?'
Want to have a protein shake together?
[She's trying to share interests with
health obsessed Kkuk.]
Protein.
[The setup is now complete.]
This place is really small.
[Taking up the smallest amount of space
in the crowded room.]
- I didn't even realize that you were in here!
- I didn't even see you there!
[Huh? A sudden sound of music playing?]
[What is that?]
Do you think that we should
get out there?
Hello, hello!
[What is this now?]
- That sounds like Suk Jin's voice.
- It does.
Your next game...
is vacate the room.
[Vacate the room?]
[Gold Bar Couple Race-
First mission- Vacate the Room.]
It's Vacate the Room.
- Vacate the Room?
Is that PD Hyung Taek?
That's Hyung Taek.
What's Hyung Taek doing?
[Flustered at the sudden
announcement by the DJ.]
Do you want to stop being friends with us?
Why are you doing this?
Please listen very carefully.
All of you will now have to shove
each other out of the room that you're in.
When the two members of any couple
are kicked out of the room
that couple will then be eliminated,
and that'll be the end of the first round.
However...
Everyone must keep dancing
when you hear the music playing.
You must keep dancing
while the music is playing
and once the music stops and
you hear the whistle sound
that is when you can start
shoving each other out.
Everyone, get up and dance!
[First up- A fun dance time!]
[Starting with, Kwang-Park couple.]
Hey, what are you doing?
What do you think you're doing?
[Idiot Brothers' dissonant dance moves.]
I haven't danced like this in so long!
Jung Chi and Jung In!
[Real couple's dance time.]
Kiss her!
Why are you telling us to kiss?
I can't dance like this!
Please stop the music!
Stop dancing!
Jung Chi and Jung In are trying to dance!
[Ha-Yuri Couple.]
[No sense of embarrassment.]
Yuri, dance by yourself.
[Complete chaos.]
[Her dance moves are on fire!]
[Dignified Monday Couple]
Kiss her!
[Want to?]
[Kwang Gyu's still got it!]
[His signature hip dancing moves.]
[Everyone together- Dance time!]
[Slowly getting to that time
for the music to stop playing...]
[Vacate the Room!]
I don't know what to do to whom!
[Everyone starting to shove each other.]
[I'm not vacating this room!]
I don't want to go!
[Everyone's target, Kwang Soo.]
[Wow... he escaped?]
[No way you're getting away!]
Why me?
Why is it me?
[Why is it always me?]
[Kkuk's ambush attack!]
[Yoo-piderman hanging on
with surprising defensive skills.]
[His hands!]
[Unable to stand up to joined forces of
Duck shop owner and Muscle Head Kkuk.]
[In that case, next up would be...]
[Kwang Gyu in hiding!]
[I'm the master!]
[Jae Suk and Kwang Gyu are eliminated!]
[Celebrate]
This is how I'm treated after
being called the master of variety?
I can't believe all of them
ganged up on me!
Hey! I've even been on The Healing Camp!
Is this how I'm going to
be treated?
All of the other surviving couples
may now come outside.
[All the surviving couples will now
move on to the next room.]
Please go into the next room.
[Into the next room?]
- This room's been upgraded!
- Why?
[Nostalgic feeling of yester-years.]
Everyone who survived the last round,
I sincerely congratulate all of you.
We will now take a guess on who will
be eliminated next.
Which couple do you think
will be eliminated?
Us.
- Yes.
- Yes, you're right!
[Knowing to nominate themselves?]
I'd like to ask this member of the crowd
who he thinks will be eliminated next.
- Hello,
- Yes, hello.
Who would you like to see
eliminated next?
The way I see it...
I'd like for it to be brawny Kim Jong Kook.
[Public citizen, Mr. Kim,
who seems to be unhappy with Kkuk.]
- Yes, I'd like to see him eliminated.
- And what about Ye Rim?
Ye Rim has to stay in the game.
- Why?
- Because she's pretty.
- Did you all hear that?
- Yes.
This man out here just told me that
he'd like to see Kim Jong Kook eliminated.
Everyone must dance.
Is that understood?
- Yes, we'll dance our hearts out!
- Start the music!
[Time for 1970-1980s nightclub!]
How about an individual dance time?
First up... Ye Rim!
Next up, Park Sang Myun!
A little more!
[The never changing Giraffe dance.]
[Dancing queen, Sa Yuri.]
Everyone go to the left!
To the left.
[Yoo Hyuk's recreation time.]
Come on!
Time for the train!
Train!
[Everyone full of excitement.]
Turn the other way!
Train!
Vacate the Room!
Everyone, let's look at one another
in the eyes.
[Indicate with their gaze
who they want to eliminate next?]
[Okay... time to vacate the room!]
Come on out!
Welcome!
Welcome, John Park!
Welcome, John Park.
[Giraffe is up next!]
[Desperately hanging on.]
[Falls out simultaneously.]
[Duck shop owner and the Giraffe
are simultaneously ousted.]
Okay, the duck shop owner...
Duck shop owner, you're still in the game!
You may go back inside.
[Kwang Soo and John Park
are eliminated.]
How did you get thrown out so easily?
- They all hate us.
- Excuse me?
- They really do hate us.
- No, they don't hate us.
Get yourself ready for revenge!
It's time for revenge!
Sincere congratulations to
all the surviving couples!
Once again,
sincere congratulations to all of you.
And let's continue this fire you've
got going on at the pension nightclub.
Pension nightclub!
It's time for you to move on
to the next pension.
We're going to move as a group.
Everyone grab onto each other's shoulders.
Hold onto each other's shoulders.
Okay, duck shop owner...
You're lasting surprisingly long in this game.
Okay, let's move on to the next room.
Choo choo!
[Jung Chi and Jung In are
eliminated next.]
[This is a techno nightclub?]
Which couple are you surprised to see
still in the game?
Ha Ha should've been the very first
to have been eliminated.
Who do you think?
I think Ha Ha is a jerk.
[Solidifying his status as the evil villain?]
I will tell you right now that
two couples will be eliminated this time.
- Two couples?
- What?
- Okay.
- Is everyone understood?
- Yes.
A round of applause for everyone!
Everyone sit down on the floor!
- Sit down!
- Stand up!
- Sit down.
- What is this?
[Acting like a brat to anger
all the couples.]
This is all part of the recreational games.
Raise your hands above your heads.
Link your hands together...
and put your hands behind your heads.
Sit down.
- What?
- You're making us workout!
- This is all just recreational.
- What are you doing?
[Remaining resolute and calling it
a part of the game...]
We will now start the music.
- Let's go!
[Time for the techno club dance.]
Let's all dance together!
[MC Hyuk having more fun
than anyone else.]
This is making me dizzy.
[This man is totally immersed
in the music.]
[Passionate MC Hyuk.]
What are you doing?
You're just supposed to be dancing.
Let's go!
- Already?
- The team with the two men aren't fair.
- It's not fair to the women.
- That's right.
Let's go!
Let's get those guys out first.
[A steamy love scene
right in front of their eyes.]
[Suk Jin and Sang Myun are eliminated!]
[Music starts to play again.]
One more couple.
Play the music again.
[Time to start dancing again
while keeping their eyes on each other.]
Both of you fell out at the same time.
[The two men livening up
the couple game.]
Please move over this way.
[The room door closes.]
Vacate the Room!
[Concentrating their attack on
brawny Kkuk.]
[But they're pushed back!]
[A bloody battle.]
[Gary gets kicked out.]
[Ha Ha free-falls out of the
room as well.]
Sa Yuri!
[An impossible situation in the room...]
If Sa Yuri gets kicked out of the room,
then Gary will stay in to the next round.
[Yuri's main objective is skinship with Kkuk
instead of staying in the game?]
What are you guys doing?
[Requesting a fair game between
the women?]
The women can duke it out
amongst themselves.
- Ji Hyo!
- Only one of them needs to get ousted.
[Only three women remain.]
[Wild beast, Yuri showing off her moves!]
[A fierce and bloody battle between
the three women!]
[Sa Yuri and Ji Hyo suddenly finding
themselves working together.]
That's right!
[Jong Kook and Ye Rim are eliminated.]
Sa Yuri, Ha Ha vs. Gary and Song Ji Hyo!
[Ha Ha, Sa Yuri and Gary, Ji Hyo-
Moving onto the final round!]
I'd like to reiterate the importance of
the men needing to meet the right women.
You're the best, Yuri!
- Ji Hyo!
- How could you have done that to Ye Rim?
[The last room is, Inkigayo Room.]
A gold bar will be given
to the winning couple.
- Really?
- Yes.
A gold bar.
This is the final round!
This is going to be a nice match.
[The start of the final round.]
[But first, it's time to dance!]
[Unidentifiable dance moves.]
[This is Kkuk's voice from
when he was in his teens!]
[Already grabbing his mic?]
[Time for Kkuk's live performance!]
It's a live performance!
[A lively atmosphere with the original
singer of the song performing live.]
[Live performance that they haven't
seen in a very long time.]
[Time is up.]
Live performance!
[He's still got it.]
[Time to determine
who the final couple will be.]
We have to grab him.
Ji Hyo!
[Fierce physical battle.]
The battle going on in there
is making the sky angry.
[A sudden downpour.]
[Everyone escaping the sudden downpour
under the roof overhang.]
What if my hair gets wet?
[A bloody battle paying no attention
to the weather outside.]
Who's it going to be?
Who is it?
[A competition that's impossible to predict.]
[Blank Ji with her brute strength
lifts Ha Ha up by his leg.]
- A little bit more!
- No!
[Ro-Ro being lifted up into the air
by their attack.]
What's taking so long?
[Moments before the fall.]
Welcome.
[Tenacious two couples.]
[Ha Ha is eliminated.]
We still don't know the outcome
since Yuri is still in there.
[Now it's a two against one battle.]
[Sa Yuri refusing with all her might.]
- She's kind of scary.
- Sorry, Yuri!
I'm sorry, Yuri!
Gary and Ji Hyo... win!
[Vacate the Room game-
Gary and Ji Hyo wins!]
Everyone must take care of their own gold.
You're all aware of how many bars you have?
Okay, the first place couple can take
two of these gold bars.
The couple that came in at second place
gets one gold bar.
- Ha Ha, this is awesome!
- What about third place?
Ji Hyo's going to hold onto
both the gold bars?
- Then Ha Ha will hold onto yours?
- Yes.
You can find your next location in the car.
You may go onto your cars.
[Off to the next location!]
Wow... look at this sudden weather.
It's really windy too.
- Are you okay?
- Of course. I didn't even do anything.
What do you mean,
you didn't do anything?
[A fascinating conversation of
a real life couple.]
But I had you around the waist.
- I tried to grab you, but you kept avoiding.
- You should've done a better job of leading.
- When did I do that?
- I was trying to grab you by the waist.
The way I see it, you two are fighting over
something that doesn't even warrant a fight.
- You were trying to avoid me.
- Should we fight too?
- You really need to get married.
- Why are you bringing that up?
[Suddenly feeling sorry
for his 47 year old friend.]
- This is all part of our love.
- That's what I'm saying.
Are you trying to tease me?
- Seriously, Jung Chi.
- He's just speaking the truth.
Couple Race.
- Go to 'H' swimming pool.
- H?
H?
[Off to the swimming pool...]
So we now have two gold bars.
I know.
We're one step ahead of the others.
That's what I'm saying.
Why are you beeping your horn at us?
Aren't you guys the owners of
a local restaurant?
- Huh? Aren't you restaurant owners?
- Yes, we are.
- Are you here for the duck soup?
Duck soup?
Come on in!
[King duck restaurant owner.]
- Is it the four of you?
- Yes.
Four!
We've got four customers.
[The rain continuing to pour down.]
[The point of their arrival is,
a pool at a traditional style pension.]
- What is this? This is scaring me.
- What is with the water guns?
Why are they holding those water guns?
- What is that?
- Water guns.
We're here on our honeymoon.
[Looks like they're here on
a group honeymoon?]
[Then is this a filial trip for his father?]
He hasn't been out in a while,
and he's enjoying all the fresh air.
- The sky looks so clear.
- Doesn't it?
When you tilt your head back like that...
all the light reflects off your head.
That's not completely untrue either.
Duck shop owner,
do you have a death wish?
- Seriously!
- Calm down over there.
When the lightening struck earlier
we all jumped.
John Park, did you understand
this whole exchange just now?
Yes.
I'm not that dumb.
- He wasn't calling you dumb.
- That's not what I meant.
Make him understand, Kwang Soo.
Explain to him what I was
trying to say.
Your next game is,
'All kill water gun quiz game.'
[All kill water gun quiz game.]
You have to name the couple that
you want to compete against
and the first couple to answer two questions
correctly in the quiz wins the game.
The couple that gets rid of all the other
teams in an 'all-kill' move wins the game.
- Which couple won the last game?
- We did.
Kang Gary and Song Ji Hyo can name
the first two couples to start off the game.
- But going first isn't always good.
- Hope it's not us.
You have to get rid of all the strong teams
in the beginning to make it easier later.
We want Jae Suk and Kwang Gyu
to go up against Suk Jin and Sang Myun.
We just have to eliminate them.
We have to eliminate them
from this game.
The subjects of the quiz is divided into
Love Quiz, and the Friendship Quiz.
Please come up with a slogan for your own
teams that you'll use to shout out..
What should we go with?
- What?
- What should we use?
Shiny bald head!
It's cute.
- We're going to go with Kwang-Gyu.
- What's Kwang-Gyu?
- Sparkle.
- How about 'Sparkle'?
- Okay, we'll go with 'sparkle'.
- Sparkle?
- We'll go with 'Quack Quack'.
- Let's just stick with Kwang-Gyu!
- But people don't really know my name yet.
- What are you talking about?
- Why are you getting so worked up?
- What do you mean, your name is unknown?
I'm telling you that
people don't know my name!
- Okay, we'll go with Kwang-Gyu.
- Let's go with Kwang-Gyu.
People still think that my name is,
'What are you doing, Father.'
[How absurd...]
- Are we going to go with Quack-Quack?
- Yeah, I like that.
Here's your first question.
We're going to do this.
- This is a friendship question.
- Friendship question?
You're all familiar with
the painter, Lee Jong Sup, right?
- Yes, of course!
- Yes, I do.
- Don't say anything out loud.
- It's a bull, not a cow.
- I love his paintings.
- It's not Lee Jung Sup?
- Isn't Lee Jung Sup a singer?
- No, that's Lee Jung Suk.
[That's singer, Lee Jung Suk.]
If this is how it's going to be,
then I'm pretty confident in this game.
The way I see it,
we're going to beat these two.
- Once these two are gone, it's all over.
- Okay, the painter, Lee Jong Sup.
When his friend was hospitalized
he had no money to help him out,
so he painted this as a gift instead.
- Which painting is this referring to?
- Lee Jung Sop painted it as a gift?
When his friend was hospitalized?
- Can we be the one to shoot them?
- Would you like to?
- Can we shoot them ourselves?
- Why are you doing that?
Ye Rim was so excited by the idea
that she ran over here to take her seat.
[Trading out with other shooters.]
Kwang-Gyu!
Rice!
He painted, rice!
[Shot in the face with the water gun.]
[Relentless water shower in the face.]
I'm too scared of the water gun
to even play this game.
- Don't answer too rashly.
- Quack-Quack.
Orange.
[The water gun bringing
huge laughter to the group.]
[The correct answer is, nectarine.]
Kwang-Gyu!
Apple.
[Firing down upon him for the
wrong answer.]
[Firing directly at the shiny Kyung Gyu.]
- Wow, they're so cruel.
- Kwang-Gyu!
[Back to the Kwang-Gyu team.]
- Apple!
- I just said that!
I just said that!
Quack-Quack!
Grapes!
Kwang-Gyu!
Mackerel!
Quack-Quack!
Melon!
[Not a melon...]
Kwang-Gyu!
Orange!
They said that earlier!
- Kwang-Gyu!
- What else is there?
- It's a three letter word.
- Kwang-Gyu!
Figs.
- Fig.
- How would he have eaten a fig?
- Quack-Quack!
- Let's discuss it first.
- I'm sure it was a rare food item.
- Guava.
- They already said that.
Kwang-Gyu!
Peach!
- Peach!
- That's right.
It's peach.
- Is it?
- Why didn't I think of that?
[Correct answer]
[Team Kwang-Gyu answers
the first question correctly.]
- I didn't know that.
- A three letter fruit.
We would like to choose...
Lee Kwang Soo and John Park.
[Ha Ha and Sa Yuri vs.
Lee Kwang Soo and John Park.]
We have to do this for real.
[Time to reveal the skills of the
Idiot Brothers.]
This is a love question.
In Europe, allowing women to
touch this...
Allowing women to touch this...
[What are you thinking about?]
I'm sorry!
- I'm sorry.
- In Europe...
Allowing women to touch this
is an expression of love...
[It's all your fault.]
[This is all Kwang Soo's fault?]
[What are they all thinking about?]
- You need to get your head on straight!
- What is he thinking about?
- Get your head on straight!
- Okay, I'm good.
What's the question again?
That is the question. What are women allowed
to touch in Europe as an expression of love?
Sa-Ha!
Nose!
Kwang-Park!
Armpit!
- Why would they touch the armpit?
- Sa-Ha!
Hair strands?
- Don't you even know the answer?
- Sa-Ha!
Nostril?
Kwang-Park.
Bottom of the foot.
Why are all the answers so dirty?
- Can you give us a hint?
- Here's your hint.
I told you that it's related to
Greece, right?
When you think of a Greek mythology,
what is the one symbol of masculinity?
- Sa-Ha!
- Kwang-Park!
- Kwang-Park was quicker.
- I was faster!
Beard.
[Correct answer]
- We got it.
- We're good.
Who's up next?
[Kwang-Park couple on fire-
They beat Jong Kook and Ye Rim as well.]
- Kang Gary and Song Ji Hyo!
- There you go.
[They choose Kang Gary and Song Ji Hyo
as their next opponents.]
Give us a lot of love questions
since Kang Gary is so full of love.
[Because Gary is an expert in love?]
With the meaning, 'Can't forget
whether asleep or awake'...
- Is it a four character idiom?
- Yes, it is.
What is the idiom that is often used to
describe the longing one feels for another?
- You have to think carefully about this.
- Monday.
What is it?
Blank-Gae!
Oh-Ri-Mu-Jong.
Why? A man could be totally
intoxicated with a woman.
- This is heard in sageuks a lot.
- Blank-Gae.
Bul-Chul-Joo-Ya?
Think about sageuks and what they say.
When they describe a young maiden.
Blank-Gae!
Oh-mae-bul-bak.
[Is he right?]
No, no!
You have to listen to it again.
- What did you say?
- Say it again.
- Say it one syllable at a time.
- It's already in the past.
- Say it again!
- Say your answer again.
Oh-mae-bul-bang.
[Bul-bang?]
Kwang-Park!
Oh-mae-bul-mang!
[Correct answer]
- Oh-mae-bul-bang?
- Ah... Oh-mae-bul-bang!
Oh my... bul-bang?
(bul-bang=Fiery room)
So the room's on fire?
[Almost had it.]
What is with you today, Kwang Soo?
You and John Park.
- What's with the Idiot Brothers?
- We're not the Idiot Brothers.
Our last couple,
the Jung-Jung couple!
- This is the final round.
- Final round.
I'd feel bad if we win this whole thing
just for beating one team.
What does it matter?
You just need to worry about winning.
Just think of winning, Jung Chi.
Then if they just win this round,
they win this whole game?
Kwang Gyu, is the sun bothering you?
- What?
- Are you dizzy?
- I think I ate too much, because I'm sleepy.
- Really?
I have food coma.
This is going to be a very
easy question.
I'm nervous.
Because of all the camaraderie that they've
shared since they were little kids
this person left many anecdotes that are still
remembered to this day. Who is this person?
- I know this one.
- Jung Jung!
Oh Sung and Han Eum?
[Correct answer]
[Gets the right answer in one shot!]
This is the quiz diva!
- This is the quiz diva.
- I can't believe she got it in one shot.
This is a survey question.
[Next up is a survey question.]
One hundred questions were asked to college
students in this recent TV program.
What is the one song that they hate to
hear the most being sung at a karaoke bar?
- I know this one.
- Kwang-Park.
You know the song, right?
- It's a two letter word.
- She's gone?
[Have to listen to the whole question.]
[Jung Chi getting a feeling from
the shot of water to his face?]
Jung Chi looks so ugly when the water
is being sprayed at him.
The number one song that the women hated
the most is, 'Confession' by Im Jae Bum.
- Yes, that's it.
- It's 'Confession'.
What is the one song that male students
hated hearing the most by the female students?
- I know this!
- Kwang-Park!
'I like strawberries'
by Pippi long stocking?
But... I actually agree with
him on that.
I like strawberries!
Berries, berries!
[Agreed that this song should
never be repeated.]
Lee So Ra loves to sing that song.
- I hate hearing that song.
- 'Gee' by Girls Generation?
- Don't you hate seeing that?
- Why would I hate seeing that?
If that's the way they look,
then it really may be a hateful sight...]
Why are you such a good shot?
Jung Jung.
Sistar's 'Now that you're gone'?
- Sing it for us.
- It's all the songs that you like.
What's wrong with him?
What's he doing?
[Giving a physical demonstration.]
Why are you doing that to me?
Stop it.
- She doesn't like to see it.
- I think it's a girl group song.
Kwang-Park.
IU's 'It's a good day'.
I bet that's it.
- Is that it?
- I bet that's it.
[Correct answer]
We did it!
[All the ladies, please refrain yourselves
from singing that song.]
- This is the final question?
- Everything's riding on this.
[The final question where
the victory is on the line.]
We'll show everyone how good we are.
I will show everyone!
- Here's your question.
- The final question.
A novel based on friendship.
In the book,
'My lime orange tree'...
I think I'm going to know this.
What is the name of the main character
in this book?
Kwang-Park!
Thomas.
Jung Jung!
Jerome?
Jung Jung.
Jonas?
I thought I've heard of that name before.
- What is it?
- That's not the name, is it?
It's a Brazilian name.
It's Brazilian.
Jung Jung.
Jiko?
[That's the name of
a Brazilian soccer player.]
He must really like soccer.
- I really like soccer too.
- I don't know any other names.
Kwang-Park!
ZeZe?
ZeZe!
[Correct answer]
I got up to the first part
of the name.
[The Idiot Brothers beat them all...]
The Idiot Brothers won?
We're the smartest ones here!
You guys are all idiots!
[Jung Chi and Jung In win one gold bar
for coming in at second place.]
- This is for the first place winners.
- They get two? Wow...
- We have to decide who'll keep this?
- Yes, you must decide.
You have to think carefully about it.
I'm sorry, but Ye Rim lost her gold.
[Jong Kook and Ye Rim's gold bar
is missing?]
She said she left it there earlier,
but now it's gone.
You never know.
Someone could've taken it.
[Did someone steal it?]
[Paying more attention to the
safe keeping of their gold.]
- You didn't have any gold earlier.
- Yes, I did.
Decide who's going to keep it,
and off to the next location.
[In just a moment, the truth about
the vanished gold will be revealed.]
[Rain starts to pour down again.]
[And ten minutes later,
the sun starts to blaze again.]
[Raining and not raining...
very strange weather.]
It is said that a tiger and a fox
get married on days like this.
Then that would mean that I'm
the one getting married?
What is this?
Give us our gold back right now.
We looked everywhere for it,
and it's really gone.
- Ye Rim lost it.
- If you lose it, then that's it.
It's really gone.
I told you earlier, didn't I?
Our staff members aren't going to
take care of the gold for you.
But I asked everyone if they put it
somewhere, and no one saw it.
Who is it?
Hurry up and confess.
[Detective Kkuk starting his investigation.]
Who is it?
Which one of you is it?
- When we were shooting the water gun earlier...
- That's where you lost it?
- Where did you put it down?
- Right where I was sitting.
Who sat down in our seat after us?
It was Ha Ha.
[The next team to take over their seats-
Ha Ha and Yuri.]
[Then that would mean that
Haroro took the gold bar?]
That's not what I mean,
but I'm sure that he stole the bar.
What do mean, I stole it?
We each had one before we even
started playing the game.
- No, you didn't.
- We won one at the last game.
It could be a ploy by Ye Rim too.
Ye Rim could be playing us.
- Do we need to go back to the courtroom?
- Let's take this to court.
- Which one of you took it?
- Since I'm a judge...
[Acting as the Judge from
'I Hear Your Voice'?]
Everyone needs to get themselves
an attorney!
Come on, seriously.
- What's wrong with you?
- He played a judge in a recent drama.
You need to be more cautious
with your own gold.
Since this is already water under the bridge,
let's just forget about it.
- He's acting suspiciously.
- It's you. Give it back.
- How many bars do you have?
- It really isn't me.
No, it's not me.
You can search for it on your own,
but we have to start the game.
[Where did the gold bar go?
But it's time to start the game.]
We're going to continue with
the couple games.
We're now going to play a
peculiar couple mission.
Peculiar mission?
That sounds like fun.
[This was a real mission that was played
in a world competition.]
Do you see the boxes that
are behind you?
You have to make a boat out of
those boxes.
[Make a boat out of cardboard boxes?]
[Rule: Must make a boat people can ride in
out of the cardboard boxes.]
- You have to make a boat out of the boxes.
- Touch the stomach?
You have 30 minutes to
make your boats.
The first team to arrive at the finish line
will be the winners of this mission.
You have to get to the line in the boat?
Both of us?
- Both of you.
- He's going to sink our boat.
- It's more than possible to do it.
- It's possible?
- A boat out of those cardboard boxes?
- This is what we make it out of?
Why don't you give it a try?
If you can make it like this,
three Sang Myun's can ride it no problem.
If you can make it that well,
it'll be a cinch.
By utilizing the tape and the boxes
that you see behind you.
You don't necessarily need to
make it in that shape.
[Make a rowboat by utilizing the
cardboard box, tape and saran wrap.]
- Okay, let's get started.
- You've got 30 minutes.
[Time to make the cardboard boats!]
It doesn't have to look like that boat.
- No, it doesn't.
- It just has to get us to the finish line.
That's right.
[Where to even begin?]
Come on, let's do this.
You're good at things like this.
- Come on.
- I don't know if I can do this.
You're good at things like this.
Running Man has high standards.
I noticed that Running Man tends to be
pretty scientific.
- We have to do a good job with the cutting.
- The cutting?
[Jung Chi being meticulous with the cutting
by using the ruler and the blade.]
Even if we can't make it that well,
let's at least try to appear smart.
[A smart looking boat?]
Even if it doesn't float.
[Meanwhile, Jong Kook and Ye Rim's box
is already starting to look like a boat.]
Yes, the boat bottoms are very taut.
In that case, I think we need to angle it
instead of making it look too boxy.
[Mr. Capable moving right along
and building the boat as expected.]
Wow, look at that.
Awesome!
- Isn't he good?
- What the heck?
- Come on, Yuri.
- Let's trade teams.
You go over there.
I want to ride on this boat with Jong Kook.
I want to ride with him.
[Meanwhile]
[Hm...]
[Kwang... Soo...]
Why isn't this sticking?
[That's because you didn't
stick it on right.]
We're going to have to wrap this around.
[The quiz winners who no longer
have anything left to say.]
We have to secure this somehow.
Should we just wing it?
Why isn't this sticking?
[Will these guys be able to complete
it on time?]
[What kind of a boat
will the Monday Couple come up with?]
Should we build it like a raft?
Like a raft?
- We can cut it up and make it thick.
- Really thick?
That's not bad.
That's not a bad idea.
We can build it like a raft.
So we agree, right?
- Okay, let's do it.
- You can't change your mind, okay?
[Monday Couple agrees to build
their boat like a raft.]
[Planning on twining the boards together
like they would with wood pillars.]
- Let's put the bigger pieces on the bottom.
- That's right! My Ji Hyo is so smart!
[Monday Couple working in sync.]
If you break it apart like that,
it's going to leak.
- Why would it leak?
- You don't think it'll leak?
- No.
- We'll take care of it ourselves.
- We know what we're doing.
- You're building it like a raft?
No, we're not.
Don't you think raft is a pretty good idea?
- What are you doing?
- Why are you copying our idea?
The most important thing is to make sure
that it's built really sturdy.
Let's make it really strong.
We have to show them what we're made of.
[Taping up the boat very securely first.]
How about we leave it like this for the back
and angle it a bit for the front?
I don't think there's a single person here
who knows how to make this.
Is this even going to float?
[Taping it over and over to make sure
that the boat is built strong.]
You think the two of you can ride
in this little thing?
Of course.
Why wouldn't we be able to?
[It doesn't seem very feasible...]
- This is just our foundation.
- You have to cut a bit more here.
[No way...]
We have to block this over here.
Let's tape it real well.
Want to tape up this whole thing
and cut a big hole over here?
Okay.
And we can add that box on
and have it shaped like a car.
- Okay! Deal!
- Deal!
- Okay, we got it.
- Were going to win this.
- We're going to win it.
- We have to tape it really well.
- We're going to have to tape the whole thing.
[And the one team who doesn't even
have an idea of what to do yet.]
What is this supposed to be?
A refrigerator box?
Seriously.
First, we're going to have to
block this end off.
[Kwang Gyu suggesting that they build
the frame of the boat first.]
[And Jae Suk suggesting that they make
sure the boat won't leak first.]
[No matter what is said, Jae Suk is too
afraid of the boat leaking and sinking.]
- That's just a waste.
- Just stick these two together first.
- This is falling apart.
[The two men thinking in
two totally different directions.]
That really hurt!
Why are you so weak, Kyung Gyu?
Here, I got it.
Let's pull this up, and tape it together.
[The two men with the least
bit of progress made.]
- From the way I see it..
- Yeah?
- I'm betting 100% that it's going to sink.
- No, it's not going to sink.
- It's going to sink.
- No, it's not.
[Will it?]
[In 30 minutes.]
[Will their boat float in water?]
[So meticulous!
Jung Chi is still measuring and cutting.]
Just wing it.
We're the only team using
a ruler right now.
Looking cool on the water is important.
The speed doesn't really matter.
[Jung Chi and Jung In with two
extremely different personalities.]
[They just need to fold it now.]
I'll do it, I'll do it.
I think I can do it with my knees.
See?
It worked.
- But you made it crooked!
- That's no big deal.
We can't have this.
[Taking on the shape of a boat.]
We need to do it like them.
Theirs is starting to look like a boat.
- Theirs is looking good.
- You have to be mindful of the design.
- That's pretty good.
- Don't look!
Okay, I won't.
[Very protective about keeping the
secrecy of his own project.]
They're like corporate spies.
What do you mean, corporate spies?
It must be nice for Jung In to
have Jung Chi.
- To have such a dependable boyfriend.
- You think?
Right?
- Kwang Soo!
- Yes, Jae Suk?
- I guarantee that yours will sink.
- No, it won't.
Did you guys build a bookshelf?
- It's not a bookshelf.
- This is a bookshelf.
[At a close look, it does look like a
dining table/bookshelf?]
- Then is it a dining table?
- No, it's not a dining table.
Is this where you eat your meals?
[What will this turn out to be?]
You're doing great!
Look at you go!
[Making the boxy boat sturdy by
wrapping the whole thing in tape.]
There you go.
You're doing great.
- Wrap it.
- Just wrap it?
Keep wrapping it.
Wrap it around like 50 times.
[Now wrapping it up. Not wanting
a single drop of water to get in.]
Let's just wrap the whole thing.
Keep wrapping it until the time is up.
[Their boat really is looking too small.]
You can ride in that one, and I'll
make another space for me to ride in
and we can just connect
the two parts together.
- Don't you think? This could work.
- Okay.
[Sang Myun in the big box,
and Suk Jin in the little box.]
[Time to begin building Suk Jin's box.]
- Should I try going in there?
- Get in there.
I think we're good.
There you go.
[Gary and Ji Hyo are wrapping up all their
boxes together in a raft style.]
Here it comes.
[Every move they make is in
perfect harmony.]
[Monday Couple- three years in the making.]
That's good.
- I'm so sorry.
- No, it's okay.
I think this is pretty good.
Let's try getting on it.
[First couple to complete their boat.]
- Doesn't it feel safe?
- It does feel safe.
- Be careful, Jung In.
- What?
- Be careful, okay?
- Okay.
That hurts.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah, I'm okay.
Be careful.
That knife scares me.
- You okay?
- What?
- Wear my gloves.
- No, it's okay.
- Is your head okay?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
You guys really care for each other.
Seriously.
We just need to coat this thing
now, okay?
Why aren't you answering me?
Okay?
What do you mean, okay?
This thing looks like it's going to sink.
It's not going to sink.
[Seemingly happy with how it looks.]
- We need to tape the insides.
- We need to finish the outside first.
Okay, Honey?
[Back to the waterproofing vs.
securing the structure.]
Have you never built anything before?
We have to make sure
that it's balanced first.
- Come on, Mister!
- It won't be balanced otherwise.
[Not a fit, not a fit...]
- This isn't going to work.
- You and I are not a good fit.
- We can worry about the interior later.
- Hang on, we have to hurry.
Stop worrying about the
inside so much.
We can do that once we're in there.
- Seriously, Mister!
- Just stop with the taping.
[Jae Suk is continuing with his
waterproofing efforts.]
- We have to do this part too.
- We have to make sure it's balanced first.
Why are you so obsessed with that?
[Time to start wrapping.]
There you go.
- Ouch, that hurts.
- You come over this way.
You go that way.
- Here, grab it.
- Are you talking to me in casual speech?
[Bickering about every little thing.]
[Jong Kook and Ye Rim complete
building their rowboat.]
[Kwang Gyu coming over to take a look
at their boat.]
Yours looks very similar to ours.
Ours is a boxy looking shape,
and yours isn't that much different.
It has to look like a boat.
- How did you do the bottom?
- Stop looking, Kyung Gyu.
Stop looking at our boat.
What are you doing?
Why are you trying to ruin our boat?
[Try to ruin other people's boats since
he's not happy with his own.]
- What's going on here?
- What?
- They made it very sturdy.
- Isn't it great?
[Fails at even his attempt to ruin the boat.]
- Don't even come near it.
- You now have ten minutes left.
[Ten minutes before the time is up.]
- that thing?
- That's going to just float.
No, it's going to flip over.
We have to consider this our
lifeboat as we build it.
Let's think that we're trying to
survive in the amazon.
Wow, I don't think I've ever worked
this hard on anything in my life before.
Hurry up and cut out the holes.
[The car concept-
Time to cut out the driver's seat.]
We got the holes!
- Park.
- Yes, Kwang Soo.
Our looks the stupidest.
It's okay.
[Giving up on the design of their boat.
Kwang-Park concentrating on the usability.]
- We have to do it on the inside too.
- Okay.
You think you're so smart.
Sorry.
[Jung Chi sweating profusely in his efforts.]
What's wrong with you, Kwang Gyu?
[The builder collapsing on the ground
before the boat is even complete.]
Kwang Gyu, are you okay?
What's wrong?
You just stay down there.
I'll finish up the boat.
You just lay down.
- I'll finish this up.
- Finish it up.
- You have to get me my revenge.
- Okay, Kwang Gyu.
[Time is almost up!]
- I think it's pretty much done, right?
- Yes, I think it's done.
If this thing will float, then it's all over.
[Each team giving their boats
one last once over.]
- What if it sinks?
- If it sinks, then we're...
[What will happen to Monday Couple's
specially built raft?]
- This thing had better float.
- Are you guys done?
[Will Jung Chi and Jung In's boat
float on water?]
The usability is more important
than how it looks.
But you guys did a good job of
making it look like a boat, didn't they?
- It'll float. I'm sure it'll float.
- You sure?
[We'll soon find out, right?]
Their boat looks really good.
Just think of this as a coffin.
- This isn't a boat. It's a coffin.
- It's a coffin?
- Our boat is a coffin.
- This is our coffin.
One, two, three spots.
It's a coffin.
- I hope it works out for you guys.
- Yes.
I'm sure it'll work fine.
[Kwang-Park]
That looks so cool.
[The point is to make sure it floats...]
Thank you everyone for all
your hard work.
[Everyone worked so hard and
earnestly at building their boats!]
Each team will go separately
and we'll time how long it takes you
to get to the finish line.
In the case where none of the teams
make it to the finish line
we will declare the team with
the furthest distance as the winner.
Okay, first contestants,
please come on out.
[Box train concept-
Linking two boxes together as one.]
[Cardboard box train-
Contestants number 1: Suk Jin and Sang Myun.]
There are two separate compartments.
It's going to sink as soon as I get in it.
- I'm afraid of it sinking too.
- I don't think it's going to sink.
I don't think it's going to sink.
[Will this boat be able to withstand
Sang Myun's weight?]
I don't think it's going to sink
on its way to the finish line.
[It just sunk down a bit,
but it didn't sink all the way!]
What if it sinks along the way?
[Most crucial thing to do now
is to make sure to balance it right.]
Water!
The water is leaking in everywhere!
[It's leaking?]
[One wrong move,
and the boat is going to go down!]
Hurry up and get going!
[The only means to surviving this
is to get on their way quickly!]
The boat is already starting to
get soaking wet.
[Will the boat be able to move forward?]
[Aren't you going to go?]
It's moving!
[A fascinating sight to see
Sang Myun seated in the boat.]
[Inching forward bit by bit
while half submerged in the water.]
[Staying afloat is amazing enough, but it's
actually moving with Sang Myun in the back!
Wow, how is that even possible?
- It's actually pretty fast.
- How is that even moving?
Watching them is making me nervous.
[The amazing power of
the cardboard box boat!]
You're doing great.
[Already past the halfway mark!]
One, two!
[Hm... is it sinking even more?]
Is that thing a submarine?
[Just hang on... just a little bit more!]
[Almost to the finish line!]
It's just amazing that we're
even moving.
[Suk Jin and Sang Myun's boat
crosses the finish line!]
[You did great, cardboard boat!]
- It's sinking pretty low.
- Its almost all the way under water.
[All they have to do now
is to get off the boat...]
You have to keep the balance.
The water is seeping in!
Keep the balance!
Balance!
[Falling into danger after having
crossed the finish line!]
How did this thing float and get us here?
[Even they themselves are amazed that
they made it in their cardboard box boat.]
That's amazing.
Okay, next team, please come on out.
[Next contestants in the
cardboard box boat race.]
[Contestants number two-
Jung Chi and Jung In.]
That looks very much like a boat.
[JJ Boat- Contestants number 2-
Jung Chi and Jung In.]
The most beautiful boat in this world!
That really is like the Love Boat.
[Jung Chi and Jung In helping to
carry down their love boat to the water.]
[They really did a great job
building the boat!]
You can take that on the Han River.
- It's really nice!
- Are you sitting across from each other?
[Oh my... this couple is too cute
sitting across from each other!]
Those two are way too cute together.
This is how we keep the romance alive.
[Jung Chi and Jung In's boat
looking very sturdy.]
But he looks too weak to row the boat.
[The boat looks like it'll advance well
as long as it's rowed properly.]
[The love boat- Start!]
Wow!
What the heck is that?
[Zipping along the water!]
[Advancing easily without having to
put any strain in rowing the boat.]
It going too fast!
It's kind of scary!
[Just like the other mentioned,
it really is a boat!]
[Already past the halfway mark!]
[Advancing along without any hesitation.]
- It looks really stable.
- Wow, he did a great job.
This is way too easy.
[The perfect boat is a result of
Jung Chi's meticulousness.]
[Crosses the finish line already!]
Already?
- Can we just stay on the boat?
- We'll come back later.
[Bet they broke the record!]
[So nice!]
- Are they coming back?
- Are they coming back here?
Wow... are they on a date
during the filming, or what?
[Jung Chi and Jung In having forgotten that
they're in the middle of taping the show.]
[Romancing each other on their boat.]
['This is how we keep the romance alive.']
[The cardboard boat floats on water,
and love floats in our hearts.]
How much for a ride in that boat?
Do you have a duck boat?
Actually, there's one here.
[Round-trip love boat ride is now over.]
You two look great together.
You two are enough to give me
goosebumps.
[Gary practicing his rowing skills
with every chance that he gets.]
You just need to follow my lead.
Okay!
[Contestants number three-
Jong Kook and Ye Rim.]
[Contestant number four-
Ha Ha and Yuri.]
Your boat is sinking!
You're sinking right now.
- The back of your boat is sinking!
- No, it's not.
Let's go!
- It's going!
- How is that thing going?
[The teams start off at a
similar speed.]
You have to row a little more on the left.
[Huh? The boat is turning?]
Doesn't the boat feel like it's sinking?
This is fun!
Are we on the Han river?
[Cautious style-
And forceful style.]
[Ha Ha and Yuri getting ahead
bit by bit.]
Wow... Ha Ha's pretty fast.
They're going to beat them.
[Which team will get the better record?]
[Ha Ha crosses the finish line
with this experienced rowing skills.]
[By the split of a hair,
Jong Kook and Ye Rim also crosses the line!]
- Aren't we awesome?
- We're awesome!
- Yes!
[Kkuk on the other hand is disappointed
with their record.]
It's not the boat that went,
but Jong Kook who made the boat go.
[Highly anticipated contestants number five-
Jae Suk and Kwang Gyu.]
Which apartment are you guys
moving into?
[Refrigerator box/Coffin boat-
Contestants number 5- Jae Suk and Kwang Gyu.]
I guarantee 100% that
their boat is going to capsize.
It really looks awful.
I bet they won't make it past 10m.
Are you ready?
You look really scared, Kwang Gyu.
I feel like you guys are going to
capsize the moment you get going.
[Looks like their boat is going to capsize
the moment the helpers let go.]
- Okay, we're good.
- They're not going to make it.
- Why kind of an oar did you give us?
- Our oar just broke!
[It's a sight to behold.]
The way I see it, I guarantee
that we won't be in last place.
They can't even get balanced.
[Making another attempt at it after
having switched out their oars.]
They're going to sink.
- Everyone, keep your eyes on their boat!
- This really is going to be our coffin.
They're never going to make it.
Let's see how well they do.
[Are they even going to be
able to get on their way?]
- You're leaning to the left.
- Start!
[Start!]
One, two!
What the heck?
[It's quite fast!]
One, two!
[Totally unexpected.]
How can this be?
[Rowing as if their lives depended on it.]
[Even funnier because they're moving fast
when they've already been discounted.]
[If we stop... we'll sink!]
What is this?
[Determined not to fall in,
they speed along to the finish line!]
[Jae Suk and Kwang Gyu
crosses the finish line!]
[What are they doing at the finish line?]
[The refrigerator box capsizes
the moment it completes its duty.]
[But they still did it!]
- Good job!
It's a boat that capsizes if you stop,
and will stay upright if you keep going.
That was good.
- Why did you kiss me?
- That was good.
- Even though everyone mocked us...
- I know!
- But we did it!
- They called it our coffin!
What are you doing, Father!
[What was their record?
You'll soon find out!]
[Monday Couple still practicing
their rowing skills.]
One, two!
Pull it through to the end! There you go.
We got it!
[This is why they say that you should never
learn how to drive from your boyfriend.]
[Monday Raft-
Contestants number 6- Gary and Ji Hyo.]
Nice long strokes, okay?
- Nice long strokes, okay? Fighting!
- I said, okay!
Stop nagging!
[Kwang-Park Boat:
Contestants number 7- Kwang Soo, John Park.]
Set, go!
[Go!]
[Both teams start off at a good speed!]
One, two!
No!
Slow down, Kwang Soo!
[Monday Couple in perfect sync
from all their practicing.]
They're fast.
Look at me and follow my lead.
[But... where are Kwang Soo
and John Park?]
[Gary and Ji Hyo moving right along.]
Gary's rowing is slower than Ji Hyo's.
Strong pull!
More! More!
[Gary and Ji Hyo cross
the finish line at top speed!]
You're such a nagger!
One, two!
[This is what they've been doing...]
[They keep turning towards the sides
because of their inability to get in sync.]
[Kwang Soo's the only one rowing
at top speed.]
Stop rowing.
Just stop.
[Now they're going backwards?]
[Nice skills.]
You guys are going backwards!
[They finally start going
in the right direction.]
[Going at top speed-
And going at a leisurely speed.]
This is so annoying!
I'm so annoyed!
What are you doing?
And what did you just say to me?
[Getting back on their way after
getting back in sync with one another.]
[How can they be so much like
their namesake?]
[Kwang Soo's rowing direction is...]
- Why aren't you rowing?
- You're rowing way too fast.
- Don't give up!
- You're rowing too fast.
One, two!
They should just go backwards.
You guys are going backwards again.
One, two!
[The boat finally starting to move forward
with Kwang Soo losing his stamina.]
[Really took a lot of effort to get here.]
[Kwang Soo and John Park
finally crosses the finish line.]
[Even though it wasn't a slow boat,
their rowing was... what was their record?]
[Time to reveal the record
for all seven couples!]
I hope we made it in the top three!
I really want to win a gold bar!
Kim Jong Kook and Ye Rim's
record was 2 minutes and 5 seconds.
- What did you say?
- Did they come in at seventh place?
What about this team?
Lee Kwang Soo and John Park's
record was 1 minutes and 58 seconds.
[Lee Kwang Soo and John Park-
1 minute and 58 seconds!]
- Kwang!
- We didn't come in at last place!
- Cross!
You have to say 'Park' first,
you dummy!
In fifth place is...
Ha Ha and Sa Yuri with
one minute and 36 seconds.
In fourth place is,
Ji Suk Jin and Park Sang Myun.
They came in at one minute 35 seconds.
- This is nerve wrecking!
- Im so nervous!
Now there are only three teams left.
[Who placed first of these three teams?]
Jung Chi and Jung In's team...
Their record is...
50.65 seconds.
[Jung Chi and Jung In with
a record of 50.56 seconds.]
Team Gary and Ji Hyo...
with a record of 50...
50...
50.76 seconds.
[Gary and Ji Hyo with a record of
50.76 seconds.]
Team Yoo Jae Suk and Kim Kwang Gyu.
42.25 seconds.
[Jae Suk and Kwang Gyu break
the record with 42.25 seconds!]
[Jae Suk and Kwang Gyu win with
42.25 seconds!]
[The winners of the first ever
cardboard boat race- Jae Suk and Kwang Gyu!]
[Second place- Jung Chi and Jung In.
Third place- Gary and Ji Hyo.]
Any other time, I'd clap for
the first place winners
but it's just absurd that they came in
at first place with a boat like that.
They won first place
in their refrigerator box!
[The will to survive is definitely
more crucial than the tool itself.]
[All the couples having arrived
at the final camping location.]
[They still haven't found
Ye Rim's missing gold bar.]
Who took our gold!
- Since I'm the judge...
- What is it was Kwang Gyu?
Whomever took our gold is a thief!
There's no respect in that situation!
- Am I right or am I right?
- You are being so rash!
- It's not me.
- We don't know who took it right now.
[Why does Jung In have four gold bars?]
Hang on a second.
Why do you have four gold bars?
Hang on a second here.
[Jung Chi and Jung In should only
have three gold bars?]
I was told to steal other people's gold
when we started the race earlier.
[Don't you remember?]
You all have to take care of your own
gold bars throughout the day.
If you lose it, or have it stolen from you,
we can't be responsible for that.
[Then it means... that we can steal it?]
[So she actually stole it!]
- She's a bad person!
- I can't believe you did that!
- She's a thief.
- I didn't take you to be like that.
The thing that scared me the most...
was when she threw away Ye Rim's
bag in the bathroom garbage can.
[Admitting to the truth?]
I was too scared to even say anything.
You stole our gold,
and threw away the bag in the trash?
You just took the gold out of there?
- She's one scary person.
- I didn't do anything illegal.
- What I did wasn't illegal.
- He did tell us that in the beginning.
[Can't say anything since it was stated
in the rules at the beginning of the race.]
- She's my teammate, but she scared me
- So I can just take it back then?
[Mr. Capable starting to get angry!]
Then I can just take it back?
- I can just take it from others?
- Counsel!
[It's too late to take it now... Only the gold
they already have will be counted.]
In that case,
these two teams are tied in first place.
[Jung Chi, Jung In and Gary, Ji Hyo
both win for having four gold bars!]
[A special mission for these two teams?]
What is it that you want us to do
with these scheme artists?
The teams who did not come in at first place
must give back their gold bars.
[All the other teams who didn't come in at
first place must give back their gold bars.]
[Say... what?]
- What kind of a filthy rule is that!
- What are you doing!
[You had to win to keep the gold...]
Listen to how my hoarse my voice sounds
from trying to protect it all day.
The race is now all over.
The couples with the most number of
gold bars at the moment are
the Monday Couple,
and Couple Jung Chi and Jung In.
Each team must now decide
whether they want to take the gold...
or stay with their partner.
You must choose between the two.
[Both teams must now decide whether
they want to keep the gold or their partner.]
[The ultimate decision.
Will it be the gold, or your partner?]
You will each be given a minute to think
about your decision in your own tent.
In the case where both members of
a team chooses their partner
they may not be able to keep all the gold
that they've won thus far
but they will be able to verify and maintain
their true love that they have for each other.
And in the case where one chooses the gold,
and the other chooses their partner...
the person who chose the gold on that team
will take all the gold for themselves.
In the case where both members choose
their greed for the gold...
they will have to turn in all the gold
that they've won thus far.
[If they both choose the gold,
all the gold must be given back.]
[Will it be the gold, or their partner?]
[These two couples...
what is their heart's desire?]
Their misfortune is our happiness.
[Non-winners unhappy about having
become the bridesmaids.]
How about we get the gold
if they don't win it?
[Jong Kook suggests that they get the gold
if the winning couples loses theirs?]
- Don't you think so?
- We can all split it.
If that happens,
like Kim Jong Kook suggested...
In the case where they both choose gold,
and they have to turn their gold back in...
then I will divide up the gold
amongst all of you.
[Even if one couple loses their gold,
it means gold for the loser teams!]
- We need this once in a while.
- Gold! Gold!
We will first go with the Monday Couple.
[Time to check where the Monday Couple's
hearts stands.]
[That woman, and that man...
Will be it the gold, or each other?]
I assure you that they both
chose the gold.
Gold!
[Just... what did their hearts choose?]
I want you, Kang Gary!
[Three years of going back and forth
in their love affair...]
[The man and the woman having relied on
each other like a lover and a friend.]
[Just what is inside their hearts right now?]
He's going to choose gold.
[Gary chooses Ji Hyo!]
- What the heck?
- You should've chosen gold.
It's been awhile since we've been
coupled up like this.
You should've been honest
with yourself.
I know that she wrote down gold,
and we can just split the stash later.
[Having prepared himself for a situation
where Ji Hyo would've chosen the gold?]
- That's true.
- You guys don't know what it's like.
You have no idea how hard we worked
together today building that boat.
It felt like we went back to the way
we used to be two years ago.
You guys don't know what
that feels like.
- Kiss her! Kiss her!
- What do you mean, kiss?
You were asking me about
French kissing in the car earlier too.
Ji Hyo's answer?
[Gary chose his partner...
What did Ji Hyo's heart tell her?]
I...
Are they saying that they're going to
start dating for real now?
- I can't even stand this.
- Gold?
No, it's her partner.
Kang Gary?
- What is this?
- What are you guys doing?
You're just playing with me,
aren't you?
Show us what your answer is!
What are you doing?
[In her heart is...]
[But still...
Monday Couple is the best!]
[My partner, Kang Gary.]
[Ji Hyo also chooses her partner!]
[Monday Couple treasures each other
more than the gold!]
Why did you do that?
- You should've chosen the gold!
- I thought you were going to choose the gold!
We should've split it!
What were you thinking!
I thought you were going to
pick the gold!
- You two are beautiful together.
- Let's do it over.
[At least one of you had to have chosen
the gold to have won anything...]
[The loser teams are too happy at the
winning couple losing their gold.]
Gold!
But it still makes me happy to know
where your heart stands.
Gary, you won something much more
precious than gold.
[Time to find out what Jung Chi
and Jung In chose.]
I'm positive that they chose gold.
Guarantee that they chose gold.
I bet it'll start off with
one of them choosing the gold.
We have to start off with the gold.
I'll start.
[Real life couple, Jung Chi and Jung In.
Will it be the gold or their love?]
[Their love for each other that's
been growing all these years...]
[Even through all of their bickering,
their hearts are full of their love.]
[That man's selection is...]
[Gold]
[Jung Chi chooses gold!]
Jo Jung Chi!
The thought of gold made me so happy
so I even drew a picture of it.
Gold!
[If Jung In also chose the gold,
it'll be time to celebrate!]
Get ready to celebrate!
[Then her selection is...]
[Will it be gold, or love?]
[Partner]
[Jung In chooses her partner!]
In that case...
Jung Chi and Jung In can keep
all the gold that they've earned today.
[Jung Chi and Jung In get to
keep all four of their gold bars!]
There was one more rule that
has been set from the beginning.
[Rule that's been set from the beginning?]
The best selection that could've been
made in this couple race today...
was for both partners to
choose each other.
- That was our rule from the beginning.
- Is there a golden turtle or something?
You will each receive twice the amount of
gold that you've earned today.
[Monday Couple will each receive twice the
amount of gold that they've earned today.]
[The ultimate winners are-
Monday Couple for having chosen each other.]
[Today was a love race, after all.]
So Gary gets two bars since he had
possession of one bar.
And since Ji Hyo had three in her possession,
she wins a total of six bars.
You knew it all along, didn't you?
You greedy person!
[Starting their bickering all over again.]
Half of that is mine!
Ji Hyo always gets so lucky with her gold.
This is putting Jung Chi and Jung In
in a very weird position.
[Putting Jung Chi and Jung In
in an awkward position.]
Congratulations for being the only one
to have chosen gold over your partner.
- That's our Monday Couple.
- Monday Couple.
Kiss her!
- Stop telling them to kiss!
- If that's what you want, I'll do it.
[Having a partner...
is more precious than real gold.]
Subtitles by DramaFever
He's not even human.
[What if... Running Man were
to be ranked?]
Welcome to...
Running Man Survivor Game.
[A desperate battle for their survival
is about to start.]
Don't come here!
[Next Week's Running Man-
The Ranking.]