[The real battle will unfold.]
[Passing the borders of
the variety world into reality.]
[Only one victor can walk out
of the battle ring.]
[The Wolf and the Lamb]
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Wangsimi Station]
I love Wangsimi!
I'm tired!
What is all this back here?
Are we voting for something?
I know that you all must be very tired
from having ran for the past 168 episodes.
So we have prepared the opening in front
of the famed 'Road of Longevity'.
- Ah, this is what it is?
- That's the road?
[A place reputed to be good for your health
due to the phytoncides.]
This guy might live a long life, but the
people around him have a short life span.
He doesn't know that about himself.
He stresses out the people around him.
- What are we doing today?
- You will be having guests on the show today.
- I think I know who it is.
- One person's been talking about it for days.
[One person... is probably
someone they're familiar with?]
- Hello.
[A debonair elder who keeps on walking
with his eyes fixed straight ahead.]
- No, he's not our guest.
- But he was so cool!
Your guests for the day are...
two people who we wish will have a
very long career in the music field.
- They're musicians?
- Yes.
Let's invite the first musician out here.
[The first musician makes her appearance.]
It's a girl.
We can tell that it's an Idol.
- Be careful of the steps.
- She looks somewhat familiar to me.
[Taking cute little steps towards them holding
a fan with the picture of a lamb on it.]
Who is it?
['I'm now a young woman', IU.]
- IU!
- Yes!
[Garnering the attention from
all the male students.]
- Her hair color threw me off.
- Yes, I dyed my hair.
- You look amazing with that hair color.
- You look like a grown up woman now.
- You've gotten so much prettier.
- What do you mean? She's always been pretty.
Why are you looking at IU
as a woman?
She is a woman.
There you go again!
I've always thought of her as a kid sister,
but she looks more like a woman now.
- She's grown up a lot.
- She used to look like a pretty kid.
I know what you mean.
Even the last time when we played soccer.
- Even the way she's behaving now.
- She never used to do things like that.
She's really hamming it up
for the camera right now.
Her hair wasn't even falling on her face,
but she keeps pushing it back.
- Why isn't the other guest here yet?
- Who is it?
He says he's the face of SBS
with his appearances on all the shows.
Who is it?
[Hiding his face behind the fan
with the picture of the wolf on it.]
[A musician hidden behind a
cloud of mystery.]
- You were right.
- Can't you just tell by his walk?
I saw the back of his head.
I think I know who it is.
[A very unique hairstyle from the back.]
[Even the crowd may be able to
recognize him from the briefest glance.]
[Along with his cup of morning coffee.]
Why is he acting like that?
Let's just have IU be our only guest today.
I see him three days out of the week.
I knew it was going to be him.
Just go back up the stairs.
Why are you here?
Why did you come on the show?
Why would you come on our show?
[Not the most welcomed guest
on the show.]
This is a good opportunity for you guys.
What are you talking about?
'Ha-Myung-Kook'...
Wow, it's been a really long time.
['Ha-Myung-Kook' together again
for the first time in a long time.]
[The trio that used to bring the audience
a lot of laughter during the 'X-Man' days.]
So you remember.
[Just like the way they used to dance
back in those days.]
- I remember now!
- It really has been a long time.
Why do you have guys like
these on the show?
What are you talking about?
[Morning threats that go hand in hand
with his morning coffee.]
First of all,
this will be an individual race today.
- Really?
- Individual?
- You will all be competing on your own.
- Okay.
But, before you get
to the final individual round
you will be competing in teams
during the course of the day.
- I'll now announce your teams.
- Okay.
For old times' sake,
the first team will be, 'Ha-Myung-Kook'.
- Wow!
- Seriously?
'Ha-Myung-Kook' is back together again?
'Ha-Myung-Kook'
is really going to be a team?
This could be an opportunity for us.
There's no need for us to be worried.
- We're all set now.
- Get over here!
I'm going to tell you this right now...
but you're dead today.
Yoo Jae Suk, Lee Kwang Soo,
and IU will be a team.
I'm stuck between the Monday Couple.
[And lastly, Suk Jin, Gary
and Ji Hyo make up the final team.]
- This makes me uncomfortable.
- You're with the Monday Couple.
- This is the best case scenario ever.
- I'm stuck between these two lovebirds.
Today's race is titled,
The Wolf and the Lamb Race.
As for the details of this race
we will tell you what the details are once
you step into the enclosed booths behind you.
What is this?
Name, wolf and lamb?
[Inside the voting booth is a voting card,
and two pictured cards?]
First, please pick one of the cards
between the wolf and the lamb card.
[Choose a card between
the lamb and the wolf card?]
[Doesn't seem to be an easy choice to make...]
Please choose a card between
the two pictured cards in front of you.
I have chosen my card.
[Everyone chooses a card.]
For some reason, I have a feeling that
everyone's going to pick the wolf card.
Because the wolf is stronger,
and I think that would mean, attack.
[The wolf card means 'attack'?]
And unbelievably enough,
my astrological sign is the lamb.
This card has the lamb on it.
I think this is fate.
I feel like this selection
is a very important one.
Isn't the wolf the predator...
and the lamb, the prey?
If that's the case,
I'd feel better going with the wolf.
But I'm pretty sure that everyone
is going to pick the wolf.
The lamb.
[In the end, he chooses the lamb.]
Please put the card you have
chosen inside your pouch.
I have a feeling that everyone
is going to choose the lamb.
[Big-nose Brother's
new conceptual thinking...]
[Blank Ji chooses the lamb.]
Aren't the wolves a breed of dogs?
Now... we will start the betting.
[Betting?]
- We will now start the betting.
- Betting?
You will choose a card between
the wolf and the lamb card.
Today's race will be about correctly guessing
which card the others have chosen.
[A total of nine players.]
[Deduce the probability of the number
of lambs against the number of wolves.]
[For those who guess wrong...
a terrifying fate awaits them.]
Out of nine total players
which includes yourself
you must guess how many of
the players have chosen the wolf card
and guess how many of the players
have chosen the lamb card
and write down your guess on
the voting ticket that is provided.
[Their deduction is now complete.]
We will now be starting the race.
But the team that comes in at first place
will have the chance to change their guess.
I have no idea what he's saying right now.
This is driving me crazy.
[The team that comes in first can change their
guess to help increase their chance at a win.]
Since the lamb and the wolf count can
change throughout the course of the race
you have to do whatever you can to find out
which card the others have chosen.
You have to do your best to get your guess
to match the actual number of people.
The most important thing to remember is
that this is ultimately an individual race.
If this is an individual race,
then does the sole winner win anything?
- Yes, of course.
- The winner usually gets gold.
- In the event of there being a sole winner...
- What will the winner get?
- What is it?
- Can you tell us?
It's gold!
- If it's gold, then Ji Hyo usually wins it.
- The winner gets all that?
- All of that?
- All that gold?
- I really want to win that.
- The winner gets all that gold?
[Even the sweet and innocent IU
is riveted by the sight of all the gold.]
- Hey.
- IU...
- That's just a lot of gold.
- IU really has grown up.
I'm actually more afraid of Ji Hyo.
Ji Hyo already thinks that
the gold is hers.
['Gold Ji Hyo' looking at ease.]
So the person who guessed correctly
will take the gold.
If only one person guesses correctly,
then that person will take all the gold.
Why are you smiling so widely all of a sudden
after seeing all that gold?
- Why are you so happy about it?
- Are you telling me that you don't like it?
- You don't like it?
- Your face changed so suddenly.
I heard what you just said about IU,
and I've never seen her smile so big before.
It means that IU's all grown up now,
and she's going to go after that gold.
We will now start
the Wolf and the Lamb Race.
- Let's all get on the road now.
- Let's go!
[Wolf and the Lamb Race- Start!]
I'm so happy be to teamed up with IU.
Do you know how nervous I was
that I might get teamed up with Myung Soo?
And it's also nice to have
Kwang Soo on our team.
We need Kwang Soo around because
he makes a very good errand boy.
Why would I be your errand boy?
Of course, you'd have to.
You expect IU to be the errand girl?
If we're going to go by age,
wouldn't IU be the youngest here?
Even though IU may be the youngest,
she's still IU.
- I.U. I miss you!
- What is that?
He's 'Lee', and I'm 'Yoo'.
So that's why we say that.
When UEE was on the show,
we'd say, 'U-EE, I miss you!'
[Depending on the situation, they'd
switch around the order of the words.]
Jae Suk, don't you and Kwang Soo
usually like Uee the most?
- Jong Kook, we said we missed IU.
- It's all about IU today.
I want to ride in the same car with IU.
Where are you taking your father?
- We're taking him for a nice drive.
- I just got a text.
[One of you nine people has
the correct guess.]
- I guess one of us must be right.
- Really?
[One of the nine players
has the correct guess.]
There is.
So one of us has the right guess?
[What could be the correct number of
wolves vs. lambs?]
- One of us has the correct guess.
- Really?
[Current count]
[Thus...]
[The current players with the correct guess
is the Monday Couple.]
- Go to the War Memorabilia Center.
- Okay, let's go!
Party time!
Which card did you pick?
- Yeah, why don't you tell us?
- Can't we tell each other right now?
We can change our guess
as long as we come in at first place.
- Yes, that sounds good.
- You're right.
- Then let's just tell each other right now.
- Okay.
Okay, seriously?
- I chose the wolf card.
- But we may not come in at first place.
- Yes, you're right.
- You can't do that!
[Not telling which card
they've chosen themselves.]
Why would I say anything before
you'd tell us what you've chosen?
And also, to be perfectly honest...
even though you told us you picked the wolf,
there's no way for me to know that for sure.
- Aren't I right, IU?
- Yes, you're right.
You lied to us just now, didn't you?
I really did pick the wolf, Jae Suk.
[Say what? Did you
just say that you picked the wolf?]
[Lying and betrayal has become a part
of this traitorous Giraffe's DNA.]
- I really do think he picked the wolf.
- You do?
The reason being, the wolf...
When it comes to a wolf and a lamb,
a wolf made me think of being on the chase.
[Once IU voiced her opinion, Giraffe
immediately goes into reasoning mode.]
- That's why I chose it.
- I do think that most picked the wolf.
It's because I know how stressful it can be
to be the one being chased.
Did you pick the wolf too, IU?
[Gazing up instead of answering
his question?]
Why are you staring up here?
[Suspicious behavior as if she's
just been caught doing something.]
What about you?
You picked the lamb, didn't you?
- Let's just show each other our cards.
- I chose the wolf.
- You did?
- Really?
Yeah, I picked the wolf.
[Because he thinks the wolf is like a dog,
that's why he chose the wolf?]
- I chose the lamb.
- You chose the lamb?
[Ji Hyo shares what she chose
with her teammates.]
Why don't we just win this thing?
Just any one of our own team members.
Let's just work together as a team.
Since there are nine gold bars,
we can just split the winnings.
[Their plan is to split the prize
if any one of them wins?]
Don't do anything like giving your prize to
Myung Soo or IU because they're guests.
- No, let's just split it amongst us.
- Yeah, keep it amongst ourselves.
I had a feeling that you'd choose wolf,
so I put you in the wolf column.
[Will it be the team that suspects each other
or the team that will work together?]
Myung Soo is amazing at Acrostic poems.
Seriously, Jong Kook.
He is a genius with those poems.
Park Myung Soo.
His first appearance on SBS weekend program.
2013's Grand Award.
No, I don't want any awards.
I'll only get cussed out for winning.
- Run! ('Run' sounds like 'Lun')
- I did some lunges.
The lunges were so hard on my body,
so I opened the fridge to get a drink.
- All the viewers together, 'Ning!'
- And it made my stomach so queasy.
I wasn't sure if it was sesame oil,
or perilla oil that I drank.
- Man!
- Man.
We will be back after this brief break.
Just what are the other teams doing?
['Ha-Myung-Kook' trio in perfect sync,
and harmony with their words.]
- My house is right over there.
- That's right, your house is right there.
Then why don't you just
call it a day and go home?
Thanks for all your work today.
IU.
[Giraffe's feelings are hurt.]
Why do you keep repeating IU's name?
What she said isn't wrong.
- Why do you mean, go home?
- This is what you call working in sync.
[Siblings 'Yoo-U' in perfect sync.]
Are you two just going to work in sync
by yourselves without me?
['Ha-Myung-Kook' is back at it
with the acrostic poems.]
- Okay, one last time.
- I need everyone's attention, please.
- Run!
- After I did some lunges...
I took a hot shower, and when I was done,
I noticed that it was 7am.
As I saw the people passing by on the street,
I shouted out to them, 'Good mor...'
What? 'Good Mor?'
Could it be what I'm thinking?
Say it with us, viewing audience.
'Ning'!
'Ning'... that's how I greeted everyone.
And once I greeted everyone,
they all told me how polite I was.
And do you know what they said to me?
'Mother, father, gentle?'
[Oh my goodness.]
[Just like his reputation that precedes him,
he really is a whiz at acrostic poems...]
Dear viewing audience,
please give him a round of applause.
Everyone shout it out with us
one last time.
Man!
'Man'.
That's what they called me.
Park Myung Soo!
- Isn't that Dong Wan?
- Where?
[Is there something ahead of them
that they're seeing?]
[First mission location-
Yongsan War Memorabilia Center.]
[An elephant is seen standing to greet them.]
It looks like a real elephant.
Animals that died of natural causes
have been preserved for the visitors.
No wonder.
It looks like a real elephant.
Don't you think?
Kwang Soo is just like the elephant
in that he's like an animal himself.
What are you talking about?
I'm a real live human being.
- What is this?
- Jae Suk. Myung Soo is a genius.
On our way here, he came up with an
acrostic poem with the words, Running Man.
- It was awesome.
- It was the best.
It was perfect.
'Running Man' wouldn't be easy to do.
- But he did it perfectly.
- He's likely to win the 2013 Grand Award.
[With his single acrostic poem attempt,
he's likely to win the Grand Award?]
The Blue Team called to say they're going to
be late because they got lost on their way.
Why do you keep people like that around?
They can't even find their way around.
- Just get rid of them.
- Suk Jin is with them.
- We have to wait for them to do the mission.
- They can't even find their way.
That's the only way for them to learn.
They even have the navigation system.
Don't provoke Suk Jin if you can help it.
Because he can be mean if provoked.
Even though we might find it entertaining.
It's the lion's nature to go for
the weakest of the prey.
- That's what a lion does.
- I can't believe he said that. That's awful!
Have you ever seen a jungle lion
going after a young lamb?
[The cruel laws of the jungle...]
- What's going on here?
- Why did you get lost on your way?
- No kidding.
- Did you take the bus here or something?
Driver Gae got us lost.
- Myung Soo here said some things about you.
- Like what?
- You really are amazing though.
- Why?
For having survived this long.
[Lion with the permed hair continuing
with his attack on the Impala.]
There's something I want to tell you.
You have no idea how tough this show is.
You can just go home right now.
It's okay, we'll understand.
You have no idea how physically
demanding this show is.
This feels like 'Of course, it is'.
[A nostalgic segment of X-Man,
'Of course, it is'?]
I'm reminded of the segment!
[Tumbling rock, Myung Soo vs.
A fixed rock, Suk Jin.]
This is amazing.
I've only seen this on TV.
Of course, it is.
A lion will hunt down the weak cow.
Weakness is written all over your face.
Of course, it is.
- Are you talking to me?
- Yes, I was referring to you.
Of course, I meant you.
You're the only weak one here.
No!
I'm not done saying my part yet.
I... think...
[Tearing up at the truth?]
[Knocked down.]
[Unable to respond in time.]
- No, I'm not going to say anything else.
- Don't air this, got it?
Why did you react like that?
You're making us all feel really bad!
[Looks genuinely hurt by the words
of Park-perm in the word game?]
I'm not even in the mood
to joke around right now.
- What do you mean, you're not in the mood?
- He didn't say those words as a joke.
[We love you, Impala.]
[I'm sorry, Suk Jin.
I was just joking around.]
No, Suk Jin. Let's cut,
and go to a break right now.
[Uncomfortable atmosphere.]
What's our mission here?
Okay, then I will tell you what
your first mission for the day is.
In this portion of the animal exhibit
you will find numerous different animals
on display for everyone to see.
In various spots throughout the exhibition
you will find pieces of marked paper
with the name of the animal written on it.
Each of you must find that piece of paper,
and return here as soon as possible. Go!
[Find the piece of paper and return
as soon as possible.]
- Where are they?
- What kind of names is he talking about?
[Everyone entering the exhibition
confused about what they're supposed to do.]
[Very realistic animals are seen
displayed all over the place.]
[Where are the pieces of paper
with the 'R' marker on them?]
- Wow, they all look so real.
- Wow, I think I see one.
Where?
[Myung Soo discovers
the turtle's slip of paper!]
Where?
[All the members frantically searching
for the marked pieces of paper.]
- I haven't found anything.
- We have to hurry back.
We only need to find one of them?
[But the mission seems to be
suspiciously simple...]
[Is this truly the end of their real mission?]
[Where are you going?]
I was only able to find one.
[It looks as though everyone came back
with a piece of paper in their possession...]
Weren't there so many different
animals in the exhibit that you were just in?
I will now tell you what
your real mission is.
- What?
- Then this was a fake mission?
This mission is called,
'Find the wrong picture.'
The truth is, inside the exhibit that
you were all just in...
there was a setup that should have seemed
wrong and unnatural to everyone.
[Find the abnormality inside the exhibition
that they were just running around in.]
[We hope that all the viewers
play along with us!]
The mission that you just did gave
you a chance to look around the exhibit.
The person who noticed the abnormality...
Do you see the mic behind you?
[The person who can shout out their answer
into the mic passes the true mission.]
[The first team to have all their members
pass the mission is the winning team!]
- No, it wasn't an animal.
- What did you see? Tell us what you saw.
- What was it that you saw?
- You have to grab onto the mic.
- Just take a guess.
- Say into the mic what you think you saw.
- Say it into the mic.
- You could be the first one to pass.
Once you grab the mic,
you have to pull it down towards you.
Only the person who wants to take
a guess can grab the mic.
[Could it be that he really knows?]
- Hello.
- Just say what you think the answer is.
It really is an honor to be back
on an SBS program.
From what I remember seeing...
I saw a mannequin inside the exhibit.
- I don't remember seeing anything like that.
- You're saying there was a mannequin?
[Could that be the correct answer?]
I don't remember seeing anything
that was out of place.
- Can you give me another chance?
- You have exactly one minute.
You need to wait a moment.
- I will tell you when.
- What are you doing?
You have exactly one minute.
So it'll be the same as before.
[Today's guests both seems to have
quite the competitive streak in them.]
- You have to be back within a minute.
- Ready, set, go!
[Must return within one minute.]
I couldn't find anything earlier.
[Taking another look around the exhibition...]
[What's the abnormality
that they're supposed to find?]
- I don't see anything.
- What is it?
[IU seemed to have discovered something,
and rushes out of the room!]
[Did Kwang Soo discover something as well?]
[The abnormality...
Have you discovered it too?]
[Huh?]
[Jae Suk also seems to have
discovered something!]
Was that a beaver or an otter?
Run!
Run, IU!
[Those who seemed to have found the answer
are rushing back to the starting line!]
- How am I supposed to grab that?
- Go grab it!
[The mic is placed too high for IU to grab.]
There's no time!
Grab the mic!
- IU!
- You're not going to be able to grab it!
Come here, IU.
[Jae Suk pulls IU up onto his back.]
[But Big-nose Brother gets in the way again!]
[A bloody battle for the mic.]
Grab it!
[She got the mic!]
[What will her answer be?]
The beaver...
- You have to say the exact name.
- The beaver.
- It's a four letter word.
- What?
- Go on with your answer.
- It's an otter.
- The beaver...
- No, it's an otter.
The otter...
The otter was holding a chancel.
[The otter was holding a chancel?]
- It wasn't the right answer?
- It's wrong.
[Just then, giant Giraffe leaps up
and grabs the mic.]
The otter... was holding a recorder.
[Do I still look like an otter to you?]
Jump up.
[Total chaos.]
Please let go of me.
Grab it, IU!
[Just then...
Tiger jumps up and grabs the mic.]
The beaver was holding onto a chancel.
- Repeat your answer one more time.
- The beaver was holding onto a chancel.
[Kkuk answers correctly.]
[The beaver, not the otter,
is holding onto a chancel in his hands.]
[If IU had just said beaver from the start,
she would've gotten the right answer.]
She would've answered it correctly
if it hadn't been for Jae Suk.
- What were you thinking?
- Why did you sabotage her?
He was acting really frustrated with IU when
he kept telling her that it was an otter.
Did Myung Soo go home?
I have no idea.
Ready, set, go!
[Blank Ji passes Round Two,
and off to Round Three!]
Either Myung Soo or Ha Ha
needs to get the next one.
[What will they find this time?]
[Kid Ro-Ro pretending to see something
to fake everyone out.]
This is part of the normal setup, right?
[Join us in our search, viewers.]
[Do you see it?]
[IU is the first to discover
the abnormality again!]
[All the other members also discover
the abnormality one by one.]
[The correct answer- The shoe brush found
on top of the zebra's head.]
[Must hurry and grab the mic!]
[What did they all see?]
[IU's seems to always be in a rush.]
[But Gary beats her to the punch,
and is the first to grab the mic.]
- Can I guess the answer?
- Yes.
[No!]
There was a shoe brush
on top of the pony's head.
[What... a pony?]
That's not the right answer?
What is it?
- Can you help me grab the mic?
- Okay, we'll help you.
[The men on the opposing teams are
helpless when it comes to IU's pleas.]
One, two, three.
I'd like to see what your answer is.
The zebra.
A zebra!
I can't believe I didn't say that!
[Finally realized
why he got his answer wrong.]
[IU answers correctly.]
Aren't they called 'ponies' from
time to time?
[The correct answer is,
on top of the ZEBRA's head is a shoe brush.]
Aren't they called 'ponies'
from time to time?
[Just which country do you think refers
to them as ponies?]
The shoe brush was on top of the zebra's head.
What did you say for your answer?
- The shoe brush on the zebra's head.
- I said that it was on a pony's head.
[Even he finds himself to be pathetic...]
- You said it was a pony?
- Did you get the answer, IU?
- Yes.
- We did it!
- How could you have lost to IU?
- You did great.
Why did I call the zebra a pony?
It's because I'm not a very smart person.
- Gary is the only one left on the Blue Team.
- We have to stop him no matter what.
- Kang Gary, give me your bag.
- Blue Team wins if Gary passes.
Blue Team will win first place.
[Entrusting his bag that contains the card
with Blank Ji to be able to move faster.]
What if Song Ji Hyo looks inside your bag
and sees which card you picked?
It's okay.
I have nothing to hide when
it comes to her.
[Look at these two!]
- I have nothing to hide from her.
- What are you talking about?
[There is no such thing as secrets
between the Monday Couple?]
- The next one is extremely easy.
- Okay, we understand.
There are only four of you left.
Ready, set, go!
[No rest for the weary.
Time for Round Five!]
- You have Gary's bag?
- Yeah.
- Why?
- Let me take a look.
- No. Why would you do that?
- This is an individual competition.
- What about it? So what if it is?
- Let's look at it together.
No, I don't want to.
She's so considerate to Gary.
Peeking in his bag when he's not here
is a very cowardly thing to do.
[Meanwhile...]
[Jae Suk and Myung Soo simultaneously sees
something as soon as they enter the room.]
[One animal looking quite warm and cozy.]
I don't think I can run anymore!
[Everyone back at the starting line is still
trying to take a peek at Gary's card.]
- I just figured something out.
- Really? How?
[Giraffe having peeked at other members'
cards when they were unaware.]
Your bag is wide open.
We all saw your card.
Unbelievable.
[If Jae Suk answers it first,
then the Red Team will win the game!]
[Haroro trying to stop Jae Suk in his
feeble attempt to stop him from winning.]
- Hurry! Hurry!
- It's all over if Gary gets the answer!
He's not going to be able to grab the mic.
[The mic not wanting to cooperate
with Myung Soo's desperate attempt.]
[Oh! He grabs the mic!]
- There's no way.
- The wildcat.
The leopard?
The tiger?
[Wildcat? Leopard? Tiger?
What are you?]
- What is the animal you're referring to?
- It's a leopard.
- A leopard?
- The scarf.
It's wearing a scarf around its neck.
A scarf.
- Be more precise.
- A scarf. The neck.
Just say it!
Say it in a complete sentence.
The leopard is wearing a scarf.
[Barely manages to spit out
the correct answer.]
- You have to get it this time, Jae Suk.
- Okay.
[The final battle!
Only one person from each team remains.]
[Blue Team's Gary vs. Red Team's Jae Suk
vs. White Team's Ha Ha.]
Ready.
[The final round of the game starts now!]
[See what you can find!]
[Even an impala needs to
protect its foot.]
[Jae Suk is first to
discover the abnormality!]
[Everyone rushes back after
having made their discovery!]
Grab him!
[This is the round that'll determine
who the victor of the game will be!]
[Jae Suk is the first to make it back.]
[Jump!]
[Ah...]
[A fierce battle for the mic
befitting of the final round.]
Look into IU's eyes, Jae Suk!
[Please!]
Think of it as you playing basketball.
[The final ownership
of the mic goes to Haroro.]
The impala!
The impala...
is wearing a running shoe!
- The impala is wearing a running shoe!
- On which foot?
['Ha-Myung-Kook' wins the first game!]
I thought Gary was going to do it.
One, two, three, four!
[Celebratory step dance.]
- Hey, why are you in the middle?
- Sorry.
- Are you serious?
- Who cares? We're on the same team.
- Weren't you in the middle?
- Yeah, I was in the middle.
- Try to remember how we used to do it.
- Look at what he's trying to do over there.
I was in the middle.
[Anyways, the winning team of the
exhibition mission is...]
[Ha-Myung-Kook]
The members of the winning team now have the
chance to trade in their cards for a new one.
Ticketing booths are available for you to
make your trade should you choose to do so.
Many of you know
which card I have, don't you?
- Yes.
- We all know.
- We can keep the card we have too.
- Yeah, okay.
- Keep it or trade it in.
- One or the other. Trade it or keep it.
[Myung Soo with his original lamb card.]
[I'm just going to keep it.]
I had originally picked the wolf card.
I had originally picked the wolf...
and I'm going to choose the wolf again.
[Kook also chooses to
keep his original decision.]
Since everyone seems to be confused
about what we're about to do...
[And lastly, Haroro, whose card has been
seen by many other members...]
[He switches his original lamb card
in for the wolf card.]
[Due to Ha Ha's exchange, the
count changes to 6 wolves and 3 lambs.]
[Ha Ha unknowingly changed the result to
match the count that he had voted for.]
[Current correct answer.]
We got a text.
What does it say?
- There are two people with the right guess.
- Seriously?
[With Ha Ha's trade, it's 6 wolves and 3 lambs.
IU and Ha Ha currently have the correct answer.]
- Two people with the correct guess?
- Two people with the correct guess.
[IU isn't even aware that
she's one of them.]
Let's go!
[Off to the next mission location.]
Which card did Suk Jin have?
- Wolf.
- Really? The wolf?
I knew you would've seen his card.
[Even though she pretended not to see it,
IU had taken a peek at Suk Jin's card.]
- There really are a lot of wolves.
- Yes, there are a lot of wolves.
That's what you think, Jae Suk.
But there are quite a few lambs.
- Really?
- Seriously?
- There are quite a few lambs.
- But think about it.
- You're a wolf too, right, IU?
- Yes.
- I'm a wolf too.
- And Kwang Soo's a wolf.
That's already quite a few wolves.
[Kwang Soo lied to them about picking wolf.]
What I think is... Ha Ha had the lamb,
and we're only unaware of four cards.
- But they had the chance to change it.
- Myung Soo had the lamb.
- Ha Ha also had the lamb card.
- Myung Soo had the lamb card?
- How do you know that?
- I saw it.
You saw it?
- Jong Kook also had a lamb card.
- Really?
[Jong Kook has a lamb card?]
[Giraffe starts his game of conning.]
[Unlike Giraffe's claim,
Gary chose the wolf.]
- So there are quite a few lambs.
- There are a lot of lambs.
[His face no longer even changes as he
lies blatantly to other people.]
After checking other people out,
I've noticed there are a lot of wolves.
- Right?
- Yeah.
I've given it some thought, but
after figuring out what others wrote
we should only change the cards that we have
in order to match our guesses.
- Okay, agreed.
- You understand what I'm saying?
[On the other hand, the traitorous Giraffe
is doing what he can to deceive his team.]
I'm going with the wolf.
[Blue Team agrees to work together
to come in first in the missions.]
[That will be their only chance to change
the cards that they have.]
Myung Soo is our lucky charm.
Things are going great with him on our team.
[Ha-Myung-Kook is flying high from their win.]
How long has it been since
Ha-Myung-Kook has been together?
- Seven or eight years?
- I think you're right.
- That long?
- Time really flies by.
We really used to have a great time.
- I got something.
- What did you get?
[We will notify the winning team what the
current count of wolves vs. the lambs are.]
[The winning team will be notified of what
the current count of wolves vs. the lambs is.]
- This is a huge advantage.
- I didn't know they'd do that.
- We have to win first no matter what.
- You really are a lucky charm.
- Right?
- The game is in the bag now.
[Once they're notified of the current count,
they can switch their cards to match it.]
[Wolves- Six; Lambs- Three.]
[Ha Ha has the correct estimate.]
[With the recent exchange of his card,
he had changed the count to match his guess.]
[Okay... we just need to keep this going.]
[And Jong Kook's guess had been
seven wolves and two lambs.]
[Okay, it's getting closer now.]
Once someone finds out what
the current count is...
they can do whatever they want with
their card to match it up with their guess.
- To increase their chance at a win.
- True.
[It is crucial to continue to win first place
so that they keep this truth to themselves.]
I bet it must be a lot of fun
to do things like this every week.
I really want to be on Running Man.
- Are you making a formal request?
- If I want to join the cast...
since this is similar to the other show,
I know I can do it if Ha Ha leaves.
[The Red Team is the first to arrive
at the second mission location.]
Come over this way, please.
- Come this way, please.
- What are we doing here?
[Spicy stewed rib restaurant in Soowon.]
[Huh?]
[Just what in the world...]
What is this?
What is this water tank doing here?
[While one person goes in the tank and
shouts out 'Ow' in one breath...]
[the other two members have to gather up all
the scattered stools inside the restaurant.]
[Just the sight of the water tank alone
is enough to terrify them.]
Why are you making us play a game like this
at the spicy rib restaurant?
- I thought we were going to be eating ribs.
- This wasn't an eating competition?
Seriously, what kind of a game is this
to be playing at a rib restaurant?
If you can't complete the mission before the
person is 'ow' loses their breath...
- Then the person is dunked in the water?
- And it's a failed mission.
- What is that chair all about?
- You'll find out soon enough.
[The chair is where one will be sitting
while shouting out, 'ow'...]
While howling?
IU looks like a mermaid.
[Trying to convince IU to take the chair?]
[The older men telling sweet IU
to take one for the team.]
[Ha-Myung-Kook saunters up to others
with ease and confidence.]
It's really crucial to come in at first place.
The game is all over now.
You might as well all just go home.
- We've got this game in the bag.
- You won't know until this is all over.
In this round, first and second place winners
will be alerted to what the current count is.
And like before, only the team that comes in
at first place has the chance to trade.
We choose Myung Soo to be the one
to sit in the chair.
[Ha-Myung-Kook chooses Myung Soo?]
This is the reason why you're
here, Myung Soo.
Don't you want the award?
[Doing this would further his chances
of winning the grand award?]
Even though this is my first appearance
on SBS this whole year?
- This is my first appearance on SBS.
- But this could be your chance.
- Is that even possible?
- Of course.
Then I'll do it.
- This one thing could be my chance?
- Of course, this could be your chance.
- He sure does love his awards.
- Yes, you're right.
- Hey, stand right up at the line.
- Talk to me in honorifics.
Please stand at the line.
- Here?
- Yes.
- No, they can't do that.
- Why are you trying to ruin this?
Don't try to cheat.
Come on now.
Your shorts and the bag seriously...
[Ha-Myung-Kook, Start.]
[The chair is slowly getting
lowered towards the water!]
[The other two members must gather up all
the stools before Myung Soo's howling stops.]
[Which of the two will be finished first?]
[Slowly starting to get
submerged in the water.]
[Once he's underwater, then his howling...]
[Will it be the stools first,
or will it be the submersion?]
[The howling is stopped!]
[Fails the mission by the split of a hair!]
Look! He looks like a fish!
[A rare species of fish!]
[Looking quite similar to the
monstrous looking fish.]
- How can he look like that?
- What the heck is that!
Isn't that Han Moo?
- I thought that you were Han Moo!
- What did you just say?
[You do look just like him...]
[Ji Hyo is in a cultural state of shock.]
You've never been so shocked by
Myung Soo's looks before, have you?
[Breaking out into a fit of laughter after
seeing Myung Soo's face.]
[His unique look that the heavens
have bestowed upon him.]
Do you think that was enough to
get me that award?
[So that's what he's really after!]
You think I may be able to get it?
[His fish imitation may land
him the award.]
I've never lost in the looks department to
anyone, but I think Myung Soo's got me beat.
You're quite handsome compared to him.
We needed three more seconds.
We were pretty fast, weren't we?
[Mere three seconds
could've meant their victory.]
[For the Red Team,
Kwang Soo takes the howling chair.]
- I'm going to do this for our team!
- Ah!
I-U- I miss you!
- Are you all ready?
- We will show you what winning looks like!
If you don't get it done, IU will
have to get on that chair next time.
[IU volunteers to sit on the chair
if they don't succeed in their first try.]
[Red Team- Start.]
[They seem to be stumbling around a bit...]
IU is really good.
[Kwang Soo is slowly starting to
get submerged in the water.]
[There are still so many
stools left to gather.]
[Fighting the inevitable.]
[Which of the two sides will be first?]
[Ultimately submerged underwater
and his howling stops.]
[Red Team fails.]
[All they needed was to
bring the stools back!]
- I couldn't do it anymore!
- You guys were so close.
You just needed to bring it back.
- Kwang Soo did the best he could.
- He really did.
He really did what he could to win.
This really is so disappointing.
[Will IU really be the next one up
on the chair?]
[Big-nose takes the chair for the Blue Team.]
- Okay, 25 seconds is what you need?
- Okay.
[Blue Team- Start]
[Monday Couple is on fire!]
Get the ones up front!
[Speedy Ji Hyo... and speedy Gary!]
They really do work well together,
don't they?
[Monday Couple on their way to
opening up their own shop.]
[His howling starts to come to an end...]
[Fails from the halting of the howling.]
[Pathetically fails the mission.]
[They were so close to winning.
Just needed to bring the stools out.]
- We just needed to bring out the stools.
- That team, seriously.
[Ah... the troublemaker.]
[Ha-Myung-Kook team gets
Myung Soo back in the chair.]
If we win it this time...
that seals the deal for Myung Soo.
[Why the sudden halt to the game?]
[The reason being... no sound
could be heard from Myung Soo.]
[Disqualified because no sound was heard
after the whistle blow.]
[Everyone who witnessed the start
can testify to the fail.]
- We can't excuse them for that.
- Can you let us start over?
Come on.
Just let us start over again.
Get down from that chair.
- Can't I just gather up my breath first?
- Just get down from there!
If I ever got a mother-in-law like you,
I'd just move out of the house.
Why would you worry about
meeting a mother-in-law like that?
Who cares if I said anything about
- Why are you saying things like that to him?
- It's not like he's the daughter-in-law.
- Why are you being so mean to Myung Soo?
- I'm the bad daughter-in-law. So what?
Put your shoes back on.
[Bickering back and forth whenever
either one of them opens their mouth.]
[Not even bothering to put
his shoes back on...]
Fine, I'll put my shoes back on!
I'll put both of my shoes back on!
- IU is going to take the chair for our team.
- Seriously?
[Just as she stated earlier,
IU gets up on the chair.]
- Okay, IU up on the chair.
- Undo your hair tie in case you're submerged.
[That's his idea of cheering her on?]
- You look very pretty, IU!
- Is IU going after the award too?
[It seems as though everyone
is after winning the award.]
I-U-I miss you!
[She may be able to hold her breath for
a long time since she's a singer.]
IU, can you howl in melody?
[Can she howl in melody?]
- Can she do it in melody?
- Ready.
[Why are they getting in that pose?]
[Jae Suk's overconfidence in his butt.]
What? I was just
looking at what's in front of me.
What else was I supposed to look at?
I thought you were covering up your eyes,
but you were just touching your forehead.
What about it?
Okay, let's do this.
[Read Team- Start.]
[Even though it's a quite howl,
IU's howling with ease and confidence.]
[Working in sync to gather up
all the stools quickly.]
[IU is already halfway
submerged in the water.]
[Kwang Soo makes it out first.]
[Now only if Jae Suk can
make it back out!]
[Will IU be able to succeed?]
You just need to make it back out!
[She hasn't stopped howling!]
[Red Team comes in at first place!]
[IU gets the job done!]
[Then who will come in at second place?]
- Why don't you give it a try?
- You won't be able to get it done.
- I have to go back in again?
- Hurry up and get up on the chair.
- So I have to get back up there?
- You listen to him very well.
Why do you listen to Jong Kook so well?
[Because Jong Kook is hitting Myung Soo on
the back while pretending to pat him.]
I can't believe how well
you listen to Jong Kook.
- He and I are really close.
- I can't believe how compliant he is.
He's changed a lot.
Gather up all your breath.
[Ha-Myung-Kook, start.]
[Gathering up the stools as quickly as
possible as soon as the whistle sounds.]
[Howling as low as he can.]
[The sounds of the stools being gathered
is awfully fast!]
[They may be able to get it done this time!]
[They just need to bring out the stools!]
[Ha-Myung-Kook succeeds!]
[Finishing up his howling like a
creature out of a horror movie.]
We did it.
What was that?
A scene from a horror movie?
[They worked together to
succeed the mission.]
[Breaking out into
their celebratory step dance.]
- Do it from up there!
- Do what!
First and second team,
please step up to the front.
[Special information given out to the
two teams that came in first.]
You will be informed of how many wolves
and lambs there are currently.
[Red Team is alerted to the current count
for coming in at first place.]
- Seriously?
- You will be given the same information.
[Wolves- Six; Lambs- Three.]
You're just going to tell us like this?
[On top of knowing the count,
they can also trade in their cards.]
[Kwang Soo's chance to trade in his card.]
By the difference of one single card.
[Quite close to Kwang Soo's current guess.]
[His current lamb card...
gets traded in for the wolf card.]
[Jae Suk's estimation.]
[His own wolf card... is kept the same.]
If I just keep the cards as is,
I could win this race.
[Therefore...
IU decided not to trade in her card.]
[Current card after Kwang Soo
trades in his card.]
[The players with the current correct guess.]
Where are we going next?
There are two players with the correct
guess out of the nine of you.
It's possible that the players from
the Red Team may not have made a trade.
- Yeah, you're right.
- They may not have traded in their card.
- That's why it's remaining the same?
- We'll find out at the next game.
Not necessarily. Even if they made a trade,
others could have the correct guess.
Did you trade in your card?
What did you do?
[It's difficult to share the information
since this is an individual race...]
We're told to go to Soowon's
Human Resources Center.
Don't you think that we should share
some sort of information?
I feel like we're being too
distrusting of each other.
But I know that you have no intention
of telling us what you have.
[How did he know?]
- That was a lot of gold.
-  I know.
- Do they really give all that out?
- The winner gets it all.
You can take the gold and run.
If I win that gold prize...
don't even come near me, okay?
Don't even look over at me,
or try to talk to me either.
[Everyone seems to be
lusting after the gold.]
I think it's crucial for us
to win this next game.
[Must win the next game in order to gain
an advantage at making the correct guess.]
- Yes, you're right. This is the crucial time.
- It all depends on what the next winner does.
Since the other teams found out the score,
I'm sure they made changes to help them win.
- Yes, you could be right.
- I bet one of them has the right guess.
[Arriving at the next mission location.]
- Isn't that the UFC...
- What's that?
That really is the UFC ring.
[Soowon Human Resources
Development Center.]
[A little unsure of it from the distance...]
[But it really is the octagonal ring!]
What is this?
What are you doing to us?
- What do you think you're doing?
- What is this all about?
Don't you think that you're being too
harsh with IU on our team?
How could you have set up a ring like this
with Jong Kook on the other team?
[This truly is...]
[The octagonal ring where the
UFC battles are fought in.]
[That hellish ring is now standing
right in front of their eyes.]
[What is that ring doing here
in front of them?]
We're peaceful people.
We're not going to be playing name tag
elimination in there, are we?
You have to give us a chance to escape!
What are you trying to do to us?
- Are you trying to get us killed?
- Are we going to battle it out?
[This is what I've been waiting for.]
It's finally time to battle it out.
Hey, look at the fear in IU's eyes.
Myung Soo is going to take on IU.
- He's going to take IU down.
- It's the octagon!
[Even the random Mr. Capable
seems to light up at the sight?]
[Even breaking out into a dance of
confidence at the sight of the ring?]
- That ring looks so official.
- Seriously...
I'm seriously going to kick your butt
if you and I get in that ring together.
Jae Suk.
Can we just have a personal match in there?
Can you allow us to do that?
I'm serious.
[You want to do this?
Seriously?]
[In moments...]
[You will witness a bloody end
to their feud?]
Okay, here's your mission.
As you can see in front of you
your third mission will be name tag
elimination in the octagonal ring.
- What?
- A name tag elimination?
As you're all already aware,
there are three of you in each team.
- This game is for Jong Kook.
- One player per team must come into the ring.
It will be a one-on-one-on-one face-off
between the three players in the ring.
However, you won't know who will come
into the ring for the battle from other teams.
You will not be allowed to watch the other
teams discussing who will go into the ring.
[The main point of the competition is that
they won't know who they'll be facing.]
This is all about the luck of the draw.
First and second place winners will
be notified of what the current count is.
And for the team that comes in
at first place...
That team will also be given a chance
to trade in their cards for a different one.
Will it still be a normal game even if
IU enters the ring?
Yes, of course. It doesn't
matter who enters the ring.
- Why would you even ask that question?
- Seriously?
- I'll be waiting for you.
- He says he'll be waiting.
The best case scenario for us would be...
if Jong Kook and Gary ended up
going up against each other.
It would be best for us if they ended up
being in the ring together.
Even though I feel a bit bad about this...
For the sake of our team...
- If IU went up against them...
- Jong Kook is weak when it comes to women.
He'll never get rough with women.
I think I can take Suk Jin down.
Try grabbing me.
Let's do a little role play.
Put some strength behind it.
I feel like you're really going to hit me.
The main thing is that we won't know
who's going to enter in that ring.
- That's the crucial part.
- That's what's important. The decision...
[Just who will the teams send into the
ring as their first players?]
I'll take IU down.
Ready.
One!
Two!
Three!
Enter!
[Round One- Start.]
[First player for each team...]
[White Team- Myung Soo.]
[Red Team- Traitorous Kwang Soo.]
[Blue Team- Boxer Gae.]
[This is going to be entertaining!]
- Kwang Soo.
- You can win this, Kwang Soo.
Myung Soo, team up with Gary first.
[High fiving each other?]
[Myung Soo and Gary
teaming up immediately.]
It's okay, you can do it.
[Attack]
Just hold still!
Why do you keep spinning around?
Stop doing that!
[Prepare yourself, Giraffe.]
What are you doing?
Stop it!
You're giving me a headache!
[The three players circling around each other
to look for their chance at an attack.]
- You're not going to rip off my tag, are you?
- No, I won't.
[A sneak attack!]
[Giraffe in danger!]
[Giraffe quickly escapes harm's way
only to be attacked again!]
[Holds onto Park-Perm with his long arm.]
[Huh?]
[Myung Soo- Out!]
[While being dragged around...]
[His name tag gets ripped off
in the process.]
[Utter humiliation.]
[Ousted before he could
even do anything.]
Is that any way to treat your elder?
What are you doing?
I told you not to get ousted!
- I've never done this before!
- Just get out here!
Gary's no easy opponent.
Gary is really good.
[Long arms vs. the Boxer.]
I never would've even fathomed that
Gary would be the first player out.
We have to get at least second place.
His arms are so long!
[Giraffe attacks first...]
[And Gary counterattacks!]
[Who will be the first to get eliminated?]
[Lays himself on the ground...]
[Gary wins!]
Wow, Kwang Soo was doing so well.
- We did it!
- I want you, Kang Gary!
I want you, Kang Gary!
[I'm the random Mr. Capable.]
[Just like the UFC champion,
Kim Dong Hyun...]
[Ecstatic Boxer Gae.]
[The joy over their first success.]
Kwang Soo got to him first though.
That was awesome.
- You were awesome, Kang Gary.
- That's just how I usually am.
[You really are...]
Second players for Round Two,
please stand in front of your entrance.
[Yoo Hyuk awaits to enter the ring.]
Two.
[Just who will enter the ring
as the second players?]
[It's me!]
[I'm ruined!]
We've got this!
[White Team's plan was to enter the ring
in the order of their age.]
Then you could go in second.
[Their simple plan seems to be
working out great for them.]
Why don't you two
go up against each other first?
What are you talking about?
- What are you saying right now?
- Watch your back.
[This is none other than the Tiger's den.]
- Those two aren't going to be any challenge.
- You're going to get yourself ousted first.
- Jong Kook.
What's going on?
What are you doing in there?
[Trips and falls back
while walking backwards.]
[That could've been big trouble.]
You have to beat them, Suk Jin.
- What are you trying to do over there?
- Just come in second, Suk Jin.
Second place would be better, right?
[It would actually better for them to
come in at second place...]
[In that case...]
Okay.
- I'm serious.
- I'm serious too.
- That's not fair.
- You're going to get yourself ousted!
[In a blink of an eye,
the Tiger and Impala joins forces.]
[Red Grasshopper backed up into a corner.]
Rip off Jae Suk's name tag.
[No!]
- Aren't you going to rip it off?
- You could be the one getting ousted first.
[I can't hear you!]
Suk Jin!
[Cruel takedown of the Grasshopper...]
Please stop!
Please stop torturing Jae Suk!
What's taking you so long?
I'm going to tie him up.
[Huh?]
[A sneak attack on the Tiger?]
[Going back to attacking the Grasshopper.]
[Grasshopper's desperate counterattack!]
[However...]
[The Tiger ultimately ends the hunt.]
You can do it, Suk Jin!
I only wanted to come in at
second place anyways.
There you go.
[The never-ending humiliation...]
That Kim Jong Kook...
[October, 20th, 2013-
The ultimate humiliation...]
I can't keep watching this
without crying.
Jae Suk.
- This humiliation...
- You did great.
- I will get revenge for this humiliation.
- No, you did fine.
[I won't forget this utter humiliation.]
Wow, he really tied you up tight.
How could he have tied you up
so tightly like that?
Do you really think that this
was necessary?
Look at what he did to me.
[Tiger has Impala's hands locked up
in his vise-like grip.]
Hang on a second.
Are you trying to take my shirt off?
Suk Jin.
That was a UFC move.
I feel like I'm watching a UFC match.
- You're doing great, Jong Kook.
- This is no amateur match.
[Tiger launching into his attack
once again.]
- What the heck?
- What are you doing?
Come back here!
It's you and me!
Stop tormenting Suk Jin!
Just kill him and put him out of his misery.
- You're a monster!
- Stop torturing our Suk Jin!
What is he trying to do to Suk Jin?
His grips are no different than
being handcuffed.
Stop torturing our Suk Jin!
- What the heck is this?
- He really has sunken to an all-time low.
[This is what you call a miserable end...]
- That was so miserable.
- We had a good plan too.
[Second round victory goes to,
Tiger of the White Team!]
[Round Three.]
Since you are all aware of who the
final players are going to be
you can all just enter the
ring immediately.
[Full of confidence?]
- You can do this, IU.
- Okay, fighting.
Fighting!
You're going overboard.
[Ace Ji Hyo is the final player
for the Blue Team.]
Ji Hyo. We need to
eliminate the White Team first.
- You have to oust them first.
- You have to come in at first place.
- Of course, you do.
- First...
- Let's get rid of Ha Ha first.
- Of course. That's the right decision.
[The beauties unite.]
[Running around in circles
to confuse his opponents?]
[What to do about this guy...]
You two girls need to band together,
and not stand so far apart from each other.
You have to stick closer together.
[He's caught by IU!]
- I'm so sorry!
- It's okay.
[They beauty duo closing in on Ha Ha.]
[Ha Ha moving fast to avoid their attack.]
[His antics of rolling around on the floor
only got him in danger.]
[Ro-Ro in danger!]
You have to watch your back.
[Myung Soo continuing to come into the ring
as if he's in a pro wrestling match.]
[Ro-Ro barely able to hold on
any longer.]
[I won't allow you to continue your antics.]
What are you two doing in there?
[The bloody UFC match between
these two middle aged men.]
[Complete chaos.]
[If you want the pro wrestling moves,
then pro wrestling moves you'll get.]
You're slowly starting to piss me off!
[Ro-Ro managing to stay in the game by
calling up on every ounce of energy he has.]
[All the spectators are really
getting into the match.]
[Even resorting to methods of biting?]
That really hurts!
Song Ji Hyo!
[Haroro- Out!]
[The cruel wrap-up to his defeat.]
[Now time to call off the truce
between the two fighting beauties.]
Why do you keep climbing up there?
When am I ever going to see
a sight like this again?
[Blank Ji vs. IU]
[They both simultaneously grab
onto each other's name tags!]
[Who will be faster with their hand?]
[Ji Hyo wins!]
Wow, that was so quick.
Song Ji Hyo's so fast.
[Blank...]
[Ace Ji Hyo wins!]
Current score is, 2 points for the Blue Team,
1 point for the White Team, and 0 for Red.
One more point, then the Blue Team
wins the game in first place.
So it'll either be Jong Kook or
Myung Soo from the White Team this time.
That's right.
[You can't be thinking...]
[The player from their most recent battle?]
We have no other choice but to use
our most secret weapon.
And I'm your ultimate weapon?
I think our team is just too weak.
[Miss Ultimate Weapon...
Please take care our biggest opponents.]
[Time for the players to enter the ring.]
[Myung Soo]
[Suk Jin]
[IU]
[All three players are totally unexpected.]
They sent IU in thinking that
I was going to enter that ring.
- You can't betray us, IU.
- You have to eliminate Suk Jin first.
[Going after the Blue Team who has the
highest chances of winning the game.]
[Launching their joint attack..]
You're being tricked right now, IU.
[Enough!]
[Hits himself in the process.]
[An emergency self-treatment?]
Hey, you have to think about this, IU.
You can't let the Blue Team win.
You and Myung Soo has to get Suk Jin.
You have to be more careful, Myung Soo.
You have to grab his arms!
[Blindly launches into his attack.]
[Frontal face-off between the two
middle aged men?]
Rip it off right now!
[Suk Jin eliminates Myung Soo's name tag!]
What are you doing back there, IU?
I just got eliminated.
[Myung Soo- Out!]
I had no idea that he could do that.
[After three years on Running Man, even
Big-nosed Brother can handle this much?]
I was holding onto him so that
you could eliminate him.
What do you mean,
you were holding him down?
[Just then!]
[IU sees her chance and attacks!]
[He even manages to immediately
position himself in a defensive position!]
IU.
Hang on a minute.
If you'd sing for me in high octave,
then I won't eliminate you.
[Giraffe's helping hand?]
[Big-nosed Brother in danger!]
Hey!
What are you doing?
- What are you doing?
- Rip it off, IU!
[Big-nosed Brother- Out!]
You can't do that!
That's cheating!
No one told him to stand there.
We did it!
[Will his elimination be accepted?]
As a continuation from last week,
the WWF regulations...
[WWF regulations can be used, and accepted.]
I can't believe this!
[Unbelievable...]
[Miss Ultimate Weapon!
IU wins!]
- You really did great.
- You did more than your share of work.
[Red Team finally earns themselves a point
all thanks to IU's hard work.]
- No, please don't mention it.
- If it hadn't been for you...
The two of us wouldn't even have a chance
if it weren't for you.
[Since IU did more than her portion,
next one up will now be...]
Okay, I'll try my best.
- I'll try my best.
- Do your best.
It's all over if the Blue Team wins.
We have no other choice.
Feel the rage from within.
In the event that Jong Kook comes out,
we need her to go out there.
[Blue Team is feeling the pressure.]
You think that would be better?
[Will it be the Tiger that steps into
the den from the White Team?]
Three.
Two.
One.
Enter!
It's Ji Hyo.
I knew it.
Hurry up and help me, Ji Hyo!
[Blank Ji is helping protect Ro-Ro.]
Kwang Soo!
[Kwang Soo having been backed up
into a corner in the blink of an eye!]
[Throws Ro-Ro's name tag into the wind.]
[Ha Ha- Out!]
Ji Hyo!
[But Ace Ji Hyo still has the Giraffe's
name tag in her grasp!]
[You're doing great!]
[Please, Kwang Soo!]
There you go!
[Delinquent Ji Hyo rears her ugly head.]
Great job, Ji Hyo!
You're doing great, Song Ji Hyo!
Use both hands.
No, you can't have it!
Why does that look so familiar,
and why am I reminded of myself?
Daddy!
Look at what she's doing to me again!
Just end him right now.
There you go! Step on it!
[Steps on his half detached
name tag with her foot.]
I feel like I'm watching a
real UFC match.
[All she has to do now is to grab the
name tag and rip it off his back!]
[Kwang Soo's desperate escape!]
[But he didn't get very far, did he?]
[Save a Giraffe's life!]
[Why don't you go run off
and tell your daddy?]
[Angry Blank wins!]
Song Ji Hyo!
And thus, the Blue Team wins!
[Blue Team wins first place
for Octagon name tag elimination!]
Wow, Song Ji Hyo...
The first place winner has now been determined
but we have to decide the second place winner.
Okay, Kim Jong Kook is going to
enter the ring.
The last remaining players from the White
and Red Teams will enter on three.
- Okay, players, enter!
- Fighting.
[Barely managing to keep himself calm.]
- Okay. Are you ready?
- Ready.
[The beast.]
[vs. the Red Grasshopper.]
Feel the rage!
Feel the rage from within!
- This is the last round!
- Hey, Judge!
I don't like the look on the Red Team's face.
I don't think they're up to any good.
[There's no way that he could have
a happy expression on his face right now.]
That's just what he normally looks like.
He's trying to end this quickly.
[Plan is to lure him into Giraffe's grasp.]
Come over here.
- Come on.
- What is this?
Look at him.
He looks like a freaky monster.
Just pull the Giraffe down
from his perch.
Use Kwang Soo to knock Jae Suk out,
and use him as your tool.
- Am I allowed to do that?
- You can't do that!
[Yoo-ruce Willis' surprise attack!]
[In the blink of an eye while
Mr. Capable let down his guard!]
[I got you!]
[Ah... ambush attack failed.]
[But he still manages to throw
the Tiger off his balance.]
You almost got me.
[The game could be over if it hadn't been
for the Tiger's quick reflexes.]
[This Tiger is angry for real!]
[The Giraffe has been bothering him
for long enough now.]
What are you trying to do?
What are you doing?
Why are you grabbing him?
What are you doing!
[First thing first.
Get rid of the bothersome Giraffe.]
- What are you doing?
- What about it?
- You guys are trying to cheat!
Seriously... what do you think
you're doing?
[Just when the Giraffe has everyone
somewhat distracted...]
[Pulls Jae Suk out onto
the middle of the ring.]
You know what's about to happen, Jae Suk.
It's all over now.
- Don't make it worse than it has to be.
- Lean off to the side.
- Come here, Jae Suk.
- Okay, Kwang Soo.
Do you really think that I can drag him all
the way there Kwang Soo?
You know that's pretty much impossible.
[Let's just end this now.]
[Oh... a pretty tight competition?]
[Strength vs. Strength]
[A true face-off!]
[An eminent end is near!]
[I won't let you beat me!]
[Mr. Capable wins!]
- We did it!
- Yeah!
You almost had him.
[He was so close to getting him!]
- The tag was almost off his back.
- You did good, Jae Suk.
I just needed a little more.
This is the current count of the
wolf cards vs. the lamb cards.
- You can take this.
- It's possible that nothing's changed.
You may take this and go to the voting booth
to trade in your cards should you like.
[The Blue Team wins the final chance
to trade in their cards one last time.]
Okay, second place winner.
The White Team.
- Let's all take a look.
- Here you go.
[White Team also gets the current count
from having come in at second place.]
What have you done today?
Don't let the others see it.
[The current count-
Seven wolves vs. two lambs.]
[Just what...]
[Will the Blue Team members
trade in their cards?]
[Off to the final location.]
We have no idea who the winner
is going to be yet.
- It's possible that we could still win.
- Yes, that's still possible.
[The result will depend on whether or not
the Blue Team members will make a trade.]
We just need to match up the numbers.
[The fate between
the wolves and the lambs.]
The current score right now is
seven wolves and two lambs.
I have a feeling that the Blue Team
traded in their cards.
[Just how will the story of
the wolves and the lambs end?]
[Final location- Soowon's
World Swimming Competition Arena.]
[Diving boards!]
- We have to climb up there?
- Everyone, watch your step.
[Completely befuddled.]
Wow, this is no joke!
- What is this?
- This is no joke!
- What is all this?
- What the heck is this?
[What is going on at the final location?]
[Nine diving boards ready for their divers.]
Is there anything that you guys
won't do anymore?
- What is all this?
- This isn't even right.
I need everyone to stand in front of
their names on the screens.
Thanks to everyone
for all your hard work today.
It is now time to reveal
the final results.
[Standings of the wolf and the lamb card
count during the opening of the show.]
Okay, everyone needs to hold your card
with your guess close to your chest.
Everyone needs to step out
to the front of the diving boards.
[Step up to the front of the diving boards
with their cards held to their chests.]
[As predicted, fearless Blank Ji is already
standing at the edge of the board.]
You have to stand at the edge
of the diving board.
Do you all see Song Ji Hyo at the edge
of her diving board?
Everyone needs to stand at the edge like
Song Ji Hyo is doing. Come on, men!
[Phobia of heights rearing its ugly head
at a 3m diving board.]
I promise that the diving boards
will not crumble under your feet.
[What's wrong with all these guys?]
Okay, please follow Song Ji Hyo's lead.
[Finally... they all start to tiptoe
carefully to the ledge, one by one.]
Please come up to the edge of
your diving boards right now.
This is really scary.
The diving boards will not
give out on you.
Everyone just needs to stand in their
place like Song Ji Hyo's is doing.
[Moving at a pace that's slower
than a turtle's.]
Ji Suk Jin?
[And finally, even Big-nosed Brother
gathers up his courage to step forward.]
We will now reveal to you
the final tally of
the number of wolf vs. lamb cards as
a conclusive result of the race.
The person who guessed correctly
will win the gold bars as their prize.
And those of you who got it wrong
will probably go for a quick dip in the pool.
Ha Ha will lead by pulling out his card
and showing the camera which
of the two cards he has chosen.
Wolf.
Unbelievably enough,
my zodiac sign is that of a lamb.
[Ha Ha's original pick had been the lamb.]
[He swaps it out for the wolf.]
Okay, Kim Jong Kook.
Wolf.
[Jong Kook's card is also the wolf.]
Something about the wolf is a bit more...
I'm going to go with the wolf card.
I'm going to choose the wolf.
- Park Myung Soo.
- The lamb.
Do you think that the lamb
even suits you?
[A lamb face mask?]
[Current count-
Wolf:2 and Lamb:1]
Wolf.
[IU has the wolf card.]
[Current count-
Wolf:3 and Lamb:1.]
Okay, Yoo Jae Suk?
[There are already three wolves? Ones
who bet on three wolves are losing hope.]
Okay, we need you to pull out your card
and show us what you've chosen.
Okay, Yoo Jae Suk?
[Which card will Jae Suk show that
will seal the fate of several people?]
Wolf.
[Goodbye, Myung Soo...]
[Goodbye, Big-nosed Brother...]
[Yoo Hyuk had started off the day
by choosing the wolf card.]
[After considering his decision when given
the chance to trade in his card...]
[He decides not to trade it in!]
Okay, the current count of the cards is...
Four wolves, and one lamb.
[Current count-
Wolf:4 and Lamb:1]
[Only four cards left to reveal.
Kwang Soo's turn to reveal his card.]
[If his card ends up being the wolf,
then Jae Suk will also get eliminated.]
Okay, Lee Kwang Soo?
[Kwang Soo's card is...]
Wolf!
Five wolves, and one lamb!
Five wolves and one lamb!
[Current count-
Wolf:5 and Lamb:1]
[Goodbye, Yoo Hyuk...]
Jong Kook.
[That means that there's hope for Kwang Soo
and Jong Kook with their guesses.]
[With the guess of six to two,
Ha Ha may also have a chance at a win!]
[And Blank Ji also has a chance
at a win.]
[Which card will Ji Hyo reveal?]
[The wolf?]
[Or the lamb?]
[Ji Hyo's original selection was the lamb.]
[Would she have traded in her card
at the final conclusive round?]
The lamb.
[Ji Hyo did not trade in her card!]
Five wolves and two lambs!
[Current count-
Wolf:5 and Lamb:2]
[Only two cards left to go.]
[Gary initially chooses the lamb card.]
[Would he have traded in his card?]
[If his card is that of a lamb, then
Jong Kook and Kwang Soo are eliminated.]
[On the flipside, if it's a wolf,
then Ji Hyo and Gary are eliminated.]
[What will Gary's card reveal?]
Lamb.
[Gary traded in his card!]
No!
[Goodbye, Kkuk and Kwang Soo...]
Okay, the card Suk Jin is about to reveal
will determine who the winners are.
Those that are currently in the running for
the win are the two with the five wolves
as well as Ha Ha and IU who estimated
there being three lambs and six wolves.
As for the rest of you, you may want to step
closer to the edge to make the fall easier.
Okay, Ji Suk Jin. Please pull out
your card towards the camera.
And shout out in a loud and clear voice
which card it is that you have chosen.
Okay, on the count of three.
One, two, three.
[Please let it be the lamb...]
[Will it be the wolf...]
[Or the lamb?]
Lamb!
[In that case, the current count would be
Wolf:5 and Lamb:4.]
[Members who guessed wrong
go for a nice dip in the pool.]
Ji Hyo!
[Absolutely amazing...
Ji Hyo and Gary are the winners!]
How is this even possible!
This is amazing!
Today's Wolf and the Lamb Race
victory goes to...
Song Ji Hyo ad Kang Gary.
Congratulations.
[Wolf and the Lamb race-
Gary and Ji Hyo are the ultimate victors!]
I was so close.
Song Ji Hyo and Kang Gary win the race
from having guessed correctly.
Ji Hyo wins again!
[When it comes to gold...
Gold Ji Hyo is unstoppable.]
[Gold Kang Gary reaping the benefits
by sticking close to Ji Hyo.]
- You go up and take a look.
- How is it the two of you?
I can't believe you both wrote down the
same thing even when you weren't together.
You can use that gold to set up
your newlywed house.
I really do think that there's
something between you two.
This is why you need to
be good to me.
What are you doing?
- Why? It just felt natural.
- You guys do look natural together.
It's too bad for IU
because she worked so hard today.
- I feel bad that you didn't win any gold.
- Yes, I'm very disappointed too.
IU herself as a person is more precious
than any gold anyway.
[Where are those kind words coming from?]
Don't exert yourself.
You'll give yourself a nosebleed.
It's because I planted my face in
the water when I fell.
Thanks to both of you for making today
a very enjoyable day for us.
- And those two over there are the winners.
- How can this even be possible?
Gold Ji Hyo and Gold Gary!
[Gold Ji Hyo and Gold Gary win!]
Subtitles by DramaFever
[The tranquil peace...]
[Then suddenly out of the blue...]
What are you doing?
[Being locked down in shackles.]
[The unbelievable agony.]
[If they can't escape the agony,
then they'll destroy themselves!]
[Must find the key.]
[A fierce battle that must be fought
in order to regain their freedom.]
[Human beings slowly being
turned into monsters.]
Run away!
[Even though they seek to escape...]
[There's nowhere for them to go.]
[The agony closing in on them
more and more.]
[Must escape.]
[A race to save themselves.]
[An evil fate.]
I always thought that this would
mean that I could have you.
Because you're my woman!
[Most traumatic drama.]
It was so that I could have you.
[Must earn the crowd's heart.]
[Next week's Running Man-
Find the key to freedom.]