[Outrageous? Fragile?
The two faces of variety's big brother.]
[Hot as his name states, Lee Kyung Gyu.]
[And the two actors challenging variety-
Kim In Gwon and Ryu Hyun Kyung.]
[Bringing tons of laughter to the show
with unpredictable energy.]
[Sleek image of the big brother
kept hidden all this time until now.]
[And the long awaited psychic karaoke room.]
[Their surreal singing skills.]
[Their shocking secret abilities
to score a high score?]
[The meeting of their variety skills.]
[Psychic Karaoke Room]
Subtitles by DramaFever
[One fine day in April-
'D' shopping mall.]
[Waiting for Running Man members
at that location...]
[One mysterious man...]
[Do they know what time it is?]
Producer?
Sir!
[The big brother of the variety world-
Lee Kyung Gyu.]
- Hello!
- There you are!
[Shocked from seeing a face
he could've never guessed seeing.]
We're going to get to
go home early!
Run, run!
Hurry up and run!
- It's Kyung Gyu!
- Hurry!
[Running up to greet his big brother.]
[The two giants of the variety world's
surprising meeting outdoors.]
- Hurry! Hurry!
- What are you doing here?
- Who's next?
- Hurry up!
- Tell them to hurry!
- Ha Ha...
- Tell them all to come out together.
- Everyone together!
- Tell them to come!
- Why are you coming out one by one?
Tell everyone to come out now,
and let's get this over with.
Tell them to come quickly.
Run, run!
- Hurry up!
- Run!
[Grabs the megaphone.]
Hello, Sir!
[Increasing their pace to lightning speed.]
- Jong Kook!
- It's an honor!
- Suk Jin.
- Suk Jin...
- Hurry up and get up here.
- We don't have much time!
- Hurry up, Gary!
- Hello, fighting champion!
Sir, my name is Kang Gary,
also known as the fighting champion!
Stop doing stupid things,
and come over here.
Suk Jin, Kyung Gyu hates
things like that.
[Even the oldest on the show, Big-nose,
remains humble in front of Kyung Gyu.]
- Ji Hyo!
- Hurry it up! Run faster!
- Hello.
I don't know if you're all aware of this,
but Lee Kyung Gyu...
he's the icon of love and consideration.
He really is a titan in the land of variety.
[A titan in the
Korean variety show industry.]
He's like a father to us whom we all
respect and love in our hearts.
Lee Kyung Gyu has joined
our show today!
[Eternal big brother of variety land,
Lee Kyung Gyu!]
We can't leave out his name when
it comes to variety shows.
With truly pure intentions...
- With truly pure intentions...
- Yes?
I have come on the show today
for the sake of Running Man.
- I have no other intentions.
- Why are you all laughing?
[Did he really come on the show with the
sole intention of Running Man's benefit?]
While on the show...
don't you think that I should at least
be able to beat this guy?
I really think I can handle him.
For the first time in a long while, a truly
worth adversary has joined us today.
[A worthy adversary for
the Big-nosed Brother?]
I can take you out as easily as
snuffing out a candle.
I see that you're wearing
tennis shoes today.
Look at those shoes you're wearing.
[Truly seems determined today...]
I wore them since I'm making
an appearance on Running Man.
But I think this is...
the first time I've done an SBS Sunday
variety show with Kyung Gyu.
- You're right.
- Isn't it?
This is my first time appearing on
an SBS weekend variety show.
This really is your first time.
And when it comes to Lee Kyung Gyu...
he really likes to listen in on
his juniors talking.
But useless conversations...
and anything that's not very
interesting...
If that's what you're going to talk about,
it's better not to talk at all in his opinion.
[Don't even think about things like that...]
If it's not funny,
I don't react to it at all.
[Big-brother's cut throat reaction.]
Even though we've been hearing this often,
you are the icon of consideration...
and you are also known as
the icon of love.
What is it that we'll be doing with
our iconic brother, Lee Kyung Gyu today?
How are the teams going
to be split up?
Senior Kyung Gyu...
do you have anything you'd like to say?
- Anything you'd like to say?
- Me?
Well, you know, I...
[Huh? Did he forget something?]
- This is your first time on our show.
- Running Man is...
- What would you like to say?
Running Man has always been
one of my favorite shows...
- I will do my best on the show today.
- Of course!
[To say such nice things like that...]
- What nice words!
- But...
- What about the teams?
- We have to divide up the teams...
How should we divide up the teams?
Are we evenly numbered?
- I think there's an even number of members.
- Two, four...
- Eight people.
- Perfectly numbered.
Don't you think that there should be
at least ten people?
Did you bring some people
on the show with you today?
- Who did you bring?
- Kyung Gyu, who did you bring with you?
Did you bring someone with you?
- What?
- Did you bring others with you?
Did you bring some other
actors on the show with you?
You're not here for us?
If we were to do the show
with some other actors...
If we were to do the show with them,
wouldn't it be livelier?
Of course, as long as it's fun,
it'll be great.
- That's why I brought two actors with me.
- Who are they?
Ryu Hyun Kyung and...
- Kim In Gwon.
- Ryu Hyun Kyung and Kim In Gwon!
[Because you need at least
ten people on the show?]
[Kim In Gwon and Ryu Hyun Kyung.]
[Along with these two who are often seen on
the variety circuit with the Big-brother...]
- In Gwon...
- Hello.
[Everyone already looks
pretty chummy together?]
[The two stars of a new movie that
Lee Kyung Gyu is producing at the moment.]
Please welcome these two
on the show today.
[Kim In Gwon and Ryu Hyun Kyung
also joining the show today.]
- We all know each other then?
- Of course, we all know each other.
- Then it's a good thing we came.
- This is really...
- I was afraid you wouldn't know each other.
- We all know each other.
Seriously though,
how many years has it been?
It's been about five to six years.
[The first movie he's produced
in about five to six years.]
I feel a little embarrassed to be
discussing my movie
so let's not talk about it.
No, you should keep talking about it
since you're on the show today.
But the way he said that...
it sounds like he was mocking me.
When it was just me earlier,
I didn't feel so bashful.
But now that these two are out here too,
I feel like I'm just here promoting the movie.
You think?
[Is the Big-brother really here
just for the sole benefit of Running Man?]
I will announce the teams for the day.
- We're going to be divided into two teams.
- Are we done talking about the movie now?
- You have something else to say?
- We still have a lot of time left today.
[Is he disappointed?]
So... how are we dividing up the teams?
- The first team is... Lee Kyung Gyu...
- Yes?
- Yoo Jae Suk...
Ji Suk Jin, Song Ji Hyo, and
Lee Kwang Soo makes up one team.
[Lee Kyung Gyu, Yoo Jae Suk, Ji Suk Jin,
Song Ji Hyo and Lee Kwang Soo.]
[And Jong Kook, In Gwon, Hyun Kyung,
Gary and Ha Ha.]
Then what are you saying? Are you
saying that we're not young blood?
We're young blood over here too.
[Significantly younger team.]
- By a stroke of luck today...
- Stroke of luck...
Our race today is,
Running Man Singing Race.
[Running Man Singing Race.]
Every time you pass a mission that will
be taking place in multiple locations...
You will gain coins for a karaoke room.
You will use those coins to challenge each
other at the final karaoke competition
and the team with the highest score will
become the ultimate winner.
Today's rules are very simple.
- Look at how happy Kyung Gyu looks.
- He looks so happy.
- Does he like the race described?
- Yes, he really like things like that.
[Seems extremely satisfied with
today's concept...]
[Singing Race- Start!]
We're heading off to the
sauna, Kyung Gyu.
[On their way to the first location-
Sauna.]
I wonder what we're going to do there?
Thank you.
Have a good day.
- Jong Kook has become so much more caring.
- Really?
I have noticed that he's become
much more caring than he used to be.
But if you mess up, it's over for you.
[A formidable ally if on the same team,
but impregnable if on opposing sides.]
I know that Ji Hyo was up all night
shooting her new drama yesterday.
[Blank Ji with her busy schedule lately.]
- Her cheeks are...
- There's no life to them.
[What is he saying?]
- I think I'm starting to really age.
- Why?
My dark circles are getting worse.
- You can't fool time.
- Hey! Why do you keep saying all that?
- Kwang Soo...
- Yes?
I'm going to be 60 years old
any day now.
I'm sorry.
Kyung Gyu even remembers you
by name, Kwang Soo.
- You should know that's an honor.
- I've seen Kwang Soo in movies...
I know that Kwang Soo is extremely
popular in Thailand and Vietnam.
[He even knows of his
popularity overseas?]
I memorized the few basics before
I came on the show today.
[This is the mentality of a variety titan.]
What were you like in the past, Kyung Gyu?
Ugh... I wasn't the scary person
as everyone seems to think.
- I've heard a lot of rumors.
- The rumors were wrong.
- That's what I thought.
- That false rumor spread like wild fire.
Rumors really can't be taken lightly,
you know that, right?
Are there any misunderstandings that
you'd like to clear up for us right now?
Here's one.
Rumor about me biting the writers.
[Misunderstanding I-
'Making the writers cry every day.']
The writers I work with these days...
they cry when we have to part ways.
Because they're so upset that I'm leaving.
[A knowing laugh?]
They're so disappointed to
part ways with me.
- That's how things are lately.
- I see, I see.
Back in the day, if I was to
come walking down the hallway...
like the parting of the Red Sea,
all the writers...
they'd all split down the middle,
and stick themselves to the wall.
[The writers would line themselves
up against the wall?]
- I heard they threw salt at you?
- What are you talking about?
- Kwang Soo...
- Yes?
That bit about the salt wasn't right.
I know that there were some rumors,
but I've never been pelted by any salt.
But you've always...
been very good to me.
- I think you've always been good to me.
- Of course, I was.
- I try to be good to my juniors.
- You were always very good to me.
There are a few people
that I don't like though.
I wonder how Park Myung Soo is doing?
[Mr. Park Myung Soo...
he's asking how you're doing?]
- Kyung Gyu, we're here.
- We're here?
[Arrives at the mission location.]
['S' Waterpark in Youngdeungpyo.]
Your first race is three step sauna race
to win the coins.
You will be playing a total of three games
with common items that you see at a sauna.
[Common items seen at a sauna-
Exfoliating towel, egg and fork.]
Neither age nor physique
will have any bearing on these games.
In Gwon used to be on a variety program
with us a long time ago.
That variety program used to be
pretty popular back in the day.
And the first person to get eliminated
during those games was always In Gwon.
[Was always the first to get eliminated
during the games.]
[The image he acquired during the days
of the old program still remains with him.]
He used to have a certain role that
he personified back then.
He used to be like Kwang Soo
back in those days.
He never got to show us his full potential
because he was the first to be eliminated.
- Jae Suk tried to save him...
- Yes, he did try to save me.
When he used to make In Gwon sing for
a chance to be saved from elimination
he would sing the song,
'The morning mist'.
[The song he chose to sing was,
'The morning mist'.]
[Even though it's a nice song,
I bet it wasn't very appropriate?]
I really thought that he had
lost his mind.
- I thought he'd sing a bright and happy song.
- I thought that too!
Even though that song is a very nice song...
Any other person would sing something
happy and cheerful.
He should've sang a happy song,
but the song he sang was depressing.
- Tell us something about Hyun Kyung now.
- Hyun Kyung?
- Hyun Kyung is...
- She's the female Gary!
- You're right!
- She really is the female Gary.
- I heard you two are close?
- She's the queen of festivals.
[Queen of festivals?]
[Specializes in livening up
the club scene?]
You know when most women dances
a sexy wave dance?
She'd be dancing
a hip hop dance instead.
[We may be able to verify that later...]
I really can't stand seeing women
dancing like that.
[Spitting out venomous words
as if he's been waiting for the moment.]
Let's just get on with the games.
Have we been talking too much?
Since the Orange Team was
the first to arrive
they can pick one of the items first,
and we will start off with that game.
- How about the exfoliating towel?
- Exfoliating towel?
- Okay, the exfoliating towel.
- Exfoliating towel.
What's the exfoliating towel game?
[The exfoliating towel game is...]
Is it the tug-of-war game?
The game we'll be playing with the
towel is the wrestling game.
[Exfoliating towel wrestling game.]
Wrap the towel around the waist
and pull your opponent
and the team to lose their footing first
loses the game.
- From our team... In Gwon will start.
- Okay, let's start with In Gwon.
- In Gwon!
- Then as for us...
- I'll start.
[Big-nosed Brother will start off
from the Orange Team.]
Do you know how to play this?
Have you played this before?
- This way?
- Have you played it before?
- You have to wrap it the other way.
- The other way?
- Seriously...
- In Gwon, In Gwon!
- Is this too short?
- What are you doing?
- In Gwon, In Gwon!
- This isn't right, is it?
You're not doing this right, Suk Jin.
[Coach Kook unable to withstand it any
longer, and steps in to interfere.]
You have to put your foot our like this.
Turn this foot around.
- What?
- In Gwon! Turn your foot around!
- Like this!
- Ah, like this?
If you do it like that,
Suk Jin's face won't show on screen.
- What are you doing?
- What?
[Ah...]
- That's how you're supposed to stand!
- Just turn your face around like this.
What if he's eliminated during his first try?
- If one of your foot drops...
- No, when both of my feet drops.
[Are they still trying to
figure out the rules?]
You're the culprit who's always
dragging out the filming, aren't you?
I can't help it that I'm in good shape.
You talk so much!
He's always talking nonstop.
[Tiger's chatter grating on
Big-brother's nerves.]
- His chatter...
- I'm sorry, I'll keep it short.
- Isn't this how we're supposed to do it?
- That's not how you're supposed to do it!
[Big-brother explodes.]
Don't even play it!
Why do you talk so much?
Just do it!
- Okay.
- Here we go.
In Gwon...
I'm not going easy on you, okay?
Ready... set, go!
[Start]
[One move, and he loses.]
[Takes ten minutes to prepare for the game,
and In Gwon wins in less than one second.]
- In Gwon!
- In Gwon wins!
[Getting more weaker and
useless by the day.]
He's good.
You stand over here.
[Kyung Gyu taking over the spot
where he'll be most visible.]
[Knows how to utilize the camera...]
That spot doesn't allow for
proper stance with your legs.
His comedic sense truly is...
His legs looks like a white person's legs.
[White as snow.]
Like a white person's legs...
like a white woman's legs.
How are his legs so white?
[In Gwon vs. Kyung Gyu - Start.]
[Quick hand moves!]
[You've still got it, Kyung Gyu...]
- Didn't he used to do martial arts?
- You've still got it, Kyung Gyu!
Kyung Gyu used to practice Kung Fu.
You have to watch out for
In Gwon's moves.
This move In Gwon does...
[Big-brother's sudden power!]
- How did he do that?
- Wow... how did that happen?
[See that?]
[Seems as though his
martial arts skills aren't dead yet!]
- Next up is...
- You have to watch out for him.
- Next up is... Ha Ha? How about Ha Ha?
- Hyun Kyung.
[It seems as though he's targeting the two
people that he's feeling confident about.]
Why can't I do that?
Why... why isn't she allowed?
Are you making your pick?
I'm on a roll here.
[Kkuk taking the challenge.]
- Okay, let's do this.
- Don't get nervous, Kyung Gyu.
[Competition between strength
and experience?]
- This isn't about strength, but it's skills.
- But he already feels...
Don't worry.
They're finally going at it.
The two who are angry 24-7...
[A battle between two men who are
always constantly getting angry.]
A battle of wills!
I heard that he used to practice martial arts
and I can feel the difference.
[Feeling the difference in
Kyung Gyu's strength?]
[Oh... even taking off his glasses?]
- Can you see without your glasses?
- Don't take this so seriously!
I want a spot on the show.
[Ah... really?]
You know what's coming, don't you?
Just concentrate on your singing career.
[Big-brother's confidence about
getting his Sunday night variety spot back?]
You're playing around too much.
- You've been doing it for 7-8 years already.
- I'm sorry.
- Shall I go?
- Go ahead.
[The exfoliating towel not even budging.]
Is there a need to go this far?
He's doing really well.
[His waist is staying alert
to stay in the game.]
He's good!
Look at the way he's playing!
He's not joking around.
[I will show you all!]
[Kyung Gyu enduring it with
a dignified stance.]
This isn't being played purely
with strength.
[Jong Kook wins...]
I thought you were showing us
a ballet move!
[Like a swan taking a tragic fall...]
[Both of his white legs falls out
of their stance and he loses...]
I thought you were doing ballet!
- Did you have to win that badly?
- Jong Kook, seriously...
Kwang Soo!
[Next up is a tiger attacking giraffe.]
- Kwang Soo...
- Move over!
Are we going to keep switching spots
back and forth like this?
- Here.
- Your arms are much longer, Kwang Soo.
Just hold it and stand still.
No, just let go for now.
[Trying to make Kwang Soo suffer
as much as he had to take earlier?]
[Just why...]
Why does he have to grab it like that?
Who says he has to grab it like that?
- Why are you making him grab it like that?
- He should just grab it as I hand it to him.
You've got a bad demeanor, don't you?
Your right foot!
[Keeps taking out his aggravations
out on Kwang Soo.]
Let's move over to the middle.
Ready...
set, go!
That's the way to do it, Kwang Soo.
[Playing around leading him to defeat.]
- This is how you play it?
- You have to pull back, Kwang Soo.
Kwang Soo just told you
that you're hurting him.
Your opponent is telling you
that you're hurting him!
Seriously... it really hurts.
How can you be so uncaring?
Take a little break,
and I'll teach him a lesson.
[Kyung Gyu's original image
is making a comeback.]
- Finally, Lee Kyung Gyu is back!
- Lee Kyung Gyu!
- Kyung Gyu is back!
- He just told you that he's hurting!
- It really did hurt.
- Let's do it again.
Are you his parent or something?
No one can stop him now.
If he says do it again, then do it again.
[Restarting the competition.]
Set, go!
Not bad, you might have a chance.
Kwang Soo...
- It hurts.
- What are you doing?
- Huh?
- It hurts.
- Just do it.
[Second chances are up to
the Big-brother's discretion.]
It feels like I'm tied up to a tree.
Kwang Soo, try pulling.
Unravel it, and then pull it back.
There you go.
Unravel it and pull it back.
[Giraffe's crumble from having
believed in his Big-brother.]
Are you okay?
- Get back to the line.
- My ears are ringing.
[Jong Kook wins.]
Maybe your inner ears are trying
to change the channel setting?
[Exfoliating towel finalists:
Orange Team's Ji Hyo vs. Blue Team's Gary.]
- You again?
- Yeah, it's me!
- Come over this way.
I'm not as strong as Jong Kook is.
- That's true.
- Why are you saying that?
I know that you're known to be
quite the fighter.
I thought you said you were
a master in martial arts?
- I thought that you said you were good?
- This is the highest I can even kick!
- Then why did you tell us you were a master?
- How are you a master?
[Kang Gary is rumored to be a
master of martial arts.]
Third level. I have a third level belt
in the art of love.
[He may not know about martial arts...
but a level three belt in the art of love?]
- He's at least a level three.
- Level three in love?
Level three in love...
- Ready?
- Ready!
- How do I do this?
- Ready, set, go!
Are we playing hard to get here?
Is that what we're doing?
[Level three Gary having changed the game
to a form of love foreplay.]
You guys are seriously...
[Is this a form of a hard-to-get scene that
one would see being played out at a club?]
- That's nice.
- You guys do make a nice picture.
These two seriously...
I'm sorry, Ji Hyo.
I have no other choice.
- She's pretty good.
- Ji Hyo's no easy target.
- Is she putting up a good fight?
- Of course, she is.
[Blank Ji's sudden counterattack!]
[Blank Ji wins.]
- Did that really happen?
- I'm good at martial arts!
- That was seriously...
- Wow...
[Orange Team wins the first round!]
There are two other items left.
There's the egg and the fork.
- What do you want to do?
- How about the egg?
- Egg.
- We'll do the egg.
[Next up is the egg game.]
The next game up for the
three round sauna game is...
It's the egg eating game.
You will find that there's a tray
of eggs set out before you.
Amongst them... there is one raw egg.
[Just one out of the 30 eggs
on the tray is a raw egg.]
The team that chooses the raw egg
loses the game.
[Will take turns to crack open an egg,
and the team that chooses the raw egg loses.]
- It's a very simple game.
- This sounds like fun!
[A simple yet a nerve-wrecking game.]
[Even if the hand grazes the egg,
that egg will be deemed chosen.]
To be honest...
I was in the chicken business
for ten years.
[Kyung Gyu's deep history with chickens?]
[Can tell just by looking?]
I can tell if the egg is fertilized or not
just by looking at it.
It's so easy for me to tell the difference
between a hardboiled egg and a raw egg.
- I think I'll be able to tell too.
- I see it right there.
- Where?
- There.
- It's that one.
- Which one?
What's the difference between
the raw egg and the hardboiled egg?
- Huh?
- What's the difference?
- Hang on...
- Why?
How many years have you
been doing this?
How many years have you been doing this?
You're a funny kid.
Did you hear that?
Kyung Gyu told me that I'm funny.
But I noticed that you don't speak
very harshly to Jae Suk.
- What?
- You don't speak harshly to him.
[Immediate discomfort]
What have I done wrong?
[Grabbing him by the throat.]
Why are you trying to grab me?
You should be grabbing him!
Kyung Gyu!
You grabbed your foot with that hand!
I already told you this earlier, but
Kyung Gyu's always been very kind to me.
- I wonder why he favors you?
- Hey...
Is it because of his popularity?
It wouldn't be very nice of me to
like him just because of his popularity.
I started liking him back
when he was still pretty anonymous.
- Really?
- That's right.
Did you know who I was even back
when I was anonymous?
The Kyung Gyu I know doesn't like
people who aren't famous.
Kyung Gyu!
[Kyung Gyu's affection fluctuates
depending on the popularity level.]
Seriously...
How should we start the game?
Since you won the previous game,
you can decide who goes first.
- They can go.
- Let them go first?
[Blue Team to pick the first egg.]
We go back and forth taking turns, right?
[Of the 30 eggs, only one is a raw egg.]
- This is the one I choose.
- One in thirty chance?
Come on, you have to hit it harder.
[King of cry-babies.]
You find this painful too?
- You want me to do it for you?
- There you go.
- Forehead seems easiest.
- Enjoy your egg.
- Miss Blank?
- Look very carefully.
You have to look very closely.
- There are 30 to choose from.
- Just choose one.
- Break it on your forehead.
- Your forehead.
There you go.
[Fearless Blank Ji's head butt.]
What kind of a woman are you?
- I didn't think it'd hurt like that.
- I can't believe the cracking sound it made.
Miss Song... she carries 80%
of this show.
[In Gwon's turn.]
- Once in a while, you...
- Why do you have that funny expression?
[Once chosen, can't switch out!]
- You have to keep that one!
- You can't switch it out!
- Do it on your forehead.
- Do it right.
[Lucky! Pass.]
You scared me.
Why are you all so afraid of this?
If that egg had turned out to be raw,
that would've been classic variety material.
- Kwang Soo!
Kwang Soo, you think the god of variety
could be smiling down on you again?
It was a hardboiled egg.
[Sense of unease increasing as more
people pass one by one.]
Ugh, that scared me for a moment.
[Gary also passes.]
- This is just pure luck.
- You can't think too hard about it.
- I'm getting nervous.
- Okay.
- Are you taking off your glasses?
- Okay, go ahead.
[Big-nosed Brother passes.]
- Do a wave.
- Don't pick the raw egg.
- Just slam it on your head.
- Maybe we can win this one.
[Pass. Hyun Kyung also
gets a hardboiled egg.]
- Kyung Gyu...
- Show us what you can do.
Save our show for us, Kyung Gyu.
Take a very close look, and
save the show for us, Kyung Gyu.
Kyung Gyu, do this for us.
Let the egg yolk sit right between your
eyebrows and become your third eye.
Please save our program today.
Crack the egg so that the yolk looks like
your third eyeball on your forehead.
- If I get the raw egg, we win?
- No, we lose.
- We lose.
- Oh, we lose?
- But that would make the show funny.
- We can't lose.
That would make the show
very funny though.
- What if that's raw?
- This is definitely a hardboiled egg.
It's a given.
[Immediately passes.]
- I hope Kim Jong Kook gets it.
- Yeah. The way he's been behaving all day...
[Been definitely pegged
as the least favorite.]
- I'm just playing earnestly.
- What?
- You're saying that's all it is?
Watch the program and see if
that's all it is.
You're more talk than anything else.
[His no-nonsense straight talk.]
Just pick one, pick it.
- Get it, Kim Jong Kook.
- Just pick the raw egg.
Just pick one!
[Coach Kkuk also passes.]
There's no need to start
worrying yet.
- He always seems to get caught.
- I know.
I doubt that.
It's not time for that yet.
[Jae Suk also passes.]
- Next up is...
- Dong Hoon.
[Made one full round,
so there are 20 eggs left now.]
- How many are there left?
- Ten of them are gone now.
- Okay, here I go.
- It's okay. It's still okay.
[Ro-Ro passes.]
- I really hope Ji Hyo gets it.
- What did you say?
- I bet it's the raw egg.
- No way.
- I doubt it.
- It's not time for that yet.
- I have a weird feeling about it.
- It's okay. Do it with confidence.
- That's such a relief!
- It hurts!
How come it sounds so loud
when you crack it?
- Oh my...
- She must have a nice forehead.
- Her forehead must be strong.
- You crack it so nicely.
It sounds like she's cracking it
with a nail and hammer.
- In Gwon...
- You have a nice forehead.
[In Gwon's turn]
- I bet it's In Gwon.
- In Gwon!
[Safely passes again]
I don't think it's going to be him.
Kwang Soo usually gets things like this.
- I still have a chance.
- He always gets things like this.
[There it is!]
[Shocked]
[Why do things like this
always happen to Kwang Soo?]
Things like this always
strangely happen to Kwang Soo.
All the real comedic things happen to him.
Here, I'll massage it in for you.
- It's just so weird!
- Kwang Soo, raw eggs are good for your skin.
Maybe the variety gods
are looking down upon you.
[Things like this and his popularity in
the Southeast are inexplicable.]
- Did a staff member tell you?
- No, he didn't know.
[So uncanny that people are even
starting to suspect him.]
What do you mean, you're jealous of me?
This is something that anyone in
variety would want to happen to them.
No kidding!
[The next round is-
One raw egg in a tray of 20 eggs.]
This time, instead of 30 eggs,
there are only 20.
Let's just count this as lunch,
and not waste time eating lunch.
Okay.
[Encouraging others not to waste time by
eating and dragging out the time any longer.]
- Why bother eating lunch?
- He thinks this should be our lunch.
We can end the shoot early,
and go out to eat something good.
What do you want to do by finishing early?
That's what I'm always so curious about.
What do you always do by finishing
up the shoot early?
Do you go home?
- Your wife thinks you work late, right?
- She thinks you work until midnight?
Most people usually thinks that I
shoot through the night until the morning.
[Open talk show?]
- We often shoot late into the night.
- You know it always happens.
We'll start with Kwang Soo.
- Okay.
- Start us off, Kwang Soo.
- If you get it again this time...
- That would seriously be...
- There's no way he'd get it.
- That would be crazy.
[No way!]
[The god of variety is smiling upon him.]
[Even though we just witnessed the scene,
it's still hard to believe it happened!]
Hey!
How can this be?
[Truly shocking and astonishing.]
Hey... that's unbelievable!
[Of all the eggs out of 20,
the one he chooses happens to be...]
The variety gods are smiling
down on you!
If this was a match,
we'd have to throw in the towel.
[Game two - Blue Team wins!]
[Streak of bad luck
that seems to know no end.]
[Icon of bad luck...
his name is Giraffe.]
How can you be so unlucky?
No, he is lucky!
He is very lucky.
If you look at it personally,
you have no luck. But on the variety side...
[Giraffe ending the game in one blow.]
- The gods are seriously looking out for you.
- The variety gods are helping you out.
- Can't we still have our turn?
- I'll massage it in for you.
You should massage it in.
This is seriously...
Since we don't get to play this often,
shouldn't we at least do it once more?
- Aren't we done with this game?
- Not fair that you get to do it all.
What wrong have I done?
What?
We're going to be done early?
Even though I like that this game
ended so quick...
Seriously... I'm not playing.
- I'm not playing.
- Out of 20 eggs, how could he...
Then we should move on
to the last game.
What is the last game?
What are we playing?
What is this?
[It's a fork related game...]
The next game...
is the coin rolling game.
You have to roll the coin to get it to
stick to the prongs in the fork.
[Roll the coin to stick between the prongs.
First team to score three points wins.]
You have to roll it to stick it
between the prongs.
- I guess it's possible.
- I think you can roll it in between.
All the games being played today are something
anyone can play as long as they're breathing.
- What are you saying?
- How can you say it like that?
How can you say that to my big brother?
[Kkuk keeps on provoking Kyung Gyu.]
- How can you say it in those words?
- I was talking about the game!
Why are you just sitting there quietly,
Kyung Gyu?
Are you saying that he's just
sitting here breathing right now?
I was talking about the games.
I was describing how simple they are.
To be honest,
just as Kyung Gyu said earlier...
that with the movie release coming up,
he says he's unable to sleep these days.
- He can't even sleep.
- I'm sure it'll be a success.
Hey... stop sounding so condescending.
- I just said it'll be successful!
- You sounded condescending.
I was being very sincere!
This was your expression when you said it.
'I'm sure it'll be successful.'
[Getting angry at the insincere way
Kkuk made his comment.]
- I didn't say it like that!
- Yes, you did!
If you had said, 'You'll be successfully',
it would've been totally different!
- You really think that's the way I said it?
- Don't even talk about my movie around me.
- Brother, that's not how I meant it.
- You...
Don't call me your brother.
Save that for your real big brother at home.
- You do as I tell you!
- You can call me 'mister' from now on.
Just call me 'mister'.
What do you think you're doing?
Don't act like we're close.
Don't you think this is hilarious?
The way he just exploded like that?
I love things like this.
It feels really lively in here now.
[A lively guest who refuses to be
treated like a guest on the show.]
You are still the same as ever.
- Seriously..
- Let's start rolling.
- Okay.
I will give you all a moment to
practice first.
- Practice?
- Can we try it now?
[Huh?]
Mister!
Why are you doing that?
Our team is trying to play.
[Actively interfering with the
other team's practicing.]
- I bet that's got to be really annoying.
- Mister!
[Plans to interfere outright
to make them too upset to play.]
When I was a younger, there was
this arcade by my house...
and the owner of that arcade room
used to be kind of infuriating like this.
- You know those mean store owners?
- And nothing was for free, right?
- Over.
- Over?
In Gwon, you go first.
Challenge.
- In Gwon...
- You think you can do this, In Gwon?
- Give it a try.
- I think I can do it.
[Oh?
His throw is...]
[The coin rolling at a super-fast speed!]
I bet if you aim it right,
it'll really get stuck there.
[Will his throw make it?]
[Ah, his throw is slightly off the mark.]
[Ah... too bad!]
[In Gwon- Fail]
Even though he has the skills,
the variety gods don't like him.
[Even with his skills,
the gods aren't favoring him.]
[Kkuk's turn.]
That's the best you can do
with those arms of yours?
[So close, yet fails!]
- That was so close!
- What do we do?
What's the point of having big arms?
Next!
- It's because you're sitting up there.
- I agree.
[Say what?]
[Fine then, I'll turn around.]
[The Big-brother's chic back turn?]
How's that?
Ha Ha's usually pretty funny.
[Ha Ha's turn]
[Ah... so close!]
- He's got it.
- He's got it!
[Another close call!]
- Wow... I thought that was going to make it.
- It's not easy getting it in there.
[Blue Team- Zero success.]
[Orange Team's turn.]
Like this, Ji Hyo.
[Blank Ji takes the first turn.]
There you go, there you go!
[Too bad...]
Fail.
[How will she do this time?]
- There you go, there you go!
- Nice!
[What!]
[It went in!]
[Amazing!]
[An amazing woman...
she truly is our Blank Ji.]
Wow...
How does she do it?
How can she be so good
at everything?
Ji Hyo always does well,
but Kwang Soo always does bad.
- You're right!
- She does well at everything.
- We need both of them on this show.
- That's what I'm saying.
So that's why the team they're on
never gets to win at anything.
They zero each other out.
She wins and he loses.
Challenge.
[Icon of bad luck, Kwang Soo's turn.]
Kwang Soo's luck, he'd knock that out.
He'd totally have the comedic effect
of knocking it out of place.
Kwang Soo would more than do that.
You can do that.
- I'll do it fast.
- You're doing good.
[Oh?]
[Wow... Kwang Soo also succeeds!]
[The variety gods must favor him...]
We've got two now.
[Orange Team with two successes already.]
Kyung Gyu it's your turn.
Kyung Gyu's taking his turn,
so let's all be quiet.
[Gets upset with everything that comes
out of Kkuk's mouth.]
- Just be quiet!
- What did I say?
- What? I was trying to help you!
- Just stay quiet!
I know I told you not to say anything.
- If you do this, your movie will be a hit.
- No, don't say things like that.
Put the success of your
movie on the line.
Don't say that.
[Will Kyung Gyu...]
[Oh my!]
[It went in!]
Mister!
It's going to be a hit!
[Is this really a sign of a hit?]
- Wow, that really was awesome.
- There are two 'Misters' in our country.
Won Bin and Lee Kyung Gyu.
And thus, our Orange Team wins!
[Orange Team wins!]
[The winning team can choose their coin.]
[Must choose between
the gold and the silver coin.]
This is brighter.
This one looks more expensive.
With how shiny this one looks...
it makes us think that we should be
taking this one, right?
So since this one is shinier,
we should take this one, don't you think?
- You're saying you want this one?
- Since this is shinier, we should take this.
[The Orange Team ends up choosing
the shinier of the two, and takes the gold.]
Okay, we'll take this one.
[Seoul's 'E' Center in Sangamdong.]
[What kind of a mission
awaits them this time?]
Dodge ball is a real game.
[A dodge ball game?]
Okay, here's your mission card.
- How is it those two go up together?
- They're always like that.
Stop following me around.
It's annoying.
[You lose if the ball hits the king.]
Then I guess Kyung Gyu will be the king?
- Kyung Gyu...
- Since he's the king of variety...
Chairman of variety...
god of variety.
[Orange Team's god of variety
is Kyung Gyu?]
[The king from each team will be
the oldest person on the team.]
- Then you'd be the king.
- I usually get hit all the time.
King of comedy and king of singing...
So you two can be the kings,
and your servants can then protect you.
[The team members must
protect their king.]
[If the king gets hit,
then the team loses.]
- I like things like this.
- Being protected.
[Big brother enjoying being protected
by his loyal subjects.]
The last protector left on the field
cannot be ousted.
That person will remain to the end
to protect their king.
We're going to play best out of three.
We need to decide who'll go first.
Both teams needs to go stand
at the edge of your line.
Okay, place the hat on your king's head.
I've never seen Kyung Gyu
wear a beanie hat.
[A rare moment?]
[Big brother being transformed
into a wooden match.]
- You have to fold it over a little.
- Really?
- Yes.
- Like this?
Kyung Gyu's really holding
himself back right now.
- Kyung Gyu's really changed!
- I told you that my personality's changed.
If it was still back in the day,
he'd never put up with this.
He'd be telling you not to bring it out.
- He would never have worn that.
- Because it's too much.
[But somehow, he's been transformed
into an icon of love and consideration.]
Okay, ready...
The team to grab
the ball first gets to attack.
Ready...
[Giraffe from the Orange Team
was the fastest!]
[Backtracking]
- We've got it.
- It's okay, Dong Hoon. Next time.
- There's no way I'd get hit in this spot.
- Even if the ball is thrown...
Even when they throw the ball,
we'd be able to block it from you.
Hit him directly.
We have to line up.
Guard Kyung Gyu.
[It's the Orange Team's turn
to play defense.]
[Suk Jin - Out!]
[Blue Team doing a good job
of escaping!]
[As soon as he's ousted, he grabs
an out of bounds ball to attack!]
- What are you doing?
[So frail all of a sudden?]
Be careful!
[Jae Suk - Out!]
One more.
There's one more.
[As soon as the ball's in the other court,
the team immediately gets into shield mode.]
[She caught it!]
[She catches that fast throw!]
- I can't believe it!
- Is she trying out for the Olympics?
Why is she so good?
She's not even a dodge ball player.
[Hyun Kyung showing
unexpected athletic skills.]
That ball should've been ours!
That's right!
[In Gwon - Out!]
[Hyun Kyung throwing the ball
with teeth gritted!]
Watch out!
Out!
Kwang Soo's out!
[Just then, the Orange Team
falls into danger!]
[If the king is hit,
the team loses immediately!]
[Ji Hyo just barely manages to block it!]
Kwang Soo's out!
[A bloody battle to take over the ball!]
Run!
Who's out?
Ji Hyo was ousted first.
Kwang Soo must stay in the game.
[With the king being the only other one left,
Kwang Soo must now stay in the game.]
Grab him!
Hurry up and get him!
[Kyung Gyu in danger!]
[Tough Hyung Kyung once again
gets ready to attack!]
[She hit her mark?]
What was that?
[Hands over it to her teammate.]
You have to stay back, Kyung Gyu.
[Giraffe having become a
shield for Kyung Gyu.]
[Beleaguered]
[Fragile Kyung Gyu sticking close
behind Giraffe's back in hiding.]
- Come this way.
- Pass the ball!
There you go!
[Giraffe steals the ball to attack!]
[Hyun Kyung - Out!]
[Kyung Gyu!]
[Huh...]
[Immediately falls into danger.]
[Unbelievably passes over the ball.]
[Throws his whole body
into escaping the ball.]
[However...]
[Will Kyung Gyu be ousted just like this?]
[Giraffe hits the ball out of the way!]
[Darn!]
[King Kyung Gyu barely escaping danger!]
Get up!
[King Kyung Gyu escapes his danger.]
Wait!
Time!
[Depleted of energy]
- I can't believe he escaped that.
- No!
Kyung Gyu really looks like a
frail female lead in a movie.
Can you get an ambulance ready for us?
Here I go!
Pass the ball around.
[The Orange Team passing the ball around.]
[Chance!]
[Succeeds in his attack!]
[King Jong Kook- Out!]
[Orange Team- 1; Blue Team- 0]
It's okay.
It's okay!
- It's okay!
- Wait...
Hyun Kyung, you're really athletic.
You look like a real competitive athlete.
[Unexpected shouts of battle cry.]
I told you!
I told you that she was like that.
- She looks like a real dodge ball player.
- Are you really athletic?
- You've played this before, haven't you?
- I've never played dodge ball before.
[On the other hand...]
- What are you doing?
- Kyung Gyu's exhausted.
[Exhausted King Kyung Gyu]
- Seriously...
- The match is about to light up on fire.
Once he's on fire, it's no joke!
Once he really gets angry...
Let's stop playing.
[Kyung Gyu's chatter
has all of a sudden ceased.]
I never knew... that Kyung Gyu was
so fragile or delicate.
- He's just so...
- I never knew either.
- You're like a little girl.
- You are like a little girl.
We have to win!
- We have to win.
- Fighting!
[Second set- Start!]
Okay, here we go.
Throw it hard!
Throw it fast.
[They all managed to avoid being hit!]
Low balls are the scariest.
[Fragile Kyung Gyu hanging on dearly.]
Send Hyun Kyung out first.
[Oh?]
[A knee kick from his own King Kkuk?]
He got me in the butt with his knee.
- You can do this.
- In Gwon!
[Catches the ball again!]
What was that?
Kim Jong Kook...
[Tough Hyung Kyung's fast throw.]
Look at the way she's gritting her teeth!
[Is it King Kkuk's turn?]
[Kyung Gyu's legs giving out on him
with the Tiger's lightening throw.]
Mister...
I'm sorry, Mister.
[Everyone doing a good job
of avoiding the ball.]
[Tough Hyun Kyung's turn again.]
[Jae Suk - Out!]
- He's out!
- I'm out.
Catch the ball.
You can catch the ball.
He's behind us.
Watch out, he's behind us.
[Huh?]
[It touched his hand...]
- I'm out?
- You're out.
- What are you doing?
- I was trying to catch it.
[Oh!]
[In Gwon losing his opportunity again.]
Why are you so bad at this, In Gwon?
[In Gwon - Out!]
- Get Gary.
- Throw it low.
- Gary...
- There you go! Gary, out!
- Gary, out!
- Gary, get out!
[In that case...]
[Tough Hyun Kyung to
protect King Kkuk...]
- You really are too much!
- That's not right!
- How does that make any sense?
- Lets just end this right now.
[As the king, Kkuk has no other choice...]
[Danger!]
[No!]
[Guard Hyun Kyung doing
everything she can.]
Hyun Kyung!
You're going to have to take the hit!
[Guarding her king!]
[Oh!
She caught the ball!]
[Huh?]
[After all her ferocious attacks...]
- The ball is ours.
- Here!
Don't throw the ball too carelessly!
[With Hyun Kyung being a better guard than
expected, they must play the game better.]
[King Kyung Gyu stepping in himself.]
[Passes off the ball!]
[With King Kyung Gyu's pass,
King Kkuk is in danger!]
[Tough Hyung Kyung throwing her body
in to protect her king!]
[Will she be able to block?]
[King Jong Kook - Out!]
[Orange Team wins!]
- I'm so tired.
- You should've stuck closer to her.
That was too bad.
[Orange Team showing fantastic teamwork.]
It's great.
[Trying to integrate himself in
the team with every chance he sees.]
- It's the same as before.
- Is it the gold and the silver coin again?
[Gold and the silver coin once again.]
You want to go with the same one?
- That's what I was thinking. You?
- Sure.
- What do you think?
- That sounds good.
Don't you think you've
gotten too nice?
Why are you asking him
for his opinion?
You've become way too nice!
- I just got goosebumps!
- What do you think?
- I agree with you.
- I've never seen this before.
- Should we go with this one?
- Let's stick to the same one.
[Orange Team chooses the coin gold again.]
Kyung Gyu... you've become so nice.
- Same as the other one.
- The next location is right next to here.
It's right over there.
It's inside that building.
[The third mission location is
inside the Seoul Energy Dream Center.]
- What is this?
- Are we doing a race?
[Which mission waits for them inside?]
- Why is there a monitor?
- What is that?
[16 different split screens
on the monitor!]
This is your last game before we
go into the final race...
It's the avatar one-on-one
name tag elimination.
Avatar?
It's avatar one-on-one
name tag elimination.
[Each team sends in one member at a time
into the name tag elimination game.]
You have to keep your transmitter on
and can only move as you're directed to move.
And thus, you must eliminate
your opponent's name tag.
Once a member is ousted,
the next person from the team must enter.
And the team with the final survivor
wins the game.
Please think carefully and choose
who will be the first avatar.
I think Kyung Gyu should be the director.
How should we designate the order?
Which style do you prefer?
Hiddink or Murino?
Which director style should I do?
[Is his style more along the lines
of Hiddink, or Murino?]
- His soccer style?
- Yes.
I don't... really know.
- What are you doing?
- I'll just wing it and yell it out.
Where you placed this is a little...
[Who will be the first avatar to go in
from the Orange Team?]
Don't you think sending Suk Jin in first
would be the best?
- Why is it always me?
- Since we don't know how this will go...
[Sending him in as experiment since
it's hard to predict what could happen?]
Let's go with Suk Jin.
[Orange Team's first avatar, Suk Jin.]
Look at the second stairwell.
- Do you see the stairwell?
- Yes.
When I tell you to jump,
I want you to jump off.
You want him to jump down
from the top?
[Rule: Must follow the director's orders.]
The reason being, we need the visual.
Even though eliminating the name tag
is also important...
[Director's theory:
Game is important too, but image comes first]
Let's all stand up.
[Blue Team's director is Ha Ha.]
We're going to get our revenge today
but you have to know
how to rip off the name tag.
[Sharing the wisdom of how to rip off
the name tags with the first timers.]
You have to snap it off.
All the little kids out there, watch closely.
[Showing the right way to rip off
the name tag in a safe manner.]
- Where is everyone?
- Sneak up on your target first.
If you rip it off like this,
he can turn around and escape.
That's why... there you go!
[Taking the time to attack
is a sure means of defeat.]
- This way...
- You have to concentrate and attack!
At all times... when you rip it off...
When you go in to rip it off,
with your left hand, grab the target.
Grab your target with the left hand,
and rip it off with your right!
[This is the years' worth of know-how.]
- Gary, out!
- Okay, I think I got it.
[In Gwon's turn to try.]
- You're saying this is no good?
- Because I can do this!
[Watch out for the counterattack!]
[That's why you must grab
the target with the left hand!]
- That's right!
- You have to snap it off.
Fighting!
[Avatar one-on-one name tag elimination-
Start!]
Fighting!
[Blue Team's first avatar, In Gwon.]
Wow, this is...
[An immediate face-off!]
- Is it In Gwon?
- They sent In Gwon first.
- Did he see him?
- If you see him, rip it off!
- There they are!
- He sees him!
- There they are.
- They're already facing each other.
[Even if they're facing off, they can't
move without the director's say.]
In Gwon... run up to the third floor.
Run off to the third floor.
- In Gwon's running away.
- He's running away.
You have to hide.
Hide yourself so he can't find you.
[Running away just as
Ha Ha is directing him to.]
You will wait.
Just stay there and wait.
- Shouldn't he go up more?
- No, I want you to wait.
You have to hide behind the door.
If you stay like that, he'll see you.
- Behind the door.
- Hide behind the door.
I think he went up to the third floor.
- Third floor!
- He's over there!
He's in the lecture hall on the third floor.
Third floor.
Let's have a face-off.
- Already?
- You don't think?
[Immediately taking his teammates'
hesitation into consideration?]
Sit down on that sofa for a minute.
Okay, I'll sit down.
- Now! The time is now!
- Come down to the second floor!
- Go back to where you were! Hurry!
- Get back down there and rip it off!
- Back down to the second floor?
- Go back to where you were.
[Orange Team is also following
In Gwon's moves.]
- He's coming back down.
- He's heading down to the second floor.
He's heading back down.
Watch your back.
Go inside that empty room.
- Into the empty room?
- Move fast! He's running away.
- He's hiding! Stop!
- He's hiding behind the box!
There he is!
- He's right behind the box!
- You're right by him!
He's right there!
[Avatar In Gwon starts his attack on
Avatar Big-nose!]
- They're at it!
- Rip it off!
[The avatar can only...
follow the orders of the director!]
- Rip it off!
- You have to eliminate him!
You have to eliminate him!
There you go!
[Avatar Big-nose barely manages
to escape his danger!]
Nice, nice!
Hug him!
Hug him to you and rip it off!
- He ripped it off!
- He did it!
[Blue Team's avatar In Gwon
eliminates avatar Big-nose!]
It's a good thing we trained him
before we sent him out.
[Seeing the benefit of sending him
off well-trained into the field.]
Avatar Ji Suk Jin, out.
Send in the next player.
Why didn't he pretend to be in pain?
He should've pretended to be in pain.
He should've pretended to be in pain,
and use that moment to escape.
You have to listen to the
direction carefully.
If the director tells you to pretend to
be in pain, you have to do it.
Please don't do it...
stop, don't do it!
- Hang on... that really hurts!
- Then how do I rip it off?
- There you go.
- He's really good at that.
- And then...
- That's it!
That's what I told him to do.
Kwang Soo, go in.
There has to be a blind spot somewhere.
Go find a blind spot on the third floor.
[Plan is to hide in a blind spot
where the camera can't pick him up.]
[Orange Team's Kwang-vatar going in.]
Turn around.
[Kwang-vatar so easy to see,
thus making it easy to direct him.]
Stay alert.
Move in slow.
You're moving too slow.
Where is he?
I don't see him.
We can't see In Gwon on the screen.
He's coming... he's heading your way.
Now! Now's the time!
[Avatar In Gwon's ambush attack!]
There they are!
They're going at it!
Go in!
You have to attack now!
Stick his back against the wall!
[Kwang-vatar pushing him against
the wall as he's instructed!]
Tell him to hold it.
If you think you're going to lose,
pretend that you're hurt.
Push his back up against the wall!
Go up to the second floor!
Run away!
What?
[Telling him to run away in
the middle of an attack?]
Run away!
[Must follow the director's orders
unconditionally.]
- Just run away!
- Get him!
- Go after him!
- In Gwon's doing a good job.
That's good!
Go get him!
Why am I running away?
[Blue Team's avatar In Gwon vs.
Orange Team's Kwang-vatar.]
[Avatar In Gwon eliminates two in a row!]
Avatar Lee Kwang Soo, out.
Send in the next player.
What do we do?
Why did you make me run
away back there?
Why did you make me run away back there
while I was attacking In Gwon?
The director doesn't have
the time to talk.
Get out.
He's in no mood to talk right now.
- I had his name tag in my hand!
- Sorry.
But you looked like you were
in trouble on my screen.
[Kwang-vatar had In Gwon's
name tag in his hand...]
Run up to the second floor
and run away!
[When he almost won... run away?]
All I had to do was pull off the name tag,
but you suddenly ordered me to run.
[His nickname is Kwang-vatar, but he
didn't even get the chance to play...]
[Avatar In Gwon already having
ousted two players.]
- It's a girl.
- It's Ji Hyo! Don't give her any breaks!
- It's okay!
- Ji Hyo's really good.
Call out In Gwon's name.
Call out In Gwon's name,
and go look for him.
In Gwon!
- In Gwon!
- Ji Hyo's a great actress too.
- There's In Gwon.
- I see him.
Second floor.
He's up on the second floor.
Go up to the second floor.
Call out to him.
Kim In Gwon!
I think she's going to come up the stairs.
You have to be careful.
In Gwon!
[Heading up the stairs
where In Gwon is hiding.]
Stay hidden in the stairwell.
[She's approaching!
Hide up the stairs, then ambush her!]
- Wait, In Gwon.
- She's coming up behind you!
She's right behind you!
Right behind you!
- Run back down!
- Run down the steps!
Run back down the stairs!
- I think we need to do something.
- Director Ha Ha...
Director Ha Ha?
Ha Ha is the director?
Oh my God!
Don't even respond to her.
Roll out your tongue at her.
Start right now.
[Obeying his orders so well.]
What are you doing?
Should I tell her to smack him?
Slap In Gwon.
Slap In Gwon in the face.
[Slap In Gwon on the face!]
[I was ordered to do it.
Sorry...]
Since you've been slapped on the left,
stick out your right cheek.
Stick out your right cheek.
- Tell her to slap your other cheek.
- Slap my other cheek.
- The moment she slaps you, rip it off.
- Slap him again.
[The headquarters is to
blame for this nonsense.]
Say it very firmly,
'Hey, Song Ji Hyo!'
Hey, Song Ji Hyo!
Let's do this!
Should we bring her down?
Start retreating backwards.
[Director Kyung Gyu telling her to
backtrack back down to the first floor.]
She's leaving.
- Run after her and eliminate her!
- Do it now!
Run after her and eliminate her!
Now's your chance!
Run!
He's coming!
Hide!
Stick to the wall right now!
Eliminate him!
Where did they go?
[A blind spot... all they can
hear is a shuffling noise.]
[Blank-vatar's ambush attack!]
[Her hand is on his name tag!]
[Blank-vatar eliminates Avatar In Gwon!]
- What happened?
- Avatar Kim In Gwon, out.
Avatar Kim In Gwon, out.
She did it!
That's our Song Ji Hyo!
[Ji Hyo's our ace.
An ace is an ace!]
Avatar Kim In Gwon, out.
- Send in the next player.
- What do I do? I'm so scared!
[Blue Team's Hyun Kyung Avatar going in.]
I saw the way you played dodge ball earlier.
It's okay, you can do it.
[A imminent face-off between
the female avatars.]
How in the world does Ji Hyo do it?
Where's their headquarters?
Should we attack their headquarters?
Let's go attack their headquarters.
Yes.
Go find their headquarters and eliminate
whomever comes out immediately.
I think it's on the
second floor somewhere.
I wonder who it'll be?
- I think someone's coming.
- She's lying in wait for you.
- She's right up against the wall.
- There she is to the right.
[The two avatars closing in on each other.]
- I know that you're behind that wall.
- Watch out! She's right there!
Back up against the wall!
She's right there.
They see each other.
- Hello.
Ryu Hyun Kyung...
Scream.
Scream right now.
Nice.
Start dancing.
Break out into a sudden dance.
[Ordering her to start
dancing out of the blue.]
[She's actually doing it?]
[Trying to figure out the reasons
behind her sudden dance moves.]
She's trying to entice you to attack her.
That conniving wench.
- Approach her... 'Who do you think you are?'
- Who do you think you are!
- I'm a dancing machine!
[Happy]
Turn around from her quickly.
Do a sudden turnaround.
- Like this?
- Turn around her.
Go behind Hyun Kyung right now.
[Director Kyung Gyu starting
to show his frustration.]
Rip it off!
Just rip it off right now!
- Just rip it off!
- Stand still!
[Hyun Kyung avatar shoves her back!]
[Completely satisfied with
Hyun Kyung avatar's brute strength.]
Eliminate her!
You can't get shoved around!
Ji Hyo... that hurts.
Please, that hurts.
[And like ace, Ji Hyo turns her body around
and avoids the attack.]
That was good.
Relax and show her another dance.
[As long as the director says...]
There you go.
- There you go.
- Enough. She's getting tired out.
Ji Hyo, listen carefully.
Listen to me carefully.
Listen carefully.
[What is she planning?]
Like this...
[What?]
[What is she doing to her
own name tag?]
[Blank-vatar self terminates herself?]
What the heck?
[What kind of a plan is this?]
Listen carefully.
Listen to me carefully.
Rip off the name tag on your back,
and give it to her.
What?
Give it to her, and once you do,
Jae Suk is going to go out immediately.
[Jae Suk avatar to go out immediately,
and spring an ambush attack.]
Like this.
Go.
[Jae Suk avatar makes his way in!]
Like this...
He just told her to self-terminate.
I think he ordered her to do it because
Jae Suk is going right in.
[Rushing to make her escape
out of fear.]
I don't think you should go that way.
[Hi!]
[Jae Suk avatar leisurely starts his chase.]
Song Ji Hyo, out.
- Hyun Kyung, make your escape.
- Tell her to come up to our door.
- Come up to our door right now.
- Come up here.
That's looks like our door.
Isn't that our door right now?
- Bring him up to our door.
- Bring him up here.
Up to our door.
There you go.
[Mr. Capable avatar getting ready
to go in immediately.]
[Luring him in deeper...]
[Hyun Kyung avatar counterattacks!]
Kyung Gyu!
What do I do with her?
[Jae Suk avatar is flustered.]
[She has it in her grasp!]
Hey!
[No... way.]
[Hyun Kyung does a circle attack!]
[Wow... she succeeds in
eliminating Jae Suk avatar!]
[Unbelievable turn of events!]
- How did she do that?
- I was getting ready to get out there.
[Plan fails...]
- Time for the director to come out himself.
- I'm sorry, Kyung Gyu.
Yoo Jae Suk avatar, out.
Director must come out himself.
[Orange Team's Director Kyung Gyu
to come out himself.]
He just saw you and went back in.
Tell him to come out.
Come on out.
I already saw you.
[What to do...]
[Blue Team's Hyun Kyung avatar vs.
Orange Team's Director Kyung Gyu.]
- I won.
- Is it over?
- What's over?
[Approaching her slowly by playing dumb.]
What's wrong with you?
[Director Kyung Gyu on the attack!]
Eliminate him, eliminate him!
- I can't believe that.
- Look at the way he's attacking.
[Director Kyung Gyu's
unexpected ferocious attack!]
[Hyun Kyung avatar in danger!]
[Ugh, my knees...]
Yes!
[Hyun Kyung eliminates Kyung Gyu!]
Director Lee Kyung Gyu, out.
Game over.
The game's over?
[Hyun Kyung avatar wins the game
for the Blue Team!]
Game over... it's game over!
- You sure you're not hurt?
- No, I'm not hurt.
- Wow... that was amazing.
- I got this one too!
Can you dance right now?
[Blue Team wins the gold coins, and
the Orange Team wins the silver coins.]
[Off to the final mission location.]
[The final location for the karaoke room race-
Seoul Town Hall.]
[A place with a mysterious bout of energy.]
- Please go on in first, Sir.
- I think we're really going to sing.
For the final mission,
as you can see behind you
it's the Running Man karaoke room.
- The two teams will take turns singing.
- Yes.
And we will see who gets
the higher score.
The team with the higher singing score
will be the ultimate winner.
The coins that you've been
earning today?
You can use those coins to win as well.
Depending on the color of your coins,
you have different songs to choose from.
[R1- 'Tears'; R2- 'End this night';
R3- Song of choice.]
[R1- 'Heartbeat'; R2- 'Shabang Shabang';
R3- 'Gangnam Style.']
[Squid?]
- What is that?
- Don't you know this dance?
- What is this?
- Don't you know that dance?
It's like this.
But what's this?
You will soon find out.
[Never know what can happen in
Running Man's karaoke room!]
Kwang Soo and Ji Hyo are going to
start off by singing, 'Heartbeat'.
The youngest of the group.
[Orange Team is using
one of their gold coin songs.]
- Do a good job, Kwang Soo and Ji Hyo.
- We will!
Make it fun.
Can you feel my heart?
['Heartbeat' by 2PM]
You look like Song Chang Soon right now.
She doesn't even know how
to sing the song.
[Just... what is the psychic power
that comes along with this song?]
[Blank and Kwang brother and sister
with no rhythm in their bodies.]
Why are they so bad?
[It seems like this is the dance
they're trying for...]
[This is the way to do it.]
[But, just then...]
[What?]
[Who are those people?]
[What... is that?]
[R1's psychic power...
ability to call in the choir.]
[Song's harmony suddenly filling
up the room!]
[Still unaware of the phenomenon.]
[Glorious sounds of harmony suddenly
ringing throughout the room.]
This must be the psychic power!
[Along with the acapella group, Genesis.]
[The dance song is
beautifully transformed.]
[Giraffe finding his stance with
the psychic power behind him.]
[Why are you so bad...]
[Listen to my heartbeat...]
The song has gotten so
much better.
[The swelling sound of their harmony!]
Louder!
They're amazing!
['Heartbeat' getting transformed with
the harmonizing voice of 50 people!]
[Heartbeat...]
[Bravo!]
[What's their score for having sang
the song with 50 choir members?]
[Blank and Kwang- 96 points.
A score they couldn't even dream of!]
- Are they helping us?
- That was amazing!
- I thought I was at a concert.
- That was unbelievable.
The only reason we got a score like that
was because all these people came to help us.
- Thank you!
- Aren't you going to help us?
I bet the power for each song
is different.
[The psychic power for each song is different
depending on the coin used.]
[Thank you to all the acapella group members
for coming on the show to help!]
- That was so cool!
- I can't believe we scored 96 points.
- Isn't 96 points too high for that song?
- I feel so moved by what just happened.
[Just because it was cool doesn't mean
that everyone should try it.]
[Next song to be sung by the Blue Team-
Hyun Kyung and In Gwon to sing 'Tears'.]
[Using one of their silver coins.]
This song is hard.
- Do you know this song?
- Yes, I know this song.
- What is that now?
- Why are you doing this to our team?
[The psychic power this time around
is the wire?]
I'll get on it.
I'm good at riding things like that.
I really like being on the wire.
[R1- 'Tears'.
How will the wire psychic power work?]
- You have to sing the song.
- You have to sing while you do it.
[Having to sing, having to get on the wire...
so much to have to do...]
This is what karaoke should be like!
[The song of all song in any karaoke bar-
'Tears'.]
[Wire is finally attached!]
[But...]
[How is the wire going to be put to use?]
[Automatic screaming reaction.]
[We'll even bring up the monitor for you.]
[Automatically breaking down into a scream
that brings up her voice five octaves higher.]
- You have to sing the harmony too!
- Is that supposed to help her?
[A nice and clean finish.]
You're good!
[With the automatic screams added in,
they score 98 points!]
[A very effective psychic power.]
It makes the screams come out automatically.
- But we have 'Shabang Shabang'.
- We do have 'Shabang Shabang'.
[Orange Team's next song is,
'Shabang Shabang' by Park Hyun Bin.]
[Orange Team uses a gold coin song.]
He's not bad.
[Park Hyun Bin's 'Shabang Shabang'.]
[Kyung Gyu and Big-nose singing a duet.]
I feel like I'm watching a real dinner outing.
They really are two middle aged men.
[The three employees
accompanying the bosses.]
[But what's the psychic power for this song?]
[The original singer...
Park Hyun Bin makes an appearance!]
[This is what you call psychic power!]
[We're all set!]
[The ability to call in the original
king of trots!]
- This is awesome!
- We're guaranteed 100 points!
[Wow... that's the true voice
of the song!]
This is so unfair!
[An unbelievable psychic power of
having the original singer sing the song!]
[Dance of joy!]
[Predicting a win?
Orange Team is already celebrating.]
But it's really exciting.
Don't you just want to break
out into a dance?
[If you're excited,
then join us in the dance!]
[Hyun Bin toying with his audience.]
[The king of trot brings the stage to life!]
[The power of the original singer's power-
99 points!]
If you're done singing, then leave!
- Why are you back here again?
- What's wrong with you guys? That's rude!
Have I been called in because of
some psychic power of yours?
I know that he's a very busy man...
[King of trot, Hyun Bin taking the time out
of his busy schedule to come on the show.]
[Seeing Hyun Bin make his appearance was
like seeing victory at the end of a battle.]
The choir coming out earlier,
and now Hyun Bin?
- This is really amazing.
- Why didn't you come out at first stance?
- If he had, it would've been a perfect score.
- Yes, it would've been 100 points.
I wanted to hear Lee Kyung Gyu sing
parts of the song before I came out.
A round of applause for
our friend, Hyun Bin.
[Orange Team's savior, Park Hyun Bin!]
- Thank you.
- Thank you so much.
[Thank you to Park Hyun Bin for taking
the time out of his busy schedule!]
Having Hyun Bin come out was
really amazing.
The really good news is that our
next song is 'Gangnam Style'.
- You think Psy will come?
- If he does, it's over!
[He was too busy to make it...]
[Gangnam Style's psychic power is
electric karaoke room!]
[Must pedal fast to generate the power to
turn on the karaoke monitor screen.]
[Must pedal to their death in
order to be able to sing.]
[Kwang Soo's rage filled pedaling!]
[Can barely even dance from
the exhaustion.]
[Switching out the peddler to
Big-nose and Blank Ji.]
Pedal, Suk Jin!
[The song's highlight that the whole world
is familiar with by now.]
You have to do the dance!
This is the highlight!
- How can you leave this out?
- What's the point if you leave it out?
You have to do this part!
- Pedal!
The chains out of place.
You guys are ruining it!
The chain is out of place.
[Back to pedaling!]
[The yellow guy into it!]
[But the music cuts off again.]
This is the lamest version of this song
I've ever heard.
[What's the score for this song
with the electric psychic power?]
- I really wanted to see Jae Suk's dance.
- More than anything else...
If this is the best I can do, then I
can't even leave the house for two days.
This is so frustrating.
All we had to do was keep going at the verse
when it says, 'Oppa is Gangnam style.'
What was I to do?
I got too exhausted.
[And the Blue Team follows
with 84 points.]
[Blue Team's last gold coin song-
A chance to pick their song!]
Their psychic power isn't about
picking out the song randomly?
That's what it truly means to pick freely.
What are you going to sing?
We're going to sing , 'Romantic cat'.
- Romantic cat?
- You're singing the musical?
Sweet little kitty?
What's that?
[Sung by: Hyung Kyung and
a legion of boys.]
[Festival lady revving up to
the main event.]
Byul!
- Byul!
- Sister-in-law!
[Hyun Kyung has a nice and clear voice!]
[About to explode!]
[A chaotic performance.]
[In Gwon's knocked out after
running into Kkuk.]
[Banging into this and that...
Blue Team is just full of energy!]
[In Gwon breaks out in a scream
from the excitement.]
[Scream!]
[Let's do it one more time!]
[Explosion of energy!]
[Blue Team's one last burst of energy!]
- Rock and roll!
- Yeah!
[Everyone applauding a great performance.]
- We'll sing one more song.
- Let us sing once more.
[Current score: Orange Team with 99 points.
What will Blue Team's score be?]
[What is this response?]
[Blue Team scores 97 points!]
[By two point difference,
the Orange Team wins!]
- We won!
- We did it!
Great job!
And unfortunately enough...
just when In Gwon found his rhythm,
it's all over.
- I really had a great time today.
- When In Gwon finally found his rhythm.
You really are the festival lady.
You were the best.
[Whatever the case, the ultimate winner of
the psychic karaoke room is, Orange team!]
[What's the winning prize?]
This is real gold here.
[Running Man singing race! A gold trophy!]
That's awesome.
- This whole thing is gold?
- No, just this part.
Why are you always trying to scrape up
all the gold on this show?
You think Running Man is
your gold shop?
Thank you!
Our singing race today...
Lee Kyung Gyu, Ryu Hyun Kyung,
and Kim In Gwon for coming out...
We had a great time today
thanks to all three of you.
We'd all like to thank you once again.
Thank you!
[Thank you to our guests for coming on the
show and bringing laughter to everyone!]
Here.
[Is Kyung Gyu gifting his winning trophy
to Hyun Kyung?]
[But after a closer look,
we realize he took the gold portion off.]
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Full of spring air...
on top of one very special ring...]
If you're a true contender,
you won't feel fear.
[A legendary battle revolving around
the king of all ddak-jji.]
[Time to determine
the ultimate king of ddak-jji.]
You can win this.
[Running Man's ultimate king of ddak-jji
will finally be determined!]
[And the wild beasts joining in on this
bloody competition to determine the king.]
[The challenger, Cha In Pyo.]
['Dunk ddak-jji' challenger,
Seo Jang Hoon.]
[And Mr. Capable of the
new generation, Ricky Kim.]
[All members of Running Man to join
In Pyo's fan club.]
[The legendary king of ddak-jji.]