[Running Man's representative couple-
The Monday Couple.]
[The Easy Brothers, who are
like one entity by this point.]
[Even with all their bickering, they
can no longer live without one another.]
[The famous couples of Running Man.]
[The strongest couple that will put
the rest of them to the test will be here.]
[The nation's couple, Lee Bo Young and
Lee Sang Yoon of 'My daughter, Seo Young.]
[The couple of destiny
will be determined today!]
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Jamwon district of Han River.
'O' riverfront cafe.]
[Running Man members gathered
together in one cozy place.]
[Ro-Ro and Giraffe putting
on a performance?]
[Banging away at the keyboard.]
They don't even know what
they're doing.
If you don't come stand over here by
the time Jong Kook counts to three...
he says he's going to beat you.
- One...
- Two...
You two don't even need
a second warning.
Gary, you actually look like a celebrity
for the first time in a long time.
- You're looking good, Gary.
- You're dressed up like a celebrity.
[Fashion conscious Gary...
Dressed up in celebrity style today?]
- Is this how you normally dress?
- Shh!
- Ji Hyo looks so pretty too.
- I think being in love makes her pretty.
What's going on with you two?
- What's going on between you two?
- I'm so confused by these two.
I told you not to wear high heels
during the opening scenes.
Wearing heels makes me look shorter.
So you have to help me look better.
- Yeah.
- That's right.
You have to take care of him.
In preparation for our fun race today,
we conducted a small survey.
These questions were formulated by
faithful viewers of Running Man
and of those questions, the best ones
were chosen through a round of voting.
Jae Suk, why don't you ask the questions?
Haven't we done something like this
before in the past?
Yes, we did. And we immediately
followed it up with a race.
- You're in first place.
- I'm so embarrassed.
I saw my name at the
top of the list.
- I don't know what it's about though.
- Gary placed first with 33% of the votes.
[What kind of a survey could it be that Gary
would place first with 33%?]
The member who still stands out the most
even when he is in disguise.
[First place for being most noticeable
even when in disguise.]
- Kang Gary is Kang Gary.
- Gary...
[What?]
[Kang Gary, strongly resistant to disguises.]
Thank you!
Kang Gary is Kang Gary!
- No matter what Gary does...
- That's very true though.
[No matter, first place is first place...]
What is this?
Popularity votes
according to our fans in China.
- China?
- It's according to a Chinese fan site.
- Really?
- Look at Kwang Soo's anticipation.
[New Prince of Asia's self-confidence?]
Why don't you reveal the results?
In seventh place...
Ji Suk Jin!
[Seventh place - Ji Suk Jin.]
Why are you announcing that so loudly?
- Why are you saying that so loudly?
- You looked at Kwang Soo as you said that.
- Okay...
- This is kind of nerve-wrecking.
- Ji Suk Jin with his 4%...
- This is interesting.
- Okay, here's the sixth place.
- This is making me nervous.
In sixth place,
with 7% of the votes...
- It's a 3% difference from Suk Jin.
- It's not a huge difference.
- Lee Kwang Soo!
- Seriously?
[What? Kwang Soo?]
That means I placed higher than you!
I guess he's not the
Prince of Asia in China!
[Vietnam's Prince.
Only 7% of the popularity in China...]
[Shock?]
- Is it really me?
- Yes, it is.
- You're at 7%.
- Aren't I the Prince of Asia?
I guess his popularity only goes so far.
- We're going into the double digits now.
- Double digit.
- 11% of the votes!
- Okay!
[Who did the Chinese fans vote for
fifth place with 11% of the votes?]
- Gary! Congratulations.
- Thank you.
It means that we've placed
higher than that!
Gary's 11% of the votes is the same as
combining that of Suk Jin and Kwang Soo's.
[Gary's 11% of the popularity votes equals
Suk Jin's 4% and Kwang Soo's 7%.]
- That's right! That's a clear result.
- Pil Chok Cross!
- Okay, in fourth place!
- Fourth place...
- With 15%... 15% of the votes...
- I bet it's Ji Hyo.
Ha Ha!
Nice, Nice!
It's okay. That's good.
[Asia's Prince, Giraffe...
is his pride wounded?]
In third place! With 16%...
One percent higher is Song Ji Hyo!
[In third place is Blank Ji.]
In first place!
With 27%...
Second place received 20%.
In first place... Me!
Me!
[Jae Suk's popularity taking over
a whole continent.]
How can he announce himself like that?
- Are you that happy?
- Thank you.
- I love you, China.
- Thank you... thank you so much!
I love China!
With how low his rank was,
Lee Kwang Soo right now...
I guess he should just go
back to Vietnam.
- What is this?
- What is it?
The order of best looking member
according to our guests for today?
[Chosen directly by today's
beautiful guest.]
This list excludes Ji Hyo.
- Then it must be a woman.
- There's no male guest today?
- This looks like a woman's handwriting.
- She wrote the list herself?
Yes.
[Popularity list that our guest
wrote out herself!]
[Fourth place?]
She didn't even write out who's
in fifth or sixth place.
- She's saying they're not even worth it?
- Not even worth mentioning?
Yes, she only wrote down four people.
Should I take out the two people?
The two that aren't even mentioned?
Okay, Ji Suk Jin!
There's one more person.
- Please... you can't exclude me on this one.
- Ha Dong Hoon!
Yes!
This is shocking.
- The two ugliest members!
- Wow... that means I made the list.
- Look, Dong Hoon's in shock.
- Don't you know how attractive I am?
[It seems as though our guest isn't
aware of those attractive traits of yours.]
You have no idea how sexy I can be.
I'm very attractive.
Do I need to show this person
how attractive I can be?
Okay, I'll start with fourth place.
- Who could it be?
- In the fourth place...
- I wonder who our guests is.
- Fourth place... Kim Jong Kook!
Me?
Did you say my name?
- Me?
- You belong here with us.
[Best looking list survivors
full of cheer and happiness.]
- Who's our guest today?
- Our guest today really is clueless.
In third place...
is me!
I'm in the third place.
Okay, between Lee Kwang Soo and Gary...
In first place...
[Who's came in first on the list of
best looking chosen by the guest today?]
Lee Kwang Soo...
came in at second place!
[The best looking member according
to today's guests is... Gary!]
- Gary came in at first place?
- Who could it be?
Gary?
- Gary came in first.
- Second place isn't bad.
- Congratulations, Gary.
- Thank you!
- Kwang Soo, you came in at second.
- Thank you.
Whoever our guest is today, I'm going
to take care of her no matter what.
In just moments...
we will be starting a couple race.
[Today's race - The best couple race.]
Our guests for today are a well-known couple
who don't fall short of our own members.
- I feel like we're at a wedding.
- I think that's where they're entering from.
[Guests' making their entrance.]
[Full of warmth and charm.]
[Who could they be?]
[Total surprise]
[Seo Young's couple,
Lee Bo Young and Lee Sang Yoon.]
[The two who've been classified as the
nation's leading couple through a hit drama.]
[The ultimate couple full of warmth,
the couple of Seo Young.]
[Welcome]
Bo Young and Sang Yoon...
please come this way.
You're the daughter all
mothers aspire to have.
I heard that you're very smart too.
I know that your weekend drama
just finished filming too...
Her face is so tiny.
[Warm and inviting handsome couple.]
- What a nice couple to have on the show.
- Who is this woman though?
[Still upset over the best looking list?]
- Why are you being so petty?
- You really are being too harsh.
Miss Bo Young, thank you so much.
- I can't believe you picked him.
- I will take care of you today.
- I can't believe he came in at first place.
- Seriously...
But why didn't you include Ha Ha
and Suk Jin on the list?
I was told that I didn't need to
write down the fifth and sixth place...
[Sorry]
- I'll reveal the teams.
- Okay.
- Yoo Jae Suk, Jong Kook...
- We're on the same team?
And our guest, Lee Bo Young...
the three of you are a team.
Why? That's going to make me
uncomfortable.
[Kkuk with some leftover resentment.]
That makes me feel uncomfortable.
Why did you team me up like that?
- That makes me real uncomfortable?
- Instead of first and second, she's with us?
We had already chosen the teams
before finding out about the results.
Why did you choose the teams without
even asking me for my opinion?
See?
She's disappointed about it.
I really should be taking
care of her today.
[Bo Young, Jae Suk, and Kkuk feeling
uneasy about the team placement.]
And next, Kang Gary and Ji Hyo...
you'll be a team with Lee Sang Yoon.
[Teamed up with Sang Yoon.]
Tra-it-ors!
Cross!
The Traitors Club is teamed up today.
Please show us lots of love and support.
[The unchosen ones
full of drive and ambition.]
But seeing the three of you lately
really has been nice.
These are the three teams that will
be competing in the race today.
I will explain today's race to all of you.
There was a lot of talk between
our guests and the survey conducted
and as I've mentioned to you earlier,
this is The Best Couple Race.
Through a series of missions, you'll
work to earn yourselves a running ball.
Running ball?
[Running ball makes its comeback
after all this time!]
The quicker you pass your missions,
the more running balls you'll earn.
These balls are currently blank
and devoid of any writing at the moment.
But when you arrive at
the final location
you'll write the names on them yourselves
to enter into the drawing.
[What will become of the lucky draw?]
[Best couple race - Start.]
- I like sitting in the middle.
- You do?
This is nice and bright,
but the pink color is a little...
It's okay, Jae Suk. It's going to
make our faces look brighter.
As long as Bo Young looks beautiful,
that's all that matters.
I think we're going to look
very bright and nice on screen.
Actually... you look really
ugly right now.
- What... you think you look pretty?
- Seriously...
Actually, I love the way
men look in hot pink.
- Really?
[Cheering up at Bo Young's comment.]
My skin is a little darker...
- So it looks sexy.
- That's what I'm thinking.
- Hot pink does that to darker skin?
- Of course.
Wearing it with darker skin
makes it pretty.
Especially with a V-neck shirt.
Jae Suk doesn't know that kind of stuff.
You don't wear V-necks.
Your collars go down to the chest.
What?
I don't wear shirts like that!
- I can't stand seeing you like that!
- When have I ever worn shirts like that?
There's a limit to the cut of the collar,
but yours comes all the way down the chest.
I really hate feeling suffocated.
I hate having things around my neck.
Where is this place?
Tree-lined street in Shinsadong?
[Go to the tree lined street in Shinsadong
and look for the Running Man landmark.]
Hurry, let's hurry.
I feel like I'm watching TV.
This feels surreal.
With how smart and studious Sang Yoon is...
I think he's going to be very competitive.
Sang Yoon's very athletic too.
- Look at what good shape he's in.
- He's very good at basketball.
He's very different from you, isn't he?
- Hey, Song Ji Hyo...
- That's not you, is it?
But I pull it off once in awhile
and get the job done.
'Random Mr. Capable?'
- You know...
- I will do my best.
Kang Gary should've been teamed up
with Lee Bo Young today.
- You must be disappointed.
- I can't betray you like that on a Monday.
Listen to you.
Why not? You were having fun with
Lee Yeon Hee a couple of weeks ago.
- Were you jealous?
- Oh my goodness.
- I'm a little jealous today myself.
- Don't kid yourself.
You have no idea how close
Sang Yoon and I are.
Really?
- There it is. There's the landmark.
- Where? Where is it?
- It's over there, Bo Young.
- Over there?
[Running Man landmark is discovered.]
There it is.
I see the yellow flag over there.
- Read it out loud.
- What is it?
Sit a member in a hand carriage
and the one being carried must make
a goal with the empty cup to pass.
- Bo Young has to do this.
- If you don't succeed at once, must move on.
- I don't think I can succeed.
- You have to do it.
[A very hot and popular street in Seoul.]
[A mecca of popular current styles,
and trendy cafes.]
This is your starting point,
and you'll see other cafes below.
You'll see cafes down
this whole street.
When you start off with her in the carriage,
you'll see various goal posts.
We have to start off from here
with her in a hand carriage?
That's right.
You can acquire the empty cups
from the crowd that is gathered.
- Can't we carry her once we get to the goal?
- Bo Young is very light, so should be okay.
- I've gained some weight though.
- Bo Young...
- You can sit right here.
- You just sit right here.
- Sit down right here.
- Sit down?
- Like this?
- Yes. You're so light!
- You're so light!
- You are very light.
[Moving on with her in their arms.]
- You're so light.
- I'm sorry!
- No, not at all.
- It's okay, you're light.
- Hello.
- What to do?
- You're perhaps too light.
- No, I'm not!
- You're very light.
- Bo Young...
If we're to bypass going to
the next location...
We've even had to carry
Noh Sa Yeon like this before.
- We've carried Noh Sa Yeon like this before.
- What do I do?
[Traitors Club is off to
do their mission.]
Have you gained weight?
[The Green Team also gets
their hand carriage ready.]
- You saw that, right?
- What? What?
One, two, three.
- Fighting!
- Fighting.
[Moving quickly on the
strong young men's hand carriage.]
Where do we have to go?
Where's the first stop?
It's marked by the 'R', right?
You've gotten much lighter
than the past, Ji Hyo.
- I lost a lot of weight.
- I know. How much weight did you lose?
- Cup...
- We have to find empty cups.
We have to get the cups
from the cafe, right?
[Even though it's said that cafes
are lined up and down the street...]
Not many people carry around
an empty cup.
Does anyone have
an empty paper cup?
Over here. She has one.
You're not done with that, are you?
- Are you done with that?
- No, I'm not done yet.
- Over here!
- Here's one.
Me!
Give it to me!
- She's not done yet.
- Give it to me.
[It has to be an empty cup...]
- One, two, three.
- There we go.
[What?
One shot?]
- That must be so cold.
- Just give it to us.
- That's good.
- Thank you!
Take turns drinking it.
[Giraffe drinking it for her.]
- Thank you.
- Young lady...
- Sorry, I bet that was cold.
- Thank you, and sorry!
Sorry for making you do that.
Thanks!
- Why are you having such a hard time?
- My arm is getting tired.
- I'm sorry.
- It's okay.
Thank you. We have to
take the lid for the weight.
[The Yellow Team finds themselves a cup.]
- Let's go.
- Hike me up. One, two, three.
I'm tired.
Give me your cup...
are you done with your coffee?
Anyone who's done with their coffee?
- Can you give us your cup?
- Are you done with that cup?
- Drink it up!
- Isn't that hot?
- Thank you so much.
- You'll be blessed.
- Even your girlfriend...
- Thank you, girlfriend!
- I promise that we'll win today.
- We'll win this mission!
- Thank you.
- Thank you!
[Green Team finds their empty cup.]
[Everyone fails at 'R1',
and all three teams arrives at 'R2'.]
Bo Young!
I don't think I can make this.
Throw it.
[Oh my goodness...]
[The empty cup just flailing
down to the ground.]
- No, it's okay.
- I'll switch with someone.
Why don't you go up?
I'll lift you.
- Let's switch positions!
- You want to throw it?
- I don't think I can do this.
- I'll carry most of the weight.
- Really?
- Yes, get up there.
[What? Jae Suk is really going to
get up and throw the cup?]
- Bo Young...
- We can do this.
Bo Young says she wants to do it.
It's only for a moment anyway.
[Making Bo Young carry him
in a hand carriage?]
Bo Young says this is what
she wants to do!
Here, I'll stand right here.
Lean towards me.
No, you can sit here.
You can sit over here!
[Leaning completely on
hot pink clad Kkuk.]
Bo Young, I'm set.
This is good.
[Using that moment to steal
the empty cup?]
You can lean on me!
It's okay!
- Why are you getting angry, Bo Young?
- Sit up straight!
- Just grab onto me!
- I'm good.
- Throw it!
- Hold still. One, two, three!
[A good throw!]
[No goal...]
[The empty cup sadly goes to the side...]
- Challenge!
- Please... you can do this.
- Please... let's do this.
- Dong Hoon, you have to make this.
[Huh?]
[Fail. Disqualified from hitting the roof.]
- Did you not see the roof?
- Let me try it one more time.
- I have one too.
- You want to try throwing it?
['R2'- second attempt.]
One, two, three.
[Impala brother makes his attempt.]
How am I supposed to throw like this?
This is your last attempt.
I don't think he's going to make it.
[I will make it!]
Hang on!
[What was that thudding noise?]
They put a rock in there!
There's a rock!
[A rock inside the empty cup...]
- They put a rock in there!
- Run. Let's run for it.
- What is that?
- Some dust got in there.
Since you cheated, you'll leave last.
Please return to your spot.
- Seriously...
- You cheated. Go back to your spot.
[No way to get out of it.
Countless number of witnesses to testify.]
- Wait.
- Hang on...
[Sang Yoon to make his attempt
for the Green Team.]
[Even Blank Ji can boast of her many
experiences with the hand carriage.]
[Totally dead on!]
That's too bad!
- That's too bad.
- One more try?
Don't rush it so much.
- Don't rush it. Come this way a bit.
- Okay.
[One more remaining chance.]
[With his proven skills,
will he succeed this time?]
[Hits the flag this time and fails...]
- Can we go now?
- Are we okay to go?
[Pink Team on their way to 'R3'.]
- Are you not done with that?
- No, it's not an empty cup.
[Keep on moving.
Must find an empty cup.]
- I think the paper cup would be better.
- Right? Paper cups are better to throw.
- Paper cups are much better.
- Where can we find one?
It's so far.
- Why is it so far?
- One, two, three.
I'm trying to find a cup.
[Unable to find any empty cups.
May have to go to a cafe at this rate.]
- Hello.
- We have to find a cup.
- Are there any cups?
- Is that a cup? Thank you!
[Finds one right before arriving
at their destination.]
Hello.
What is that?
[Arrives at 'R3' for their third
chance to throw the cup.]
- It's not that much closer.
- It's a little closer this time.
- You can throw it.
- No, no.
No, I don't want to.
I can help lift you up instead.
- Let's end it this time. Let's really end it.
- This agony...
- Let's end this agony.
- We have to end it this time.
- We can end it right here.
- Bo Young...
- Okay.
- Bo Young is no joke.
- I'm fine. This isn't difficult.
Please... please.
Let me make it just this once.
- Bo Young, are you okay?
- Yes!
Okay, here I go!
[Oh... it went in!]
[A goal in!]
- This is unbelievable!
- We did it!
[Pink Team succeeds!]
- That was great!
- We did it!
In one single shot!
- That was great!
- That was a nice throw!
- We can go?
- That was unbelievable!
Can we go?
I can walk now, right?
- I can't believe this.
- I can't believe that either.
Did they succeed?
- Hey... did you pass?
- Did you succeed?
You succeeded?
Who did it?
- Who threw it?
- With just one throw.
Did you make the goal?
- They must've succeeded.
- They must've made the goal.
Bye!
- Did you make it?
- We are finished here!
Coffee!
I can't believe you made it in one shot.
That was seriously no joke.
- Is it okay to be this cool?
- I don't know, but that was awesome.
A throw like this...
I can't believe that just happened.
- Why did you do that?
- What have you done?
Are you out of your mind or what?
Do you have any idea what
you've just done?
[He's about to start a talk show
with his own hand.]
- Let's each take a turn.
- Should we each take a turn?
- Yeah, let's each take a turn.
- I'll go first.
[Each fairly taking a turn.
Giraffe to throw the first shot.]
Let's lift him up on our shoulders.
- Hang on, that hurts.
- Can you scoot me up?
- Okay, on the shoulder.
- Okay, this is good.
- Suk Jin! Wait!
- What? What is it?
[Almost got smacked in the head...]
- I didn't know.
- Please be a little more careful.
[Yellow Team's giant, Giraffe's turn.]
- First attempt!
- Challenge!
- Get it in there.
- Make the shot.
[Misses it by a long shot.]
Let's go.
Okay, my turn.
[Little Ro-Ro to take his turn.]
Hey, you're standing too far apart.
Hey, get closer.
[Basketball mania Ro-Ro to
take his turn.]
You can do this.
[Success]
[Yellow Team succeeds their mission.]
Tr-ai-tor!
Cross!
- We're in second place right now.
- Second place. Let's go.
[Rather than friendship,
winning is the Traitors Club's priority.]
Let's do this.
- Where's our car?
- I wonder if we can do this.
- Over there.
- Are those trash cans?
- You came in at first place, right?
- Yes.
Here you go.
[Three running balls each!]
[The next mission location is...]
I bet you'd be shocked.
I had no idea I could do that.
[Go to Ttukseom Amusement Park by the
Han River and find the Running Man landmark.]
- Please get in.
- I still can't believe that.
Thank you!
Bo Young had a good plan.
If it wasn't for her, we wouldn't have won.
This was possible all because of
Bo Young's self-sacrifice.
This is what you call teamwork!
I'm sure it wasn't easy on Bo Young.
[These men are such chatterboxes...]
I was so worried that she may
hurt her wrist by doing that.
Since leaning all my weight on you
throws off the balance.
- That's right. So you had no choice.
- I had no choice but to do that.
- There's the Yellow Team.
- Did you succeed?
We're following right behind you.
- This is great!
- Today is the day!
- I'm getting a good feeling about this!
- We're in second place.
- We've still got it, Traitors Club!
- Everyone, together!
[Spreading out their cheers
amongst all the citizens.]
We've still got it, Traitors Club!
- Nice!
- Let's go!
- Bye!
- What is that?
[Yellow Team coming in second.]
- Trash can?
- You came in second, right?
[Two running balls each.]
[Green Team having had to go
all the way to 'R4'.]
First attempt.
[Oh?]
[Success]
[One shot!]
[Green Team each receives one running ball
and gets on their way.]
Wow... that first game
was too exhausting.
That was hard.
- There's something I'm curious about...
- Yeah?
Do you two keep in close contact
on other days besides Monday?
On Mondays, more than any other couple...
we're as sweet as candy.
[Monday Couple gives it
their best on Mondays.]
Sweet, yet combative.
If we stay close and do the show
together for seven to eight years...
then I bet you'll become the longest
relationship I've ever had.
[Han River Ttukseom district.]
[Pink Team is the first to arrive.]
- Let's all get out.
- I think there's something here.
- Seriously...
- What is this?
What is this? This looks like
some sort of jumping game.
- Is it distance jumping?
- Something else I'm not good at.
[A long and unidentifiable green board.]
What is this?
An acupuncture mat?
- Seriously...
- Seriously!
[The green liner mat is...]
[The frightening acupuncture mat.]
[The very same acupuncture mat even
the world action star, Jackie Chan hated.]
What do we do about this?
It's three level jumping
on the acupuncture mat.
I'm wearing very thin socks.
You have to take off your socks
and do it barefoot.
Each of you must jump while barefoot,
and we'll record the distance.
Is it the acupuncture mat?
- I'm going to have to work again.
- Oh my God...
- Oh my, that hurts!
- This really hurts your feet.
[Shocks of pain even at the
slightest touch.]
[At an advantage with tall Sang Yoon
on their team?]
But I'm a chicken when it comes
to the acupuncture mat.
If your combined distance is 20m or over,
then you succeed the mission.
- We should've gotten here first.
- I'll go first.
You're going to go first?
I need to go first to determine what
the remaining distance is going to be.
- You're right.
- That way, we'll know what we need.
Okay, Bo Young is going to go first.
We're in trouble.
That's prickly!
[And laughs it right off...]
- I'm telling you, this is no joke.
- One, two, three...
Bo Young...
[Why is she walking so far back?]
If you go too far back,
it's going to hurt having to walk back.
- I'm trying to numb my feet right now.
- To desensitize your feet?
That's good.
That's the stuff Jong Kook really loves.
[Her ferociousness is the style
that Coach Kkuk really likes.]
- This is some serious stuff.
- Ouch!
[Jumping in place?]
- Jump. Try it. You have to get used to it.
- It hurts enough to just watch.
[Coach Kkuk's forceful guidance.]
[Pads of the feet are desensitized.]
Okay. Now you're used to it.
You should be okay now.
I'm not good at things like this.
- Okay, here I go.
- Will you be okay?
[A woman who belies her image...]
[The woman who volunteered
the take the first leap!]
- Be careful.
- One, two, three!
[Easily leaps three bounds.]
[Wow! 4.6m!]
She jumped a good distance.
Unbelievable!
This really hurts!
- He says that was a foul.
- Why?
- You went over the red line.
- I did?
[Bo Young having been too eager.]
[Ah... her foot crossed the red line
by a smidgen which resulted in a foul.]
That's absurd!
This is too painful for it
to count as a foul.
[Pink Team's current record is 0m.
It's now Jae Suk's turn.]
He's disqualified already.
[Walking onto the mat?]
[Three step walk?
A mere 2m record?]
- What are you doing?
- That hurts too much.
I don't think I can run on that thing.
- You give it a try. Seriously, try it.
- What?
[Mr. Capable has to jump more than
18m for them to succeed...]
If you keep doing that,
you're going to start bleeding!
[Displaying the fierce, painless
side of him.]
- You're going to start bleeding!
- Don't end up at the hospital!
Whenever he's like this...
[The agony sets in...]
You deserve it.
I'm glad.
He deserves it.
He seriously deserves it.
That seriously hurts!
Wow...
- Hey! Why don't you ever listen to me?
- That seriously hurts!
- Ji Hyo, you need to...
- Gary, hang on. I don't think I can jump.
Ji Hyo, you have to take off your socks.
You have to take off your socks.
Take off your socks.
- Hang on a second. Give me a second.
- Miss Blank, take off your socks.
- Take off your socks.
- I said, okay!
- Sang Yoon... take off your socks.
- What is this thing?
- Sang Yoon, your socks.
- Hurry up and take off your socks!
- Sang Yoon, take off your socks.
- Take off your socks right now!
- I'll take them off!
- Take them off!
- Okay!
- Take them off, Song Ji Hyo.
- There you go!
- Get up!
- Song Ji Hyo, just endure it.
Hey!
Kim Jong Kook!
How does that feel?
The three kings of the acupuncture mat
are on their way right now.
[The three people who had Jackie Chan
in tears of laughter with their antics.]
- Hurry!
- Hurry up!
- They're coming.
- Challenge!
[Sang Yoon of the Green Team's turn.]
- Challenge.
- I don't think he's ready yet.
[How will Sang Yoon's skills in three step
distance jumping measure up?]
- Sang Yoon...
- I think he can do it.
[Unbelievable jump!]
[Easily jumps the 8m distance?]
[The start off point is okay!]
[A whopping 8.2m!]
Since his legs are so long...
he practically flew in the air.
- What is it?
- They're here.
[The kings of the acupuncture mat
have arrived.]
- Three step distance jump.
- Three step distance jump?
- Barefoot.
- What?
- It's an acupuncture mat.
- We have to jump barefoot?
[Flustered upon hearing that it's been
upgraded to barefoot status.]
- Get up here right now.
- Wait...
Bo Young is worse than me!
She's telling me to stand up here.
- These two on my team...
- Hurry up and stand up here.
I really don't like this team.
- They're way too competitive.
- Bo Young and I are a good match.
Challenge.
Sang Yoon did really well.
What is she... what are you doing?
- What is she... what are you doing?
- What is that?
[Taking small cautious steps.]
[Three light steps...]
- What was that?
- What are you doing?
- Are you kidding around?
- You give it a try!
- You have no idea how much it hurts!
- Does it hurt that much?
2.7m.
[Ji Hyo's record is 2.7m...]
I feel like I can fly across the mat
if I'm allowed to wear socks.
Can we do it with our socks on?
- Gary.
- Challenge.
[Gary needs to get minimum of
9.1m for them to succeed.]
[Huh?]
[Cringing]
It hurts your hand when you try
to push yourself off the mat too.
It really hurts!
[Green Team - Fail.]
[Yellow Team's challenge.]
[The shock that can be felt
throughout their whole body.]
Suk Jin, the fact that you're standing
on it is a miracle in itself.
I thought he was good.
I thought you said you were good at it?
The kings of the acupuncture mat.
Lee Kwang Soo, you know
what you have to do, right?
I sleep on a mat like this.
- I sleep naked on a mat like this.
- You're a master at this?
Are you a master?
I had no idea.
You promised, okay?
- I'm perfectly fine.
- Really?
- That really hurts.
- You want me to go first?
There's no time.
Five, four, three...
- Fighting!
- Let's go!
Challenge!
[Along with a ferocious battle cry!
Huh?]
[Slow video mode?]
[One step, two steps, three steps.]
[1.7m. The lowest record.]
You're even worse than Ji Hyo.
- Why are you playing around?
- It really hurts.
[Big-nosed Brother's turn.]
Challenge!
[Enduring the pain to run...]
[And just keeps going forward?]
[Just as they're nicknamed, they are
the kings of the acupuncture mat.]
[My hand...]
Kwang Soo...
he has to jump 20m by himself.
- Okay, I'm going to jump.
- You can do this.
[Giraffe showing his confidence
on top of the acupuncture mat.]
Kwang Soo!
Hey, Giraffe!
[A serious warm-up...]
- Challenge!
- Okay, nice!
[Wait... you're starting off there?]
Fighting!
Nice, Kwang Soo!
[An energetic start off.]
- You can do this!
- Kwang Soo!
[Starting off much further back
than anyone else...]
[Using his long legs to take
three huge bounds.]
Foul...
[Ah... he went over the line...]
He stepped over the line.
[Giraffe is disqualified.]
[Giraffe's dead run
which ends up being disqualified.]
- What?
- That was a foul.
How can you mess that up?
Okay, everyone... one person
of each three member team...
I will allow one person
to wear socks.
[Only one person from each team
will be allowed to wear socks.]
- No socks. Forget it.
- Let's not wear the socks.
We don't need it.
Let's just do it as is.
- Why are you saying no to socks?
- Just do it as is!
You two are the only ones opposing
the idea when everyone else is agreeing.
- What do you think?
- What is their problem?
- I'll wear the socks.
- Whatever.
[Unbelievable]
- Bo Young is so good at it...
- You're something else!
- Bo Young's already good at it.
- You are good though, Bo Young.
Since you're wearing socks then,
you have to jump 8m.
If you still do bad with your socks on,
I'm not going to let you get away with it.
- You won't get away with it.
- I won't wear them then. I won't.
- Wear it.
- I'll just do it barefoot.
Why are you burdening me like that?
Seriously...
[Green Team decides to give the advantage
to their hope, Sang Yoon.]
What's the deal with this team?
- Kwang Soo's putting socks on over his shoes!
- No, I'm not!
Kwang Soo's putting his
socks on over his shoes.
[What is he doing?]
- His feet are just swollen.
- I'm going to wear the socks.
- My feet are just huge to begin with.
- I saw him!
How is it...
it gets more painful as you go.
Do you know why the pain
gets worse as you go?
- Why?
- Because you're aggravating the same spots.
- You think I don't know that?
- You're aggravating the same spots.
- What did you say?
I'm sorry to tell you this,
but bickering is my thing!
Ji Hyo... if you can jump 7m,
we can do this.
- How can I jump 7m?
- You can do it! Why not?
Jong Kook only jumped 6m.
Okay, no need to get mad.
- You can do it, Ji Hyo.
- Yes, you of all people can do it.
- Give it a try, Ji Hyo.
- Ji Hyo, start from back here.
- I'm just going to jump from here.
- Okay.
[As a man...]
- She's got you whipped.
- You do whatever you'd like.
[Will she be able to jump
properly this time?]
If you jump in place like this,
your feet get used to it and hurt less.
[This coach is ferocious...]
She's the world champion
amongst all the women.
Having both of you act like this on
my team is just too much.
Is it your normal behavior
to disregard others like this?
- Coach Lee is not like that.
- You like to impose, don't you?
No, it's not like that.
You do whatever you want.
[Coach Lee lashes out.]
Why are you angering her?
And just let it go if you can.
[She was just trying to help...]
- Coach Lee was just trying to help.
- I know that.
- Are you embarrassed of me?
- No, I'm not.
She asks him if he's
embarrassed of her.
- My dream is to become more like you.
- Mommy!
Challenge!
- One, two, three.
- That was a good jump.
[Wow... 4m?]
[Blank Ji - 4.4m]
[Next up is Sang Yoon Long Legs
with sock clad feet.]
Your feet don't hurt, they don't hurt.
Your reputation is on the line.
[Will he be able to surpass
his previous record?]
His socks match his hat.
I've never known anyone like that.
[Flies through the air with his socks on...]
- 8m?
- 8m is a lot!
[A whopping 8.1m!]
Let's please get this over with!
Challenge.
[Must jump a minimum of 7.5m
for them to succeed.]
- Good luck, Gary.
- Someone needs to succeed.
[Random Mr. Capable, Kang Gary...
could today be the day?]
[He's in the air...]
[Amazing!]
[Seems as though he flew over 8m!]
- Amazing.
- That was an awesome jump.
- Unbelievable.
- He did it.
[Wow!
A whopping 9.3m!]
Kang Gary!
We did it!
[This is the random power!]
- Great job.
- Kang Gary, you're the best!
- However...
- Did he overstep the line?
No, he didn't go over the line.
I saw it.
- He overstepped the line?
- No, he didn't.
Song Ji Hyo's jump was disqualified.
[What...]
[Blank Ji's overstepping
the line by a margin.]
You should've told us sooner!
Then I would've jumped 15m!
[How can this be...]
[His random power isn't something
that comes to find him all the time...]
I'm so sorry.
- I'm sorry, Gary.
- No, it's okay.
Let's do this!
[Yellow Team's turn at the challenge.]
I can't believe I have to do this again.
I'm going to have to do that again.
Challenge!
This is comfortable know.
Suk Jin, the bottom of your
feet look funny.
[Did he discover the Yellow Team's trick
with those hawk-like eyes of his?]
- Something's strange.
- Just run, just run!
[Stopping his further advancement.]
- Something's not right.
- Grab him.
- Do you have insoles in there?
- Why are your feet so thick looking?
- What are you doing?
- I can't believe you have this in there.
- What is this about?
- What are you doing?
Isn't there a break for senior citizens?
What are you doing?
Your socks are already thick enough.
- Lets get it done this time.
- Fighting.
- Let get it done this time.
- We can do it.
Bo Young, why don't you
wear the socks?
- No, that's okay.
- You don't want to?
- I can do it without the socks.
- Then I'll jump 6m.
- She's good enough as is.
- 6m isn't going to be enough.
Okay, 7m then.
I can't believe I'm stuck with
these two competitive people.
[Suffocating level of competitiveness.]
They're like a pair of coaching siblings.
Do I look like some sort of
an athlete to you?
Then just do it right.
You're even wearing socks.
They're treating me
like an athlete in training.
Seriously...
Okay, Coach Lee Bo Young is
going to start first for us.
[Coach Lee's challenge.]
Hang on.
I haven't loosened up my feet yet.
[Coach Lee's adamant insistence
on proper stretching techniques.]
- Go ahead.
- Go ahead, and loosen up.
- I have to get my feet used to it first.
- Okay.
Just do what you did earlier.
- You have to do better. You need to do well.
- Okay, I'll do it this time.
Seriously.
- Seriously...
- Take off your socks and get on the mat.
You want me to stand up here?
[Coach Lee's fierce training style.]
- She's scary.
- Is she number one?
- Yes, she's number one.
- My feet are good now. Challenge.
Challenge!
Be careful, Coach Lee.
[Coach Lee doesn't even hesitate.]
I saw that glint in her eyes.
[Did she jump further than 5m?]
How far did I jump?
- She doesn't even sit down.
- Your distance was 5.2m.
- How far did she jump?
- 5.2m?
She jumped further than you.
- How did she do that?
- That's amazing.
Challenge.
You have to do well this time.
[Will he be able to recover
his reputation this time?]
[Running at full speed...]
[Wow! Pretty far!]
[Good job]
Please do something about
the soles of my feet.
Ugh, that hurts!
That hurts so bad!
Ugh, that really hurts!
Yoo Jae Suk's record was 7.1m.
[Wow... 7.1m.]
- That's a good jump.
- You need to jump 7.7m.
[But his walk back is a little...]
[Is he slow dancing?]
- Hey, Gary...
- Yo!
Are you doing the crooked man dance?
Okay, here I go.
[If Coach Kkuk can jump a minimum of
7.7m, then his team succeeds.]
Jong Kook's really determined right now.
[Did he pull it off?]
[Did he jump over 7.7m?]
8.1m!
[Wow... 8.1m!]
You've succeeded with a
total record of 20.4m.
[Pink Team wins
three running balls each.]
- Don't you think this is unfair?
- This is too much.
How can you keep coming in at
first place like that?
And the Green Team is
in second place.
[With second highest record,
Green Team comes in at second place.]
- Lee Kwang Soo?
- Yes.
Here's one for you.
[Yellow Team each receives one ball
for participating in the game.]
- There aren't any more?
- No, there aren't.
[Third mission location-
'S' restaurant in Non Hyun-Dong.]
What is this?
- There are so many delicious looking things.
- Look at this!
[All sorts of different dishes
when they're so hungry?]
Seeing how there are things written...
Everyone must find a table that corresponds
to your team color and sit down.
- One per table?
- Yes, and in any random order.
- Bo Young already ate a lot before she came.
- Yes, she did.
I thought we were going to be running
all day, so I filled up before I came.
She said she gets really cranky
when she gets hungry.
I know Bo Young a little bit,
and she tends to be very impatient.
And she tends to have that bit of crankiness
that all beautiful women seem to possess.
[With all this bounty around,
what kind of a game will this be?]
What is this?
[Time to reveal the third mission.]
Lee Kwang Soo, Song Ji Hyo,
and Yoo Jae Suk, please stand up.
- Why?
- You want us to get up?
There are 70 different types of food.
I want you to head over to the buffet...
70 different types of food?
Of those 70 dishes in the line...
I want you to pick out 25 dishes each
to bring back to the table of your choice.
- Of our choice?
- Bring back whatever you'd like.
[However, you can't discuss what
kind of a dish will be brought back.]
[Cannot know what
each other are bringing back.]
Spaghetti.
But the amount is too tiny.
Look, there's a giraffe up here.
Can I choose this too?
[Must bring back the food in a way
that no one can tell what they are.]
[Bo Young concentrates on the fruit line.]
[Sang Yoon concentrates on the meat.]
Orange!
Grapes.
[Mr. Capable concentrating
on the healthy food.]
[Starving Gary.]
[Sharp and painful screams
in front of the food items.]
Where have you been all my life?
Deep fried sweet potato.
[All the members complete picking out
25 menu items each.]
I will reveal your next
mission to you.
The name of this game is...
Buffet Bingo.
The food items that you each
have on the tray...
you'll notice that each of your tables
are divided into 25 different compartments.
Please place your food items
into each of those compartments.
- You have to be careful about the placement.
- This is the craziest bingo ever.
I bet we can get full from
eating our table.
- This is going to be too easy.
- It's going to be a double line bingo.
Once you get two lines, shout out, 'Bingo'
and you can step out of the game.
We can step out of the game
after two lines?
[Fruit heavy, healthy food heavy,
and a kid-like palate.]
[Carnivorous menu, just plain hungry,
and epicurean taste buds.]
[Omnivorous, Omnivorous, Omnivorous.]
[Going first is more advantageous.
Pink Team's Bo Young to start.]
Bo Young can start by describing the dish
and then eat it afterward.
If Bo Young calls out something and if
I have it too, do I eat it as well?
- Of course.
- Everyone will eat it together.
- And if I eat it, I take away the dish?
- That's correct.
- Okay.
- Do a good job, Lee Bo Young!
Can I have some soy sauce?
Can we get some
soy sauce over here?
- Then can I get a cola?
- Spicy pepper sauce!
Then I'll take a mineral water.
I can't eat the sushi by itself.
- You're saying sushi then?
- No, I'm not!
I have a lot of other things on here.
I'm going to go with grapes.
Once you mention the food,
we have to go with that one.
- Grapes.
- Grapes?
- Are we starting?
- Grapes!
I should've grabbed it!
If you ate it, then pull out the dish.
Do I not have any grapes?
Grapes?
[Quite a few people who did not
grab any grapes.]
- Okay, grapes!
- Okay, grapes.
- Sweet and sour pork.
- What?
- Yeah!
- Sweet and sour pork.
- Sweet and sour pork!
You can't leave out
the sweet and sour pork at a buffet!
Everyone's favorite,
sweet and sour pork!
- Kim Jong Kook...
- Yeah?
- You don't have sweet and sour pork, do you?
- No, I don't.
Nice!
[I hate fried food.]
You're finished!
Jae Suk already got rid of two?
What you call out is important too.
I get it now.
[Must call out the food that their own
team mate likely would've brought back.]
I don't think this is
going to be good for me.
- Where should I go? This way or that way?
- Kim Jong Kook, what have you got?
- Is it my turn?
- It's Suk Jin's turn.
Here I go.
- Grilled eel.
- There you go!
[The food of stamina
that many of the men had chosen.]
I have the grilled eel.
You can't call that out.
Of course, Jong Kook would have that.
Of course, I'd have the eel.
[I didn't pick the eel.]
[What will Jong Kook choose?]
- Tofu!
- Tofu! I chose tofu, Jae Suk!
- Where was it? I didn't see the tofu.
- Bo Young, don't you have tofu?
- Bo Young, you didn't get tofu?
- I don't like beans.
[Coach Lee with a picky palate.]
- Okay... pepper!
- Yeah!
Who eats peppers at a buffet?
I eat it!
I eat peppers at a buffet!
[Herbivore Giraffe is enjoying his pepper.]
- Seriously...
- Who eats that at a buffet?
- Who eats peppers at a buffet?
- It's good. I'm even hungrier now.
- Everyone finished?
- Yes.
- Please, please...
- Come on, Dong Hoon!
I have to pick something
no one would have.
- Please...
- Jjamppong!
- Yeah!
- Yes!
- Jjamppong!
- Yeah!
- Dong Hoon, jjamppong!
- Jjamppong!
- I have jjamppong!
- There was jjamppong up there?
- I didn't take one because it was cold.
[Who knew their tastes would
differ so much?]
It's still delicious even though it's cold.
- I didn't choose the right ones.
- These two right now...
- What are they doing?
- Why are they so quiet?
- Why aren't they eating anything?
- Our preferences are so different.
- Okay, here I go.
- Go for it!
- Strawberry!
Strawberry!
[Finally! I have this one!]
- Strawberry!
- I have it too! I can eat it?
- Eat it!
- Strawberry! I love it!
I have it!
[Sang Yoon finally gets to eat something!]
I...
- Kimbap!
- Nice!
[Kimbap, a regular at a buffet line!]
- Kimbap!
- Do you not have kimbap?
- No, I don't.
- Song Ji Hyo, your taste buds are like mine.
- Kimbap!
- I had a feeling that was going to come.
Everyone's food preference is
so different from mine.
- Jae Suk, did you free up a lot of space?
- What?
- Did you get a lot already?
- I've got a lot.
- Okay, it's Lee Kwang Soo's turn.
- I'll go.
Kwang Soo, you know which one, right?
- I'll go with that one, Suk Jin.
- Okay.
- Pickled radish!
- What?
I got it!
Pickled radish!
Who picks pickled radish?
[Bo Young has it!]
What's wrong with pickled radish?
- Bo Young!
- Who eats pickled radish at a buffet?
Bo Young!
Tell us if you have it.
I chose it because I thought I'd have it
after the rest of the meal
but I didn't think
we'd be eating it like this.
- Who picks pickled radish?
- I didn't even see it up there.
[I thought I'd be the only
one who'd have it.]
Bo Young, it's your turn.
- I pick chocolate.
- Yeah!
- Chocolate!
- I thought you said you were on a diet!
- I was going to save this for dessert.
- Who gets chocolate while on a diet?
- Chocolate!
[It's all great and all...
but are you keeping BINGO in mind?]
- Bo Young!
- You're not just eating randomly, right?
Bo Young!
You didn't choose that because you were
craving sweets after the salty radish, right?
[She chose that because she was
craving sweets instead of BINGO?]
- Bo Young!
- Do you even know the rules?
- You can't just eat what you want.
- You have to follow the line.
- Sang Yoon, you're up next.
- I'm still chewing!
- You're still chewing?
- Let's do this, Sang Yoon.
- Okay, my turn?
- Telepathy!
Jjajangmyun!
- What?
- There was Jjajangmyun up there?
- It was up there?
- Jjajangmyun was up there?
[That dish is too greasy...]
- I have to follow the line.
- I know Suk Jin's taste preferences.
- Here I go.
- Okay.
- Hang on. Wait until Sang Yoon is done.
- Can't you eat it faster?
- I'm done eating.
- Okay.
[Such a good eater...]
[Battle of minds
getting fiercer by the minute.]
- Why isn't anyone calling this one out?
- It's time for someone to call this one.
- I really want to eat this one!
- I really want this one.
- Okay, here I go.
- Go ahead!
Everyone...
- Ripe persimmon!
Ripe persimmon, Ripe persimmon...
- How is it that I don't have a single one?
- You don't have ripe persimmon?
- I have it!
- Ripe persimmon? Our whole team has it?
- Yes, our whole team has it.
- Nice.
[Needs two lines to win!
Jae Suk with one complete line.]
Miss Blank?
Ribs!
- Ribs!
- Ribs! Do you have ribs?
- Of course, I have ribs!
- Ribs!
- What? Ribs?
- I don't have ribs.
- You don't?
I should've chose ribs.
- Ribs is a given at a buffet.
- Kwang Soo, it's your turn.
- Kwang Soo, you know which one.
- Okay, here I go.
Everyone's favorite...
- Lettuce!
- What?
- I was going to pick lettuce...
Why are you always saying that
you almost did something?
- I really was going to!
- Stop trying and just do it!
What in the world did you bring?
- I really was going to get lettuce.
- What did you bring? Air?
[No one else brought lettuce.]
[Giraffe doing well
with his eclectic taste buds.]
- Bo Young?
- Yes?
- Bo Young!
- Go ahead.
- Is it my turn?
- Yes.
- Then I choose tomato.
- Tomato!
- I pick tomato.
- I was going to pick that one too!
I was going back and forth
about grabbing one.
Bo Young and I have similar taste buds.
What are you talking about now?
You said she made you feel uncomfortable.
No, we suit each other well.
[Coach Kkuk and Coach Lee
with their similar taste buds.]
I... choose sushi.
- Sushi!
[Finally!]
- I've really been wanting to eat the sushi.
- Sushi!
- I wish I had soy sauce.
- You want some soy sauce?
- Here you go.
- I already ate mine.
- Can I have some soy sauce?
- I'll take some soy sauce.
- Just eat it plain.
- Give me the soy sauce.
[Can't eat sushi without the soy sauce.]
- It's good even without it.
- It's better without the soy sauce.
[What? Cola?]
- Can I get some soy sauce, Jae Suk?
- Sure.
- I really want some soy sauce.
- Okay, hang on.
Here you go.
[Passing over the cola soy sauce.]
Do you really need the soy sauce
for one piece of sushi?
I bet everyone's lines are
pretty much similar by now.
Do you guys think this is
a restaurant?
- What are you doing?
- What's going on?
I think Kwang Soo's been pranked.
Thank you for the bubbly soy sauce.
I'll do a one shot with
the soy sauce.
- Sausage!
- Yay!
- I like sausages!
- Egg rollups!
- Yay!
- Dim Sum!
- Yeah!
- I'll go with a popular item.
- Okay, that one.
Perelli leaves!
- What?
- No one has the perelli leaves, right?
- Did he just say, perelli leaves?
Everyone's favorite...
Chicken!
[Is that really chicken?]
- Do you have it?
- Just hurry up and eat it!
Look at the way he's eating it.
- Sang Yoon, you have it too?
- You're eating one too?
[I can eat much more than this...]
[After a full circle,
it's back to Bo Young.]
Sweet cinnamon drink.
- Sweet cinnamon drink!
- Sweet cinnamon drink?
- I'm ruined.
Who would choose
sweet cinnamon drink?
[Jong Kook also has one complete line.]
- Is it my turn?
- Yes.
Pickles.
- What?
- Did he say, pickles?
[Giraffe also has the unique menu item.]
- Pickles?
- I have to finish this?
You have to finish it.
[Even if it's sour, must eat the whole thing.]
Did you really choose pickles?
Ji Suk Jin, it's your turn.
Here I go.
[Oh... close to two BINGO lines?]
- Duck!
- Yes, duck!
[Two BINGO lines completed!]
Everyone...
it's BINGO for me.
BINGO!
[How like Suk Jin...
being the brain that he is.]
- Congratulations.
- Fighting.
You guys can't even do that?
Seriously...
Suk Jin, I guess you'll be waiting
by yourself again.
[Even though he won first place,
it looks like he's heading off to jail...]
I have a feeling someone else
is going to have this one.
I'm sure someone is going to have this.
Sweet pumpkin!
- I have it too, but...
- Sweet pumpkin!
- By myself!
- I have it too.
- I have it too!
- All our team members have it.
- I really don't want to do this one, but...
- Just do it.
- Tuna sushi!
- Tuna!
[Yellow Team's Ha Ha completes
both his BINGO lines!]
- BINGO!
[Green Team's Sang Yoon also
completes his two BINGO lines.]
- BINGO.
- BINGO?
[Now if Kwang Soo can get a BINGO,
Yellow Team will win the game!]
You're the only one left to go!
Have none of you ever played
BINGO before or something?
Mushrooms!
BINGO!
- What?
- Mushrooms?
[Jae Suk completes his two BINGO lines!]
I would've grabbed mushrooms.
But I didn't see that up there.
- You can't coach anyone.
- Can I finish the rest of my food?
- No.
- No, you can't.
Why not?
Those are the rules.
Why are you asking about it?
You can't leave an empty bowl on there.
It's to keep a record of it.
- All that is being kept track of.
- You can see this?
Don't you even know the basics
about filming a show?
There's such a thing called 'Insert Filming'.
[A lesson by broadcasting specialist, Gary.]
- I'm sorry, I had forgotten about that.
- Is it my turn?
Yes.
I... pick fried rice!
- Fried rice!
- BINGO!
[Green Team's Ji Hyo completes
her two lines for BINGO!]
- I'm the last one for our team.
- Kwang Soo, you have to finish for us to win.
- Our team is the only one with two members.
- Kwang Soo, we're in first right now.
[This is the only food item he needs to eat
for him to get his two BINGO lines.]
- Kwang Soo...
- Do I have a chance?
No, you don't.
- Kwang Soo, we can do this. Let's win.
- Let's get first place, Kwang Soo.
- Let's take three running balls.
- It's Kwang Soo's turn.
Okay, it's my turn.
Spaghetti in tomato sauce!
I do have it here...
- We won first place. Say, BINGO.
- BINGO!
BINGO!
[At last, the Yellow Traitors Club wins!]
- The tomato sauce tastes...
- If it tastes weird, then don't eat it.
- Don't eat it.
- Don't eat it if it tastes weird.
- Can I...
- What?
Why?
It's good.
This is spicy noodles.
- This is spicy noodles.
- He just said he picked a wrong dish.
He shouted out spaghetti in tomato sauce
when it's actually spicy noodles.
[Having made the mistake of thinking
the spicy noodle was the spaghetti...]
[BINGO call is cancelled!]
[Just when we thought he had won,
what the heck is this?]
- You already shouted it out.
- But it looks exactly alike!
You should've checked it more carefully.
- That doesn't count.
- That's not BINGO.
[Spicy noodles- Spaghetti in tomato sauce.]
- I can't believe you did that.
- It looks so much alike!
I can't believe something like this
even happened.
[If he had shouted out 'Spicy noodles',
they would've won first place...]
You have to pay closer attention!
- Can you even see what's on your dish?
- Kwang Soo's in last place now.
- Kwang Soo's in last place.
- Seriously!
How could you have done that?
We were in first place!
- Bo Young needs to win this time.
- I can't stand these frustrating people.
[Two seriously pissed off people.]
What do you mean, frustrating people?
- You're so frustrating!
- They look exactly alike.
- What does this look like?
- Spicy noodles!
Spicy noodles!
Can't you even tell?
- Bo Young?
- Is it my turn?
Pineapple, BINGO.
Pineapple!
I have it!
[Pink Team's Bo Young completes
her two BINGO lines.]
Get out of my way!
- BINGO!
- Just because of the spicy noodles...
- I'm seriously so pissed right now!
- Me too.
[Seriously...]
You can't even tell the difference
between the two dishes?
I was so shocked because the spicy noodles
suddenly started tasting like spaghetti.
You mean it should've tasted like spaghetti,
but it tasted like spicy noodles instead.
- You can't even say that right?
- Are you serious?
[Don't you remember? You were going to
eat spaghetti but had spicy noodles instead.]
- Spaghetti!
- You were supposed to eat spaghetti!
- I was supposed to have spaghetti...
- Spaghetti in tomato sauce!
You were supposed to grab spaghetti,
but you grabbed spicy noodles instead.
Okay.
I will now take my turn.
- It's Jong Kook's turn.
- One, two, three!
Acorn jelly!
[Jong Kook completes his two line BINGO!]
[Crap...]
Acorn jelly... BINGO!
You're really eating just what
we would expect you to.
Seriously... he really is something.
- Acorn jelly got him his BINGO?
- Pink Team wins first place!
They won first place again?
[The Pink Team ultimately wins
first place again.]
[Dumbfounded]
- It's over.
- Kang Gary, Kang Gary!
How could it turn out like this?
Please...
What do you mean, please?
We lost.
- We have not come in last.
- He's choosing his dish right now.
[The final round of battle.]
I'm pretty sure he has this.
Please, I really hope you don't have this.
[If they both get BINGO simultaneously,
they tie for second place.]
I really thought today
was going to be the day.
Okay, Gary...
one, two, three!
Bacon!
[Green Team's Gary completes
his two BINGO lines!]
[Yellow Team comes in at last place.]
Take a good look at the spicy noodle!
[No thanks to the Giraffe,
they went from first place to last...]
Eat it!
What is it? What are you eating!
- Tell me what it is!
- Spicy noodles.
It's spicy noodles!
Let's go, Suk Jin!
- I can't believe this!
- Third place team has to leave last.
We were in first place!
This isn't something that usually happens!
- You were in first place.
- Unbelievable...
How could he have called spicy noodles
spaghetti like that?
The Pink Team members each get
three balls for coming in first.
- That should've been ours.
- That's ours. Bo Young, that's ours.
- Green Team, you get two each.
- Yes!
- Thank you.
- I can't believe we're last.
The team that came in last,
please come this way.
Tell him to go away.
- Pil!
- Whatever.
He's really annoying me.
- Suk Jin... we're friends.
- I'm so annoyed!
Suk Jin, Sir!
Why don't you lead the way?
- You, sit in the back.
- Since I've been driving...
- Don't even joke.
- Sit in the back!
Just sit in the back!
Seriously!
- How could you...
- Hey!
- Those two dishes are written differently.
- Didn't you even see the writing?
Even the ingredients are different!
It's spicy sauce and tomato sauce!
- I've been saying today was our day too.
- When else would we ever have won?
This is just the beginning.
Kwang Soo, if we don't win today,
we have to wait another year!
We've never had a day like today.
If you two are going to be like this,
I'm not going to play anymore.
Suk Jin... if you're going to be like this...
- Then I'm not going to play anymore.
- Fine. Let's just end it then.
I can either work very hard for this team,
or I can ruin this team too.
Okay, fine.
You...
Just think about when we first met.
When you say you want to end it...
don't you think you should think twice
before you say those words?
- No matter how angry we are...
- I never said I wanted to end it.
You're the one who's thinking that way,
and twisting the thoughts around like that.
- I never said that we should end it.
- Please be quiet!
- Let's not be like this!
- What are we doing?
What are we becoming to each other?
Even if we were to gather our strength
together, it still wouldn't be enough.
Just what are we sitting here doing?
[Final mission location-
Children's learning center in Gwanjingu.]
[Winning Pink Team is the first to arrive.]
[Write down names on the balls you've
earned and enter them in the drawing.]
Couples will be determined
through a drawing
and the person left remaining
will become the seeker.
If the seeker breaks the couple's bracelet,
the couple will be ousted.
If the couple rips off the seeker's
name plate, the seeker must cease activity.
Time allotted will be an hour.
Either the last couple or the seeker
left remaining will be the ultimate winner.
Then the seeker has the advantage.
- There's only one seeker?
- There are nine of you right now, right?
There will be four couples,
and the person remaining will be the seeker.
- There's only one seeker?
- Yes.
Then one of us could be the seeker?
[Yellow Team arriving after the
explanation time is already over.]
- Would it be better to be the seeker?
- Maybe that'll be better.
If Jong Kook was the seeker,
then it'd be all over.
We can't have Jong Kook be the seeker.
Everyone should write down
Jong Kook's name at least once.
- No, don't do that.
- I should write down Jong Kook's name.
We can't have Jong Kook
be the seeker.
- Why did you write Bo Young's name?
- I just did.
What are you doing?
[Big-nosed Brother having wrote down
Bo Young's name as his hopeful partner.]
I just wrote her name, okay?
[All the members complete submitting
their balls in the drawing.]
[Each team waiting in separate
rooms inside the building.]
I wonder if they're going to
make the announcement on the TV.
- I think you're right.
- I think they are.
[These staff members are preparing
to choose and announce the couples.]
[A familiar face.]
It's Hwan!
Look, there's Hwan.
Hello, this is Announcer Kim Hwan
to announce the fateful couples of the day.
[100% live broadcast.]
Hi, Announcer Kim Hwan!
By having a drawing of the running balls,
it will ensure 100% fairness in the drawing.
[The announcer guaranteeing and
vouching the fairness of the drawing.]
Please rest assured in the fairness.
- Of course,
- Yes, we'll follow!
We will now begin the drawing.
- I'm so nervous!
- This is nerve-wrecking.
Judge Go Dong Wan,
please press the drawing button.
Who will be our first lucky winner?
Okay... the balls are still spinning.
The first lucky ball.
Who will be the lucky winner?
- There it is.
- They have a ball.
Please don't let it be my name.
Okay, it's this person that you see.
The first running ball
belongs to Song Ji Hyo!
[The first running ball belongs to...
Song Ji Hyo!]
- Song Ji Hyo is the first ball drawn.
- I didn't think she had many names.
Then the next person drawn is
coupled with Ji Hyo.
Just who will be Song Ji Hyo's partner?
Okay, the lucky ball...
we've got it.
- Please, please...
- Don't let it be me, don't let it be me!
[Who is the person that's going to be
coupled with Blank Ji?]
The second name is... Yoo Jae Suk!
Congratulations.
Ugh... that's an ace couple.
[First couple drawn,
Song Ji Hyo and Yoo Jae Suk.]
[They were recently coupled up on
'That Winter, That Typhoon Blows'.]
[What if he starts nagging me again?]
Just who will be on the next running ball?
Okay, we've got the ball,
so let's check who it belongs to.
The winner of the third running ball is,
Lee Bo Young! Congratulations.
[First person chosen to be a part of
the second couple is Lee Bo Young.]
We will go on to drawing the next ball.
[Who'll be Coach Lee's partner?]
I'm getting a good feeling about this.
[Who's to be Bo Young's partner?]
Lee Bo Young's partner is...
It's Ji Suk Jin.
Ji Suk Jin!
[Bo Young's partner?
Ji Suk Jin!]
[A partnership that's harder
for the bystanders to watch?]
[Bravo]
- How did that happen? Suk Jin!
- Suk Jin... congratulations!
[A sincere round of well wishes
as if he's a groom about to be married.]
- I bet she's right now...
- Bo Young, you poor thing!
[I guess I'm going to be
ousted early on...]
Fighting!
Bo Young, fighting.
Is it okay if I scream?
- Who did you get partnered up with?
- I'm partners with Ji Suk Jin.
[Everyone that hears the news breaks out
in laughter against their will...]
Can I switch partners and
team up with Ji Hyo instead?
I hope Kim Jong Kook comes out
soon with a partner.
The first name for the third couple...
The first name drawn for the third couple is,
Lee Kwang Soo. Congratulations!
Lee Kwang Soo's partner is going to be...
and here it is, it's Kim Jong Kook!
Congratulations!
No way!
It's Kim Jong Kook!
Congratulations!
- Lee Kwang Soo and Kim Jong Kook...
- I'm all set!
We are about to pick the final two names
for the fourth couple.
It's Kang Gary.
Congratulations!
As for the last remaining ball...
we are going to eliminate the balls that
belongs to people already chosen
and we will recommence the drawing
after that's been completed.
I only wrote down my name once
because I wanted to be the seeker.
[Haroro wanting to be the seeker
to hunt the rest of the members down.]
I really want to be the seeker.
I truly do.
I have this urge... this rage and urge
to get some sort of revenge.
Now that we've taken out all the other names,
there are three balls left in the drawing.
This is a very nerve-wrecking situation.
We've got one remaining spot left.
This isn't going to be a simple drawing.
- There it is...
- We have the ball...
Okay, we've checked the name.
The fourth couple's final member is...
It's Lee Sang Yoon.
Congratulations!
Yeah! We don't even
have to go anywhere else.
Okay!
[Just as he had wished,
Ha Ha becomes the chosen seeker.]
[I will show you all...]
I will show them all what a
frightening person I can be.
I'm not going to go easy
on any of them.
I hope that you make your escape before the
seeker comes after you with bells on.
Couple Hide and Seek... start!
[Welcome to Couple's Hell.]
We have to hide.
- Its nice outside.
- Oh my goodness.
[Couple Suk Jin and Bo Young
looking for a place to hide.]
We have to find a place.
- Are you a good runner?
- I'm a pretty good runner.
Because you have to assume that we're
going to get ousted if we get caught.
Why?
We have to stop him!
But if he slams his hand down
on our wrist...
You better hide yourself well...
I think I see your hair strand!
You better hide yourself well!
[All the couples in a state of panic
with crazy Haroro on the loose.]
[The terrorizing sound of the bell ringing
that they haven't heard in a while.]
[Starting to hunt them down
with fire in his eyes.]
Okay, let's just start running!
Catch them!
Jae Suk...
I'm so scared just standing here.
- Put your hand behind us like this.
- So he can't come between us?
That's right!
Then I can rip off his name tag.
[Taking on their opponents by brute force?]
[Using their VJ as a test subject
to try out their method of attack.]
And we can rip off the name like that.
[It looks as though they're planning
on attacking the seeker.]
Tiger-Giraffe-Cross!
To be honest,
we are the strongest couple out here.
He can't beat us.
If you grab onto him so
that he can't move...
That's right!
With your long arm.
That's not a bad idea.
He's going to go after
anyone he sees.
Since there are only four teams...
if the seeker is determined, it's a quick out.
If we're caught, we're out.
[Bells ringing...]
[Extreme state of nervousness.]
Move!
Move out of my way!
[A full on explosion of rage.]
[Escape is their only chance of survival!]
[Has Ha Ha always been this scary?]
[The animal couple on their way
to face the seeker.]
[The Tiger stops him with one hand.]
[A strange sight of seeing the seeker
caught by the Tiger...]
Get out here and help me!
Time out for the seeker.
What the heck was that?
[What a humiliating turn of events
for the seeker...]
[Once a time out has been called out,
must wait to be resurrected by Dong Wan.]
What is it?
It's smaller?
[Tries to attack the animal couple
as soon as he's resurrected.]
Hey! Why are you
running away from them?
- You have to oust them!
- Come down here!
- Who would we go down there?
- Come help me!
Why would they help you?
[Who's the seeker here?]
This is really a stab to my pride.
Do you really want me to oust you?
[Hm... he is trying...]
See? He's about to get
his name ripped off again.
[Again?]
I'm glad you ripped it off!
Good job.
How am I supposed to oust
them like this?
How am I supposed to oust them?
Seeker is resurrected.
Come down here.
[Now everyone thinks
that I'm an easy target...]
- Just come down here.
- We're all waiting for you.
- Come down, come down.
- Come on and let's do this!
Let me oust at least one couple!
[No matter how many times he gets up
the energy to attack again...]
Time out for the seeker.
[Why aren't things going my way?]
I think I'm going to lose it.
[About to lose his sanity from
the rage and the resentment of it all.]
[Chu Sung Hoon, please come back
on the show and get that man for me.]
My pride can't take this anymore.
[Running Man Theater.
Stay strong, Dong Hoon...]
- I don't think we'll get ousted.
- I feel reassured. I feel untouchable.
- Is it different to be with them?
- Yes, it feels different.
[The couples feeling much more relaxed after
having witnessed the defeated looking seeker.]
We're going to end up ousting each other
while on the run at this rate.
[Full speed chase!]
[Seeker Ha Ha is different!]
- Just hold still.
- His eyes looks crazy!
[Enraged Haroro!]
[I will pay you back for the humiliation
and the insult from earlier!]
This isn't going to be easy this time.
Get him in a headlock!
[Their bracelet!]
[Gary and Lee Sang Yoon couple
is ousted within moments!]
One couple is ousted!
Gary, Lee Sang Yoon, out.
[Ha Ha is determined!]
Ugh!
Seriously...
[Couple Big-nose and Bo Young in hiding.]
[Coach Lee slowly starting to
approach Ha Ha.]
[Ha Ha turns around at
lightning fast speed to retaliate!]
[He rips off their bracelet!]
Unbelievable.
Ji Suk Jin, Lee Bo Young, out.
[It's not over yet...
I'm on fire today...]
[Seeker Ha Ha proposing a plan.]
If I don't oust them,
you'll have to go up against Jong Kook.
We are, aren't we?
- He's right.
- What are you going to do?
[Proposing that they work together to
oust the formidable animal couple.]
They're not going to be
easy to take down.
Right now, I'm...
- Jae Suk...
- It's okay. Don't cry.
[Having gone through so much humiliation
in such a short period of time.]
[Falling apart at the seams
emotionally and physically.]
[All the hurt feelings coming to surface
as soon as he sees his big brother.]
They didn't show me an
ounce of respect.
Please help me oust them.
Please, Ji Hyo.
I beg of you.
[Jae Suk and Ji Hyo agree to
help him out of pity.]
Thank you.
[Only five minutes left on the clock!]
There they are.
[If both couples are still left alive in
five minutes, it's couple against couple!]
Be careful and stay close.
[Time for a face-off.]
[Imminent showdown.]
[Unbelievable battle of wills.]
- Hang on...
- I'm getting really dizzy.
[Mr. Capable grabs Ha Ha!]
[At the same time,
Blank Ji grabs Kwang Soo by his leg!]
[The allies hang on tight to the Giraffe!]
Stop tickling me!
Stop that!
Don't tickle me!
[Everyone's fighting desperately.]
[Mr. Capable gets his hand on
Ha Ha's name tag!]
[And Ha Ha gets his hand
on the bracelet!]
[Who'll be faster?]
[By the split of a second,
Ha Ha was quicker!]
[Couple Kim Jong Kook and
Lee Kwang Soo - Out!]
[I did it...]
You two are like monsters.
- You two guys are monsters.
- Jae Suk...
What are you doing?
What is this?
There's still time?
[Ha Ha breaks off their partnership
and immediately attacks them!]
No!
[Humiliation, revenge, betrayal...
At the end of it all, Ha Ha ultimately wins!]
Seeker wins.
[A sea of tears at the end of it all.]
- Look at Ji Hyo right now.
- Look what you've done to me.
[Looks like a lead in a melodrama.
Facing the ultimate punishment.]
Thank you, Ji Hyo.
I had no other choice.
Hey!
- Me aside, look at Ji Hyo!
- Look at what you've done to me!
Just endure it, Ji Hyo.
I can't believe he did that.
[A flying kick]
Look at what you've done to Ji Hyo!
Look at what you've
done to my hair!
I... won!
[What prize did he win?]
[Gold couple bracelet]
You can gift one to
whomever you'd like.
Whomever I'd like?
Go Eun!
I got you a bracelet!
- Ha Ha!
- Who did he say he's giving it to?
I think he's really leaving!
- Is the show over?
- Why? How can it be over?
What the heck is this?
I guess the exit is over there.
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Running Man karaoke bar-
Singing Giraffes, Muscle Ballad singer...]
[15 year veteran rapper- Running Man
members who know how to hang.]
[The writer of this show...
with a Midas touch.]
Hello.
Run! Hurry!
- Hello!
- Come on, let's go!
- What are you doing here?
- We're going home early!
What do you take me for?
He's the God of variety land.
[And super attractive Kim In Kwon
and Ryu Hyun Kyung to boot!]
I came here with a purpose.
[Super patient?
Strong endurance?]
[Gentle game manners...]
[And the two actors with the
potential to explode.]
[Let's play.]
[Psychic karaoke bar]
- Jae Suk!
- Should I slap him?
[Next week's Running Man-
Psychic Karaoke Bar.]