[The ultimate guest list]
[A battle of pride with all the top
representative idols of K-Pop.]
[A battle against time.]
[Countdown to victory!]
[The King of Idols- Battle against time.]
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Locale for 2013's Biennial Celebrations.]
[A sleek black car sliding into the lot.]
[Infinite's Sung Gyu.]
[Infinite's L.]
[A nice start to Running Man's opening.]
[And one other person?]
[Haroro!]
[Thinking of himself as an idol after
having shared a car ride with them.]
[Oh? Standing on top of the
stage with them?]
[Dressed just like a member of Infinite.]
[Dancing alongside them to the beat?]
[Handling it pretty well in between them...]
[This is where the real dancing starts.]
[Haroro's lone freestyle dancing.]
[Ultimately dancing his usual dance.]
Everyone...
I want you to be mine.
Who's up after Infinite?
[Who will make their appearance next?]
[A-Pink's Na Eun and Eun Ji.]
[A fierce welcome.]
Ugh, Kang Gary.
[And, Kang Gary.]
[A-Pink and Gary on one team!]
Have you ever heard of Gary-Pink?
[A celebratory dance stage
upon their arrival.]
[Gary-Pink]
[100 points even for his gaze!]
[Alongside these flower-like beauties.]
[Totally into it!]
[In perfect sync with their footsteps.]
[Even his hip swings are perfect!]
[We're Gary-Pink!]
Hey, A-Pink.
Be mine.
[Welcome to Running Man.]
Who could it be this time?
[Another car pulling up right behind.]
I bet it's someone popular.
It's Ji Suk Jin, I think.
[Who could it be this time?]
[Beast's Doo Joon.]
[And behind him is...]
[Beast's Ki Kwang.]
[And Ji Hyo makes a team!]
What is she doing there?
[Will Ji Hyo be able to handle
Beast's choreographed dance moves?]
You're looking happier than I've seen
you in a while, Ji Hyo.
Yeah, I'm happy.
[Finally, time for
the three of them to dance!]
[Ji Hyo's following along!]
[A new dance move for the woman
who'd only dance to 'Hot Issue' dance moves.]
From the top of her head to
tips of her toes, Hot Issue!
[But she's still dancing all the moves
without slipping up!]
[Congratulations!-
Blank Ji knows another dance move!]
Good job.
I don't think I could've danced anymore.
- You looked really good.
- There's someone else here.
[Another team makes their arrival!]
[Killer heels?]
[Gorgeous ladies stepping out
of the vehicle!]
Girl's Day!
[Girls' Day- Minah.]
[Girl's Day- Yura.]
[Huh?
And, Yoo Hyuk?]
[Entering the stage full of excitement.]
Look at his shirt and the pants!
[With his pants hiked up
as high as they could go.]
Let's see what he can do.
I feel very confident in my abilities.
Don't you worry about it.
[Should I show them what I've got?]
[Will he be able to handle this dance?]
[don't you know who I am?
I'm the legendary dancer, Yoo Hyuk!]
[Totally serious.]
[Yoo Hyuk, totally feeling the moves!]
[The sexy glint in the eyes.]
[And the sexy moves of his body.]
[His eyes are remaining serious as ever.]
[And his body moves are sexy too!]
[He's lips are about to cramp up
from his attempt to not laugh.]
[Jae Suk and Girl's Day.]
[Still seems to be full of energy!]
Take this off!
- I said, take it off!
- I'll cut off your suspenders!
[This place is on fire!]
[Kwang Soo]
[MBLAQ's Lee Joon.]
[MBLAQ's Seung Ho.]
[This is how you make an entrance!]
[On Kwang Soo, these cool dance moves
take on a new comedic effect.]
Why is he being so serious?
This is so annoying!
[His gaze wants to swallow up
the camera whole.]
[Face scrub dance.]
[Transforming himself into batman?]
[100% perfect lip sync.]
[You again?]
We don't want to watch this anymore.
[Serious dance moves!]
[The red carpet is slipping out of place.]
[Explosion of his serious gaze.]
[Why did you dance on the carpet
instead of dancing on stage?]
The stage was too far away.
The stage was so much further away
than we had expected.
[Time for another member to make
their appearance.]
[Sistar]
[What?
And Mr. Capable?]
[The Muscle Boy making his
relaxed entrance.]
- What is this?
- Do you see the way he's walking in?
You look like an aerobics instructor.
[Will Jong Kook be able to dance
Sistar's dance moves?]
Why is he wearing a tank top
with those arms of his?
[Will Mr. Capable be able to handle
the dance moves?]
[This is the dance...]
[A dance that is the epitome of femininity.]
[Mr. Capable's explosive curves.]
[Horrible shrieks of terror
heard in the background.]
[And as highlight,
the swaying of the hips!]
[Breaking out his sexy moves!]
[Lift up the leg... and shake, shake.]
[His facial expression is sure Sistar.]
[Mr. Capable and Sistar.]
Can you do that last move again?
This one.
I want to see his arm muscles.
Why?
- That was so shocking.
- That was the best.
That was truly shocking.
[The last team finally makes their entrance.]
[They're here!]
[2PM's Chansung.]
[2PM's Woo Young.]
[And, Big-nose...]
[Welcome to Running Man.]
[Awkward]
[Relaxed stage presence.]
[Relaxed until the music starts to play.]
He's totally getting into it!
[What kind of a dance is that?]
[In perfect sync with the dance!]
[And this is it!]
[A dance machine
that doesn't know how to stop!]
[He was doing so well until the slip!]
[Big-nose and 2PM.]
You're good.
You were awesome, Suk Jin.
- Where do I go now?
- You can just go on home.
- This is one of their actual outfits.
- It's Junho's clothes.
[Big-nose dressed in Junho's
real stage clothes.]
[It looks very different on you...]
We will be holding today's race in Chungjoo
where the 2013 Biennial Ceremony will be held.
[In Chungjoo, where the 2013
Biennial Ceremony is to be held!]
The race you will all be participating in
will be to celebrate the end of the summer
and they are all missions that can only
be done in the summer heat.
The title of today's race is,
Goodbye Summer Vacation.
[Goodbye, summer vacation!]
At the end of each mission, you will win a
time card with a certain time stamped on it.
If you guys hold on to your time, and
come in at first place at the final mission
then you will be the ultimate winner
of this race.
- Is this our team?
- Are these the teams we'll be playing?
Yes, the idols that you are
standing with at the moment
are the members you'll be teamed up with
to become the ultimate winners of the race.
- We're all set!
- A-Pink!
Suk Jin, we can win this.
Let's win this together.
Then wouldn't it give the all-male teams
an advantage from the rest of us?
Who cares if you don't come in
at first place?
- Then you have no intentions of winning?
- No, I don't care. I'm so happy right now.
And to help out the idols that may be
interested in other idol members
the teams that come in at first through third
place will be given a special privilege
to choose the other members that they can
travel together with to the next location.
[First through third place winners can choose
the team that they want to travel with.]
Yeah, they should have other things that they
can play for now that they're on the show.
There has to be other advantages to
being on Running Man.
They should get a chance to go home
with a few new phone numbers.
- Get a few new phone numbers, right?
- You can be text buddies.
That's right.
- You're staying out of it, right?
- Why do I have to stay out of it?
Why are you telling me to stay out of it?
- There's no need for you to partake.
- I'm the best looking of this bunch.
- Then should we play Rock-Paper-Scissors?
- How about Na Eun does the first round?
[Time to choose the other team that they
want to travel with to the first location.]
We won!
[Jong Kook and Sistar wins.]
Then we can make the first selection, right?
- We'd like to travel with MBLAQ.
- MBLAQ!
[Jong Kook and Sistar's choice?
Kwang Soo and MBLAQ.]
Kwang Soo.
[Is Kwang Soo really the best looking
of the bunch?]
- We picked them because we like Kwang Soo.
- Really?
They said that Kwang Soo reminds them
of a water skater.
- That's what they told me in the car.
- I guarantee that they don't like Kwang Soo.
I'm serious. I guarantee
that they don't like Kwang Soo.
Remember when we were younger how we
always used to like the weird people?
- That's pretty similar to that.
- That's true.
How can you say that?
- Like Lee Young Jung.
- Next is A-Pink.
[Who will Gary and A-Pink choose?]
Ha Ha and Infinite.
[Gary and A-Pink chooses
Ha Ha and Infinite.]
This is the final selection.
If I can be honest about this
right now...
- Please help us.
- Did he just ask for help?
- This team isn't bad...
- We really have a chance to win.
[Who will Jae Suk and Girl's Day choose?
Suk Jin and 2PM or Ji Hyo and Beast?]
There's even a good chance of marriage
between my team and your teammates.
I bet the 2PM guys have a lot of
money saved up too.
[Older guys with money?]
- No, these guys from Beast are good too.
- Yes, Beast is a good choice too.
- Okay.
- I heard her say, 'B'.
[He heard her say, 'B'?]
They're feeling anxious now that
it's time to make our selection.
Beast!
They were pretty relaxed about it earlier,
but now it's decision time, it's 'Beast!'.
[Jae Suk and Girl's Day selection-
Ji Hyo and Beast.]
This is just the beginning though.
We're going to go with Beast.
It's okay.
We're fine by ourselves.
Thank you.
Why are you blushing?
It's no big deal.
[You just wait and see...]
2PM is really strong,
but Suk Jin is ruining them right now.
I want to pick Woo Young and Chansung.
- It's because of Suk Jin, right?
- It's because of Suk Jin.
But, seriously though...
Minah chose Ki Kwang and Doo Joon.
- But we know the truth.
- We know we weren't first choice.
[Could it be that they just made
a desperate and hasty decision?]
[Is Beast their second choice
after Kwang Soo and MBLAQ?]
No, it's not!
Where is this place?
We're in Chungjoo right now.
You don't even know where you go because you
get shuttled from one performance to another.
You just assume you're where you're supposed
to be when your manager drives you there.
You just think to yourself,
'So this is where I'm working.'
[So busy they don't even notice
where they are.]
[Just get out of the car,
and shout out, 'Hello!']
And once the show's over, shout out,
'Thank you!' and pass out in the car.
[And pass out once in the car...]
- I'm right, aren't I?
- Yes, you are.
I'm so happy today.
[Everyone in high spirits from
working alongside the fresh faced idols.]
What's your ideal type, Eun Ji?
Pick one of the two guys from Infinite.
Um... Sung Gyu?
Yes, Sung Gyu.
I think he has a great personality.
What about you, Na Eun?
Me?
First...
I find both of them to be very attractive.
That's a very good answer.
If you answer it like that,
then what does that make me?
That means you like Sung Gyu, doesn't it?
[Eun Ji's choice is Sung Gyu.]
[Eun Ji likes Sung Gyu!]
Sung Gyu's sitting very still back here.
He's not even budging right now.
- He's trying to be very cool right now.
- He's trying to play it cool right now.
I'll consider your love confession.
He says he'll consider her love confession!
- I want to get closer to Kwang Soo.
- I want you to do that as well.
Kwang Soo was the second celebrity
that I ever met.
And when I saw him in person,
I noticed how tall he really was.
- I thought to myself, 'He's so cool'.
- Really?
I think Dasom really likes you.
I'm just a real fan of his.
[That's... pretty sweet.]
[These joint car rides are full of
good cheer and laughter...]
Should we come up with a battle cry
for our team?
- There's something that we normally do.
- What is it?
It's a battle cry that our group always
uses before each performance.
- Okay, what is it?
- Chansung or you can say the first part.
When Chansung would shout out,
'Who Am I?'...
- Then the rest would say, ' I Am Champion!'
- Oh, I like that.
Let's give it a try right now.
Set, go.
- Who am I!
- I am champion!
Wow, sports center!
[First mission location-
Chungjoo's 'P' swimming pool.]
What is this?
[Flag stands in the swimming pool?]
Where are you going to stick it?
[Stick their team's flag wherever
they would like to.]
I don't know where the best spot
would be to stick this flag.
[All the other teams are also rushing in!]
[Although they don't know what the mission is,
they're aligning themselves in order.]
- Do you think this would be a good spot?
- Let's just pick that one.
Your first mission...
is 'The Swimming Pool Island.'
[First mission- Swimming Pool Island.]
All 21 of you will start off
at the same time...
and you have to pull yourselves up
on this float that you see in the middle.
Every single one of us?
But... this is on a first come,
first served basis.
At the end of each round, the
people whose names I mention will pass.
And the first team that has all three members
of their team to pass is the winner, okay?
[All three members of the team must pass
in order to succeed the mission.]
What did he say?
Basically, we have to get up there quickly
in order for us to win.
- And once we get up there?
- You have to stay up there.
It's not always best to be
the first ones up there, right?
So being first ones up there
isn't what's most important.
- It's important, but...
- But we have to make sure to stay up there.
It's also important that we have to stop
the other team members from getting up there.
Ugh... this isn't looking good.
No, we can do this!
Jong Kook.
[Traitor Kwang Soo already trying
to forge an alliance?]
- We'll help you.
- But I'm afraid to fall in deep water.
We'll all help you.
[Just which one of the teams
will be the first to succeed the mission?]
[Round one- First come, first served...
First five people.]
[The five people found standing on top of the
float at the end of the time limit passes!]
[First Round-
First come, first served mission- Start!]
[As soon as the bell sounds...
Everyone jumps in with gusto!]
[Giraffe on the other hand tries to pull
a stunt right from the start.]
[Lets you and I die together!]
[Everyone heading towards the
island in the middle!]
You have to get him!
[Chansung of 2PM is the first
to pull himself up onto the float!]
[MBLAQ's Joon, and
Beast's Ki Kwang as well!]
[It's goodbye for Joon as soon as
he pulls himself up onto the float!]
Suk Jin!
[If Suk Jin can pull himself onto the float,
Sun Jin and 2PM will be the first to pass!]
[Chansung and Woo Young of 2PM are
fighting a lone battle on the float!]
[Gary is doing whatever he can to stop
Suk Jin from getting on the float.]
[The island still only belongs to
Chansung and Woo Young of 2PM!]
[Wow! Even Mr. Capable gets eliminated!]
[2PM's monstrous power!]
[Oh! Is Suk Jin finally getting up there?]
[If Suk Jin can only pull himself up there,
Suk Jin and 2PM will be the first to pass!]
[No!]
Hurry up and get up here!
[End of the first round!]
[The time's up!
Woo Young and Chansung passes!]
- Who am I!
- I am champion!
Hey, you gym brats!
[With their monstrous strength, two
members of Suk Jin's team already passes!]
- Suk Jin! Fighting.
- Fighting!
- Who am I!
- I am champion!
At this point, 2PM will win this mission
as soon as Ji Suk Jin boards the float.
It's an advantage and disadvantage
right at the same time.
It doesn't matter how good
Woo Young and Chansung are.
They'll never win because of Suk Jin.
You have to get in your heads that
you're going to come in at last place.
[Suk Jin will never get up on the float,
so be prepared to come in at last place?]
We're jumping in as soon as
the whistle sounds, okay?
Hey! Don't even
think about grabbing me again.
You really are a dirty player.
[Round Two- First come, first served race.
Three people.]
[Start]
[Giraffe as we know it!
Interfering with Jae Suk once again.]
[The rest of the members make their way
towards the island without any hesitation!]
[First to climb up is...
Team Ji Hyo and Beast's Doo Joon!]
Suk Jin!
[Suk Jin is actually doing a good job
of climbing aboard the float!]
[Utter chaos.]
[Common enemy?
Must stop Suk Jin!]
[Suk Jin succeeds in pulling himself
aboard for now.]
[Please stay up there!]
[This isn't looking good...]
We have to pull Suk Jin down!
[If he can stand to stay up there,
then Team Suk Jin and 2PM wins!]
[Will Suk Jin be able to stay up there?]
[No!]
[Ah... ultimately...]
[Guys, I'm sorry...]
[Utter disappointment.]
[Ah... if I had stuck it out
just a little bit longer...]
[On the other hand,
it's utter chaos on top of the island.]
[Doo Joon of Team Ji Hyo falls into the water
after having been the first one to climb up.]
[Jong Kook eliminates Seung Ho of
Team Kwang Soo and MBLAQ.]
[It is absolute chaos on the island!]
[Dasom pushes Ji Hyo off the island!]
[More and more people falling
in the water!]
[MBLAQ's Joon ultimately loses to
the crowd and falls in the water!]
[All the members of Team Kwang Soo
and MBLAQ are now in the water.]
[The first three people on the float-
There are currently five people on board!]
[Gary is eliminated!]
[And...]
[L challenges Mr. Capable head on!]
[Just who will manage to stay up there?]
[L and Jong Kook fall into the water
simultaneously!]
Yura and Dasom pass.
[The ultimate survivors are,
Girl's Day- Yura, and Sistar- Dasom!]
Lee Kwang Soo, and Yoo Jae Suk...
take your hands off and get down from there.
[Slyly sneaking up there and pretending
that they were on top of the float?]
- He told you guys to come down.
- Why do you keep doing this to me!
Okay, this is the third round.
[Round three- First come, first served mission.
Five people.]
[Take this and see how you like it!]
[Doo Joon is first to climb aboard again!]
[Joon pulls himself up as well...
and lays himself flat on the surface.]
Suk Jin!
[They are about to lose their minds!]
[But he doesn't give up and
just pulls himself back up again!]
Okay!
Nice!
- Sung Gyu!
- No!
[But someone else is doing a good job
of sticking it out...]
Hang on... that's my appendix!
[Sung Gyu is in danger!]
[At a closer look, it seems
Eun Ji is quite the power house!]
She's stronger than me!
No!
- Don't push our Joon off!
- Why is she so strong?
[Eun Ji is keeping her grip tight
on both Seung Ho and Joon!]
[Falling victim to Eun Ji's strength?]
[It ultimately requires the strength of
two men to pull her off!]
[Two men barely manage to pull
Eun Ji off the platform!]
- They are ruthless!
- You were good, Eun Ji.
[Eun Ji is discovered as the new
powerhouse of the idol world.]
[And... just then!]
[Joon is dumped in the water
as he briefly lets down his guard!]
[Round Three- These five people
barely manage to pass the round!]
Do you know what I had to
do to get here?
- You're the one with all the dirty tricks!
- What were you doing?
[And in round four-
Ha Ha, Eun Ji and Gary passes.]
[In Round Five-
only two people manages to pass.]
[Minah and Sung Gyu passes.]
[Team Ha Ha and Infinite win first place
for being the first team to pass all three!]
[By Round Six, a total of four teams
have managed to pass the mission.]
Let's do this!
This is the battle between real men!
- Only the real aces are left!
- The real ace of all the teams!
This finally feels like a real battle!
[The three usual suspects are all in
one place for the first time in a while.]
I can understand the three of us here,
but what is he still doing here?
[Please add Joon of Team Kwang Soo and
MBLAQ to that list of usual suspects.]
You know how Chansung and Woo Young
were the very first two to pass?
We'll show you how they're going to
come in at last place.
[Will Team Suk Jin and 2PM really come in at
last place after being the first two to pass?]
For Round Seven...
the first two will pass the mission.
[Round Seven- First two people to pass.]
[Jae Suk, in fierce battle mode.]
[Why are you getting in the middle of this?]
[Let's get rid of the big brother first.]
- No!
- Please!
[And thus, Suk Jin is once again...]
[Jae Suk seizes his chance
and eliminates Kwang Soo too!]
Don't give up!
[Joon and Kwang Soo doing whatever
they can to make it up on to the float!]
Don't look!
[Revenge]
[Time's up!]
Yoo Jae Suk and Girl's Day
passes the mission!
[All members of Team Jae Suk passes,
and Joon of Team Kwang Soo passes.]
I don't even know who this battle
is being fought for.
[Who is this battle being fought for?]
Now is a one on one battle between Kwang Soo
and Suk Jin to determine the last place.
[Time to determine the last place winner-
Kwang Soo vs. Suk Jin.]
- Suk Jin!
- Kwang Soo, fighting!
Fighting!
[Not even paying attention.]
- Are you going to cheer him on?
- Oh! Fighting, Kwang Soo!
Fighting!
You can do this!
[Who will suffer the humiliation
of coming in at last place?]
He landed on his belly.
[Kwang Soo climbs up first for now.]
[Where do you think you're going?]
[But he shoves aside the attack
to pull himself on board!]
[A real battle between the Easy Brothers
that we haven't seen in a long time!]
[Is this the UFC championship?]
[Both of them look to be in pain.]
[By this point, it's a battle of pride!]
That's a bloody fight.
They don't have much time left.
They have to get up there quickly.
[At this point, time is of the essence!]
[Why is he taking off his shoe?]
[A mannerly foot attack?]
[A dirty, yet respectful attack!]
Stop it.
Just stop it, Suk Jin!
[Suk Jin isn't giving up!]
[This isn't going to work!]
[Throwing him off like a
sack of garbage.]
[Team Kwang Soo and MBLAQ pass,
and they come in at sixth place!]
Chansung and Woo Young are
in last place!
[Team Suk Jin and 2PM ultimately
come in at last place.]
I'm sorry.
I'll apologize to you over and over.
[No need to apologize repeatedly...]
I love our team!
[It's okay.]
- Who am I!
- I am champion!
The advantages you'll be given are all
different depending on your placement.
Please come on out and take what's yours
depending on which place you came in at.
[First place is, Ha Ha and Infinite.]
[On the mysterious card is...]
[100 seconds?]
- The teams that tied for second place?
- Yes.
[Second place tie- Team Ji Hyo, Beast;
Team Gary, A-Pink; Team Jong Kook, Sistar.]
[90 seconds.]
- We came in at fifth place.
- Okay, here's fifth place.
[Fifth place winners-
Team Jae Suk and Girl's Day.]
[60 seconds.]
[Sixth place- Team Kwang Soo and MBLAQ
with 50 seconds.]
Okay, and the team that came in
at last place?
This is lucky number seven.
[Last place- 2PM and Suk Jin.]
This is your time card.
You have to take good care of the card
and you have to turn it back in when
you arrive at your final destination.
Let's shout out our battle cry.
- Who am I!
- I am champion!
[Being greeted by Ha Ha and Infinite.]
Hello.
[Minah's face breaking into a huge smile.]
- Minah.
- Yes?
[Full of cheer.]
Minah, why are you acting so
feminine all of a sudden?
Did you just hear how you said
'hello' to them?
I don't know what you're talking about.
The team that'll be traveling alone is,
Team Kwang Soo and MBLAQ.
[Team Kwang Soo and MBLAQ didn't get
chosen as traveling partners.]
How can this be?
[How can this be...]
But we're a pretty popular group.
We'll show them at the next mission.
Let's win and come in at first place,
then just opt to drive by ourselves.
Okay, I agree. I don't
want to travel with them either.
Here, this is for you girls.
[Sharing sweet candy with
everyone in the car.]
- Hey.
- It's a token of our affection.
Shouldn't you be giving out
three pieces of candy up here?
The atmosphere in here
is quite different, isn't it?
Yeah, it's different than earlier.
The atmosphere earlier...
- It was our first time seeing them.
- Who did you ride with earlier?
- We rode with Girl's Day.
- Girl's Day.
- Ah, Girl's Day?
- Those girls are so cutesy.
They're so adorable.
Should we get out?
- We're not that cutesy.
- What does the 90 seconds mean?
[What is the meaning behind the seconds
written on those cards from earlier?]
- Do you think it has to do with a game?
- A game involving combining all the seconds?
I think we're going to combine all the seconds
and when it's time to do something...
I bet it's the time limit that we'll be
given to do something.
- It'll be the time given to do something.
- Then the more seconds, the better?
I think so. It's something that we have to
do within the time limit that we're given.
[Just what is the meaning behind
those seconds that they're given?]
[The King of Idols-
Arrives at the second mission location.]
- Look at this.
- Look at the inflatable thing.
[Hmm... what's this?]
[A new repertoire in their list of games,
a blob jump!]
It doesn't look that high.
But the blob jump is no joke.
It's no joke once you're up there.
Doesn't that look much higher than
it did the last time?
[A much higher jumping post
than it was the last time?]
- I think they've added at least another foot.
- I remember Woo Sung fell off twice.
[Woo Sung's unexpected charm over
the new blob jump game.]
Your next mission is the Blob Jump.
[King of Idols- Second mission.
Blob Jump.]
It's gotten higher since the last time.
[Higher and bouncier than the last time!]
Your order of winning will be determined by
how high you bounce off the platform.
[Their order of winning will be determined
by how high they bounce?]
To let you know about who we are,
we are 'Every day is a Girl's Day!'.
That just comes out automatically.
This is unfair to the teams that has
two female members on their team.
The height of the jump varies on
the weight of the jumper.
Then will there just be one jumper per team?
[Just one jump opportunity per team!]
[It's important to be careful about choosing
who your jumper and flier is going to be!]
[It is important that the two jumpers are
in sync with their jumps.]
[Practicing over and over again.]
One, two, three.
[Practicing as much as possible
before the real jump.]
[The first team up-
Team Ha Ha and Infinite.]
Fighting!
[The fear is making scaredy cat Sung Gyu
lose his ability to think coherently.]
Will you be alright, Sung Gyu?
- Will you be alright?
- He's known for being a scaredy cat.
Okay, here we go.
[It's time for the show to start!]
- Show us what you've got.
- I can't wait to see how they do.
[Just which idol team will throw their fear
in the wind to claim the throne as king?]
Let's get ourselves in sync again.
[Scaredy cat Sung Gyu letting out a scream
as soon as he steps onto the platform.]
You have to jump right on three,
Sung Gyu.
[Being the older one of the group,
Haroro is trying to show them his bravery.]
[I can't hear a thing that you're saying...]
['L', the human bullet positioning
himself on his launching spot.]
- Fighting!
- Good luck!
Is the film crew not ready yet,
or are you holding the film crew back?
- Wait, hang on. Hang on!
- Come on up here.
[Taking every ounce of his energy to take
that final step onto the jumping platform.]
Sung Gyu!
You can't be afraid of it!
[Frozen block of ice.]
Get that expression off your face, Sung Gyu!
You're stealing my expression!
If you use that expression right now,
what am I supposed to use when it's my turn?
- Don't look down, Kwang Soo.
- Don't be afraid, Kwang Soo!
[That's been my expression since
the beginning three years ago!]
[But...
the expressions really are the same...]
- Sung Gyu is really adorable.
- Yeah, he really is cute.
Why are you getting worked up
over his expression?
Do you have exclusive rights
to it or something?
[When are they going to jump?]
[Working up the courage to take
another step forward.]
He's laughing deliriously now.
- Look at him laughing.
- You're not sane right now, are you?
[I'm not really laughing right now...]
[My legs are going to burn at this rate.]
- Okay, let's go.
- Fighting!
Fighting!
Once you're up there, cheers
like this are actually more annoying.
You know when people cheer you on?
It's annoying.
[True meaning beneath the cheer is,
'Just hurry up and jump'?]
Just step up to the ledge first, Sung Gyu.
It's okay.
- Sung Gyu!
- Just look off into the distance.
You have to look up at the sky
when you jump.
[Where is this place... and who am I?]
You have to look up into the sky
as you're falling down onto the mat.
[Blah, blah, blah...
Everyone adding their own two cents.]
You have to jump
and lean yourselves back.
Kick back as you jump off.
- Just do it.
- Hurry up and do it!
[Amount of time passed- Ten minutes.]
[Are they finally jumping?]
Wait, wait.
- Sung Gyu, you just have to do it.
- I'm not the problem! He's the problem.
[How did these two manage to meet?]
Let's do this for real!
- Let's just do this.
- Fighting!
[Will they really do it this time?]
[Here they go!]
[They jumped!]
[Infinite... flying into the sky!]
[They conquered their fears,
and flew into the sky!]
Great job!
[We're alive...]
How high did I go?
[L worrying about his record.]
I didn't get that high?
[On the other hand, these two are just
happy that they had the courage to jump.]
[In a few moments, we will reveal the
height record for Team Ha Ha and Infinite.]
Next up is, Team Suk Jin and 2PM!
[Next up is, Team Suk Jin and 2PM.]
[Jumpers- Suk Jin and Chansung.
Human bullet- Woo Young.]
I'm nervous.
- We can do this.
- Yes, we can do this.
Suk Jin.
How is it up there?
- I'm nervous.
- I think I need to use the bathroom first.
- It's scary up there.
- How did you ever jump this, Ha Ha?
I just gritted my teeth and
thought of the person I love the most.
I'm going to think of my son too.
- Me too. I thought about my baby too.
- I want to be a cool dad for him.
[Their reason for courage!
To be a cool dad for their kids!]
Okay, great job.
[Bullet Woo Young getting himself
into position?]
Woo Young, since we have to do this
anyway, let's get first place.
[Huh?
But his position is a bit...]
[He has himself positioned backwards?]
This is driving me crazy.
It'll be our turn soon.
Okay, we're going to jump!
Here we go!
[His heart is starting to pound again
even just as a spectator.]
- Think of Hyun Woo as you jump.
- I love you, Hyun Woo!
I love you, Hyun Woo!
Here we go, Woo Young.
[Ready to jump!]
One, two, three!
[Are you watching your dad, Hyun Woo?]
[Woo Young flies into the sky!]
[The human bullet!]
[Three flips in midair!]
[That's 2PM!
A ten out of ten for his jump!]
[Human two shot- Not even comparable to
Woo Young's dashing flying act.]
What are they doing down there?
[Team Suk Jin and 2PM's human bullet!
What is their record? Stay tuned!]
That was so fun.
[Next up- Jae Suk and Girl's Day.]
[Jumpers- Jae Suk and Yura.
Human bullet- Minah.]
[Yura doesn't seem to be too nervous.]
- Are you okay, Yura?
- Yes. It doesn't seem that high up.
- Is she not nervous?
- No, Yura's not nervous.
[Minah's already excited at the
thought of flying into the sky.]
- But it's not as high up as you'd think.
- Really?
[If you say it like that,
then what does that make of us?]
- Scoot up a bit more, Minah.
- Can you give me a sign before you jump?
- We'll count to three really loud.
- Okay.
Are you jumping after three,
or are you jumping on three?
- After we count to three.
- One, two, three, jump.
- Three.
- Okay.
Here we go!
[Now that she knows it's time to jump,
she automatically breaks out in screams.]
[Gathering in one last deep breath...]
- You have to just do it!
- Fighting!
One, two, three!
[Wow, a vertical toss into the air!]
[An unbelievable height!]
[Predicting an unbelievable record.]
That was awesome.
Seriously!
That was fun.
[Stay tuned to find out the shocking record
for Jae Suk and Girl's Day.]
[Next up is Team Jong Kook and Sistar.]
[Woo Young, the knight in shining armor
jumping in Hyorin's place.]
[Sistar's Dasom-
Jumping high into the sky.]
[Next up is perfectly synched
Team Ji Hyo and Beast.]
[Fly, Ki Kwang!]
[A clean dive into the water as if
he's taking part in a diving competition.]
I guess Ji Hyo really does have
some weight to her after all.
[Superwoman Eun Ji to be the
human bullet for Team Gary and A-Pink.]
I'm sorry, Eun Ji!
Please come back to us!
We're still together, right?
[Can't hear...]
I want you guys to make it to
your 100 days!
[Gary and Na Eun leap off without
a single moment of hesitation.]
[A clear shoot into the sky!]
[Just which of the teams will have
scored the highest record?]
[The final team that has everyone
feeling uneasy right from the get-go.]
[Team Kwang Soo and MBLAQ.]
- Count to three and then jump, okay?
- Okay.
Are you okay?
Jump on three?
[Everyone cheering on the final team.]
Okay, we're going to jump.
[There's the 'Idiot Expression' again!
Exclusive rights by Kwang Soo.]
It's really high up.
I knew it was going to be like this.
Here we go!
Hang on.
- Lee Kwang Soo! Fighting!
- Fighting!
[Giraffe drawing courage from
his cheering fans.]
I will do my absolute best!
Here we go, Joon.
[For real this time?]
- One, two...
- Here they go.
[What will the record be for
Team Kwang Soo and MBLAQ?]
[I'm Jackie Joon!]
[In a flying leap position...
High into the sky!]
[That's so Lee Joon!]
[Is he fit to be a Hollywood action star?
One cool action jump!]
Can we have Woo Young redo his jump
with all three guys?
[Proposing to have Woo Young be the
human bullet again with all guy jumpers.]
Kwang Soo!
- You have to jump one more time.
- Why? What?
- What wrong have I done to deserve that?
- Have Woo Young jump one more time.
[We just want a good show.]
[2PM Woo Young's celebratory jump?]
Kwang Soo! It'll be you,
Chansung and Doo Joon jumping.
[For the sake of entertainment,
Kwang Soo, Chansung and Doo Joon to jump.]
[Doo Joon, Chansung, and Kwang Soo
aligning themselves to jump in unison.]
[Woo Young positioning himself
in his previous position.]
The three of you have to jump
in perfect unison.
Don't you think we already know that?
[His nonstop nagging before they
even had the chance to jump.]
I love you, Kwang Soo!
- Fighting!
- He looks so ugly next to all the idols.
[Everyone's ready to go!]
[Let's see what happens!]
[High up in the air!
Flipping through the sky! Perfection!]
[But his dive into the water is a bit...]
[But still... Bravo!]
[A grand success for Woo Young's
celebratory jump!]
You flipped like five times in the air.
- That was good.
- That was so cool.
That was nice, Woo Young.
[Very cool, Woo Young.]
[It's time to reveal the records!]
In seventh place is, 5m 30cm.
[In seventh place is, Team Suk Jin and 2PM
with 5m 30cm.]
We're not in last place?
[Earns 10 seconds for
coming in at seventh place.]
In sixth place at 5m 80cm.
Team Gary and A-Pink.
[In sixth place at 5m 80cm.
Team Gary and A-Pink.]
I knew I could do this!
[20 seconds for coming in at sixth place.]
[In fifth place, at 6m 00cm.]
[Fifth place- 6m 00cm.
Team Ji Hyo and Beast.]
[Team Kwang Soo and MBLAQ placed
much higher than they anticipated.]
[In fourth place- 6m 40cm.
Team Ha Ha and Infinite.]
I guess we're much higher than
we thought.
[Team Ha Ha and Infinite
earns themselves a 40 second card.]
- You guys must've done well.
- It's because of my big head.
Then it means that Jong Kook and his team
got higher than 7m?
The third place winners came in at
6m and 50cm.
[Third place- 6m 50cm.
Team Kwang Soo and MBLAQ.]
This is how skilled we are.
[It's between Team Jong Kook, Sistar
and Team Jae Suk, Girl's Day for first place.]
Stop comparing the two of us like this.
[Nonstop bickering between Jae Suk
and Kkuk as expected by everyone.]
- Come on, seriously!
- Okay, it's above 7m.
[Which idol team scored the highest record
for the Blob Jump mission?]
[Team Jong Kook and Sistar-
Record of 7m 00cm.]
[Team Jae Suk and Girl's Day.
Their record is...]
[7m 40cm.]
[First place winners in Blob Jump mission is,
Team Jae Suk and Girl's Day!]
This is so annoying!
Every day is... Girl's Day!
It's okay.
We came in at second place.
[A whopping 70 seconds
for first place winners!]
[Second place winners- 60 seconds.]
[But what is the meaning of
all these time cards?]
[Team Kwang Soo, MBLAQ and Team
Gary, A-Pink traveling together in one car.]
We got 90 seconds the first time,
and just got 20 seconds.
- What do you think that all means?
- We have a total of 110 seconds.
We're behind you guys by ten seconds.
I thought that it meant that we had to
eat our lunch within 110 seconds.
You're so obsessed with eating.
We lost because Woo Young was too focused
on looking cool rather than flying high.
[Team Suk Jin and 2PM with a total
of 50 seconds for their combined time.]
You have a total of 50 seconds?
[Looking pathetic for some reason...]
- Your combined time is 50 seconds?
- What are the seconds for anyhow?
I'm not sure,
but I think the more time the better.
[Not sure of the meaning behind time,
but the more time the better?]
Should we just keep going
for the artistic points then?
- Since we're already in last place...
- But don't you think we need some time?
Instead of coming in at ambiguous 4th or 5th,
let's just go for the last place.
- Let's just go for it then.
- Let's go for the artistic points.
What is that?
- There are so many people here!
- What is this?
[A huge crowd of people?]
What are we doing here?
Is it somebody's birthday today?
[Choongbu University]
I have no idea
what we're going to be doing here.
[An unbelievable crowd of people!]
[A huge crowd of people
filling up the whole stadium!]
[Each team entering the stadium in order.]
Everyone.
This is... Choongbu University.
Your next mission will take place here at
Choongbu University facing the end of summer.
Your mission is, Prime Dodge ball.
[Prime Dodge ball.]
But... this mission isn't just
going to be about the teams.
But all 21 of you will enter within
the boundaries of the dodge ball field
and you have to avoid the flying dodge balls
to remain alive until the end of the game.
- That's absurd.
- This is crazy.
I'm scared!
[A total of 52 university students gathered
to play the game of Prime Dodge ball.]
No!
How are we supposed to avoid
being hit by their throws?
[Surrounding them teams in an
straight and orderly manner.]
The balls that you'll all have
to be dodging...
will be thrown by these students who are very
angry about their summer vacation ending.
Please don't be angry!
Please calm down!
The team that avoids being hit by the ball
to remain alive to the very end...
will be the winner of this mission.
So ultimately, the very first team to get
eliminated will be in last place. Okay?
[Please go easy on us...]
[Greeting all the university students first.]
Ready, set!
[Prime Dodge ball- Start!]
[The whole crowd moving along
with each small movement of the ball.]
[The strange sense of terror that comes from
unknown directions of the 104 hands.]
[Idol members scurrying around in fear.]
[Please...]
[A direct hit on Yura of
Team Jae Suk and Girl's Day!]
- I got hit!
- Step outside the lines, Yura.
[Muscle Boy and his quick moves.]
- The ball is curving.
- The wind is giving the ball a curve.
[Passing the ball around to confuse them?]
[Woo Young in danger!]
[A direct hit!]
[Woo Young of Team Suk Jin and 2PM- Out!]
[19 others are still in the game!]
[Chansung's dodge results
in a direct hit on Kwang Soo!]
[The students are getting
the feel for the game!]
[A direct hit on Eun Ji.]
You're hitting the girls too hard!
Look here!
How could he have done that?
Why couldn't I have avoided the ball?
[Big-nosed Brother is out!]
[A ferocious direct hit on his back
from not having looked behind him.]
I was running and someone
hit me from behind.
[Big-nosed brother in the midst of his jog.]
[The ball hits him out of nowhere.]
You're the only one left, Chansung!
[Chansung, the lone survivor
of Team Suk Jin and 2PM.]
[14 survivors left in the game.]
[Harder to get a hit
with fewer people left in the game.]
They have to throw as soon as the ball is
in their hands to get a hit.
Please let me back in the game!
All of the disqualified members...
I bet you're bored, right?
Yes!
- We don't want to sit here!
- Get in the throw line.
[Eliminated ones back in the game!]
You have to scatter yourselves in the line.
Aim for your opponent teams.
[Students are even more enthused with
the joining of the eliminated players.]
Hyorin!
[A huge turnabout in the game
is about to come!]
[Sung Gyu's nice catch!]
[Haroro in danger.]
[Haroro- Out!]
Ha Ha, out!
[Throwing the ball as soon as
it's in her hands!]
[Eun Ji's attack.]
[Minah barely manages to avoid the ball.]
Kim Jong Kook!
[Wow... one student aiming
for Mr. Capable?]
[An immediate smile on his face.]
[Eun Ji ousts Sung Gyu!]
[No mercy in the face of victory!]
Keep passing the ball!
[A ferocious hit on Seung Ho!]
[All the members getting ousted
one by one!]
[Wow... Haroro's fierce throw!]
[Gary- Out!]
Why did you oust Gary!
[Na Eun is the only survivor left of
Team Gary and A-Pink.]
There are four teams that only have
one surviving member left on their team.
We have to oust the orange team.
There are too many
orange team members left in the game!
- Everyone, what color?
- Orange!
- What color?
[Crap...]
You guys are being too harsh!
I randomly hear people screaming out,
'Kill them' here and there.
Why are you saying that?
What wrong have we ever done you guys?
[Even though we can understand that you're
angry about your summer vacation ending...]
We're not the ones ending
your summer vacation here.
[In a violent state of mind over their
rage of the summer vacation ending.]
You guys are all being too violent.
There's no need for you to want to kill us.
You guys all look like such nice people!
Teams with only one member left need to
work hard to stay in the game.
Okay, we're going to start
the game again.
Orange!
[Everyone's common goal is... orange!]
Here's what we're going to do.
Everyone start passing the ball around.
Throw it as soon as you catch it.
[Counting on a plan of confusion
from rapid ball pass play.]
Don't even think about it,
and just pass the ball.
[Danger everywhere!]
[Ah... way out of bounds.]
Throw it immediately.
Nice, as soon as you catch it.
Immediately. Nice!
[With their quick pass play,
Ki Kwang is out!]
[I did it!]
Let's ride the wave!
[Time to ride the wave!]
[Since he's already riding the wave,
time to take it to the stands!]
He really loves doing things like that.
[Wave of a gigantic proportions.]
[The atmosphere makes it feel like
he's in the Olympics.]
Thank you.
Ready, set, go!
[Resuming the game.]
[Where is he aiming the ball?]
- Why aren't you hitting anyone?
- You guys are being too meek.
- Throw it immediately!
- Nice.
[Jae Suk- Out!]
You have to stay alive, Minah.
It's over now!
[Thank you. I'll kill them all.]
It's all over now!
It's all over!
[What's he saying?]
[Dasom- Out!]
[Na Eun- Out!]
[Oh no!]
All the members of
Team Gary and A-Pink are now ousted.
Team Gary and A-Pink
are no longer in the game.
[Team Gary and A-Pink are ousted!]
[From 21 members...
only 7 left remaining.]
Nice!
[Muscle Boy doing a good job
of avoiding the ball.]
Are you okay?
[Almost hit by the ball!]
How could you...
Why are you trying to kill her twice?
[Time to decide on the victor...]
[Kkuk sure is good at avoiding getting hit.]
[Minah- Out!]
[The student standing right next to him
ousts his last remaining team member.]
She's my team member.
[Team Jae Suk and Girl's Day are all out!]
[Only six survivors left in the game!]
[Team Ji Hyo and Beast is the only team
with two survivors still in the game.]
[Doo Joon doing a great job of
avoiding getting hit by the ball.]
[Team Ji Hyo and Beast having become
everyone's main target.]
[In the end... Doo Joon is out!]
You have to oust Kim Jong Kook!
Why me?
- Kim Jong Kook!
- Why? Why me?
Kim Jong Kook!
[Formulating a plan?]
[The legendary five point star pass?]
That's right!
[The ultimate strategy according
to the legendary cartoon.]
You have to do it right!
This is going to drive you guys crazy!
Quickly!
This is making me so dizzy!
Let's do this!
[A successful plan?]
You all have to concentrate!
Since there aren't many survivors left,
to help you with your throwing aim
we're going to tighten the
boundary lines for the game.
This is your chance, everyone!
Let's finish this quickly and go eat!
Ready, set, go!
[Only five survivors left in the game.]
[Chansung's quick moves.]
This is really scary.
[Ah... L is out!]
Good job.
- Infinite is out.
- Too bad.
[Only four survivors left in the game.
Blank Ji is truly amazing.]
- Where's the ball?
- Over there.
[Be careful of your own team member!]
[Almost aimed for
his own teammate, Chansung.]
[Muscle Boy still doing a good job
of avoiding the ball.]
We have to get Jong Kook.
[Ah... the lone female survivor,
Blank Ji is out!]
That guy is ousting all the female players.
I want to speak to you after the game.
I want to talk to you after the game.
[Can't believe that
Joon is still in the game...]
Jong Kook is our next goal!
This is the time when first through
third place will be determined.
- Let's win first place, Chansung!
- Pass the ball around!
[Giraffe getting too overly excited.]
Wait, wait.
[Only three survivors left in the game.]
[Huh?]
[Prepping for another cartoon
dodge ball move?]
[The fire ball?]
[The fire ball's demise.]
There you go.
Stay calm everyone.
[Oh... Big-nosed Brother ousts Muscle Boy!]
Ji Suk Jin!
[A huge celebration breaks out.]
[Team Jong Kook and Sistar in third place.]
[The final two survivors-
Chansung vs. Lee Joon.]
This is the first time I've ever seen Joon
survive this long on our show.
[Will it be ditzy Joon...]
[Or fast footed beast, Chansung?]
[The ultimate battle starts now!]
[An ambush throw by
Joon's teammate, Seung Ho!]
[A perfectly aimed throw at Chansung!]
[This is dangerous...]
[A direct hit!]
[The final survivor, Lee Joon!]
[Team Kwang Soo and MBLAQ
come in at first place!]
[A round of applause to the victors.]
You were awesome, Chansung.
Thank you so much to all the students
who made this game possible.
[Time to hand out the time card
to the first place winners.]
[Overly excited at this rare and
unexpected turn of events.]
Hurry!
[Thank you to everyone for cheering us on.]
[Time for the final mission!]
It is now time for the final mission.
Are we going to start the game
in the order that we're in right now?
[With the time cards that they've
been able to gain thus far...]
[It is time to determine...]
[The ultimate victor.]
[Huh?]
I'm here on my own.
My Girl's Day team members...
have an event scheduled overseas.
Since they have their schedule to get to,
I have to finish this race on my own.
[Yoo Hyuk to complete the final mission
all on his own.]
I may be able to win first place
so don't worry about me being alone.
- Good luck with your event.
- You have to win the race, okay?
[If things had gone according to plan,
they could've finished the race together...]
- I'll send you the gold if I win.
- There's a gold prize?
[Thus... Yoo Hyuk is alone.]
Then please carry on for your team members
by doing their impersonation as well.
What do you mean, impersonate them?
What are you talking about?
Okay, for your final mission...
Time is Gold.
[Final mission- Time is Gold.]
Throughout the day today, you've
won yourselves the time cards, right?
If you combine all the time cards
that you've gained thus far...
that's the total time that your team
has to complete your mission.
[This is their allotted time
to complete their mission!]
That means, the more time you have,
more advantageous it is for you.
You'll see different colored cages
set up behind where you're standing.
Starting with the team with the most time,
each team will go into that cage...
and unravel the knotted rope...
and once that's done,
come back to the table set in front of it...
to complete the traditional game
that's placed on top of the table.
And once the game has been completed,
a key will fall out onto the table.
Once you've gained the key
come up to the King of Idols flag,
and turn the key in the lock
to pull out the flag from its stand.
The team that gets the flag wins the race.
- Does everyone understand the rules?
- Yes.
Okay, the team with the most time
will first head towards their cage
and wait on standby for the
game to start.
Everyone, please turn in
your time cards.
In first place is,
Team Jong Kook and Sistar.
[In first place-
Team Jong Kook and Sistar.]
- 200 seconds.
- Okay, 200 seconds.
- Please turn in your cards.
- 200 seconds?
Stake your flag in the cage,
and ready yourselves behind the cage.
And the team in second place?
Team Ha Ha and Infinite.
And also,
Team Kwang Soo and MBLAQ.
How many seconds do you have?
- We have...
- 170 seconds.
- How many seconds to you have?
- We also have 170 seconds.
And the next team with
the most allotted time is...
Team Ji Hyo and Beast.
- How many seconds do you have?
- 160 seconds.
160 seconds is more than plenty...
What am I supposed to do
on my own here?
You said you'll win first place
all on your own earlier.
I was just saying that.
I can't win this game on my own.
Okay, the fifth team with the most
allotted amount of time is...
Team Girl's Day.
[In fifth place, Team Girl's Day.]
I have 150 seconds.
- Can you shout out your team's battle cry?
- How am I to do that? I'm here by myself.
[We're not alone!]
How am I supposed to shout out,
'Every day is a Girl's Day' alone?
- Every day is Jae Suk's day.
- Good luck playing by yourself.
Every day... is alone day!
I can't believe I have to do this alone.
We're not in last place!
- We're not in last place.
- Are you teasing us right now?
- We have 120 seconds.
- That's only a 10 second difference.
- We have 110 seconds.
- 110 seconds.
[In final place- Team Suk Jin
and 2PM with 110 seconds.]
Everyone to the start line.
The first team to complete this mission
will be the ultimate winner.
You must check the light on your cage,
and we'll start at the sound of my whistle.
Ready.
[Green light on Team Sistar's cage!]
We have to remain calm.
Let's stay calm.
[Team Sistar with the most amount
of allotted time to complete the mission.]
- I think I've got the hang of this.
- Really?
[Team Suk Jin and 2PM feeling anxious
with their measly 110 seconds.]
This is all knotted very tight.
You can't try to force it.
You have to lightly unravel it.
[Everyone's light still remains red...]
This is making me feel very anxious.
[At last...]
[Time for Team Ha Ha and Infinite
to start!]
Our turn?
[Team Kwang Soo and MBLAQ
also starts their mission.]
You have to push the knot through.
Quickly, quickly!
How do I unravel this?
- You're really fast.
- Quickly.
Okay, I'm almost done here.
[Hyorin showing some talent in
unraveling the knots.]
- Ki Kwang!
- What is it?
[Team Ji Hyo and Beast- Start the mission!]
Let's remain calm.
It doesn't look like it's very easy.
How am I supposed to do this alone when
all three of them are struggling over there?
[Team Beast working quickly
to unravel their knots.]
Okay, it's my turn!
[Finally time for
'Every day is Jae Suk's Day' to start!]
How am I supposed to unravel this knot?
How did they even tie this knot?
We're next.
We're up next.
The more I unravel it,
more knotted it's becoming.
[Team Sistar calmly unraveling
all their knots.]
This too?
Do we have to unravel all this too?
Wow, Ji Hyo.
You're really good at this.
[All around Ace Ji Hyo is good at
even unraveling stubborn knots.]
Quickly!
[Finally time for
Team Gary and A-Pink to start!]
We don't have enough time.
- No, don't think like that.
- Okay, I'll relax.
This is... a time for us to build
more memories.
It's our turn.
[And finally, it's Team 2PM's turn.]
Okay, I'm getting this side.
Let's win this.
Let's really win this.
[It is now, a full on battle!]
[Team Sistar is ahead of everyone else
from having been the first ones to start.]
You're really quick.
Why isn't this unraveling?
How am I supposed to do this one?
We have to work fast.
Wow, this is unbelievable.
[And this one person...]
[A frustrating world of knots
to handle all on his own.]
[I want to cry.]
Girl's Day, fighting!
Stay strong, Team Girl's Day.
[Now resorting to the usage of his teeth.]
Okay, I'm getting this now.
- Mine's unraveling now.
- I'm really getting this.
Get greedy with it.
Get greedy!
I am starting to feel greedy.
[While all the top teams are struggling,
the bottom teams are remaining driven.]
[Must unravel all the knots before
they can pass the first course.]
[Which team will be the first
to pass through the first course?]
[Team Sistar almost finished
with their course.]
[Team 2PM having unraveled
quite a good portion of the knots.]
Okay, we're moving along here.
I can't see anything over here.
[Wow, look at Blank Ji's hands move!]
We were doing such a good job!
[Team Ji Hyo and Beast completes
unraveling all their knots!]
Raise the bar.
[Succeeds in escaping their first course.]
[Team Ji Hyo and Beast are in first place!]
[Second course- Puzzle time.]
They're already out?
Okay, good!
[Team Kwang Soo and MBLAQ
are also finished!]
[Heading straight towards the puzzle.]
This is the last knot.
Okay, we got it.
[Team Ha Ha and Infinite also
passes the first course.]
How in the world does this work?
Let's stay focused.
Team Sistar isn't even through yet.
[Is it because of his muscly arms?
Team Sistar struggling at the end.]
[Finally able to escape!]
[Oh... Team 2PM also escapes!]
[Team A-Pink are also on their way!]
[Only Jae Suk's Day is still
behind his cage.]
What is this?
I'm the only one still stuck back here?
[Even though it's only seven pieces,
the puzzle is harder than expected.]
Over here.
What are you doing, Joon?
[If they just placed it where they were,
then they could've completed it.]
This doesn't fit.
[The more people doing the puzzle,
the more confusing it becomes.]
- This is hard.
- Hang on a second.
[This is the correct solution.]
[Oh yeah, this guy!]
[Still struggling with all the knots.]
What one of these pieces
are shaped like this?
[Try it fitting it this way,
and try fitting it that way.]
This is really hard.
[But Team Suk Jin and 2PM has
quite a bit of the puzzle completed.]
Hang on a second.
Hand me this piece.
[Has Team Ji Hyo and Beast
figured it out?]
We got it!
[The 'R' is complete!]
- It's right there.
- Here.
[Wow... Team 2PM also completes it!]
[Gains their keys!]
[Heading off to the final stage!]
[Team Beast vs. Team 2PM...
Just who will be in first?]
Go!
[Sticking the key into the camera?]
[Open!]
[Wait a second...]
[Darn!]
We won!
[Team Ji Hyo and Beast succeeds
in winning the flag!]
[But Team 2PM with the least amount of
allotted time comes in at second place.]
We're the King of Idols!
[Team Ji Hyo and Beast wins!]
- Everyday...
- Is Jae Suk's Day!
Every day's Girl's Day!
The final victor of today's race is,
Team Beast!
[Today's victors-
Team Ji Hyo and Beast.]
Beast!
Please come up and get your prize.
[Time to give out the prize.]
We came in at second place with only
110 seconds. We did pretty great.
We would've won if we had
a little bit more time.
First place.
Is this real gold?
Blank Ji and Beast!
[Blank Ji Hyo and Beast wins!]
Every day is Girl's Day!
Subtitles by DramaFever
[The legendary beauty, Princess Ji Hyo.]
[An epic fairytale written just for her.]
[Princess Ji Hyo, please accept my heart!]
[A gang of Flower Boy Princes-
GD, Dae Sung and Seung Ri.]
[A battle for the princess.]
[If you want to win...
steal the princess' heart.]
[A project to earn Princess Ji Hyo's heart.]
[Just who will earn the princess' heart?]
[Tune in next week-
Steal Princess Ji Hyo's heart.]