[Running Man Christmas Special]
[The Christmas Nightmare]
[One rainy day in December...]
What are you doing here?
What are you doing in front
of my house?
You will be doing individual missions today.
Really?
Good morning.
Why are you doing that to me?
What is this?
[What is their mission for the day?]
You'll be calling on this
to give us our orders?
I'm not going to ask
what's going to be happening today.
Wow... that's quite a bit of money.
I got a message.
[Couple off in pairs and
come to the bakery in Gangnam.]
meet at the bakery in Gangnam!]
I still remember how Ha Ha tricked me
for our last year's Christmas special.
[The Christmas nightmare he's reminded of
whenever he thinks about being paired off?]
The customer you are trying to reach
is on the other line...
Gary.
Is this fate or something? Why is
Kang Gary's phone the only one ringing?
I've tried calling others, but Gary's
call is the only one going through.
- I have to go to the bathroom real quick.
- Make it quick.
Take the phone with you,
and answer the call if it rings.
[Hands the phone back...]
Take the call if you're able to.
You have to answer
the phone if it starts to ring.
My phone's ringing.
Who is it?
[Who could be calling at a time like this?]
Hello?
Are you really going to talk
to me like that?
Hello?
Is this Song Ji Hyo?
Are you going to talk to me
so roughly like that?
No, I had a feeling it would be you.
Where are you, Gary?
I'm out in front of my house right now.
[Her voice is making him forget about
his urgency to go to the bathroom.]
Who are you going to partner up
with today?
Just accept that you and I
are a couple every Monday
until the day we die.
Well, I...
Even if you get married, you need to come
sleep over at my place on Mondays.
[You're mine on Mondays...]
This is no time to be joking around right now.
Tell me where you are.
- Tell me where you are.
- I told you that I'm in Apgujeong.
Apgujeong?
Where in Apgujeong are you?
Can you come to where I am instead?
Or how about we meet at that train station
in Gangnam instead?
- How about there?
- Meet in the middle?
How about in front of that cafe?
Okay, then I'll wait for you there.
Hurry up, okay?
You remember the cafe where you bought me
the caramel macchiato from, right?
- Turn around and look behind you.
- You want me to turn around?
[Ji Hyo... do you remember?]
- Why are you telling me to turn around?
- Just turn around.
[The Christmas that felt warmer
than any other Christmas' in the past...]
This is no time to be reminiscing
about the past. Just get on the road.
- Okay.
[Heading straight to the bathroom
as soon as he's off the phone.]
Thank you.
Hello.
A place full of memories.
This is the place where
I betrayed Kang Gary...
and gave him my affection,
as well as sadness.
[The place where she left Gary memories
of both joy and sadness.]
Kang Gary may be hungry when
he gets here.
One for me, and one for Gary.
[Gary... please come to me.]
Hi.
Where are you?
You're pooping?
No, no.
Where's the bathroom you're in?
You're still at the house?
Okay, Gary.
Finish pooping quickly,
and call me back.
Hurry up, okay?
Gary's still at his house right now,
and he's...
He's on the toilet.
[Gary heads off to do his mission with
a much lighter body and spirit.]
I have to go to the cafe first.
I'm going to text this picture to Gary.
I'm going to tell him to come quickly
because I've bought him a treat.
Kang Gary's not answering his phone.
The person you are trying to reach
is unavailable...
[Kang Gary...]
[Just where in the world are you?]
[To a place where Gary's joy
and sadness was once felt...]
[Add on an order of Ji Hyo's sadness.]
[Destination- 'P' Bakery in Gangnam.]
[Yoo-Lee-Ji trio makes their appearance.]
Thank you.
- Where is this place?
- I know this place!
- Let's all...
- A couple must walk in hand-in-hand.
[Must walk in hand-in-hand for them
to be acknowledged as a couple.]
- Where's everyone else?
- I don't know who to walk in with.
- Let's give the others a call.
- Should we try calling others?
Okay, let's give the others a call.
One, two, three.
- Go on and give them a call.
- Let's try giving them a call.
Let's see where they're at.
Don't act so antsy.
Which one of us three do you all think
will be left all alone?
Yoo Jae Suk!
- A lot of them seem to think that way.
- You think?
- I see someone.
- Where?
[Fighting amongst each other.]
- You don't have to hesitate right now.
- We don't need to do it like this.
[Are they playing around?]
You're probably wondering what we're doing,
but you'll find out once this show airs.
- Someone's coming.
- Where?
Move!
[Just then, Kkuk and Haroro
show up on the scene.]
- You two are together?
- I said, get out of the way.
- Move out of the way so that we can go in.
- I said, get out of our way!
Get out of the way!
Out!
Get out of our way!
- What are you doing?
- Get out of our way!
[Big-nosed Brother giving
the Tiger the eye.]
Get out of my way.
Get out of the way.
Out of my way!
[Big-nose and Jae Suk succeed
entering as a couple.]
[Please...]
[I can't be left alone like this...]
[Kkuk and Haroro succeed as a couple.]
You have to step outside, Kwang Soo.
Is it okay if we eat this?
- We can eat this, right?
- Go on and eat.
[A table full of delicious
baked goods for the couples.]
I can't believe they're coupled off again.
- What can I get for you?
- Let's just eat whatever is in front of us.
[No matter what the others say,
Kkuk and Haroro are a good match.]
I have a feeling that things are going to
get really entertaining out there.
[All the couples are in
comfortable viewing mode.]
The other three are going to gather
out front in a few.
Hurry!
What's taking you so long!
Where have you been?
- Where's Gary?
- I don't know! He stood me up!
- Forget Gary!
[Just where in the world did Gary go?]
- Where's Gary?
- What the heck?
What is this?
[Totally unexpected!
Ji Hyo and Kwang Soo are a couple!]
- What happened?
- What happened to Gary?
- This is not what I expected.
- Kang Gary stood me up.
- Seriously?
- Gary's not even answering his phone.
- He's not even answering his phone.
- What is this?
Kwang Soo!
This really ended working well for you.
[Congratulations to Kwang Soo for escaping
his single-dom.]
This is a very happy ending for him.
- Why won't Gary answer his call?
- I tried calling, but he won't answer.
Gary was on the toilet at his house
when I talked to him earlier on the phone.
[Suk Jin tries calling Gary...]
- What's going on here?
- Maybe Gary's running late.
What's this?
Isn't that Gary's phone?
[What is Gary's phone doing here?]
- Answer the phone.
- See if it really is his phone.
Answer the phone.
Hello?
- Hello?
- That is Gary's phone.
- What is this?
- What's going on here?
[Where did Gary go...
and what is his phone doing here?]
[It's Gary!]
- What is this?
- Come on.
Please untie me!
You deserve it!
- What happened?
- He's talking in casual tone to someone.
Why have you had me tied up
all morning? Huh?
Please!
- Please just untie me.
- No, Gary!
Don't take my freedom away from me.
Please!
What is this?
He's been kidnapped.
[Gary's been kidnapped!]
- We're all coupled off anyways.
- We can film without him today.
- What do you mean, film without him?
- Gary's been kidnapped anyway.
We have to go rescue him.
Why do we need to rescue him?
We can just make a report to the police.
Just call 119.
Why bother going to rescue him ourselves?
- Don't you have any loyalty?
- Calling 119 is the best thing to do.
[Ah...]
[Gary's phone...]
Let me see that.
Has he received any weird texts?
Check his phone call logs.
Nobody move.
- The criminal could be amongst us.
- You're the one who should stop moving.
Who has he been talking to the most?
[Start investigating the numbers which
show up most frequently on his call logs.]
It's Ji Hyo.
[The owner of that number is,
his Monday girlfriend, Ji Hyo.]
- It's you.
- Yes, it's me.
- You're the culprit?
- No.
[Oh?]
[There's a suspicious looking number?]
[Immediately tries calling that number.]
- It's none of our phones.
- Hello?
It's a familiar voice.
Hello?
Who is this?
[A familiar male voice.]
Kang Gary's been kidnapped.
Who is this?
- Mister!
- There's a call history made to this number.
Mister?
- What is this? His voice is...
- Is it Gil?
- Did you just call me, 'Mister'?
Gil, is it you?
- Hi, Jae Suk.
- It is Gil!
[The man behind the voice is,
Gil, from Leessang!]
The way you guys are speaking to me
right now is a bit rude.
- What did you say?
- How are we being rude?
- It's because we're...
- Why are you all talking to me like that?
It's because we're all flustered too.
We didn't expect you to answer the phone.
Where's Gary, Gil?
- I'm not sure where he is myself.
- This is Gil's real personal number.
- Is this really your number?
- This is his real number.
- I'm sorry.
- Sorry, Gil!
You really are just answering your phone
instead coming out on our show today?
[Did they just call Gil
on his personal cell number?]
- Yeah.
- Should we go pay Gil a visit?
Gil, where are you right now?
- Hello? Who is this?
- Hi, Gil. This is Kwang Soo.
Stay out of this, Kwang Soo!
- Sorry, Gil. We'll talk to you later.
- Wait, we should go see him.
There's no reason for Gary to have called
Gil from his mission cell phone.
[It's suspicious to see Gil's number
on this phone's phone record...]
Gil was the last person
he talked to on the phone.
What did you and Gary talk about
this morning on the phone?
- Who is this?
- This is Jae Suk.
Yes, Jae Suk.
I respect you and love you very much.
Where are you?
Right now, I'm...
I'm over in my neighborhood.
- You're in your neighborhood?
- Then let's go over to his neighborhood.
[Off to Gil's neighborhood!]
Please don't bring any awkward people.
Okay, who do you want me
to leave out?
At least... Jong Kook and Kwang Soo.
Why me?
Why do you not want me there?
You don't want them to come?
You know me, don't you?
You know my personality.
- If I even see their faces nearby...
- Okay, I got it.
- Don't worry, I got it.
[Gil is more sensitive than he may look?]
- Okay, we'll see you soon.
- Sorry, Gil!
- Okay, see you.
- See you soon, Hallyu star.
That's the way he needs to be treated.
Gil has been acting as Gary's
assistant of some sorts lately.
- They've been doing fan meetings in Asia.
- Gary's been doing fan meetings.
Even though they're doing
the meetings as Leessang
but Gary's been getting more attention,
and Gil could be getting jealous.
- So he could've been the one to kidnap him.
- Then maybe he's the culprit?
As you may have guessed, your mission
today is to find and rescue Gary.
We're not going to be
giving you a single hint.
You have to figure things out
for yourselves.
You must rescue Gary before
the time runs out.
The team that steps onto the platform we've
prepared with Gary, wins today's race.
[Gary's kidnapping case.]
If we don't rescue Gary today,
then he'll leave the show.
Yeah, and we can't have him
leaving the show ever again.
[Must hurry to rescue their flight risk icon.]
- Hello.
Can you take us to Seol-Rae village?
[Everyone is heading off to Seol-Rae
where Gil is there waiting for them.]
Let's hurry and follow
the car in front of us.
Hello.
[Mission to rescue Gary-
A battle amongst the three teams.]
[The last person Gary spoke to, Gil,
is their only clue so far to his whereabouts.]
Hello, Gil.
This is Ji Hyo.
- Hey, Sis-in-law!
- Yes, hello.
- Hi.
- It's been way too long.
- I haven't seen you since the concert.
- Gil is a softie when it comes to women.
- Have you been well?
- Yes, I have.
I'm actually on my way to see you right now,
and wanted to know where I need to go.
I enjoyed the ad the two of you
shot a while ago.
- Who's sitting next to you right now?
- My PD is sitting next to me right now.
- Are you the one who kidnapped him?
- Be quiet!
[Kwang Soo is a secret
that Blank Ji wants to keep hidden.]
- Yes, we're shooting Running Man right now.
- He must not be our guest for the day...
What's going on?
I'm at the cafe that I was told to go to.
Are you at a cafe right now?
Is it the cafe by your house?
The cafe right by my house.
In your neighborhood?
I... don't know where you live.
I know where he lives.
I once had to give him a ride home.
I know that's Kwang Soo's
voice next to you.
- No, PD Myuk is sitting next to me.
- Do I really have to lie about my existence?
- What wrong have I ever done?
- I'll come to the cafe right now.
I haven't done anything wrong to Gil.
- Hey! I told you not to say anything!
- Do I have to lie about me being here?
Gil didn't want you to come.
Did you not hear him saying that earlier?
You're like a blend of Jong Kook,
and Jae Suk put together.
[Kwang Soo is calling Gil with a number
that Gil wouldn't recognize.]
Hello?
- Hello?
- This is PD Kim Chul Woo from Running Man.
I know it's you, Jong Kook.
Hello?
[Gil is mistaking Kwang Soo's voice
to be that of Jong Kook's!]
Do you actually think that
I wouldn't recognize your voice?
He must be stupid.
I think he really must be stupid.
Hey, Baldy.
(Trying to impersonate Kkuk?)
[Going all out on his 'Kkuk' impersonation.]
Where are you?
I really don't know what's going on
right now, Jong Kook.
You're dead when I see you.
[Gil wholeheartedly believes
Kwang Soo to be Kkuk right now.]
I really have no idea right now,
but I'm out here after receiving Gary's call.
Just tell me where you're at right now.
[Feeling the confidence that comes with
Kkuk's name, and acting foolishly brave.]
I'm warning you right now not to tell anyone
where you're at even if it's me calling back.
What?
Even if I happen to ask you again later,
don't tell me where you're at.
[Trying to think of ways to stop Kkuk
from finding out where Gil is.]
- Aren't you filming right now?
- I am filming right now.
Even if I were to call you again asking you to
tell me where you're at, don't tell me.
[Making a nonsensical request to Gil.]
- Okay, Jong Kook.
- Okay.
Bye, Jong Kook.
I didn't know I was such a good
impersonator of Jong Kook.
How could he think that
my voice was Jong Kook's?
- How could he think that?
- My beloved Gil...
My beloved Gil.
Where are you, my beloved Gil?
Our team has the best chance of
winning right now, Gil.
Where are you, my beloved Gil?
Isn't this PD Kim Chul Woo?
[Gil really seems to have fallen for
Giraffe's trickery.]
- Where are you, Gil?
- There's Jae Suk over there.
- I really miss you, Gil. Where are you?
- We need to follow Jae Suk.
Come on, Gil. Today's
not your last day on this earth.
Don't do that, Jong Kook.
Don't go around threatening him.
- I wasn't threatening him.
- Why are you speaking to him like that?
No, that's not what he meant..
He wasn't threatening you at all.
- Apologize for the way you spoke to him.
- I'm sorry.
You can't talk to him like that.
He's very sensitive.
- That's not what I meant to do.
- You were threatening him.
- I want to apologize. I'm sorry.
- Tell him that's not what you meant.
Sorry, Gil.
I want to apologize.
That's not what I meant.
I'm telling you I didn't mean it like that.
- I just meant that we're filming now.
- Just accept Jong Kook's apology.
What I meant by that was,
I want to keep seeing you after today.
It's not like we're going to stop
being friends or anything.
- Ha Ha.
- Yes, Gil?
Bring PD Kim Chul Woo,
and come to Bang-Bae Middle School.
Bang-Bae Middle School?
That's where we are right now.
Come towards Jae Dong's house
which is right in front of that school.
Really?
To Jae Dong's house?
Yeah, come towards his house.
But Jae Dong's house is
really far away from here.
[Gil is at a cafe that is about halfway
between the school and Jae Dong's house.]
Jae Dong's house is
a really far walk from here.
Wait, over there!
[Oh?]
[That round head is...]
Over there!
He's over there!
[It's Gil!]
[Finding Gil by pure coincidence
on their walk over to Jae Dong's house.]
- What are you wearing right now?
- I thought you were Jae Dong.
[Gil is dressed in what seems to be
his most comfortable outfit.]
[Extra glad to see him from having
run into him by such sheer luck.]
- What took you so long?
- Why didn't you come on sooner?
- I don't even know what's going on right now.
- What's going on here?
Let's just go in and talk.
[Agreeing to get out of the rain,
and head inside to talk.]
- Have you seen Jae Suk?
- No, I haven't.
[Could Gil give them any clues to solve
the mystery behind Gary's kidnapping?]
Did you not see any cameras
around here?
[There are no cameras surrounding Gil,
and he's not even wearing a mic.]
- You really are here alone?
- I told you that I've got nothing.
I just came out here after
receiving Gary's call.
Seriously?
But doesn't this look like the perfect place
to keep someone locked and hidden away?
Maybe he's in the basement or something.
[Could kidnapped Gary be hidden away
somewhere in this place?]
- You got a call from Gary?
- And he told you to come here?
- Yeah.
- He called you?
Gary called me earlier this morning.
He called me and told me
to come and meet him here.
[Gil tells them that he's just as confused as
they are about what's going on.]
- So what happened?
- Wait, do you really eat like this?
- Yes, Jong Kook.
- Then why does your body look like that?
- What are you saying?
- His body is just fine right now.
His body is just fine right now.
[How many times do you need to be told?
He's a very sensitive man!]
- Then do I actually have something?
- We'll figure this out.
- Jae Suk, Gary's been kidnapped.
- Why would Gary be kidnapped?
I don't know either.
I don't know why he's been kidnapped.
Gary's been kidnapped, and to be honest,
we thought you had something to do with it.
We thought that you kidnapped Gary
because you were jealous of him.
Why would you even think that?
I'm Gary's carrier.
- That's what Jae Suk said.
- Jae Suk said that?
We found Gary's phone after he was kidnapped,
and when we searched through that phone
we found your number in
the call log.
- You were the person he called.
- What did Gary say to you?
- He asked if I heard.
- So I asked him what he was talking about.
That's when Gary just asked me to
come meet him here.
- So he told you to come here?
- Yeah, so I came here, and no one was here.
- There weren't even any cameras here.
- Then he must've been kidnapped on his way.
He must've been kidnapped on his way
here to meet you.
- We're going to put a mic on Gil.
- You're giving me one after all this time?
I was wondering what I was doing here.
He seriously didn't have any cameras
or any mics on him?
- You must've been so lonely.
- I've had a ton of unknown calls.
I seriously have no idea
what's going on right now.
Here it is.
[The Yellow Team followed the
Blue Team here.]
There they come.
[Everyone gathers together where Gil is.]
- Hello, Gil.
- Where's Gary?
- Hi, Gil.
- Gil has no idea what's going on right now.
- Hello.
- You really don't know what's going on?
[Everyone's shocked at how overly
casually dressed Gil is at the moment.]
- They just put this mic on me.
- They really did just put it on him.
I went to the cafe,
and there was no one there.
- There was no one there.
- He's telling the truth.
- There wasn't even single camera there.
- There was no one when we saw him.
- No cameras when you guys arrived?
- We searched all over that place.
- There was nothing there.
- Seriously?
- What does that mean?
- But... what am I doing here?
That's what we'd like to ask.
What are you doing here?
- I don't know why I'm here.
- Give us a clue.
- Are you a guest on our episode?
- He doesn't have any clues.
Gil really doesn't know anything?
[Gil really doesn't know anything?]
- What are you doing?
- Checking to see if you're hiding anything.
So this is how you guys film this show?
- What is all this?
- There has to be something on Gil.
There must be something here for us to
have been directed towards him.
There must be something here in the cafe
since this is where Gary said to meet.
- Why do you keep trying to strip me?
- Gil really must not know anything.
- What is it? What do you know?
- I'm going to lose my mind here.
- You really don't know anything?
- No, I don't!
- Do you know where Gary went?
- I don't want you talking to me.
When you tried to abandon me
by the riverside expressway...
[Huh? What's he talking about?]
We went to hangout after some dinner outing
that Running Man had.
So I asked Kwang Soo to give me a ride back
to my house since it was on his way.
He didn't take you home?
- You know how he is though.
- How?
He told me that he'll take a right
at Donjak Bridge
and that I should get out at the bridge
and walk the rest of the way home.
- That's not what I meant.
- How could he have said that?
- So I want you to stay away from me.
- How could you have said that to him?
- Why were you trying to abandon him?
- I wasn't trying to abandon him.
I want you to go wait outside.
- You can't take him anywhere.
- Go wait outside.
[Giraffe has been kicked out from the group.]
- You know that wasn't right.
- He never should've said that to you.
How much is this?
[Huh?]
- Go away and stay away from him.
- What is that?
[You're not... really thinking...]
[A pink headband... that's suitable for Gil?]
[And Jae Suk actually
puts that on Gil's head?]
[The bald man with the pink headband on his
head is getting fired up from the shame.]
- Please get out of here, Mister.
- That's my gift to your future wife.
[The baldheaded headband?]
- This really isn't right.
- That's wrong.
[I told you that I'm a sensitive man!]
Sit down. Let's let Gil sit down.
He's having a really tough time right now.
Get away from me, Kwang Soo!
Here's some water with lemon.
[Everyone's trying to grab Gil's attention
since he may have the only clue.]
- Do we have to play a game or something?
- What game?
[Feeling like he has to do something
now that he's on the show?]
- Don't feel like you need to do something.
- You just need to be.
Anyone who wants to get out of
here can leave.
[Just then]
[A delivery?]
I have a delivery for Mr. Gil Sung Joon.
- This must be it.
- Then he really didn't know anything.
- Why don't you open it?
- He really didn't lie to us.
- He wasn't lying.
- I'll open it.
[Gary asked Gil to meet up with him...
but receives a mysterious package instead.]
You can't get all immature on me,
and try to take this away from me, okay?
- We don't like doing things like that.
- Don't try to intercept me or anything.
What's 'intercept'?
- Seriously?
- You're trying to be too original.
- Wait... hang on.
- Okay, you go take a look on your own first.
Why don't you open the box over there?
- I'm just trying to take a peek.
- Leave him alone to open the box.
[Just what did he find inside the box?]
- What is it?
- What's in there?
[A clue behind Gary's kidnapping?]
[There's not just one?]
- Where did the delivery come from?
- You don't need to know.
- Don't even ask him anything.
- Stop talking to him!
- He told you to leave him alone.
- Just go home!
- Don't you think you're being too harsh?
- Just go home.
I'll call you later, so just go home.
[Yeah... why don't you go and
get some rest?]
- What's in there?
- This is exactly what I thought it'd be.
- Let me switch spots first.
Let the Blue Team come up here.
- Switch spots with us.
- The moment you see this...
you're going to run out of here.
- I guarantee.
- You must be quite athletic.
[Blue Team to the back and Yellow Team to
the front due to Big-nose's comment.]
- Why would you say that?
- He just made fun of me.
[Whatever Gil says goes!
He's the one with the only clue.]
This is really...
I know exactly what this means.
- So what I mean is...
- So it's a clue to the next location?
What's with this guy?
- What did I say?
- Go, get away.
[Back to their original spot
in less than ten seconds.]
Can I share what I know with them
however I want?
- Sure!
- Seriously?
Then I'll just give all of you
a piece of the clue.
Let's all see it together.
[A total of three clues inside the box.]
[Just what do these clues mean?]
[A wedding photo, video tape,
and A-Pink's album.]
- Let's go.
- Thanks for your help, Gil. Let's go.
[Completely different treatment
the moment they got their clues.]
- Are you all really abandoning me like this?
- That's what usually happens.
Thanks for your help, Gil.
Let's look at it together.
[They're all taking a close look at
the videotape that was delivered to Gil.]
[It's Gary!]
[It's the scene of his kidnapping!]
What are you guys doing?
What are you doing here?
[Someone's in the car?]
- That's an A-Pink song!
- Ah! A-Pink!
- This is A-Pink's album.
- I think that car was A-Pink's car.
[A-Pink's album that was delivered,
and their song that was played...]
Seeing this picture means that Gary's
somehow close to these people, right?
[A picture of Leessang, Dynamic Duo,
Jung Chi, and Jung In?]
I'm sorry to say this, but can
you leave since this is Running Man?
Jae Suk... remember how Gary was
teamed up with A-Pink the last time?
Wait!
I just got a text.
- What does it say?
- That the culprit is inside the delivery box.
[The culprit is inside the delivery box.]
The culprit must be one of the five
in the picture.
- Then it must be one of these people.
- Then couldn't Gil be the culprit?
- Gil's not the culprit.
- You can leave if you're not the culprit.
Can't I stay since I'm already
on the show?
- This is a picture.
- What else is in there?
[If they put all the clues together...]
Stop hanging around and just leave.
- Stop being like this.
- This is Sunday now.
- I'll see you on Saturday.
- I saw a picture in there.
I told you that I'll see you on Saturday.
- You really are being too harsh.
- Let me work with my Sunday buddies.
I'm close to all these guys too!
All these guys and I are really close!
But we're in the middle of filming
our show right now.
You're putting me in a tough spot right now,
so quit it, and just leave.
[Today is Sunday-
Saturday work buddy is forced out.]
- Where are you going to go?
- I'm going home and taking a shower.
I guess this is it.
[Gains their first hint from Gil,
dressed in his workout outfit!]
[The culprit is in this photo?]
[Kwang Soo is quietly searching through
the numbers off in the corner.]
[Gary knows Eun Ji's number
from A-Pink!]
A-Pink's album was in the box.
Should we give Eun Ji a call?
[Could Eun Ji know anything?]
- Hello?
- Hi, Eun Ji.
- Who is this?
- It's Kwang Soo.
Hi, Kwang Soo!
This isn't your number.
I'm calling you from a different phone.
You're calling me from a different phone?
Anyways, why are you calling me?
Why would you ask me why I'm calling?
Can't I just call to say hi?
- I'm so happy to hear from you!
- Yeah, it's been awhile.
- What are you doing?
- I'm at practice right now.
- You're at practice?
- Yes, we're at the studio right now.
I see... by any chance, is there
anything between you and Gary?
- Do you, Eun Ji?
- Why are you being so blunt?
I did receive some sort of
a delivery today.
- Tell me where you're at.
- Where's your studio?
Tell me where your practice studio is.
- I'll send you the address.
- Send the address to this phone, okay?
- Yes, I'll send it.
- Thanks.
[Mission to rescue Gary-
Yellow Team is off to get their next clue!]
So if the culprit is one of the people
in that picture...
- Since their song was playing...
- Maybe we'll get another clue to the culprit.
Just where in the world is Gary?
- I'm sure we'll find something there.
- I'm sure we will.
[On their way to see the newlyweds,
and possible suspects, Jung Chi and Jung In.]
- I'm sure something will work itself out.
- Of course.
The future is shining brightly ahead of us.
- Hello?
- Gaeko. ('Dog nose')
Tell me what your address is,
or do you want to meet somewhere else?
- How do we get to where you are?
- There's a snack shop and a bakery out front.
A snack shop?
- Go to the ddukbokki snack shop.
- Okay.
- And make sure you get the curry ddukbokki.
- Okay, we got it.
Isn't curry ddukbokki a little weird?
[In front of 'S' Elementary School
in Shinsadong.]
This is the place?
- Why didn't he just tell us this was it?
- Who is it?
[They're there!]
Mister!
Oh my goodness!
You're both here?
[The ultimate hip-hop duo:
Dynamic Duo- Choi Ja and Gaeko.]
- It's really nice to see you guys.
- You guys have a gym right across the street.
You guys should start working out.
[Workout fanatic trying to talk them into
starting to work out right away?]
There's nothing better than working out.
Just come workout with me.
It's the best stress reliever out there.
Sit down. You guys should sit down.
Come on and have a seat.
[Waiting until after they're done eating
to start the questioning?]
This place has the best curry ddukbookki.
[The delicious taste of their curry ddukbokki
that's making them forget why they even came.]
I heard this place is good.
Wow, this is so delicious.
Unbelievable.
- Why don't you guys start talking?
- What do you guys know?
[Could these guys be the culprits?]
I'll be honest and tell you
what's going on.
- The truth is, Gary's been kidnapped.
- Gary has?
Yeah, we don't know who kidnapped him,
and why they would've done it.
Gil received a delivery while
he was with us.
And there was a picture inside that box.
As a clue?
In the picture was Leessang,
Jung Chi and Jung In.
[And these two men who were also
clearly in the picture.]
Or could they be accomplices?
Gary's also in the picture.
Gary?
- Why would Gary be here?
- No, he's in here.
[Could Gary, who's been kidnapped be in here?]
What is this door?
I have the washer in there.
You're just wasting your time.
[Searching every nook and cranny.]
You'd be wiser to look elsewhere than
to waste your time here.
Look at how he keeps nervously trying
to send us away somewhere.
Something feels suspicious.
[Could these two be the kidnappers?]
[Big-nose and Hyuk arrive to meet with
Jung Chi and Jung In.]
That's the place.
Right over there.
What are you guys doing here?
[Another set of possible suspects!
Jo Jung Chi and Jung In.]
- Hello.
- Congratulations on getting married.
- Congratulations on the wedding.
- Thank you.
You actually got married
on the mountains?
- We got married while on our vacation.
- How can you get married on an impulse?
- We're out on our date right now.
- Really?
- Where are you guys going to go?
- To Yuksang.
- We just finished having dinner.
- Seriously?
- What are you guys doing here anyway?
- We needed to talk to you about something.
Gil received a delivery while he was with us,
and there was a picture inside the box.
There was a picture of you two, Gil, Gary,
and Dynamic Duo in there.
[The clue stated that the culprit
is inside the box.]
So you guys were also in the picture.
[Big-nose Brother going into his
full on investigative mode.]
- What color is your car?
- Our car?
- Yes, we do have a car.
- What color is it?
- What color is the car?
- It's black, I think.
- Are you the culprit?
- Tell us if you're the culprit.
- That's just absurd.
- Let's tell them we are and just end this.
[His statement flusters the investigators.]
I don't think this will do.
Get up out of your seat right now.
- Why are you getting mad at me?
- I think that you need to be taken in.
[Two middle aged cops
pulling out their tough guy act.]
- You guys need to come with me.
- Do you see how Jae Suk is getting violent?
Do you have anything in your pockets?
You leave me no choice but to
make you guys take the lie detector test.
- You have a lie detector test?
- Yeah.
Isn't that a basic prop
for any investigator to have?
- You guys think we wouldn't have one?
- If this is the way you want to do it...
You can't ask us if we love each other
or things like that, okay?
- Just don't ask.
- Are you afraid?
[Could these newlyweds... be the culprits?]
[Yellow Team arrives at A-Pink's studio with
the snack they requested in hand.]
- Is A-Pink here?
- Eun Ji.
Miss Jung Eun Ji?
Do you see her anywhere?
[Where could A-Pink be?]
- Hello!
[The young girls start
chanting for their snack.]
- What is all that?
- We don't know. We just got it ourselves.
They were just delivered to us.
[Their rehearsal studio
is full of gift boxes.]
No, don't give them anything yet.
- This isn't the delivery we were meaning.
- These were all delivered here.
[Then all these are supposed to be clues?]
So you guys...
you guys must be the culprits.
- Gary is...
- Gary's disappeared?
- Gary's been kidnapped.
- Really?
[Something feels a little suspicious...]
See?
Something feels really off.
[Starting their investigation.]
- There's nothing else here?
- This is your delivery?
- Thank you for the snack.
- Thank you.
- No, you can't start eating that yet.
- You can't take it back from us now.
You can only eat after we find our next clue.
You guys could be the culprits.
Don't even think about stepping out of here.
- Let's look for it together.
- Shut the door.
- Okay, we'll help you.
- Gary could be in here.
[Gary's kidnappers... just who are you?]
We have to find something.
But I don't think this is the same delivery.
What is this?
- You haven't seen Gary?
- No, we haven't.
- All we got was a delivery.
And we just heard that he's been taken.
[Then could something be inside
one of these boxes?]
I feel like something could be in here.
I really think something could be in here.
[Never-ending boxes...]
[A dud!]
None of you girls can leave this room
since you could be the culprits.
- Okay.
[Could these girls be the culprits?]
Couldn't it be possible that Gary could've
been held hostage in this cafe earlier?
[If these two are Gary's kidnappers,
then it means Gary could be in here.]
Can you come with us?
[Asking them to come along since
they're a flight risk.]
- Come with us.
- We need your cooperation.
Go search upstairs,
and I'll go search downstairs.
Why are you looking for Gary?
We have to find Gary.
- Where's Gary? Be honest with me.
- I feel bad seeing how hard you're searching.
Where could he be?
There's a reason why you guys are here.
There's either a clue in here,
or you two are the culprits.
- Don't you agree?
- Do you even know what you're looking for?
- I don't know either.
- You're just looking around?
There's a basement in here.
[Inspector Yoo heads down to the basement.]
Isn't this the type of space where
Gary was being held earlier?
I really am sorry.
We're not the type of investigators who
go by our gut feelings.
We're taking the scientific approach to this
by watching for any changes in your
behavior or facial expressions.
We're watching out for even the slightest
bit of change in your behavior.
We're very scientific people.
What about this right now is
being scientific?
- You're just rummaging around.
- I thought this was a letter.
- I don't know what they're doing.
- Where's our Gary?
I think their concept for the day is,
'Dumb and Dumber'.
- What are you guys talking about?
- We're tough detectives.
- We're being very scientific.
- I feel bad. I wish I knew something.
[Are these two really just out on a date?]
I'm going to find something.
- What are you two looking for?
- Hey!
Look at this!
What is it?
- Did you see how scientific we are?
- You guys are smart.
[Discovers the hidden cellphone...
through their scientific investigation?]
- What is that?
- There's something here.
[A mysterious cellphone,
that's locked down with a passcode.]
- What is it?
- How would we know?
- We need the secret code.
- Tell us what the code is.
- This is our first time seeing the phone.
- We've never seen this phone.
- What's the date of your wedding anniversary?
November 29th.
1129.
No, that's not right.
How are we to unlock this?
- This is still locked.
- Tell us what the code is right now.
Is it, '0000'?
[It's not '0000' either...]
This is driving me crazy.
Do I have to go into my hacking mode?
[Say what?]
Oh yeah...
I forgot that you used to be a hacker.
[The truth we weren't aware of for 40 years-
Yoo Hyuk used to be a hacker.]
Too funny.
I think this is the only thing
we're going to get out of here.
- Let's go back down.
- Let's get out of here.
[Now that they've found their cellphone...]
[It's now time to pay a visit to
Dynamic Duo?]
We need to pay them a visit
and see if they're the culprits.
Good luck catching the culprits.
- Scold them once you get your hands on them.
- Okay.
[But... are these two
really not the culprits?]
[One hour ago.]
- That'll be too hard to find.
- You think?
[These two are the ones who hid
the cellphone under there?]
But why are we the suspects?
- You guys were inside the box of clues.
- Hey, look at this.
[Blank Ji seems to have found something.]
Awesome.
[A puzzle piece?]
We'll get our next clue once
we piece the puzzle back together.
[Piecing the puzzle together.]
Look for a piece that looks like this.
[What could it be? The puzzle is slowly
starting to come together.]
- This is hard.
- I'm really bad at things like this.
[What could the completed puzzle
be a picture of?]
When we saw that footage of
Gary being kidnapped earlier...
He didn't seem all that glad to see the person
nor did he seem all that shocked either.
- Yeah, you're right.
- If...
- I really don't think it was A-Pink.
- He would've given a big smile if it was.
He would've looked really elated.
The way I see it, it's not A-Pink.
No, I don't think it's A-Pink.
I have a feeling...
that it's Gaeko and Choi Ja.
I called Jae Suk earlier,
and he just texted me back.
I'm in the middle of my class right now.
I'll call you back when the class is over?
What is this?
[Blank Ji is dismantling
their completed puzzle.]
[Destroying the hint!]
- Thank you.
- Thank you!
[Did they find any helpful clues?]
- We just need one more clue.
- One more clue, and I think we'll know.
- There could be accomplices.
- Yes, that's possible.
We can't be thinking that
there's only one culprit.
You're right.
We need to be suspicious of everyone.
What do you think this phone means?
I feel like we need to unlock this
if we want to get our clue.
But I don't know what the passcode is.
You don't think it's Jung In
and Jung Chi either?
No, I really don't think
its Jung Chi or Jung In.
No, I don't think so either.
We shouldn't tell anyone what we think.
We shouldn't tell anyone else that
we don't think it's them.
What is that?
Are you getting a video call?
- Gary!
[It's really Gary!]
- It's Gary?
[Their first phone call since his kidnapping.]
Just wait a little bit longer.
We're going to come rescue you.
Where are you?
[Can't really understand what he's saying
because of the mask blocking his mouth...]
I can't hear you!
What did you say?
- Gary!
- We want to find you, and we need more clues.
Is it Choi Ja, or Gaeko?
Who's the culprit?
- You don't know?
- Who is it? Who did you see earlier?
- Tell us something.
- Where are you?
[Who took Gary?
And where is he right now?]
No... what happened?
[Gary's call is abruptly disconnected!]
What happened?
What's going on here?
No.
Gary, no!
[Blue Team is paying Dynamic Duo a visit.]
- Who is it?
- Hey, Dog nose. It's me, Big-nose.
- Choi Ja. You're here too?
- What are you two doing here?
- Are you okay?
- I don't know. Am I okay?
- So this is your office?
- This is our work studio.
- This is where we work on our music.
- Really?
- You guys are the culprits, right?
- What?
- That's the first thing you ask?
- Sorry about that.
- Are you guys the culprits?
- You are, aren't you? Take a seat.
[Makes them sit back down.]
- Did you see Gary this morning?
- This morning?
- Gary? No, we didn't see him.
- You saw him, didn't you?
[Nonstop questioning.]
- I have no idea what's going on.
- Did you see Gary?
- No, I haven't seen Gary at all.
- I haven't seen Gary in a week.
- Did you two...
- I feel like we're getting interrogated.
- So tell us the truth.
- Tell us why you kidnapped Gary.
We really haven't seen Gary
at all this week.
How could you suspect such innocent
looking people as us?
Of all people, you can't be saying things
like that to Big-nosed Brother.
Let's not be like this to each other.
Come on, Dog-nose!
- Yes, Big-nose.
- Come on, we're both nose people.
Then we're going to look around here a bit.
Hope you understand.
You can look around all you want,
but you'll really be wasting your time.
Did you bring a search warrant?
You can't be doing this without a warrant.
You can't search around without a warrant.
What color is your car?
- Mine?
- Is it black?
- It's black, isn't it?
- Why don't you have a seat?
[Making them sit whenever
they're suspicious about something.]
[Big-nose takes a seat too?]
Maybe you should sit down.
I know that we're all friends,
but we can't help this.
We need to wrap up this investigation.
- This is injustice.
- The real culprits are getting away.
- I feel bad for you guys.
- I think you're wasting your time.
- You think A-Pink would be better suspects?
- You know they're not those type of girls.
- Why did you kidnap him?
- This is all we have.
[Wait... that's?]
['Mid' and 'Low' envelopes?]
- This is all we've got.
- We received this earlier.
- This is all we ever got.
- Give us the middle one.
- We can't just give it to you.
- What do you want from us?
Jong Kook and Ha Ha had to
take a test.
[Kkuk and Ro-Ro already took the
top hint after completing a test.]
- Show us how well you can rap.
- Rapping is our...
I used to make my living by rapping.
Seriously?
[Going straight into rap mode.]
[Rap machine, MC Big-nose!]
- He's a rapping machine.
- Oh yeah.
- Why are you writing the lyrics?
- Can you do it impromptu?
Of course!
We can freestyle it.
[Freestyle rap!]
Freestyling fits us better.
We're not the type to write it down.
- This is how I was taught to rap.
- Want us to give you a beat?
[The beats starts to flow right away.]
I can understand that
you're having fun, but...
[Hyuk is trying to put a stop to
Big-nose's rapping.]
If that's how you're going to rap,
then we might as well just talk.
We might as well just have a conversation.
That's not rapping.
- Just take the low hint and go.
- Come on, yo!
[Firing up the atmosphere.]
- Come on, Bro!
- Let's rap this out!
[Meanwhile...]
We were thinking about it, and
the last time you were on the show...
You guys didn't take the win,
so you didn't get the winning gold.
So we're thinking that you're bitter about it
and that's why you kidnapped Gary.
[Could this couple have been the culprits
to have kidnapped Gary?]
Give us our Gary back.
- Where is he?
- How could I have kidnapped him?
[Jung Chi and Jung In are still
claiming their innocence.]
- Give him back. Where's Gary?
- It really isn't me.
- How could I have kidnapped Gary?
- Then who else could've taken him?
Just tell us what it was that
Jae Suk and Suk Jin asked you guys.
They asked us what had happened,
and they asked if we knew where Gary was.
They walked around here for a bit,
and they found something.
[Immediately starts to
search their surroundings.]
This place is quite large.
There's upstairs and downstairs too.
There are three floors.
- I'm going to go downstairs.
- Search downstairs, Ji Hyo.
[The newlyweds have finally
found some peace.]
Let's check down in the basement.
[Searching every nook and cranny.]
[Searching thoroughly.]
There's nothing up here.
[Kkuk is also searching
up on the third floor.]
What's this?
[Kkuk discovers the cellphone!]
Come up to the third floor, Dong Hoon.
Come all the way up to the corner area.
[Ji Hyo also discovers the cellphone!]
I need an unlock code.
Do we need to go and find out what
the code is from Jung Chi and Jung In?
From what those A-Pink girls told us...
[Could the secret code have anything to do
with the puzzle from earlier?]
[Still ongoing with their freestyle rapping.]
- What is this?
- What are you doing?
[ A brand new style of rap?]
[A very unique song.]
[His feet are automatically moving along
to the beat?]
Just give us the low hint.
[His face is now beet red.]
[They don't deserve anything better
than the low hint?]
What the heck was that?
- That was the absolute worst.
- What do you mean, the worst?
[The two middle aged rappers are
disappointed with their feedback.]
We're leaving only because we
don't have a lot of time.
We're leaving because of our lack of time.
[Any more time, and they could've been
dubbed the newest rappers on the scene?]
[His passion for rapping
has been discovered.]
[Their numerous sheets of lyrics.]
- We'll email you more in the morning.
- Okay, we'll be expecting it.
- We really were expecting something.
- I really wanted to show you something new.
I haven't shown you my new cicada rap.
You guys would flip out if you saw.
If you saw me rap like this,
you guys would just flip out.
[His one emergency weapon?
The cicada rap.]
- You're lucky that I'm out of time.
- I've seen him do it before.
You know who Eminem is, right?
I'm Meminem.
- You should've sang about that.
- You should've used that in the lyrics.
- Wait, we'll give you another chance.
- Another chance at the mid hint.
Rap about being the Meminem,
and we'll give you the mid hint.
Okay, Meminem.
[Meminem immediately starts
to write the lyrics.]
- I think he may have a chance.
- This is American style rap.
The God of American rapping is...
His name is... Eminem.
The God of Running Man's
rap is... Meminem.
- And...
- I shout out all the time, 'Mem, Mem...'
[This is what you call, cicada rap!]
- That's perfect!
- Doesn't that sound good?
- You may have something.
- I'm telling you that we've got this.
- We're fine.
- This is good.
[Cicada rap position.]
[Meminem featuring Big-nose.]
[This is cicada rap!]
[Big-nose and Meminem!]
[A rapping style that only needs something
for them to cling themselves to.]
[Even the ultimate hip-hop duo can't help
but break out into an applause.]
You saw that, right?
It wasn't because we couldn't do it.
[Meminem's performance is making the duo
give all the clues that they have to them.]
You want the song for yourselves,
don't you?
If you ever need any rap lyrics,
you just let me know.
- We've got a lot more where that came from.
- We can come up with a song on the spot.
You saw how quickly we wrote the lyrics?
It only takes us five seconds to write it.
You can use our song if you want.
We're going to get going.
Bye guys.
[Their cicada rap earned themselves
the mid-level hint.]
- Squeezing got something out of them.
- What do you mean, squeeze?
[Meminem and Big-nose's pride is hurt.]
We've got a lot more than that.
We're just saving it for later.
- What's that?
- You really want to see?
[Ah... so this is what they meant.]
- We've got a mocking bird rap too.
- A mocking bird?
We've got a variety of different styles.
- We're going to go now.
- Bye.
[They earned themselves the mid-level hint
with their spontaneous cicada rap.]
Low hint only had one card,
and the mid hint had three.
[Three cards inside the mid-level hint...]
[Hip hop, wig mania, fedoras.]
Wig mania?
[Could it be...]
- Isn't it Gil?
- I think it is.
- He wears wigs. Is it Gil?
- It's Gil!
[30 minutes ago.]
[The puzzle that the Yellow Team completed.]
This is Gil.
[That's definitely Gil!]
Why is there a puzzle of Gil?
It has to do with Gil.
[Why is Gil in the puzzle?]
Gil's in that picture too.
Then is Gil the kidnapper?
[Could Gil be the culprit?]
We have the top level hint right here.
L.
L? What's this?
[The four cards indicate...]
What does it say?
Gill?
[Gil?]
[I'm sure that they
all must've guessed by now.]
It's the perfect weather for some chasing.
[Then the Gil that they saw earlier is...]
I'm sure they must've started to figure out
that it must've been me by now.
Shall we get going?
[Then it means that Gil is...]
[The culprit?]
I know of a place...
that makes amazing udon.
Tofu udon with a ton of
hot pepper flakes.
We've still got plenty of time
before they catch up to me.
- Gil is the culprit.
- We need to figure this out.
- What do we need the passcode for?
- We need it to get the clue.
We need it to get the information and
figure out where Gary is.
Everything is pointing to the fact that
Gil is our culprit.
[All the clues are indicating that
Gil is their culprit]
[The completed puzzle showed
a picture of Gil...]
It's Gil.
Street?
What are you talking about?
You think that the secret code
is 'street'?
Gil!
(Gil=street)
Let's just try it.
[It is 'Gil' after all...]
[That's not the code!]
Hip hop.
The hint that we just got, and the
hint we got from Dynamic Duo earlier.
- Could that be it?
- You think?
Could 'Gill' be the passcode?
[The correct passcode!]
[The code to the locked cellphone
is, 'Gill'!]
- Is this the order?
- No, it's 'Gill'.
[The name the four cards indicated...]
['Gill' is the code!]
[Time to go get the culprit?]
Thank you for all your help.
- Yes, thank you.
- You guys are our good luck charms.
[Thinking...]
If it's Gil... then could it be this?
Gill?
- Try it.
- G.I.L.L.
[The phone is unlocked!]
- This was the hint.
- I see!
- There's no need for us to go here then.
- We don't even need to go.
There's a map.
It should be indicating to a location.
Where is it pointing to?
[A map to indicate Gil's location?]
Are we supposed to chase him down?
Can you take us to Banpo?
That's our first destination.
[The phone unlocks to reveal a map
to indicate Gil's location?]
What did you press?
What did you just do?
This is a GPS finder.
It's a map to help us find where Gil is.
[Gil is currently in Banpo.]
- Let's go.
- Let's get on the road.
I'm going to go and get a big bowl of udon
with a ton of red pepper flakes on it.
Oh my goodness... here's my first caller.
Hello?
- Yes, Jae Suk.
- Where are you?
Where are you headed?
I'm heading towards your heart!
I see that you're not done
here on our show.
I thought we were finished
filming together.
No, we're not finished!
Where are you?
You're the culprit?
- I don't know!
- Are you by a bus station or something?
Is that where you're at?
In Banpo?
We're watching you right now!
Hello?
How did they know that?
Lock your window.
What's going on here?
How did they know that I was here?
They know exactly where I'm at.
Then it means that all the other members
know where I'm at too.
They must have something to help them
find my location.
[Gil is smarter than we thought?]
Then I need to exercise Article 16
of the law.
He's at the intersection heading
towards Jamwon-Dong.
[Heading towards Jamwon-Dong.]
It's been Gil all along.
So he's the kidnapper.
Seriously...
We've got you now, Gil Sung Joon.
See?
- Meminem helped us figure it out.
- Meminem helped us find him.
[Meminem- So good!]
[Red Team on Gil's tail!
Off to capture their suspect!]
He's on the move.
I don't think he's on foot.
He's moving right now.
He must be in a car.
[All the teams are fixated on their GPS.]
He's coming towards us right now.
[Gil is heading straights towards
the Red Team on the same road!]
We could be passing him right now.
[They could even be passing each other!]
This is starting to get fun.
I'm starting to get into this.
[They're closing in on each other.]
This is where we're at right now.
[Gil is stopped at the light
at the intersection.]
He's stopped at the light right there.
I bet that he's right over there.
I still can't forget the look in their eyes.
Telling me to leave as soon as
I gave them the hint.
Where did they think I was going to go?
Since he's over there right now...
This feels more like Running Man now.
I haven't done anything much so far.
I've been stuck too long at a standstill.
[They're right next to one another!]
[Just then!]
[That car going by is Gil's car!]
[They just passed by one another!]
They know exactly where I'm at.
He just passed by us.
[Lost Gil right in front of their eyes...]
Where did he go?
[Where could Gil be going?]
- Is he trying to get on the highway?
- He's right by the highway right now.
I think he's trying to get on Gyungbu highway.
[Getting closer to the entryway
to Kyungbu highway.]
[All three teams are seeing
exactly what Gil is up to.]
- He's already on it.
- He's on the highway.
- Is he going to Bundang?
- Either Bundang or Pangyo. Keep going.
Where are you in such a rush to get to?
Why are you driving on Kyungbu highway?
Gil Sung Joon.
We can see that you're passing Woomyunggyo.
You're just driving right along.
We're right on your tail right now.
I think we're going to be catching up
to your car in just a few moments.
And you may get slightly hurt
during the arresting process.
- You're being too harsh with your words.
- Yes, sorry.
My actions are harsher than my words.
Which I will show you later.
Let me just make one thing clear.
If that's the way you guys want to play
then I can't give you any of the information
that I know and have.
No, we'll just get that information
out of your throat ourselves.
In that case,
come meet me in Bundang.
Anyway, we're on your tail right now.
- Well see you later, Gil Sung Joon.
- Okay.
There must be a tracker of some sorts on me.
What the heck?
Where is the tracker?
Ah, it must be on the car.
[The tracker is actually on his phone!
Mistakenly thinks that it's on his car.]
Then there's no point in trying to
thwart them off right now.
- Hey, he just got off the highway.
- Off where?
- Hangyo exit?
- He must be heading to Bundang.
Can you take us to Seohyun-ro?
[Where could Gil be going?]
I wonder how I can shake them off?
[The destination he's heading to is...]
['N' building in Bundang.]
[This is the place...
where Gary is being held captive!]
I need to get rid of this car first.
[Wanting to get rid of the car from thinking
that the tracker is somewhere in the car.]
He's at Jeongjayeok.
I bet it'll really confuse them if I leave
the car parked in the parking garage.
But is the tracker really hidden
somewhere on the car?
[No!
The tracker in on your cellphone!]
[Car is parked!]
[Just then, he makes a phone call
to someone.]
Gary.
[Gary?]
[Hasn't Gary been kidnapped?]
[It's Kang Gary!]
[How can this be!]
Hello?
[What is going on here?]
[The kidnapper?
The victim?]
I've been hearing rumors that
you're doing a really good job.
How about you?
Did you do a good job?
[Accomplices?]
[Nine o'clock this morning.]
It's nice to see you.
We're Gary and Gil, a.k.a. Leessang.
It's nice to see everyone.
What are you doing?
Why are you acting like that?
The name of today's race is...
The Christmas Nightmare.
Gary's kidnapping case.
This is fun.
Are we on the same team?
The two of us are supposed to
fool everyone else?
He's more of a foe than a friend.
I don't know if we can work well together.
[This is when Leessang's
Christmas Nightmare began.]
[During their morning mission opening...]
[Gary purposely didn't show up after
promising Blank Ji that he'd be her partner.]
What if she continues to wait around?
I feel like she's going to wait all day.
[Even then... Gil was with him all along.]
[Even when Kwang Soo had called...]
There's not even a camera in the bathroom.
- Can you stick the mic in there?
- Why do I have to hold out the mic for him?
Answer the phone.
I've got the mic outside the door.
[And the kidnapped video footage
that the members saw earlier...]
[Was taped by Gil himself!]
How as my acting?
- I think you've tied it too tight.
- You have to if you want them to believe you.
[When he was kidnapped
and dragged off to the car...]
[The person that Gary saw in the car...
was Gil.]
[A perfect kidnapping scene!]
Let's all make them suspect you
right at the start.
- Right from the get go?
- Right from the get go.
Should your number be the last call
on my call log?
Then they're all totally
going to think that it's me.
What's this number right here?
[They all fell for the bait.
Everyone came to see Gil as they predicted.]
Then I'll go back to my house
and act like I was just leaving my house.
Your role in this is very important
from this point on.
The way I see it, it would be much better
if none of the cameras even followed me in.
No cameras, or mics.
As if I was really just leaving my house.
He's really flustered right now.
He had nothing on him.
[Gil's stellar acting skills totally
tricked all the Running man members.]
- He really looks like he was just at the gym.
- He must be telling the truth.
But if I were to go in there,
it would be me against all six of them.
[Gary's plans to lure in the attention
of his fellow members even further.]
[That's none other than his
delivery package.]
[Gary's the one who sent the package himself!]
[And also...]
Brother.
- Brother.
- Hi Gary.
[He paid an early visit to Dynamic Duo.]
You have to buy me as much
time as you can.
- Keep talking to them?
- Drag it out?
Hey, Jung In.
Where are you?
Congratulations on getting married.
- Congratulations.
- Thanks, Gary.
I don't even know what to get you.
But we can talk about that some other time.
- What's this about?
- I need you and Jung Chi to help me out.
[Asking the newlyweds for their help.]
These are clues.
You have to hide these for me,
and make it really hard for them to find.
- Hide them all separately?
- Yes, that's right.
Hide them all separately.
[And lastly, Gary-Pink.]
The most important thing is,
you can't tell them that you saw me.
Of course not.
[Delivering the packages himself to
make sure nothing gets said.]
[All these were planned out by
Leessang themselves!]
You have to make sure not to get your plan
caught by any others for the next 12 hours.
If the two of you can stand on the platform
together at the final location, then you win.
[Leessang wins if they can stand together
on the platform at the final location.]
[The gate to this final stage will open
only when the set time has been reached.]
[Everything will burst into bubbles if Gary is
brought up onto the platform by others.]
[Leessang's kidnapping case-
Will they be able to succeed?]
What about you?
Did you do a good job?
There's not too much that I could do.
I just sent them a video to distract them.
[A video file that he purposely sent to
the members to thwart their suspicions away.]
- I called them on video.
- Right now...
We've got 45 minutes left to go.
We have 45 minutes to go back to that
building where we started this morning.
You and I really have to work on
timing our plan perfectly.
And we have to meet back
at that building.
If you can buy me some more time...
then I'll go hide myself inside the building
and meet you at the platform
when the time comes.
I don't think that any of them know that
you and I are in on this together.
No, I doubt they know.
I'm sure they're all only suspecting you.
- Then stall.
- Okay, I got it.
- I'll go and hide somewhere.
- Okay.
- I'll see you at nine o'clock.
[Agrees to meet at nine o'clock
in front of the platform.]
He had me tied up so tight
that it's way too easy to get myself out.
[Heading out to find a place
to hide until nine o'clock.]
I have to go hide somewhere.
It's an octagon.
[The final platform is inside the
octagonal cage on the first floor.]
[The door is still tightly locked up.]
How am I supposed to get in here?
I can't get in if Jong Kook is here.
I think I need to go into hiding first.
I wonder where I should hide.
I need to get rid of the car first.
I'll leave the car parked here.
[Leaving the car that he suspects to
be tracked parked in the garage.]
[Nervously walks out of the garage with
uncertainty of who may pop out at him.]
[The three teams that have
been on his tail...]
- Hello?
- Hey, Gil.
[The Blue Team calls him on his phone.]
- Tell us where you're at.
- Come find me for yourself.
Can't you even do that?
- Seriously...
- You little fatty!
- You done talking, Fatty?
- Fatty?
- That's right, Fatty!
- Yeah, Fatty!
I'm just a little stocky.
I'm not a fatty!
Seriously.
You're dead if we get our hands on you.
- Then come and get me if you can.
- You just wait for us.
Fine, come and get me.
Where does this mean he's going?
I'm not really sure I get this.
I feel like I'm going to lose it.
You startled me.
[Super anxious at this point.
Scared at even the slightest sound.]
This is just the beginning.
I have to keep my eyes open when I walk
because you never know who'll pop out.
Always have to be on the lookout
as to where I can escape to.
We're almost there.
We're at Jeonjayoek right now.
Okay, there he is.
We're practically at the same place.
[Gil is merely 300m away.]
We know that he's around here,
so we just need to go find him.
[The chasers are closing in.]
[Gil is now on the run!]
[Extreme state of nervousness.]
Wow, I'm getting really nervous.
Where do you think I can hide?
I'm being chased right now.
[Gary's asking the employees for their help.]
How am I supposed to fit
myself in there?
Which way?
[Heading towards the corner that was
recommended to him...]
I can definitely hide in there.
[A remote place behind the walls.]
I'm going to hide right here.
Right here in the corner.
[No one's going to be able
to find me here.]
Gil just crossed the street.
The intersection.
I think he's at the intersection.
- Where?
- At that intersection. Let's run.
Here, put this on.
[Gil is paused in his tracks right then
to put something on.]
To the right.
Who's that over there?
[Gil is discovered!]
Isn't that Gil?
- That's Gil, isn't it?
- That's him.
- Gil!
- Hey, Gil!
[Save me, my swift feet!]
[Escapes into some building.]
[Huh?]
[Who is this guy in the wig?]
Hello?
[Leessang's in danger!]
[They're right across the road
from each other!]
I'm hiding up on the seventh floor.
Which floor is the final location on?
- First floor.
- First? I'll come up to the seventh first.
Okay, I got it.
[All three teams are now surrounding
the two buildings.]
Gil is inside this building somewhere.
[Just across the street...
is the final location.]
[Time to run.]
[But all the chasers are watching him
from across the street.]
[Gil is discovered.]
- Gil!
- We can see you!
- Where's Gary?
- Let's meet up and talk.
[Back on the run.]
[Gary is witnessing all the chaos
out the window.]
we're going to make a run for it
as soon as the light turns green.
Once I'm in the building,
I'm going up to the seventh floor.
[Up to the seventh floor
where Gary is waiting.]
[Gary is keeping an eye on what's
going on outside on the street.]
[And discovers Suk Jin and
Blank Ji out the window,]
I should send a text to Gil.
[Immediately texts Gil.]
[Ji Hyo and Suk Jin are out by the gas station
so you'd better be careful.]
Gary just texted me to let me know that
Suk Jin and Ji Hyo are waiting for me.
[Right behind him...]
[Gil really is running
all over the place today.]
What the heck is this?
[Yoo Hyuk shows up like the wind
out of nowhere!]
[Calling Gary to let him know what's going on
in case he's caught by Jae Suk.]
[The two on a dead run.]
[Will he be caught... or will he get away?]
[He's caught!]
Gary.
[Gil is trying to let Gary know
that he's been caught.]
[And quickly hangs up the phone
to prevent themselves from getting caught.]
[Have they been caught?]
[Jae Suk hands Gil over to Suk Jin.]
Seriously... seriously.
Gil... why are you doing this?
[He's not going to have any other choice but
to lead them to right where Gary is.]
[What do I do now?]
I don't think that they know
you and I are in this together.
[The members are still unaware of the fact
that they're in on this together.]
I'm hiding up on the seventh floor right now.
[Gary said he was hiding
up on the seventh floor...]
- We have to go to basement level seven.
- What? What doesn't exist.
That's where he is right now.
[Trying to lure them into the basement
storage where Gary had been in all day.]
[As long as Gary's well hidden...
we still may have a chance to win.]
So this is the place.
- Tell us where Gary is.
- Hang on a minute.
[Arrives on the basement level
where Gary was being held captive.]
- Gary!
- See the chair?
Gary!
- What is this?
- This is where he must've been held captive.
- Where did he go?
- That's where he must've been held.
[The members only discover an empty chair!]
- What is this?
- He must've escaped.
- He freed himself and escaped.
- Where did he go?
- Gary must've escaped.
- Gary!
- He escaped.
Do you see any clues?
[Stay in hiding... and let's meet up in front
of the platform when it's time.]
Do you think that the members will
figure out that it's all been staged?
What's going on here?
[Members with their suspicions...
and Gil continues to put on his act.]
[The clock is ticking...
and only 19 minutes left on the clock.]
- There's not much time.
- Who kidnapped Gary?
- I kidnapped him.
- You kidnapped him?
[Let's wait just a little bit longer...]
[They're suspicious of us right now,
so stay well hidden.]
- Where is he?
- What else do you know, Gil?
I'm sure that you know something.
Tell us everything you know.
[The members are trying to
get Gil to spill the beans.]
I'm sorry to say this, but we're going to
have to strip you if you don't tell us.
You could be hiding something.
The way I see it...
there's something here.
He's trying to distract us right now.
[Suspicious of Gil,
who won't leave the seventh floor.]
I can't believe how tough it is
to find Gary.
[Searching every nook and cranny.]
[The clock is ticking down...]
[Oh?]
[Isn't that?]
[That's where Gary is hiding!]
Gary!
There you are.
[Gary is discovered by Yoo Hyuk!]
Okay, I'll come out.
I'll come out right now.
[Let's stay calm...]
[It seems as though the members are still
unaware that everything's been staged.]
I'm here with Suk Jin right now.
[They still don't know my part in this...]
[Gary follows Jae Suk out to avoid
their suspicion.]
- I was held captive for like 10 hours.
- Where have you been all this time?
[Leessang wins as long as they can stand on
the platform once the door opens.]
[Disguising Gary so that the other teams
don't recognize who it is.]
[Yellow Team keeps Gil under watch.]
This is a violation of my personal privacy.
- Come on, Kwang Soo. That's too much.
- Stop it, Kwang Soo.
- He's texting Gary.
- Gary?
[No way anyone would be texting personal
messages during the filming of a show.]
How would you know?
I could be texting my mom.
[Gil- I've been caught. Go wait by the cage.
Let's run in when it opens.]
I was held captive all day long.
Gil tied me up in that chair.
- Where did he keep you hostage?
- How did you escape?
I used every ounce of strength I had
to get myself freed from the ropes.
[And they actually believe
what he's saying...]
[Less than six minutes left on the clock!]
Come here.
Do you know how much you had me
walk around this whole neighborhood?
[Got a full on tour of the
neighborhood all thanks to Gil.]
We even went to the police station, you liar.
Seriously though... where's Gary?
- Where is Gary right now?
- We could be missing something.
It's possible Gary and Gil might win if they
were to go on that platform together.
[That's our Ace Blank Ji!]
[Leessang's plan...
will they be able to succeed?]
- Why is he even on this show?
- He's been fooling us all day today.
We had to go see Jung Chi, Jung In...
and you have no idea what else we did.
- Even Choi Ja.
- What?
[Sorry, I asked him to come on the show.]
[Oh, Mr. Gary...
Your acting skills have improved!]
You have no idea how hard we worked
to find you.
[Jae Suk... just be
a little bit more patient with me...]
[One minute before their fate is decided!]
You kidnapped Gary?
You kidnapped him?
Then Gary didn't stage this whole thing?
[We need to hold out
just a little bit longer...]
[Which team will put an end to
this Christmas nightmare?]
Let's go.
- Wait, don't hold onto me anymore.
- Okay.
[The countdown!]
[The team that steps up onto the platform
when the gate open is the winner!]
[The door is finally opening!]
[The door will stay open for
only 10 minutes!]
[Blue Team rushing towards the door
with Gary in the middle!]
[Will Gary go on the platform with someone else,
or will Leessang stand together?]
[While all the other teams are fighting
amongst themselves...]
What is going on here all of a sudden?
[This is it, Gary...]
[It's now or never, Gil...]
[Leessang makes a run for it!]
[Why is Gary trying to step up on
the platform with Gil?]
[Can't be...]
[News of Gary's kidnapping
that came out of nowhere...]
[But it wasn't a kidnapping case...]
What are you doing here?
[This was all a part of Gary and Gil's plan.]
[It was a perfectly staged kidnapping!]
[This was all an act
planned by these two!]
[If Gil and Gary makes their stand,
then they win the race!]
It was all Leessang!
They're going to win this!
[Others must drag Gil off the platform
to stand on there with Gary!]
[Just then!]
[Gary and Gil's feet!]
[They both have to be standing there together
to be declared the winners!]
[Did they succeed?]
[Leessang's plan is a success!]
- See? I told you.
- These two planned everything.
Come on, be happy for me.
[Gil has been crucial in fooling
all the members into falling for their plan.]
[All seven gold prizes!]
We're the ones that found Gary.
[Is it another Gary Christmas?]
- Gary always wins the Christmas special.
- We were playing defense today.
[Thank you to Gaeko, Choi Ja, Jung Chi,
Jung In and A-Pink for helping me out- Gary.]
[Have a very Gary Christmas!]
Subtitles by DramaFever
End of the year special
against the writers.
[An event that's never been seen before.]
[Cross the Han River all on their own!]
[The final hot battle in the year of 2013.]
[Who will be the ultimate winner?]
[Next week's End of the Year Special-
Running Man vs. The Writers.]