[Star of today's show - Traitors Club]
[The team of detectives chasing after them...]
- I know that you're guilty!
- Do you have any evidence?
- Hurry!
- Go find the evidence!
[Traitor's Club -
Operation: Apprehend]
[Gimpo Domestic Airport]
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Arriving at the airport early in the morning.]
[Haroro dressed in a
suspicious looking outfit.]
[Ha Dong Hoon-
Specializes in leg tripping actresses.]
What's going on?
What's going on here?
Am I the star of the show today?
Why am I the only one here?
[Huh?]
[Ji Suk Jin- Bodily gag stunt specialist,
and eternal weak physique.]
What? What is it?
Who's here?
Who is that?
Suk Jin?
[And one more...]
[Lee Kwang Soo- Betrayal specialist.
Also specializes in snide remarks, and biting.]
What's going on here?
All the traitors are here.
[What's going on with this picture?]
[Can't stand to look at one another.]
- What is this?
- What's going on here?
What's going on here?
What are you two doing here?
You have to share that with us!
I thought I was the only one they called.
[Their unstoppable greed to
star in the show.]
Whatever the case, I think the three of us
are the stars of the show today.
Let's all do a dance of joy.
[There it is.]
- Don't I look like Tom Cruise today?
- I feel like I'm in Mission Impossible.
- This is totally Mission Impossible.
- Totally!
[But what is written on the skeleton card
that was thrown at them?]
[We're the three criminals?]
[The three members of the Traitors Club-
Having endured the battering and humiliation.]
- Finally!
The three of you will be
given a chance!
[This is our chance!]
[Traitor's Club unite!]
Find the treasure chest at the final location
and claim it for yourselves!
You will thus become the stars
of today's show.
- Yes!
One of the 200 keys that are in the bag
will be the one that'll open up the chest.
- 200?
- Let's check it!
Hang on.
[The suspicious looking bag...]
[Automatically breaking out into
song out of their excitement.]
- We got it open.
- 200 keys?
[And here are the 200 keys.]
[Just one out of these 200 keys
will open up the treasure chest.]
Every time you succeed a mission,
you'll be given the number of a fake key
which will help whittle down the
possibility to the right key.
In the case that you don't
succeed your mission
the chase team will be given a sketch
of you which gives them
a chance to rip off your name tag,
so make sure to do your absolute best.
Take the plane and get to Gyungju.
- Gyungju?
- Gyungju!
[Take the plane and go to
the beach in Gyungju.]
Every time we succeed a mission
they're going to let us know which one is
fake so we can start eliminating the fakes.
Then does it mean there are
199 missions?
[Do you think this is
a four year long special episode?]
And how are these guys going to catch us?
[Unable to understand this?
Full of questions.]
- Every time we don't succeed...
- What about our sketches?
[Traitors lack the amount of perception
needed to be the stars of the show.]
- They need our sketches to arrest us.
- Ah...
We need to succeed our missions
to find the correct key.
Then are we ousted as soon as
they get a hold of our sketches?
- I doubt it.
- Probably not, right?
- I have a bad feeling about today.
- Let's get on the road first.
We have been waiting three years
for this day to arrive.
If we don't win today,
we have to wait another three years.
- First time in three years...
- Suk Jin will be fifty by then.
- Tra-it-ors
- Cross!
[Covertly making their moves.]
[Criminal Traitors Club-
Start your mission!]
[Find the real key amongst the 200, and
open up the treasure chest to claim it!]
[A moment later]
[Detective Team One-
Swift Yoo Jae Suk.]
[Detective Team Two-
Fiery Kim Jong Kook.]
- What are we doing? What's going on.
- Be quiet!
- That's a lighter.
- Really?
When are the rest of the members
going to arrive?
I'm going to teach them a lesson
when they get here.
Someone's coming.
- Are you on DT1? (Detective Team One)
- Detective Blank!
[DT1- Detective Blank a.k.a. Song Ji Hyo.]
- Detective Gae is on your team.
- Detective Gae!
[DT2 (Detective Team Two)-
Detective Gae a.k.a. Kang Gary.]
Do you know what time it is,
Detective Gae?
Detective Blank!
- Do you know what time it is, Detective Gae?
- What's going on here?
- Detective Gae!
- You're late, Detective Gae!
So detective Blank is on my team?
- We're Team One.
- We're detectives?
They're Team One,
and we're Team Two.
This is for people with slender wrists.
[Toy handcuffs are no match for
Kkuk's muscles of steel.]
This thing broke.
Why did it break?
- Someone else is coming.
- Look, there's someone else coming.
[And...]
[Lead investigators finally arriving?]
[Wait, those two are...]
[Smooth and charismatic...
the handsome actor, Kim Sang Kyung.]
[Infamous singer...]
[And now an infamous actress,
the multi-talented Uhm Jung Hwa.]
Mr. Kim Sang Kyung will be the
Lead Detective (LD) for DT1.
And Uhm Jung Hwa will be
the Lead Detective for DT2.
These two are our guests
for the day?
You have a message from the headquarters.
The three traitorous criminals have decided
that they want to be the stars of this episode
and have escaped with the
keys for the treasure chest.
Really?
If you succeed your missions at
the various locations
you will gain sketches of them which will
grant you the chance to eliminate them.
[Detectives will win a sketch to arrest the
criminals upon success of each mission.]
You can arrest the criminals by eliminating
the name tags only when you have the sketches.
You have to arrest the criminals before
they get the treasure in their hands.
Over.
[DT1 vs. DT2-
A race to capture the criminals!]
[Before the criminals acquire
the treasure chest...]
[Secure the proof of their sketches
and arrest them!]
[Board the plane immediately
and head over to the Gyungju Beach!]
[Ulsan Airport]
Kwang Soo's getting to do something
that he's never done in any of his dramas.
- You're looking cool today, Kwang Soo.
-Thank you!
[Off to Gyungju Beach!]
I can't help but hum
out of joy right now.
- Today really is...
- Why don't you sing us a song, Suk Jin?
- Sing us a song.
- Want me to drop you a beat?
- Okay, one...
- One, two, three, four!
[Get a nice beat going...]
We're at the top!
Oh, oh!
Kwang Soo, Ha Ha and Suk Jin!
- The top!
We are the main stars!
We can't get any higher than this!
Oh, oh!
Try and catch us!
You won't be able to catch us!
We are as strong as Iron Man!
Strong as Iron Man!
[A shocking ending to the song...]
We are as strong as Iron Man?
Where are we going?
It's really great weather today.
- I see the car.
- There it is.
Each team has their own car?
Let's see... where are we going?
[Find the informant disguised as a deliveryman
and get the composite of the criminals.]
But, you have to comply to the delivery
instructions to gain the package.
I bet we're going to get
ordered to do something.
An army of ladies who are guarding the
village will attack with water guns.
But be cautious of the army of ladies
guarding the village with their water guns.
Those ladies are really tough to deal with.
- Gyungju Beach?
- Let's go.
We have to get there faster
than the other team.
- We're battling against them, right?
- Of course! This is a battle.
Gyungju Beach...
I wonder where the beach is?
It really is great weather today.
I bet the two of you have been
all over this country by now.
There's not a place we
haven't been to.
I bet it's really nice if you happen to go
back to your hometown by chance, right?
- I'm from Seoul.
- Oh, Seoul?
Ji Hyo, did you know this about
Sang Kyung?
- Know what?
- He's quite the chatterbox.
- Really?
- Yeah, he really loves to talk.
Rather than calling it chattering,
I enjoy talking to other people.
Yes, that's right.
That's what most chatterboxes say.
- That's what I say about myself too.
- Really?
I really used to like you.
Then instead of searching far,
why not look at the one next to you?
That's right!
- How much older are you okay with?
- Me?
- Jong Kook...
- You're not bad at all in person.
[She finds his profile attractive?]
Don't you think someone younger
than me would be better?
It's okay, I think you'd be perfect.
Congratulations.
[Detective Kkuk, the love line specialist...]
It's okay, Monday is a day for love.
Suk Jin, we're here.
- We're here?
- We're here.
We've finally arrived.
Okay, let's all get out.
- Let's go!
- Yes, let's go.
Let's go enjoy this beautiful ocean.
[Gyungju Beach and the Mural Village.]
- Let's go, Suk Jin.
- Shall we?
It's the ocean!
Look at the beautiful sandy beach!
[The vast and open view of the ocean.]
[The beautiful and mystical
Yangnam-myun lagoon of the region.]
We are the stars of the show today.
Yes, please give us lots of support!
[It may seem strange,
but we are the stars of the show today!]
[The criminals with a few screws loose
are enjoying this uplifting atmosphere.]
[Their dancing not matching up
to the beat whatsoever.]
- Are you okay?
- My foot got caught on something.
[Happy about their rare opportunity
to shine on their own.]
- What is it? Is it the skull card?
- Wait!
Where did it come from?
[A skull command card!]
[Find the informant disguised as a
deliveryman and gain the fake key number.]
But make sure to meet the delivery time,
in order to accept the package.
We have gained information that an
army of ladies guarding the village will
shoot any suspicious characters on sight
with their water guns, so stay cautious.
How are we to approach the deliveryman?
Are there instructions on there?
Yes.
Grab the deliveryman's hand...
- Without laughing.
- We can't laugh?
Look him in the eyes without laughing.
- And say, 'Ding-dong'.
- That must be the secret code.
[Avoid the band of detectives and
get the number of the fake key!]
Can we do something with these keys?
I hate lugging this thing around.
- No, don't think like that.
- We can take turns carrying it.
- Let's get this done, okay?
- Okay, Suk Jin.
[Brimming with determination.]
[DT1 and DT2 vs The Traitors Club.]
The ladies may come out and
shoot us with their water guns.
[The Traitors Club infiltrating
the Mural Village.]
[Carefully walking into
the center of the village.]
What the heck?
[The army of ladies protecting their village
with their arsenal of water guns!]
Ladies!
Why are you ladies doing this?
- We're here.
- So this is the place?
So where in the world are these
three criminals hiding?
[Where is the Traitors Club?]
Huh?
[Could one of the criminals be
in the front yard of this house?]
[Shoots on sight without any hesitation!]
Hello.
Ma'am... Ma'am!
[Attacking without discrimination.]
What do we do?
[Mural Village falling into chaos.]
My butt!
Those ladies scare me the most.
- So we have to start searching now?
- Yes, we have to find the deliveryman.
Isn't that the deliveryman?
- It does look like he has a package.
- It is a deliveryman!
Mister!
- Mister! Deliveryman!
- Don't call him out. See? He's running away.
Why did you call him out?
Why is he running away?
- Jong Kook!
- It's the ladies!
Run!
Jung Hwa!
[Water gun loaded ladies attack!]
Jung Hwa, where are you?
[LD Uhm persistently
chasing after the deliveryman.]
Hey!
Wait!
This is no joke!
Oh my God!
There he is!
Jung Hwa!
Why are you running off by yourself?
Why are you fighting
with the ladies, Jung Hwa?
Come here, Gary!
Over here!
[Totally caught!]
[LD Uhm's relentless pursuit!]
[Got him!]
[Receiver: Running Man.
Delivery request: 30 sit-ups.]
Right here?
By myself?
[LD Uhm - Begin your 30 sit-ups!]
Jung Hwa's over there doing sit-ups.
Jung Hwa!
Stay strong, Jung Hwa!
Fighting!
Guys!
This is too hard!
- How many have I done?
- 28.
[Delivery request complete!]
Guys!
I think I need to go home now.
- What?
- I think I need to go home.
Where do you think you're going?
We're just beginning!
[What could be inside the delivery box?]
- What is that?
- Poop?
Poop?
How can the word 'poop'
come from such beautiful lips?
- What is it then? It's nothing?
- I don't think it's anything.
Seriously!
- Guys... guys!
- I'll go catch another one, Jung Hwa.
You guys are a disappointment.
You're dead!
[Village guardians keeping a tight watch.]
I can't even run away anywhere.
They have the place surrounded.
Those ladies are coming out attacking
with smiles on their faces!
That makes them even scarier!
Our enemies are everywhere.
Ding-dong!
Play 'Rock-paper-scissors' with a kid
in the village and win three times in a row.
Ma'am! Does she know how to play,
rock-paper-scissors?
[Play Rock-paper-scissors with
the adorable little girl.]
Hi, it's Uncle Ha Ha.
Hi! How about a belly bow?
I love you!
You're so cute!
Say, 'I love you' towards the camera.
[A future daddy-to-be
who adores little children.]
Let's play, Rock-paper-scissors, okay?
Rock-paper-scissors!
[Paper - Rock]
You're really good at Rock-paper-scissors,
aren't you?
I love you!
Belly bow!
Kiss!
Okay, one more time.
You only throw out 'paper', right?
Okay, I got it.
Rock-paper-scissors.
Okay, I won one round.
She'll only throw out a paper.
Rock-paper-scissors!
[Hmm...]
What's your name?
Lee Ga In?
I love you, Ga In.
A belly bow!
Let's play another round.
You know how to throw out a rock too?
Then what am I to do?
Rock-paper-scissors.
[Paper - Rock]
I love you, Ga In!
You're so good at playing
Rock-paper-scissors, Ga In.
Yes, Ga In.
You're just adorable.
Belly bow!
[So well-mannered!]
Let's play one more time and if I lose,
I'll go somewhere else, okay?
Okay, what are you going to
throw out this time?
You're going to throw out a scissors,
and I'll throw out a rock, okay?
You're a good girl, Ga In.
Rock-paper-scissors.
[Paper- Rock]
I love you!
Belly bow.
I can't beat Ga In.
Ga In, you did great.
You're so adorable.
[Skilled Rock-paper-scissors player,
Ga In wins!]
You bark, and I split.
Is that it?
Right now, I...
[Delivery request-
Do a splits and touch the box with your butt.]
Okay, you touched it.
[The agony of the muscle stretching out.]
Thank you.
[Inside the delivery box that he
worked so hard to acquire is...]
Right is this it?
What is this that you're doing?
Are you saying that I pooped this out?
You're saying I pooped this out?
Is this a trick?
Hello, Sang Kyung!
- Here he is!
- Wait!
[The criminal and the detective team
finally coming face to face.]
[A criminal?]
What is this?
[Immediately getting flustered after
finding out about the detectives.]
There are guests on the show today?
- Suk Jin.
- Yeah?
- I just ran into Kim Sang Kyung.
- Really?
- I just ran into him.
- Really? He must be our guest then.
- Did you greet him?
- I greeted him, and then ran away.
You ran away? Why did you run away?
We haven't done anything wrong.
[Without the evidence of the sketches,
they can't be investigated.]
[Detective Blank also
discovers the criminals.]
What?
What are you doing!
- Go away! I said, get away from me!
- Run away, Suk Jin!
You have to do the mission first!
Are you able to do this?
- Hey! You have to help me!
- Jae Suk!
- Hey!
Take this with you, Kwang Soo!
- Hey! Lee Kwang Soo!
- Jong Kook!
- Lee Kwang Soo!
- Ding-dong!
[All the detectives moving in
like a swarm of bees.]
Hello, Gary.
What?
Wait, what are you doing?
- Aren't I supposed to catch him?
- Hang on a second!
- Kwang Soo!
- Hello, Jung Hwa.
[Criminal Giraffe caught in a mousetrap.]
- Hang on a second!
- Come here, Kwang Soo!
- Why are you saying 'Ding-dong' to me?
- Ding-dong!
- You're not supposed to say that to me.
- Why are you saying 'ding-dong' to me?
- Long time no see, Jung Hwa!
- What's going on? You're a criminal too?
- Hang on a minute.
What's in this bag?
Wait, do you have any proof?
[Since they don't have any composite,
he can't even arrest him right now...]
This is my dog house.
Do you guys even have any
evidence or what?
- Seriously.
- You can't do it like this.
In this world where everyone
is innocent until proven guilty
you can't just assume that we're guilty.
[Overly cocky from knowing the
detectives have no proof.]
We don't need to be treated like this.
Don't even talk to them.
Let's just pretend they're
not even here.
- What?
- They're acting suspicious.
[The criminals not even able to
speak without fumbling their words.]
- Why can't you talk clearly?
- Treating us like this is...
Why are you treating like this
without any cause?
[Scaring another criminal member, Haroro who
is in the midst of completing his mission.]
You're the criminal, aren't you?
What are you saying?
I'm not a criminal!
- You're a criminal, aren't you?
- I'm not a criminal!
- Yes, you are.
- No, I'm not!
[Denying adamantly.]
I'm not the same person that
I used to be!
I'm a detective.
I'm the lead detective, Detective Yoo.
Then bring some proof!
Then bring evidence or something.
You have nothing!
- Wait...
- What do you think you're doing right now?
- Do I need to get a warrant for you?
- I'm not that kind of a person.
Do you need for me to go get a warrant
so you'll get your head on straight?
Do you want to eat some beans and rice?
(Beans and rice= Staple menu in jail).
- I've always liked beans and rice.
- Do you want beans and rice?
I've always been a good beans and rice
eater and my mom loved me for that.
- Don't you know what beans and rice means?
- No, I don't!
There are only two grains of rice
for every 100 beans!
- That's what beans and rice means.
- Ah...
[That kind of beans and rice...
I guess he'll get plenty of protein.]
- Two grains of rice for every 100 beans.
- Listen here, Mr. Detective.
I'm a little busy right now,
so I need to get back to my business.
Just know that I'm going to work to
make sure you get your beans and rice.
- Do you even have any evidence?
- Know that you'll be eating beans and rice.
- Bring me your evidence then!
- Get ready for your beans and rice.
Mr. Detective!
Get back to what you were doing then.
[Where are the composites
of the criminals?]
I have no idea what's
going on here today.
- Excuse me, Detective Kim?
- What is it?
- I've washed my hands of everything.
- What did you say?
I'm not that type of a person.
I'm not that type of a person anymore.
- What are you doing back here?
- Where is it?
What are you doing?
Let go of me!
Do you even know who I am?
Where is it?
[Rough detective-criminal role playing.]
- That hurts! That really hurts!
- Where is it?
- Where is it!
- Wait! Hang on!
Let go of me!
What do you think you're doing?
Bring me your proof!
- Or bring your warrant or something!
- Just wait until I get the evidence.
[Totally immersed in his role.]
Wait until I get my hands on you.
- I won't let you get away with it.
- What are you doing?
[The one he really wants to go after is
Kkuk from Detective Team Two?]
I will get you!
I will make sure to get you.
- But I will let you go for right now.
- I've got you all now.
[Playing the role of an enraged detective
is all the rage right now.]
- We have to work together.
- Seriously.
- Team Leader, let's work together.
- Of course.
We have to work together.
The way I see this...
The real deliveryman would be
someone with a really good physique.
What I did to you before is making your
neck muscles look bigger.
Someone who's in really good shape,
and who'd be a fast runner.
- It's going to be a younger person.
- The next time you come back...
Unless you bring back some
solid evidence... wait!
I'm going to get the evidence.
Do you understand?
And until then... wait...
wait!
- And until then... wait... wait!
- You're the evidence!
What are you doing!
[Realistically battling-
Detective Team One vs. Detective Team Two.]
[Detective Blank closing in on
another deliveryman.]
Why are you...
Ding-dong!
[Shout out the name of the person you love
3 times and write it with your butt 3 times.]
Mom...
Park Gui Ja!
[Working earnestly to write out
each letter neatly and perfectly.]
- That was my second.
- Great job.
Good job.
There's nothing that Ji Hyo can't do.
At a quick glance,
it looks like you're writing my name.
How long have you been watching?
- I've been watching you from the beginning.
- I just need to do it once more, right?
[Once more to complete the mission.]
[Whose name is that?]
Gui.
Ja!
I love you!
Thanks!
I heard you.
Why did you make me do that?
That was so embarrassing.
That really was poopy.
[It's not poop....]
This is awesome.
Ji Suk Jin.
I got my first composite.
Park Gui Ja... I love you.
- Jae Suk! Hurry, Jae Suk!
- What is it?
Hurry!
Hi!
- What is it, Ji Hyo?
- Jae Suk!
- It's Suk Jin.
- Is it his composite?
Hurry, Jae Suk!
Hurry!
[Capture criminal Ji Suk Jin!]
Twelve, thirteen...
Could they be...
It's him.
[Persistent Detective Uhm on the chase.]
Hey!
I'll take you out to dinner.
Wow, I got myself a handsome boy.
Ding-dong.
[Do 20 jumping jacks.]
Why do they keep doing this to me?
I don't have to count the last rep?
I must be on the show today
for my diet, right?
[Starting her 20 reps of jumping jacks.]
Three... four... five...
[A full workout in the middle of the day.]
Eight.
Sixteen.
Seventeen.
Eighteen, nineteen.
[Success]
There's something in there.
Yes!
[Criminal Ji Suk Jin's composite!]
- Catch Ji Suk Jin!
- Why?
- Ji Suk Jin!
- Did you find something?
- Hurry up and catch him. Hurry!
- Let's go get him.
- Lets go catch him.
- You're the best!
Hide it for right now.
Hide it.
- Why do we have to hide it?
- We should just hide it for now.
Don't make it seem obvious, Jung Hwa.
- Did you find the poop?
- Why do you keep coming around me?
I just want to know if you found it.
- Huh?
- You look like you found something.
- I haven't found anything.
- What?
- I know you found something, didn't you?
- No, I haven't.
I'm serious, I didn't find anything.
I hurt my leg.
Hurry, Jung Hwa.
Hurry!
[Detective Uhm with
Suk Jin's composite also arrives.]
We have to get Suk Jin.
- Jung Hwa's got it.
- I'm sorry Jung Hwa, but I hurt my leg.
[Total danger.]
[Success?]
Hang on, I need to put a lift in there.
[A skull card inside the box!]
Keys 151-200 are fakes.
Throw them out without others finding out.
If you want more information,
Go Dong Wan has more information for you.
Dong Hoon.
- I found it.
- You found it?
[The criminal team fulfills their mission.]
Get rid of all the keys numbered 151-200.
Let's go find Suk Jin and tell him.
- Where's Suk Jin?
- And we have to find Go Dong Wan.
Dong Hoon...
- I think Suk Jin's fallen behind.
- Where did he go?
I heard other guys screaming out that
Suk Jin is the criminal.
- What are you talking about?
- I think they found Suk Jin's composite.
Really?
- They found a composite?
- I heard they found one.
Then we have to hurry.
If they found a composite, then are
we all in danger of being eliminated?
- Jung Hwa...
- That hurts. That hurts my wrist.
- You hurt your leg?
- Yeah, I really did hurt my leg.
I think I twisted something earlier.
See?
- See?
- Hey!
How can he run that well
if his leg is hurt?
Suk Jin!
[Desperate Traitors Club.]
Where did Suk Jin go?
[Big-nose using the excuse of his old age to
barely escape from a dangerous situation.]
When did they find my composite?
Seriously... that could've
been big trouble.
It would've been big trouble
if I had been caught.
As soon as the guys get here,
I'm going to get us out of here.
[You just wait...]
- Have you seen Ji Suk Jin?
- No, we haven't seen him.
- There's Suk Jin.
- Lets go get him.
[Ji Suk Jin caught in a mousetrap.]
There he is!
There's Suk Jin.
Run!
Hey, hurry!
Come on!
Hurry up!
[Detective Uhm discovers Suk Jin!]
- I'm not falling for that. Open the door!
- No way!
- Hurry up and open it!
- Just go, Suk Jin. Just go!
You can't!
[There's no way you're getting
out of here.]
No!
You can't go.
- Let's get Jung Hwa out of here.
- No!
Hurry up and get in the car!
[Suk Jin escaping out of there by himself?]
- Hurry up and get out of here!
- Get out of here! You can't get caught!
- Escape out of here!
- Hurry!
Hey!
Seriously, you guys!
- Suk Jin!
- You have to get in quickly.
Hurry!
Hurry up and get in! Hurry!
Hurry up!
- Hurry!
- No!
Hey!
They still left even though I fell?
I'm so mad!
How can they do that?
I pretended to fall...
but they still left? How can they do that?
They seriously...
leave a bad taste in my mouth.
[Fails to arrest the Traitors Club.]
We can catch them later, Jung Hwa.
I saw which way they went.
Does it hurt? Let me see.
- It really hurts!
- He was too rough.
- Catch him for me.
- I will. I'll catch him for you.
- I promise I'll get him.
- My wrist suddenly doesn't hurt anymore.
[Attractiveness of Detective Uhm's
positive attitude.]
- Wow! She is so persistent!
- Wow!
- Wow, she is so frightening!
Wow, she was like a zombie!
Wow, she really was scary.
Did you find the key?
- Yes, Suk Jin. But it's not a key.
- Which one is the fake one?
- What is it? Read it out loud.
- Throw out the keys numbered 151-200.
- 151 through 200?
- Yes, 151-200 are all fakes.
We have to throw them out right now.
[Only one of the key is real.
Now 150 keys left in the bag.]
- If they catch you, you're eliminated now.
- If they catch me, I'm out.
- You guys have to protect me.
- Okay, okay.
- We're here. This is the place.
- We're here.
You really have to be careful, Suk Jin.
[Could Captain Go Dong Wan be
on that boat?]
- Hurry, Suk Jin!
- Hey! You two are supposed to protect me!
[The Traitors Club must rush to get
on the boat before the detectives arrive.]
Wow... I never knew how scary it was
to get chased around like this.
We found it!
[Taking a sigh of relief
now that they're on the boat.]
Traitors Club!
[Exhilarated by the fact
that they're still alive.]
- We won!
- We beat the detectives!
We're the stars of the show today!
- I feel like we're in a blockbuster movie.
- This is on a bigger scale.
- This is the scale that we deserve.
- There's always a boat scene in those movies.
- What is it?
- I think that's Captain Go Dong Wan.
- It's Captain Go Dong Wan!
- Where?
- It's Captain go Dong Wan!
- It's Captain Go Dong Wan!
Captain Go Dong Wan!
[Target discovered]
Captain Go!
- Oh my!
- Hello, Captain Go!
- Captain Go!
- We've finally found you!
- How long has it been?
- It really has been a while.
- What are you guys doing here?
- We've come to get you!
- You're our hostage now!
- Hand that over!
What are you doing?
That's mine!
[A skull instruction card inside the case!]
Gather up your knowledge,
to put together a quiz.
[If the detective team can't correctly answer
more than three questions of your quiz...
you will be given
the number for the fake keys.]
[But if you fail to succeed...
you have to hand over your hostage with
the known composite to the detectives.]
[Fail to succeed, and the hostage must be
handed over to the detectives.]
Hurry up and start the boat.
Just hurry up and start the boat.
- Get us over to that island right now!
- Start the boat!
[Totally immersed in
their kidnapping role play.]
- Hurry, hurry, hurry!
- Hurry up and do it!
- Hurry!
- If not, my rage virus will be triggered!
[Traitors Club with strains
of the rage virus.]
- Start the boat!
- Start it!
Over there.
Get over to that harbor over there.
But what does this message
mean exactly?
The criminals have stolen a boat and
are heading towards Eupcheon Harbor.
[The criminals have taken over a boat,
and are heading towards Eupcheon Harbor.]
- Boat?
- They took a dog?
- Not 'gae' (dog), but 'bae' (boat).
- Oh, I thought you said, dog.
Detective Team Two thinks
they took a dog right now.
- Not a dog, but a boat.
- Oh, I see.
- They took what?
- They took a boat.
- What? A dog?
- No, a boat.
[I guess Detective Team Two
needs new walkie-talkies.]
How are we going to
come up with three questions?
[Arrives at Eupcheon Harbor
past the Mural Village.]
- Hey! Over there!
- Hey! Lee Kwang Soo!
- Come and get us if you can!
- We've got a hostage!
So what?
Hurry up and come over here!
Our hostage...
knows where a composite is hidden!
[Huh?]
[Top grade information... Is that so?]
Where is the composite?
Why would you tell them that?
- Seriously... how could you tell them that?
- Where is the composite? Tell us.
He told them that we know
where the composite is.
You have been surrounded.
- Don't make us laugh!
- You have been surrounded!
You're dead once I get
my hands on you.
You better run far away!
- There are a lot of angry people here.
- Kim Sang Kyung...
Kim Sang Kyung, step forward.
Hey, Kim Sang Kyung!
- Have you even been feeding yourself?
- Of course, I have been feeding myself.
- Don't get sucked into their ploy.
- I'm not getting sucked into your ploy!
I should've said I haven't eaten anything.
I should've said that I was starving.
- Look, you guys have to answer our questions.
- Questions?
- What questions?
- Why?
We will hand over our hostage
over to the winning team.
This is a quiz game.
Ask for a jjajangmyun.
I want some jjajangmyun.
We'll give you your question
if you bring us a jjajangmyun!
[Jjajangmyun?]
First, bring us a jjajangmyun.
Have it delivered to us.
- How are we supposed to deliver it to them?
- I want fried rice.
Here is a phone number right here.
[Just then, they discover a phone number to
a Chinese restaurant on the seawall.]
[Moments later.]
Who ordered the jjajangmyun?
Who ordered the jjajangmyun!
- Hey, jjajangmyun is coming.
- Over here! Jjajangmyun is over here!
- Over here!
- Here!
[Hardcore delivery mentality.]
Wow, I can't believe he delivered.
Thank you for your hard work, Sir.
How is it even possible he delivered
all the way over there on a boat?
- Thank you so much.
- He delivered that on a boat?
- He's not coming here?
- There will be a separate delivery.
- Were you about to get angry?
- Yeah.
- Thank you for the food!
- The world sure has improved.
The criminals dare to start eating
while the detectives are watching?
- Oh my! What delicious looking jjajangmyun!
- Thank you for the food!
- Thank you!
- Thanks, detectives!
Enjoy your jjajangmyun.
You'll be eating beans and rice from now on.
- I want to eat too.
- That's what you're always saying.
Where do you live?
- You did it, didn't you?
- You did!
- Want to confess, or get a beating first?
- Confess or a beating first?
Wow, I'm getting so annoyed.
Hey, Lee Kwang Soo!
What, you rascal?
[What?]
What did you say?
Hey!
What? 'You rascal'?
You dare call me a 'rascal'?
What mommy?
(Two words sounds extremely similar.)
Our jjajangmyun is coming!
- We ordered the jjajangmyun!
- We ordered it!
I can't believe they deliver the food
all the way over here.
This is going to be so delicious and to get
the chance to eat it under the lighthouse.
- Wow, that looks so good.
- Let's eat!
- Can we start eating?
- Let's eat first.
- It even has the pepper flakes on it.
- Wow, there's pepper flakes!
Wow, this is amazing!
[The delight of being able to sit down and
enjoy a bowl of jjajangmyun while working.]
- I love jjajangmyun and jjamppong together.
- This is so delicious!
- Here is your first question.
- This isn't the time for you to be eating!
[What did you say?]
- Get up and pay attention!
- What did you say?
Did you enjoy your lunch, detectives?
Person who knows the answer will run over
to the mic and answer the question.
You've got 30 seconds.
Hurry up and give us the question.
- This is a nonsense question.
- What?
What are the two legendary dragons
that live in the arcade room?
- I know this one!
- Answer!
- What's your answer?
- Two dragons!
Wrong!
- It's not the two dragons?
- They don't know that answer?
- You don't know the answer to this?
- This was a good question to pick.
- The time is ticking!
- You've only got 20 seconds left!
Answer!
- Uhm Jung Hwa?
- 'Adult dragon' (Translates to adult fantasy)
What are you doing?
[Detective Uhm's incorrect answer
drawing a shocked reaction.]
How could you say that
as your answer?
- What are you saying, Jung Hwa?
- It's obviously not what the kids play.
- How many letters in the answer?
- It's four letters.
You're running out of time.
Legendary dragons?
- Five, four, three, two...
- Wait!
Answer!
- He might get it.
- Let's see what he says.
Ppi-yong ppi-yong!
(Yong=dragon. Play on words.)
Correct!
[Correct]
[Detective Team Two gets the correct answer!]
That was the correct answer!
It's Ppi-yong ppi-young,
not ddi-yong ddi-yong.
- Our team is the best!
- This is a very hard question.
'You must never spit in front of the King'.
How would you say that in a character idiom?
- You can't spit in front of the king!
- Is that another nonsense question?
It's a nonsense question!
- Nonsense.
- You can't spit in front of the king?
- Your time starts now.
- Kim Sang Kyung?
Yong Jae Ho Tu!
- That's absolutely ridiculous!
- Yong Jae Ho Tu? ('Tu' as in spitting.)
- Yong Jae Ho Tu?
- No!
[Seriously thinking.]
- You can't spit in front of the king?
- Answer!
- Uhm Jung Hwa.
- Im Jeon My Twe.
Im Jeon My Twe.
You got it right!
[Correct answer]
[How can this be?]
- That's crazy! How does she know that?
- How does she even know that?
[Detective Team Two answers
the second questions in a row.]
- What the heck.
- I'm good at things like this.
You've got some skills, LD!
This won't do.
What's the current score?
The adult fantasy lady got
the correct answer.
This time... it's an English question.
English question!
What do you say to the king as
you bid the king farewell?
When you say farewell to a king?
- I doubt you'll get this one.
- Answer!
- Answer?
- Bye King!
Bye King.
[Detective Team Two gets
three questions right in a row.]
What did you think?
Did you think that we wouldn't know?
- What the heck?
- Bye King!
Bye King!
What kind of a car does Girls Generation
ride around in?
Jessi-ca! Jessi-car!
Which member of Girls Generation has
the highest sales figure of her clothing line?
- Selling her clothes?
- Tiffany!
Which member of Girls Generation would
sit still even if a fire breaks out?
Taeyeon!
[We're ruined...]
- You call these questions?
- How do they know this?
- They know all the answers!
- They're so simple-minded.
- I can't believe they call those questions.
[Too embarrassing to even deal with?]
- You can't beat us.
- You guys win.
I can't believe the simplicity
of your questions.
And look behind you.
There are only six people left out of that
huge crowd from earlier.
Do you see them?
They couldn't believe the simplicity of your
questions and everyone but six people left.
[Ro-Ro tries his luck with the audience?]
- How do you say farewell to a king?
- Bye King.
[Unbelievable]
You guys are so stupid!
- Hand over the hostage.
- Give us the hostage.
- Hand him over.
- Pick him up at the harbor.
[Detective Team Two to pick up
the hostage at the harbor.]
- It's over.
- It's all over.
They're here.
[Detective Team Two arrives
for the hostage exchange.]
Lock the doors.
- You guys know your time is ticking, right?
- What?
- What life of a fly?
- Listen to him.
[Big-nose mispronouncing his words.]
How are you going to catch me?
- Bye!
- You're ousted once you're caught.
Then catch me if you can.
- We're off!
- See you later!
Catch us if you can!
[Heading off to where the composite is
hidden with Captain Go Dong Wan in tow.]
Okay.
There it is!
[Ha Ha's composite.]
[Detective Team Two now possesses
both Ha Ha and Suk Jin's composites.]
- Suk Jin! There's a case over here.
- What?
What is it?
Open it.
Of course, they wouldn't send us
off empty-handed.
- What is it?
- It's a mission.
[Get over to Bongil Beach and
succeed your mission there!]
[Discouraged Traitors Club]
- No, don't say weak things like that.
- Why have you become so weak?
Huh?
Stop with all your useless talk.
I want you to stop that.
Why are you weakening so much?
[With the failure of their mission,
they still have 150 keys left.]
- And only one of them is the right key?
- One out of 150... ugh!
but you're good at things like that.
You found the raw egg out of 20 right away.
[No kidding.
Is the God of variety coming today?]
You and Dong Hoon can get ousted
the moment they rip off your name tag.
[With their composites in the detectives hands,
they can be ousted the moment they're caught.]
Why are they so good with
the nonsense questions?
[Criminals' current location-
Bongil Beach in the district of Gyungju.]
- What is that?
- Are we playing a game?
- What is it?
- What are we doing?
[Countless number of
inner tubes on the beach?]
- Suk Jin, be careful.
- Let's stay cautious and hurry.
Hey!
It's another skull card.
Find the number to the fake key
buried somewhere on the sandy beach.
Tip: Detectives will dance unconditionally
whenever music plays, so use the time wisely.
[Numbers to ten fake keys
are hidden here somewhere.]
- How am I going to find all that alone?
- But you're still safe.
[Kwang Soo's still free to roam around
since his composite hasn't been found.]
Run out whenever they
start dancing, okay?
What is this?
[Just then, Detective Team One arrives.]
- Hurry up and get in. Hurry!
- Lock the doors.
[With the freedom to roam around,
Kwang Soo must hurry to find the numbers.]
Kwang Soo, fighting!
- Get out! Get out of the car!
- I'm not getting out!
Why are you always so angry?
We're trying to catch the criminals here.
We should make them feel nervous.
[The first team to gather ten inner tubes over
to the team's home area wins the composite.]
[But whenever the music plays, you
must cease all movement and start dancing.]
- First team to get ten inner tubes?
- You have to get it over to your home base.
[Stack ten inner tubes
in your home area first!]
- Where's our home area?
- Get ten tubes!
Ten tubes!
We have to get ten tubes!
- What are you doing?
- Ji Hyo!
[Tube stuck in the sand,
and deflated tube.]
I'm sure we have one of those too.
[You're going to inflate it yourself?]
Look for it on the ground, Kwang Soo!
Kwang Soo, find the keys!
[Kwang Soo is the only hope
the Traitors Club has!]
Where are they?
I never knew that
Kwang Soo would be our hope.
No kidding.
- Ji Hyo!
- Hurry up and stack it up there.
- Here, Jae Suk.
- I have to go get that.
[Kwang Soo starting to feel
extremely anxious.]
- Don't we have an air pump?
- There it is!
[It's a box!]
[Discovers the first of the ten boxes.]
[What's the number to the fake key?]
Found it!
- He found something.
- He got something.
- Kwang Soo!
- You found it!
- Kwang Soo, fighting!
- What happened?
- He found what?
- What is it?
- What did he find?
[Just then... the music starts.]
[Rule: The detectives must cease all movement
and start dancing when the music starts.]
[This song is one of LD Uhm's hit song,
'Festival' from 1999.]
[Time for the criminals to start moving.]
[A dance party on the sand.]
[Even with the criminals right in front of
them, the detectives can't pursue them!]
- We can't go after them.
- They can't catch you right now.
[Ha Ha and Big-nose using this time
to start searching for the boxes.]
[There are nine boxes left. Must
find more boxes before the song ends.]
- Five seconds before the song ends!
- Get back to the car!
You've only got five seconds!
[Ha Ha and Big-nose must rush
to get back to the safety of the car!]
[Blanking out after the dance party.]
What's going on here?
Hey!
I don't know what's going on.
[Ha Ha and Big-nose make it
back to safety.]
[Hearts beating one hundred miles
per minute.]
We made it.
Wow, those five seconds.
Wow!
- Good job, Ji Hyo.
- We haven't gotten a single one?
Yellow one.
There's a yellow one out there.
- The yellow one.
- What do I do about my shoes?
[LD Uhm running into the ocean
without a moment's hesitation.]
[Can't let her beat me!
LD Kim also going into the water.]
[Kwang Soo just keeps on
searching for his boxes.]
This is a very lonely battle!
That really hurts!
- The water is freezing!
- My feet hurts!
[Is that music?]
[This song is?]
[Everyone automatically breaks out
into a familiar dance.]
They're starting to dance!
[Ro-Ro stealing the detectives tubes
in order to buy more time to find the boxes.]
[Immediately jumps into the dance.]
[Another one of Uhm Jung Hwa's hits,
'Betrayal of the Rose'-1997.]
[She's back!
The original dancing queen!]
Go, Jung Hwa!
[Perfect reenactment of her
stage performance 16 years ago!]
[Yoo Hyuk's dance moves automatically
flowing out of him.]
[Sandy beach really starting to heat up.]
Uhm Jung Hwa!
[Mister... aren't you going to search
for the boxes?]
[Music- Over!]
[On the run again!]
Is this even living?
This is no way to live a life.
[Pitiable life of a criminal.]
[Current tube score-
DT1: 5 vs. DT2: 1.]
[Hardworking LD Kim trying to gather
more from his enemy camp.]
What are you doing?
[Give it back!]
What are you doing, Jung Hwa?
You and I are nothing to
each other anymore.
No more movies or anything else
for us anymore.
I'm really sorry that I can't
be of any help.
I'm busy trying to inflate this thing.
- I think that's good enough.
- Come on, Jung Hwa.
Seriously, what are you doing?
- What are you doing?
- Bring it back!
[Cutthroat battle between the two
detective teams for the composite.]
This is just too much.
[What? A tube on top of the camera?]
[The camera backing up...]
What are you doing?
[Catch me if you can!]
[LD Uhm moves in on him!]
Can you help us out, Director?
Excuse me!
Over here!
What are you doing?
Give it to me!
What are you doing, Jung Hwa?
What do you mean, give it to me?
- Give it to me.
- What are you saying?
What do you mean, give it to me?
What are you doing right now?
- Back up, Jae Suk.
- Okay, Jung Hwa.
Give it to me.
[Uhm Jung Hwa gets the tube!]
[If he keeps this up,
he's going to dig up a well.]
This really hurts my feet.
Everyone, these Running Members...
they really do work hard.
I didn't know it would be like this.
Wow... seriously!
[Final song, 'Poison'.]
This is our last chance!
How many boxes do we have left?
[You do have pants on, don't you?]
[LD Uhm concentrating on her
dance moves rather than the mission.]
Are you sure you don't go clubbing?
[I dance at home...]
You're in the rhythm, Jung Hwa!
Are you sure you don't go clubbing?
[Everyone, dance together!]
[All three dancing nicely together.]
[Jung Hwa's couple dance with Gary!]
What are you doing?
Jung Hwa!
Do it to me too!
[Yoo Hyuk asking Jung Hwa
to do a sexy wave on him too.]
Here!
I'll do it!
[Music ends!]
It's over!
[DT1 with nine tubes!]
[Just one more,
and DT1 gets the composite!]
[Kwang Soo blocks it!]
[Traitors Club needs to buy more time
to find the boxes.]
[But Detective Yoo uses the moment
to find himself another tube!]
[But Detective Gae blocks it this time!]
We can't lose this one, Jung Hwa!
I'm not very ticklish.
Don't even try.
Detective Team One currently
has nine tubes!
- Last one!
- You're not going to get it!
[Will they win?]
[The victory is right in front
of their eyes!]
Steal it from them, Gary!
[Uses that moment to score their tube!]
[Detective Team One wins the mission!]
Gary is very ticklish.
Detective Team One,
please step forward.
[Kwang Soo must make his getaway
before his composite is handed out!]
- Here's the criminal's composite.
- I'm going to teach him a lesson.
I'm seriously going to teach him a lesson
when I get my hands on him.
I can't believe we had to do that.
[Detective Team One wins Kwang Soo's
composite from winning the mission!]
- You have to have the composite on you.
- It's Lee Kwang Soo.
- Let's go!
- Let's go arrest them.
- We've got something.
- What is it?
[Final location-
'Find the back of an outdoor stage'.]
[On the eastern coast of Gyungju.]
This really is a miracle.
- Just the fact that we're all still alive.
- We should be happy we're all still alive.
- Let's all congratulate ourselves.
- This is as good as winning.
Congratulations, Suk Jin.
This might be our first win.
[Extremely upbeat.
Could this be their first win ever?]
La la la la la la, Traitors Club!
[A radio message from the headquarters.]
Yes?
The criminals have infiltrated the final
location, the nuclear exhibition hall.
They have infiltrated the final location,
and you must go arrest them.
What now?
Are we eliminating them?
The ones we can eliminate are,
Ji Suk Jin and Ha Ha.
We can eliminate them for now.
- We can eliminate two?
- We can eliminate Suk Jin and Kwang Soo.
But only the person with the composite in
their possession can eliminate them.
[Only the detective with the composite in
hand can make the arrest!]
[I will... arrest you.]
[The location where
the treasure chest is hidden.]
['O' nuclear exhibition center.]
- Today... is the day.
- Our day has finally arrived.
[The criminals succeed in infiltrating
without losing any one of their members.]
Let's go!
- They have your composite, right?
- I only need to stay away from Jae Suk.
We're good as gone
as soon as we're caught, right?
We're good as gone when they catch us.
So we have to find the treasure chest first.
Jae Suk can't eliminate me
right now, right?
Jong Kook's team can eliminate you,
and Jae Suk's team can eliminate me.
- Where do you think the box is?
- Isn't this where they told us to go?
[The instructions told them to find
the outdoor stage...]
[Outdoor stage is discovered!]
This is it, right?
- There's nothing here.
- What's behind the stage?
[What's supposed to be back here?]
[Detective Team One arrives!]
Now starts the detectives'
undercover investigation.
However, since there's a chance of
the criminals making their escape...
only one detective per team
can infiltrate the grounds.
You must decide right now which detective
will be going in with which composite.
Second detective will go in
15 minutes from now.
And the last detective may go in
30 minutes from now.
After you've placed the criminals
under arrest...
the team that regains the treasure and
brings it back to the headquarters
will be the final winners of the day.
- Just one team can win.
- So we have to eliminate the other team too.
Who's going to take the composite
is what's really important here.
- Then I'll go in to arrest Suk Jin first.
- Okay, let's do that.
And if you see the opportunity, oust
one of the members from the other team.
- Okay.
- Good luck.
[Detective Uhm makes her move
with Suk Jin's composite in hand.]
- I'll be back.
- Okay, Jae Suk. See you in a bit.
I don't know how to do things like this.
There they are.
Isn't that tall guy, Lee Kwang Soo?
Wow, he really stands out.
Doesn't he?
[190cm Giraffe easy to spot from anywhere.]
Those guys aren't even paying
any attention to me.
Jung Hwa...
Come here, Jung Hwa.
I'll help you win today.
I'm serious.
- Okay?
- That's what I was going to say.
- That really is what I was going to say.
- I didn't know you were such a liar.
I seriously will help you win.
If you just trust us and do what we say,
you'll win the race today.
I'm serious.
[Will it be about justice or victory?]
I'm so confused right now.
What do I do?
I think I'm about to get schemed.
[The criminals following the instructions
to search behind the stage.]
- Be careful and watch your back.
- Is that a bomb?
What?
I seriously have no idea
what's going on right now.
You startled me!
[Scaredy cat, Haroro
scared of the wind rustling.]
- Look, there's a shovel.
- Where?
- Are we supposed to dig?
- There was a big rock here.
- I bet there's something under there.
- What are you searching for?
- Be careful, Suk Jin.
- Uhm Jung Hwa...
That's hard for me to find too.
[Criminals digging into the earth with
a detective in plain sight.]
Is it okay for us to be doing
all this in plain sight?
- We don't know what we're going to find.
- What else are we supposed to do then?
Shouldn't we knock her out with
the shovel first or something?
[Say what?]
- You're making it too obvious, Ha Ha.
- I know you have a composite on you.
I don't know who's it may be,
but you have one.
- Someone's coming.
- Someone is coming. This won't do.
[Someone is heading their way!]
It's Jae Suk.
- Its Jae Suk.
- What am I supposed to do?
[Traitors Club making their escape for now.]
There they are!
Over there!
[Detective Uhm having lost them
from all her indecisiveness.]
They're coming to get us!
[Detective Yoo
chasing them down at top speed!]
Run, Suk Jin!
[Finally gets his hands on Suk Jin!]
- I'll give you a piece of information.
- What information?
- Suk Jin is ousted.
- I know.
- What should we do?
- Lets hide.
[Detective Yoo and Detective Uhm
both have Suk Jin's composite in hand.]
[Detective Yoo arrests Suk Jin.]
[That was mine...]
You are placed under arrest.
[Displays Suk Jin's composite
as his piece of evidence.]
- I was going to do it!
- You are placed under arrest.
Hey!
Traitors Cross!
Fighting to the end!
- They all ran away from you.
- How could they have abandoned me?
[What did he expect from the guys who ran
away without even a backward glance?]
- That's what those guys are like.
- They didn't even look back.
Did you bring Suk Jin's composite too?
I guess my composite is popular.
- Jung Hwa...
- I'm so upset!
You two were battling over
who gets to get me?
[Whatever the case, the first
arrest goes to Detective Team One.]
- This really is...
- I'll see you later!
- What's going on? What are you doing?
- I don't know!
You think I'd tell you that?
[The criminals' big brother is arrested!
What fate awaits them?]
[Is Jung Hwa suddenly turning
her attack on Jae Suk?]
- Jung Hwa...
- I have something to tell you!
- I'm being serious.
- Then just tell me.
- I was going to oust Suk Jin earlier...
- Yes?
But I honestly didn't want to
do it like a coward.
That wasn't being a coward.
Jung Hwa, I wasn't being a coward about it.
That wasn't what I meant.
I was about to do it then you chimed in.
- I didn't chime in, but I went after him.
- You stole what was mine.
- Seriously, Jung Hwa...
- He was mine.
Why are you being like this?
- I didn't know you were like this.
- That's not right, Jung Hwa.
- I was just playing the game fair and square.
- How could you do that to me?
Jung Hwa...
[Suddenly falling to the ground?]
Jung Hwa!
[What is she doing?]
- Jae Suk! I just hurt myself.
- Where?
My gobang.
Where in the body is gobang?
[Gobang = Part of the knee.]
What's gobang?
What do I do?
I don't think I can even walk.
- You can't walk?
- No.
- Then just stay there.
- Come help me.
Where are you even hurt?
Jung Hwa!
What are you doing?
Seriously... how do you
expect me to fall for that?
Seriously, Jung Hwa.
How do you expect me to fall for that?
Do I look like I'm laughing?
- I can see you're laughing right now!
- I'm crying right now!
- Can't you see my tears?
- I don't see any tears at all!
I didn't know you were like this.
- What are you saying, Jung Hwa?
- I didn't know you were so heartless.
Come here.
[Starts to chase after him again
after closing up the gap between them.]
- Jung Hwa!
- I told you to come here!
- How could you be like this?
- Jung Hwa!
Jung Hwa!
[They're allowed to eliminate one another.
A battle to arrest amongst the detectives.]
[Another show of falling down!]
Jung Hwa.
I'm serious this time.
I think I tore my ligament.
What... what are you doing?
[Slowly closing in on him.]
Jung Hwa, I can't do anything about this.
Jung Hwa, I can't do anything!
What?
What is it now, Jung Hwa!
- What is it now, Jung Hwa?
- My leg!
- It jammed in the doorway.
- No, it didn't.
I saw it.
It didn't get jammed.
Help me up.
[It's the hand this time?]
What are you doing?
What is all this, Jung Hwa?
- What are you doing, Jung Hwa?
- Open the door for a second.
The thing we have to keep in mind
is that no matter who did it,
Suk Jin has been eliminated.
- Then share the gold with me.
- What?
[Detective Uhm showing her desire
for the gold winnings.]
- What gold are you talking about?
- I'll melt it down and make you a necklace.
Seriously, Jung Hwa.
We're both detectives.
Since we're all detectives,
let's oust all the criminals first.
- And then we can talk.
- I want to oust you first.
- You're not kidding around, are you?
- I'm not joking!
What the heck?
What are you doing?
[Detective Uhm having lost her mind
over the thought of gold?]
- This is all your fault!
- This isn't my fault, Jung Hwa.
[What are the detectives doing
instead of catching the criminals?]
Wait.
Come on, Jung Hwa.
- Jung Hwa... what is it?
- You... you gripped me too hard.
Jung Hwa, I'm just going to leave.
I don't care what you do.
Okay?
I'm just going to leave.
If you get in my way,
I'm just going to push past you.
Seriously?
I seriously don't know what I should do.
- I don't know any of the rules...
- Yes.
And I was going to capture Ji Suk Jin,
but you got to him first.
If you're like this...
At my age... I'm not even married.
Make sure to get yourself married, okay?
[Stay strong!]
[Succeeds in avoiding the danger
to make his escape!]
Look at them.
[After all the whining about
not being able to stand the exertion...]
But look at how well she's running.
Her nickname is 'crybaby'.
- Crybaby.
- That's my new nickname for her.
She scares me.
I'm scared of seeing her in my dreams.
Look at her chasing after him
with her hair flying around like that.
She looks like a ghost.
I'll go in.
I'll go in and corner them.
[Detective Kim goes in without
a composite!]
Okay!
Let's start the investigation!
Fighting!
[Detective Gae goes in with
Ha Ha's composite in hand.]
Here it is.
I'm going to go catch this culprit.
[On the other hand...]
[The Traitors Club hides away the bag
with all their keys in a secret place.]
[And makes their escape from
all the detectives.]
Let's go up there.
- I don't know. I'm running back to Seoul.
- I don't know either.
[Unsure who'll be making their
appearance with their composites in hand.]
It's a soccer field.
You're right.
Where are you guys going?
- Let's talk. Let's talk.
- You want to talk?
Yes.
[Criminals and the detectives conversing
with a net separating them.]
I've really missed you, Jae Suk.
You guys... are you guys even
getting to eat?
We haven't had anything to eat.
- We've really missed you.
- Who's composite do you have?
- I see someone else coming.
- Turn yourselves in.
- Just surrender and turn yourselves in.
- What have we done that's so wrong?
- We'll help you beat the other team.
- We can't eliminate anyone.
Let's really talk.
That team has Kim Jong Kook.
How do you plan on taking care of him?
We'll take care of him.
- You guys are just so dense!
- You guys being like this...
This is why you never win!
- It's not like that.
- I'll surrender myself to you.
I'll sacrifice myself for you guys.
I don't need that.
- We don't need that.
- I'll give you Ha Ha's other hand too!
[Traitor Giraffe sacrificing
his own comrade, Ha Ha.]
- That's why...
- Wow, that really hurts.
[Just then!]
[Detective Team Two with
Ha Ha's composite joins the scene.]
- I see everyone's here now.
- Sorry, Gary. I have Jae Suk here for you!
- Wait!
- I'm holding onto both of Jae Suk's hand!
[Kwang Soo is eliciting the detectives
to fight amongst themselves!]
- I got him!
- Hurry, Jung Hwa!
[Detective Team Two's Jung Hwa
eliminates Jae Suk's name tag!]
Jung Hwa, remember that
we helped you!
[This pair is in a total uproar.]
We shouldn't be fighting
amongst ourselves!
[Traitors Club uses this moment
to make their escape!]
Jung Hwa!
I'm not your enemy!
Why did you eliminate me?
Why?
You want me to put it back on?
[Gary hands his composite of
Ha Ha over to Jung Hwa.]
- You two need to work together for now.
- Those sneaky foxes.
I can't believe he held me down
by holding onto my hand.
That Lee Kwang Soo.
You two stay alive, okay?
- You two work together for now.
- Bye!
- Jung Hwa.
- You shouldn't be happy about eliminating me!
You really are no joke!
- Gary...
- After all the complaining about being tired!
What have you said to Jung Hwa for her
to come after me like that?
We haven't told her anything.
We just gave her a glance.
[Ripping off the name tags is fun!]
I wouldn't be surprised if Jung Hwa rips off
Jong Kook's name tag at this rate.
- She doesn't even know the rules!
- Yes, I do! I was told to rip off Jae Suk's.
You can't rip off Jong Kook's, okay?
Just because you think it's fun to do it,
you can't go around ripping his off!
I wouldn't put it past her if she did.
She's all about ripping off
the name tags now.
[On the other hand...]
[The criminals searching behind the stage
as told in the instructions.]
[Something has to be in the ground!]
- There's too much dirt.
- Move over, I'll do it too.
- Here! I feel something!
- You hit something!
Good, good.
Let's do this quickly.
Let's hurry it up.
Okay, we're doing good.
I don't see anyone around.
I don't see anyone, Kwang Soo.
No one is around right now.
Let's hurry.
Quickly.
[A case with a lock is found
under the ground!]
We just need to find the right key
out of the 140 keys that we have.
[Just needs to open the lock with
the correct key!]
[Retrieving the 140 keys that
they hid away earlier.]
We just have to find the right one.
Let's go in.
Shut all the doors.
[Going further into the back of
the room to conceal themselves.]
Let's do this. Even though I don't know
what's in here, let's see what we've got.
There are too many keys.
Look at all this, Ha Ha.
[Only one of these is the correct key!]
Let's unravel them.
This is it.
It's this shaped key.
It would be amazing if it's the first key.
This one isn't the one.
Let's try number two.
[And key number two?]
[That's not it either...]
It's not this one either.
[When are they going to try them all?]
[30 minutes have passed.
Time for Detective Kkuk to go in!]
[Detective Blank goes in with
Kwang Soo's composite in hand!]
I'm going in to get Lee Kwang Soo.
I'm going in.
What if they went up on the roof?
Was something there?
I think there was something here.
[Discovers a patch of dirt that
looks to have been disturbed!]
What were they digging for?
Gold?
I really thought that Gary was
going to remain alive.
- What did you say?
- Sang Kyung rushed in on me.
Jong Kook, you told me to attack
Jae Suk, right?
You told me to attack Jae Suk, right?
When?
- Come on.
- What the heck!
[Everything was ordered by
Detective Kkuk of Detective Team Two?]
You just wait and see!
- See what?
- You did, right?
- You did good, Jung Hwa.
- You did the right thing.
- Jae Suk asked me why I ousted him.
So when he asked me that,
I started doubting if I did the right thing.
No, you did the right thing.
I saw the three of them earlier
digging at the patch of dirt over there.
- The ground is sunk in. They were digging.
- I'm sure they found something.
- We have to find out what it was.
- Did they take my gold?
- My gold. Could it be my gold?
- Huh?
Okay, Jung Hwa.
I'll find it.
- Let's work together.
- Sang Kyung!
- Lets work together.
- Let me tell you something first.
Since I've been in these situations
many a times before...
- Let me tell you what we should do.
- Work together.
The first thing to do right now
is to capture the criminals.
The reason being,
Im sure that they have a mission to do.
If they complete the mission
while we're fighting amongst ourselves
then it's all over for both
you and I.
- The detectives need to win.
- Let's go capture the criminals first.
- Okay.
- A joint investigation.
- Joint investigation.
- Together.
- Let's work together on this.
- This is what you call a joint investigation.
Yes, a joint investigation.
We've decided to do a joint investigation.
[Surviving detectives are in agreement to join
their forces together to make the arrest.]
- We have to work together and get them.
- Okay.
Let's take care of those two first
before we do anything between ourselves.
- Let's not do anything until then.
- Okay, promise.
Let's promise each other.
- No attacking each other.
- Look at these guys.
- I was just playing.
You need to familiarize yourself
about Running Man a bit more.
- Familiarize yourself more.
- Stop this. I'm a detective.
- Okay?
- Okay.
- These are all the same.
- Let's try this one.
Let's try all of these one at a time.
[Instead of trying things at random,
decides to try them one at a time.]
We have to try the right shaped ones.
Let's try this one.
Okay, it's not this one.
How about this one?
Number 83.
[Since they've worked so hard all day,
today may be the day!]
We're miracles for having
survived until now.
[Every single one of them is a dud!]
[they can't even remember which
of the keys that they've tried.]
We don't have much time.
We're dead if Jong Kook shows up.
Hurry, hurry, hurry!
We have to hurry.
[I hear something jingling...]
I smell something.
I can smell something.
What's this smell?
I smell something!
I can smell something!
[Sang Kyung discovers the criminals!]
[Detective Uhm also barges her way in!]
- Show us the evidence!
- Do you have any evidence?
[Detective Uhm reaches for her
composite of Ha Ha!]
[Just then...]
[In the midst of all the chaos...
reaches for her name tag!]
Do you have any evidence?
Do you have evidence?
[Sang Kyung eliminates
Jung Hwa's name tag.]
[Mental meltdown.]
- Do you have evidence?
- Jong Kook!
[Detective Kkuk rushing in after
hearing all the commotion.]
- You're in trouble now.
- Come on...
- Why are you out?
- He did it!
- Sang Kyung ousted her!
- Jong Kook!
[Even after being ousted,
Detective Uhm throws a fit.]
- Come out here, Jung Hwa.
- This is unfair!
Jung Hwa, you have to get out of there.
[Pulling out all the tricks
right up to the very end.]
- You can kill us at any time, Jong Kook.
- Why did you do that, Sang Kyung?
- Why are you being like this?
- I can't understand why you did that.
- Wait...
- Sang Kyung!
That's so unfair!
So this is what happens?
This is so annoying!
[Traitors Club uses this moment
to make their escape!]
- No!
- Why did you do that?
[What are you doing?
The criminals have escaped!]
- Why did you do that?
- Come on.
- It's all a big misunderstanding.
- What's a misunderstanding?
- Her back was right in front of me.
Her back was right in front of me.
No, you can't do this.
- Let's catch them together.
- Yes, we should. So why did you do that?
- And to a fragile woman!
- It was right in front of me. Right in front!
- But still!
- What else was I supposed to do?
It was just sitting there
right in front of me.
[At this rate,
the detectives are going to oust each other!]
- Rip off his name tag!
- Wait! Stop it for a moment.
This isn't the time for us to be
fighting like this!
- I'm saying we should do it together.
- Why did you do that?
This really isn't the time for us
to be behaving like this right now.
Just ousting each other isn't
going to get anything done, Sang Kyung.
We have to get rid of them first.
[Detective Kim just trying to
get himself out of his situation.]
What else was I supposed to do
when it was right in front of me?
- Even if it was in front of you!
- I thought it was there for me to rip off.
That's all it was.
This is all a misunderstanding.
Why did you rip it off?
This is a joint investigation.
Aside from that, it was just waiting for me
to rip off of her back.
Do you have Ha Ha's composite, Jong Kook?
- Yeah.
- In that case, let's do this.
- Let's seriously...
- Catch them.
- What's wrong with you?
- I had them trapped!
Both of them!
I had both of them here!
- Let's just go.
- What are we all doing here?
This isn't the time for this right now.
Those guys have some of the keys.
If they open up that treasure chest,
everything will be over!
Okay, let's go.
[Calling a temporary truce as
Detective Blank says and heads back out.]
I can see that you're really angry.
I'm telling you,
I had them both cornered.
You shouldn't have taken so long
to get over here.
You should've gotten here faster.
I got frustrated just waiting around.
[Just will this joint investigation end?]
Hurry!
[Right around the same time]
[Traitors Club having escaped
their certain demise.]
If it's not one of these,
then we're dead.
[Still haven't been able to find the key
that opens up the treasure chest.]
Please!
This isn't the one.
It won't fit?
It's not turning!
[The time is ticking,
but they can't find the right one!]
Kwang Soo, we're almost there!
We're almost there, Suk Jin!
[The two criminals slowly starting
to lose their minds.]
- We have to win today.
- Please!
We don't have time.
Kim Jong Kook is still alive.
[Detective Kkuk is closing in!]
[Getting ready to run again with
all their lights turned off.]
Come here, Lee Kwang Soo.
Lee Kwang Soo, come here!
Hey!
Lee Kwang Soo, listen to me.
[Does Detective Kkuk really have
something to say to the Giraffe?]
I want to get Kim Sang Kyung.
Okay?
I'll pretend that I've captured you.
- Hurry.
- Okay, how?
[Is Detective Kkuk planning on using
Kwang Soo to eliminate Sang Kyung?]
Hang on!
- Come on, Jong Kook.
- Who has Kwang Soo's composite?
[The Tiger and the Giraffe really can
work very well together at times.]
Hurry!
[Sang Kyung walks towards them
without suspecting anything.]
- Okay, I got it. I got him!
- What?
[Detective Kkuk attacks Detective Kim!]
Watch out!
- Dong Hoon!
- What are you doing?
- Hey! Kwang Soo!
Why are you betraying me after
telling me not to betray you?
[Joint investigation once again
comes to a ruin.]
- Seriously.
- You need to feel what it's like too.
But this is different
than what happened to me.
I was about to catch the guys,
but her name tag appeared in front of me.
I just did what I did out of curiosity
because I was frustrated from the waiting.
This really isn't the time for us
to be doing this, Jong Kook.
Those two running off like they did
means that they've found something.
- This isn't the time for this, Sang Kyung!
- I know.
- What's wrong with you?
- Why am I the only one thinking?
You're the one who started this!
Both of you stop it!
- Let's just go find them together.
- We should've done that from the beginning!
- Then we wouldn't have this problem!
- That's what I'm saying too!
You two figure it out
and come when you're done.
- You two figure it out.
- Let's go.
[Atmosphere of walking on thin ice.]
You have a weird glint in your eye.
You're going to betray me again, aren't you?
- Let's end this later.
- Okay.
That's what I'm saying.
- Are we working together again?
- Lets end this right here.
[Declaration of a duel!]
This is unfair.
I have a bad feeling.
You've been doing this for three years,
so I'm sure you're more skilled than I am.
- All I've done is sing ballads.
- I'm a ballad singer too!
- You know what I meant.
- But you've danced too.
- I'm a ballad singer.
[Competitiveness that can't be avoided.
What will come of this?]
Let's just end this here, Sang Kyung!
Let's just end this here, and move on.
Let's just end this.
[They're finally going at it!]
[I'm... the one... who'll catch the thieves!]
[Who will be the man that will
become the ultimate detective?]
[Sang Kyung...
eliminates Jong Kook's name!]
[Detective Kkuk of DT2 is out!]
I told you that we should do it together.
You should've listen to me.
I told you we should work together.
I told you that repeatedly.
I told you that I'm a ballad singer.
Everyone, I'm a ballad singer.
I guess... I'll go catch the others now.
Give me the composite.
[Giving up the composite of Ha Ha
over to Sang Kyung.]
- I didn't know.
- I'm a ballad singer, and I'll catch them.
I'll go take care of them.
Thanks.
I had my grip on him,
but I grabbed his hood instead.
I thought his hood was the name tag.
His hood was in the way of
his name tag!
[On the other hand...
the criminals...]
[Ha Ha hiding in the corner
of some random office.]
Everyone, hide!
[Still not sure which one of them
is the correct key.]
- Dong Hoon!
- Hey! Over here. Come over here.
How did you escape?
- Kwang Soo, how did you escape?
- Dong Hoon!
[The two criminals are back
together again!]
Jong Kook proposed that I help him
eliminate Kim Sang Kyung.
- I seized the moment to escape.
- Good job.
[Not may keys left for them to try.]
Wait, I think this is turning.
[It opened!]
Number 43.
It was number 43.
[A large note is inside the case?]
[But nothing is written into the booklet...
This is the treasure?]
Here's another death note.
['Only one person can utilize this'?]
[Giraffe's hand slowly moves
up Ha Ha's back.]
[Giraffe ousts Ha Ha!]
[Since only one person can utilize it...]
[The Traitors Club with a firm
understanding of how betrayals work.]
I didn't win this alone.
We won this together.
I smell something here.
[Detective Kim chooses that moment
to barge in on them.]
I can smell something in here.
[Detective Team One's plan
to capture their criminals.]
Dong Hoon, make your escape.
Run, Dong Hoon.
I said, make your escape!
Without Jong Kook here, Ha Ha is safe.
[Must write his name on the line
for him to be the winner!]
Ha Ha's already ousted?
Wait!
[The Giraffe is captured the moment he
gets ready to write down his name.]
Please!
Please let me win just this once!
I'm right there!
I'm right in front of my victory!
I don't have anything.
Hurry up and eliminate his name tag.
Just do it.
Hurry up and do it.
- Hurry up and do it.
- Ji Hyo, please!
Please!
Please, Ji Hyo!
[Detective Blank of DT1
completes the roundup!]
I even wrote down my last name!
- All you had to do was write your name?
- I just needed to write in 'Kwang Soo'!
- You just had to write your name?
- I'm glad this happened!
- This is your punishment!
- You are a joke!
[A fitting ending for the traitors.]
- Let's see how well you end up!
- I'll see you in jail!
[Traitors Club once again self-destructs
from their own betrayals...]
[How was anything going to work out
with this type of teamwork?]
[Winners! Detective Blank
and Detective Kim enters!]
- You're so greedy!
- You scribbled out my name?
[Ji Hyo already wrote in her name
where Kwang Soo's name would've been.]
I had no idea it would end like this.
- We've all been betrayed.
- We're the winning team.
The note is a promise of making a special
episode that would star Song Ji Hyo.
[The treasure is a promise to write a special
which would star Song Ji Hyo.]
- Thank you.
- Great job, detectives!
Congratulations, detectives!
What is it?
- It's a medal.
- Is it real gold?
- Is it gold?
- It's real gold.
[Jealous]
Why don't I ever win
something like this?
- Let me see your medal.
- Why?
- Just give it to me.
- Let me just see it.
- Let me just try it on.
- I've never won anything like this.
- Let me just see it.
Let her just try it on.
She's just going to try it on.
Take it home with you.
[The filming quickly ends!]
[Is Detective Uhm making her escape?]
- She actually ran!
- Did she leave?
[Thanks to Uhm Jung Hwa and Kim Sang Hyun
for bringing joy and laughter on our show.]
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Do flower pants make you a flower boy?]
[Havana style flower boy?]
[This is what a real flower boy
is supposed to be.]
[You should at least look like this...]
[Together with Kim Soo Hyun
and Lee Hyun Woo.]
[A flower boy athletic competition.]
[Most amazing!]
[Uproaringly funny!]
[Variety's ultimate athletic competition
with our favorite flower boys!]
[The flower boys...
are not the same as they came.]
[And also!]
[Competing along with 300
college students!]
[Next week's Running Man-
Flower Boy Athletic Competition.]