[August, 2013]
Subtitles by DramaFever
[The Running Man world frozen in
a cloud of deceit and conspiracy.]
[Caught in a situation where all
loyalty and friendships are lost.]
[An emergency cleanup situation is needed.]
[A place where deceit and conspiracy
reigns free.]
[An icy district.]
[A world frozen over in ice that's
different than any other world.]
[Now... the real cleanup is about to begin.]
[Snow Elevator]
['O' University in Bucheon.]
[Custodian of the Ice Building, Go-Tilda.]
What is this?
Why are you being like this
lately, Dong Wan?
[Transformed himself into Go-Tilda.]
[Arriving on the sixth floor,
the top floor in the Ice Building.]
What is all this?
[A grand set on the sixth floor.]
[Suspiciously being wined and dined.]
You don't have to do that.
I'm fine.
[Security camera settings in
various different areas.]
[Every floor has a different looking setup...]
What the heck?
[Breaking out in laughter as soon as
he boards the snow elevator.]
Doesn't he really look like the character?
Are you purposely doing that
with your lips?
[A botanical garden on the fifth floor.]
What the heck is this now?
What is all this?
[Ha Ha, the fourth person to arrive is
taken to the aquarium on the third floor.]
[Blank Ji, the fifth person to arrive
is taken to the second floor.]
What is this?
[Gary, the sixth person to arrive is taken
to a steamy sauna on the first floor.]
I can't open this now?
Is this where I get off?
What is this?
[Last person to arrive gets this...]
[His daily bread, bean jelly.]
What is this?
Seventh place in the ice building?
I'm in the last place out of
all seven of us?
Welcome, Running Man members.
Here's today's mission.
[Their mission for the day
in the ice building.]
Today's race is... The Icy Order Race.
Icy order?
The Icy Order Race.
Icy order...
The order does need to be redefined.
During the course of today...
we will determine the order of Running Man
members through cold and calculated methods.
First... everyone needs to change into
their uniforms immediately.
[Pre-assigned uniforms.]
I'm in second place.
Why am I in second place?
What? Sixth place?
That's just ridiculous.
I get it, is it according to looks?
I'm going to work my way up.
Mark my words,
I'm going to work my way up!
[Already behaving like a resident
of the corner space in the ice building.]
I want some steak too!
Change into your clothes.
Okay.
[Thus, without even knowing the reason...]
[Running Man members are relegated
to their position in The Order.]
Is that my breakfast?
How is this steak?
[Frozen meal that anyone can enjoy
in the middle of the hot summer.]
I guess I should just be grateful
that I'm even getting this at all.
[A meal that's given to the person
in first place only.]
So no one else is getting this?
Everyone has different food depending on
which order they're in, don't they?
[Giraffe with his bean jelly.]
I'm so sick and tired of this.
Just how long do I have to keep
putting up with this kind of treatment!
I want some protein too!
Give me my steak!
Running Man members, you are now all aware
of your own standings in The Order?
I can't even hear what he's saying
down here in the basement.
This isn't a guarantee of your
position in The Order.
But you will have several different chances
to change your position in The Order.
Your first mission which will give you
a chance at changing the order...
is the Snow Elevator.
- The Snow Elevator.
- Snow elevator?
You are all placed in different spots
depending on your position in The Order.
First place is on the very top floor
and seventh place is on the
very lowest level.
In order to change your position
in The Order
you must first board the elevator that will
take you up to higher floors in the building.
You must get off on the floor that is
higher than the floor that you're currently on
and by playing and winning a game,
you can take over that place in the order.
But, you only have one chance
to change your position per game
and the person who lands in the last place
per round will be eliminated
and will be given a treatment
very befitting of the position.
We wish everyone luck in maintaining your
upper position to avoid this treatment.
We will now start our first round.
For your first round...
it will be sixth position vs. seventh position.
Fifth place vs. fourth position.
And third place will compete
against second place.
If the person in the seventh place
loses this round
that person will firmly establish
their position in the seventh place
and will no longer be given any more chances
to escape from their position in rank.
I won't have any more chances
to move up in my position?
This is the first and last chance
that I will ever have in my life.
My last chance to get away from this rubble
of trash that I'm so sick and tired of!
This is my first and final opportunity.
[None of the members are aware of
who is on which floor.]
- Okay.
- Please board the elevator.
Please board the elevator.
[Basement Giraffe dreaming of moving up
in his position up to sixth place.]
Just how far are you planning on going
with all your transformations?
I've finally moved up one floor.
Hello.
- Hey, are you in last place?
- You're in sixth place?
- Why are you in sixth place?
- I don't know why I'm in sixth place either.
I thought the order was based on age,
but I guess that's not the case.
- I think the order is based on looks.
- Hey!
- Then why would I be in seventh place?
- You're in seventh place in looks.
- Gary! I'd be in fourth place, at least!
- You're just being absurd right now.
- Hurry up and get back down.
- Gary.
I bet you that you'll stay in
seventh place for the entire day.
It's no joke down there.
- You can't even betray anyone..
- No!
You can't even betray your way
out of this one!
You have to win this race based
purely on your skills.
Why don't we work together?
What do you mean, work together?
This is an individual battle.
This isn't a name tag elimination.
[Blank Ji on her way to compete with
the person in fourth place.]
What the heck?
- Ji Hyo, it's you?
- Ha Ha, you're in fourth place?
- Wow, I didn't know it was going to be you.
- What the heck is this?
This is too strong of an opponent
right from the beginning.
Anyone but Jong Kook.
I'd be happy with Ji Hyo.
Someone's here!
The door is about to open!
[Oh no... the Tiger is here.]
Keep going up.
Just keep going up.
- I said, just go on up.
- Can you pass?
- Why is he here?
- Are you in third place?
Here's your first round.
Your first round game is...
I guarantee that I can beat you as long as
it's not the name tag elimination game.
A one-on-one name tag
elimination game.
Your first round game is...
one-on-one name tag
elimination game.
- One-on-one?
- A one-on-one name tag elimination game.
[First place winner can watch the
first round in the comfort of his seat.]
Bravo!
This is too much.
Why does it have to be this?
This is just absurd!
- This isn't really much of a competition.
- Then just give me your name tag.
I should make it entertaining, at least.
This is absolutely ridiculous.
It's absurd that this is the first game.
- That's what I'm saying.
- I guess it's better to be punished upfront.
I think it's better to just
get it over with.
Come on!
- Are you trying to use your strength on me?
- What other choice do I have?
- Suk Jin, I have no other choice.
- I can understand that you have to do this.
- I have no other choice, Gary.
- Nothing I can do about it either.
You're just made to live
on the bottom floor, Kwang Soo.
- I'm sick of having to eat the bean jelly!
- Okay, I hear you!
I should be doing this with Ha Ha instead.
[Neither are happy about having to
compete with each other.]
Kwang Soo, let's end this quickly!
Ji Hyo!
This isn't easy.
[With the exception of one floor,
the rest of the face-off's aren't as easy.]
[Basement Giraffe's attack.]
I vow... I vow to move up!
Hey!
What's wrong with you?
[Current seventh place holder
desperate to win his battle.]
[Simultaneously?]
[Wow! Seventh place holder,
Kwang Soo wins!]
I vow to move up in my rank!
[Fourth place Ha Ha and fifth place Blank Ji
taking a brief break.]
[Picking a strand of hair off of
Blank Ji's clothes.]
[Figures...]
You're such a cheater!
Ji Hyo!
[Fourth place Ro-Ro eliminates
Blank Ji's name tag.]
- I'm sorry, Ji Hyo. Forgive me just once.
- I won't have it!
How could you take me out
and cheat like that!
Ji Hyo could've won that battle
if her shirt hadn't been turned around.
I can tell that Ji Hyo's
really pissed right now.
I had no choice, Ji Hyo.
- I had no other choice.
- You tricked me!
[His cheap shot brings out
the thuggish Ji Hyo.]
I had no other choice, Ji Hyo.
Please understand where I'm coming from.
I wonder if there are any ropes around here?
I can leave you tied up here.
[And one obvious battle.]
[Second place holder, Big-nose
is backed up into a corner.]
I'm going to protect my second place!
[That doesn't seem to be possible...]
Did you tie me up or something?
[Not even able to budge a muscle
against Mr. Capable's strength.]
Why do you have me tied up?
Suk Jin... you have to stop moving.
I'm sorry. It's too hot
to be doing this in the summer.
It's really hot to be doing this
in the middle of the summer.
Being in third place isn't so bad.
I was actually pretty happy in third place.
I didn't even do anything.
You're going to be pretty cold
down there.
Go away. What kind of
a humiliation is this? Seriously.
- Why do you find this humiliating?
- Hurry up and just go away!
[The positions are starting to move around.]
I'll see you later.
- I've made up my resolve.
- Gary.
I'll see you later, Gary.
I promise to move up in my position.
[Giraffe moves up one position
to sixth place.]
You're now delegated to being
in the last place.
But it's not forever.
[Gary is moved down to the basement.]
What the heck is this?
There's not even a place for me to sit?
[The sad reality of being in last place.]
[Gary's new position in
seventh place- Confirmed.]
We will now start the second round.
For the second round...
sixth place will compete
against fifth place
fourth place against third place
and second place will compete against first
place for a chance to take over their position.
That's Kim Jong Kook.
If the sixth place holder loses
this round...
that person will establish
their spot as the sixth place holder
and will no longer have any more chances
to move up from their position.
So it's all over for me if I lose this?
You may now board the elevator.
There are five people left to go.
I'm going to make it up to
the very top.
I'm going to put
everything I have on the line.
I wonder who'll be on this floor.
You scared me.
- Hey!
- Ji Hyo, you're in fifth place?
Are you in sixth place?
Were you in sixth place to begin with?
No, I moved up from seventh place.
[Third place holder, Big-nose
vs. Fourth place holder, Ha Ha.]
Have you been well?
Mr. Third Place Holder?
[Kkuk arrives at the very top floor.]
Muscle boy!
Hey, Muscle Boy.
[Muscle Boy makes it up
all the way to the top floor.]
Welcome, Muscle Boy.
Why are you going around
twitching your shoulders like that?
I guess you've been watching
everything that's been going on?
I have been watching all that's been
going on since I'm in first place
and I had a steak for breakfast too.
Ah, I see.
What kind of a steak is that?
Is that the best they had for you?
While I was down there eating my bean jelly
amongst all the trash cans...
Did you have more bean jelly?
They're really good.
I had five of those things.
- They're about to make an announcement.
- We will now start the second round.
For your second game...
you will play a round of the
hand slap game.
It's the hand slap game.
You will take turns slapping
the tops of each other's hands
and the first person to scream out loud
from the pain will lose this game.
- Your next game will be the hand slap game.
- What kind of absurdity is this?
How does this make any sense?
Let's talk about this first.
This game is absolutely ridiculous!
- You will now start the game.
- I'm good at enduring my pain.
- I'm confidant I'll win this.
- Five.
Four, three, two, one.
This is insane.
Look at his arms.
Have you seen his arms?
Let me give you a tip.
You need to knock me out
with your first hit.
[He's telling Jae Suk to knock him out
with the first attack?]
I don't know about this.
If I can't get him in one shot,
then it's all over for me.
This isn't the arm of a human being!
Why are you getting all tense about this?
Can't you loosen up your hand a bit?
[It seems as though Yoo Hyuk is in
more pain for having slapped Jong Kook.]
My hand is a little sweaty today
from this heat.
- I feel like... it's going to be a good slap.
- I'm in trouble.
- Doesn't it even hurt?
- No, it doesn't hurt.
[Preparing himself for the slap.]
[Cringing at Jong Kook's hand movement.]
- What's wrong?
- What?
Why did you pretend like
you were going to hit me?
Fine, I'll slap you.
It's not going to hurt as much
as you think.
[Falling apart at the seams from
Muscle Boy's spike slap.]
[Silent gasps of pain due to the
inability to scream out loud.]
What's wrong?
Here.
This is seriously...
Here I go.
Ugh, my palm is burning.
Ugh, my palm hurts even more.
[Fourth place vs. Third place-
Slapping each other's hands with glee.]
[Slapping each other back and forth
without any rest in between.]
[Sixth place vs. Fifth place-
Back and forth as expected.]
[Second floor on fire.]
Scream if it hurts.
Just scream if it hurts.
Call out your father's name, or your
brother's name. Just scream out loud!
I want to scream out so badly!
[It's Muscle Boy's turn to
attack on the sixth floor.]
[A slam dunk!]
He avoided it!
He avoided my slap.
He avoided the slap!
He avoided the slap and I was
only able to hit him right here.
That hurts!
It hurts like you can't even imagine!
Look at my hand!
Look at the state my hand is in!
I don't think that was a proper slap,
so let's do it over.
- You can start.
- I just screamed out in pain!
I screamed out loud.
[Admitting that he screamed out loud.]
- It hurts! Hurts!
- I didn't really hear him.
I can't do this!
[Taking it upon himself to switch out their
tags indicating their order.]
But I really didn't hear you
scream out loud.
- I screamed! You take it!
- But, it wasn't a proper slap!
Let go.
Let go of it.
[Second floor exchanging slaps
at a lightning fast speed.]
[Slapping himself in the face?]
You can't do that.
Let's switch hands.
Does it hurt?
Scream if your hand is hurting you.
It really tickles, and it's hard
for me to endure the laughter.
Really?
Then let's keep going.
It hurts.
Let's switch hands.
Here.
Me first?
[Starting over after having
switched out their hands.]
[A fierce battle because neither one of them
wants to be confirmed in sixth place.]
[Already on their 50th slap
on the fourth floor.]
Fine, I lost!
Hey!
[Big-nose throwing in the towel
from all the agony.]
How old are you?
How old are you!
[Still in the midst of their slap battle.]
[Explodes out in suppressed screams.]
- It hurts!
- How much!
I feel like I'm going to die
from the pain!
This was already a
lost game from the beginning!
- I'm hurting too!
- I'm going to stay on the 6th floor forever!
[Kwang Soo fails his attempt to
move up any further in rank.]
Do you think that you'll be able to maintain
your first place position forever?
I did it!
[Ha Ha moves up to third place in rank.]
- Third place!
- Things are looking worse and worse.
Things are looking worse by the floor.
[Kwang Soo confirms his spot in
sixth place from his basement origin.]
Are we going?
Heading towards second place in rank.
Let's go!
Moving up like this isn't
a bad feeling.
[Just who could be waiting for him
up on the sixth floor?]
Is it Jong Kook?
Those are Jong Kook's shoes.
It's me.
- Welcome.
- It's you?
[The bickering brothers facing each other
for the second place rank.]
- Welcome.
- Let me see your hand.
[Hiding his right hand which is
beet red from the slapping.]
Oh my, look at how red it is.
Wow, Jae Suk.
Your hand looks bruised.
- Can you guess who it was?
- Jong Kook.
Your place...
is seventh place.
You've come too far up.
Do you know how this is ranked?
I'm asking if you know that.
- Isn't it in order of debut date?
- No, the face.
You're about fifth place in that.
Yeah, you're in fifth place.
This round will determine who will be
confirmed in fifth place in ranking.
It's the Egg Roulette Game.
- It's an Egg Roulette Game.
- Egg Roulette?
You will take turns to cracking eggs
with your head...
Ah, we have to find the raw egg?
And I'm sure you can figure out
who loses the game when that time comes.
This is all about luck.
You should've had us playing this game
when I was facing off with Jong Kook!
Two, one, start.
[Basking in the comfort of the top floor.]
Yes, thank you.
[The cool and refreshing taste
of being in first place.]
The water is so cool and refreshing.
What amazing service.
You don't have to do all that.
Egg roulette?
What if Jae Suk comes back up here?
Seriously... he's lucky like that.
Who goes first?
[Person with the higher position
in ranking gets to go first.]
Can't be.
Can't be it already.
- First blow.
- Let's just be cool about this.
Let's just be cool about it.
Okay!
What if this is the one?
I worked so hard to get up here.
- Let it be the raw egg, let it be...
- Who dares to try to kick me out now?
[If he wins this round, he'll be
moving up to second place in rank!]
Come on, come on, come on!
Okay, come on!
[Will it be the raw egg?]
Come on!
Please.
[Hardboiled egg...]
[Fifth place and Fourth place-
Third floor is also cracking away.]
This is all about the luck of the draw.
[A dull thud?]
You have to smack it really hard
for it not to hurt on your head.
[Again!]
Why are you having such a hard time
cracking that open?
Come on, come on, come on!
[Back to Yoo Hyuk's turn.]
This is the game that I should've played
against Kim Jong Kook.
I won!
I'm number two!
Two, two, two!
Look at you.
You did great.
You've been up here way too long.
I won!
Third place!
Song Ji Hyo!
You've done great.
Why don't we grab dinner
together sometime?
Just remember that this
isn't the end.
- There will be another chance!
- What did you say, Mr. Third Place?
I'm so annoyed!
I'm not going to let them
get away with this.
Everyone has to hit the bottom
before they climb back up in their lives.
I really hate to say this...
but this place isn't
all that different from my house.
I have bean jelly at home too.
What's with all these flies!
Suk Jin won the game?
Wow, that's unbelievable.
Okay!
[Going back up a floor.]
Who knew the eggs would help
me out like that?
The eggs were a great help.
I love eggs!
I have to win this round.
I have to win it this time.
- You're in third place?
- Welcome.
Did you fall from first place?
Which spot did you fall from?
[Fourth and Third Place holders
warming up for their next game.]
- I feel strangely confident.
- I feel good about this round.
I know I can beat Suk Jin.
Hey, Ji Hyo was overly confident
and lost too.
Oh my... nice to see you again.
Climbing up is a hobby of mine.
[Haroro taking on the first floor
after having started in fourth place.]
Come here, kiddo.
Mr. Jong Kook.
What's going on here?
Oh, you can see everything from here?
Yeah, I enjoyed watching you guys.
Then I guess I can sit there and
watch once I'm first place?
You've climbed up too high in the rank,
which doesn't really suit you.
[First place and Second place holders'
tight mental battle.]
Your fourth round mission is...
Put on the workpants without
the use of your hands.
What?
Put on the workpants without
the use of your hands.
- Huh?
- What?
But we have to do this while lying down?
[But it has to be done on top
of the acupuncture mat.]
I'm feeling pretty competitive today.
Okay, you're feeling confident,
but you're still in fourth place.
I'm going to keep climbing up.
[Screaming out in pain
the moment the game starts.]
[Starting to interfere in each other's
progress in order to maintain their spot.]
[A child-like fight between the two
40-something men.]
Okay, this is good.
- This is good.
- This is not really happening.
[Oh... already?]
[The key is to get the pants
past their hips.]
Ouch, that hurts!
[Are they trying to launder the pants?]
You need to hike them up
another three cm.
Where's the opening to these pants?
[Taking over Suk Jin's workpants!]
Thanks, Suk Jin.
Thanks.
[Throws him off.]
[Even breaking down into a belly dance
in an attempt to hike up the pants.]
[Utilizing any sharp points.]
Sorry, Suk Jin.
I have no other choice right now.
- Seriously!
- How can I hike these up?
[Suk Jin's legs?]
[Exhaustion hits.]
I got it.
I got them on.
[Yoo Hyuk wins.]
Thanks for your help.
[Suk Jin's position
confirmed in fourth place.]
[Working themselves into a frenzy.]
[On the acupuncture mat,
known to be good for blood circulation.]
[Just who will take the first place?]
I got it!
[Ha Ha wins!]
[A personal win! Takes over first place
after having started out in fourth place!]
I'm number one!
[Yoo Hyuk, currently in third place
goes back up a floor to second.]
Please, anyone but Kim Jong Kook.
[But his opponent is...]
There you are.
- Listen...
- You're here.
- Did you lose to the kiddo?
- The kiddo has a lower butt than I do.
You'd better get yourself ready
to go down a level.
- You can just keep that tag on.
- What did you say?
- I'm just going to end it for you here.
This hand still doesn't feel like
my own hand!
Let me see.
What's wrong with your hand?
It's now time to determine who
will be in third place.
Your next mission...
Let's do a game like the egg game.
Is one-on-one table tennis.
- Table tennis?
- Instead of your normal tennis racket...
you're going to use other items to
hit the tennis ball.
The first person to score seven points
wins the game.
- Then do I get to choose the prop first?
- What did you say?
[Kkuk gets to choose the prop first
for being higher up in rank.]
- This one looks good.
- Once you grab it, you have to stick with it.
- What are you talking about?
- You have to stick with that one now.
I think this would be good for attacking.
[Second place Kkuk being meticulous
about which prop he chooses.]
- But for playing defense, maybe this one?
- Come on.
Maybe this will be better?
Maybe this would be better for it.
When you were slapping my hand earlier...
your hand felt like a frying pan.
[Second place holder Kkuk chooses
the hand fan.]
I'll go with this one.
[Third place holder Yoo Hyuk chooses
to go with the frying pan.]
Here I go.
Okay, let's start.
That's right!
[Yoo Hyuk- 1 vs. Kkuk- 0.]
- This has no strength.
- This puts a spin on the ball.
This thing has a spin to it.
Give me the ball.
- You made a bad decision.
- This has no power. I have to hit it hard.
That's right!
[Yoo Hyuk- 2 vs. Kkuk- 0.]
- Hurry up and do it.
- Okay.
- It's two to one, right?
- Yes.
[Yoo Hyuk- 2 vs. Kkuk- 1]
Ah! Two to two!
[Yoo Hyuk- 2 vs. Kkuk- 2]
I'm used to this now!
[Yoo Hyuk- 4 vs. Kkuk- 3]
That's right!
- There's nothing to this.
- That's right!
That's right!
[Yoo Hyuk- 5 vs. Kkuk- 3]
You and I are a great fit.
There's no need to put too much
strength behind this.
Let's go.
That's right!
[Yoo Hyuk- 6 vs. Kkuk- 3]
- This is the last point.
- I know!
- This is the game point.
- Let's go.
[Yoo Hyuk- 6 vs. Kkuk- 4]
[A spike serve!]
Awesome.
Don't hold yourself back, Jong Kook.
Don't hold yourself back.
- I can't believe how this is turning out.
- I'm good under pressure.
Let's play real table tennis now, Jong Kook.
Real table tennis.
Just think of this as a
regular table tennis game.
[An ambush attack?]
[He fails at his trick attack.]
Wow, that was amazing.
Okay, it's a deuce.
[Yoo Hyuk- 6 vs. Kkuk- 6.
Deuce.]
Who am I, and what's going on here?
Don't you know what a deuce is?
It's impossible to predict who'll win.
Just get going!
I'm going to end it this time.
Let's just end it here, Jong Kook.
Just take it easy.
- Take it easy.
- That's right!
[Yoo Hyuk- 7 vs. Kkuk- 7.
An even score again!]
- Just take it easy, okay?
- What happened?
- This is a little slow.
- That was good.
I feel like we're at
the Olympics right now.
[Running Man's bitter rivals-
Hyuk and Kkuk.]
[Who knew that sparks would be flying
during the table tennis match like this?]
[Pulling out all the moves- Unbelievable.]
You don't even see that move very often
during the Olympics.
[A surprise attack while Kkuk is
too busy talking.]
[But he catches the serve!]
That's not a move that you
see very often.
I won!
[7 vs. 9.
Kkuk wins!]
[Enraged...]
I can't believe I lost.
- I guess I'll be going back up now.
- There was even the cheating.
What did you say?
You're the one who cheated.
That's what I mean.
I cheated.
You're the one who cheated!
According to the rules... I should've waited
to serve when he was ready.
- But I jumped the gun on that.
- It's okay, I can let that go.
In that case, we'll declare that
you lost by cheating.
I seriously can't believe I lost!
It looks like I'll be competing
against Mr. Jong Kook again.
[Yoo Hyuk confirmed for third place.]
Seriously... I went easy on you.
- That was an unbelievable win.
- I still can't believe I lost!
I could've won that game.
We will now move on to
the final round.
This final round... is the playoff round.
This round will determine the first and
second place holder in rank
and the person who wins this game
will take over first place in rank
for the time being.
I have to play with the kiddo again?
[In the midst of dining?]
Seriously...
Wait just a little bit longer.
I'm almost finished with my meal.
This is a great meal.
So you made your way
back up here?
Well, since the seat belonged to me
in the first place...
[The last final round which will determine
who will take over first place in rank.]
- You did great work.
- Yes.
- This is your final round.
No matter who wins between
the two of you
the person who comes in at second place
must be completely obedient of the winner.
The first place winner will be determined
by a round of table tennis ball toss.
[Table tennis ball toss.]
The first person to toss the ball
into the wine glass...
[The first person to bounce the ball and
land it in the wineglass wins the game.]
Just think about it lightly.
This game is advantageous for you.
[The other members with confirmed ranks
join to watch the match.]
I should be the one playing in this round.
[Haroro's attempt to take over first place
that surprises everyone.]
But how did we get ranked when we
first got here anyways?
- Isn't it in the order of our debut?
- Our debut years?
[It was determined in the order
of your variety debut.]
Ah, variety show debut?
Variety show debut date.
[Must score the ball
in this wine glass to win.]
The person who wins first place right now,
will have one chance
to chance to change the order
between third and seventh place holders.
- They can change their spots?
- Only the first place winner?
I'm going to have to win this.
- Wow.
Then does it mean that he can switch
from seventh to third position?
Yes, he can do that.
[Possible to switch from
seventh to third place.]
- Kim Jong Kook! Kim Jong Kook!
- Ha Ha! Ha Ha!
- Kim Jong Kook!
- Ha Ha!
Excuse me, Mr. Jae Suk?
Can you hand me one too?
- Yes, no problem.
- Oh my, I dropped my balls.
[Transformation-
A smart Kwang-retriever.]
[You must be hot!]
[Ha Ha takes the first turn.]
[Very close, but misses!]
- Here you go, I wiped it up for you.
- Okay.
[Kwang-retriever following Ha Ha
around like a loyal puppy.]
[Kkuk's turn.]
[Not even close...]
I'm sorry.
[Kwang-retriever playing havoc
with Kkuk's mental state.]
Think of this as your last chance.
[That was so close!]
- This is making me nervous.
- This isn't an easy shot.
[On the other hand, it seems like Kkuk
still hasn't gotten the feel for it.]
I think I'm getting the feel for it.
[Suggesting that they divide
up the cheer crowd.]
[Huh?
Gary's standing behind Kkuk?]
I've always stood behind Jong Kook.
[Again, that was so close!]
- Where are you going, Gary?
- I've always stood right back here.
[Seventh place holder Gary sliding over
to stand behind Ha Ha?]
It's okay, it's okay.
I know I can do this.
[It seems as though Ro-Ro has gotten
a total hang of this game.]
We're all dead if you don't win this.
[Continuing on with the close call shots.]
I got it now.
I know what I have to do now.
Here I go.
[Thus, they kept on repeating their
moves over and over again...]
Since the glass is a bit small...
we will switch it out to a larger glass
with the current first place to make it fair.
- Sounds good.
- With that one?
[Switching out the glass for a container
with a wider mouth.]
[With this turn of events, the
next shot could determine the winner!]
[Yet again, another very close call!]
[The winner could be determined
with just one shot!]
You have to score it now!
Can you move all the way down?
What is this?
This ball is crushed.
I'm sorry.
[He handed him a crushed ball...]
He really is trying to undermine
my chances of winning.
[Kwang-retriever's unabashed attempt to
interfere in Jong Kook's game.]
I totally lost the feel for it.
Challenge.
[Again!]
[The end seems imminent for this match!]
They both have the feel for it.
Challenge.
There you go!
[He scores!]
Come here, Mister.
Mister.
[Explodes at Yoo Hyuk whom he's had
a lot of pent up grudges against.]
I'm number one!
[Lower rank people all gathering
around Ha Ha.]
Excuse me, you all need to
apologize to him.
You all need to apologize to him!
Everyone line up in front of me.
Seriously.
As I have told you earlier,
people that are in third to seventh place...
the first place winner can switch
one person out of their position.
Please, Sir!
I really want to switch out one of you.
Both of you were a lot of help to me.
- I really believed in you.
- I was behind you from the beginning.
[Feeling nervous.]
I really don't want to go
down any further.
Kang Gary and Yoo Jae Suk,
switch your positions.
[With the authority of first position holder,
third and seventh position swaps spots.]
Was I being too obvious?
I don't know if that was
too obvious of a move.
I won't let you get away with this.
I can't go down any further than this!
- What did you just say?
- What are you going to do about it now?
[Seventh place holder exploding in rage.]
I can't fall any further from
where I'm at!
- What are you going to do?
- You just wait and see.
Don't tell me what to do!
- Do I tell you what to do?
- There's nothing else you can do to me now!
- I'm your boss!
- How are you my boss?
- I am your boss!
- How do you think that you're my boss?
- Please keep your composure.
- Okay, I understand.
I will now reveal to you the differences
between all the ranks.
[Everything from this point on will be
determined by their position in rank.]
You all have to take very good care
of your own things.
You need to experience what it's
like to hit rock bottom.
I want you all to observe how I'll use this
to work my way back up to the top.
I have six.
[Gold coins that are distributed
according to the ranked position.]
This gold in my hand looks so good after
having looked at bean jelly for so long.
You will continue to earn your
gold coins in this manner.
You will continue to play for rank.
We will now move on to the lunch segment.
[Off to dine!]
[First round of Snow Elevator-
Currently ranked positions.]
[The icy locale...
suddenly transforms into summer.]
Gary just proved that one single moment
can change a person's life.
Don't you remember how I told you all
that I'm going to turn my life around?
Playing all those countless games
isn't the point here.
Who knew that Gary would work himself
up to third place like that?
Do you know how good it feels to have
Jae Suk below me in standing right now?
You have no idea what that means.
You and I always gets beat by him.
Right now is your chance.
Take your opportunity.
[All the shame and indignity
that they've been put through...]
[Something feels off about this...]
It must feel so uncomfortable for you to
have me above you like this.
- This position is uncomfortable for me.
- Listen, Kwang Soo.
Are you kidding me?
What are you doing over there?
- Listen, seventh place holder?
- Yes?
What kind of a brutish behavior
are you exhibiting right now?
Seventh place holder just shoved me!
People without any future or hopes are the
ones you should watch out for the most.
[First place holder trying to put
the order back into the rankings.]
[Trying to enforce everyone back in line
according to their rank with a wrist slap.]
- Don't judge us like this.
- Why don't we do this instead?
Look at it this way, you can hit Jae Suk.
Then do we do it in a relay?
[Wrist slap to be done in a relay form
down the line in ranked position.]
Okay, let's start.
Go ahead and hit me.
Pass it on.
[Is he actually passing that on?]
[Confused with what's going on.]
I have no more room to fall
from where I'm standing right now.
- In that case...
- Yes?
- You two swap your spots.
- Okay, that makes more sense.
[Sixth place holder who behaved more like
seventh place holder ultimately...]
[Outraged!]
[Having the Giraffe be the youngest in
the group is desirable in many ways?]
- Yes, this works.
- Pass it on.
Are you out of your mind?
[Teaching a stiff lesson to
the mannerless youngest member.]
Don't you have any manners?
[Entering the diner after having confirmed
everyone's position in the rank.]
I'm so hungry.
[What kind of differential treatment
awaits them inside the restaurant?]
- What is this?
- What kind of a meal is it?
- They're all different.
Wow, that's a traditional formal meal!
[This is the meal table for
the first place holder.]
[Second place holder's menu.]
[Third place winner's meal.]
I love seaweed soup!
Up to fifth place holder is pretty good.
[Even though it's a humble affair,
their menu is still full of nutrition.]
- Let's all sit down.
- This is amazing.
- Is that tuna?
- Ji Hyo's isn't bad either.
[Seventh place holder, Kwang Soo's meal.]
Dong Hoon.
Just be grateful that you even got that.
I don't even get a chair?
I have to sit on this newspaper?
[His own chef carefully grilling up
the meat for him on the grill.]
He's even grilling the meat for him?
- Kwang Soo? Come here.
- Yes, Dong Hoon?
- Excuse me?
- Come here.
I feel bad about what happened,
so come over here.
[Even though it's a little late, is he
trying to reward Giraffe for his help?]
Here, just take it.
What are you doing?
- Was that not enough?
- What in the world is this?
[Big bro in first place slipping some
cabbage leaves over to his little bro.]
- Ha Ha's more generous than I thought.
- Thanks.
Can you pass some of the
meat down here?
You sure are greedy down there!
I'm sorry.
I really like how this is playing out.
I really feel like I'm going to start
crying in the middle of my meal.
Seriously!
- Would you like one of my eggs, Jae Suk?
- Yes, sure!
- Come here.
- That looks really good.
- Can I eat this?
- Sure.
- You can take the whole egg.
- Thank you so much.
You want something too?
- One of these?
- Yes, go ahead.
Thank you!
I'll wear this in the suit pocket the
next time I have to attend a wedding.
- Hey, bring that egg over here.
- No, thanks.
I'm in fourth place.
[Fourth place holder hijacking the egg?]
- Bring me the egg.
- What the heck is this?
That's so funny.
[Fourth place holder, Big-nose
acting like a neighborhood bully.]
Which one do you want?
This or this?
I'll take the fish.
[Then I'll take the fish for myself...]
Just go eat the egg.
- Jae Suk?
- Yes?
I'm going to give you this piece
because I know how much you like it.
You go on and eat that,
and I'll give you this fried egg too.
- That's an egg fried sausage.
- Thank you so much.
- Go ahead.
- Thank you.
Thank you so much!
[Making an attempt to
hijack his sausage this time.]
Give me the sausage.
This is seriously... so ridiculous.
- Okay, I got it.
- You want to lose everything or just this?
This is a pretty good spot to be in.
Hey, come here.
- What?
- Give me your water.
[Sixth place holder having learned
all the bad behavior.]
I'm thirsty!
Give me your water right now.
Let me at least keep my water!
I need that for my food because
this thing is too dry!
Jae Suk!
Wow, that was refreshing.
Since I drank your water,
I'll give you some roasted seaweed.
I have plenty of the roasted seaweed!
- You can have more of it then.
- My whole meal is wrapped up in seaweed!
[Is this what the whole world is like?]
Excuse me, fifth place holder?
Would you like a piece of sausage?
I want some sausage too.
[Love is wrapped up in fried sausages.]
- Here, you can have some.
- Thank you.
[Giving her all his sausages?]
I had too many of these sausages,
and I'm sick of them now.
- Thank you.
- Song Ji Hyo!
I had no idea that you had such a soft
and gentle voice like that.
'Thank you'.
- Was that really her voice?
- She's such a sly fox.
[This is part of fifth place holder's
surviving methods.]
- Can I have a piece?
- Why? You have a lot of side dishes.
- I'm in fourth place.
- Help me, third place!
He's trying to take my food!
Do you want to stop eating?
[Light and shadow in this
cruel, ranked world.]
Must be nice, Ji Hyo.
- Tell me if anyone else bothers you.
- Meeting a good man is the key.
It's important to meet a good man.
You really are good to your woman.
You really are acting like a real man,
looking out for your woman like that.
Mr. Gary.
Why don't you come over here?
Yes, Sir.
Maybe he'll give me something new.
[Being generous with his
delicious looking grilled ribs.]
- Thank you so much.
- You can go back to your seat now.
[Giving some meat away to
the sixth place holder as well.]
- The ribs are so good!
- Hey!
Give me your meat.
[Only way to deter that is to shove
the meat in his mouth!]
Spit it out!
[The two 40-something men fighting
over a piece of meat!]
Wow, I can't believe how fast
I ate that.
It's really nice to share a meal
with all of you like this.
- Yes.
- It's all thanks to you.
Please don't mention it.
This spot wouldn't exist without all of you.
[The members feeling the difference in their
position while seated in their ranked seats.]
- Did you all enjoy your meals?
- Yes.
- It was delicious.
- It was okay.
- It was very good.
- We will now move on to your next location.
The cameras that you all have
are different from one another.
Excuse me?
First place holder can move his camera.
[First place holder gets filmed with
a high quality ENG camera.]
[Being filmed with the ENG camera.]
I'm the first place holder.
There are two of these cameras?
[ENG camera,
and a high resolution 6mm camera.]
Am I getting filmed with this camera?
- That camera films really well!
- That's not fair!
[Second place holder-
DSLR camera and a high res 6mm camera.]
Okay, here's the camera for
the third place holder.
[Third place holder gets a
high resolution 6mm camera.]
- Here's the camera for the fourth place.
- It's the same thing.
- Isn't that the same as third place holder's?
- It's a little less in quality.
[Fourth place holder gets filmed with a
low resolution 6mm camera.]
[For fifth place holder is...
a camera attached to a helmet.]
[Sixth place holder gets a handheld
personal camera.]
[Speechless.]
As for the seventh place holder...
Do you have a cellphone?
Please tape your own footage with your phone
and make sure to get it to us later.
[If he doesn't get them the video file...
then there won't be a single shot of him.]
But the battery is almost out
on my phone!
I'm not going to be on it
much either.
[The writer hands over his own phone to
replace Kwang Soo's almost dead cellphone.]
[If I film myself like this,
will it even make the cut onto the show?]
- Hello, everyone.
- Is that even going to make it on the show?
[Seventh place holder's self-shot footage.]
- Okay, we will move onto the next location.
- Let's go!
[Fifth place holder's screen.]
I can't believe I'm having to film myself
with all these people out here.
This is my camera.
This is my only camera.
- What are they going to think of this?
- Come on!
[And here he is filming himself
sideways...]
First through third place holders can ride
in the nice car parked up front.
- What about us?
- The rest of you can ride in this car.
[A classic midsized car from 1991.]
You can turn on the air conditioning,
but if you do, the engine might die on you.
Okay.
[Which car will first through third place
holders be riding in?]
Seriously?
Look at this!
[The latest full sized sedan!]
What is this?
Let's get in.
[First place winner's seat is marked
in the best spot with his label.]
[All the comfort of a luxury car
with air conditioning!]
- This is so nice.
- This is awesome.
[The eye glaring difference between
the two cars.]
This is so nice that I don't even know
how to pull the seat up.
- Where is it?
- Gary.
It's right in front of your eyes.
[First time being in this luxury car...]
It's all automated.
- The air conditioner doesn't work.
- Try pressing the button.
[I'm sure you can figure something out...]
The engine really is starting to sputter.
The air conditioning...
- No, we can't turn the air on.
- Get your act straight.
No, I'm not joking.
We really can't turn the air on.
Hey, you don't have to do all that
since the camera is right here.
Then I'll just shoot myself.
Why are you doing that?
You can't film yourself with that.
Give me the camera.
[Trying to hijack the camera too?]
[Steaming hot inside the car.]
- Those guys gets to ride in that nice car...
- Turn the air conditioner off!
Turn off the air conditioner right now!
The engine really is going to die out
on us if we turn on the air conditioner.
- Don't turn the air on, Jae Suk.
- No, I'm not going to turn it on.
We have to make sure to rank within the first
three positions. It's too hard otherwise.
First the meal, and now the car?
- To drive around in a car without air...
- I had a kimbap triangle for lunch, okay?
What?
And I'm supposed to be riding in your seat,
but I'm driving for you instead.
What do you mean, you are?
You were in 7th, and I was in 6th position!
Hey, if we're going to talk like that,
I was in first place to begin with!
- Come on, that's enough.
- Seriously.
You two keep it down up there.
[Guys in the upper level get on
their way with ease and comfort.]
Bye!
Wow, this is...
This car drives so nice.
[Extremely satisfied and happy
with their luxury car.]
I'm going to make my way up to the top
no matter what I have to do.
It's seriously so hot in here.
Don't you think that this is
just too harsh?
- What the heck is this?
- This is seriously too much!
Are you not even going to
say anything, Ji Hyo?
Say something about how you feel.
- What do you want me to say?
- It's way too hot in here!
I don't think that we should let this go.
The wind blowing outside is
making it even hotter in here.
[Having their windows open is only helping
to blow in all the hot air from outside.]
You have to use that camera to film me.
- My phone doesn't have much battery left.
- You have to use it to film me.
- Hello.
- Can we take a picture of you?
Yes, sure.
[With their windows rolled down, everyone
driving by can watch and be amused.]
How am I supposed to use this when you have
it password locked with a code I don't know?
[I guess that's the end of Kwang Soo's
face on this episode...]
Goodbye!
[Pulling up right next to the upper crust
in their luxury car.]
That's just ridiculous.
- Wow!
- I'm so envious right now.
[Endless jealousy.]
[Nice and cool...]
[Giraffe trying to turn the
air conditioner on.]
No, don't do it!
You can't do that!
Don't turn the air conditioner on!
- You're going to get us stranded.
- I can't stand this heat!
What am I supposed to do when I
feel like I can't even breathe?
Kwang Soo, go get us some water.
Get us some ice water.
I don't have any money.
You have to film me with
that camera!
Film Jae Suk.
I can't even roll my window
down over here.
Where are we going?
[No end in sight to their driving...]
How fast are you driving?
You're only going 70km an hour
when the car is being this loud?
This is...
Whenever anything passes by next to us,
it sounds like a tiger is roaring in my ear.
Every time a car passes by next to me,
it sounds like a huge roar.
[Are you still alive?]
Hope you realize how lucky you
are right now.
Do you know how hot it is
in here right now?
[Taking his anger out on his VJ
who's riding in the car next to him.]
- We're here.
- Haven't we been here before?
- I think we were here before.
- You're right.
[Arriving at the tidal shore where
they wrestled Chu Sung Hoon.]
- This is that same tidal shore.
- Ugh, tidal shore.
[First through third place arrives at their
destination in comfort and ease.]
Do we have to change our clothes?
Wow, it's so hot.
- Kwang Soo.
- Yes, Jae Suk.
It feels a little bit cooler
when you open the door.
[Opening the door isn't going to
feel that much cooler.]
I'm just grateful that this car
even made it here.
[The Rank Determining Race-
Second mission location- Tidal Shore.]
This is your second mission of your
Rank Determination Race.
It's the Line of Rank mission.
What does it entail?
Dong Wan is going to kick
the ball in his hand.
You have to pick up the ball that he kicks,
and the person to get to the flag first wins.
You have to pull the flag out of the ground
in order for you to pass.
The winner will be determined
in the order of your arrival.
The first person to arrive and get the flag
will take over the first place.
Do you see the chaise lounge and
the parasol that is set up over there?
That's where the first place winner gets to
rest until the race is over.
- This is really...
- Wow.
I have to place within the top three
spots to make my life a little bit easier.
I really want to come in within
the first three spots.
People who haven't been in that car
don't even have the right to say anything.
Is it fourth through seventh place
that has to ride around in that car?
- Yes, of course.
- Let's win this!
[Determined to do whatever it takes
in order to avoid getting back in the car.]
Ready!
[First round of second mission.]
Set, go!
[The first place winner...]
[is going to be me!]
[Mr. Capable is first to get to the ball.]
[And everyone crowds around him.]
[He breaks through that mob
and gets up on his feet?]
[Yoo Hyuk is knocked down with
one swipe of his hand!]
[Break free!]
[Faking from left to right
just like a rugby match!]
[Huh? Where is he going?]
[Rule: Must pull out the flag!]
[Mr. Capable's energy on full force!]
[If we don't stop him, then we'll lose!]
[Mr. Capable on full power!]
[Mr. Capable,
Running Man's tower of strength!]
[A man who's strength can't be matched...]
[Will he be able to claim his throne
as first place on Running Man team?]
[He's unstoppable even with the
strength of all six members combined!]
[He has the flag!]
[Kim Jong Kook solidifies his position
in first place!]
[The ball is all crumpled in his hand.]
Give me some water!
[Kwang-retriever switching over his
loyalty to the new king of the throne.]
Here, I'll get you some water.
Are you okay?
I knew it!
Jong Kook is the winner!
[Everyone bowing down in front of
the new wielder of power.]
Wow, you did so great.
[This is how Running Man members survive.]
That's good.
Kim Jong Kook came in first
during the first round of this mission.
[There's still a chance to avoid
getting back in the steaming car!]
I can't get back in that car!
The first three spots.
Kim Jong Kook can now lie in his chaise
and rest in comfort.
How am I supposed to rest in comfort
in this state?
[Looks like you're resting
comfortable enough.]
[Second round is as fierce of a battle
as the first round seemed to have been...]
[Gary makes a touchdown!]
No!
[Kang Gary claims his spot in second place!]
- Why did you lose the ball?
- I can't believe you lost the ball.
[You guys lost the ball too!]
- Gary!
- Yes!
[Kkuk and Gary both moving up a spot
in their rank.]
It's nice to meet you again like this.
There's even a fan over here.
There's even a fan and an umbrella
over here.
[Second place winner even gets an umbrella
to protect himself against the hot sun.]
You two have no idea how good
you have it right now.
You two are so lucky not to have to
ride in that car.
[It's useless to give him nice things...]
This is like pure hell.
[A line in rank- Round three.]
- Dong Hoon is quick.
- Nice!
[I will... not ride in that car!]
[Battle for the third place is
bloodier than it ever has been!]
Everyone...
Why are you battling like your life
depends on it?
Have you forgotten who's in
first place right now?
- It's Mr. Kim Jong Kook!
- Who do you think will get swapped out?
- Of course.
- I understand.
I will work harder.
[Lee Kwang Soo solidifies his spot
in the third position.]
In third place... Lee Kwang Soo.
[Are you happy?]
Do you know who's in first place?
[The problem is...
Kim Jong Kook is in first place.]
Lee Kwang Soo, are you not going to take
your place in the third place spot?
I'll go once I feed
my master some water first.
[First place winner has the power to
swap places around for lower level people.]
- You worked hard, Kwang Soo.
- I worked hard so that I could do this.
No, it's okay.
- You dropped muddy water everywhere!
- No, I didn't!
- I can't even eat that now!
- I'll feed it to you!
[Line of rank- Round four.]
[No more places to run to!]
What the hell is this!
[A fierce and bloody battle.]
Your face looks way too clean.
[Kwang-retriever's desperate attempt
to stay alive in the race.]
We can't have that.
[Yoo Hyuk uses every ounce of
energy he has left in him!]
The master wishes to see a more
entertaining battle from all of you!
Don't you think that you're all playing
too rough with a lady in the game?
[A frontal collision.]
[Ha Ha picks up the ball Yoo Hyuk drops
and scores the touchdown!]
[Ha Ha claims his spot in fourth place!]
[Kwang-retriever's earnest fan service.]
Ji Hyo... do you really need to
go this far?
- Do you have to go this far?
- I do have to go this far!
You two are getting too touchy feely!
- You're going too far!
- You two are getting too physical!
I can't ride in that car anymore, Ji Hyo.
I can't ride in that car anymore.
Do something!
[What? Big-nose Brother takes it?]
[No way I'll let that happen!]
[Picking up the flag pieces, and the ball...
and Blank Ji wins!]
Wow, that's a fierce battle.
This is the final battle.
- Everyone...
- Yes?
The person that comes in last
during this round...
we don't know yet whether he'll be in
last place or the third place yet.
- Yes, I understand.
- We'll work very hard!
- Yes, I understand!
- Don't think of it as your last chance.
[The final battle of this mission- Go!]
Even if you lose this battle,
you could be entitled to a bonus!
- Yes!
- It depends on how well you play the game.
[Big-nose's attempt to make the game
more entertaining for the viewers.]
[How is it that the two oldest
members of the team...]
No.
No, I can't get back in that car.
You're going to have to get back
in that car anyway.
[The only way to avoid getting back in
that car is to earn that man's favor...]
There you go!
That's it!
[45 year olds tear wrenching
tidal shore show.]
[Pulling out all the stops in
their desperate attempt.]
You can't grab it!
Your reach is too short!
[Does this look like an act?]
You're flailing your arm out towards
the flag! There you go!
Reach for the flag!
There you go!
[Yoo Hyuk pulls out the flag!]
[Yoo Hyuk earns his spot in sixth place.]
[And Big-nose confirms his spot
in seventh place.]
[It's now time for the first place winner
to wield his power over ranking.]
- Right here.
- Yes, I want to ride in that car.
Me!
- Please, Sir...
- I'd be grateful, Sir.
Whenever the Monday Couple is together...
our fans really seem to love that.
I would like for Lee Kwang Soo and
Song Ji Hyo to swap out their spots.
[Third place Lee Kwang Soo to swap
with Fifth place, Song Ji Hyo.]
- Thank you.
- Sure.
- You're being so compliant and polite today.
- Come down here.
- Coming in at third place has no meaning.
- Coming in at third doesn't matter.
- Fine, let's do this.
[Running Man's ranking, 3 years in the making!
Let's see how far we can take this today!]
I'm going to put my life on the line
to come in at top three.
- You already did that the last round.
- You're right. What does that even matter?
I really hate how this feels to have to
come back down after being at the top.
Yeah, it sucks.
What if the next first place winner is here?
We have to look out for each other.
[The lower rank people vowing to look out
for each other in their steamy car.]
We can't even catch up to that car.
[They can't even keep up with
the staff car, who's their guide back.]
- You can't go too fast in this.
- I can see the steam rising.
This isn't a car we're riding in.
It's basically a desert.
- I wore this long sleeved top on purpose.
- Why?
- Because the sun's burning my arm.
- I know.
I wanted to ride back in that car
no matter what I had to do.
How desperate do you think I felt
to beg for this cup of ice water?
[Meanwhile...]
[The upper crust arrives at the airport
in their luxury car.]
[Helicopters?]
[First through third place holders are
first to board their choppers.]
[Just where are they being taken to
that they need to get on the helicopter?]
[Blank Ji is the only person excited about
the flight enough to take pictures.]
[And up they go!]
[I'm so scared!]
[Just where are they headed to next?]
[Cool and refreshing scenery that can be
seen outside their window!]
[Ji Hyo, holding onto their hands to
help calm down their fears.]
[As for the other group...
well, you can see for yourselves.]
[The rest of the group also
takes flight off the ground!]
[Over the mountain... and over the ocean?]
[Flying over the ocean, and past Incheon...]
[to arrive on a beautiful island.]
[But... there's a hidden secret
on this island!]
[A pirate ship?]
[In a few moments...]
[The hidden secrets on
this island will be revealed.]
[A refreshing beach to chase
some of the stifling heat away...]
[First through third place holders
are the first ones to arrive on the beach!]
What is this now?
What is this?
Your next game is...
Upward mobility quiz battle.
What?
A quiz?
All of you will formulate
your own questions.
You just need to gather up the knowledge that
you already have for the questions.
You may get started before
the others arrive.
Gary, that seat is designated for
the first place holder.
Can I sit over here?
[The rest of the group finally arrives.]
[These guys have to come up with
their own quiz questions as well.]
What is this?
What kind of questions should
I come up with?
I can't even think of any questions
since there's not much that I know.
No one would know the answer to this question
unless they're really a giraffe lover.
[All seven members complete their own
list of questions!]
I really have to win this round.
- This could be our last chance!
- Let's do this and move up in the rank!
- First up, Ji Suk Jin in seventh place.
- Yes?
You will step forward
to ask your question first.
And the rest of you will write down your
answer in the sketchbook that you have.
Once everyone has written down
the answer
you will close your sketchbooks
and the questioner will observe
the rest of the group's eyes,
and behavior to determine
the one person that he thinks did not
answer the question right
and call them out to the front
and challenge their answer.
In the case that the person chosen
answers the question correctly...
the banana boat Ji Suk Jin will be sitting on
will get pulled out to the water right away.
But if the person chosen has the wrong answer,
then that person will be the one to go.
After the first round of questioning,
the sixth place holder will then take his turn.
[Battle of their knowledge-
Who will take the top spot in this battle?]
This is a cartoon movie question.
- What is it?
- In the early 70's...
What is he doing?
- What kind of a question is that?
- This is my question.
- What year were you born in, Kwang Soo?
- I was born in '65.
You were born in '85, right?
I'll keep that in mind.
There's a cartoon that was a huge hit
amongst the children back in the early 70s.
- Yes, we know.
- It was called, 'The Ghost Man'.
- Yes, I know that one.
- You know that one, right?
[A cartoon where a family of ghosts
were the main characters of the show.]
With it being a horror cartoon theme,
this show traumatized many kids...
- Maybe that's not the right word.
- What do you mean, traumatized?
Were you traumatized by the show then?
What do you mean?
That cartoon didn't traumatize any kids.
Please write down the names of the
three main characters from that show.
The name of all three characters?
You all know the answer
to this question, right?
I'll accept the answer if you can correctly
come up with two out of the three names.
Kwang Soo was born in '85?
[Kid born in '85 who probably
doesn't know the answer.]
I remember seeing that cartoon.
- I remember seeing that.
- Song Ji Hyo.
- Do you know the cartoon I'm referring to?
- Yes.
- Did you think that they were scary looking?
- Yes, I just remembered what they look like.
You look very confident in yourself.
[Does Ji Hyo really know the answer?]
- You're so shameless with your lying.
- She really is.
Who amongst us wouldn't know
the answer to this question?
Do you know what it is?
[Just which one of them wrote down
the wrong answer?]
Should I play it safe with Kwang Soo,
or take the risk and go with Gary?
Kang Gary, come out here!
Let's go!
[Seventh place holder is challenging
the second place holder!]
Why am I always the one
to get dunked in the water?
[First thing first-
They both get aboard the banana boats.]
Now, Ji Suk Jin will first reveal
the correct answer to his question.
[Suk Jin to reveal his answer first.]
[Bam, Vera, Vero.]
[Being similar in age, Jae Suk
answers the question correctly!]
- Gary.
- Yes?
[Time for Gary to reveal his answer.]
[Who will take over the second place spot?]
[Gary, Gil, Leessang.]
[Gary- wrong answer!]
[A ride on the banana boat for
getting the wrong answer!]
- I had no idea what the answer was.
- That was really hard.
[This is now Suk Jin's new seat.]
I knew the right answer.
Why did it have to be me!
Life can be changed in one
single moment!
[Second place, Gary is swapped out with
seventh place, Suk Jin.]
[Yoo Hyuk is currently seated
in the first place throne.]
- This question... is about nature.
- Wow... nature?
Giraffes are...
known for having the highest, what?
What is the highest thing that they're known
to have because of their long necks?
- Giraffes has the highest, what?
- The highest thing that they're known for?
Isn't that too easy of a question?
[Giraffes are known for having the
highest 'what' because of their long necks?]
[The correct answer is... 'blood pressure'.]
[They're known to have the highest blood
pressure to get the blood up their long necks.]
It's high, you say?
How many letters in the answer?
Less than three.
- Yes!
- I know the right answer.
I know what the two letter answer is.
I got the right answer.
This must be it.
I feel bad for Kwang Soo.
I feel like everyone knows the answer.
How many characters in those two letters?
The two letters both have
three characters.
[Hm...]
- I already know the answer to this.
- Suk Jin.
- Yes.
- In those two letters...
is 'P' a part of the character used or not?
No, it's not used.
[Uh oh...]
What about 'S'?
- It's used.
- Come out here, Song Ji Hyo!
Lee Kwang Soo,
please reveal your answer.
[Lee Kwang Soo's correct answer-
Blood pressure.]
Song Ji Hyo, your answer?
[What did Ji Hyo come up with
as her answer?]
[Blood pressure- Correct!]
What?
Me?
[Challenger Kwang Soo is off
on his boat ride!]
[Ace Ji Hyo having pretended not to
know the answer even when she knew!]
[A forceful plunge into the water!]
- Ji Hyo knew the answer!
- Ji Hyo knew!
- I didn't think Ji Hyo knew.
- Ji Hyo was faking!
Yeah, she faked it.
[Time to tally up all the gold coins
that they've gained so far.]
I have 11.
- Why does Gary have so many?
- Gary has a lot.
- I have 14.
- Wow!
- I have nine.
- Nine.
I have 14.
I have 14, too.
I have eight.
- How does he have eight?
- How did you get that many?
[His count sounds a little fishy...]
We will now determine the final
ranking of your positions.
[Using the number of coins to determine
the final ranking of their positions.]
The four of you with the 14 coins,
please step over to the side.
[A total of four people with 14 coins!]
[The four people who've worked hard all day
are feeling excited about their standing!]
Am I still in last place even with
these two that I stole away?
In the order of your win from the last round,
Song Ji Hyo is in the top spot.
Then am I in second place?
Then Kang Gary, Ha Ha, and
Kim Jong Kook.
[Ji Hyo, Gary, Ha Ha, Jong Kook,
Jae Suk, Suk Jin, and Kwang Soo.]
- What the heck!
- I can't believe I'm in first place.
- Give me your third place badge.
- You never know what could happen in life.
What the heck is this?
- Then I'm in fifth place?
- Who gets my fourth place badge?
So if I hadn't taken this from Gary's bag,
he would've come in at first place?
What?
You stole my coins?
[Traitorous Giraffe having stolen two coins
from Gary's bag when he wasn't looking.]
We were told to keep it safe,
but Gary left his bag next to me.
Starting with the first place winner...
Do you see the treasure ship behind you?
[Treasure ship?]
Look!
It's a pirate ship!
Wow, that is a pirate ship!
[Something... is coming
into their view on the water!]
[A black ship gliding towards them
on top of the water...]
[Just what is the identity of this ship
that appeared suddenly out of nowhere?]
- What is that?
- Is that really a pirate ship?
- That's our ship.
- Really?
The Black Pearl?
- Oh my goodness.
- That's your ship?
[The mysterious black ship...
What is the secret that it carries?]
[Starting with first place winner...]
[Everyone will have a chance to board the
ship and increase the amount of their gold!]
- Wow, what is this?
- This is so cool.
- Then can we lose it too?
- You'll find out once you're on-board.
- Then I'll go first.
- We have to go on-board to find out?
Good luck, Miss Blank.
[Ji Hyo is the first to head off
towards the black ship.]
Okay, good luck.
[Just what awaits them on that boat?]
You don't think that they'll kidnap
Ji Hyo, do you?
[Nervous...]
[Ji Hyo is getting closer and closer
towards the black ship...]
Wow!
It's so dark in here.
What is this?
- Second place holder may get going.
- Okay.
Wait... you're pirates!
Why are you doing this to me?
[Taking the pouch full of her gold
away from her!]
That's my gold!
I worked so hard to earn that gold!
All of the other members are heading
here without knowing what awaits them...
Why is it so dark in here?
What's going on in here?
What is this?
What the heck?
That's my gold!
[Gary has his 14 pieces of gold
taken away from him as well.]
What is this?
I don't know either.
They took my gold away from me too.
[Everyone who boards the ship is
taken hostage by the pirates!]
I thought we were going to get the
chance to earn more gold!
[The pirates are taking all their gold away!]
This is a pirate ship.
No!
[That's what you think.]
[All of Running Man's gold is
taken away from them!]
What is this?
- What's going on? Where are we going?
- What's happening to us?
[The ship... is moving?]
Please!
Please let us go!
[The next morning...]
[The mysterious pirate ship
full of their stolen gold.]
[The occupants of that boat have
been on that boat the whole time...]
[The pirate ship sailing the ocean
once again in search for more gold.]
[The hostages being taken against their will
after having their gold taken from them.]
We don't have any money.
You've already taken
all of our money away from us.
[It's time to meet the owner of this ship.]
- Get up there.
- We have no money.
Let the first three...
I mean first place spots live.
[Welcome, Running Man!]
[We are the owners of this ship!]
[Shinhwa.]
[Eric]
[Min Woo]
[Jun Jin]
[Hye Sung]
[Andy]
[The owners of this ship-
Top Idol Group in Korea, Shinhwa!]
Hurry up and get up here!
- Are you seriously going to be like this?
- What are you guys doing?
[A scary atmosphere?]
Wow!
It's Shinhwa!
Hello!
We're pirates!
No, you're Shinhwa.
What are you talking about?
We are... pirates!
[Look at these guys...]
Don't you recognize me, Eric?
We are... pirates!
- Look at these guys.
- Where's the other guy?
Where's Dong Wan?
We dunked him in the ocean.
[It's a good thing that they're
nice pirates.]
Why did you take our gold away from us?
- Your gold is now in our possession.
- Where did you guys put it?
Right here.
- You want me to open it for you?
- Why can't you open it?
[For a pirate, his strength is a bit...]
- Can you open this for me?
- Say 'please'.
What kind of a pirate are you?
[What?]
[What happened to yesterday's gold?]
[The curse in the movie,
'Pirates of the Caribbean'...]
[All their gold has turned into scrap metal!]
There was gold in there last night.
[A letter inside the chest?]
There's a letter.
[There you go.]
- Give it to Ji Hyo to read.
- You shouldn't have given that to them.
We have to stay in charge here.
The curse of the tides.
- Is it the tidal shores again?
- The curse of the tides?
Your treasure has been cursed.
Through a series of competitions,
you will be given hints to lift the curse.
The winning team will be given a useful clue,
and the losing team, an ambiguous one.
The first team to gather up all the hints to
lift the curse will take all of the treasure.
No!
That enough.
Give it a rest.
- We have to find our treasure.
- What is the matter with you?
So we have to compete against each other
to take over the treasure?
But there are only five members on
the Shinhwa Team, so what do we do?
- I know.
- Then I'll join this team.
- I think five of them would be plenty.
- Why are you saying that?
That is true though.
The way I see it, these guys...
- These guys are really competitive.
- We love competition.
Seriously though,
it's not just that they're competitive
but even when we they did that bungee jump,
they were all so fearless about it.
[Fierce competitors who know
no fear when it comes to competing.]
- Hye Sung and Andy over here...
- He's like a superman.
Andy's super athletic.
- They're all too good.
- I normally wouldn't say this...
but these guys are just fine
to compete against the seven of us.
If anything, it's better that Dong Wan
isn't with you guys today.
He's like a sink hole amongst us.
Isn't he really strong though?
Let's just do the race the way
we're grouped right now?
- No, I don't know.
- Can we do that?
I think this setup is just fine if
we're going to compete with Shinhwa.
I can smell the blood in the air today.
But Eric really suits his character today.
[Eric looks as though he can be included
in the cast of a pirate movie.]
- You can be in a pirate movie.
- Yeah, you look like you'd fit perfectly.
You look really handsome.
- He's always been good looking.
- He's always been handsome.
But he wasn't this good looking in the past.
He looks like he's gotten even
better looking.
Okay, we lost.
[Off they go to lift
the curse off of their treasure!]
There it is!
[Appearing in front of their eyes...]
[is a scene of wild, natural beauty!]
[A grassy sandbank in the middle of the ocean
acting as the ocean's own desert!]
[Mystical sandy island that shows
the grandeur and beauty twice a day!]
[Running Man and Shinhwa touches shore.]
- This is like a work of art.
- I can't believe a place like this exists.
So this is underwater part of the day?
You didn't make this island
just for the show, did you?
[The first leg of their journey to lift
the curse off of their treasure!]
[Just who will get their hands
on the real treasure?]
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Next Week]
[Running Man vs. Shinhwa-
The beginning of a ferocious battle.]
[The fierce and formidable sportsman.]
[The fiercest enemies with 15 years
of teamwork history between them.]
[The battle of the fiercest.]
[Fateful battle that cannot be avoided.]
[The battle between the real hunters.]
The game is all over.
[We'll determine who the best is
here today!]
The curse of the tides.
Your treasure has been cursed.
The first team to lift the curse
can keep all the treasure.
[In order to get the treasure,
obtain the item from the 'Undead'.]
These people are so scary.
Running Man really are Running Man.
It's mine!
[Pirates of the Western Sea.]