[A double agent's mission!
Infiltrate into the depths of your enemy!]
[Two teams and two identities.]
[But the truth that they weren't aware of!]
[If the right handed man someone
that they could trust?]
[Running Noir 'Double Agent', starts now!]
Subtitles by DramaFever
[One rainy winter day in 2013.]
[SBS Broadcasting station in Seoul.]
[PD waiting for someone
on top of the roof.]
[And making his entrance...]
[One man full of dignity and
majestic air...]
[The person who's come all the way
up to the dizzying heights is...]
Hello.
[Hwang Jung Min]
[Something is being handed over.]
[And exchanging a conversation with
the PD in charge...]
[A moment later...]
[Someone else...]
[Gar... Gary?]
[Kang Hee Gun]
I'm not supposed to be here, right?
Is that Jung Min?
It is Jung Min!
- Oh!
- What are you doing here?
[Enthusiastically greeting one another.]
I knew that it was Jung Min
just from looking at his back.
- Hi, Gary.
- Jung Min, what are you doing here?
- I came to play.
- You're all wet. You been here long?
Then does this mean Jung Min
and I are a team?
[If Jung Min had been waiting for Gary...]
I think I'm going to need your help.
[Help?]
You are our team's... spy.
Really?
[What... a spy?]
[You can do it, right?]
[At the same time, by Han River...]
[Someone is getting out of the car.]
Why have you...
asked to see me so covertly?
[Kim Jong Kook]
[Song Ji Hyo]
You're a spy today.
And you have to do your best
so that our team can win.
First...
- Let me see who else is coming.
- Get yourself together!
- You have to concentrate right now!
- Why are you yelling?
It's time to concentrate.
Who cares about anyone else coming?
No matter who else comes...
Today's Running Man will be divided into
'Actor Team' and 'Singer Team'...
and that's how we'll be
playing our games today.
- Hwang Jung Min will be on the Actor Team.
- Yes.
- And of course, Gary will be...
- Well, I do a bit of acting too...
- Of course I'll be on the Singer Team.
- Yes, you'll be on the Singer Team.
You're the spy that's been sent
over to the Singer Team
by the head of Actor Team,
Hwang Jung Min.
[Head of Actor Team, Jung Min dispatches
Kang Hee Gun to the Singer Team as a spy.]
[Don't let the enemies find out
about your true identity.]
Kim Jong Kook will be the Team Leader
for the Singer Team.
And Song Ji Hyo is
the spy for the Singer Team.
[Ji Hyo is the spy for the Singer Team
while undercover in the Actor Team.]
Be a part of the Actor Team and
be the spy for the Singer Team.
[Be a part of the Actor Team and
be the spy for the Singer Team!]
Kim Jong Kook's Singer Team needs to win
in order for Song Ji Hyo to win too.
Do you understand?
I... I mean, I will be the spy...
but I've never lasted
for more than five minutes.
It's because you keep fumbling with
your words like you're doing now!
You'll be fine if you don't say anything.
Just don't do anything.
- I understand.
- Okay?
- Then I really am a spy today?
- You're a spy.
Thank you, Jung Min!
You have no idea how much I've been
wanting to be a spy.
[Two boys immersed in the spy game.]
[The last order is...
to keep his eyes wide open.]
I've been betrayed a lot before,
but at least for today...
- Life is all about betrayals!
- Yes, you're right!
Then I'll continue on with
betrayal being my goal for the day.
- I will show them what 'betray' really means.
- I really hope that you do.
Please don't worry.
This is Running Man,
and Running Man has given us a mission.
And your role for today is to be the spy.
- Our lives are all about betrayals.
- Yes, you're right.
You just need to do this earnestly.
Then you're... going to win today.
We're just people following the orders
given by our mission today, Ji Hyo.
[Will Spy Ji Hyo and Spy Gary...]
[The victory is ours!]
Let's do this.
[Undoubtedly... the victory will be ours.]
Let's go.
Open up our umbrellas.
[The two teams vying for the victory...]
[And the two spies infiltrating
into each other's teams.]
[Spy vs. Spy]
[An hour later]
[Han River waterfront]
How can it be so cold?
[Members huddling together for warmth
as soon as they see each other.]
- How can it be this cold?
- Ugh, it's so cold!
- It's freezing out here!
- The wind feels like knife cuts.
- So cold!
- Wow, it's cold...
[Fashion is all about confidence?]
- Where did you get that?
- You look so funny, Gary!
[Inciting a huge response just by
donning on a hat.]
Flip it back like this.
- You're Gae-roro! Gae-roro!
- I don't care how ugly it is!
- Staying warm is what's most important!
- It's Gae-roro!
He's Gae-roro.
We have very special guests who'll
be joining us today.
[As I'm sure you already know who
one of them is going to be...]
They'll make their entrance once you're
ready, so please welcome them.
- We're ready.
- We're ready!
- Please come on out.
- Come on out!
[Braving the bitter cold of the winter...]
[To join Running Man as today's guest.]
- Who is it?
- Here it comes! Here comes the car.
[Inside the black luxury car...]
- Who is that? It looks like a guy.
- It's a guy?
It's a guy!
[And another person!]
[Having received critical acclaims for his
acting in 'Baker King, Kim Tak Goo']
[Actor, Park Sung Woong]
[The two are the guests for the day after
having met on the set of their new film.]
- What?
- Is that who I think it is?
[Jae Suk's friend, Sung Woong
makes his appearance.]
[And Hwang Jung Min!]
It's so cold!
- Hurry up and get out of the car!
- What the heck?
What's taking him so long?
- Jung Min, come on!
- Hurry up and get out here!
[Top level actor who's playful side is
still the same as ever.]
- It's so cold out here!
- We all know it's cold!
It's been so long!
- It's so great to see you!
- We haven't seen you in so long!
[With the cold weather,
they keep the greeting short and sweet.]
[Greeting Blank Ji enthusiastically since
they recently wrapped up a film together.]
What brings you on the show today?
It's so good to see you!
[Making sure to greet everyone
even with the cold weather.]
- Sung Woong, it's so good to see you!
- It's freezing out here!
- Sung Woong used to be volleyball player.
- Really?
Volleyball, as in this?
If you used to be a volleyball player,
how about landing a spike on his cheek?
- I came to get Jong Kook.
- Jong Kook?
[Mr. Capable has become
a common target for everyone.]
Okay, since there are nine of you
right now...
- Yes.
- There are nine of you right now.
That's why since you're being split up into
two teams, there will be one more guest here.
- There's still hope!
- Is it a woman?
I have a good feeling about this guest.
- It's freezing!
- It's really cold.
What's taking so long?
- Here it comes!
- Look, it's a sports car!
[A red sports car that
grabs all their attention?]
[And that woman is none other than...]
[4Minute's Hyuna]
- It's Hyuna!
[The heroine of the world renowned
music video, 'Gangnam Style'...]
[The choreographer of the
sexy yet powerful dance, Hyuna.]
It's Hyuna!
- What are you doing here?
- You must be freezing!
Hyuna! You're going to freeze
dressed like that!
- Are you even of the sound mind?
- You're saying you're not cold?
No, I'm freezing!
- Don't you even know how cold it is?
- Hyuna! It's Hyuna!
[An awkward greeting between
the singer and actors.]
Shake her hand.
- Why can't you look her in the eye?
- Sung Woong, say hi to her.
[Jung Min keeps on greeting her while
averting his eyes elsewhere.]
Why do you keep looking elsewhere
as you're saying hello?
- It's because I'm so cold!
- Because you're cold?
Since I'm sure you're all very cold right now,
I will announce the two teams first.
As I mentioned earlier,
you will be divided into two teams.
It will be
Actor Team vs. the Singer Team.
- That will be the two teams.
- What about the comedians?
I will start by announcing
the Actor Team members first.
The Team Leader will be
Hwang Jung Min.
[Actor Team's Team Leader is
Hwang Jung Min.]
And the first team member is,
Park Sung Woong.
And... Song Ji Hyo.
And finally...
- Weren't you in a movie?
- Yes, I was in a movie!
- And lastly...
- You're putting Kwang Soo in the Actor Team?
- Since Lee Kwang Soo is an actor...
- No way!
- He's a comedian!
- How am I a comedian?
- Lee Kwang Soo is the next member.
- I was in a movie too!
And the final member is, Yoo Jae Suk.
[What? Jae Suk on the Actor Team?]
Even though I'm sure that you may all know,
back in the day, Yoo Jae Suk...
[I guess... he has some experience with
being in a movie a very long time ago.]
No way!
[His brief appearance in
'The Space Monsters'.]
The mission that all of you
will have to carry out today...
is a mission that your boss...
Go Dong Wan will be giving you.
Today's mission is...
A bloody bag acquisition race.
[A bloody bag acquisition race]
[Carry out the mission at each location...]
[And the winning team will earn hints to where
the bag is hidden at the final location.]
The first team to find all seven bags at
the final location and get them to the boss
will be the ultimate
winning team of the day.
[We will win!]
- Why are you guys singing?
- Let's say a cheers!
With each mission that your
team wins
you will be given hints to where
those seven bags are hidden.
So it's important for you to
win these missions.
I understand.
[Bloody bag acquisition race - Start!]
I feel like we're going on a picnic.
Want to go somewhere?
Where do you...
what do you mean, go somewhere?
You really like
getting out of the house.
[Full of joy whenever he's out
of the house?]
At least Kwang Soo's been in movies,
but I...
Weren't you in a drama once?
Maybe you're like our manager
for the day.
What are you talking about?
Kwang Soo... Ji Hyo knew it.
I used to be in parody dramas.
[His parodies that used to be
shown every week.]
- That's what I used to do.
- Yes, you did do that.
- We have to go to Hongdae first.
- Hongdae?
Go to the streets of Hongdae
and find the Running Man landmark.
Kwang Soo, don't you know your way
around Hongdae pretty well?
Yes, I really like Hongdae.
- Hongdae isn't what you like.
- Then what is it?
I'm sure it's the women in Hongdae
that you like.
It's because you keep teasing me like this
that I can't even date.
- What do you mean, you can't?
- Kwang Soo really like girls?
- He loves girls.
- Honey?
- It's no joke how much he loves them.
- Honey... hilarious!
- Why are you so suddenly...
- What is he doing?
- Why are you calling your wife so suddenly?
- What is Sung Woong doing?
[Actress, Shin Eun Jung]
My wife just called, so I had to answer.
- Yes, go ahead.
- We're filming right now though.
You should just apologize and tell her
that you'll call her back later.
But how can you just say honey,
and answer the phone instead?
Above all else, it's phone calls from
the wife that shouldn't be answered.
Jung Min, you really are something else.
- It's not because he doesn't love her.
- Of course not.
- It's because this is work.
- I have a honey too.
Jung Min, everyone has
their own style.
Jung Min, did you know that Sung Woong used
to be a volleyball player back in the day?
No, I didn't know that.
And Sung Woong trained for a long time
at the action school too.
That's why Sung Woong provoked
Jong Kook as soon as he arrived earlier.
I'm not sure if Jung Min's good at games,
I don't really remember.
You have no idea how charismatic Jung Min is
on site when we're shooting the film.
- Jung Min...
- Hey, where are you going?
- Oh my goodness.
- That car was just slowing down.
- Ugh, you really scared me.
- You have a lot of fear, don't you?
As soon as Sung Woong tells us
about how charismatic you can be...
[Charisma pulling a disappearing act.]
Is Jung Min really like that on movie sets?
Really?
Yes, he's really amazing.
Oh... I've never once seen that side
of him while shooting variety shows.
I think he's very good at
fitting into the environment he's in.
So that's why his name is
Hwang Jung Min...
[What was that?]
Hey, that's why his name is
Hwang Jung Min.
- Go to the streets of Hongdae...
- It's Hongdae.
- There it is!
- Look... there it is.
- Let's go!
- Let's get out.
[Even in the midst of cold winter rain,
the streets are still busy and bustling.]
Okay, you're the first team to arrive.
The Singer Team.
- Singer?
- Yes, he is a singer.
I made my debut back in 1991.
'Secret mission'- Find the members who are
undercover and get them dressed?
What does that mean?
From each of the teams...
[Pick one person who's confident in
their abilities at finding people.]
[And the remaining four members will stay
in hiding at their designated spots.]
- Yes, then what?
- We've already designated your locations.
You have to choose one person
who's going to go on the search.
[Undercover?]
[Search and find all your team members that
are in hiding around the streets of Hongdae!]
- Don't you think Gary would be good at this?
- Do you know your area around Hongdae well?
- Yes, I know it very well.
- Okay, then let's go with Gary.
- I used to hang out here a lot.
- Okay, then let's choose Gary.
- We choose Jung Min.
- Then I just need to find you guys?
- Yes, you just need to find us.
- Okay then.
Then, why don't we have the searchers
come out here? Jung Min and Gary.
Don't these two give off a similar vibe?
[The feeling is a bit...]
- Why are you saying that?
- I'm curious as to who's going to win.
I get a very similar vibe
coming from those two.
Then the rest of you will be going to the
location we've designated for you.
Those of you who will be hiding...
please take off your coats right now.
- What?
- Huh?
[The searcher will go around looking for his
teammates while wearing his coat.]
And the moment you find one,
you give them a coat.
- Okay, let's do this quickly.
- Let's do this. Go! Go!
As soon as a person is found,
that person has to go in the ladder.
Okay, we get it!
Unless it's in order,
we won't get in the ladder.
Now, since it's cold,
why don't you all say a cheer before...
- What the heck are you saying!
- It's cold. Let's hurry!
Okay, numbers two through five,
go towards the back and you'll see a car.
[The members who are to hide
heads off first.]
- Find us quickly!
- Fighting!
Sung Woong, fighting.
Here's the map to the designated areas
where your teammates will be waiting.
[A map where their teammates are hiding...]
[Only the locations are marked,
but there aren't any numbers!]
If you find number three when you're supposed
to find two, you can't pick up that person.
Jung Min...
[Now that we take a look...]
For now...
I'll work hard at the first couple games.
- I've got a great idea!
- What?
Whenever you and I see each other,
we'll just...
- Like this?
- It'll be our sign.
I understand.
If others see us doing that, they'll
think that we're greeting each other.
- We'll just... say that's our greeting.
- A greeting we've always done.
Jong Kook... what should we do?
How should we do this?
- Do I have to keep losing at everything?
- No. No, you don't.
You need to get close to the team members,
and get me whatever information you can.
So get me whatever information
you can.
- Really?
- Of course.
I'll signal to you like this
if I want you to lose a game.
Ah... that's your sign for me to lose?
Jung Min... depending on the situation...
Depending on the situation,
I'll lose if I can.
Then I'd be grateful.
But if there's no way around it, I may
have to win since it's the first game.
[Okay... since we can't get caught,
let's just play it by ear!]
[The important thing is information
on the other team!]
[Going undercover is complete!]
- Gary...
- Yes?
- Let's at least do our thing.
- Okay.
[Heading off to find
their Teammate number two!]
Wait...
[Could this real estate office...
be the one on the map?]
- Is this the place?
- No, this isn't it.
[Team Leader Hwang heading on
without a slightest bit of hesitation.]
What if this is number five?
I feel like this is going to
be number five.
- Number five...
- I'm just going to keep on following you!
- We're number two!
- You're here!
[Discovers number two while
on their way!]
[Putting the coat back on quickly...]
Here, put your coat on.
You were standing out in the rain?
- We've just been standing out here.
- You've been standing in the rain?
- There's a real estate office!
- Where?
- There. Up there.
- Watch your feet... be careful.
[Could number three be towards
the real estate office?]
Don't you think it would be around here?
Oh! there it is!
[Oh? But that's number four...]
What the heck? This isn't it.
It's not time for you yet.
- You're number four.
- Number four is over here!
- Jong Kook, it's not Hyuna. Not Hyuna.
- It's not Hyuna! Not her turn yet.
Where are those guys going?
I see someone over there.
- You see someone?
- Jung Min, I'm over here!
- He's number five! Keep going!
[Huh? Number five team is...]
- No, it's not time for them yet!
- Wait.. wait right there.
We need number three!
- Kwang Soo, what number are you?
- I'm three! Go to your left!
[With the exception of number three,
they've discovered four and five...]
How is Jung Min supposed to find me when
we're hiding so far back like this?
There's no way they're going to
be able to find us here.
[Automatically breaking out the boxing
moves from the frigid weather.]
- Have you boxed before or something?
- Of course!
[Their playfulness makes it impossible
for them to hide out in quiet.]
[Joking around with one another
as if they were back to being little kids.]
Do you have to change the tape
on that thing?
[A surprise attack!]
Jae Suk, your shoelace is untied.
Oh, hi there!
[Nonstop...]
You can't beat that, can you?
[Their lightning fast kisses.]
- This is exhausting!
- I'm exhausted!
- There it is!
- This is it!
[Finally discovers three!]
- There they come!
- What the heck?
How did you find us here?
There they are!
They're here!
[Singer Team also arrives]
- Come on, hurry up!
- Okay, I'm done.
Okay, let's go.
We're good to go, right?
[Actor Team heads out first by
split of a second difference.]
We can't go like this.
- We have to go horizontally.
- How did you find us?
- We were given a map.
- You had a map?
- We have a map.
- Ah, you have a map?
We saw everyone else
on our way here.
We can just follow them.
Let's hurry.
Let's hurry up and follow them.
- Let's follow them.
- One, two! One, two!
- Run... run!
- Let's stay strong guys. Stay strong!
- Fighting!
Wait...
- I feel like I'm going to collapse.
- Stay strong... stay strong.
[Is Gary in his full operation mode?]
That place we thought earlier
must be the right place.
Hurry!
We have to run faster.
- Jong Kook!
- What?
- Don't you think they'll be to the left?
- No, we have to go right.
- Isn't Hyuna the last one?
- No, it's not Hyuna.
- Suk Jin is the last one.
- Suk Jin is last.
[Team Leader Kkuk
not getting roped in very easily...]
[Actor Team heading to where
number four is waiting!]
No!
- Are you leaving?
- Yeah.
Don't go...
[Attacking him with her gaze.]
Hyuna won't let me go.
- What?
- She doesn't want me to go.
So you're not going to come?
[She's got her hold on me,
what am I supposed to do...]
- Come on!
- Just come.
[Team Leader Hwang's screaming order!]
- Come on, hurry!
- Does he really have to go?
It's really been a long time since
something like this has happened to me.
- What is?
- It really has been a long time.
- Hurry up and come on!
- But she doesn't want me to go.
Kwang Soo, please don't go.
- They're coming. Let's go.
- They're here.
- They're here. I have to go.
- Wait...
- Hyuna...
- Look what you did.
- Hurry up! Hurry!
- I was holding onto Kwang Soo.
We have to walk horizontally.
- Let's go horizontally.
- Hyuna, it's been fun.
- Hurry.
- Don't forget me, okay?
[The gap between the two teams are
closing in from Hyuna's little trap.]
[Walking down the main street of Hongdae
in the rain with the ladder.]
- Is this the place?
- This way... it's this way.
[Arrives at the location where
their fifth team member is waiting!]
Come on, hurry.
Here, put your coat on.
How did you guys get here so quickly?
[Singer Team also arrives at the location.]
[All they have to do now is
to get to the finish line!]
[Kkuk with a tight grip on the
other team!]
[You're not going anywhere!]
[After obstructing their path...
overtakes them in the race!]
[Heading towards the finish line!]
[The final flag!]
[The Singer Team is first to arrive!]
[It's not over yet.]
It's not over yet.
Please take your mission.
['Undercover mission'- Quickly
move the beans with the chopsticks.]
Challenge!
[Starting from the right to the left,
and back to the right to succeed.]
Kwang Soo...
you have to be careful and fast.
Kwang Soo!
- Kwang Soo!
- Hey, brat!
Hurry!
[Passes after quite some time...]
[And the Singer Team is caught up
during Hyuna's turn.]
- Hyuna!
- Hyuna's from the fork generation.
What do I do?
- Hyuna, come on...
- I got it!
- That's right, that's right.
- I'm not used to these chopsticks.
[Gary's overtly obvious
fumble with the chopsticks.]
What's wrong with you?
You're good at this!
[Sneaking in a look to see
how the other team is doing.]
Please!
[This team is still stuck on Jae Suk...]
Hey!
[Finally passes it on to Ji Hyo.]
Ji Hyo... Ji Hyo!
[Is he trying to eat it?]
[Blood curdling screams at
the drop of one little bean.]
[Quickly moving it back to the right.]
We need to get it back to my plate.
[Quickly getting it
all the way back to Jae Suk!]
[Drops it! Darn!]
Seriously...
[While Jae Suk tries to grab
the bean that he dropped...]
[The bean gets passed back to Gary.]
- Lift it. Lift it off the plate.
- Slide it to the side and get it.
It's not easy to lift.
[Trying to lose the game without
making it so obvious....]
[Spy Gary trying to stall some time.]
[Finally moves the bean on to Hyuna.]
[How is the other team doing?]
[It's still Kwang Soo's turn...]
[Will Kwang Soo be first?
Or will it be Hyuna?]
[Hyuna is the first to succeed
at moving the bean!]
Are we done?
[Singer Team wins!]
[Darn...]
[The main culprits of their defeat,
Yoo-Lee Brothers.]
- Are you not good with chopsticks?
- No, that's not it.
- It's the Singer Team's win.
- Yeah!
Move back, and you come here.
It's not me!
It really isn't me!
[Team Leader Hwang's style is to scold
those who needs scolding.]
It's not him. Jae Suk is the one
who dropped the bean.
- It wasn't me.
- Really?
If I had just dropped it on his plate,
we would've been fine.
Come over here.
What's wrong with you!
- Jung Min, we're just starting right now.
- Scold him and teach him a lesson.
Here's a clue which will help you find where
the bags are at your final location.
[Earns two hints!]
[The seven bags that are hidden
at the final location.]
[Able to earn two hints to the whereabouts of
the bags when they win a mission.]
I can't believe I dropped that
at the end.
Jung Min, why are you
looking so deflated already?
Don't look so depressed and chin up.
It's no big deal.
[Team Leader Hwang remaining silent
with his lips firmly shut.]
Jung Min, we can just do
better at the next one.
We'll just win at the second mission.
Please help us win, Kwang Soo.
- Jae Suk...
- Yeah?
Since the cameras are rolling,
I can't really cuss at you right now.
That's why I'm staying quiet right now.
[Frustrated because he can't even scold
Jae Suk with the cameras rolling?]
Ji Hyo, Sung Woong and I
really worked hard.
- Is that why you're so mad?
- Why are you so bad with chopsticks?
Is that why you're quiet?
[Ah... even though he's angry,
because of the camera...]
- He's really annoyed right now.
- Ah... you're that annoyed?
That's good then. It's better to be annoyed
than sitting there all deflated.
You're really holding
yourself back right now, aren't you?
You're really holding back even though
you're angry right now, aren't you?
Can't we shut this out?
Jung Min, what's wrong with you?
Why would we want them out?
Why would you want to shut
the cameras out?
- What are you doing, Jung Min?
- Say you were wrong! Say you're sorry!
- Why are you shutting them out?
- Tell him you'll work harder!
- Seriously...
- He's really scary.
Why... would you drop the bean when
you already had it in your grasp?
Things like that can happen
during a game.
[Team Leader Hwang with
a never-ending grudge.]
Seriously...
When that bean dropped, I thought
my heart was going to drop too.
[They're acting very suspicious...]
- Here it is...
- I see it, there it is!
[Arrives at the second mission location.]
- We're here.
- What is this place?
[Second mission location -
Chinese restaurant.]
- What is this?
- What are we doing while sitting down?
Wow... a Chinese restaurant.
It smells so good in here.
Your second mission is...
a psychological battle.
I like psychological games.
Jung Min said he's not going to leave me
alone if we don't win the second game.
- It's 'Catch the thief'!
- It's a catch the thief game!
[Catch the thief - Find the
person who is hiding an extra card.]
We used to play this a lot in the past.
As you can see...
there are four jjampong cards,
and there's one jajangmyun card.
[Four jjampong and one jajangmyun card]
Take these five cards and decide which one
of you will hold on to the jajangmyun card.
And for the next five minutes precisely,
you're allowed to ask each other questions.
And when the five minutes are up
you will each guess who on the other team
has the jajangmyun card simultaneously.
We will start with the Singer Team
since they arrived first.
The team to guess who has it
twice in a row is the winner.
- First, just don't give it to Kwang Soo.
- Okay.
[Giraffe has no poker face.]
Kwang Soo really is a horrible liar.
- Okay, you take the card.
- Thank you.
[Does Team Leader Hwang
really have the jajangmyun card?]
- I guarantee he doesn't have it.
- No, he really could have the card.
No, he doesn't have the card.
Sung Woong, you can have a jjampong card.
[Just which one of them has
the jajangmyun card?]
Since they're all actors,
I'm sure they'll all be good at acting.
[Their opponents are actors!
This may not be an easy feat...]
Okay, we will start the clock now.
If you're ready... set, go!
[Five minutes for questioning starts now!]
It's not Jung Min.
He's being too obvious about it.
- Did you see what I saw?
- He's shaking his leg really hard over here.
Before they stuck up their cards...
Sung Woong was the only one who was holding
tightly onto it like it was really important.
[Could Sung Woong have the card?]
I was doing that just so
that you don't find out what I have.
I put everything I have on
Park Sung Woong having the card.
I don't think it's him.
I'm not going to ask any questions,
but I'm going to look with my mind.
[Team Leader Kkuk...
you're going to see with your mind?]
- My young fans know what they're saying.
- Let's not be like that.
Why don't we just ask the questions?
I think we'll find out who it is
once we all each ask a question.
- Kwang Soo, it's not you, is it?
- Kwang Soo... you're jajang, aren't you?
No.
- What do you mean, you're not?
- Ji Hyo, you're jajang, aren't you?
No.
- Jae Suk, you're jajang, aren't you?
- Yes.
Yes.
[Jae Suk confessing to having jajang?]
You know it's not him!
[Jae Suk's psychological game
throwing everyone into confusion.]
I have the jajang card.
- Wait, think about this...
- I have the card, why?
Wait, we need to think about this.
Jung Min, you're jajang, aren't you?
It's not Jung Min.
- Look at how relaxed he is.
- No, it's not him.
For sure it's not Kwang Soo or Jung Min.
Look at Jung Min's face.
My face is just red to begin with.
[Impossible to remain poker faced
with his already red face.]
- I really think it's Ji Hyo.
- Gut instincts are always right.
Gut instincts are always right.
It's Sung Woong for sure.
- I'm telling you, it's him.
- No, it's not Sung Woong!
- He just always look stone faced!
- I'm telling you, he has the card.
- What about Ji Hyo?
- It's not Ji Hyo.
I can tell by looking at her face,
and it's not Ji Hyo.
I can guarantee that it's not
Jung Min or Kwang Soo.
How can you be so sure?
- I'll bet my life on it.
- I think it's Jae Suk.
You think life can be taken so lightly?
- Are you being serious?
- Jung Min is so funny!
Can you bet your fortune on it?
Me? Of course, I can bet that.
[Are his lips quivering?]
[His lips quiver at the mention
of betting his whole life's savings.]
- Did you see his lips quivering?
- Are you jajang or jjampong?
- Which one do you want me to say?
[What does that mean...]
Just tell them what you have
instead of saying things like that.
What are you talking about?
This could suddenly change
into sweet and sour pork.
- It could be Jae Suk.
- No, it's not Jae Suk.
[Which one of them has the jajang?]
- The way I see it...
- It's definitely nor Kwang Soo or Jung Min.
[I'm telling you, it's me.]
Trust me on this, I know I'm right.
It's either Park Sung Woong or Song Ji Hyo.
- It's one of those two.
- I'm telling you, it's not.
- Why is it that no one is suspecting Ji Hyo?
- She was just saying that it was Ji Hyo.
[Suspicious...]
Why are you saying useless things
like that?
- It's Ji Hyo, isn't it?
- It must be Ji Hyo.
- It's Ji Hyo...
- Song Ji Hyo?
- I think it's Song Ji Hyo...
- It's Ji Hyo!
[Does Ji Hyo really have the jajang card?]
[Or is it poker-faced Sung Woong?]
[Or could it be Jae Suk?]
- It's Ji Hyo!
- No, it's Park Sung Woong.
It's Ji Hyo!
[Is it really Ji Hyo?]
[Or is it Kwang Soo's mind trick?]
- It's Ji Hyo... it's Ji Hyo!
- No, it's Park Sung Woong.
I'm telling you, I'm clairvoyant!
Even if it's not her, I'm sure that
Jae Suk isn't going to get picked.
[Are they going to choose Ji Hyo since
Hyuna and Jong Kook are convinced it's her?]
- No, no... it's Jung Min!
- It's Ji Hyo!
[Conflicting opinions]
- I'm telling you, it's Jung Min!
- No, it's Sung Woong!
[Singer Team's pick is... Song Ji Hyo.]
Song Ji Hyo,
please turn your card around.
- I'm telling you, it's Jung Min.
- No, it's not him.
- I'm telling you, you guys are wrong.
- I think it's Sung Woong.
- Sung Woong is just really good at acting.
- You picked Song Ji Hyo.
I don't think Ji Hyo is good at lying.
[Just what...]
[Is the card that she has?]
[Jajangmyun!]
[Singer Team succeeds in ferreting out
the holder of the jajang card!]
I told you that I could see!
I told you I was clairvoyant!
Why did you have to say that earlier?
- You and your mouth...
- No, that's not what I meant...
What were you thinking?
Why did you say that?
[Getting blasted with their scolding.]
- Me saying that wasn't...
- He knew because of what you said.
- Why did you have to say that?
- What I said wasn't a factor.
Wait... wait, wait...
Kwang Soo, get out of here.
[Outside?]
Kwang Soo, you're on our side, aren't you?
Kwang Soo, X-man...
- Stop talking about each other's faults.
- Is there X-man in this game?
- Is there?
- No, there isn't.
[X-man? Doesn't that mean... a spy?]
- We're only down to four men now.
- It's all because of you!
- No, it's not because of that.
- Why did you have to say that about Ji Hyo?
- Yeah, why did you have to say that?
- Hyuna was the only person who thought that.
Didn't you see how Suk Jin kept telling
Hyuna it wasn't Ji Hyo?
So you should've just kept quiet, but you...
Just don't do that from now on.
I keep getting framed as a troublemaker
even if I do good...
You're not even a maker.
You're just trouble.
Maker is too nice of a word for you.
[Giraffe trouble]
Let's not pass it out one by one,
and just mix it up instead.
[Singer Team's plan is
to just play it randomly.]
- Okay.
- So we don't even know who has it.
- We should've done that too.
- Just mix it all up.
- So we don't even know who gets it.
- Pass it from the bottom so they can't see.
[Just who will end up with
the jajang card?]
- You can usually sense who it is.
- I'm not even going to look at my card.
- I can be too obvious about it.
- Start!
[Five minutes of questioning starts now!]
I shouldn't even look at what I have.
- I don't think it's Ha Ha. Ha Ha is out.
- I don't think its Hyuna either.
Kwang Soo, you stay quiet.
Is it okay to be excluded
from playing the game?
- Kang Gary, are you jajang?
- Yeah, I'm jajang.
What?
Ji Hyo... does just looking at Gary
make you that happy?
- Why are you just asking me?
- Do you like him that much?
Did you not wash your face today?
- Why don't you wash it for me then?
- Why would I wash your face for you?
- Why would I do that? Why?
- You can just wash it for me then.
Wash your face in the morning.
I can tell that it looks dirty.
I was going for the tough look today!
You're going to ruin
his image as a celebrity...
Ugh, I'm so mad!
- I think it's Gary.
- Why?
When Gary was doing this...
Jong Kook grabbed his card
while looking from the side.
[As the tablecloth moved...]
[Team Leader Kkuk made a move.]
- The way he grabbed the card...
- It was because the cloth was moving.
- I was just trying to stop it from moving.
- You're speaking with a bit of anger.
- Suk Jin is jajang!
- Jajang, my butt...
Suk Jin... you're not...
you're not jajang, are you?
- Huh?
- You're not jajang, right?
Not jajang?
[When the question gets twisted around,
his reflexes gets twisted around.]
[What am I talking about?]
- Not jajang, right?
- Ask me normally.
- You should say, you're jajang, right?
- You're not jajang, are you?
Jajang... no, I'm not.
- Kang Gary, you're jajang, right?
- I'm definitely jajang.
I'm jajang.
I'm always jajang.
I'll be jajang tomorrow, and
I'll be jajang the day after that too.
- Kang Gary... it's totally Kang Gary!
- No, it's not!
- Kang Gary!
-Yeah, I'm jajang.
- It just may be Gary.
- I know... it may be him.
- Hyuna, are you jajang?
- Yes.
- I can't figure her out.
- I don't think it's her.
Are you saying that you can't
figure out her heart?
What are you trying to do right now?
- Do you like Hyuna?
- Yes.
[More interested in Hyuna's heart
rather than finding out who's jajang?]
In this case, everyone close your eyes and
the one with jajang raise your hand.
[A show of hands for jajang!]
- With confidence...
- With your eyes closed.
- Jajang, please raise your hand.
- One, two, three.
[Jong Kook and Gary?]
Okay, please open your eyes.
You've got five seconds left.
- Five, four, three, two, one.
- It's Gary.
- Gary?
- I'm going with Gary.
Please give your answer.
One, two, three.
[Gary who says he's jajang today,
tomorrow and the day after.]
[Big-nosed Brother getting flustered
over a single question.]
- One, two, three!
- Kang Gary!
[They choose Gary as jajangmyun?]
- Gary, please turn your card around.
- Seeing their reaction...
- Seeing their reaction, I think we got it.
- One, two, three!
[The card Gary has...]
[Jajangmyun!]
[Actor Team succeeds at
their deduction!]
- You're really bad at lying.
- See?
[Ji Hyo having caught Gary's suspicious
facial expression.]
Song Ji Hyo...
Ji Hyo really knows Gary best!
- I honestly didn't know it was Gary.
- Didn't you think he was good at faking?
- Jung Min can pass it out this time.
- Sounds good.
You want me to pass them out?
It's actually better to be out early
since I can't even act.
Ji Hyo was the one who guessed it.
[Now down to one jjampong, and one jajang-
Team Leader Hwang passing out the cards.]
Here... you can stick it up.
[Switching the cards back?]
- Everyone, stick up your cards.
- I got it figured out 100%.
- I know.
- I know too.
- It's Park Sung Woong.
- One, two, three!
- Park Sung Woong!
- Park Sung Woong...
- Let us do it one more time.
Why? Why are you flipping them back?
- Why? Why are you doing that!
- You can't do that!
- Let us do it one more time.
[Team Leader Hwang making it too obvious
when he handed out the cards.]
[Handing the jajang card to
Sung Woong.]
[Embarrassed...]
You made it too obvious!
Look at how much redder
your face is getting right now.
If you want to do it again,
you have to apologize to us.
- I'm sorry.
[Sincerely apologize...
for making it obvious.]
- He made it way too obvious!
- You are so obvious!
- You have to apologize to us.
- Seriously now...
You're making Jung Min feel
really flustered.
He switched it when he thought it would be
too burdensome to have the jajang card.
[Totally caught...]
I had no idea that I'd find
jajang so burdensome like this.
[Thanks to the generosity of the Singer Team,
they get to redistribute the cards.]
So you decided to swap them out?
I saw him hesitate.
- I don't think I can do this.
- In that case...
I'll pass them out.
[Poker face Sung Woong offers
to hand out the cards.]
- I'm just going to keep my eyes shut.
- Look at him closing his eyes.
I can't figure Sung Woong out.
- He has a poker face.
- Who's this for?
- You.
- Me?
[Passing out the cards one at a time
with an indiscernible face.]
Is this mine?
[Just which one of them is jajang?]
It's not Kwang Soo, and it's not Jae Suk.
- Why does my face always get so red?
- I don't know either.
I think you're going to have to start
putting makeup on.
[Did Hyuna figure something out?]
- Hyuna says she knows.
- You know?
- He has jajang.
- He's jajang?
[Is Jung Min jajang?]
- I'm 100% sure. He has jajang card.
- She says she's 100% sure.
- Can you look at us in the face?
- I'm telling you, it's not me.
[Singer Team feeling sure
that Jung Min is the jajang card holder.]
- You're jajang, aren't you?
- I'm jjampong.
He's definitely jajang!
No! No, I'm not!
[100% convinced that Jung Min is jajang!]
- Listen to Hyuna.
- Listen to me.
In the midst of all this chaos...
Kwang Soo is staying way too quiet.
[Suspecting silent Kwang Soo?]
I've been talking nonstop.
Kwang Soo's not smiling like
he usually does.
He's been doing that ever since
we called out who has the jajang card.
Close your eyes.
We're going to try the same thing.
- What?
- Close your eyes.
Raise your hand if you have
the jajang card.
- One, two, three.
- Kwang Soo, raise your hand.
You're the only one who hasn't raised it.
Your hand is the only one down.
[Slowly raising his hand.]
Kwang Soo!
I know Kwang Soo very well.
- It's not Kwang Soo.
- No, it's definitely him.
- I'm telling you, it's Kwang Soo.
- No, it's Jung Min.
You all know how well I
know Kwang Soo.
- No one has suspected Jae Suk once.
- It's Kwang Soo!
I will show you just how
clairvoyant I really am with this.
- Are you serious?
- It's Jung Min...
- I'm telling you, it's Kwang Soo.
- You're not jajang, are you?
- I'm not jajang.
- See? It's Kwang Soo! Look at his face!
- It is. Look at his face! It's him.
- I think it is Kwang Soo.
It's Kwang Soo.
I'm positive it's him.
- Let's go with him.
- I think it's Kwang Soo.
- It hasn't been five minutes yet though.
- We'll say it now though.
- It's not him...
- You should use what's left of the time.
No, no... it's okay.
- One, two, three!
- Kwang Soo.
[Singer Team's selection is...
Lee Kwang Soo.]
- I don't think it's him.
- I think it's Sung Woong!
- It's Kwang Soo. I'm sure of it.
- One, two, three!
I'm telling you, I think it's Sung Woong.
[Wow... jajangmyun!]
- Hyuna...
- How did they know that?
- How did you know that?
I can understand why no one
trusts you with anything now.
[His blood pressure on the rise
because of Kwang Soo?]
He should've been saying something.
I get yelled at for talking,
and I get yelled at when I don't talk.
- Why were you staying so quiet?
- Jong Kook having known him so long...
[Is this really...
Team Leader Kkuk's clairvoyance?]
They're guessing everything right today.
How did they guess so well?
[Does he have clairvoyant abilities now?]
[You're awesome!]
[But the truth is...]
[Team Leader Kkuk's eyes...
Spy Blank Ji!]
[Poker face Sung Woong's
perfect distribution.]
[However...]
[Ji Hyo... who is it?]
This time...
Since we kept saying it's not Kwang Soo,
he may have given it to him.
- I don't think it's Kwang Soo.
- Sung Woong...
Jae Suk?
Kwang Soo?
[Nodding her head right away
at the mention of Kwang Soo's name.]
[And Kwang Soo was the jajang holder!]
[Mr. Capable's secret to clairvoyance
is none other than...]
[Spy Ji Hyo's hawk eyes!]
[Blank Ji who's acting skills
are commendably good.]
[Even her confidence is world class!]
[Macau's landmark]
[Macau tower!]
I love you, Ji Hyo!
[Atop 233 meters!]
[Blank Ji is airborne!]
[Bungee jumps without any hesitation!]
She's insane!
What is she doing?
[An astonishing scene!]
Song Ji Hyo!
That was so awesome!
[Next week's Running Man,
Macau and Vietnam special.]
[Singer Team wins for ousting
two members of the opponent side.]
- We win again?
- I feel bad for winning again.
Team Leader...
[Singer Team wins two hints to
the whereabouts of the bags.]
[The real Spy vs. Spy competition
starts now!]
[The final location - 'A' domestic airlines.]
The team to get all seven bags to
Boss Go Don Wan first is the winner.
[The locations for six bags have been
given out so far...]
[And the last bag is hidden
around here somewhere.]
Then, since we know where four are, and
they know two, we have to steal the location?
The cards we have show there are two in
the education building and two in the main.
Then let's start off by finding
the one that's hidden around here.
[It's now time for the spies
to spring into action.]
[At the same time, the Actor Team
enters the main building.]
- We should find ours first.
- I know.
- Who don't we find the one in here first?
- We should find the one here.
Not the educational building, but the one
in the green environmental cabinet.
Green environmental cabinet.
[Starting the search by looking for
the bag in the main building first.]
- Hello.
[According to the hint, one of the
bags should be here somewhere.]
I'm sorry.
- It's not here.
- Not here?
I found it.
- Found it.
- You found it?
[Actor Team's Sung Woong
finds the first bag!]
- So this is what it looks like.
- Let's get out of here for now.
[Precisely in the location mentioned
in the hint card.]
[Finding the bag is easier today
than usual.]
Why don't we split up the team?
How many people should we have
go over to the educational building?
I'll go to the educational building.
- Why do I feel so uneasy about that?
- Right? I feel the same way.
- Why don't the two of you go for now?
- Us two?
- Make sure you don't get it taken away.
- I understand.
Once you find the bag, don't do anything
and just bring it back to us first.
[Okay... shall I keep an eye on
how things play out first?]
I'm sorry, but do you have a shopping bag
that I can borrow from you?
- I bet they won't be able to find it.
- It shows through though.
[Hiding away the bag that they
just found a moment ago.]
[Even though they have it
securely hidden away...]
[Ji Hyo has been a witness
to everything.]
[Jung Min and Sung Woong not even fathoming
that Ji Hyo is a spy in their midst.]
[What fate awaits this bag?]
[At the same time, the Singer Team is
in the Educational Building.]
- Hey, this is way too easy.
- It's supposed to be behind this curtain?
- Is it there?
- It's here.
[Singer Team discovers a bag!]
[There's a bag hidden in this room?]
[Singer Team discovers their second bag!]
Let's cover it up with that...
just wrap it around.
That sounds like a good idea.
Jong Kook, that's absolutely perfect.
[A perfect disguise]
- That's good... good.
- They won't know even if they open this.
[However...]
[Spy Gary is a witness to everything.]
This is the place?
[The last two bags are in
the main building.]
[Heading into the flight attendants' coat
room in order to find their last two bags.]
- The bag...
- Is it 1,382?
[Hiding the two bags that they found in
the main building in this location.]
[Okay... it's time I start to report
all this to Jung Min...]
[In the first class locker of a B747
on the second floor.]
[On the other hand, the Actor Team heads to
the educational building for their last bag.]
- Hello.
[Asking where the
B747 simulation room is.]
- Here it is!
- It's B747.
[In the first class locker of a B747
on the second floor.]
Here it is!
[Actor Team finds their second bag.]
[Must safely get it back to their teammates
without having it taken from them.]
We found the bag.
[Singer Team - four bags.
Actor Team - two bags.]
- Did you find it?
- Yeah, we found it.
Here, why don't you take it?
[Actor Team safely getting back together
as a team in the main building.]
The important this is, seeing how they don't
have any bags in their hand
I'm sure they have it hidden away
somewhere. Don't you think?
I'm 100% sure they have them
hidden somewhere.
[Actor Team trying to hide
the second bag somewhere.]
I'll go hide it then.
I'll go hide it in the area where
we hid the first bag.
They're not going to be able to find it.
[They're convinced that the bags Singer Team
found are hidden in the other building.]
Jung Min, let's go there and find it.
[Go to the educational building to steal the
bags away from the Singer Team!]
Let's go.
[Ji Hyo having arrived near where
the other bag is already hidden...]
[Should I just secretly take these
over to Jong Kook?]
- Did you wrap it up?
- Yes, but you really scared me.
[Sung Woong heads in her direction!]
You really scared me.
The rest of the guys went over to the other
building to steal their bags.
Really?
[Right now doesn't seem like a
good time to be making my moves...]
[Concealing their second bag in
the same manner as their first.]
[Okay... so both the bags are going to be
hidden in here, is that it?]
[On the other hand, the Actor Team arrives
in the other building for the ambush attack.]
- Should we look around here too?
- I bet those are good hiding spots.
[Searching for the bags that
the Singer Team hid away.]
[Jung Min searching the area
for the hidden bags...]
[It's Jung Min!]
Yes, Jung Min.
Where did you hide the bags
in the education building?
There's a studio in some sort of classroom
on the first floor and it's in there.
Where in the studio?
If you go in there, you'll find a studio.
And when you go into the studio...
It's a black...
Jung Min, don't hang up!
Jung Min...
Any problems over there?
- Who were you talking to?
- Huh?
- My wife. It was my wife.
My wife called...
- I thought you said you weren't answering...
- What?
[Earlier in the day, he was talking about how
he doesn't answer his wife's calls often...]
- Who were you on the phone with?
- I told you, it was my wife.
It won't... someone else?
Where are you?
Huh?
[Something feels funny...]
Hello?
[This is driving me crazy... why are
things getting so twisted around?]
Sung Woong...
- Go ahead.
- Oh, there you are. Okay.
Kwang Soo, I don't see anything here.
- Jung Min is acting weird.
- Why?
He was talking on his phone
in hiding.
Was he just calling his wife?
- That's what he said...
- Yeah?
But earlier, he was talking about how he
doesn't answer calls from his wife...
[These two who's suspicion of Jung Min
is growing deeper by the second.]
What? I'm searching around
right now.
When I started to get suspicious...
he said, 'Yes, Ji Hyo' into the walkie talkie
even though there was no one talking.
No, Ji Hyo was talking earlier.
I...
I have nothing to say anymore.
If this is how it's going to stay...
How are we going to beat a spy
if there is one?
Come on... there's no way
Jung Min could be a spy.
We can't just ignore all these clues.
Your useless thoughts like these
complicate everything.
Just go and find the hidden bags...
who knows where they have them hidden?
- Where could they be?
- You'll regret this later.
You're going to wish that you
listened to me when that time comes.
You're going to ask me how Jung Min
could've done what he did later on.
[Jung Min arrives at the studio as
he's been instructed by Gary.]
[Gary said something about 'Black'...]
It's not in here.
[Discovers the two bags
singer Team hid away!]
[A huge discovery thanks to
Gary's information!]
[Now he has to secretly get them back
to where their bags are hidden...]
[Caught by the Singer Team!]
- What's wrong?
- He has the bags!
- He took the bags!
- Move... move!
[Ah... he almost succeeded...]
How did he find those?
Wait... I bet we have a spy.
- You think there's a spy?
- I'm sure there's a spy.
I think I know who the spy is.
I think it's Gary.
[I knew there's a spy within
our team too!]
Sung Woong?
[For now, Jung Min is like a mouse
caught in a mouse trap.]
Yes, Jung Min?
I'm trapped right now.
Right now, I'm... I'm um...
unable to get out because I'm trapped.
Why are you trapped?
Since all these guys are blocking me in,
come here and help me out.
Just listen to me. Hurry.
- Hwang Jung Min...
- Yes?
- Come on..
- You just wait there.
Hwang Jung Min...
let's work something out.
What would you like to work out?
If you give the bags back to us,
we'll let you live.
we won't rip off your name tag.
- Jong Kook...
- Yes, Jung Min?
Just send in Suk Jin for now.
Come on, Jung Min...
You're being too obvious right now.
It's because I can't match your
strength if I had to face you.
It's not like that... we'll give you our word.
We locked the outer door too.
So no one will be able to get
in here anyway.
You have to open your door
for the outer door to open.
I don't need that. If I really needed to,
I can get out through the ceiling.
Jung Min... why would you go
through the roof?
- Why don't you just...
- Why don't you give up the bags first?
- You'll have another chance.
- Okay.
- Just give us the bags.
Just give us the bags.
Give us both the bags.
Give us one... and the other.
- Give us both the bags.
- Give us the other one.
- That's right.
- We'll let you live then.
- Come out after you count to 100.
Jung Min, come out after you've
counted to 100.
[Although it's too bad to give them up,
I can't get ousted now!]
Where should we hide these?
Let's hide them in here.
It'll be dark in there.
[Singer Team hiding them nearby.]
You can't come out yet, Jung Min.
We're trying to find a way
to get out too.
Should we hide them in here?
Put them in here.
Jung Min!
[Jong Kook trying to not get caught
while hiding the bags in the room.]
- I'm waiting to make sure no one is coming.
- It's too hot in here.
Just wait in there for a minute since
we have to get our backup too.
- I promise we won't betray you.
- Just keep the door locked for now.
Since we've made you a promise...
- Count to 100 when we tell you.
- I know how to count to 100!
Why do you keep telling me to
count to 100?
Start counting now!
Count them out loud!
- Start with one...
- One!
Two, three...
[Singer Team carefully making their exit
in case their opponents come running.]
Ah... why did I have to get caught?
Are they gone?
[Why do I keep getting caught?]
Yes, Jung Min?
Where are you?
I'm in an office on the second floor.
[Jung Min and Gary arranging a meet.]
[The two meeting back up
after a close call.]
- Did you find the bags?
- I did find them...
I did find them, but got caught
by Suk Jin on my way out.
How could you have gotten caught?
[Information that Jong Kook is suspecting
there's a spy amongst their team.]
He hid them away in a place
where Ha Ha and I don't know about.
He's trying to find out who
the spy is.
This is what we need to do. Get the
bags that Jong Kook hid away again.
- This is the quickest way.
- You said you had them taken away by them.
- I saw it.
- You saw where they hid it?
I have an idea of where they're at,
so I'll just have to get them back.
[Deciding to keep going along
with their plans for now...]
[A moment later...]
[Jung Min heading off to get the bags
back with Sung Woong.]
Is it not in here?
Oh! There they are!
Awesome.
[Steals two of the Singer Team's bags!]
[Lucky that he caught a glimpse earlier
when he opened the door.]
[Moving the recently found bags
to a third new location.]
[Concealing it in the closet of
the 747 simulation plane.]
- Jung Min, it's Ji Hyo.
- Let's go find Ji Hyo.
We're coming, Ji Hyo.
[Jung Min gathers Sung Woong
and Ji Hyo around...]
I... planted a spy on the other team.
- I planted a spy over there.
- Really?
[Ji Hyo didn't think in her wildest dreams
that there would be a spy on the other team.]
[Ji Hyo acting as though
she doesn't know anything!]
The spy is helping us out.
It means that there's without a doubt
a spy planted on our side too.
- You're right.
- That's what Kwang Soo...
[Jung Min is suspecting Kwang Soo
to be the spy amongst them.]
That's why I haven't told him anything.
[Jung Min not telling Kwang Soo about
where the bags are hidden...]
Since I'm telling you,
we can't tell Kwang Soo and Jae Suk.
- Understand what I'm saying?
- I understand.
You're not the spy, are you?
- How can I be the spy?
- You're a spy in your movie.
Hearing you say that...
that's really making me sad.
I'm telling you, I'm not the spy.
[Must meet up with Jong Kook!]
Jung Min...
Tell us where you hid our bags.
Just wait a little bit longer.
[Jung Min not telling them anything due to
his suspicion of Jae Suk and Kwang Soo.]
What have you been doing?
I'm a spy... I wanted to
tell Jung Min that I'm not it...
[Huh?]
I've already told Jung Min
that I'm not the spy.
Why would you have to convince us
that you're not the spy?
The other team could've planted
a spy on our team too.
- So you're saying that it's not you?
- That's right.
How could you... anyone
can see that you're not the spy.
- We know you're not the spy.
- Really?
Can the same team...
Can your own teammate rip this off?
- Sure, you can.
- Really?
There are a few who's name tags
I'd like to rip off.
- There are a few?
- Or maybe just two.
- There are just two.
- Seriously...
- In my opinion, the bags...
It's not just your opinion,
but the bags belong to our whole team.
- Hand over the bags.
- Hand them over. Where are they?
- Hurry up and tell us.
- Where are they?
- Why are you playing around?
- They're not here.
Why aren't you telling us
where they're at?
Since the day I was born,
I wouldn't tell anyone about the location.
[What does that mean?]
[Of all the excuses they've ever heard...]
But why are you so desperate
to find out where the bags are?
There you go starting again.
You think I'm the spy?
It's possible that I'll catch the grasshopper
and the giraffe as a set today.
What in the world are you
talking about?
- How could you say such a thing?
- The words just stumbled out.
I guess this is the way I've always
talked since the day I was born.
Why were you all born so strangely?
Hey... is it us two against the rest?
First... I will tell you one bit of
important news to all of you.
Two of our opponent's bags are
now in our possession.
- Really?
- You found them?
- Isn't that a good thing?
- Yes, it is.
- Isn't it a good thing?
- Yes, it's great.
- But your expression says...
- You don't think it's great?
- You're not looking so happy.
- How am I supposed to react?
- Oh, yes! Yes!
- That's right.
[Is he supposed to act that excited?]
- Why do you keep suspecting Kwang Soo?
- He's known for his betraying.
- How did you find those two bags?
- There's no need for you to know that.
[Totally eliminated out of the loop.]
- What's there to like about this?
- You don't like it?
- What is there to like? I'm kept in the dark.
- Are you a spy?
Okay... let's just go and
find our last bag.
Isn't it just better for you to do it alone
instead of us getting involved then?
In hopes that we find the bag,
Mr. Kwang Soo, fighting.
- Jae Suk, fighting.
- He called you Mr. Kwang Soo.
[Even attaching 'Mr.'
in front of his name now...]
- Are you separating me now?
- Why are you suddenly distancing yourself?
- What... what are we then?
- Why are you treating us like this?
- We're just misters to you now?
- No, you're not.
Let's go.
Off we go!
Why don't you two come with us?
- Yes, we'll go.
- Let's all go together for now.
- What just happened?
- What are we going to do?
[Two innocents being suspected by Jung Min.
What will become of these two?]
[A moment later...]
- Jong Kook, where are you?
- I'm in Room 116 in the basement.
[Spy Ji Hyo and Jong Kook
arranging a meeting.]
Really? Where are you right now?
Kim Jong Kook!
Kim Jong Kook, hurry!
Where did they hide the bags?
You know the two bags that you hid?
The two bags that you hid away?
- Jung Min found them.
- Who told him where they were at?
I don't know that either.
I don't know who told him.
Send me a text with the location of
your bags or something.
The two bags that we found are
in the main building right now.
We're going to find the two bags that are here
and put them all together in one place.
- Really?
- You get what I'm saying?
- Tell me where that location is.
- I don't know the location right now.
But until I find out and tell you where...
don't oust Kwang Soo and Jae Suk.
[Planning on using Jae Suk and Kwang Soo
as her scapegoat to keep up her watch.]
[A moment later in the main building.]
[Moving the two bags they previously
hid away in the 747 to this location.]
We got it.
[Concealing it inside tag number 221.]
Ji Hyo, where are you?
- Tell him we're in the main building.
- We're in the main building, Jae Suk.
[Keeping it a secret from
Jae Suk and Kwang Soo.]
[Current number of bags that the
Actor Team has is four.]
[I will go to steal
all four of those bags!]
[And the two scapegoats...]
Let's try this again.
[Since we don't even know where our bags
are at, let's start searching all over.]
[A room that they've never
been in before...]
[Searching everywhere in hopes
of finding something.]
- Jae Suk...
- Yeah?
- Did you know that this opens?
- What opens?
This thing opens up.
- What?
- This wall opens up.
I knew that.
[But you still can't open it?]
You're supposed to slide it?
[That's!]
[The last seventh bag that they weren't
even given a hint about is discovered!]
I'm the one who guided you over here,
but you end up finding the bag...
[The bag no one was able to find
comes into their hands!]
We're good.
[Carefully concealing back into
where they found the bag.]
It's good.
[Is this the end of their sorrow of being
suspected by their own team leader?]
All seven of the bags have to be
gathered together to win anyways, right?
We have a weapon too now.
[This is when the victory started leaning
towards the ending we never predicted...]
[Actor Team - four bags,
Singer Team - two bags.]
[Jae Suk and Kwang Soo
in possession of one bag.]
[All seven bags have now been discovered.
Now time to start the elimination...]
All five of them are going around together.
[Are they starting to make their
moves to eliminate each other?]
- We have to eliminate them, so get him!
- Jae Suk is behind you. Watch your back.
- Wait, Jae Suk...
- Hang on...
[Just then!]
[Jong Kook vs. Sung Woong!]
[So quickly!
Who will come out the victor?]
[Jong Kook eliminates him first!]
[Jong Kook eliminates
Sung Woong's name tag.]
[Park Sung Woong, out!]
[After talking about eliminating Jong Kook
all day, so easily...]
- Why didn't you help him out?
- I didn't even get a chance to.
Let's think about this carefully.
Since you eliminated one person
from our team...
So why don't you eliminate
one from your team too?
- No... no!
- Don't put your hand on me.
[Gets upset just by a mere touch
of his hand on his shoulders.]
I have...
a total of six bags.
What?
[What? You have six?]
- Why didn't you tell us that?
- Why are you keeping that a secret from us?
How can you have six when we have two?
[When the Singer Team has two bags,
how could he have six?]
Let's go check to make sure
that we still have those bags.
- Please go ahead and check.
- Then we'll go check and come back.
[Agreeing to meet back again after verifying
that they still have their two bags.]
- We'll go check that first...
- And you're coming back?
[My plan... you figured it out,
right Gary?]
[Go check on the bags and let me know
where the bags are kept hidden.]
Isn't it better for me to go
and check on them?
Why don't I go and check to see
if they're still there?
- I can just go check.
- No, Dong Hoon and I'll go.
No, no... not you.
We moved the location.
Why are we being like this?
Wait... wait.
It's just that we're a little suspicious.
I'm positive that their two bags
are in the basement somewhere.
It's hidden somewhere in the basement.
[Jung Min having guessed where the bags are
kept by the other team's movements.]
[If I can get the two bags from them,
the victory will soon be mine!]
After thinking about it...
I'm getting really suspicious of Hyuna.
- So I moved the bags elsewhere.
- You did?
- I moved them to a new hiding spot.
- Okay, you did good.
I moved it to a new spot,
but I told Dong Hoon about it.
The reason being...
I thought that he would be
the safest.
But if that's gone,
then Dong Hoon is the spy.
- You're right!
- If that's gone, then it's Dong Hoon.
The spy on the other team...
I planted Ji Hyo as the spy.
- Okay... I get it now.
- You get the idea?
[The place where Big-nosed Brother hid away
the bags are... in the basement dining room.]
[Verifying the two bags.]
[So that's where they're at...]
[Basement dining room]
[Jung Min... hurry up and steal them!]
[Both spies working earnestly
in their roles.]
Basement... the document library.
Basement... the document library,
inside the shopping bag.
She found out the location.
[Both teams on the move at the same time
from the reports made by their spies.]
Shopping bag.
Here it is. It was so light
that I almost didn't know.
[Discovers the bag thanks to the information
given to them by their spy, Ji Hyo.]
[Re-hiding it in the same area
without moving it too far away.]
- Suk Jin, I think there's another one here.
- You found something?
[Discovers another hidden bag!]
Where should we hide these now
so that they can't find them?
Look in the boxes over there.
Are there any empty boxes?
[Concealing it in the empty box
through the help of an employee.]
Can you tape it too?
Okay, and let just put it up there.
[Marking the box so that it doesn't
get mixed up with other boxes.]
Okay, let's go.
[Changing the ownership of the bags
to the Singer Team!]
You know the last two bags?
- They're down in the basement dining room.
- Really?
[My goodness... Jung Min still has
utmost trust in Ji Hyo.]
[Jung Min is heading off to check on the
two bags in the document library.]
I have a feeling they haven't found it.
Please excuse me.
They found it.
[Verifies that his two bags
have been found.]
[Just how did this happen?
What is going on?]
- Ji Hyo, what have you heard?
- Oh my goodness!
- I'm looking for the bags right now.
- We've been robbed.
- We've been robbed?
- Yeah.
There's no way they could've
known about that.
[Acting as though she's shocked.]
- There were only two in there, right?
- Yeah, only two.
You and I are the only two
who knew about that hiding spot.
[Jung Min is still not suspecting Ji Hyo.]
Jung Min, I'm sorry...
[Spy Gary told me they were
here somewhere...]
[Nice! Found them...]
[In this case, the Actor Team's
bag count goes back up to four!]
- Let's take the whole basket.
- Let's just get them out of here first.
Let's take these and get back
up to the first floor.
[With the spies working internally,
the ownership of the bags keeps changing.]
[At the same time...]
If our name tag is ripped off,
is it all over then?
[Gary calling Hyuna out alone
to take her somewhere...]
[Spy Gary eliminates his own teammate,
Hyuna's name tag!]
Hyuna... wait.
[Hyuna, Out!]
Seriously...
[So you are the spy!]
[At the same time, Ha Ha gets
attacked by Jae Suk and Kwang Soo.]
What are you doing?
[Ha Ha, Out!]
[Spy Gary fleeing the scene
immediately.]
I told you that it wasn't me.
Why can't you believe me?
- You were both grabbing onto me.
- Why didn't you tell us?
You weren't listening to me,
you Dumb and Dumber!
[Dumb and Dumber...]
- What did we do that was so wrong?
- You idiots!
But... I thought we would get lucky
and catch the spy.
[Dumb and Dumber not getting
what's going on today whatsoever...]
- Jong Kook...
- Let's oust the idiots.
[Proposing to oust Dumb and Dumber,
who has no idea what's going on.]
[At the rate it's going, Gary may
get ousted by his own Actor Team.]
- I lost Kwang Soo at the last minute.
- Really?
[Jong Kook eliminates Gary's name tag!]
[Spy]
[Verifying that Gary is the spy
for the Actor Team.]
Gary, I'm sorry.
[Confirms that Gary was the spy.]
[This is a big problem...
Jung Min, what do we do?]
[Gary, out!
Gary, out!]
Let me explain this again.
First...
there were two in the document library.
[The two bags that were kept hidden
in the documents library have disappeared.]
I went and checked for myself.
- Then why did you keep lying to us about it?
- That's what I'm trying to explain.
It's because I couldn't trust any of you.
Gary was a spy for our team.
[So it was Gary.]
- Then Gary was getting information for you?
- Yes, he got me information I needed.
And that phone call earlier was to Gary and
everything was a plan Gary and I made.
Then doesn't that make you a spy?
[Dumb]
- What?
- Then aren't you a spy?
Then why am I not a spy?
[Dumber]
- What are you talking about now?
- You're not a spy?
I planted a spy over there so that
our team could win.
- Then the other team planted one on our side?
- Then there's a spy here too?
- That's right.
- Then Jong Kook planted one here?
- But why isn't that person doing anything?
It's because the spy did something that the
two in the documents library are gone.
[Dumb and Dumber finally starting to
figure out what's going on.]
- What were you guys doing?
- Seeing what's going on here...
There's a spy on both of the teams.
- This is really fun today.
- But the spy from your team was Gary.
Now that I think about it,
this is really fun today.
[Dumb and Dumber getting excited
after finally having figured things out.]
This is really awesome.
- This is really exciting.
- I hope the viewers are enjoying it.
This is really fun.
Are you sure that there's a spy
from both teams?
Jung Min's spy was Gary.
And a spy from your team is here somewhere.
- Where?
- It's one of us three.
Do you trust each other then?
We've come too far now
not to trust each other.
I thought you guys were stuck together
because you've been together all day.
I even know how many times
Jae Suk's gone to the bathroom today.
[In the meantime, Jung Min brings the bags he
found in the dining room to the coat room.]
[On the other hand]
Why don't you go up that way?
And we'll go up this way.
Lee Kwang Soo...
why don't you come this way?
You keep getting suspected because
you two have been together all day.
Just go for now since
even Ji Hyo is starting to get suspicious.
[Dumb and Dumber finally separating
just as Ji Hyo had planned.]
[And this is how the Actor Team
ended up going their separate ways.]
[Closing on the grasshopper who's been
separated from the rest of his herd.]
Where did Kwang Soo go?
- Kwang Soo's downstairs.
- I'll go this way.
[Separated Dumb and Dumber are
now an even easier prey.]
[Attacking Jae Suk who's finally
starting to figure things out.]
Kwang Soo!
Kwang Soo... Kwang Soo!
[Eliminates Jae Suk's name tag
from the Actor Team.]
[Jae Suk, Out!]
[Team Leader Jung Min getting flustered at
the announcement of Jae Suk's elimination.]
[Now only two team members left...
who's the spy?]
Jae Suk!
[Wait...]
[If Jae Suk's been ousted,
and he's not the spy...]
[That means...]
[Ji Hyo is the spy?]
It's not down in the dining room?
Jae Suk...
Stop!
[Kwang Soo eliminates Ji Hyo's name tag.]
Trust me.
Hang on... look at her back.
Look at her back.
She's a spy... she's the spy.
[Ji Hyo that he trusted so much...]
[After giving Jung Min a mental meltdown,
Ji Hyo is ousted!]
[Panic]
[Wait! This isn't the time for this!]
Wait here... wait here.
[It's possible Ji Hyo could've told them about
the bags in coat rack 221...]
[Rushing to move them to
another number.]
384... 384.
[Who knew Jung Min would be left with
Kwang Soo who he's mistrusted all day...]
How did you find out?
Because I knew that it wasn't
either Jae Suk or myself.
Are you aware that I'm the only one who knows
where the last remaining bag is hidden?
Really? Where is it?
- Only Jae Suk and I knew...
- So where is it?
[The location of the seventh bag that only
Dumb and Dumber were aware of.]
[More urgent than that...]
[Is to find out where their two bags from
the documents library were taken to!]
No, let's just leave those there for now.
I'm positive those two
are around here somewhere.
I think this man knows where it is.
Where is it?
[The employee who's witnessed
everything.]
- I don't think I'm supposed to tell you.
- No, it's okay.
He can't tell us? But I know it's here.
I'm positive it's in here somewhere.
[Positive they're hidden in this room somewhere
since it's hard to move the bags around.]
I'm positive it's in here somewhere.
It's not here.
[Jong Kook eliminates Jung Min's name tag!]
I'm the only one who knows where
all the other bags are being kept.
- We can find it.
- No, I don't think you can.
- Kwang Soo doesn't know?
- What?
- Kwang Soo doesn't know where?
- No, Kwang Soo doesn't know.
- The way I see it, he knows everything.
- You know, don't you?
He already knows.
The reason being, there's no other way.
[Singer Team slowly closing in
on Kwang Soo.]
I'm sure that he's been told everything.
In case something happens,
I'm sure he's been told everything.
[Jung Min... what do I do...]
[You have to do something!
Think carefully...]
I'm sure that he's been told.
Let's get out of here for now.
- Come out here.
- Jong Kook...
Don't get any closer.
[Giraffe threatening to off himself?]
[Threatening them with his knowledge
of where the bags are located.]
But if he eliminates himself, we'll
be searching for the next five hours.
[If Kwang Soo sacrifices himself,
it'll be few more hours of searching.]
- Go...
- Then let's do this.
Why don't we bring all the bags
and put them together?
Then the two bags
that are in there right now...
Bring those bags out first.
You have to bring yours too then.
Then do whatever you want.
I don't care.
[Wow... the Giraffe is coming out strong!]
Are your ears deaf?
What do you mean, deaf?
I'm saying, let's put all the bags together.
Where are you going?
Forget it. I don't want you
two to talk to me anymore.
Kwang Soo, don't be like that.
Kwang Soo... Kwang Soo!
- Kwang Soo...
- Where is he going?
- Come back here, come on.
- Why are we groveling to him?
He's not turning around.
Kwang Soo, come back here.
He really isn't turning around.
I'm going back in there to look for the bags,
so you two do whatever you want.
- Kwang Soo...
- What are you going to do with them?
[Since he's made the threat...
he needs to find the bags.]
- That Kwang Soo, seriously...
- Why are we groveling right now?
- There are two of us.
- But he knows where they're all at.
If we oust him,
we have no other answers.
- We're going to be searching for two days.
- I know.
I've looked everywhere...
Unreal, isn't it?
- It's not here.
- I'm telling you, it's not in there.
Even with my hand on it, I can't rip it off.
- I can't even rip it off.
- Get your hand off of me.
- Even with my hand on it...
- You can't rip it off.
- Should we just...
- This is a big problem.
[Huh? Where is he going off to now?]
[Wait, that's...]
Even if I carry it around....
it doesn't matter since they
don't know where the others are.
[Carrying the bag out confidently,
but what is it that he's planning?]
- What are you doing with that?
- What good is one going to do?
Here, hang onto this.
[Confidently carrying it out to Jong Kook?]
- Is this 'R' real?
- Yeah, it's the real bag.
Are you sure that it's real?
The 'R' is a different color.
I'll let you each pick it up once.
- Okay, I get it.
- Put out your hand.
Two hands.
[Kwang Soo attacks Mr. Capable!]
[Wow! Giraffe uses his resources
to eliminate the Tiger!]
[Kim Jong Kook, Out!
Kim Jong Kook, Out!]
[You just wait and see...]
[Now the only fight left is between
the fateful Easy Brothers...]
- Just rip mine off.
- Suk Jin...
Just go look for it yourself.
Look for it all day. Rip it off.
[Oh... Big-nosed Brother
is coming out strong too?]
Rip it off.
I'm tired too now.
Hang on a second...
You're really going to rip it off?
- I'll rip it off.
- You'll be searching all day.
[Giraffe not paying any attention
to anything Big-nosed Brother is saying.]
Kwang Soo, no matter...
the day is here for the Easy Brothers.
This really is...
Pil-Chok-Cross.
[We made a mistake by hiding
them in there...]
[Huh? Those bags are...]
Hey!
How did you find those?
[Kwang Soo, how did he find the two
bags that were hidden away?]
[A little while ago while Jong Kook
and Suk Jin were headed his way...]
[Why does this box only look as though
it's been opened recently?]
[Giraffe already discovered it
before it all happened!]
[Leisurely walking over to where the remaining
four are with three already in hand.]
[The four bags he hid away with
Jung Min in coat rack 384.]
- Thanks for your hard work.
- Did you get ousted?
What do you mean, ousted?
Look at all the bags I have.
Thank you very much.
Thank you, everyone.
Thank you.
Thank you, thank you.
You're all so very beautiful.
I wish you all a safe flight.
[The place he's heading to
with all seven of his bags...]
[Boss Dong Wan!]
Boss Go!
[Team that brings all seven of the
bags to him is the winner!]
Oh I see how this works...
And the last one.
[With Kwang Soo's work,
The Actor Team wins!]
Thank you.
Pil!
- Forget it. You're always...
- Pil!
You're not going to do it?
[A really pissed off Big-nosed Brother?]
What is this?
Kwang Soo...
What happened?
- Did he win?
- I'm the winner today!
[For Kwang Soo, the Dumber to win...]
Since Gary was a part of our team,
he shares our prize?
- Of course!
- I see.
- He did great work for us.
- How are you on our team?
What are you talking about?
I got you all the information.
Gary gave us all the information,
so he's on our team.
[Even though he won, he still
hasn't got it all figured out...]
- Just watch the broadcast.
- Why else would Ji Hyo be over there?
Don't even explain it to him.
With this being a first visit from
Sung Woong and Jung Min...
the way I see it, they had no cause
not to suspect Kwang Soo this whole time.
You shouldn't have suspected me.
Then maybe you should've been better
at how you played the games.
I'm telling you this now,
but I'm just weird to begin with.
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Running Man going into history...]
[The beauty of pure nature
overwhelming their souls.]
[A journey into the legendary
scenery of Vietnam...]
[The ultimate secret hidden within
the depths of Vietnam.]
[Find the nine swords scattered about
the world by nine members of Running Man.]
[First location, Macau]
[Conquer your own fears...]
[And the one who becomes one
with the sky will win the sword.]
[If a sword is to be found,
it will go anywhere in the world!]
[And in the blink of an eye,
land in Hanoi, Vietnam.]
[This is the last chance for them to
solve the mystery of the nine swords.]
[The spell that finally unlocks
the mystery of the absolute sword.]
[Scale that cannot be compared...
A spectacular variety fantasy]
I'm the ruler of this land!
[Next week's Running Man:
Golden sword expedition.]