[Running Man Athletic Competition]
Subtitles by DramaFever
[One warm spring day at a cafe in Ilsan.]
Hi.
[Killer smile, Lee Kwang Soo
of Namyangjoo.]
Everyone I know...
sings praises of my killer smile.
[Muscle smile, Kkuk of Ahnyang.]
Jong Kook, you're here!
Hello, Jong Kook!
When... I first saw you,
I thought you were athlete, Son Ki Jung.
- I'm a flower boy today.
- Why do you have that on your head?
I'm wearing a flower crown
because I'm a flower boy.
What are you doing?
Huh?
[Posing every chance he gets.]
Straighten out your legs.
[Um... Girls Generation pants?]
Hello.
[Skinny Yoo Hyuk of Apgujeong.]
What's that bed of flowers
you've got on your head?
- Flower bed?
- Wait a second...
- Isn't that a bed of weeds?
- We're all flower boys.
- What did you say?
- We're flower boys.
I was wondering who took my jacket.
But I see you're the one who took it.
That is so tacky!
That's so totally tacky!
- The least I could was dress up like this.
- You are a sight for sore eyes!
- What in the world are you wearing?
- Isn't this kind of fashion a given?
Don't you have a stylist?
[This time it's handsome Mr. Gary
from Jamsil.]
- You're here.
- Nice to see you guys.
- What are you wearing?
- What country are you from?
I'm from Havana.
[Hails from Central and South America...]
What do you have going on here?
Are you here on business?
- Yes, I do have some business.
- You have business here?
[A man dressed in a chic head to toe
outfit enters the cafe.]
[The best looking man in Ilsan, Blank Ji Hyo?]
- You're the best looking one here.
- I know. I'm the best looking one here.
- You make a good looking man.
- Let's all each have a drink.
[Toasting with juice?]
I saw that you popped up in first place
in all the search engines.
Song Ji Hyo and Jung Jin Woon.
- Really?
- That's right!
What the heck!
All the netizens were curious
about you guys.
[But is this how the Flower Boy Special
is going to get filmed?]
- Ji Hyo...
- Oh!
[Someone... is coming.]
[The two flower boys that will put
the others' looks to rest.]
[The real... flowers boys... are here.]
[Flower Boy Kim Soo Hyun with
undisputably impressive acting skills.]
[Handsome boy, Lee Hyun Woo who grew up
to be as handsome as expected.]
[The coming of the ultimate flower boys.]
- It's Soo Hyun and Hyun Woo!
- I thought we were the flower boys today!
[The two young men who get better looking
with each appearance they make on TV.]
- Your face has gotten even smaller.
- Come. Come over here.
[Bringing Hyun Woo into
the middle of the group...]
[Nothing but leftovers for this guy.]
We now have all the legendary flower boys
in the neighborhood gathered here.
Today's mission is...
Flower Boy Athletic Race.
[Flower Boy Athletic Race.]
You will be divided into three groups
to play in the athletic race.
And each time that you complete a game,
you will gain a card with a number on it.
These numbered cards will become extremely
helpful to you at the final location.
And the final winning team of the day
will be crowned with the honorable title
of being the ultimate flower boys.
[Flower Boy Athletic Competition- Start.]
Where are we going?
[Move on to the grassy fields of
'Y' Training Center.]
Grassy field always means...
A grassy field is a given since
this is an athletic competition.
I guess we'll be running our butts off.
Let's go.
[Off to the first location!]
- How are you now, Soo Hyun?
- I turned 26 this year.
I was 26 when I first started
on Running Man.
Were you with us from the beginning?
[Weak initial presence on the show.]
I'm sorry. I forgot you
were with us from the beginning.
Yes, I remember now.
- Soo Hyun, may I lower my speech with you?
- Yes.
No, that's not right.
You can't lower your speech with him yet.
How can you think of lowering your speech
with Soo Hyun when you've only just met him?
[Forbidden from acting friendly!]
- You've only just met him!
- But between us two...
Why do you keep bringing up how many
times he and I have met?
This is only your second time meeting Soo Hyun
since his first appearance on the show, right?
Do you like me or something?
- You sound like you're jealous.
- The reason being...
Let me tell you why, Kwang Soo.
Listen to me and don't misunderstand.
It's not good for the guest star.
How can you say that?
[It means, don't ruin that star's future.]
I have to get stuck between these
two lovebirds again?
We get along really great if we don't get
any male or female guests on the show.
I have a feeling someone will be
getting pissy a lot today.
- Who?
- I bet Gary will get pissy.
Gary is much better looking
than Kim Soo Hyun.
- Oh!
- Really?
- Kang Gary is very attractive.
No one is better looking than
Kang Gary on Mondays.
Thanks, Ji Hyo.
My Tuesdays through Fridays become so
difficult with her saying things like that.
[His Mondays with Ji Hyo
is the highlight of his week.]
That's just so cute.
I feel like I'm going out with my girlfriend
and my girlfriend's father.
- I oppose. I oppose this relationship.
- Darn!
[Finally arriving at their first location.]
This is... wow, this really looks like...
- I think it's going to be hard.
- I bet it's going to be something hard.
It's a real athletic competition.
[Entering the
Flower Boy Athletic Competition arena.]
It seems you haven't seen it yet,
but you should take a good look around.
[The immense scale of the athletic track.]
[But...]
[Acupuncture mat]
- We're going to have to do this barefoot.
- Oh!
We have to do this whole thing
on top of the acupuncture mat?
- Ugh, seriously!
- That hurts your feet, doesn't it?
Try stepping on it, Soo Hyun.
- What is this?
- It's like a path of thorns.
Are you kidding me right now?
This whole this is an acupuncture mat?
- I didn't even wear socks today.
- Oh!
- I thought this was a sponge mat.
- That really hurts, Soo Hyun.
I feel like I'm going around with
my girlfriend and father-in-law right now.
- I oppose her relationship with you!
- Why?
- I oppose this relationship.
- I have my dreams!
That really does suit you guys.
- He does look like your father-in-law.
- This is exhausting me!
I oppose!
And our clothes are the same color
as this grassy field.
[Camouflage colors]
How am I going to do the hurdles when
my legs don't split very far?
The problem we have right now is,
this is all acupuncture mat, Suk Jin.
- What is?
- Oh!
- That's just absurd!
- Look at the acupuncture mat.
You can tell that it's an acupuncture mat
even at a quick glance.
I bet they're going to make us
do this barefoot.
Sorry!
I thought you were part of the grass.
Why did you give us this color?
When they're dressed in blue and red!
- Sorry! I thought you were grass.
- Hey!
I thought you were part of the grass.
Did you hear what he said?
He thought she was part of the grass.
I really thought you were
part of the grass.
We welcome you to the first round of
the Flower Boy Athletic Competition.
[Whatever the case,
welcome to the first round of competition.]
As you can see for yourself,
the first round of the competition...
It's a 200m obstacle race
on the acupuncture mat.
The rule is, participating athletes
are not allowed to wear their socks.
You have to play the round
while barefoot.
You will be running a relay on
top of the acupuncture mat
and if you can make it in within the time
allotted, you'll pass the round.
First runner will start,
second runner will run to the corner
and the third runner will run
back to the start line.
- I understand.
- All this on top of the acupuncture mat?
We can't do this on top of
the acupuncture mat!
The allotted time is 45 seconds.
- Let's not let them get away with this.
- How can we run 200m on this?
We can't run that track within 45 seconds
even if we ran normally in our shoes.
It's 15 seconds per person.
That is extremely doable.
That's absurd.
15 seconds per person?
You're talking about people who can't even
run 100m within 15 seconds.
It is more than feasible since it's
only 70m per person.
Since he put it that way,
I guess it sort of makes sense.
What do you mean, it makes sense?
This is totally absurd!
But it kind of makes sense
when you hear him put it like that.
We have to endure the pain and beat this
in order for them to stop.
Don't even give them the satisfaction
of letting them think that it hurts.
- Let's all just endure it.
- Just endure the pain.
- Let's just fight the pain.
- Does it really hurt that bad?
Hyun Woo.
If you just think that it doesn't hurt,
then it won't hurt.
It's not going to hurt at all
since we're invincible.
You just need to keep telling yourself
that it doesn't hurt.
[Is he attempting to brainwash himself?]
[Already in sync with Coach Kkuk.]
[200m acupuncture mat obstacle race,
Start!]
How are we supposed to
run on this thing?
[Training himself to get used to
the feel of the mat under his feet.]
If our feet start to bleed,
does it count as having succeeded?
It doesn't?
You have to get all the way over here
within 10 seconds.
Ten seconds?
[Will he be able to pull it off?]
[The Blue Team is now ready!]
[Allotted time is 45 seconds.]
Three.
Wow, he's so fast!
[Lightning fast speed!]
[Unbelievable!]
[How is he running that fast
on the acupuncture mat?]
[Oh no!
He dropped the baton!]
[Rule- If the baton is dropped,
they must pick it up to go on.]
He's doing so great.
Look at how fast he's running.
Be careful!
[Lightly... jumps over the vaulting horse.]
- Hey! Doesn't it hurt?
- Amazing.
- Doesn't it hurt your feet?
- How is he doing that?
[Passing off the baton to Yoo Hyuk!]
[Could this acupuncture mat not be
as painful as the previous ones?]
[No, it is one and the same.]
You can do it, Jae Suk!
Don't stop!
You have to keep telling yourself
that it's not painful!
[The second course-
Pass the tunnel of netting!]
[Feeling the effects of the
acupuncture mat with his whole body.]
This is just wrong!
- How am I supposed to do that?
- How am I going to do that?
Kwang Soo!
- Kwang Soo!
- You're going off the course!
Jae Suk! You're on the grass!
You can't go that way.
Jae Suk, you have to get back
on the thorny mat!
Just a bit more!
Move a little bit more!
[Is he trying to shoot a scene from
'The Shawshank Redemption'?]
I feel like my back is starting to bleed!
- Kwang Soo!
- A little bit more!
[No longer able to just stand by and watch,
Kwang Soo rushes in to help.]
[A new concept- The lending hand.]
[Blue Team's third runner,
Kwang Soo- Go!]
[Kwang Soo is pretty fast on his own!]
[The third course-
Eat the cookie hanging on the horizontal bar.]
[Oh no...]
[Crashes on the acupuncture mat
with the weight of his whole body.]
Oh no!
- Oh no, Kwang Soo!
- It hurts so bad!
The wind!
The wind is blowing the cookie away.
- Why can't you do a better job of that?
- There you go.
That's not what a flower boy
is supposed to look like.
[Barely succeeds in eating the cookie.]
I bet we took five minutes.
[Blue Team- Finish!]
Blue Team's record is...
Three minutes and ten seconds.
[45 seconds to succeed.
Blue Team's record- 3 minutes and 10 seconds.]
First runner, Kim Soo Young finished
his portion in 17 seconds.
[Record for first runner,
Soo Hyun was 17 seconds!]
Even with the 17 seconds,
that's still not enough to succeed.
So Soo Hyun needs to step it up
and shorten his time quite a bit?
In order for us to do it within 45 seconds,
you have to do your portion in 10 seconds.
In some ways, you could say
that our losing was your fault.
- Soo Hyun, let's step it up a notch, okay?
- Yes, I'll step it up a notch.
You have to shorten it
by about five seconds, Soo Hyun.
[You worked hard, flower boy...]
It hurts, doesn't it?
It hurts but you're enduring it, right?
- Right? Yes, you have to endure the pain.
- But...
- That mat really does hurt.
- But when you kneel down once you're done...
I can feel all the blood in my body
circulating throughout.
It means that it's good for you.
- It's because it's good for your health.
- That sensation means it's good for you.
[Next up is the Green Team's turn.]
I remember this sensation all over again.
- Is it really hard and rigid?
- Oh yeah.
How am I going to do this?
I'm in big trouble.
[Green Team is ready to go!]
[First runner Gary's wriggle run.]
- Gary!
That's normal.
[Barely makes it to the second runner
of the Green Team, Ji Hyo.]
Ji Hyo!
[Ji Hyo gets off to a strong start!]
Ji Hyo, are you okay?
[That's nothing for our Ace.]
I know how much that hurts.
[Second Course- Pass through the netting!]
- This hurts!
- What do we do?
- Ow, that hurts!
- Just endure it!
Just think that there's gold
waiting right behind you.
I think my back is starting to bleed!
You're really going to get it from me
if you're slower than Ji Hyo.
There he goes again.
He's threatening you again?
They haven't even started their turn yet,
and he's already angry.
Why are you so angry already
when you guys haven't even started yet?
- I get angry when I just think about it.
- He's like a ball of anger right now.
Why are you the one getting angry
when another team is having their turn?
I don't know, but I'm angry.
Make sure that you do it right!
I haven't even done anything yet.
[Green Team's third runner,
Big-nose Brother... Go!]
What is he doing?
Is he walking?
[Just a faster paced walk.]
Father!
Will you give your daughter to me?
- No, I can't give her to you!
- Why?
- How is Suk Jin going to do that?
- You have to jump higher than you think.
[If he's in that position...
how is he going to get to the cookie?]
- Why are you grabbing it there?
- You have to grab it in the middle!
[What to do...]
Father, just let go!
- Just let go.
- What do I do?
Just let go!
[What would you do if you were
stuck in this situation?]
Wow, even my hands hurt!
What is he doing?
[Green Team- Fail.]
Suk Jin, seriously!
But why did you get so angry when
it was the other team's turn?
[Getting angry again while watching
the other team perform.]
- How is that anything to get angry about?
- But I do feel angry.
Seriously...
That's why you should've just
given your daughter to me.
- I can't give my daughter to you!
- Why are you being so stubborn?
My physical stamina isn't what
it used to be.
Father!
Just think of it as not being painful.
Tell yourself that it doesn't hurt.
Just hold still!
[Attempting to train
the second runner, Ha Ha's back.]
- Let's go!
- Seriously!
[Will the Red Team be able to
get it done within 45 seconds?]
- Soo Hyun, that really hurts!
- I know!
- That thing really hurts, Hyun Woo.
- My father really likes this mat.
You'll be fine.
[Red Team members are all ready to go!]
- Hyun Woo, fighting!
- Fighting!
- Who just made that noise?
- He did.
[His screams keeps on getting louder
while his pace keeps on slowing down.]
His voice is getting
higher and higher pitched.
- You're doing great!
- You have to jump that carefully.
[Passing off the baton to Ha Ha,
the second runner.]
[As predicted...]
- He really is horrible at this.
- Jong Kook is going to kill him.
- He's awful at jumping those things too.
- You have to go faster!
It's all over.
Jong Kook is really angry.
- Jong Kook is on fire.
- You have to move faster!
- Jong Kook is really angry right now.
- I told you to endure it!
Run!
Ha Ha, you have to run!
- Run faster!
- Yes, Sir!
Lie down on your back!
[Second course- Pass the netting!]
Quickly, quickly!
Move faster!
[Like a frozen block of ice.]
It hurts!
[Relaxed spectators all thanks to Ha Ha.]
- You have to move faster!
- Come on, Ha Ha!
[He's on the move!
Mr. Capable, Jong Kook!]
[Mr. Capable's speed!]
[Running at lightning speed as if
he's running down a flat surface!]
[Makes it all the way to the
horizontal bar in no time at all!]
[Is he even human?]
- Fall in, fall in!
- Drop the cookie, drop the cookie!
Drop the cookie, drop the cookie!
[Red Team- Finish!]
- He's not human.
- He's the terminator.
- He's the terminator, Gary.
- I felt like I was watching a movie.
If you think that it doesn't hurt,
then it doesn't hurt.
Come here.
You come here right now.
He's your second runner.
That kid, seriously...
- Let me see the soles of your feet.
- Hang on a second.
[Why does he want to see
the bottoms of Ha Ha's feet?]
We need to condition your feet,
so let me see the bottoms of your feet.
- Pick up your feet.
- Let me see your feet.
You just need to get used to it!
It doesn't hurt once you're used to it.
Get used to it and it won't hurt at all!
- Hyun Woo... it's your turn, Hyun Woo.
- But I ran as fast as I could.
- But you still need to condition your feet.
Running fast isn't everything.
- You're going to thank us for it later.
- Jong Kook.
- You have to treat us the same.
- What?
You have to treat him exactly
the way you treat me.
Do you think you can get it done
within 45 seconds?
- No, we can't.
- You have to give us some more time.
- I think we need a full minute.
- Give us two and a half minutes.
- I'll give you one minute.
- Okay, one minute.
- Why are you two deciding everything?
- Hang on a second.
Why are you two making that decision?
- What are you two doing?
- Why are you two deciding everything?
Why are you saying one minute when
they were about to give us more time?
I think they were about to give us
a minute and a half.
- We should be happy with the minute.
- Why don't you listen to what we say?
Let's do a minute and a half.
- They were about to give us more time.
- Let's go with a minute and a half.
[We were going to give them 90 seconds...]
- It's good to challenge ourselves.
- Are you okay with a minute?
- We're good with a minute.
- Then let's go with a minute.
- This is seriously unbelievable.
- He drives me crazy.
[In the end, they get 15 extra seconds,
and settle for a minute.]
[Allotted time - 60 seconds.
Blue Team's Soo Hyun ready to go.]
[Blue Team's Giraffe- Second runner.]
[Blue Team's third runner- Yoo Hyuk.]
- Kim Soo Hyun, fighting!
- Fighting!
Okay, ready!
Set!
Stay strong, Kwang Soo!
[An even faster speed!]
We're going to do this!
[Lightly jumps over the vaulting horse!]
[Blue Team's second runner,
Kwang Soo- Go!]
Kwang Soo!
[Pretty fast!]
You have to get through it, Kwang Soo!
[The problem is the netting course!]
Come over here.
You're doing good.
He's still pretty fast.
Kwang Soo, you have to come this way.
You have to come this way.
Where are you going?
It's this way.
That's not the right way!
You have to come this way!
This way, this way.
That's right.
[Kwang Soo got through
the net at a record time!]
[Third runner, Yoo Hyuk- Go!]
They may be able to get it done.
- Are you okay, Kwang Soo?
- My back is bleeding.
[Almost at the third course,
the horizontal bar!]
[Aren't you going to eat the cookie?]
- How are you going to eat the cookie?
- What about the cookie?
[All he thought about was making it easier
on himself to grab the horizontal bar.]
You have to eat the cookie.
You can't hold the baton with your mouth.
[If you stick it under your armpit,
how are you going to grab the bar?]
[See how simple that was?]
[Blue Team- Finish.]
That may have done it.
- Are you sure you're not stupid?
- Blue Team's record is...
- You need 60 seconds to succeed.
- Yes, that's right.
Blue Team's record is 88 seconds.
Yeah!
My team is full of idiots.
He's nothing but a good looking idiot.
[Automatic reaction from having firmly
believed that they were going to win.]
[Embarrassed]
If we had gone with the 90 seconds,
we would've succeeded.
But it's 60 seconds. You can do it
within 60 seconds the next time.
If I hadn't...
Can't we leave this out?
Are you sure you're not stupid?
What were you thinking putting the baton in
your mouth when you have to eat the cookie?
- You never think.
- Were you not thinking or what?
- What were you doing?
- My head...
- My head... it's not very clever.
- No, it's not, is it?
You have to hold it like this.
This would've been easier.
Put out your hands.
- I said, put out your hands.
- You don't have to hit me.
You should go and take a
beating too, Father.
- Why are you standing over here?
- I'm going to stay out of it.
If you need to little pick-me-up,
let me know.
- Is the Red Team ready?
- Yes.
[Red Team members- Ready!]
- He's actually running pretty fast.
- Dong Hoon! Run straight forward!
[Unbelievably frightening team where the
coach is even telling them how to run.]
There you go!
Jump it.
Hurry up!
[If he had only jumped the vault better,
he would've been quite fast...]
He doesn't even have the time to
bump his butt.
Wow, he's just flying over here.
[Red Team's second runner-
Mr. Capable Jong Kook.]
[Makes it all the way to the netting already
in crazy speed of light!]
You're going off the course!
No!
You have to go towards the left.
[Even goes through the netting course
at lightning speed.]
[Finally passes the baton off to
the runner, Hyun Woo!]
[Even though he's making a lot of ruckus,
his footsteps are fast and light!]
I think they're going to do it.
If he gets that cookie fast, they got it.
As long as he can get that cookie quickly.
I think they're going to get it.
[Red Team- Finish!]
[Besides for Ha Ha's slight fumble,
the team made it through very quickly!]
Your feet hurts, don't they?
Are you okay?
Here is your record.
The Red Team's record is...
[Allotted time is 60 seconds!
Red Team's record is...]
A minute and three seconds!
[Allotted time is 60 seconds!
Red Team's record is 63 seconds!]
[Over the time limit by three seconds.
If it hadn't been for Ha Ha's fumble...]
- That was just a mistake.
- Come out here.
[Soo Hyun practicing for the second course.]
- Faster! You have to move faster!
- Soo Hyun...
You have to do it without your jacket.
[Look at that giraffe!]
[He looks like a little lizard.]
- Kwang Soo.
- You should go around like that all day.
[Haroro on the other hand
is still getting scolded.]
- Does it hurt or not?
- It hurts! No, it doesn't hurt!
It doesn't hurt!
[Blue Team members- Ready!]
[Blue Team's first runner- Yoo Hyuk.]
[Blue Team's second runner- Giraffe.]
[Blue Team's third runner- Soo Hyun.]
[Conditioning his feet is now complete!
Moving at a fast speed!]
[With the baton firmly in his mouth.]
Be careful!
- Nice!
- Wow, he's fast.
[Second runner, Giraffe- Go!]
- They might make it.
- Fall down!
See?
Their feet are now used to the sensation.
[No more feelings left on their feet!
Unbelievable speed!]
[Here comes the lizard!]
This way, this way!
- I think they're going to do it.
- Kwang Soo!
Kwang Soo!
You can do it!
[Hands off the baton to
the third runner, Soo Hyun!]
[The final spurt with their fate
hanging on the line!]
Soo Hyun!
- Fighting!
- Look at how fast he is!
- He's so fast.
- I think they're going to make it.
Come on!
[Almost falls off the bar!]
- He's stuck! They're stuck right here!
- He's having a hard time with it!
[Taking too long!]
They're stuck right there.
[Blue Team- Finish!]
[Too bad about the last part...]
He was so fast.
The Blue Team's record is...
[Allotted time is 60 seconds!
Blue Team's record is...]
57 seconds!
[Allotted time is 60 seconds!
Blue Team's record is 57 seconds- Success!]
Seriously?
[If Ha Ha would've jumped better on the
vault, the Red Team would've won...]
Now each team...
[Each team receives something in the order of
their record and moves on to the next place!]
We'll see you later, Ha Ha!
- No.
- You don't need it?
There are three numbered cards
as you can see in front of you.
- We don't know which is good or bad?
- No, we can't tell you that.
[Just pick one card and get on the way!]
Do you think it's better or worse
to have the greater number?
- Don't you think greater the better?
- Okay, let's take the greater number.
[Blue Team chooses the number five!]
[What role will this number
end up playing in the end?]
- Higher number is better, right?
- We don't know if it'll be good or bad.
- What should we do?
- Let's go with the higher number.
You can pick.
No, why doesn't Ha Ha choose it instead?
So I can blame him for it later.
[Ha Ha chooses number three
for the Red Team!]
[Green Team gains number one!]
- Do you think we'll even come close today?
- Don't worry so much.
- Father...
- But I still oppose you with her!
Please stop saying that.
We have to go this way.
- We're still doing okay, Father.
- At least we're still on the plus side.
[Go to 'M' hotel's swimming pool in Ilsan
and find the Running Man landmark.]
I'm feeling more confident now.
- Why doesn't Kwang Soo lower his speech now?
- Kwang Soo? No, no.
[Jae Suk discourages the idea of Kwang Soo
lowering his speech to Soo Hyun again.]
- But we've already lowered our speech...
- I don't think it's time for that yet.
[He lowered his speech during the games,
but is now back to using formal speech.]
- But it really was disappointing earlier.
- Right?
[The purpose of the numbered cards
that they can't figure out the meaning to.]
So we don't know if it's better to have
the higher or the lower number?
[Flower Boy Athletic Competition's
second location- Ilsan's 'M' Hotel.]
[What is the next course in the
Flower Boy Athletic Competition?]
[This is...]
[The flying chair?]
- This is...
- Are we going to be flying now?
You may be calling this the
Flower Boy Athletic Competition
but what the heck is this now?
It really is nice weather
to be flying through the air.
It's a nice day to go in the water.
[Perfectly fit for the concept.]
The Iron Man is getting too much of
a beating from the Hulk.
Get out of the way.
The Iron Man is getting too much of
a beating from the Hulk.
Then why don't you start playing
the game like the Iron Man?
[A petty revenge?]
Ha Ha did this to you behind your back.
I saw him do it.
I was really shocked by his behavior.
How dare he act like he was
going to hit you from the back?
Welcome to the second round of
Flower Boy Athletic Competition.
The Blue Team will move on
to the final round.
It's swimming pool Mook-Jji-Ppa.
[One member of the team plays Mook-Jji-Ppa
while the other two members sit in the chair.]
[Moment the member loses Mook-Jji-Ppa...]
[If Mook-Jji-Ppa is lost, then the members
will get thrown into the water.]
[If the team loses,
then it's a flying leap into the water.]
Why don't you go up?
Go on up.
[If they win three Mook-Jji-Ppa's in a row,
then it's on to the final round.]
[Green Team's Suk Jin vs.
Red Team's Ha Ha.]
- Let's win at least once.
- Show them an all kill game.
Do we go flying through the air
the moment Mook-Jji-Ppa is lost?
- Yes.
- Suk Jin!
[The fate of the team members is
in the hands of the Mook-Jji-Ppa player!]
- Just think that you're going to go in.
- I'll make sure that you do.
- I'm so nervous.
- Me too.
- I feel like I'm going to lose this hand.
- I feel really nervous.
Okay, let's start.
[Semi-finals... Start!]
Jji!
Ppa!
[Thrilling!]
- Ppa!
- No one won yet?
Mook.
Mook!
[Huh?]
[Why did he throw out a 'Jji'
when he shouted out, 'Mook'?]
[Welcome...
First time in the flying chair, isn't it?]
[Once you've done it a few times,
it's no longer a big deal...]
[Three wins to move on to the finals!
Green Team with their first win!]
I feel like I was flying through the air
for a whole three seconds!
He's pretty good at exaggerating too.
He exaggerates things too.
We weren't in the air for three seconds!
Give me just one more chance, Jong Kook.
No, you get out of there.
[Ha Ha wants to play another round
before the Tiger gets to him?]
- Ha Dong Hoon, get out of there!
- They already started the game.
- I said, get out!
- Ppa!
[He loses again behind Jong Kook's back...]
- I said, get out!
- Go sit down in your chair.
Get out!
Get out of there!
[Flies through the air again
without knowing what had happened.]
[Green Team's second win in a row!]
- Can I try it once, Jong Kook?
- Sure, you go and play.
- Play me once, Suk Jin.
- Sure, come over here.
Hyun Woo really is soaked.
I told you to get out of there.
I'm sorry.
- I'm sorry!
- I told you to get out of there, didn't I?
[Third round of the semi-finals.
Green Team:2 vs. Red Team:0.]
Show them an all kill, Suk Jin!
Rock, paper, scissors!
Jji!
- That was some flying!
- Her feet were kicking around.
[That's because I'm pretty light...]
[The Red Team finally wins a round!]
[As soon as the player is switched out...]
What the heck!
[Green Team:2 vs. Red Team:1.]
Rock, paper, scissors!
- Please.
- Jji!
Mook!
Jji!
[Are you that nervous?]
[Green Team:2 vs. Red Team:2.]
[The whizz kid of Mook-Jji-Ppa who
evens out the game within moments.]
[The better Hyun Woo starts to do,
more scolding Ha Ha gets.]
She's not heavy enough.
I'm going to lose my mind.
A Leessang hat?
Me?
[Gary with Ji Hyo's hat...]
- Is this how you guys are going to play?
- Just ask me for my heart instead.
[Instead of taking my hat,
you can take my heart instead.]
What are you two doing?
['Just ask me for my heart instead'-
The birth of a new catch phrase.]
What are you two doing?
- I think my daughter does like you.
- Yes, Father. Just let me have her hand.
No, I still oppose.
When did our hats get switched?
Wow... she doesn't even know when
their hats got switched.
You're going to start dating without knowing
at the rate that you're going.
[The winner of this round
will go on to the finals!]
Paper, rock, scissors!
Mook!
Ppa!
- Ppa!
- Mook!
[You got him!]
Mook!
[Iron Man?]
[Batman?]
[The relaxed finale with them
getting into their pose.]
Jong Kook... I couldn't stand the way
he looked when he flew into the air.
- The way he punched the air.
- He's like the muscle bat.
[Fly, muscle bat!]
[Green Team moves onto the final round
with Big-nose Brother's lucky play!]
Are we up now?
- Kwang Soo!
- Yes, Jae Suk!
Let's fly.
[That look is...]
Are you a judo player?
[Ninth level in judo.]
Are you a judo player or something?
I think it would work just as well
having Jong Kook throw us in.
[If the chair breaks down,
then Jong Kook can throw them in.]
- Don't worry about us, Soo Hyun.
- Good luck, Ji Hyo.
- Teach her a lesson, Soo Hyun.
- You can win this, Ji Hyo.
Just think of it as having just one
panty when you're playing a water game.
You have to play with the mind frame
that you can't fall in the water.
I've got no panties on.
This is all about one panty!
[Five rounds of Mook-Jji-Ppa.
Finals- Start!]
- Ppa!
- Jji!
There they go!
[This is how you fly...]
[or not to fly into the air.]
You've taught him well.
[Jae Suk only has one pair of underwear...]
I'm sorry!
- You can borrow my underwear if you'd like.
- It's okay, Soo Hyun!
It's okay, Soo Hyun.
It's not a big deal.
Then is Jae Suk not going to have any
underwear on after this today?
No!
I'm going to wear your panties!
It's okay, Soo Hyun!
You're doing fine.
[Green Team:1 vs. Blue Team:0]
- Soo Hyun, fighting!
- Yes!
Paper, rock, scissors!
Ppa!
Jji!
- Soo Hyun, don't...
- Ppa!
Soo Hyun!
[They barely got back into their seats...]
- You raised your daughter very well!
- She's got everything!
- Yes, she does.
- That's why I can't give her to you.
[A totally different expression on his face
after Soo Hyun's second loss in a row.]
Let's do it and see who wins!
- Soo Hyun.
- Yes?
Don't worry about this...
and try it one more time.
Huh?
What?
What's wrong with my pants?
[The line on his wet pants...]
Is there a problem?
[His self-confidence in his behind
explodes again.]
[Oh my!]
He thinks that's sexy.
What are you doing?
- Why?
- Seriously!
- What's wrong with the way I came up?
- Does he think that he's sexy?
- Soo Hyun?
- Yes?
- Don't be burdened by this.
- Get your head on straight!
I've only got one pair of panties.
Look at the back of Ji Hyo's head.
[The two need to get closer
so that they can't see from the back.]
What is she doing?
[Ji Hyo's towel...]
[is around my shoulders.]
[Seriously...]
She plays her games very seriously.
What are you doing, Song Ji Hyo?
[Using the game as an excuse
to have a towel date?]
That Song Ji Hyo, seriously!
Why are they having so much fun
playing Paper-rock-scissors?
Jji!
[Blue Team's Soo Hyun wins!]
Nice, Soo Hyun!
[Did Ji Hyo all of a sudden
weaken her resolve?]
Make her heart beat even faster!
[Did she get all shaken up
by the towel move?]
- Why don't you try it, Jae Suk?
- Should I give it a try?
- Okay, Ji Hyo.
- Hey, Ji Hyo...
[Blue Team switches out their player
with Jae Suk.]
He's going to throw out a paper first.
- What?
- I can't stand looking at you this close up!
Listen to her!
She really is something else!
Seriously!
It's a mind game.
I'm playing mind games with her!
- Seriously.
- It's mind games!
[Planning on giving her a
mental breakdown.]
Don't get flustered by him.
Even after all these years,
I still can't get used to that sight.
You have an eye booger.
Don't be like that.
[Final round-
Green Team:2 vs. Blue Team:1.]
Paper, rock, scissors!
Jji.
[Again?]
[Oh no!]
Nice!
Nice going!
[No idea what's going on.]
How did she win that so quick?
How many times does this
make for you?
[First experience with the flying chair.]
Come on, let's win at least once.
[Final round-
Green Team:3 vs. Blue Team:1.]
- Jae Suk is really bad at this game.
- Paper, rock, scissors!
I won this portion.
Yes, keep reporting every
step of the game.
- I won this portion.
- You can do this.
Please, please!
Jji!
Ppa.
[I can't see!]
[The towel chooses just that moment!]
[Flies far into the air again!]
Wait!
Time!
That's not right!
[Finals round-
Green Team:4 vs. Blue Team:1.]
[His second flight is still
just as thrilling?]
- Did you see my daughter?
- I couldn't see because of the towel!
[Seriously...]
- What do you mean, do it again?
- Then start Running Man over from Episode 1!
You're being too harsh, Gary!
[If the Green Team wins one more round,
then they win the game!]
- Kwang Soo, you can do it.
- Here, use this.
- Here, Kwang Soo.
- Do you want another chance?
It's because the towel is all wet.
Even with it wet, you still
shouldn't have fallen that hard.
You try it.
Is it that heavy?
[It really is!]
Have a seat and take off your hat.
Seriously?
[The ultimate wet towel experience.]
That's no joke! What the heck?
How much does this thing weigh?
- That's too funny.
- You know what happens when you lose, right?
[You need four wins in order
to win the game!]
Here we go!
Paper, rock, scissors!
Jji! Jji! Jji!
[What is he doing?]
Jji!
Ppa!
Wait!
[While momentarily distracted...]
[Flying higher into the air than usual
to fall into the water!]
[Flower Boy Athletic Competition-
Flying Chair Game- Green Team wins!]
[Special request made by the producer-
A specially held game.]
A request came in to see which
one of you is the weaker one.
- Forget it, forget it.
- You two sit down in the chair.
- Is it just one round?
- Yes, just one round.
- Find out the weaker player.
- Okay.
If I win this, I'm going to
lower my speech to Soo Hyun.
Okay, call.
- You still haven't lowered your speech?
- He won't let me!
I didn't let him lower his speech with him.
He told me not to act friendly with him.
I told him not to get in
the way of a star like him.
[Flying chair Mook-Jji-Ppa.
Determine the weaker player.]
- Paper, rock, scissors!
- Please!
Please.
Mook! Mook!
Mook! Ppa!
Wow, that woke me up.
That really woke me up.
Jji!
Mook! Mook!
Mook! Mook! Mook!
Jji!
[Yoo Hyuk- Chosen to be the
weakest player.]
- Lower your speech now.
- Soo Hyun!
I can now finally address my younger
brother as my younger brother!
- I haven't been able to do it all morning!
- Don't do it.
I said, don't do it.
Don't lower your speech with him yet.
[Now that he's gotten past Jae Suk,
Jong Kook steps forward.]
- What?
- You can't lower your speech.
Then why don't you play a round
with Jong Kook too?
If I win, why don't you start
using honorifics towards me too?
That's not a bad idea!
Really?
Fine. Yes, let's do that.
[A honorifics Mook-Jji-Ppa game
out of the blue.]
If I win, then we both use honorifics.
But if you win,
I'll keep using honorifics with Soo Hyun.
- Okay, let's do this.
- Wow, I really want to win this.
Paper, rock, scissors!
Paper, paper!
That's a scissors!
I can't believe I lost to him.
Mook!
Ppa!
Look at the girth of his arm!
[Even though it's an added game,
all the attention is focused on it!]
Jji!
I'm going to call Soo Hyun
by his name!
Mook! Mook!
Mook! Jji!
Jji!
[Honorifics bet- Jong Kook loses!]
[Kwang Soo can now lower his speech to
Soo Hyun and have Jong Kook use honorifics!]
Okay, let's go now.
[Everyone rushing to go before
the Tiger gets out of the water.]
- How about the higher number this time?
- Don't you think the higher would be better?
Let's take this one.
Then we'll take this one.
You can now go on to your
next location.
[Green Team- 5, Blue Team- 3, Red Team- 1.]
[What do these numbers mean?]
Go to the mural village in Hwajeondong
and find the Running Man landmark.
[Giraffe happy to be able to
lower his speech to Soo Hyun.]
- Soo Hyun.
- Yes?
What kind of nicknames do you have?
There was a nickname that I gave myself
back when I was in elementary school.
- Nickname you gave yourself?
- You gave yourself a nickname?
What was it?
- Well my name is so feminine...
- Yes, Soo Hyun.
I think that used to bother me a lot.
So I nicknamed myself... Soo Man.
That really seems...
fitting of an elementary school kid.
Soo Man.
Because you wanted to be more manly?
So you nicknamed yourself Soo Man.
Kim Soo Man?
- Yes, Kim Soo Man.
- You nicknamed yourself 'Soo Man'.
Kim Soo Man.
Good looking kids like Soo Hyun
usually don't have many nicknames.
You had some, didn't you, Kwang Soo?
I used to get called a Q-tip.
[Q-tip]
[Hwanjeondong Mural Village]
[A place full of beautiful murals
all throughout the village.]
I wonder what we'll be doing here.
This is so cool.
[A village market...]
[And there's lady Dong Wan.]
Hello.
- Ma'am!
- Here, take your mission.
Three courses.
In the order of arrival.
[Complete your mission that's given to you by
lady Dong Wan and come back once complete.]
[But only those that arrive first can go!
The team whose members all pass first wins.]
Dong Wan!
Here, take your mission.
- It's lady Dong Wan.
- I want an ice cream too.
Give me one too.
It'll be chaotic once the mission starts.
Hyun Woo has the money.
Ask him to buy it for you.
- Hyun Woo.
- Don't, Hyun Woo. Don't give them any.
Give me the money.
You borrowed it from the
producer, didn't you?
[Bingo- Forcefully borrowed the money
from PD Myuk earlier.]
- When did Gary go in there?
- Does he have any money?
He has money?
- Do you have money?
- Did you get some money?
They don't even have any money.
They're in trouble now.
- Where did you get this?
- I just assumed Hyun Woo would buy it.
They have everything here.
Which one do you want?
Thanks, Hyun Woo!
I'll show you what it means
to get them.
[Can't hear you!
You wouldn't not pay for us, would you?]
- You're in trouble, Gary.
- Why?
Why?
[Absolutely clueless.]
[Why am I in trouble?]
- What is it, Gary?
- I have no idea!
- He says we're in trouble.
- Why?
- I don't know.
- I have no idea.
Here, have a seat.
You probably think that
I'm paying for you, right?
I'll show you how to get them.
[Say what?]
Can you go ask Kim Jong Kook
for the money?
[Giraffe is telling on the owner?]
Ask Jong Kook for the money.
Ma'am, how much is it for all this?
- Jong Kook.
- Yes?
You have to pay for the ice cream.
[I was told to get the money from you.]
[Who knew the owner would come out
and ask to be paid herself!]
I don't have the money!
You have to pay me.
He says you have the money.
They're the ones eating it.
It really isn't for me to pay, Ma'am.
[Encouraging her to get even
closer to him.]
I told my mom on you!
Mom!
It's him!
Mother.
Come on, Mother.
See the red clothes?
My team is dressed in red.
The ones dressed in blue
aren't my team.
Come on, don't be like that.
You're a good looking boy!
Hurry up and pay her.
She wants to get paid.
[Ultimately ends up handing
her the money.]
They just went in and took it
without even asking.
Just take that and bring him
back the change.
You don't have to see
Kim Jong Kook again.
Mother!
- I'm going to upload it.
- Excuse me?
If you keep that up,
I'm uploading your picture.
[Chastising Kkuk for his endless arguing.]
I'm not responsible for them!
[A smart world where people
can easily get exposed.]
- They're not even my team!
- Even ladies know how to do everything now.
That was quick thinking.
[Nervous...]
Excuse me!
You come over here.
- You're supposed to use honorifics!
- What did you say?
- What are you doing?
- My mom!
[She was watching!]
- Take the picture!
- Mother.
Mother!
[It's not like that.]
[Unbelievable timing!]
[Who knew that the citizens that live
here would be so sensible?]
Okay, let's start the mission.
[First come first serve mission-Start!]
If you keep sitting like that,
you're going to end up with scoliosis.
You just worry about yourself!
- Seriously!
- He hasn't been sitting like that for long.
Just keep it to yourself!
It's my back.
My back.
With the weather so nice today,
I was thinking of doing some laundry.
If you go deeper into the village, you'll find
laundry baskets with an 'R' sticker on it.
Wring out the laundry in the basket
and hang up a piece of the laundered clothing
on the laundry line you see in front of it.
But it's no fun if you just go
and hand it on the line, right?
You have to hang it up
with your toes.
You have to hang it up with your toes.
[Throw the laundry to hang it on
the line by using your toes!]
- With your feet?
- How?
Yes, you have to use your feet.
If you succeed with the laundry,
you'll be giving clothing pins.
Once you're giving the pins,
you just have to bring that back to me.
Okay, let's start the game.
It will be a first come first served basis.
One person, go!
- What does that mean?
- First come first served.
Just one person.
Get going!
- How many of us can go?
- What does he mean?
There's a total of nine of us right now.
- We have to find the laundry basket.
- Laundry basket!
[Soo Hyun leads the pack with
his lightning fast run.]
Look for it carefully.
[Where is the laundry?]
Where do you think the
laundry basket is?
I feel like it'll be around here somewhere.
- There it is!
- Right here!
[Must hang it up on this line to succeed.]
Right here?
This one?
- On that line?
- Here it is!
[Total of three people.
Gary can also participate.]
[Kkuk and Giraffe also discover
the laundry area.]
- We just have to hang it with my feet?
- After wringing them out?
You have to be careful with
what you pick.
[While everyone is getting ready to hang up
the laundry with their feet...]
[Lightning fast Soo Hyun is...]
[Huh?]
There's a laundry basket with
the 'R' sticker on it.
[Where's the 'R' sticker?]
[Was the first to run off,
but is still looking for the laundry...]
This is someone's house, right?
[Is it over there?]
Something doesn't seem right.
[He's going to go around the
whole village.]
- I can't believe what we're doing.
- We can go if we succeed?
I don't think this is going to work.
One, two...
[Hang it up?]
[No way...]
[Flower boy Hyun Woo's turn.]
I think I can do this.
Try it.
[Wow...]
Here I go.
[Ha Ha and Ji Hyo are carrying out
the mission at this site.]
[Darn!]
Challenge.
[Blank Ji's challenge.]
[What?]
[Too bad...]
I got it!
It's first come first serve, isn't it?
I should get it done quickly.
Move out of the way.
[Giraffe waiting for a chance
from the side?]
You're blocking the line.
Move out over here.
- I'll just stand still.
- Move out over here.
I'm wringing out the laundry
to get it ready.
[As predicted...]
[He really is a Tiger eating Giraffe.]
I'm going to try it again.
[Only one person can pass this,
and the Giraffe keeps interfering.]
[Soo Hyun finally having found
a laundry basket.]
[Hm...]
[The laundry getting caught
in the tree.]
[Second attempt.]
[Again!]
[Third attempt]
[In the tree again.]
They all keep getting caught in the tree.
[At least the laundry will dry well.]
[Yoo Hyuk making his attempt.]
[He got it caught on the line!]
[Success!]
[Off to the supermarket with
the clothing pin in his hand!]
Just one person on
a first come first serve basis.
That's me.
- Did you get the laundry hung?
- It's like the shoe throwing.
- Have a seat over there.
- There's nothing I can't do.
I can't believe I got it hung
on my second attempt.
Ever since I was little...
there's something my father
used to say to me.
He used to ask me if I used
my feet to write.
[He used to ask me if I wrote
with my feet...]
[Guess there's a reason for everything.]
- I got first place, Ji Hyo.
- You came in first?
Then there must be a lot of areas.
How many laundry areas are there?
There is an advantage given to
the first place winner.
What is it?
Go get yourself a cookie.
- What?
- I'm jealous.
Although I'm grateful...
But telling someone older than you to go
get himself a cookie with 2,000 won is...
- This guy seriously...
- I'm jealous.
[Sticks it into his pocket.]
Of course, I'm going to eat.
You should have a better
sense of duty.
Instead of finishing up so early...
I'll take my sense of duty
and buy myself a cookie.
[If there was a lip battle,
he'd be the world champion.]
- Stop it!
- Oh no! What do I do!
[A bug...]
[Bolts out of their seats.]
[All the little brothers jumping out
of their seats to her rescue.]
She's not scared of anything
else but bugs.
Kwang Soo, just stay back and let
Gary go to her instead.
She's not yours!
How would you like it if I started
acting like the group idiot?
You're the group idiot and she's mine!
[Getting worked up over Kwang Soo's
confusion of their roles.]
I'm sorry!
Please don't take my idiot role away!
If anything happens to Ji Hyo,
just let Gary go to her rescue!
I can be the idiot too!
[I can be the idiot too...]
That's my role!
Please don't do that!
Okay, we'll start your next mission.
Your next mission is to eat
the refreshing watermelon.
I love watermelon.
Eat the watermelon and spit out the seed
to put a mole upon your own face.
Up to two people can attempt the
mission at the same place.
You have to cross this line with the
seeds still on your face.
But if it falls off on your way back,
you have to go back and do it over.
So we have to find a close
place to do it.
Stop speaking up!
We'll take care of it ourselves.
You just stay and we'll take care of it!
Fine, okay.
Did you hear what I said, Kwang Soo and
Soo Hyun? You have to find a close location.
Do we have to eat
the whole piece of watermelon?
Seed.
Just the seed.
You just need to spit out the seed
to get it to stick to your face.
We know that!
- You have to spit out the seed...
- We already know that!
[The two poor suckers stuck
between the two loud mouths.]
Just spit out the seed
and get it to stick on your face.
You're so strange!
We know what we have to do!
The first time I ever played this game
was sometime in the mid 90's.
[Showing his ability to talk nonstop
without any regards to those around him.]
Mister!
[Why is he getting up?]
An unexpected situation just occurred
because of me.
- How do you run so fast?
- Where is it?
[Soo Hyun having run like the wind falls
behind the others from lack of direction.]
[Watermelon!]
[Two people per location!]
[It stuck!]
Did it stick?
Did I get it on my face?
No, it didn't stick.
[Why is the Giraffe following him when
he hasn't even played the game yet?]
They're already back?
You have to come over to me
so that I can check it.
Fail.
[Giraffe succeeds in his plan
to interfere.]
What is it that you brought back?
I saw you running back with your chin
jutting out. What was that for?
- You have something on your neck!
- Where? On my neck?
[A mole on his neck that's
as big as a watermelon seed.]
I'm sorry, but can you just
stay out of this?
- Isn't that one on your neck?
- I'm trying to do a show here.
On your neck over there.
Seriously.
What is that thing on your neck?
You got it.
It's stuck on your face.
[It stuck!]
Please!
I'll give this to you.
- Leave that watermelon.
- Here, I'll give it to you!
[Begging and pleading to the Giraffe.]
- Here, I'll give this to you.
- Spit a seed on my face.
[He wants Hyun Woo to spit
one on his face?]
[Hyun Woo drops the seed,
and heads back to the watermelon lady.]
I got it, right?
[As expected, right next to his big nose.]
[Off to the supermarket!]
Hey!
Wow!
I'm actually the first?
- What the heck, Suk Jin?
- Why?
- Did you even get one on your face?
- It's not there?
- I don't see it.
- It's on there.
- Where?
- It's not on there?
No, I don't see it.
- It's not there?
- No, I don't see it.
[Big-nose Brother wipes off the seed
with his own hand...]
Hey!
I failed?
You didn't cross the line.
- Seriously!
- You had one on your face?
- Yes, there was one!
- Then you should've showed it to him.
[Mr. Yoo doing a good job of
interfering the other teams.]
[Shaking hands?]
Let's hold hands at the
finish line together.
[Tiger and Giraffe agreeing to
not to interfere with one another?]
Why were you just about to
give that to me?
- Why were you about to give it to me?
- For you to play with it.
This feels like the supermarkets that I used
to hang around in when I was little.
I used to hang out in front of
a market like this all the time.
[Tiger and the Giraffe both having succeeded
heads off to the market together.]
Someone's coming.
[Walking in together side by side.]
[End of their truce.]
- Jong Kook dropped his.
- Right here.
- Where is it?
Success.
[Giraffe also succeeds.]
So the others failed?
Soo Hyun and Hyun Woo...
[First come first serve basis.
Only Kkuk and Kwang Soo passes.]
[Darn!]
- Is it still on my face?
- Where?
[The watermelon seed must have
fallen off of his face again.]
There it is.
Fail!
Where is it, Soo Hyun?
[Even running fanatic Soo Hyun fails
even though he eagerly runs back.]
- Soo Hyun.
- Is it even on your face?
Ji Hyo.
- Come here, Ji Hyo.
- I got it.
What are you doing going around
with that watermelon in your hand?
I got lucky with getting it on my face.
- Good job though, Ji Hyo.
- None of our team made it?
You need to step it up a
notch, Dong Hoon!
You really need to get it done this time.
Yes, I understand.
You think he's just scolding me, right?
He's scolding you too.
You're the only one left
to succeed now, Soo Hyun.
- We have to stop him any way that we can.
- Let's win this, okay?
[Other teams need to do what they can
to stop Soo Hyun from succeeding.]
Okay, this is your third mission.
- This mission is... a yogurt...
- Yogurt?
Were you singing that?
[All the neighborhood kids are
joining in on the song.]
It's a yogurt bowling game.
Bowling?
If you start looking around the village,
you'll find a yogurt bowling alley.
When you find it...
roll up the socks that you're wearing
to use it as your bowling ball.
- If you get a strike...
- I'm only wearing ankle socks.
- We have to stop Soo Hyun. Stop him.
- We have to stop Soo Hyun.
If Soo Hyun wins, the Blue Team wins.
First come first served.
Two people can win.
[First come first serve basis-
Two people per location!]
[Mr. Yoo trying to interfere again.]
He's so fast!
[Runner Soo Hyun leads the pack again!]
[He finds the bowling alley!]
Okay!
I told you to stop Soo Hyun.
[Now must take off their socks
to use it as their bowling ball.]
I'm already done.
Then you can go first.
[Hyun Woo takes the first turn.]
[Even though he did a good job of rolling,
he only succeeds in knocking down seven.]
Too bad!
[It's Soo Hyun's turn at last.]
[Huh?]
[Gutter ball]
We have to stop Soo Hyun
from winning.
I think he's competing against Hyun Woo.
- Since he's playing with Hyun Woo...
- We have to win this quickly.
[Oh?]
[Strike!]
Hurry up, Suk Jin!
Hurry back there!
Hurry!
[Back to the market with a yogurt in hand!]
Suk Jin!
- Is that Suk Jin?
- Huh?
- Success!
- Seriously?
[Suk Jin passes.]
[Still room for one more winner.]
I haven't seen anyone else go by.
[Too bad!]
I think Suk Jin is the only one
who's passed so far.
Really?
I'm going to make it this time,
and go back, okay?
[I'm going to be
the next person to make it in!]
[Strike!]
Give me my yogurt!
[Darn!]
Bye, Soo Hyun!
See you later!
[Red Team's Hyun Woo arrives.]
[Lee Hyun Woo- Pass.]
- Soo Hyun really is...
- Soo Hyun was the first to find one.
- Really?
- He was the first to find a bowling alley.
He was the first one to arrive.
He told me that he was actually out
bowling with his friends last night.
He was out bowling?
He must play a little bit of everything.
- How many did Soo Hyun knock down?
- He knocked down nine.
- He knocked down nine?
- Really?
Fail!
[Soo Hyun having unfortunately failed.]
- How do you run so fast?
- He really is a fast runner.
He may be a fast runner,
but he has no sense of direction.
Soo Hyun...
For all the talent that you posses,
you have too big of a gap.
You've got the speed,
and are physically in good shape.
He's nothing but a good looking idiot.
Okay, your next mission.
- Catch a chicken and bring it back.
- What the heck is that?
[Catch me if you can!]
- Catch a chicken and bring it back.
- What the heck!
- How am I going to do that?
- You just grab it!
It's just an animal.
Go and catch it.
- Catching chickens is so easy!
- I've never done it before.
I'll tell you where they are.
If you follow the path where
you found the watermelon ladies
you'll find a little garden to the right.
If you go in there,
you'll find your chickens.
- Aren't they really fast?
- I've never even touched them before.
- I don't think I can do it.
- There's no way Dong Hoon can do it.
- He won't be able to do it.
- He's really scared of chickens.
Okay, get ready.
- What do I do?
- I don't think I can run any more.
- First come first serve. Two people!
- Yes!
[Runs like the wind even after saying
that he couldn't run anymore.]
[Runner extraordinaire!
Run, Soo Hyun!]
What do I do?
I can't catch them.
[First to arrive at the farm
where the chickens are waiting.]
[Approaches the chickens while
breathing very heavily.]
[Who is that kid?]
[Ambush attack?]
[After saying that he's never done it before,
he works desperately to catch a chicken!]
How am I going to catch
these chickens?
[The chickens and the chase that has
Soo Hyun throwing his body around.]
- They're so quick!
- How am I going to catch one?
[Attacks again!]
[Two chicken in the corner!]
[Catches one of them!]
Just hang still.
[Runner Soo Hyun succeeds in
catching a chicken!]
[With a fierce determination
to catch a chicken...]
- Gary! We have to stop him!
- No, Ji Hyo! You can't!
- Please!
- Gary!
- We can't let him go!
- Ji Hyo!
[Wrangles Ji Hyo away from
him to leave.]
[Run, Soo Hyun!]
- Soo Hyun will get it done this time.
- I'm sure he'll bring back a chicken.
Soo Hyun said earlier that
he's never done it before.
And they could scare him once
he sees them in real life.
The roosters especially...
[There is no fear.
All he knows is to just run!]
- Who is it?
- It's Soo Hyun.
Soo Hyun!
[Soo Hyun succeeds!]
- Why didn't they stop him?
- They should've stopped him.
- Why didn't they stop Soo Hyun?
- It's Soo Hyun that embraces the chicken.
[Soo Hyun That Embraces the Chicken.]
[Don't come close...]
[But don't go too far either?]
It's Soo Hyun that embraces the chicken.
I'm going to take it to my mom.
- Look at this one.
- I got one.
[Of the three remaining players,
Gary succeeds in catching one.]
- Come on, Ji Hyo!
- Okay.
[Only ones left remaining are
sole female, Ji Hyo and scaredy cat Ro-Ro.]
How are you going to do this?
I don't think I can do it.
I really can't do this.
I really don't think I can do it.
Do you think you can do it?
[But after thinking about it, his face
keeps popping into Ro-Ro's head...]
Rather than dying by
Jong Kook's hands...
How are you doing that?
- Seriously... how are you doing that!
- Here, grab it.
- Hurry up and take this one.
- How am I to grab that?
Hurry up and take it!
[Blank Ji is conceding to Ro-Ro?]
- You're giving it to me?
- Hurry up and go.
Why are you giving it to me?
Thank you so much, Ji Hyo.
I'll be good to you for the rest of my life.
Mommy!
Thank you so much, Ji Hyo!
[Thank you, Ji Hyo...]
Ji Hyo caught it for me.
Gary that embraces the chicken.
You've become the dog that stole
the chicken just like the proverb goes.
Is this the dog chicken?
- Ji Hyo caught it for me.
- Really?
- Are you that scared of it?
- You try holding it.
They're really scary.
I know they are.
[Even Blank Ji is heading back
to the group.]
- Why did you give the chicken to Ha Ha?
- Ha Ha can't even get near the chickens.
- He was so terrified of them.
- But why did you give it to another team?
- Gary made it in, so you should've came.
- Thanks, Ji Hyo.
So thus, the Blue Team
is our first place winner.
[Blue Team wins first place
for all the members making it in first.]
- We have to pick again, right?
- Which one should we pick?
We don't have a three yet.
[First place winner, the Blue Team
chooses number three.]
It's time to move on to
the final location.
Okay, let's go.
[Go to 'S' university in Shinsoodong
and find the Running Man landmark.]
What is this?
[Blue Team's total number is 11.]
I wonder if we should've
picked five instead.
But we don't know if the higher number
is a good thing or a bad thing.
If we have to do something like
jump roping at the university...
If we have to have ten people
join in on the jump roping...
That would be disadvantageous.
[In that case, the higher number
would be disadvantageous.]
[What kind of a mission awaits
them at the final location?]
[Green Team's total count is seven.]
Some kind of a chance?
[Total count for the Red Team is nine.]
['S' University in Shinsadong.]
Look at all the people gathered here.
[Countless number of students gathered
upon hearing the news of their arrival.]
What is this?
[Unbelievable number of students
gathered around the field as well!]
[Just what is their final mission?]
I wonder what we'll be doing?
What is that?
[Three teams are finally gathered
around the field.]
The final mission for the
Flower Boy Athletic Competition.
There are over 300 students that
we have gathered around here.
Really?
[A few hours prior]
[Have accepted a total of 300 students
for the final mission participation.]
We love you!
We love you, Gary!
All the people over there?
[Through the process,
300 students have been gathered.]
[Thanking them in advance.]
You can take 100 students of
the 300 students that are gathered.
- A hundred?
Don't you think that's too large
of a scale?
Let's win this together!
[100 students per team.]
I'm so nervous!
[The students to run towards
the team they want to be on.]
[Come over here!]
[Once each of the teams have
gained their 100 participants.]
Thank you all for coming.
Song Ji Hyo!
[Green Team is full of male participants
thanks to Blank Ji's allure?]
We're full of men!
We're already a family.
Don't listen to him.
He's lying.
Jong Kook is lying.
Once the game is over...
[And thus, 300 students became
divided into three separate teams.]
There is one important rule.
What is it?
- You've all received numbered cards, right?
- Yes.
Blue Team is plus 11.
Green team is plus seven,
and Red Team is plus nine.
What is that?
[Could that be...]
[The secret of the numbered cards?]
[The power guides makes their entrance!]
This is crazy.
They all look so strong.
[Power]
The 27 men that are here will be added to
your teams depending on your numbers.
Can we pick them ourselves?
Oh my!
Look at this right up front.
[Red Team can choose nine men.]
[Green Team chooses their seven.]
Anyone here like Song Ji Hyo?
- Me!
- Pick me!
[Carefully inspecting their powerful thighs.]
Please save our team.
[Blue Team chooses their 11 members.]
I will now reveal the final mission.
[Time to reveal the final mission.]
It's a three way tug of war.
[Three way tug of war.]
- Nice!
- Hey!
We're all set.
[A never before seen scale of tug of war.]
[Blue Team- 114, Red Team- 112
and Green Team- 110 people!]
[Each team full of determination to win!]
What are you doing?
Each team must now get
into their position.
[Each team must get into their position.]
[A game on a unbelievable scale
made up of 330 people.]
[The final game of the
Flower Boy Athletic Competition is...]
[A giant three way tug of war.]
- Can I touch you?
- Sure, go ahead and touch me.
[Muscle Kkuk going around
spreading the energy.]
[An impromptu dance demonstration.]
You're going to have to pull
at a faster speed.
Let's all leave here with good lasting
memories even if we lose.
[Winning isn't what's important.
Let's make good memories together!]
You know what our battle cry is, right?
- Yes!
- Our battle cry is 'Ji Hyo'.
You pull on 'Hyo'.
Ji Hyo! Ji Hyo!
Ji Hyo!
- They sound like they're in the army.
- What do they expect us to do?
We'll be heaving at faster successions.
We'll do it in very quick successions.
Pull, pull, pull!
Let's do it in a very quick succession.
Let's just rip the rope out of their hands!
Fighting!
[Gary is bringing up
the tail of the Green Team.]
[At the tail of the Blue Team is Soo Hyun.]
[Bringing up the rear
for the Red Team is Ha Ha.]
[Ready]
Ready!
Nice!
[Go!]
[Red Team with quick successions.]
[Blue Team pulling just as fast.]
[Green Team is...]
Ji Hyo!
[Wow!
Unbelievable power of the Green Team!]
What do I do?
[The tail of the Blue Team not
seeming to budge at all.]
[Then perhaps the Green Team
is looking most likely to win?]
Ji Hyo!
[The Red Team getting pulled closer
and closer to the middle.]
[Is the Blue Team starting to lose
their ground and getting pulled in too?]
[The Green Team is getting
closer to the bell!]
[Will the Green Team win?]
[No!]
[First round- Green Team wins!]
[Green Team with the smallest number of
participants wins the first round!]
Ji Hyo!
It barely even moved.
It went much better than I expected.
You guys did a great job.
[Seriously?]
- Let's gather up a little bit more strength.
- We can do this!
We can do this!
- Blue Team, fighting!
- Fighting!
We're going to start again as soon
as we're centered and in place.
[Re-centering the prop
to ensure that it's good.]
- Do you want to be in charge of the bell?
- Can I try it?
- Want a taste of the bell?
- Should I? What do I do?
[Big-nose Brother going to
the tail for this round.]
Cheat.
Pull the rope towards you before starting.
[He's teaching
the innocent students to cheat?]
We're going to cheat.
Our team is going to go with cheating.
As soon as they start saying 'Start',
just start pulling the rope towards you.
We have to stay strong up here.
Let's pull it towards you as fast as you can.
- Blue Team, fighting!
- Fighting!
Ready!
[Second round]
[Start]
[Still standing power of Ji Hyo's army.]
[Red Team starting to get pulled in again.]
No way.
[The battle is between
the Blue Team and the Green Team.]
[Green Team is almost to the bell!]
[Blue Team clenching down
on their teeth!]
[This round is ours!]
[Just a little bit more!]
[Pulling a bit more in the direction
of the Blue Team?]
[Blue Team vs. the Green Team-
A very close game!]
[Just who...]
[Will it be the Blue Team or
the Green Team?]
[Blue Team wins!]
[Soo Hyun gets to his bell first!]
[And Big-nose Brother rings his bell
immediately after!]
[Blue Team wins by the split of a hair!]
[We won!]
[Blue Team's 114 members
enraptured in their joy!]
[Good job!]
We won?
It's okay!
This is what you call entertainment.
You fools!
Hey!
[Red Team is full of disappointment.]
Get your heads on straight!
What do we do?
It's okay, everyone.
We've just been given more time
to build our memories, right?
Something that could've been over in three
has been extended to four to five rounds.
So let's all cheer up and have fun, okay?
Let's make good memories.
Feel free to take pictures too.
- Is that okay?
- I'm sorry, Ha Ha!
[But the atmosphere is still bright and
cheery with all the female students?]
Okay, everyone back to their places.
This could be our final round.
Let's bring all the men to the front,
and the women to the back of the line.
[This could be the round
that determines who the victor is.]
[Ji Hyo's team rearranging
their team members.]
- Fighting!
- We can do this!
We can win it this time.
Let's win this!
Fighting!
Ji Hyo!
We're going to keep our place as is.
This is our chance!
[Let's finish it!
This is our chance!]
Our chance!
Fighting!
[Which team will the victory go to?]
Let's do this!
Ready!
[Ready... Go!]
[The round that could determine
the victor.]
[The three way rope that is
staying taut between the teams.]
[Lets finish it!]
[Red Team with a
high ratio of female students.]
[Starting to fall behind from
exhaustion...]
[The Green Team on the other hand...]
Ji Hyo!
[More Ji Hyo power!]
[Starting to gain more distance?]
[Will Ji Hyo claim the victory?]
[A little bit more!]
[The Blue Team gathering up
their last bit of strength!]
Just a little bit more!
[It's the Blue Team vs.
the Green Team again!]
Two more steps.
Just two more steps!
[Will it be the Blue Team's victory?]
Pull!
A little bit more!
[Or will it be the Green Team's win?]
[The round that will determine
the victor!]
[Will Blue Team's Soo Hyun get
to his bell first?]
[Then will it be the Green Team?]
[Green Team wins!]
[The final mission-
Giant three way tug of war.]
[The victory goes to the Green Team!]
No, we won.
We won!
Great job!
[Even though they lost,
because they gave it their best...]
- We were so close.
- We were, right? You all did great.
- You all did so great.
- We love you!
Ji Hyo!
[The ultimate victory of the
Flower Boy Athletic Competition...]
[Goes to the Green Team!]
To the winning team of the race today...
Congratulations!
[All thanks to Ji Hyo for
bringing in mostly male students!]
As I've always said,
a man needs to meet a good woman.
Ji Hyo and those men were very strong.
I sincerely want to thank all
the students here at the university.
- Thank you.
- Thank you very much.
Wow... Flower Boy Athletic Competition.
[Time to give out the prizes.]
[An awesome trophy for the winners!]
[Does this mean that the Green Team
is the ultimate flower boy group?]
We would like to thank all the students
here at the university once again.
And also to all the fans who stayed to
cheer us on to the end...
Thank you, everyone!
We'll see you next week!
[We'll be running again next week!]
Subtitles by DramaFever