You jerk!
What do I look like to you?
Do you have a death wish
or something?
[Kim Soo Mi has arrived.]
Stop right there!
[The woman that belies her age-
100% real action!]
[The frightening woman that will devastate
the members of Running Man today!]
[Most fearful woman in history of Running Man-
Just who will be the one to stop her?]
Go! Go away!
Die! Die, you jerk!
[Want to give it a try?]
[The Legendary Gumiho-
Running Man's glory?]
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Early one summer morning...]
[An amusement park covered
in a cloud of dread.]
What is this?
[Mysterious roman numerals in
the background?]
But I don't see a number one.
- Two, four... it's a couple race.
- Is Sa Yeon here?
It's about time for Sa Yeon
to come back again.
- Stop thinking so negatively.
- What? Why is Sa Yeon negative?
Why is wanting Sa Yeon here negative?
I really miss her.
- I know, I miss her too, but...
- What are you saying?
Why are you cutting me off?
I'm not done talking.
Sa Yeon has to come on as a guest for
all the other pretty girls to come on too.
- Really?
- That's how it's always been.
You're right.
That's very true.
I'll start off by telling you the
title of our race today.
Today's race is...
My love, Gumiho race.
(Gumiho = Nine tailed fox.)
[Mission title-
My love, Gumiho race.]
[Gumiho seduces unassuming men to
steal their souls.]
Wow!
Why are you so happy about that?
It's gumihos.
When it comes to gumihos,
only the pretty girls play the roles.
Only the top best looking actresses
have always played the role of a gumiho.
- Kim Hee Sung and...
- There's something sexy about gumihos.
- Yeah, you're right.
- And recently, it was Shin Min Ah.
- Yeah, I bet it'll be really pretty girls.
- Wow.
There are six beautiful ladies who
are waiting in the back.
I bet Ji Hyo's one of them.
There's Ji Hyo...
- Ji Hyo's back there.
- Ji Hyo will definitely partnered with Gary.
- Gary...
- But today is a Tuesday.
As for a hint as to who the gumihos are...
you'll find there are numbers behind you.
The identity of the ladies are
related to those numbers.
If you call out the first gumiho,
the guest will come out to the front.
Okay, shall we call them out?
Come on out!
[Who's the first gumiho hiding
behind roman numeral two?]
[Roman numeral two going up in flames
like an act of magic.]
[Who's the woman behind the mystery?]
- Wow!
- It's magic!
- What is that? Magic?
- Who is it?
- Who's back there?
- It's Kwon Ri Sae!
Kwon Ri Sae!
[The first gumiho is Kwon Ri Sae of
Ladies' Code!]
[Made her formal debut as a member of
Ladies' Code on Audition Star.]
Let's welcome Kwon Ri Sae!
Welcome!
- Kwon Ri Sae!
- Hi!
- Why do you keep blocking me?
- I'm sorry.
[Yoo Hyuk all flustered at
having seen their first guest.]
- Seriously.
- I just want to see her!
- What about our next guest?
- Come on out!
[Their second gumiho is...]
[The elegant form...]
[The deep gaze in her eyes...]
[Shock]
[The screen next to it catches fire!]
Oh no!
- No!
[Complete chaos.]
[A sudden mad rush to escape the fire.]
One is still okay.
That one is still okay.
[One fortunately survives the fire.]
- That one is okay though.
- But Ji Hyo was behind the second one.
The second one was Ji Hyo.
- What was that?
- What kind of a mess was that?
Did you see our guests running away?
[All the guests fleeing from the fire.]
- Who were the ladies that ran away?
- I saw Kim Suk.
Kim Suk, right?
[A familiar back view.]
- I saw Kim Suk!
- I'm positive it was Kim Suk!
It's Kim Suk, isn't it?
Kim Suk!
Come on, seriously...
- I'm positive I saw Kim Suk.
- Okay, number three, please come out.
- Come on out.
- Song Ji Hyo, I saw you.
- Just come out here, Ji Hyo!
- Just come out.
- Look at how pretty she's dressed today.
- Hey, Song Ji Hyo!
[The second gumiho is,
our very own Blank Ji!]
[Mouth gaped wide open.]
[Looking so beautiful these days.]
- When Ji Hyo's dressed like that...
- I was hiding back there.
You look so pretty
when you're dressed like that.
- Why are you dressed like that today?
- You look so pretty.
Your behavior is so different all of a sudden
after you saw Kim Suk back there.
[A difference in his behavior
after seeing Kim Suk?]
- What's wrong with you?
- Ji Hyo is mine.
- Ji Hyo, you look so beautiful.
- She looks like an angel.
Ri Sae and Ji Hyo are
the best looking right now.
There are some unbelievable woman still
waiting to come out back there. You just wait.
But when I saw their retreating backs,
it looked like a bunch of middle aged ladies.
[And continuing on...]
[even more amazing guests
makes their appearance.]
[Their third gumiho is... Kim Suk.]
Look, it's Ri Sae's mother.
- Why did you run away earlier?
- I felt the hot flames coming towards me.
- We saw you running.
- Why did you gain so much weight?
I had no idea that I'd be called out
so early in the morning.
I made two bowls of ramen before
I went to bed last night.
[Unaware of the early filming schedule,
she ate two bowls of ramen before bed.]
- I don't know who else is back there.
- There are two other back there, right?
- No, there are three others.
- If I were to give you a hint...
- I was the weakest woman back there.
- Seriously?
Yes. There are some
fierce women back there.
I wonder who else is back there.
Number six who still didn't get burned
in that situation...
I'm curious to see how fierce
that woman is.
[The last screen that's still standing
remaining untouched after that chaos...]
[Frightening for some reason...]
When all the screens caught on fire,
we all started screaming and getting scared
but she didn't even blink an eye.
- There could be only one woman.
- She didn't even budge during that chaos?
No, she didn't even move
from her spot.
[Just who could it be?]
Gumiho number four,
please come on out!
- Who is it?
- It's not a man, is it?
No, it's Song Eun Ee.
[A permanent fixture in the comedy world,
Song Eun Ee.]
[Flustered]
- What is she doing here?
- Look, she's wearing a skirt.
[The rare sight of Eun Ee in a skirt.]
- What are you doing in a skirt?
- I barely walked over here in this thing.
I barely made it here wearing this thing.
[Yoo Hyuk embarrassed to see his friend
of 20 years wearing a skirt.]
- Why are you wearing that?
- Why?
I wore it to look pretty.
What!
[Her friend not knowing what to do from his
embarrassment of seeing her in a skirt.]
- Just put your regular sweat pants on.
- I wore it because I was told to wear it!
- What are you doing?
- I was told to wear it!
- I'm so scared of her like that.
- What is she doing dressed like that?
- What is this?
- Why are you dressed like that?
- Why did you dress her in a skirt?
- Why did you tell her to dress like that?
- I can't stand seeing her like that!
- Stop that! Stop doing that!
[Just because she's in a skirt doesn't mean
that her nature hasn't gone anywhere.]
- Seriously.
- Seriously!
Why are you guys all frowning like that?
Is this the best you
can treat a guest on your show?
- Stand with your legs closed together.
- I do have them closed.
Let's all give her a round of applause.
If we're not teamed up with either Ri Sae
or Ji Hyo, then it's all over.
- Did I shock you? Were you really shocked?
- I was really shocked.
Then what about the fifth gumiho?
[Time for the fifth gumiho
to make her entrance.]
- Is it going to get worse?
- Can't you tell by how this is going?
- Who is it?
- Is it someone pretty?
[What?
It's someone pretty?]
[A fierce welcome.]
- It's a pretty girl!
- Park So Hyun!
[The ultimate baby faced beauty,
Park So Hyun.]
- Park So Hyun!
[A total different response from Eun Ee
who's also in her 40's like So Hyun.]
- What a relief!
- It's Park So Hyun!
- I don't know if she'll remember.
- She has a bad memory.
- Do you remember me? It's me, Ha Ha.
- She has really bad memory.
[She's known for her forgetfulness.]
- Wow, this is really...
- Okay.
Do you have a vague idea of what
these numbers mean by now?
- Is it their age group or something?
- Number six, please come on out!
[At last...]
[The sixth, and the final gumiho.]
- Look at how pretty she is.
- She's pretty!
[She's... pretty?]
[Automatically breaking out into
an expression of shock.]
[The godmother of comedy,
Kim Soo Mi is here!]
[Her overwhelming charisma!]
[Unstoppable force and power!]
[She is here!]
[So nice to be here!]
[All the men quieting down
at the sight of seeing her.]
- We didn't know it was you.
- We had no idea that it was you.
I had no idea.
- Wow...
- You look so beautiful.
What a sweet sack of lies.
[She really is one fierce woman!]
Wow... I really had no idea.
- I had no idea.
- They really don't tell you?
No, we had no idea.
I will explain to you how
The Gumiho Race is going to play out.
All the guests that are on here today
are our loveable gumihos.
Yes, they are.
- We love them!
- Yes, we do.
- What's wrong with your expression, Jae Suk?
- Excuse me?
- What's wrong with your expression?
- Right now...
I was just thinking to myself that there
aren't many knockouts here.
And this is the second time in my life
seeing Eun Ee in a skirt.
Okay, each of the gumihos will seduce
one man to be their partner in a team.
How about instead of seducing a man,
we just gobble one up?
I will first tell you how many tails
each of the gumiho has.
Kim Soo Mi has six tails.
Park So Hyun and Song Eun Ee
each have four tails.
And Kim Suk and Song Ji Hyo
each have three tails.
And Ri Sae has two tails to start off with.
I guess it's more advantageous to
be teamed up with Kim Soo Mi.
- Since she already has six.
- Yeah, which means she only needs three more.
Each of the gumihos needs to seduce
the man they're going to team up with.
Each of the men will have a brief chance to
showcase their attractiveness to the gumihos.
There aren't many knockouts amongst
you men either.
- What are you talking about?
- What are you saying?
- Just like you said earlier...
- We're all good catches over here!
No, there is one knockout.
- There's only one?
- There's only one.
- Yes, there is one.
- Really?
- Who could she mean?
- The person who said, 'Really'.
[Just then, an appropriate song
starts playing in the background.]
We don't have that kind of a relationship!
[It seems as though Kkuk
has already been marked.]
You each have one chance to say
something quick about yourselves.
Ji Hyo, if there's anything that I haven't
been really nice to you about in the past...
I will apologize to you
for them all right now.
Ji Hyo, I've always thought...
- Ji Hyo, it's Monday today!
- Ji Hyo!
Ji Hyo, since the very beginning...
I've always liked you from the beginning.
Ji Hyo, you've always been
so beautiful to me.
Ji Hyo, you and I used to be so close.
I love you!
Gumihos will start their selection
according to their age.
We will start with Kim Soo Mi.
She has six tails.
Yes, she has the biggest advantage.
Jae Suk has always been very
good with elders.
[Going around checking out
their physical condition?]
She looks like she's at the cattle market
trying to pick her cattle.
All you need is to check that guy out.
- Don't flex your muscles.
- You're being too lax.
You're the best out of them all.
[She chooses Yoo Hyuk.]
- You look very good together!
- You two match in your greens.
- It's a couple look.
- It's a couple outfit.
[After a closer look,
they're even dressed like a couple.]
They're dressed like a couple today.
The new couples can now
move off to the right.
Let's see a big smile on your face, Jae Suk.
You're starting off with six tails already.
[A huge advantage! Soo Mi and
Jae Suk starting off with six tails.]
If we're talking in a marriage sense,
it's like starting out with six houses.
I'm jealous!
- I'm so jealous.
- It's like starting out with six houses.
We have a bigger advantage
than any other teams.
- Yes, I'm jealous.
- We're just better than you guys.
- Yes, you're better off right now.
- Yes, we are.
- Next up is...
- There are two in this age group.
Park So Hyun will now make
her selection.
- I don't know what to do.
- Take a look at each of us.
Yes, go ahead and take a look at them.
All you're doing is playing a game with
the person for a few hours today.
- You're not choosing someone to date.
- Just take it easy and think comfortably.
You guys all know that Park So Hyun
is starting out with four houses right now.
[Gumiho So Hyun starting out with
an impressive number of four tails herself.]
- Gary.
- Gary?
[Chooses Gary without any hesitation.]
It's an honor.
I'm staring out with four houses!
Congratulations.
Come stand over here.
Next up is Song Eun Ee,
who is also starting out with four tails.
I can already see where this is headed.
I know Eun Ee very well.
[Will it really be the man
she seemed to have chosen earlier?]
- Do we have no choice in this matter?
- Cue the music.
La la... here I come.
[You can guess, right?]
There we go!
[Finally standing next to the man
she's alluded to earlier.]
[What?
She's just passing him by?]
[Just who will she choose?]
- I choose Ha Ha.
- Seriously?
- Wow!
- Really?
I was totally expecting to be picked.
[Gumiho Eun Ee chooses Ha Ha!]
[Totally speechless.]
You should be happy with
the four houses!
Okay!
- Wow, this is...
- At this rate...
You never know who
you're going to be paired up with.
Is Kim Suk next?
[It's now Gumiho Kim Suk's turn
with her three tails.]
[Is this what you call over one mountain
only to encounter another one?]
Come on, don't do that!
[Taking the cue to get out of the way.]
[Praying?]
Suk!
- Suk!
- Show him what you've got.
One, two, three!
You better not float away from me.
Tighten up your arms here so that
no wind blows through to carry you away.
Jong Kook...
Jong Kook?
- Yes?
- Just endure it for a few hours.
Just endure it for a few hours.
[A word of advice from the big sister...]
Do you see how she's standing right now?
Look at how relaxed she looks.
[Extremely relaxed pose.]
[The ease of someone
who already has six tails.]
We're starting out with ease.
Okay, it's Song Ji Hyo's turn.
[Gumiho Blank's turn with her three tails.]
Look at how nervous they look.
Why is this making us so nervous?
[Please Ji Hyo...]
[Hm...]
Let's go.
[Blank Ji's self-sacrifice to help out
Kwang Soo in his quest for romance?]
- What are you thinking?
- What is she thinking?
You better realize
what an honor this is for you.
- Look at them over there.
- Look at how happy Kwang Soo is.
[His grin is stretched from ear to ear.]
[There he goes again with his
farfetched romantic dreams.]
Ri Sae... I guarantee that he's going to ask
you for your number before the show's over.
- Don't tell him what it is.
- Come one now.
- I don't have a cell phone.
- You don't have a cell phone?
Why are you refusing already?
[Strong line of defense.]
Are all the gumihos happy with
the men that they've seduced?
- Yes.
- We will now start the race.
- Okay, here we go!
[My Love, Gumiho- Start the race!]
[Boards the bus waiting for them
to take a spin around the park.]
[The Running Man Bus-
Bus number 9999.]
We've got the couple with an older woman,
with a younger man.
- And over here is...
- An older lady with her regular kid customer.
Okay, an older lady with
her regular kid customer.
And this couple over here
just met for the first time.
[Jong Kook and Suk are a couple
meeting for the very first time.]
Those two are the chairman
and his secretary.
This is my Madame and I'm
her attendant.
- What would you like to be?
- Stalker. You're her stalker.
[Kwon Ri Sae and her stalker?]
Just be her stalker.
- Why?
- What did she say?
I just asked her what she thought
of these two up here.
She said that she thinks that
he looks very sincere and honest.
- Thank you so much.
- Then she asks me what he does for a living.
[Doesn't even know who
the Giraffe is.]
- What is your job?
He started out as a model,
and is now a comedian.
He's an actor.
SBS comedy department wants me to
tell you that your taxes are due.
[So he does have a job...]
- This is my first time here.
- You've never been here before?
- No, I haven't.
- Seriously?
What is that?
There's something up there.
- They're tails.
- Look, they're tails.
- We have six tails.
- Six?
Congratulations!
[Four tails for So Hyun.]
- That looks like a fashion statement.
- It suits you.
- I'm sorry.
- The belt is too small.
[Gumiho Eun Ee having difficulties
putting her tails on.]
[Two tails for the youngest gumiho, Ri Sae.]
Kwang Soo's not even
cracking a lot of jokes today.
- What's wrong with you, Kwang Soo?
- We're just starting.
He always tries to be cooler than he is
whenever he meets a pretty girl.
Don't even think that you have a chance.
[Giraffe always trying to combine
work and romance together...]
So what are we doing today?
It's a mission.
My love gumiho-
round about karaoke bar.
Pick an amusement ride to sing a song on
and score above 90 points to succeed.
If you look behind you, you will see that
there are three rides with a mike installed.
- Okay.
- The amusement rides to choose from are...
The Viking.
And the orbiter that you see over there.
And finally, the rotator teacup
over there.
Find the mike that is installed on the ride
and sing the song as loud as you can
to score the highest score possible.
There can be up to two teams
per amusement ride.
I see.
[The Orbiter, Rotator Teacup, The Viking]
Kwang Soo, you have to hold her hand
while you two are heading to your missions.
- He says we have to hold hands.
- Really?
[Oh my, look at that Giraffe blush.]
Move!
- Move! Move out of my way!
- Get out of my way!
[Older lady and her regular kid customer
acting like a couple of brats.]
What are you two doing?
- What songs do you like to sing?
- I only know recent songs.
- I don't remember any of the older songs.
- Then do you not even remember me?
[Since it's forgetful So Hyun,
that's more than possible...]
Hello.
[Eun Ee and Ha Ha are the first
to board their ride.]
Where should we sit?
Do we just sit anywhere?
- This isn't a rollercoaster?
- Please get on the ride.
We're going to be hanging
upside down on this thing.
I think this is a combination of the Viking
and the rollercoaster ride.
But this is... this isn't right!
- So this goes back and forth?
- This isn't right!
- Check out where the mike is located.
- Ah... the mike.
So I can't place the mike
wherever I want to?
- Where's the mike?
- Oh my gosh! There's the mike!
[The mike is located...]
[Way up there?]
[There's one here.]
[And one over here!]
[The only way to get the score needed is to
sing well when they're right by the mike.]
- There's the mike up there!
- What?
How are we supposed to sing like that?
[Here's another one right here.]
- We should've gotten on the Viking.
- No kidding!
We're ruined!
- We're ruined!
- I can't believe they're starting the music.
I can hear the music playing!
I can hear the music!
[The orbiter gets on the way,
with the music starting in the background!]
No way!
[Once around backwards.]
[The mike is waiting for them
to start singing.]
Save me!
I'm sorry,
but I can't handle rides like this.
Seriously?
Don't say that!
Eun Ee, you have to sing!
I already passed the mike!
[The key is to locate the mike
and sing out loud towards it.]
[Isn't it easy?
Just sing towards the mike.]
[The key is to locate the mike
and sing the song towards the mike!]
Oh my goodness!
I passed by the mike again!
I sang a verse.
I got to sing one verse.
I'll tell you where the mikes are.
Do you see them up there?
- Where?
- Up there. It's way up there.
- What?
- There's one at the top over there.
Up there?
- What? Way up there?
- That twinkling thing up there?
It picks up your voice very well.
[Sing the song towards this mike.]
[A total of three mikes on the Viking.]
- You have to sing towards those three mikes.
- This is really hard.
Come on, you know how forgetful she is!
We're going to sing, 'On the bus'.
- Let's do this!
Wow, my heart is pounding.
[Fearless Blank Ji singing happily
at the top of her lungs.]
[Singing at the top of her lungs
towards all the mikes.]
What did you say, Suk Jin?
One more time.
What did you say?
[Unable to sing.]
- Why aren't you singing?
- This is too scary!
- How is this scary?
- You should see your hair!
- This is too scary!
[Big-nosed Brother's hair sticking
straight up at the roots.]
[Soo Mi and Jae Suk taking their turn.]
[The song they chose is Gumiho Soo Mi's
very own song, 'The Gentleman'.]
- This is Soo Mi's...
- This is my first time at an amusement park.
This is her first time on an amusement ride.
[Extreme nervousness.]
Look at how high up we are.
Does it normally go up this high?
- What to do... I have gastroenteritis.
- Come on, seriously!
Why do you have so many problems?
You look healthy as a horse to me.
Don't scream at me like that.
I have gastroenteritis.
If I get too stressed out, I have
to rush to the bathroom right away.
- Oh my goodness.
- The mike is up here.
[A total of four mikes on this ride.]
Okay, here we go.
[But the key is to sing loud and clear
towards where the mikes are located.]
- Behind you! There's a mike behind you!
- There's a mike behind you!
- There's another mike behind you.
- Be quiet!
[Soo Mi bursting out into
a fit of laughter.]
It's really scary when it flips
upside down like that.
[Keeping his gaze fixated straight ahead,
and his pronunciation accurate.]
[But he needs to be
singing towards the mike...]
- There's his usual expression.
- That's the normal expression on his face.
Yeah, that's what you
really look like.
[His usual idiot of Sundays expression
is back on his face.]
[The couple in the teacup are singing
with every fiber of their being.]
[There's a mike over here!]
The song's finally over.
I feel like death.
- My head is killing me.
- You did good.
My head is killing me.
- Zero points.
- Nothing?
Zero points?
How can that be?
[So Hyun and Gary taking their turn
on the Viking.]
[The song of their choosing is 'Gee',
but no one seem to be singing?]
So Hyun!
You have to sing!
You have to sing the song!
Please sing!
Sing!
Sing the song!
No, that's not it!
That's not the right lyrics!
[Forgetful So Hyun not knowing
the words to the song.]
That's not the part, So Hyun!
Why are you singing a different song?
What's their score?
[Oh my...]
29 points?
That's just absurd!
How can it only be 29 points?
- Let's sing something upbeat.
- okay, how about 'Night after night'?
Night after night.
You two look good together.
- You two look good together.
- Really?
[Gumiho Kim Suk in a much more uplifted
mood after hearing Jae Suk's remark.]
Let's do this!
[A mike hidden in the corner.]
[On their way after having
loosened up their vocal cords.]
Okay.
[Their song selection- 'Night after night'.]
[Screaming out loud from
their excitement.]
[Screaming out loud towards the mikes.]
Over here, over here!
The mike is over here!
Wow... he's really good.
Must be because he's a singer.
You two look good together!
- What did you say?
- I said, you two look good together.
Wow... is it really possible to score
90 points on this thing?
[Sing the song towards the mike.]
[Singing loud and clear towards the mike.]
Their timing is great.
[End of the song.]
- They really scored 95 points?
- How did they do that?
- They seriously scored 95 points?
- The timing on the song was perfect.
- That one part...
- The timing on that part was perfect.
95 points indicates the chances
of the two of you working out as a couple.
[Us two?]
I'm a little embarrassed.
[Kim Suk and Jong Kook heading out
with their hands clasped tightly together.]
I can't believe that just happened.
- How did that happen?
- We must really be in sync.
Are we the first ones to pass?
- We're the first ones to pass the mission?
- Yes, you are.
[Wins themselves a tail!]
[Her position is a little...]
- Here, you can put it on.
- What are you doing?
What's wrong?
Great job!
- Great job!
- That frown is finally starting to go away.
[Gumiho Suk now with four tails!]
[The perfect Idiot of Sundays expression.]
Louder!
[Singing 'The wrong meeting'.]
[Just sounds like a bunch of screaming.]
[The song finally ends.]
- What's the score?
- 98 points!
[What?
They actually passed?]
How did they do that?
- Eun Ee...
- Get down quickly.
Yes, I'm coming down. I'm never
even going to look at that again.
[The older lady and her regular kid customer
pass their mission!]
- That wasn't even right.
- Good luck.
[Envious of their success.]
- Let's go.
- Lets go.
The sooner you finish the mission,
the sooner you can get going.
- Let's go.
- Let's finish this.
[Finally gets to escape from the orbiter.]
We passed the mission.
- Did we win first place?
- Did we come in first?
- Are we the first ones to pass?
- Kim Jong Kook came in first.
- Are you serious? Already?
That's amazing.
- We have five tails!
- Do you like me now?
[Gumiho Eun Ee now has five tails.]
Let's go!
Let's go to our next location.
[The final tail goes to...]
93 points!
[Jae Suk and Soo Mi is the next couple
to pass the mission!]
- That game was very disadvantageous for me.
- Why, So Hyun?
She would forget the lyrics she just saw
by the time she got up to the mike.
[Expecting forgetful So Hyun to
memorize the lyrics...]
- So then she wouldn't sing the song at all.
- What was the score that you received?
We scored 29 points.
Okay, here's a sudden game
we're going to play.
Shout out your favorite between
jjajangmyun and jjamppong. One, two, three!
- Jjajangmyun.
Wow, they both gave the same answer.
Kiss her!
Okay, your turn. Ddukbbokki
or blood sausage. One, two, three.
- I don't eat that stuff.
- Ddukbbokki.
- One, two, three.
- I don't eat that stuff.
[Not a match.]
I don't eat that stuff.
I really don't eat that stuff.
I never eat that stuff.
I'm serious.
I really don't eat that stuff.
- No, he doesn't eat that stuff.
- No, he really doesn't.
Don't be offended, Suk.
He really doesn't eat that stuff.
- He really doesn't eat it.
- I really don't like that stuff.
- I really want to take my fist and...
- I don't eat that stuff.
- You know that she comes from a rich family?
- Really? Are you serious?
Her sister is a doctor.
Ah! Jong Kook's older brother
is also a doctor!
- Her older sister is a doctor.
- You two have a lot in common.
- See that?
- Why do we have so much in common!
- Ri Sae started out from beauty pageants.
- Really?
- Where? Where from?
- From beauty pageants.
I was the runner up
for Miss Korean in Japan.
- Wow!
- Seriously?
- That's amazing?
- In Japan?
Ah... really?
[Huh?
Suddenly starts speaking in Japanese?]
Excuse me?
[Ri Sae can't understand what Soo Mi
is saying to her in Japanese.]
- No, I was just trying to...
- What were you trying to say?
No, it was just a line that I memorized
from a movie that I was in.
- I remember you speaking Japanese in a movie.
- That's right, you did.
Yes, I remember that.
[Jamwondong Han River District]
- I have a bad feeling about this.
- What is this?
[The next game is... water bucket?]
- What is that?
- Water bucket?
Is that the mission?
[Gumiho's levitation- Run with gumiho on your
piggyback and put the bucket on their man.]
[But if you drop your gumiho on your way,
you fail the mission.]
The men will carry their gumihos on their
piggybacks from here
and start off from this starting point.
If you look at all
the water buckets over there
you'll see that there are some with
water in them, and some without.
The sooner you get there, the
better chances of getting an empty bucket
and you must get back to the starting line
to pass the mission.
- Okay, I understand.
- Get into your position.
You won't know which one has the water
in it until you get there.
If you find that there's water in
the bucket that you ran up to
you may run up to a different one.
Do your job, Jong Kook.
[Come on...]
[The regular kid customer feeling anxious.]
Seriously!
[Run towards the buckets
as fast as you can!]
[Screams heard from all over the place.]
[Random Mr. Capable taking the lead]
[So Hyun and Gary arrive back
at the starting line.]
[Gary and So Hyun come in first.]
What took you so long, Jong Kook?
[Suk and Jong Kook taking their
sweet time to come back.]
Wow, that was quick.
[Random Mr. Capable picking up speed to
make it in first through the finish line.]
That's disappointing.
- Okay, let's go.
- Let's go!
- Kang Gary can commence the show.
- What?
[Flustered]
Okay, I'll give it a try.
- Let's do it!
- Everyone, take the water bucket...
and pour it over your heads
however you'd like.
- We understand!
- Okay.
- Are you all ready?
- Yes.
Then starting with Kwang Soo,
everyone shout out a number.
One, two, three, four, five.
Finished with the numbers!
Run! Run!
What are you doing?
[Dumping his water into Jong Kook's bucket.]
[A total waterfall.]
[Wow! Ji Hyo and Suk Jin
take second place!]
[Total exhaustion.]
Suk Jin and Ji Hyo, pass!
- Sorry, Jong Kook.
- Hilarious.
- It's the mike giving me the problem.
- He's lying. He did that on purpose.
- He usually isn't the type to lose.
- Jong Kook...
Jong Kook, this time...
It's not because Suk is heavy.
It's because his heart is feeling heavy.
- You know what I mean, right?
- Yes, you're right.
He just wants to get it over with.
And this is the first time I've seen
Jong Kook so unmotivated to win.
This is the second time I've seen
Jong Kook being like this.
The other time was when
Bong Sun was on the show.
- I understand why now.
- You get it, right?
I think I get it too.
I really think that I get it.
Okay, let's do this again.
This is hurting my pride a little.
- Two people have already won.
- Everyone to the starting line.
- My next guess is Kwang Soo.
- We have to find the right bucket.
Let's check how many tails
each team has!
- Two!
- Two tails. How many tails for you?
- We currently have seven tails!
- How many tails?
- We have four tails.
We have five tails!
Lee Kwang Soo's team
needs to pick it up a notch.
- Attention!
- You're doing great!
Attention!
Pay attention!
- With your eyes straight ahead!
- You're doing great as an MC!
[Ri Sae-Kwang Soo and Soo Mi-Jae Suk
are neck and neck.]
[Wow! Soo Mi and Jae Suk
come in at third place!]
- Why are you...
- Why did you guys spray it on us?
- No, we didn't!
- You guys sprayed us with water!
You guys really are something else.
- Things like that can happen.
- You're acting like a rude little brat!
Just because you're pretty,
you think you can just do whatever?
- Calm down, Suk.
- You better watch yourself.
I'll grab you by your hair
if you're not more careful.
As of this point,
all the tails are now gone.
- What?
- We were playing for the tail again?
What do we do?
This time, the team that comes in last will
give up one of their tails to the winner.
[The team to come in last at this round
gives up one of their tails to the winner!]
- This round?
- We have to win no matter what.
- We have to make sure to win this time.
- Okay, MC!
[MC Gae once again makes his appearance.]
We are standing by the Han River
in Jamwon District.
We now have two rounds left
to play in this game.
Can you tell us how you feel right now?
I will always remember this lady's grace,
and pay her back for it somehow!
- Little kid, I love you!
- Then two more helpings of the blood sausage!
- Okay, fighting!
- Fighting.
We are now meeting with a couple
who's love is just starting to bud.
How do you feel right at this moment?
[Punishing the stalker?]
What are you doing?
Stop it!
Don't do it!
What about Lee Kwang Soo
do you find attractive?
Excuse me?
- What did you say?
- Okay, let's move on.
[A clean cut-off over to the next team.]
- Team Kim Jong Kook and Kim Suk. How are you?
- I don't think he's putting in the effort.
- I'm very discontent.
- Why aren't you putting in the effort?
I'm not in my best condition today.
Why is it that you're in a bad condition
whenever Bong Sun and I come out on the show?
Attention!
- Attention.
- MC Gary.
- You're doing great!
- You're a great MC.
- MC Gary.
No cheating.
No cheating!
- MC, fighting.
-  Sportsmanship.
- Check your mike one time.
- Yes.
[The team that comes in last in this round
will have to give up one of their tails!]
[More focused on revenge
rather than winning.]
[Eun Ee, Ha Ha and Gary, Ri Sae
makes it back to the starting line!]
[Suk and Jong Kook comes in last.]
This is so much fun!
This is so fun.
- What are you doing?
- Don't you think that this is too much?
- How am I being too much?
- I'm getting my revenge if you keep this up.
- I'm going to marry you if you keep this up.
- It's not that bad!
- You're seriously being too much.
- That's a scary revenge.
- What have I done that's so bad?
- That's too severe of a revenge.
- That's too harsh.
- Suk loses one of her tails, right?
- Yes.
- Do I just take one off of her?
[So Hyun and Gary takes one of Suk's tails
for having come on at first place.]
Now I'm left feeling kind of bad
for Jong Kook.
Please excuse me while I do this.
Hang on.
Hang on a second, So Hyun.
I know how that must feel,
but you need to hold still for a minute.
Okay, all set.
[So Hyun and Gary's tail count
is now up to five.]
- And the team that came in second...
- You have more?
[The second and third place team
also gets a tail.]
Palmiho!
(Meaning eight tailed fox)
- Palmiho?
- So you just need one more?
- How did that happen?
- We all have to join our forces together.
- He's right.
- We have to work together.
We all have to join our forces together.
Join our forces together.
[Join their forces together?]
[Next week... the moment where they truly
will have to join their forces will arrive.]
Eliminate each other's name tags to
be the last one left remaining.
[Superhuman superpowers.]
[At last, all the superheroes are
gathered together in one place.]
- Hulk!
- Ironman! I'm the Ironman!
[The battle of the superheroes.]
[Will they join their forces together?]
[Or will they battle each other
to stand as the best amongst the group?]
[Next week's Running Man-
Running Man Avengers.]
[9999 bus heads off to their next location.]
- Did you enjoy your second mission?
- Yes.
I actually feel a little nervous
about having too many tails.
What if we get them all stolen from us
at the end in an elimination race?
- I'm sure you will.
- I'm sure that's what we're doing.
- I'm sure that's what'll happen.
- Ones with a lot of tails will be targeted.
Wait, don't you guys only need
one more to get all your tails?
- We're a palmiho.
- We have to stop them.
- We really do have to stop them.
- Yes, we have to stop them.
We only have two tails.
My elbow here is like a hammer.
I'm going to knock you all away with this.
[Don't even come near my tails!
I'll knock you out with my elbow!]
- You're scaring me.
- With your elbow?
It hurts even more because
there's no flesh over my elbow bone.
Want to see how it feels?
It really hurts.
[A frightening declaration of war.]
She made a clear declaration of war.
She said she'll knock you all out.
- I'm going to knock you out like this.
- Her elbow.
- Isn't Gary a Chilmiho? (Seven)
- No, we're a Yookmiho. (Six)
Yookmiho?
- Then are you Ohmiho?
- Ohmiho.
- What about you?
- Sammiho. (Three)
- I'm sorry, honey.
- She just said, 'I'm sorry, honey'!
- She's apologizing to him.
- What are you so sorry to him about?
- What about your team?
- We're a Samiho.
- We're Eemiho.
- Eemiho?
Stop focusing on dating then,
and focus more on the work at hand.
- Concentrate more on work.
- Stop focusing everything on romance.
- How many tails do I have?
- Six.
- I have six?
- Please try to remember things!
- Please, So Hyun!
- Why? What is it?
She can't remember anything!
I've already had to remind her three times
that we have six tails.
[Forgetful So Hyun forgetting things
in the blink of an eye.]
- Yookmiho!
- Yookmiho.
She's unexpectedly high maintenance.
[Forgetful So Hyun turning out
to be pretty high maintenance.]
[Arriving at their next destination.]
Hello.
[Gumihos enter the restaurant first?]
The table isn't even set.
If it's a game about eating fast, then I'll be
the first one to finish and get out of here.
[What's the mission that awaits
them here at the restaurant?]
- Hello.
- Yes, hello.
- Have you decided what you want to order?
- No, I haven't decided yet.
Do I just tell her what I want to order?
- Yes, make your food selection.
- Okay.
[What kind of meat should I
order for my wraps?]
- Enjoy your meal.
- Thank you.
[A tray full of side dishes
over to Blank Ji as well.]
[Let's just eat for now.]
- The top sirloin.
- Okay.
Is it a speed eating contest?
I'm really confident I can
win that one.
I ate a lot this morning at breakfast
so my stomach is already stretched out.
You can just choose whatever you
want to eat from the menu.
[Happiness from having seen the menu.]
- I'm going to eat a lot of meat.
- But this is kind of making me nervous.
- Why?
- I feel like they're up to something.
What is this?
- Come over here.
- We don't know what the mission is yet.
You still don't know?
Then what is this?
They told us to order something,
so I ordered something from the menu.
[A lettuce wrap for the man who's
been put under their spell.]
Stop complaining and just eat it.
[Time to reveal the next mission.]
When you were ordering off the menu...
remember the order in which the
waitress put down the side dishes
and make a lettuce wrap with that dish to
feed it to your men in the same order.
- What?
- Huh?
Do you understand the game?
[Lettuce wrap eating contest
according to your gumiho's memory skills.]
[Do you remember this contest which became
the topic of conversation two summers ago?]
Then that gives Ji Hyo the advantage.
No, because I was looking at the menu
when she was setting the table.
[A mission that the gumihos couldn't
even have fathomed a guess at.]
How can you not remember a single thing!
I can't remember the first and the last
dish that she set down whatsoever.
- Let's just hurry up and do this.
- This isn't even right.
Wow, this is unbelievable.
This is very sneaky.
She says she doesn't remember at all.
She says she was looking at the menu
when the food was brought in.
Ri Sae just lied to me and told me that
the table was already set when she came in.
No, it really was.
How are we going to do this?
[Correct answer- Kimchi, lettuce wrap sauce,
perelli leaves, seaweed, anchovy, garlic...]
[eggplant, peppers, quail eggs,
soybean paste soup, rice.]
- In the order it was placed on the table?
- The order it was placed on the table?
- I have no idea what she did.
- Do you know what she laid down first?
I'm pretty sure the table was already set.
Was it not?
Are you going to keep lying?
I remember walking in here and thinking
how delicious everything was going to be.
All I could think about at the time was
getting my silverware.
Because I was just so eager to eat.
We're ruined.
[A tough mission where they will
have to keep trying until they succeed.]
We have to do it in order.
[Hang on...]
[I saw the kimchi first!]
[Then I stopped paying attention because
I was looking at the menu.]
Okay, I'm going to give it a try.
[Going off her memory and
wrapping up the kimchi first.]
Watch her reaction.
See? This is right.
- I don't know if rice was next.
- Look at her reaction.
She just turned her head.
The waitress just turned her head.
Was that the first thing?
I bet this was next.
I'm sure these were the first ones placed.
This one next?
How about this one?
Then this one?
[Right or wrong,
let's enjoy the meal first.]
- How many did they get right?
- They got the lettuce and the next one right.
[A nice start thanks to Eun Ee's memory.]
They got up to the
second ingredient right.
[Ri Sae and Kwang Soo get lucky
and gets the kimchi correct.]
- Nice to see you.
- Is it good?
Let's work together to get on
to the next round together.
[Is she trying to cheat?]
- You're being so blatant.
- She's just stretching out her achy legs.
Do you want to get beat?
Please stop being so blatant.
- Let's try to remember what we did.
- I know.
We have to remember what we did.
This one?
Oh, I forgot this one.
I forgot to put this one in.
This one here.
You didn't put that one in?
I guess we left it out.
Okay, how about this?
I can't remember what the order was.
[Having gotten the whole order wrong
with the exception of one ingredient.]
- Did you put the meat in?
- Sorry, I forgot the meat.
- Sorry.
- You didn't put the meat in?
I really am sorry.
[He's putting that whole thing
in his mouth?]
[But they still get it wrong.]
Can't you just tell us what it is?
We'll tell you guys if we get it right too.
- The first one?
- Just tell us what the first one is.
No, we can't.
We have to figure it out ourselves first.
- We'll tell you what the first ingredient is.
- Okay, we're not going to get this anyways.
- Lettuce.
- What?
- First thing is lettuce.
- That's a given.
So Hyun is getting mad.
Can't you just tell us?
Just tell us what the first one is
so that we can be in the game too.
Why are you getting angry?
- I can't remember anything right now.
- None of us remember.
The only thing I can remember is...
this thing being placed in front of me
and I grabbed a spoon to take a bite.
So what I mean is,
I think this thing came last.
Because this was placed in the end in
front of me for me to open the lid for a bite.
That makes sense.
So I'm pretty sure that this
one came last.
Eun Ee, the feeling I get is that
this thing definitely isn't next.
There's no other choice but for you to
have to eat a lot right now.
- Okay.
- Right?
- Except for the one we know...
- Put this one in.
This one.
Perelli leaves?
The rest isn't as important.
The rest is all about freestyle.
We have no other choice
but to guess at the rest.
- Wrong.
- You got up to the fourth ingredient right.
[They got it right up to the perelli leaves!]
- Let's try to go from here.
- Lets share what we've got.
- What?
- I'm sorry, but we don't want to do that.
Sorry.
[Gumiho Soo Mi's attempt at
making the lettuce wrap.]
Who are you staring at as
you're doing this?
I'm just looking up at the wall.
I'm just staring up at the wall.
It's already wrong?
You're telling us we've got it
wrong already?
- We already know that much.
- You'd better be careful.
- Why?
- Kwang Soo's watching what you're doing.
We already know up to that point.
- But he can learn something he doesn't know.
- If you keep peeking like that...
you may get knocked out with her elbow.
[You haven't forgotten, have you?
Her sharp elbow jab?]
Let's just share with everyone
what the first ingredient is.
What's the first ingredient?
Wouldn't it be much better for everyone if
we at least get the first ingredient right?
Okay, let's do that.
Then what's the first ingredient?
We can't tell you what
the first ingredient is.
- No, we can't tell you that.
- We'll tell you what the third one is.
If you tell us what the first one is,
we'll tell you what the third one is.
Okay, and we'll tell you
what the sixth one is.
Okay, tell us.
If we tell you what the first one is,
then tell us what the third and sixth one is.
- Okay, since we have to get the game going.
- Lets just do it.
[The three teams in this room are
attempting to share their information.]
- Then tell us what the first one is.
- You tell us yours first.
Okay, we'll tell you the first one.
The first one is kimchi.
Ah... that was the one.
We could've gotten that one.
- Third one is perelli leaves.
- What's next?
- The sixth one is garlic.
- Okay, sixth one is garlic.
And also...
Who puts in kimchi first
when they make lettuce wraps?
[Finding it shocking that kimchi is
the first ingredient in a lettuce wrap?]
[That's because it's up to the lady
who set down the side dishes on the table.]
[Wrong- The second ingredient is the sauce.]
How did they get the garlic right?
How many ingredients is that
for them so far?
Put this one in?
[Wow!]
[She just guessed but gets it right!]
They're really getting it right?
[Will they get it right?]
[Suk and Jong Kook seeming
to have it figured out.]
How many did you guys get right?
I bet it's this one.
[All the other teams are still in the
process of throwing out wild guesses.]
[But thanks to their wrong guesses,
they're eating until their bellies are full!]
Can't you just let Soo Mi eat in peace?
We got it.
Let's finish it this time around!
Let's finish it.
If we can get it right this time,
it'll be a pure miracle.
We just ran out of kimchi,
and this is our last piece.
[Making a clean sweep through the board.]
That also was our last piece.
How is it all working out perfectly
with the last bits of food?
Just put one in!
[She puts in all the
remaining cloves of the garlic!]
Are you crazy?
That's enough.
[All the remaining pieces of the hot pepper!]
[And no more of the quail eggs either!]
You have to eat as
your gumiho tells you to eat.
Okay.
Don't do that!
[It's the gumiho's choice.]
That's not even right!
No matter how happy you are about that,
that's still not right.
[Open up your mouth!]
Are you crazy?
Let's take some of that out.
I can't eat it like that.
She must've made a very big bite.
She wrapped everything?
[Suk and Jong Kook wins
the memory lettuce wrap mission!]
[Mixing up all the dishes
so the others can't see.]
[Thanks to all the food in their mouths,
they're being kept nice and quiet.]
You really won?
How did you guys get it right?
Your belly is sticking out, Suk.
Stick it back in.
She didn't even know that her belly was
sticking out because she was so excited.
[How did they get it right?]
[And the heat of the garlic and the pepper
finally hitting Jong Kook's taste buds.]
[Soon thereafter,
So Hyun and Gary gets it right.]
[Ji Hyo and Suk Jin come in third.]
[The gumiho bus hits the road once again.]
This brings Kim Jong Kook and Kim Suk's
tail count up to four.
[First, second, and third place winners of
the lettuce wrap game wins a tail!]
Really?
You really have to be careful
about the woman you meet.
After the meal we had after that game,
I'm still really full.
You started out with all those tails anyways.
- You still  have the most number of tails.
- Just know that the elbow is coming out.
[The elbow will soon start flying!]
The most important thing is
if we can't touch Soo Mi,
it's all going to come to you.
But still keep in mind that
she's the one with the tails.
And just to let you know,
she's been sharpening up her elbow.
[She's been sharpening up her elbow
in the meantime?]
- Are we here?
- The bus is turning in here.
It's the national folk museum.
- It's so beautiful.
- I love places like this.
[The final location-
National folk museum in Kyungbok Palace.]
[A national folk museum
inside of Kyungbok Palace.]
[Still the same as what
the country used to look like.]
[What is the mission that awaits
the gumihos in here?]
[Entering the museum with the
tails that they've earned thus far.]
- With all these tails we have...
- I feel better since we have a few tails.
It makes you feel more secure, right?
Great job on having made it
to your final destination.
Since a gumiho needs to have
nine tails in order to ascend...
the gumihos need to eliminate the
other gumiho's name tags
in order to gain more tails
for themselves.
We have to eliminate other
gumihos' name tags?
Every time a gumiho eliminates another
gumiho's name tag
they earn themselves another tail.
However, if a man gets his name tag eliminated
by another gumiho other than their partner
that man becomes entranced by
the gumiho who eliminates their name tag
and thus becomes a man of
the new gumiho.
If I eliminate another gumiho,
then I win their tails?
If you eliminate another man's name tag,
that man will become our teammate.
- Oh my.
We will now start our final mission.
Five, four, three...
So I just eliminate whomever I can?
Three, two, one.
Start!
You just need to eliminate
one gumiho for us to win.
I have to make sure not to lose
any one of my tails.
Let's eliminate one of the men first.
But why are you doing this
with your hands?
- Just... just because.
- Just because?
- Trying to be cute?
- Yeah, I'm just trying to be cute.
Why?
Don't I look like a cute gumiho?
- I'll grab one for you to eliminate.
- Yeah, you grab someone and I will.
- I can do that, but I think...
- But I feel uncomfortable eliminating Soo Mi.
Because of her elbow?
My elbow is a total killer.
I can take someone out with this.
[Declaration of war]
[I'm going to take everyone out with this.]
- With my elbow.
- Watch out for her elbow.
[The last gumiho left remaining will win
no matter how many tails she has.]
[Who will be the gumiho that
will the battle?]
We don't even need to think about it.
We just need to get out there
and target Soo Mi.
- Let's not eliminate each other.
- Okay.
- Let's help each other out.
We'll make sure that you win today.
- There she comes. Suk!
- Who?
[A surprise attack!]
You're pretty quick!
[They may get eliminated right away
if they let down their guard at all.]
[Discovers Jae Suk and Soo Mi
with their eight tails.]
- We need to attack Jae Suk. Hurry.
- We only have two tails.
I know, so hurry. Are you
going to help us catch them or not?
Do you know how strong Eun Ee is?
I'm not strong.
I don't know how to do any of this.
Jae Suk is over there staring
at us right now.
Soo Mi is headed this way.
[Elbow gumiho Soo Mi makes
her entrance.]
[No... I'd better eliminate Ri Sae first.]
[All of a sudden, it's Ri Sae and Kwang Soo
vs. Eun Ee and Ha Ha!]
We have to seize this chance
to eliminate one of them.
[Kwang Soo attempting to protect Ri Sae
by holding onto her name tag.]
Ri Sae!
No!
No, Kwang Soo!
You can't leave me!
[Ri Sae...]
[Gumiho Ri Sae having lost her guardian...]
Ri Sae.
We've all failed.
Don't run from us.
I'm running away from all of you!
I have to remain alive to the end.
I'm all alone now.
[Chasing after her at the speed of light.]
Soo Mi, wait.
Stop right there!
[What do I do...]
Come here.
[If a man gets eliminated by a gumiho,
he becomes the new gumiho's ally.]
- You're entranced by her now.
- How does that even make any sense?
Do your entrancement dance.
- What's your phone number?
- No more!
What's your name?
[the Giraffe becoming entranced
by Gumiho Eun Ee.]
I can't... I can't deny it any further.
[Transformed into a pink colored shirt
just like Gumiho Eun Ee.]
No, Ri Sae!
What's your name?
- What's your number?
- I can't endure this any longer!
My number is...
I can't endure this any longer.
Why do I feel this way?
[Having lost his mind over
Gumiho Eun Ee's allure.]
Ri Sae!
[The Giraffe is now Gumiho Eun Ee's ally.]
Hey, rookie.
I'm the first.
I'm her real guardian.
You think just because she has you,
she can't have me either?
You can't take my place.
You won't take my spot away from me.
- I'm going to work hard to take his place.
- Who do you think you are? How dare you!
[Spellbound men fighting over
their position amongst themselves.]
Who do you think you are?
[An embarrassing scene
for everyone involved.]
Eun Ee has both of them now?
How did she get so lucky?
- How did she get so lucky?
- We have to eliminate one of them.
- Let's go.
- Let's go over there right now.
I'll grab Ha Ha and you have to
try to eliminate his name tag.
- Okay?
It's Jae Suk!
Remember her elbow.
You'd better watch yourself.
- There are three of us here though.
- Watch out for her elbow.
I have two subjects working
for me right now.
- You'd better watch yourself.
- You'd better be careful.
- Soo Mi...
- Go grab Jae Suk right now.
[Ha Ha and Kwang Soo attacking
Jae Suk as their target!]
Grab Jae Suk!
Oh my goodness!
Go! Get away from me!
Get away from me, you scoundrel!
[Gumiho Soo Mi attacking the Giraffe
with full force!]
Go!
Get away from me right now!
[Giraffe is now entranced by
Gumiho Soo Mi!]
- What are you doing?
- What's your deal?
[Who does he think he's messing with?]
- What is his deal?
- What just happened?
[He now has to change into an orange shirt
to join Jae Suk and Soo Mi's team.]
- Are you okay, Soo Mi?
- Yeah, I'm okay.
I'm sorry for cussing you out.
I called him a scoundrel.
- Okay, Kwang Soo.
- Yes, Jae Suk.
[Now these three are on the same team.]
I've been under Eun Ee's spell
for all of three seconds.
- Really?
- I'm not that flighty of a person!
- He's bouncing around all over the place.
- I usually stay loyal to only one person.
Just go and change your shirt.
I love you.
I love you!
[His style is to fall in love easily.]
- I will do my best to serve you.
- Change your shirt.
This is scary.
I don't know where they'll jump out from.
- You really have to be careful.
- I'm going to have nightmares about this.
- It's scary.
- You have to be careful.
- But those girls are not to be messed with.
- Ji Hyo, she really is no joke.
- Should we slowly get going?
- Eun Ee's no joke either.
I know.
I have to watch out for Eun Ee too.
She used to be pretty athletic
back in her day.
Why is it taking you all day to
change your shirt?
We're in a hurry.
Be quick and change you shirt.
Shouldn't you be welcoming me
with open arms right now?
- We've got ourselves another lump now.
- How am I a lump?
- Seriously.
- Soo Mi, where are you going?
[She needs to reattach Kwang Soo's
name tag for him to be resurrected.]
[Giraffe is now resurrected under
Gumiho Soo Mi's spell.]
Since there are two...
Since there are two of you now,
we have to eliminate one of the girls.
Even though I'm your second,
can you be more affectionate with me?
She's too focused on the game
right now to think of doing that.
I feel like we're in the scene from,
'Marrying the Mafia'.
[A scene from 'Marrying the Mafia'.]
[On the other hand, Gary and So Hyun,
the older woman and younger man couple. ]
[Who will the frail Gumiho So Hyun
be able to eliminate?]
- Over there.
- I see.
There's Gary over there.
Gary!
- Tell him to come over here.
- I don't even need to say it, do I?
- Let's go get Jae Suk together.
- You agree with us, don't you?
Of course!
That's a given!
[Their plan if to go after Jae Suk
and Soo Mi and their eight tails for now.]
Come here, So Hyun.
We still need to be careful.
- Yeah, you're right.
- Jong Kook and Suk makes me nervous.
- What did you say?
- Hang on a second.
Why is your right hand in that position?
Why are you being like that?
[Unable to trust each other.]
Even though Suk may do something like that,
I'd never be like that.
I can't even eliminate a man's name tag.
- But you can eliminate mine.
- Yes, I can eliminate yours.
They can betray us at any time,
so you have to always be careful.
- Because they can turn on us at any moment.
- Let's eliminate someone with a lot of tails.
We have to eliminate Jae Suk first.
They only need one more to win.
They only need one more tail
for them to win the game.
[Eun Ee attacks So Hyun's name tag
and eliminates it!]
[Gumiho Eun Ee never loses her chance
when she sees one!]
You're the best.
Wow... Eun Ee, you're amazing.
[Totally betrayed.]
You're so fast!
Wow... I can't believe how quick you are.
You're seriously the best.
[Too bad...
Gary and So Hyun had seven tails!]
[Gumiho So Hyun - Out!]
We should've targeted So Hyun.
Why are there so many people there?
- They're all headed somewhere.
- They're all looking around.
- We have to somehow separate them first.
- What are you doing? You scared me.
You have to always be on the lookout.
It's a habit of mine now. Stay cautious.
They're coming.
They're coming this way right now.
[All the couple starting to
head over in their direction.]
Let's back out of here for now.
Since they're coming from that way,
let's go around this way.
We don't know where
they're going to come from.
[Whether she likes it or not,
best choice is to listen to Mr. Capable.]
You have to go around like this
so that they can't know where you're at.
You always look so aggressive on the show,
but why are you being so passive right now?
They're running.
I can see them running.
[Eun Ee and Ha Ha figure out
what's going on.]
[It seems as though everyone is
gathering up at one place.]
- Let's go this way.
- Let's go back to where we were.
- Why do they keep circling around here?
- Hurry up and come this way!
- We have nowhere else to run to!
- We're not running away.
There's something going on over there.
There are two men on that team.
[The two team discussing eliminating
the team with the eight tails first.]
You can grab Kwang Soo,
and I'll grab Jae Suk.
- Then one of the girls can eliminate Soo Mi.
- That sounds like a plan.
This will work as long as the two of you
don't betray us.
[The plan could work as long as
they don't betray the other two...]
[Just then, Soo Mi, Jae Suk and Kwang Soo
starts heading in their direction.]
Hang on.
Don't do anything and just hang on.
Don't forget what we all
just agreed to.
They always say that you'll
meet your enemy under the bridge.
I have two subjects now.
I got myself another guard.
Lee Kwang Soo, how can you do that?
How can you try to eliminate us right away?
Lee Kwang Soo, what are you doing?
[Jae Suk and Kwang Soo starts their
protection of Gumiho Soo Mi!]
[While Suk Jin and Ha Ha are protecting
the two men under Soo Mi's spell...]
[Eun Ee and Ji Hyo are targeting
Soo Mi's name tag!]
Run away from here!
Run away, Soo Mi!
[Spellbound again!]
What's your deal?
[What's his problem?]
[Giraffe is now under Ji Hyo's spell.]
- Just what is his deal?
- I was trying to block them off!
Are you doing a fashion show?
How many times are you going to change?
- He's just jumping from team to team!
- I'm not that flighty of a person.
How can you say that you're not flighty?
[Now he has to change his t-shirt
for the fourth time today.]
I'll just put several layers
of shirts on over this one.
Since I don't know which team
I'm going to end up on.
- Just give him several shirts.
- I'll wear several shirts all at once.
Put the name tag on me, Ji Hyo.
[Resurrected as Ji Hyo's man.]
[Now Ji Hyo, Suk Jin and
Kwang Soo are a team.]
- They're here.
- Let's see what they're doing.
- Someone is coming.
- You should just hold on to it.
- Come here. You're on our team now.
[Oh yeah!]
[Confused from having switched
teams so many times.]
What in the world is going on?
How many times are you changing teams?
- Where's Ri Sae?
- This is his third time.
- Who's Ri Sae?
- Where di Ri Sae go?
- That's right, I don't see Ri Sae.
- Ri Sae is missing.
[Ah... Ri Sae...]
Ri Sae!
If Ri Sae eliminates your name tag...
then don't you go back to being her partner?
- Here they come.
- Soo Mi, can we talk first?
Let's go.
Let's get out of here for now.
Grab Jae Suk.
Be careful.
[The target-
Gumiho Kim Soo Mi and her eight tails!]
[I need to escape from here.]
[Jae Suk in extreme danger!]
[Wow... spellbound again?]
What is he doing?
Did you really have to do that
when we're already working together?
I just grabbed anything I could
because I was feeling so anxious.
You need to fix that habit of yours!
[Going around a full circle
to go back to being on Eun Ee's team.]
Kwang Soo's eliminated again?
He got his name tag eliminated again?
He got his name tag ripped off again?
He's like the neighborhood kick can.
[On the other hand, Gumiho Soo Mi takes
the chance to flee from the chaos.]
[Meeting back up with Jae Suk.]
You have to be careful.
Always watch your back.
[Grabs a huge mop?]
Why do they keep attacking Soo Mi?
They just won't leave us alone.
[Giraffe back to being on Eun Ee's team
in his pink shirt.]
[Unwavering in their targeting of
Gumiho Soo Mi and her eight tails.]
[Discovered!]
There they are again.
- There they come.
- Want us to help you?
[Ji Hyo and Suk Jin reaching out
their hand to help?]
Are you offering to help them?
- Think about it, Suk Jin.
- They only need one more to win.
- We have to eliminate them first.
- They already have eight tails.
- What did you say?
- Do you want to get beat up again?
[They're right.
If we're not careful, Soo Mi will win.]
[Gumiho Eun Ee's team slowly
closing in on them.]
Rip it off!
Rip off her name tag!
[Gumiho Soo Mi is caught!]
Get her!
Eliminate her!
[Eun Ee eliminates Soo Mi's name tag.]
- We already had eight tails!
- Sorry, Soo Mi.
Why didn't you use your elbow on her?
I used my leg on her instead.
I should've elbowed her first.
She flung out her leg instead
of elbowing her first?
She's angry right now.
Seriously...
Your quick speed is no joke.
[Eun Ee, Ha Ha and Kwang Soo
are about to sweep up the game!]
- This is our Eun Ee.
- What's your name again?
Lee Kwang Soo!
My number is...
- My name is Ha Dong Hoon!
- What is your number?
You just remember that you
come after me.
- No.
- She's mine.
I've never once thought of myself
as coming in as second from the beginning.
She's mine!
Who do you think you are?
No! I'm going to oust you
and have her for myself!
There, there.
You can each have half of my wealth.
- Thank you.
- Let's go.
I love you.
Let's go get Ri Sae.
[A nice and easy prey.
A lone Ri Sae without her Kwang Soo.]
- We should've gotten someone in that chaos.
- Just where did Ri Sae go?
- Let's go get her right now.
- Let's go find her and get her.
Ri Sae.
Come here, Ri Sae.
Come to me instead of getting caught
by that other scary lady.
I'll make sure that you're not hurt
when I eliminate you.
[Having entered the interior of the museum
in their search for Ri Sae.]
Where are you, Ri Sae?
Come here, Ri Sae.
Who is that?
[Just then...]
[Suk and Jong Kook comes face to face
with Eun Ee, Ha Ha and Kwang Soo.]
[A face-off]
- There's no reason to avoid them.
- Let's just face them.
Why do they look so angry?
Look at that angry couple.
What's going on?
How many tails do you have?
I don't have a lot.
I don't have as many as you do.
It doesn't matter how many tails
since you can only get one from elimination.
I just want to know how close
you are to winning.
We're going to eliminate your team,
and move on to the next one to win.
- You have seven right now?
- Kwang Soo is being really aggressive.
Get him.
Eun Ee!
Come and get her!
[At this rate,
it's Gumiho Eun Ee vs. Gumiho Suk!]
Eun Ee!
[Feisty gumihos pulling on each other
by their hair!]
You can't grab her by her hair!
[Ji Hyo and Suk Jin arrive at that
moment to join in on the melee!]
- What's going on here?
- Come here, Ji Hyo!
[Complete chaos!]
Are you okay?
[Gumiho Suk not worrying about her body and
doing what she can to protect her name tag!]
Run!
Run away from here!
Run away from here, Eun Ee!
[Are you guys doing this on purpose?]
[Just how many times has it been?]
[Now Suk, Jong Kook and Kwang Soo
are a team.]
Kwang Soo has now worn shirts
of every different color.
[Congratulations, Kwang Soo!
You've been in all five different colors!]
Kwang Soo, this makes a
grand slam for you!
[A grand slam!]
- Come here. Hurry.
- Come here. Let's not betray each other.
I can guarantee that
they're going to work together.
So what we have to do is...
This isn't the time for us to
be battling amongst ourselves.
- We have to work together.
- Think about this carefully.
If you eliminate me or take Suk Jin onto
your team, you'll be eliminated right away.
[Mr. Capable was difficult enough,
but now even Kwang Soo on their team?]
You know that if we eliminate each other,
then it's an immediate end for us, right?
- That's why we need to work together.
- Let's go find Ri Sae.
Let's go find Ri Sae and have her
join our side.
- Let's go get her and we all take them on.
- That's a good idea.
If we find Ri Sae,
we may have a chance to beat them.
I bet you Ri Sae can put Kwang Soo
back under her spell.
- Good. I like that idea.
- Kwang Soo will then go back to her.
[Use Ri Sae to get Kwang Soo under her spell
to get him away from the other team.]
- Lets send him back.
- Yes, that's the plan.
[Will they succeed in their plan to
put Kwang Soo back in his original spot?]
- You have to protect my back, okay?
- I understand.
[But right at that time, Kwang Soo is
practicing being loyal to Gumiho Suk.]
That's a good stance.
There you go.
- The sun is too bright.
- I'm sorry.
What are you doing?
Hurry up and block the sun.
Ri Sae.
- Ri Sae.
[The other two couples are rushing around
to find Gumiho Ri Sae.]
Ri Sae.
- Check over there.
- Don't be afraid.
Ri Sae.
We're on your side. Ri Sae.
[Not easy to find Ri Sae who's hid herself
deep away out of her fear for others.]
- Ri Sae.
- Let's join forces and work together.
- We have to join our forces together.
- Ri Sae, you can trust me.
- Ri Sae.
[Finally discovers Ri Sae!]
- We're serious. We're not coming for you.
- We really do have to work together.
- Are you being honest with me?
- We're being honest. Let's work together.
We're being honest.
Over here. She's over here.
- Ji Hyo, we're over here.
- We finally found Ri Sae.
- We're being honest.
- Ri Sae.
- Listen. Hear us out.
- Listen to us carefully.
[First priority is to calm Ri Sae down
and calmly explain things to her.]
We have to pull that team apart.
So we're trying to recruit you.
We're not trying to oust you, okay?
- So you have to get Kwang Soo back.
- Our plan is...
We're trying to get you to rip off
Kwang Soo's name tag and return him to you.
[Really?]
I'll hold onto Jong Kook while you do it.
And one of us will eliminate Suk
in the meantime
and while we're doing that, you
have to rip off Kwang Soo's name tag.
[Will Gumiho Ri Sae be able to
bring Kwang Soo back to her?]
[At the same time]
- I think she's too scared to come outside.
- I think you're right.
- What is that?
- Look.
- Oh my goodness.
- Look at how beautiful it is outside.
I found the woman who's going to
weave a spell on you.
[Ri Sae... is back.]
- Ri Sae.
- Can you deny Ri Sae?
[The woman Kwang Soo spent the whole day
building everlasting sweet memories with.]
What is this?
- Why did you bring her here?
- There he is.
I told you not to show up
at my work!
- Kwang Soo.
- I told you not to come when I'm working!
Wait... wait!
[Suk Jin and Ha Ha grabbing Jong Kook
just like they had planned!]
- Hurry!
- Let's go get Kwang Soo!
[Now's the chance!]
Kwang Soo!
- Grab him!
- Hurry!
- Ri Sae!
- Go grab Kwang Soo!
[Eun Ee and Ji Hyo's target is Kim Suk!
And Ri Sae targets Kwang Soo!]
Hurry up and rip off his name tag!
[She rips it off!]
[After being passed around five other teams,
Kwang Soo is finally returned to Ri Sae!]
- Kwang Soo!
- It is nice, but...
Are you going to edit all this stuff out?
[No matter what the case,
Ri Sae and Kwang Soo are reunited!]
Okay, is it a real face-off now
between the four couples?
[Eun Ee, Ha Ha and Ji Hyo, Suk Jin vs.
Kin Suk, Jong Kook and Ri Sae, Kwang Soo?]
Then you and I need to stick together.
[Time to attack!]
[Mr. Capable grabbing onto Suk Jin
and Ha Ha just as they had planned.]
[Now all that needs to happen is for Kwang Soo
to attack either Eun Ee or Ji Hyo...]
[Traitorous Giraffe!
He attacks defenseless Gumiho Suk instead!]
- Rip it off!
- What are you doing?
Run for your life!
[Traitors Club exchanging secret glances
while no one else was looking!]
- Okay, let's go eliminate Kwang Soo now.
- Let's go!
[Traitors' Club changing sides
every three seconds.]
I'm sorry to ask you this,
but can you go get the tail for us?
- Hey, Ri Sae.
- Yes?
You'd better not run into me
out on the street anywhere.
Don't ever come around Mapogu.
- Don't go around Mapogu.
- Let go of me.
You don't know how scary
this world can be, do you?
Let go!
Ri Sae!
- Don't even come near Mapogu, you hear me?
- I'm so sorry!
You'd better watch your back.
[I love you, Kim Suk.]
[Traitors Club first shouting out their
cries of joy over their victory of Jong Kook.]
- Come on, do what you were going to do first.
- Why are you being like this?
I've been in the show business for 20 years.
You should pay your respects first.
- Come on, pay your respects first.
- Tra-it-ors Club Cross!
Get him!
[Eun Ee gets her hand on
Big-nosed Brother's name tag!]
[This time, Ri Sae gets her hand on it!]
[Big-nose Brother's name tag becoming
everyone's target within moments!]
Kwon Ri Sae!
We have to oust Ri Sae now.
The rate of their betrayal is...
faster than anything else I've ever seen.
[The nonstop relay of betrayal that
they're getting to witness firsthand.]
[Loyalty switching sides
at the blink of an eye!]
- It's a dirty filthy game.
- I can't even keep my thoughts straight.
How can it happen so quickly?
- That's amazing.
- It's been a while.
Pil-Chok-Cross!
[Back to battling one another!]
Come here and get him!
Grab Kwang Soo by his legs.
Grab Kwang Soo's legs.
there you go.
- No, come here.
- Come here, Ji Hyo!
[Ji Hyo targeting Ri Sae's name tag!]
[If Gumiho Ri Sae's name tag is eliminated,
Suk Jin and Kwang Soo will be ousted too!]
No, no!
Lay down on the ground, Ri Sae!
[Gumiho Kwon Ri Sae - Out!]
We have to get Ji Hyo!
It's two of us against one!
Ji Hyo! We have to get Ji Hyo!
She's the only one left!
[Immediately turning around to
attack Gumiho Ji Hyo!]
[Gumiho Song Ji Hyo - Out!]
We won!
Wow! We won!
[Eun Ee and Ha Ha succeed in
collecting all nine of the tails!]
We won!
Our team won!
[Eun Ee and Ha Ha are the ultimate winners
of the Gumiho Race!]
[Utter exhaustion]
[And finally...]
[Gumiho Eun Ee is able to ascend...]
What is she doing?
[Gumiho Eun Ee standing atop the
platform with the wings on her back.]
[Goodbye, Gumiho Eun Ee.]
[Gumiho Eun Ee ascending to the heavens
with all nine of her tails.]
[After all the waiting around,
she finally gets to float up into the sky.]
What if she comes back as a man instead?
[Oh? A treasure chest
in the middle of the sky?]
[Inside is a golden ball!]
[Envious]
- I'm so jealous!
- You should be thanking me!
- How many karats is that?
I'm going to become a woman now!
- What is that?
- Wow.
Eun Ee's become a human now.
I'm pretty competitive myself.
- I know.
- I hate just going home empty handed.
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Running Man presents]
Who's coming on the show today?
[A.D. 2013. 06
All the heroes come to gather in one place.]
No way!
This is over.
[Superheroes everywhere...
gather around!]
[Captain Running Man, Yoo Jae Suk.]
[Thor, the God of Thunder,
Kim Jong Kook.]
[Giraffe kid, Lee Kwang Soo.]
[Hip Hop Spiderman, Gary.]
[Sexy Blank Lady in black, Song Ji Hyo.]
[Hulk, Ji Suk Jin.]
[Ironman, Ha Ha.]
[The ultimate battle between
the heroes starts now.]
You're all dead!
[But...]
[The surprise attack by
their mortal enemies!]
[Next Week's Running Man Special-
Running Man Avengers.]