Running Man
[2013 Psychic Baseball.]
[A totally upgraded
psychic baseball has returned.]
[A fantastical game with legendary players.]
[Extraordinary!]
[Uproarious laughter!]
[Even though fall baseball games may be over,
psychic baseball is still alive.]
[2013 Psychic Baseball]
[Last week]
[Suzy makes another comeback
to Running Man.]
[Along with the Korean Monster,
Monster Pitcher Ryu Hyun Jin.]
[Late fall MT along with
members of the Running Man cast.]
[And in the midst of the MT,
Ryu Hyun Jin succeeds his secret mission.]
[And...]
[The cutie of a man quietly taking
care of lovely Suzy.]
[Thus, the MT evening
slowly passes into the night...]
- Are you all having fun?
- Yes, we're having lots of fun.
Do you all know what 'MT'
stands for?
Yes, I do!
- Mountain teenager?
- Mountain trouble?
It stands for, 'Membership Training'.
- Yes, it stands for 'membership training.'
- You think we actually didn't know that?
- I really didn't know.
- Our MT Trip...
Our MT trip actually stood for
'Money is Time'.
You all have money that you've
earned throughout the day, right?
You'll be trading in your money for time.
The time you've earned is the time you'll be
allotted to participate in the final mission.
Please check how much you've
each earned.
- 13,000 won.
- I have 25,000 won.
He earned an extra 8,000 won for
succeeding his spy mission.
What's your deal?
Then just give me 1,000 won
out of your stash.
Just give me 1,000 won.
There you go.
[Generously giving out 1,000 won
to his own team members.]
- Give me 1,000 won too.
- I will now tell you your final mission.
You have to find the pillows that we
have hidden throughout this place.
You either have to find the pillows that
have been marked with an 'R' or steal it.
If you look over there,
you will find your sleeping quarters.
If you look inside the sleeping quarters,
you will see some blankets laid out.
If you take the pillows you find and lay down
in the blanket, then you succeed.
The problem is,
we've only prepared six pillows.
- What about the other three?
- As for the remaining three people...
They won't be able to lay down in the bedding
since they don't have a pillow.
The remaining three people have to wash the
dishes from the dinner you all enjoyed
and have to finish cleaning up before
you can go into the sleeping quarters.
- I don't think I can do that.
- I hate washing dishes.
- I was already thinking of doing them.
- There are so many dishes to wash.
- Then why don't you wash the dishes?
- Why are you saying that? Don't say that.
Every 1,000 won you have can be
traded in for one minute.
- Then I only have 13 minutes?
- That's correct, 13 minutes.
- Then you know what you have, right?
- Yes.
Suzy at the moment has the most amount
of money to be traded in for time.
Suzy will be the first to start.
Start your mission!
[Suzy's off!]
I don't think I'll be able
to find any here.
[Steal the Pillow mission- Start!]
[Where could they be?]
There's not much time.
- Gary, and Ryu Hyun Jin may now start.
- Has it already been a minute?
The time is going by way too fast.
- You guys don't have much time, do you?
- This is too much.
[The three feeling apprehensive with
the little time they're allotted.]
[Gary and Hyun Jin starts by searching
all the nearby areas.]
What the heck?
You startled me!
[Hefty Ryu scared off by the cute puppy.]
What are you doing there, dog?
I don't see any pillows.
I don't think there are any
around here.
I think this is the sleeping quarters.
Ji Hyo may now start.
[Ji Hyo's turn to start.]
[Searching the area around the carriage.]
[I wonder if anyone's found any yet.]
[Discovers a pillow!]
[Where are all the pillows?]
[On top of the wooden platform below!]
[There's a pillow!]
Are those ducks?
[Ducks taking their leisurely stroll.]
[She must be looking for the pillows.]
[Suzy finds her 'R' marked pillow.]
[Huh?]
That's so cool.
Hang on a minute... what if
someone takes it away from me?
[Gary searching in the lower village circle.]
['R' marked pillow on top of the swings!]
Isn't this one of the pillows?
It is!
[Hefty Ryu is headed his way!]
It's up way too high!
No, hang on!
You won't be able to reach it either.
[Getting on top of the swing
without any hesitation.]
[Hyun Jin gets the pillow!]
Hey, you traitor!
Did you find one too?
Suzy, you found one too?
[Members with the pillows are desperately
trying to find the sleeping quarters.]
Ryu Hyun Jin found a pillow!
Ryu Hyun Jin!
We have to steal his pillow!
Where did you find it?
Where did you get that from?
- Where's the sleeping quarters?
- Where did you find that?
[He did find the pillow,
but where's the sleeping quarters?]
[The sleeping quarters are in the
lower village circle.]
- No!
- I was the one who found it first.
[Still haven't been able to find
the sleeping quarters.]
I think almost all the pillows
have been found already.
There's no time to waste right now.
Please give us a chance
and let us go.
[These three are still waiting
for there to get started.]
Just give us one chance.
- When are you guys getting started?
- You found one?
- You already found one?
- I looked everywhere around here.
- You just wait.
- Fighting!
I'm going to take hers away from her.
[Blank Ji is running around desperately in
search of the sleeping quarters.]
Hey, where did you find yours?
Hey, come on.
[Those who haven't find theirs
must steal one from others.]
- Tell me.
- Let go of me!
Where's Suzy?
[Zero consideration. Warning Suzy
of Big-nose's imminent approach.]
- Run faster!
- Come here!
[Stop right there!]
We have to find the sleeping quarters!
[Cold hearted Big-nose
always going after the women.]
[But...]
[This is the sleeping quarters!]
[A full out battle right in front
of the sleeping quarters!]
[Is that where the sleeping quarters is?]
[Hyun Jin arrives at the sleeping quarters
with his pillow in hand.]
[Blank Ji also makes her careful approach.]
- Rock paper scissors?
- No way! I stole it, so it's mine now!
[Another thief, Haroro also arrives.]
[Just who will take the possession of
Suzy's hard earned pillow?]
[Kkuk finds his pillow from somewhere and
attempts to make a breakthrough to the room.]
My pillow!
Where did they go?
[All the members crowding in
like a pack of hungry wolves.]
This is Suzy's.
Suzy!
- Come here, I'll give it to you.
- We'll give it to you.
Come and take it.
You can take it.
[Rather than have someone else steal it,
they'd rather give it back to Suzy?]
- We know that it's yours.
- You know that I wouldn't take yours.
- Sorry.
- Here, you take it.
Let's just give it to Suzy.
Let's not be like this, and give it to Suzy.
Hurry up and get out of here.
- Just go, Suzy.
- There's still one left to find.
- Was that the last one?
- No, there's still one left.
[Why are they all following her after
telling her that she can keep it?]
[Escape to the sleeping quarters!]
Hey!
Stop right there!
[That's what we thought...]
[Hefty Ryu still hasn't claimed his bedding.]
Is this the last one?
- No.
- It's not, is it?
No, it's not. Don't take it!
Don't take it from her!
[Defending Suzy from the wolf pack.]
[Hyun Jin becomes
the wolf pack's prey instead.]
Who are you trying to look
cool in front of?
[Escapes with his monstrous strength.]
- Ji Hyo.
- There are two spots left.
- Two left?
- Two?
[Two spots still left.]
What if we don't find it?
Thank you!
[Monstrous Hefty Ryu pulling his weight
and getting the job done.]
[Dish washing candidates
starting to lose hope.]
I guess I'll be washing dishes.
[Pillow]
[Found it!]
Suk Jin!
[Caught within a second
of finding his pillow.]
[Big-nose surrounded by ravenous wolves.]
[The pillow determining the fate
of the future dish washers.]
Rock, paper, scissors.
Let's determine it that way.
- We have to get him.
- Let's just play rock, paper, scissors.
Okay.
- Kwang Soo's here too?
- Is it here?
Okay, let's play rock paper scissors.
- Let go.
- Let's do this for real.
- Let go. Let go for now.
- Let's play rock paper scissors.
- I said, let go!
- Let's just play rock paper scissors.
- Let's settle this with rock paper scissors.
- Okay.
[Agreeing to settle with rock paper scissors.]
Rock paper scissors.
Okay, you're out.
There's still one left, so go and find it.
- Okay, just go.
- You guys are out.
- There's still five minutes left.
- That's what I'm saying.
There are still five minutes left, so go.
Come on, let's stick to our word, Kwang Soo.
Let's keep to our promise.
[Playing one last round of Rock paper scissors
with the 'R' pillow on the line.]
Rock paper scissors!
[The traitorous wolf pack immediately
going back on their word.]
Let's seriously play one more round
of rock paper scissors.
- I just beat you guys.
- Let's play one more round.
- Seriously, just one more round.
- Get away from me.
Hey!
[In the meantime,
Ro-Ro is looking for the last pillow.]
[Discovers the last pillow!]
[The wolf pack is causing a scene in
front of the sleeping quarters entrance.]
[Pillow piggyback ride?]
[I just want to lay down!]
- Jae Suk, did you find it?
- No, I haven't found it.
Get him!
Kwang Soo!
[Full on pursuit of Ha Ha and
the last pillow.]
Get him, Kwang Soo!
Kwang Soo!
[Lying down as if sliding into home base.]
You have to take out the pillow.
[Arguing that he can't keep the pillow
hidden under the coat on his back.]
[Ha Ha succeeds.]
The remaining four of you must
all exit the room at the same time.
[One pillow and four remaining players.]
- Okay!
- None of you are even acknowledging us?
[I don't know any of you guys!]
[Dish washing candidates step back outside.]
[Gary fails his attempt to steal.]
[Kwang Soo?]
[He's on the blanket with the pillow...]
[Kwang Soo succeeds!]
It's so slippery over there.
It was so slippery over there.
[Suk Jin, Jae Suk and Gary are confirmed
as dish washers for the night.]
Why did we all eat so much?
[Darn...]
Gary.
I can't believe this.
What are you doing?
Suk Jin, do you not want to do this?
I feel like my back is going to break off.
- Here, give me that.
- But you haven't even done anything.
- You have yours right there.
- You go get another one.
Come on, Suk Jin!
You're good at rinsing.
- It's just that you're not doing anything.
- You're not even doing anything.
Who in the world is either
good or bad at washing dishes?
[Neither Gary nor Jae Suk
want to do the dishes either.]
Don't re-wash anything we've already done,
and wash something of your own!
- There are plenty of dirty dishes here.
- Why are you re-washing Jae Suk's dishes?
- I just want to make sure that it's clean.
- Seriously.
The three of them are out there working
hard to wash the pile of dishes.
Six of you men can sleep in this room.
The women's room is right next door,
and that's where the ladies can sleep.
- Yes.
- Thank you.
- Okay, I understand.
Let's play rock paper scissors and
have only one person finish the rest.
- What do you think?
- I'm in.
- One round.
- Just one round.
[One round of rock paper scissors to
determine who'll finish up the rest.]
We're going to head out then.
[Big-nosed Brother is it.]
This is unbelievable.
[The other two are leaving
at the speed of light.]
- You're the one who suggested it.
- We're leaving.
How could this have happened?
- Good luck, Suk Jin.
- Bye!
- There's not that much left.
- This is ridiculous.
How could this have happened when
I'm normally so good at this?
[Twice in a row- His confidence in his
rock paper scissors skills is crumbled.]
[Washing and washing some more...]
[Thus the 48 year old big brother...]
[washed all the dishes all by himself
long after everyone else was asleep.]
[Second day of Running Man MT- 7 a.m.]
[Peaceful]
Time to wake up.
The first person to get up will have
the biggest advantage. You'd better get up.
[No movement.]
Time to get up.
[Just who will be the first to get up?]
[Blank... Blank Ji?]
[The goddess of sleep.]
[The woman who can sleep anywhere.]
[No qualms about sacrificing her style
in the name of sleep.]
Is everyone already gone?
[The guru of sleep, Blank Ji.
She's the one?]
[Wow! Blank Ji is the first one up!]
[Still in dreamland.]
[Too tough to open their eyes
this early in the morning.]
[So cold...]
Say, good morning.
Hello.
[Tying his shoelaces.]
Where are my socks?
Wake up.
[Everyone's starting to wake up
one by one.]
[Even the cutie patootie Hefty Ryu
is awake.]
Did you all sleep well?
[Nation's first love, Suzy,
looking bright as sunshine in the morning.]
[Slow mover, Gary is finally
starting to put his socks on.]
Your mission today is
Running Man Psychic Baseball game.
[2013 Psychic Running Baseball series.]
[Upgraded psychic baseball
making its comeback.]
[An unbelievable game played with
the best of the best in baseball.]
[The game that supposedly taught Chu Shin Soo
and Ryu Hyun Jin a thing or two...]
- The game has been upgraded in the past year.
- We're playing psychic baseball?
- We've come up with a new method to the game.
- Really?
Hyun Jin told me that he was able to improve
on his batting skills because of us.
- Really?
- Yeah, he made that confession to us.
- That's what Hyun Jin told us yesterday.
- So we were a big help to you, weren't we?
[Even though he may have said something
along those lines...]
We'll help you do even better
next year.
- Even better.
- We're going to have to divide up into teams.
Until you are divided up into teams,
you'll be playing in an individual race.
You have to collect as many
psychic powers as you can until then.
[Collect as much power as you
can until then.]
To the winner of the morning wake up
mission, Song Ji Hyo...
- She'll be given an extra psychic power.
- She gets extra power?
[Is he her escort?]
What are you doing?
Why are you escorting her?
Why are you guys being so picky?
- What is it?
- Can you tell us?
[Blank Ji getting the upper hand by
earning additional psychic power.]
You know what you say at a time like this?
You say, 'I don't want to be too selfish'.
I just earned two psychic powers.
[Running series]
[Move onto 'K' market.]
Change and clean up your bedding,
and you may get on your way.
Let's play rock paper and scissors
to determine who'll clean up all the bedding.
- Why doesn't everyone just clean up their own?
- No, let's just play rock paper scissors.
- Since the ladies slept separately...
- We'll do our own.
- You can't do that.
- Why not?
Hey, we're all here together.
We should all play together.
- Okay, then you want us to play too?
- If you don't want to do it, then just win.
[Only one person who doesn't know
the plans behind the game.]
Rock paper scissors.
[Wow... Big-nosed Brother is the
only person who threw out a 'scissors'.]
- Yes!
- That doesn't count.
[Their plan totally failed...]
[Immediately blames Kwang Soo.]
You guys planned this, didn't you?
[Big-nosed Brother finally catching on
to what's going on.]
- No, we didn't plan anything.
- Suk Jin always threw out a scissors.
We should've thrown out a rock.
- We should've started off with a 'rock'.
- We shouldn't have done that.
- Come on, Ji Hyo.
- You have to do it with us.
If you think this is fun,
why not do it with us?
[Trying to convince the ladies
to join in on their game?]
Look at how they're trying to be
sneaky just so that they could win.
[Giraffe trying to get all the men
to throw out a 'rock'.]
Rock paper scissors.
[Everyone throws out a 'rock'...
except for Jae Suk and Suzy.]
[Only Jae Suk and Suzy who didn't catch
on to the plan fails.]
Did you not see what he was doing?
You need to get your head
on straight.
Didn't you see me throwing out a rock?
- Suzy didn't know what you meant by that.
- She thought you were just cheering her on.
So if I win this,
then Suzy has to do all the work?
[Final round between Jae Suk and Suzy to
determine who'll clean up all the blankets.]
[Suzy wins!]
[Yoo Hyuk is chosen to clean up
all the blankets!]
This is awesome!
You guys are all traitors.
I'm not going to let any of you
get away with this.
- No, don't do any of that.
- Why?
I'm not supposed to help?
You're right. It's no fun if we help.
[Adamant about not helping.]
Come here, Kwang Soo.
- Kwang Soo.
- Yes, Jae Suk?
Come here for a minute.
- Are you not going to do anything?
- What do you expect me to do?
Look at him.
Jae Suk, how can you try to prevent me
from being filmed on camera?
- You should've known better.
- He's trying to get me off the air!
- Hey, Yoo Jae Suk!
- Don't you think you're being too much?
- I didn't do anything.
- I was just trying to get on film.
But he told the cameraman to
get the camera off of my face.
Why aren't you shooting anyone?
[An early morning teaching for
Giraffe and Ro-Ro.]
We're finally doing this!
Hyun Jin is three times the size of Suzy.
Only three times the size?
[He's sleepy all of a sudden?]
- What's wrong with you?
- How can you suddenly be sleepy?
- Are you embarrassed or something?
- You need to wake up.
You're cute.
Hyun Jin was the only person who
looked after Suzy.
- Yeah, you're right.
- I saw that too.
You really can't forget about
the fish bread, Suzy.
That's right, he bought her the bread too.
[Hyun Jin's gentle care for Suzy.]
There you go again, Gwon Yeol.
Why are you shooting me all of a sudden?
You were only shooting Suzy before.
That's what I don't like about you.
He's been shooting Suzy all this time
with a smile on his face
and then I see him suddenly
shift over to me.
- You saw that too, didn't you?
- I saw it.
[In a place full of fresh produce
and customers...]
- This game is called, Market Strike Game.
- How do we play it?
Before we explain the game to you...
Do we have to go out and buy
something again?
What's that?
A step counter?
- Make sure that it's set to zero.
- It is a step counter.
[Set it back to zero.]
Depending on the number
that you get on the step counter...
you'll be able to earn your mission fee.
Really?
The higher the number,
better it'll be for you.
Is everyone set to zero?
- You have to shake it up and down.
- Start the music.
[Jae Suk, Hyun Jin, and Suzy's music is...]
[Miss A's 'Hush' sung by
none other than Suzy.]
[The song that showed a more
feminine side to Suzy.]
[How will Suzy dance to this song?]
[Ready]
[Huh?]
[A random shuffle dance.]
[Can't hear you!]
What's wrong with you, Suzy?
[Dance machine,
Yoo Hyuk's shuffle dance?]
[A strong glint in his eye.]
[Taking the center stage while dancing.]
[Quietly going to the back
so that others can see Suzy.]
[But Suzy's not even paying
any attention.]
[The king of dancing starting to get
more and more excited.]
[I want you!]
[Climatic part to the song.]
[The pole dance from the music video?]
[Reverting back to the jogging dance.]
[This man is overly excited.]
[Dance energy going off the charts.]
[Hefty Ryu not breaking the beat and
continuing to dance the same dance.]
You have to be more serious.
[Huh?]
[Is he sweeping the floor?]
- What kind of a dance is that?
- The floor is dirty!
This is my dance!
[Over the top back performance.]
[Suzy's still going strong
with her crazy dance moves.]
Okay, time to check your numbers.
- Ryu Hyun Jin's count.
- I got 90-something.
- What did you get?
- 114.
- He got 114.
[Hyun Jin's count is a mere 114.]
- 263.
- That's right.
[Dance machine, Yoo Hyuk scored 263.
329.
[A total count of 329 for Suzy!]
- You're a pretty decent dancer.
- Of course, I am.
He really loves to dance.
Okay, cue the music.
[Blank Ji, Kkuk and Ro-Ro's turn.]
[Which music will they play?]
[Automatically breaking out in a
turkey trot dance to the upbeat song.]
[The hip shaking dance that
they have yet to identify.]
[Blinding hip shaking dance that's
a sight to behold for the crowd.]
I can't even bear to watch him.
[A dance that concentrate most of
it's focus on shaking the hips.]
It's possible that Ha Ha may not
score very high with those moves.
[The last hip shake.]
[Gary, Big-nose, and Giraffe's turn.]
Why are you playing this kind
of a music for us?
[Retro styled music for this team.]
Why are you playing this for us?
Why are you doing this to us?
What is this?
Can't you play something more upbeat?
Play something more upbeat for us.
[The music doesn't matter to him.]
I think Suk Jin is reminiscing
about the old days.
[Very excited guy back here.]
[This is fun!]
[No care for the beat of the music.]
[Someone is already exhausted.]
[Come on, step counter!
Climb up in numbers!]
[The hips starts to shake
whenever he gets excited.]
[This dance machine doesn't know
how to stop.]
[Is he scratching his back on the wall?]
[Time to check the numbers.]
[Gary- 184.]
[They're all pretty much the same.]
223.
[Ha Ha- 223; Jong Kook- 318; Ji Hyo- 253.]
You will all now be going out into the
market to buy your items.
[Earned money based on their numbers
to go shop out in the market.]
[But...]
[Due to a sudden influx of people...]
[It made it impossible to do
their grocery shopping mission.]
[Resulting in a sudden change
in their mission.]
[Settling for a mini restaurant game.]
[Suzy is given psychic powers for having
the highest number from the first mission.]
[The rest of the players are disgruntled.]
- What are we going to do now?
- We have another game in mind.
[So... another game is suggested.]
We're going to play the
'Strike Out the Book' game.
['Strike Out the Book' game.]
There are three books with a coin
laying on top of each book.
You can only move onto the next round
if you get three strikes in one attempt.
[Must flip the coins over to the 'S' side
all in a row in order to succeed.]
- I'm going to win this!
- I'm good at this game.
Okay, buddy!
- We can set up our own game, right?
- You set up your own game.
[Everyone to set up their own games.]
She's learned something from us.
[Suzy's up first.]
Suzy Q.
[Fail]
[An identifiable reaction from Suzy.]
- What kind of a reaction was that?
- I've never seen that kind of a reaction.
What was that?
A bird?
[Next up is, Hefty Ryu.]
Okay, second player up.
Please make sure to shout out, 'Challenge'
before you take your turn.
- But I didn't shout that out.
- Then you may go again.
[Say what?]
- What are you doing?
- You can't do that.
- She didn't shout it out.
- Let's just let her go again.
Are you switching it back around
for her because she's right handed?
[Hefty Ryu's thoughtful gesture.]
Seriously, Hyun Jin.
You're making us all look bad.
[Teacher Kkuk starting his lessons again.]
Just knock it off.
[Everyone's starting to get annoyed
by Kkuk's nonstop meddling.]
- Just wait until I get my hands on you guys.
- Get out of the way, Mr. Turbo.
[Meddling Mr. Turbo.]
[Oh my!]
[Hefty Ryu giving Suzy helpful hints.]
[How will she fare after his one pointer?]
[Strike]
- One strike!
- What is that thing she does?
Two strikes!
[Two strikes]
Hang on, wait.
[At this rate,
Suzy could succeed in one blow?]
Suzy's pretty quick to pick up on things.
[The last coin that stands in her way
of getting three strikes in a row.]
No way.
She's not going to get another one.
[Will she do it?]
[Ball- Ah...]
[Fail]
Okay, you're out.
- Suzy's out.
- He just shoved Suzy out of the way.
Suzy is out!
[Suzy's unique reaction to failing.]
Challenge.
Hyun Jin.
[Ever so lightly...
As expected, he gets a strike.]
[He seems to have figured it out?]
- You don't need any psychic powers.
- No, I need at least one.
[Even the monster pitcher is focused
on earning his own psychic powers.]
You're going to get a ball this time.
[Gets the second strike just as lightly.]
- It's over now.
- You're not going to make it.
[Two strikes and no ball.]
[The last pitch...]
[As tense and thrilling as any other
games they've seen him play...]
[Ah...]
[Giraffe times it perfectly
to throw off his game.]
[Seriously no more touching
from now on!]
No touching from now on, okay?
- I seriously am not going to do it.
- Jae Suk, okay?
[Next up is Yoo Hyuk.]
- You're all set up to go.
- I'm going to do it fast.
[Three quick pitches in a row
without any pause in between?]
[Did he succeed?]
[One strike]
[Two strikes]
[Ball]
[So close to succeeding...]
[He would've succeeded right away
had he flipped over the first one.]
Is this how he did it?
[Suzy's failed reaction.]
Ah, seriously!
I was so close!
- Just do it.
- Challenge.
[Fails right off the bat...]
[Fails from the first pitch.]
You really are bad at this game.
The scientist is about to take his turn.
This is going to take a while,
but please be understanding.
[Teacher Kkuk focusing all his concentration
on the best way to slam down on the book.]
- Hey!
- Challenge.
[Challenge]
[Fail- Ball.]
- That was a good hit.
- No, it wasn't.
No, it was good.
That's how you're supposed to hit.
I'm sure it would've flipped over
if it was a good hit.
Challenge.
Okay, okay, okay!
[One ball]
[Two ball]
[Three balls...]
[None of the coins even budged...]
[Okay, three balls.]
[Automatically breaking out
in Suzy's failed reaction.]
Okay, my turn.
We don't have much time, Kwang Soo.
You need to hurry.
[Prank No. 256- Rush Kwang Soo.]
[Kwang Soo feeling rushed all of a sudden.]
- Challenge!
- One, two, three.
[Fail...]
[Fails immediately from the first pitch.]
Why do you keep doing this to me?
Why are you suddenly doing
a countdown with me?
- We have to hurry.
- Challenge.
[What?]
[After getting his two strikes...]
[He covers up the third coin with
his hand.]
[Covered up the coin from
having missed his mark.]
Can you let me do this one again?
I accidentally covered it up with my hand!
What have I done!
[Pissed off.]
I hit the last coin with my hand.
[Back to Yoo Hyuk's turn.]
- We're really short on time right now.
- You know me. I'm going for it.
[Rolls over and over...]
[Strike]
That was a strike.
[Two strikes]
Are you going to play dirty like this?
- You're playing dirty.
- You have to play fair and by the rules.
[What will come of this turn?]
[Three strikes]
[Strikeout]
[A dirty play...
but still managed to strikeout.]
[Three strike, strikeouts- Jae Suk wins.]
[Yoo Hyuk is the winner of the
book strikeout game.]
[Earns himself psychic power money.]
[Welcome to psychic baseball field.]
[Players entering the field.]
[Running Man's Jae Suk]
[Running Man- Jae Suk]
[Hitter with a big heart-
Baseball manic, Yoo Hyuk.]
[Running Man's Jong Kook]
[All the players enter
the field with confidence.]
[Hm...]
[A cheerful greeting to an empty stadium.]
[And...]
[Ryu Hyun Jin with Running Man.]
[The captain of Running Man's psychic
baseball team, Ryu Hyun Jin's entrance.]
Look at him run.
[Running head on towards his
rightful place on the mound.]
I didn't know you could run that fast.
I can't believe that you were able to make it
here with your busy schedule.
[And today's special umpire.]
Today's event makes anything
in this world possible.
Please allow me to introduce myself.
My name is Huh Joon.
The truth of the matter is
it's impossible to play a game of baseball
with the number of players you have here.
That's why there are some special guests who
have come on the show to join you today.
[There are more players that will
be joining the psychic baseball game?]
Where are they?
[Who could it be?]
[First additional player enters the field.]
[How can this be?]
Isn't that Lee Byung Kyu?
[He's here!]
[The king of all hitters,
the pillar of strength for Team LG Twins.]
[Lee Byung Kyu with Running Man.]
Byung Kyu!
[The indestructible player, Lee Byung Kyu.]
Awesome!
- Byung Kyu!
- Hello, Jae Suk.
- It's been so long!
- I haven't seen you in ten years.
[He and Jae Suk are friends?]
- Jae Suk, you know him?
- Of course!
[Junior Hyun Jin takes off his hat
the moment Lee Byung Kyu enters the field.]
Hello, Byung Kyu.
- I can't believe you're here!
- I'm a huge fan of yours!
[A formal 90 degree bow in greeting.]
[Just then]
[Someone else is entering the field!]
[The machine who never misses his hit!]
[Top hitter, Kim Hyun Soo who ever constantly
shocks his fans with his skills!]
[Kim Hyun Soo with Running Man.]
Why are you here?
[Totally starstruck-
The hearts of Korean baseball are all here!]
- Who is it?
- Who is it this time?
[Hyun Jin and Kim Hyun Soo are friends
who are of the same age.]
[And last but not least...]
Isn't that Shin Kyung Hyun?
[The man who made everything possible
for Ryu Hyun Jin, Shin Kyung Hyun.]
[My mentor...]
[Having been by Ryu Hyun Jin's side
as they took home 81 victories together.]
[Ryu Hyun Jin-Shin Kyung Hyun duo
that broke Korea's pro baseball history.]
[Shin Kyung Hyun with Running Man.]
[Having retired back in September,
he is now the coach for Hanwha Eagles.]
[Sir, you came...]
['I just threw the ball however my mentor,
Shin Kyung Hyun told me to throw'.]
[A quote from Ryu Hyun Jin
during one of his interviews.]
We're not playing with magic?
Isn't that what we were doing?
[They're going to play the game with
the famed legends of Korea's pro baseball?]
Are you all here to play baseball?
You expect us to play baseball with them?
- How are we going to play against them?
- How about a round of introductions first?
[Time to calm down for now,
and do a round of formal introductions.]
First is, Lee Byung Kyu from LG Twins.
Hello, my name is Lee Byung Kyu
of the LG Twins.
I feel honored to be a guest
on Running Man today.
I will do whatever I can to play my best.
[We're the ones who feel honored.]
- He and I are very...
- What now?
He and I used to hit up all the nightclubs
together back in the day.
You're such a liar.
[He used to hang out with Jae Suk?]
Well... we mostly...
About three to four times a week?
[Matching wit for wit, and joke for a joke.]
[They're curious to know Jae Suk's
success rate with all the women?]
[Zero success rate.]
And next to him is...
He is the coach for Hanwha Eagles.
Welcome Shin Kyung Hyun.
[Coach Shin Kyung Hyun of the
Hanwha Eagles.]
You caught Ryu Hyun Jin's first ball
when he first started out, right?
- Really?
- His first ball?
[Catcher Shin Kyung Hyun, having caught
Hyun Jin's first ball at his debut game.]
We even used to be roommates when
Hyun Jin first started out in his career.
- I see.
- You two were roommates?
I used to make Hyun Jin do a lot
of my chores and errands.
[Hyun Jin used to be his errand boy.]
[Sorry about all that back then, Hyun Jin.]
And standing next to him...
You and Ryu Hyun Jin are friends?
- You two are friends?
- Please welcome, Kim Hyun Soo.
You went to the same school as I did,
didn't you, Hyun Soo?
- Why are you talking in casual tone?
- He's my high school junior.
- Seriously?
- But this is your first time meeting him.
- Did you see him while you were in school?
- Of course not.
- Then why are you speaking to him like that?
- He's here as our guest.
- You should speak to him more formally.
- Did you know that Suk Jin was your senior?
- Yes, the teachers at school mentioned him.
- What? What are they saying about me?
What did the teachers say about him?
That he wasn't good at anything in school,
but he became successful on TV.
But I bet this is the first time for any
of you playing psychic baseball.
- You're going to feel very flustered by it.
- Have any of you seen the game being played?
- Yes, I have seen it.
- You've seen us play?
- Yes, we have seen it.
- How are we going to divide up the teams?
It's going to be Team Yoo Jae Suk
vs. Team Ryu Hyun Jin.
- Those are going to be the two teams.
- I want to be on Hyun Jin's team.
Why does it have to be me
against Hyun Jin?
- Why do I have to play against him?
- You're not going to be on his team!
[Everyone is hoping to be on
Hyun Jin's team.]
It's very simple. Play rock paper scissors,
and the winner gets to choose first.
And then the loser gets to pick next until
all the players have been chosen.
Rock paper scissors.
[Jae Suk wins.]
[Everyone's avoiding meeting his gaze.]
You're all turning your backs on me?
Byung Kyu!
[Jae Suk chooses Lee Byung Kyu.]
- It's all over now.
- His team seems much better now.
[Hyun Jin chooses Coach Shin Kyung Hyun.]
He still has respect for his mentor.
Okay, rock paper scissors.
Rock paper scissors!
But... since you already have two
professional players on your team...
- Can you give him to us?
- I'm not picking Hyun Soo. I want Suzy.
[A total shocker!
He picks Suzy over Kim Hyun Soo!]
You're here to play baseball, not to date!
I can't believe you chose Suzy
over him!
I choose Kim Hyun Soo!
[What luck!
Jae Suk chooses Kim Hyun Soo.]
- This game is all over now.
- Okay, the game just got evened out.
With these two players on my team?
It's all over now.
Okay, it's now time to pick from
all the minions over there.
[Now the selection is slim pickings.]
Rock paper scissors.
- Gary.
- Gary? Me?
[Team Hyun Jin picks
Mr. Random Capable, Gary.]
He knows what's up!
Ji Hyo!
[Jae Suk selects Blank Ji who has
a lot of money to buy psychic powers.]
How do you feel now, Ji Hyo?
Rock paper scissors.
Okay, Jong Kook.
Come here.
- I'm fast. I'm super-fast!
- Pick me.
[And the familiar three amigos.]
I'm not even kidding around right now.
You can't pick Kwang Soo.
Please don't pick Kwang Soo.
- Why?
- Definitely not him. I've seen him play.
[Kim Hyun Soo saw
last year's psychic baseball game.]
- No Kwang Soo for you either?
- I really am good!
- You don't know how to play.
- Hyun Soo doesn't want you.
Why not me?
- Ha Ha!
- That's right!
[Team Jae Suk recruits Ha Ha.]
We have the psychic powers.
We'll win with our psychic powers.
- Seriously?
- I seriously can't believe this.
Rock paper scissors.
This is a really tough decision.
We're going to have a team huddle.
I watched your last year's
game very closely.
- But Kwang Soo really can't be on our team.
- You think Suk Jin's better?
[But it's not like Big-nose
is that much better...]
[These two with an astonishing
level of low talent for the game.]
[Not much difference there.
It truly is a tough decision.]
I noticed how Kwang Soo kept getting angry,
and lashed out at everyone.
I'm not going to get angry.
I'm not going to do that anymore.
That's when I used to be immature.
[The meeting is now over.]
Senior.
- Okay!
- Join the other team.
[Choosing temper tantrum prone Giraffe
over physically weak Impala.]
[Team Ryu Hyun Jin vs. Team Yoo Jae Suk-
Team selection complete.]
I'll explain the simple rules
of the game to you.
The bottles that you see hanging there
will be your psychic powers.
[It is time to shop for their
psychic powers.]
[Names of the psychic powers
that are up for purchase.]
You have to recite a magic spell
before you can use your psychic powers.
- You can't be embarrassed about it.
- It'll be tough if you get embarrassed by it.
Jae Suk's very good at it.
Want to see him demonstrate?
The one who controls space!
That's how you recite the spell.
Did you see how amazed they were?
You'll regret it later on while watching the
broadcast of the show if you get timid.
You'll wish that you were more
enthusiastic about it.
[Byung Kyu seems to show great interest.]
What's happening to me?
I feel it coursing through my body!
This is how you do it.
Roll-roll!
[Screams and shouts heard
from everywhere.]
You have to do it too, Byung Kyu.
Stop the ball!
I can see your body glowing.
The psychic power is within you.
Look at that.
We can see your body shaking.
[Will Suzy be able to pull it off?]
- That's how you do it?
- You're doing great.
Are you okay?
Do you feel anything different?
Ugh, I feel weird.
It tastes good.
The one who controls the bases!
He's absorbing the power!
[Competitive energy felt
from both team's dugouts.]
Hefty Ryu!
Fighting!
[Psychic baseball game starts now.]
Ji Hyo!
You're on the defense, Ji Hyo.
- Where are you going?
- Get your head on straight!
[Blank Ji following the opposing team to
play defense when her team's the offense.]
- I was just following them out.
- Start of the game is most important.
Catch the ball that comes towards you,
and throw it over to me.
[What is this thing used for?]
We will now start your psychic
baseball game.
[Psychic baseball game- Play Ball!]
- Fighting!
- Play ball!
- Kim Hyun Soo!
- It's Kim Hyun Soo.
- We have to stay alert.
[All the opposing team's players
are feeling the pressure.]
We'll show you how it's really done.
[Preparing themselves for the hit
by spreading out their defense.]
This is making me nervous!
[Monster vs. Batting Machine.]
[Even though they've faced each other
countless number of times in pro baseball...]
[The competition between the two players
has always remained a very close call.]
[Let's determine who the better player is
in psychic baseball today!]
[What will become of the first match
between the Monster and Batting Machine?]
[Foul]
[Kim Hyun Soo moving over
to the other side of the base.]
[Monster vs. Batting Machine- Second pitch.]
[Hyun Soo takes a pitch to his body!]
[The bench clears out immediately.]
[Hyung Soo, who was hit by the ball
can only laugh at the sight.]
[Angered teammates.]
[Both teams are fired up
from the very first pitch.]
Go back out that way.
Seriously... they're out to get us.
Hey, I didn't hit you on purpose.
Why does it hurt so badly
if you didn't do it on purpose?
Why are you going to first base
instead of batting again?
- Why is he going there instead of hitting?
- Who?
[Suzy... doesn't know much
about baseball.]
Suzy's asking why he went to first base
when he didn't even hit the ball.
Suzy just asked me why he went to first base
When a batter gets hit by the ball,
he just gets to walk to first base.
[Ah... I see.]
[Lee Kwang Soo; Nickname- Asian Prince.
Specialty- Antagonizing his opponents.]
[Indicating a homerun?]
Hit it short.
- It's a ball.
- Good job. You're doing good!
I like how you're staying calm.
[Gary calmly catches the ball
and throws it over to first base.]
[Safe]
He's safe.
- No, it's okay.
- I just hit a ball that Ryu Hyun Jin pitched!
Why doesn't Kyung Hyun switch spots
since we're in a bit of trouble?
[Proposing a swap of position with
the opposing team on the bases?]
- What are you doing?
- You can't switch out the players!
[Already predicting danger
from the first inning?]
[Second pitcher for Team Hyun Jin-
Shin Kyung Hyun.]
- Play ball!
- Watch out for third base!
[Ha Ha; Specialty- Temper tantrums.
His treasured items- Shoe lifts.]
[Nice hit!]
[Too difficult of a ball to catch
for Big-nosed Brother.]
You have to catch it!
[First batter, Hyun Soo makes it
safely across the home plate.]
[Ha Ha's successful hit.]
What are you doing?
Why couldn't you catch that ball?
[New pitcher who came in to put the fire out
making the flames burn even hotter instead.]
Lee Byung Kyu!
[Discussing strategy with Coach Kkuk.]
[How will he beat this formidable batter?]
[Plan is to avoid a possible homerun
by hitting this batter with the ball too?]
You can't even hit him with the ball?
Why aren't you getting hit?
Just let the ball hit you.
[Are they playing baseball... or dodge ball?]
You have to throw it towards his body.
[Sends Lee Byung Kyu off to first base by
throwing four intentional balls.]
- Then what use is it to have a strong hitter?
- We need to strategize.
What's the use of even having
a strong hitter on our team then?
- You can't throw four balls like that.
- We need to talk about this.
- Jae Suk!
- Seriously.
- Good job!
- Is our team winning?
- No, we haven't even scored yet.
- What is she talking about?
[Baseball... is so difficult.]
- Everyone come up closer.
- You can do this, Jae Suk!
[Two outs with bases loaded.]
- Fighting, Jae Suk!
- All the bases are loaded!
[Yoo Jae Suk; Nickname- Nation's MC.
Specialty- Mouthy baseball?]
[One hit could give them a
huge advantage!]
[Strong groundball!]
Wow, that was a strong hit.
[Grasshopper gets stopped by
the monstrous wall?]
[Three outs- Switch out!]
You can go in now.
You can give me the glove.
You have to go hit the ball now.
Go to second base.
Gary is first up to bat.
Play ball!
[Kang Gary; Weakness- Song Ji Hyo.
Unique situation- Random Mr. Capable.]
[Team Jae Suk's pitcher- Yoo Jae Suk.]
Okay, that's good.
Okay, that's good!
[Huh?]
[Runs right into the ball that he
just hit himself.]
Kang Gary, out!
What just happened to me?
[Just what in the world
happened just now?]
I can't believe that just happened.
[A never before seen situation?]
- How can you get hit by your own ball?
- I've never seen that happen before.
If you get hit by the ball that you just
hit yourself, then you're out.
If the batter gets hit by his own ball,
then he's out of the game.
- Really?
- But not if you get hit while still at base.
But you're out if you get hit
once you're away from the home plate.
[It's okay...
it was a homerun of entertainment.]
Two out with the bases loaded.
Play ball.
It's Suzy.
She's up to bat.
[Suzy; Nickname- Nation's first love.
Specialty- First time playing baseball.]
[Kim Hyun Soo's face breaking out in a smile
as soon as Suzy steps up to plate.]
Why are you being so greedy
with it, Suzy?
[Suzy getting ambitious and greedy for a
big hit with it being her first time to bat.]
Do it if you think you can.
Hold onto the bat a bit tighter.
[She really shouldn't be doing that...]
Go out there and give her a tip, Hyun Jin.
Go out there and show her how it's done.
This is your chance!
- This is your chance, Hyun Jin!
- What is he doing?
[The nation's pitcher...
and the nation's first love are together.]
[Their own private
Introduction to Baseball.]
[I'm so... jealous.]
And you have to run to first base
if you hit the ball.
[Team Hyun Jin's tip- Hit the ball and run.]
You have to run this way.
Run over to that spot.
No, no, no.
[That was a foul...]
You have to drop the bat
before you run.
[As mentioned,
this is her first time playing baseball.]
[Giraffe coming in to
relieve the first pitcher.]
- Kwang Soo!
- Hit the ball, Suzy.
Use it now, Suzy.
[Yeah... now's the time.]
The one...
The one who makes men freeze
in their spots!
[Just what kind of a power is that?]
[Who are those people rushing onto
the field all of a sudden?]
[The ability to make men on the opposing team
freeze in their spots and unable to move.]
Byung Kyun looks a little annoyed.
- How is this even baseball?
- What the heck is this?
[Play ball in that position!]
[She hit the ball!]
[Unable to move.
Can't go after to catch the simple fly ball!]
[Wow! Suzy hits the ball
and makes it to first base!]
Suzy's even better than I am.
[Thank you.]
- That was unbelievable.
- Suzy's better than Jong Kook.
[The score is now even thanks to
Suzy's great play.]
[The bases are still fully loaded.]
[Ryu Hyun Jin; Nickname- Korean Monster.
Hobbies- Hitting batters.]
[An extremely nervous Giraffe.]
[Hyun Jin is remaining calm as usual.]
I'm going to strike him out.
[The ball is headed towards Hyun Soo!]
[Kim Hyun Soo's costly mistake!]
[Big-nosed Brother makes it
safely across the home plate!]
[Having difficulty controlling the ball
since they're playing with a tennis ball.]
What happened?
[What... did I just do?]
[Shin Kyung Hyun; Ryu Hyun Jin's mentor.
Specialty- Hilarity out of the blue.]
[The bases are loaded and it's a critical
moment that could determine the victor.]
- Play ball!
- Time, time!
Cease the ball!
[Shin Kyung Hyun activates his powers!]
[Team Hyun Jin is already
in celebration mode.]
- What does 'Cease the ball' mean?
- Take a look.
[What kind of a power is this?]
[Pitching the ball with all his might...]
You have to say it.
Stop, stop!
Stop!
[The ball... stopped moving?]
[The truth is,
the ball flew in out of somewhere...]
[And the ball stopped just where
Coach Shin wanted it to stop.]
[Team Jae Suk in an extreme state
of bewilderment.]
[He's known for even hitting a ball
that's being pitched at 150 km an hour.]
[If it's a ball that just stands in place...]
Just run as fast as you can
as soon as he hits the ball.
[The ball must be stopped!]
[Foul!]
[Over ecstatic Team Jae Suk.]
You can no longer cease the ball
during this inning.
[Team Hyun Jin lost their
crucial chance at winning.]
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
- Are these just look-alikes here?
- What's going on here?
[Just stand-ins that looks like
the real players?]
[Even the real players are nervous
at playing psychic baseball.]
[Immediately flies off the handle to attack.]
[Even the slightest bodily contact
results in bench clearing.]
[Even this is a show of their teamwork.]
[The psychic power was used needlessly
since they still got to score a point.]
- What happened back there?
- The ball was all mangled.
How could the ball be mangled?
It was a perfectly round ball.
[Team Jae Suk is at two outs,
and Byung Kyu comes up to bat.]
Okay, this is good.
- We could've had a chance.
- I'll do it.
Switch out the pitcher.
[Huh? Big-nosed Brother to pitch
for the Batting King?]
Play ball!
[Will Batting King, Byung Kyu be able to
save his team from two outs?]
[But just then...]
The controller of darkness!
[Activates his darkness spell.]
[What could it be?]
[Here's your adorable blindfold.]
That's going overboard!
He should still be able to hit if he's
played baseball all his life.
[Batting King suddenly transformed into
the epitome of cuteness.]
- You can still do this.
- Okay.
Suk Jin may not be able to throw a strike.
- You can still hit it.
- Throw the ball on a count of three.
One, two, three.
Wait for it!
- Wait for it!
- Swing!
[The ball hits his knee.]
[Uses his psychic power only to
hit him on the knee.]
[How could this be?]
[Turning into a big crybaby.]
[Making him walk to first base by hitting
his knee after calling upon the darkness.]
Okay, let's use our powers too.
- Okay, let's use it.
- Calling upon the power of Roll-Roll!
Roll out the special defense!
- Roll Roll!
- What's that?
- That's too much!
[It's the little league!]
[Strong little league defense team
coming onto the field endlessly.]
How many of them are there?
Come on, guys!
What the heck is this?
You're so cute.
- Don't you think that this is too much?
- How many of them are there?
[Absolutely adorable
Namyang Little Leagues Team.]
[The most adorable Roll-Roll to date.]
- Hi guys!
- The Roll Rolls are way too cute!
- I don't see any empty spots.
- Fighting!
- This is good.
[Nice catch!]
[Three outs- Time to switch.]
- Seriously!
- Don't you think that's going overboard?
Don't you think that was going
way too overboard?
- Roll Roll!
[The formidable wall of defense dissipates
as soon as their job is done.]
Thanks, you guys!
[Thank you to Namyang Little League Team
for coming out to help in this cold weather.]
[Running Man Series- Second Inning.]
[Gary on first base with Kkuk on third base.]
We're going to switch out the pitcher.
[Team Jae Suk switches out their pitcher.]
[Ha Ha walks up to the mound
with his weapon in hand.]
It's the legendary pitcher!
[How have you been, my friend?]
[So we meet again...]
[About this time last year...]
[Their first face-off.]
[Legendary pitcher, Haroro,
who struck out Hyun Jin.]
[They face off again today
for the second time.]
Am I going to get struck out again?
Get ready to get struck out.
You're going to find yourself crying home.
Controller of baseball!
What was his power?
[What is it this time?]
[I vow to hit your throw.]
[That's not going to happen.]
[The ball...]
[Transformed itself into a pigeon?]
[Magical pitch that can't even be seen
on the field of major league baseball.]
[Just when everyone's gaze is fixed
upon the flying pigeon.]
[The ball drops directly into
the glove during that moment.]
[Strike!]
- I'm a fan of yours, Legendary Pitcher!
- That was cool.
The legendary pitcher.
I can't believe I just witnessed that!
Goodbye!
Was that a pigeon?
Ryu Hyun Jin hasn't improved at all
in the past year.
You're still no match for me.
Okay, you can start your crying now.
[Cocky pitcher, Haroro.]
[What's his next magical pitch?]
I can't believe I'm witnessing this!
It's like a dream!
The legendary pitcher!
[Attack of the CO2.]
[Amazing!
Hyun Jin still manages to hit the ball!]
[But he's unfortunately ousted.]
[Amazed that he was still able to
hit the ball through the smoke.]
I can't believe he was able to hit it.
I can't believe he managed to hit that.
That's unbelievable.
- Fighting, Suzy!
- Show them what you've got.
- Play ball!
- It's okay, it's Kim Hyun Soo.
- Time, time.
- Hyun Soo!
The fence.
The one who moves the fence!
Why would you move it as
a baseball player?
[The fence... is closing in.]
[The fence has been upgraded by
having wheels under put under this year.]
What if I use this power,
and I still can't hit it over the fence?
You have to hit a homerun
since you used the power.
I still have to hit it right
for me to hit a homerun.
[The Batting Machine being more cautious
after his mistake during first inning.]
Aren't you a pro baseball player
for a living?
[The fence moves in right behind
the diamond!]
Okay!
- That's too much.
- Suzy.
We're swapping out our pitcher.
[An eye for an eye.
Team Hyun Jin swaps out their pitcher.]
[Batting Machine, Kim Hyun Soo.]
[Vs. Korean Monster, Ryu Hyun Jin.]
[A real face-off.]
[Homerun!]
[Total excitement.]
- That's a homerun!
- He's good at baseball!
- He really is good at this game.
- I'll admit it, he's good at baseball.
Did you see the expression on his face?
He was so serious about hitting it.
[I'm going to hit it!]
[That's Kim Hyun Soo!
Reputation redeemed in one blow!]
I threw that bat out of nervousness.
I hit it like I was playing in a real game.
But thanks to the fence,
you were able to redeem yourself.
[Thank goodness.]
Play ball.
[One out and Kwang Soo's at bat.]
- It's one out.
- Calm down, Kwang Soo.
Ryu Hyun Jin.
You struck me out last winter.
I will show you how
I've improved in the past year.
My parents' enemy!
I was talking!
[Totally ignored.]
Hey, I was talking!
Just keep your chatter to a minimum.
- That was a dirty play.
- You're hitter number four, Kwang Soo.
- Hey, use your powers!
- Use it!
I'm going to hang everything I have
in this hit!
Bet everything you have.
- Lee Kwang Soo just bet everything he has.
- Okay, good!
[What will come of this?]
[He somehow manages to hit!]
He finally manages to hit it
after betting everything he has.
Can you cancel that?
Cancel what I said about betting everything.
- I was being too greedy.
- No, it's okay.
[So close!]
[But Kwang Soo endures the temptation.]
- I did good.
- Hyun Jin!
Isn't that something you do only to
the major league players?
[Top speed.]
- You're being too much.
- You're being too harsh.
[This is how you pitch in the major leagues.]
[Kwang Soo is struck out again.]
Why did you throw the ball that fast?
That was fun.
[Ha Ha at first base with
Batting King up to bat.]
Fighting!
I will show you how it's really done.
The one who controls the pitch!
I forgot that our opposing team has
a legendary pitcher as well!
Hey!
Your pitch was nothing!
- I can't hand this.
- I will show you a true masterly pitch.
[Gary vs. Ha Ha.
Battle of their pride.]
- Just show us what you've got.
- Controller of the pitch.
- It's an honor to be witnessing this.
- You just wait.
I've always been in awe of you!
[Just what kind of a magical pitch
will Pitcher Gae show us?]
It's an honor to witness this.
What is it?
[Smoke?]
[The ball disappears right in front
of their eyes in a cloud of smoke?]
- Did you not see my ball?
- I didn't see it.
- The ball disappeared.
- What was that?
- What just happened?
Just hit it, Byung Kyu!
I will show you what real
pitching is like.
[Pitcher Gary showing his skills as
Batting King as his opponent.]
[Winding up for his second pitch.]
What was that?
[Unidentifiable pitch gliding towards the base
as if sliding on its own accord.]
[Strike- Sliding into the catcher's glove
as if attracted by a magnet.]
- What was that?
- What are you guys doing?
Did you not see my ball again?
Why was that ball crawling on the ground?
I will show you my last final pitch.
[Gary's final pitch.]
[One more strike,
and Byung Kyu is struck out.]
You're not going to be able to hit this.
[Strikeout for Byung Kyu.]
[Speechless... I'm the Batter King!]
[Top of the third inning.]
- Fighting!
- Get ready for his psychic powers!
[Pitcher Kim Hyun Soo vs.
Batter Shin Kyung Hyun.]
Controller of the batter!
What is that?
What is he doing?
You just have to pick
whatever you want.
- Ah, I see.
- Do you see any chopsticks in there?
[Can choose any object he wants
for the opposing batter to hit with.]
Why are you doing this to me?
[Shin Kyung Hyun's bat
transformed into an oar.]
[Hyun Soo seemingly happy
with his psychic power.]
[I'm not letting you get away with this.]
[With the right hit,
it could be a homerun.]
[Due to Blank Ji's slight delay,
Shin Kyung Hyun's safe.]
Kwang Soo!
Use your power!
I wasn't going to use this power.
It's you!
Field of thorns!
Spread yourself from first to second base!
Why do you keep doing this to me!
[Once he steps onto the mat...
he realizes that it's no joke.]
Hey!
You have to keep standing on it.
[Must run on the acupuncture mat as he
makes his way over to second base.]
We've run on that so many times.
- You have to run on it.
- I'll hit a homerun for you, Kyung Hyun.
Don't hit, and just let him strike you out.
I said, don't hit it!
[If you hit it,
then I have to walk on this mat...]
I'm going to do this.
[Shin Kyung Hyun ultimately starts running
on the mat over to second base.]
[Ha Ha on second base makes a huge mistake!]
[Succeeds in making it safely
to second base.]
- How could you have missed it?
- The ball was thrown wrong.
[That mat is no joke.]
[Bases are fully loaded with two outs.
This could be their chance!]
I have no other choice.
[Team Jae Suk seems to be
planning something.]
[What did they come up with?]
After you struck me out last summer...
- That was last winter.
- Oh yeah, it was winter.
After you struck me out last winter...
I have been waiting for this moment
this whole past year.
- Poktusul!
- Poktusul? What's that?
[Poktusul?
What kind of a power is that?]
Is he going to do something weird?
[Everyone's caught off guard.]
[But Hyun Jin...]
[That's right!]
[I've been waiting for this!]
[The king of remaining calm, Hyun Jin!]
[A nice hit with all the bases loaded!]
[He beat the Poktusul pitch!]
[Amazing, Hyun Jin...]
I'll see you next year!
I'm going to work on a another skill
until we meet again next year!
[To make a joke of a skill that
he's worked on for the past year.]
No!
- What was that? Even I was shocked.
- That was amazing.
You were awesome.
You're really good at playing baseball.
You're really good at batting.
- Use your powers, Byung Kyu.
- Okay.
Use it, Byung Kyu.
Magical zone!
[To recant the spell so perfectly!]
[Happy with himself.]
[Shouting it out proudly without
a hint of embarrassment.]
What is that?
[Huh? A net?]
Touch the net, and you're out!
What is that?
[This is the Magical Zone.]
[The bases are still fully loaded,
and this could be their chance!]
Hit it out of there!
Play ball!
[Must make sure not to hit
the magical zone with his ball!]
[Where is the ball headed?]
[Gets sucked directly into the magical zone.]
[Shin Kyung Hyun- Three outs.]
[Lee Byung Kyu's magical zone
proves to be a huge success.]
[Team Ryu- 4 vs. Team Yoo- 2.]
[And during the fourth inning...]
I'm the Batter King!
[Blank Ji shows that she's
the true Batter King.]
[The play continues on until the opposing
team can find the real ball out of others.]
[Team Jae Suk manages to score a point
thanks to Ji Hyo's power.]
[Team Jae Suk- 3 vs. Team Hyun Jin- 4.]
[Team Hyun Jin scores three more points
during bottom of the fourth inning.]
[Team Jae Suk tricks Jong Kook
and gets him ousted.]
[Bottom of the Third-
Team Jae Suk- 3 vs. Team Hyun Jin- 7.]
[The last inning.
Team Jae Suk's last chance to score.]
This is our last chance.
We have to use all our powers.
- We have to use everything.
- We have to turn this game around.
- Okay, let's do it.
- Let's turn this game around.
One, two, three.
Fighting!
We have to be smart about this.
We have to keep them on their toes.
They're going to try to use their powers.
Team Hefty Ryu, fighting!
This is Team Jae Suk's last chance to score.
No score, and Team Ryu wins.
[Will they manage to turn the game around,
or will they lose?]
The real beauty of baseball is
a turnabout in the game.
Come to me, magical bat!
What's that?
You can't throw the ball,
but you have to roll it on the ground.
- How is that even baseball?
- Okay, we got this!
- Ji Hyo!
- You can do this!
- You can do this, right?
- I can do this!
The one who controls the
defense line!
[They really are using
all their psychic powers!]
I want all the defensive players to be taken
to that corner over there and stay there.
[All the defensive players to be moved
to that tiny corner over there.]
What is this?
All of you, back up!
Back up!
[Then the pitcher is
the only line of defense?]
[Team Hyun Jin's whole defense line
is moved way back.]
Hurry up and move it!
- What is this?
- This is making me nervous.
- How am I going to do this?
- Hit the ball and make a run for it!
[Roll the ball like kickball.]
[The pitcher must carry the ball
all the way over to first base.]
[Touches down safely at an empty base.]
[Team Jae Suk manages to get
the first base loaded.]
[Team Jae Suk with all the bases loaded,
and two outs.]
Am I the last batter?
[Jae Suk is ultimately the final batter?]
[Must hit a homerun to turn
the game around.]
[Ousted, and it's game over.]
Anything can happen on the bottom
of the ninth with two outs in baseball.
I'm really nervous.
If you get ousted, then it's game over.
Stop saying that to me!
You don't think I know that?
You could go down in history!
[Will I be the last to get ousted,
or will I save the team?]
[Two outs and the bases are loaded.]
[If I hit a homerun...]
[Then I can turn this game around!]
[I have to do this!]
[Strike one.]
- I'm nervous.
- This is making me really nervous.
[One ball and one strike.]
[Hits the ball towards Gary!]
[Gary loses the ball!]
[This is it!
Run with everything you have!]
[Blank Ji makes it home!]
[Hyun Soo makes it home!]
[And even Kwang Soo makes it home!
Three points scored!]
[Yoo Jae Suk helps score
three points for his team!]
[Bottom of the fifth inning.
Team Jae Suk- 6 vs. Team Hyun Jin- 7.]
[How can this be...]
[Only a one point difference!
One more out and it's game over.]
We just need to get one more.
Play ball!
[Will they turn it around...
or will this be their end?]
Come to me, magical bat!
[The ball transforms itself.]
[The fate of the team rests
in Blank Ji's foot.]
- We have to stay on our toes.
- Kick it hard.
[Please...]
Kick it hard.
[It's game over if they oust Blank Ji!]
[Will they be able to pull it off?]
[Safe]
[Team Jae Suk making it possible
to turn the game around.]
[Next up to bat to throw more fuel
to the fire is, Kim Hyun Soo.]
[And Hyun Jin steps up to the mound
to stop him.]
It's two outs at the bottom of the last inning
and it's Kim Hyun Soo against Ryu Hyun Jin!
- Wow, this is nerve wrecking!
- Nice!
[An unavoidable final face-off.]
[Ball]
[Hyun Soo being picky with his swings.]
[Second pitch...]
[A strike!]
Don't get flustered, Kim Hyun Soo.
It's okay.
No need to be that nervous!
It's okay to breathe!
[Jae Suk on third base flies
towards home base!]
[The score will be tied as long as
no one gets ousted in first or second base!]
Keep going!
[Blank Ji ousted on second base.]
[Flustered Blank Ji
rushed back to first base.]
The one who controls time!
Why isn't it working?
Why isn't my power working?
[Game over]
[Final score-
Team Jae Suk- 6 vs. Team Hyun Jin- 7]
[Team Hyun Jin wins
2013 Psychic Baseball.]
Byung Kyu's the Batter King and all he did
was wear a blindfold a couple of times.
[We apologize, and we hope
that you come back on our show.]
['R' marked gold ring is given out
to the players of the winning team.]
I should wear this when
I'm rapping.
It's pretty.
To Lee Byung Kyu, Kim Hyun Soo and
Coach Shin Kyung Hyun who joined us today...
We'd like to thank you all again
from the bottom of our hearts.
Suzy, who's been with us
for the past two weeks...
And also, Ryu Hyun Jin!
[We'll keep cheering for you,
Korean Monster, Ryu Hyun Jin!]
- Byung Kyu was really good at chanting.
- He was awesome at recanting his spell.
- That was the best I've heard it being done.
- How did you do that?
Magical zone!
Subtitles by DramaFever
[All the secrets were cloaked
in a numerical sequence.]
[Appearing out of nowhere...]
[All of these unidentifiable numbers.]
[A riddle that they've been faced with.]
[The countdown has already begun.]
[Using everything they have
to solve the riddle.]
[A bloody battle bringing out
the true nature in everyone.]
- What are you guys doing?
- He helped me peel my orange.
[A new love?]
[And...]
[Lee Seung Gi!]
[Han Hye Jin!]
[And Sistar's Bora!]
[A challenge that they're faced with.]
[If you can't... solve the riddle...]
[You end up disappearing.]
What the heck is this?
[December, 1, 2013-
Unlock the secret code.]