[Somewhere from a faraway galaxy]
One mistake, and it could all be over.
- It has antennas on its head.
- It came to find what it needs.
[Their goal is to find 21 liters of
water of life.]
[Complete the mission and
return to planet 21.]
[Trade the overflowing energy of aliens
from planet 21 for water of life.]
[Will they be able to get their hands on
21 liters of water of life?]
[Running Man - Attack of 2NE1]
Subtitles by DramaFever
[One rainy morning...]
[Han River Park in Seoyoondo.]
[Even though the day is cloudy and overcast,
the members are in cheerful moods.]
- It's another cloudy day today.
- Yes.
Even though the day may be cloudy,
we're still dressed very bright.
What do you mean, bright?
You look like a snake dressed like that.
[Brightly dressed, silky, muscular snake.]
- This is the latest style.
- That's what bicyclists wear.
If you want to talk about pants,
take a look at Ji Hyo's pants.
- Ji Hyo's pants...
- Did you sew your pants together?
[Ji Hyo's high fashion pants
in need of an explanation.]
- I was told to wear these.
- Did your mother sew them up for you?
What are we doing today?
- I was told to wear something futuristic.
- Why did you ask us to dress like this today?
- Even though you may not remember...
- Yes?
All of you... are space aliens.
[Space aliens?]
There he goes again.
I remember!
[Moment of awakening?]
Just how far are you going
to take this?
Even though you may not really remember
since you've been on earth for so long...
I don't remember a thing.
Even though you may look like earthlings,
all of you are space aliens.
I sincerely welcome all of you
here on earth.
I received word that some other aliens
have just arrived on earth.
- Please ask them to come out.
- Really?
- We'll welcome new aliens out here.
- Please come on out!
Come on out!
[Spaceship doors start to open...]
[Who are the other space aliens
that have made their way to earth?]
[Wait, these are...]
[The ladies are here!]
[Four dimensional alien idols, 2NE1!]
[Welcome to earth!]
[Entering while dancing
their alien-like dance.]
That's the way we should've
dressed today.
[Hi, earth.]
[A glaring entrance.]
[Even though they may be from outer space,
their manners are still impeccable.]
[Please don't do that.]
Please say a word of greeting
to our viewers.
- Hello.
- What's up! We 2NE1!
I can now understand why we were asked
to wear flashy futuristic clothing.
But it's not easy to get outfits like
the ones they're wearing.
This is the way to dress if
you're to dress in futuristic fashion.
The outfit that you're wearing
is the most conservative.
- The way Min Ji is dressed...
- She and I are dressed very similarly.
[Same clothing look,
but different feel to it.]
But, Sandara Park is...
[Huh? Who's Sandara Park?]
We have a long established relationship
with Sandra.
But you don't wear your hair
like that much these days, do you?
I usually have my hair up like this when
I'm just lounging around at home.
I know that these ladies don't usually
come out on variety programs.
- Isn't this your first time?
- I think this is their first time, isn't it?
- Yes, it is.
- It is, isn't it?
- We were determined to come on this show.
- Really?
[2NE1's declaration of being determined
to make their appearance on this program.]
[Their unstoppable spirit!]
[Overflowing amount of energy!]
[Their sense of humor that they've
kept hidden comes out in full force!]
[They're on fire!]
What's that guy's name again?
[Michael?
It's me, actor Lee Kwang Soo.]
- Is it Michael?
- He's younger than us.
- Really?
- Yes, it's true.
- Kwang Soo's younger than you?
- Yes, these two are older than him.
[This face is younger than Sandara Park
and Park Bom?]
- How old are you?
- How old are Bom and Sandara?
- We were born in '84.
- Then you are older than him.
Don't even think about addressing them
as your older sister.
- Don't even think about it.
- I'd like to see you try.
[Never address them as your older sister!]
I'll tell you the reason why all you aliens
have made your way to planet earth.
- Why? Why did we come here?
- What is our mission here?
You all came to earth in search of water from
a planet that is in desperate need of water.
The amount of water that you all need
to take back to your home planet is
exactly 21 liters.
[The amount of water needed to save their
home planet is exactly 21 liters.]
I see... it's because they're 2NE1.
[The meaning of 21 liters...
quite easy, isn't it?]
Your mission is to obtain that amount
of water by the end of your final mission
and return it back to your home planet.
Whenever you fail to complete your mission,
something unfortunate will happen to you.
So please make sure that you
pass each of your missions.
- I will now announce the teams.
- Sounds good.
- Yoo Jae Suk...
- Yes?
- Lee Kwang Soo.
- Come on!
[First team- Jae Suk and Kwang Soo.]
Park Bom and Minzy will also join your team.
[First Team-
Jae Suk, Kwang Soo, Park Bom, Minzy.]
Bom, and Minzy... come over here.
So there are going to be
three teams?
Ha Ha and Gary...
with Sandara Park and CL.
[Got lucky, didn't you?]
[By default, the third team is
Suk Jin, Jong Kook and Ji Hyo.]
- We've got your manager, coordinator...
- He's our department head.
- Wait a minute!
- What?
[Seems like Department Head Jong Kook
will become butt of Jae Suk's jokes all day.]
An agent that will guide you
is about to make his entrance.
Really?
Look, it's Dong Wan.
He's from Men in Black.
[Men in Black's top agent,
Agent Go makes his entrance.]
It's nice to meet you all.
I'm MIB's top agent, Agent Go.
Just go on with it.
It's time for you to receive your tools
that you will be needing.
One member of your team can
choose a bell.
And the rest of the team members will
choose one earthly item.
A bell and an earthly item?
First, choose a member of your team
that will be using the bell.
Should I do the bell?
But what is it? What's the bell for?
[Jae Suk from Team Jae Suk
to use the bell.]
- We choose Gary.
- You do it, Gary.
[Gary from his team chooses the bell.]
- Jong Kook, you do it.
- The rest of the team members...
You will step forward and choose
your earthly item.
[The rest of the team members to choose an
earthly item numbered from one through nine.]
- Number three.
- I'll take number five.
- Number five?
- And I'll take number nine.
The rest of you can take these numbers.
[With the exception of the bell takers,
the remaining members to take the numbers.]
You will now start your mission.
But before we do that...
Please give me your attention
for a moment.
Wow, what's that?
That's the thing that makes you
lose your memory.
[The memory eraser from Men in Black?]
- What do you take us for?
- Are you going to embarrass us like this?
[It's not like this is the first time...
Just accept it and let him do it.]
Okay, here I go.
One...
[One member with his sunglasses on.]
Take off your sunglasses, Mister.
Okay, I will.
Hurry up and do it.
He thinks that he's a big time celebrity
ever since we got back from Hong Kong.
- I wore them because my face is puffy.
- What's wrong with your face?
Just hurry up and do it.
Why, you want to see?
This is what I look like.
[Frightened!]
Everyone, look over here.
Here, I go.
One, two, three.
[Space aliens... enjoy yourselves now.]
[Because things you never even dreamed of
will soon start happening.]
Here, I go.
One, two, three.
Three.
Where are we?
[Running Man aliens having been
transported somewhere.]
Yeouido?
Isn't this Yeouido Park?
[What is the reason for them
being transported to this location?]
What is this?
What is this cellphone doing here?
[Every alien is given a mysterious item,
and a cellphone.]
Is this what I chose?
[The earthling item that
Kwang Soo chose is a mannequin.]
The mannequin itself?
Everyone, this is my friend,
Kang San Yi.
Say hello, Kang San Yi.
He tends to be pretty shy.
The little scoundrel.
We got a text.
Space aliens, we will test you to see how
well you've disguised yourself as earthlings.
Those of you that have chosen
an earthly item
must avoid other teams' search parties who
are disguised as earthlings with their bells
and find your team's UFO that
is hidden somewhere in this park.
If your name tag is ripped off by anyone
wearing a bell, you are immediately ousted.
You must make sure to carry your
earthly item with you to the end.
What do I do?
I don't have to respond to this, do I?
Wow... seriously.
Of all things, this is what I chose?
This is so unfair.
What the heck is this?
How am I supposed to carry this around?
I can't even lift this thing.
This is about to drive me insane.
Why did I have to choose this thing?
[All the earthly items are things
that will make them stand out in a crowd.]
[Since you're already in this situation,
run quickly and find your UFO!]
I'm supposed to carry this around
to the end?
Just hang on.
How am I supposed to find anything
with this on my back?
How am I supposed to find
the UFO like this?
No!
Hey.
Put that thing on here.
- Look at Ha Ha.
- Where is he?
He's over there carrying around a tent.
- How are we supposed to stay hidden?
I should hide somewhere.
This stands out too much.
[Standing out like a sore thumb
no matter where he goes.]
I have to stay hidden.
This is driving me crazy.
What the heck is this UFO?
- I think I saw Lee Kwang Soo earlier.
- It won't be easy to eliminate Ji Hyo.
I'm going to go after Lee Kwang Soo.
[Alien hunters also arrives at Yeouido Park.]
[Jae Suk, Jong Kook and Gary are the hunters
from each of the three teams.]
[With the sound of their ringing bells,
they start their hunt right away.]
What's with the umbrellas?
[So many people walking around the park
with their umbrellas in hand.]
Wow... there are so many out here.
How am I supposed to find them
with all these people out here?
[Alien Sandara with her
erect antenna.]
I have to find the UFO.
I don't know how I'm going to find it.
What does the UFO look like?
I'm really curious to know.
Oh my goodness, seriously!
I can't even do anything with this.
I bet all these kids would be shocked
to find out that I'm an alien.
[You're already plenty strange.]
Since there are so many kids here,
I can disguise the tent as one of the kid's.
Ma'am!
I brought a tent with me so that
the baby doesn't get wet in the rain.
Why don't you bring the baby
and sit in the tent?
Should we close this up?
Just sit right there, okay?
[Completes his perfect disguise with
the help of the grandmother with the baby.]
[Is this a little snail house?]
You have to let me know if
you see Jae Suk coming by.
[Just then!]
See?
He doesn't even notice.
No way for them to know that I'm here.
Isn't this a great idea?
This is the perfect disguise.
Too many mosquitoes.
[With all the mosquitoes in the woods...]
There are way too many
mosquitoes out here.
Since I'm not strong enough,
I won't be able to battle them physically.
So my plan of action is to run
away from them.
- Sandara!
- Oh my God!
[Discovered by Hunter Mr. Capable!]
Oh my God!
I can't die already!
Sandara!
There's Jae Suk!
- Sandara!
[Jae Suk and Jong Kook hot on
Sandara's tail!]
[Rule- Alien hunters can utilize bicycles.]
You stand out too much with that hair!
No!
I have to get away!
Sandara Park!
[Bom and Minzy from the Pink Alien Team
joins in on the chase!]
- Come on, Jae Suk! Come get her!
- That's right!
[Sandara of the Orange Alien Team
is completely surrounded!]
Sandara!
Be careful not to hurt yourself.
- Sandara! Get off the ground!
- You have to get her!
Be careful not to hurt your head.
- Yes!
- Hurry up and run!
[With amazing teamwork,
Pink Team ousts Sandara!]
Okay, this is good.
Let's just keep staying here.
This is the first time I've been on a show
like this in four years.
I can't believe that I'm ousted
as soon as the show starts.
Hey, but this hair of yours is
way too cute.
It's because of this hair of yours.
You can't hide with that antenna hair.
[As soon as the hunt starts, Sandara is out!]
Minzy.
I'm sorry.
[Moments before Minzy is about to be
captured by Jong Kook.]
[Minzy's teammate, Alien Jae Suk
blocking Jong Kook's path.]
Look at Minzy's face.
Look at how exhausted she looks right now.
That's why I'm going to end her
suffering for her right now.
[Minzy throwing herself
down onto the ground.]
Listen to me.
- Just give me a break just this once.
- I can understand what you're saying.
- I'm sorry.
- Come on, please!
Sandara just joined the game too,
but she's already out.
- I can't believe you ousted her already.
- I'm going to stop you from getting to her.
Get out of my way!
[Jae Suk's desperate attempt to
save Minzy from getting ousted.]
- Minzy, I really am sorry.
- Why me of all people?
The reason why is because...
[Makes her escape once again.]
I said, get out of my way!
Ouch, that hurts!
That hurts!
I said, that hurts!
Stop it!
[Minzy takes advantage of the time
and makes her escape far away.]
Don't grab me with the name tag.
That really hurts.
Do you want to know how that hurts?
Give me that.
You want to see how much that hurts?
That hurts, doesn't it?
- That hurts!
- Hurts, doesn't it?
That hurts!
- Where's Kwang Soo?
- We can go find him.
- Tell me where Kwang Soo is.
- Let's try to find him.
- I'm sorry.
- Here. Take that with you.
Seriously.
What kind of an item is this?
[Extremely displeased with
their earthly items.]
- It could've been a cellphone or something.
- Something small that we can carry.
What's this UFO?
[On top of everything else, they
don't even know what the UFO looks like.]
Do you think it could be this?
Since we're aliens...
Do you think it could be a car?
It was the UFO that supposedly
brought us here, isn't it?
[A very likely deduction.]
Could it be some sort of
transportation?
[The UFO that they're supposed to find
is a mode of transportation for the teams?]
I think you're right.
Wow, you're really smart.
Just trust me and follow my lead.
Wow, you're seriously so smart.
Okay, let's hurry.
Let's hurry and find it.
Just trust me and follow my lead, okay?
Be quiet!
- I'm going to shock you today.
- You with your four arms.
- What do you mean, I have four arms?
- Look at you with your four arms.
[Alien with four arms attached.]
- You have arms sticking out of your pockets.
- No, I'm just borrowing them for a bit.
- You need to escape.
- Did you run into anyone?
Kim Jong Kook and Jae Suk are
over there fighting right now.
Jae Suk's trying to stop Jong Kook
from eliminating me.
You have to be careful.
- It's Gary.
- We need to hide.
[Orange Team's Hunter,
Gary is approaching!]
Hey!
Your arm!
Kwang Soo!
You dropped your mannequin's arm!
Hey, Lee Kwang Soo!
[Coming too close for comfort to Gary
in his attempt to retrieve the arm.]
Jae Suk, help me!
Come on, Gary.
[Is Jae Suk going to help
Kwang Soo this time?]
Hey, Gary!
Hey, Kwang Soo!
Just stick it out!
- What do you think you're going to do?
- I have four hands.
I have four hands!
[All he is a high maintenance Giraffe.]
Jae Suk!
You have to come help me!
[Pink Team's four armed alien is out!]
Come here.
[Jae Suk in the meantime makes
his attempt at capturing Ji Hyo.]
- Ji Hyo.
- Jae Suk!
I have an earthly possession!
Don't do this to me!
Ji Hyo, don't do this.
Minzy is coming.
There you go.
Come here, Minzy.
[Minzy assists Jae Suk in ousting Ji Hyo.]
- But our team only has three members.
- But you've got Kim Jong Kook.
[With some assistance,
Green Team's Ace Alien is out!]
This stands out too much.
I'm not the one swerving around.
It's too windy out here.
Hello, Ma'am.
[Wait, this tent is?]
Would you like some shade?
- No, it's okay.
- Really?
I'm sorry.
[Nice.]
Stop right there!
Don't come here.
Don't come in this direction.
Hey, don't come here.
Can you get yourself ousted for me?
Don't come here.
Don't come this way!
- Stop right there!
- Don't come this way, Minzy.
[Alien Suk Jin is surrounded instead!]
[Jae Suk and Gary work together
to capture Suk Jin!]
Is it over?
[Green Team's Alien Suk Jin
is ousted!]
[Is Alien Park Bom disguised as a music
student on her way to class?]
There he comes again!
There he is again.
[It's the athletic alien hunter
on the scene!]
Is that the UFO?
That looks like it could be it.
- Bom!
- Is that the UFO?
What did you say?
No, you can't!
- This is the UFO!
- No!
[It's not easy to run away with
the bulky cello in hand.]
- Bom, I'm so sorry!
- No!
I'm sorry!
You shouldn't have told me that.
Telling me that was the UFO was a mistake.
- I was lying.
- Really?
[Music student Alien, Park Bom - Out!]
[Out for a leisurely stroll.]
[Alien Hunter, Mr. Capable!]
[Jae Suk is also hot on CL's trail!]
[No way to escape,
and the only option is to scream.]
[Gives up as much fight as she can,
but in the end...]
CL!
- This is your item?
- Yes.
- It's really heavy.
- Nice, nice.
[Baby stroller Alien CL- Out!]
[Snail Alien finally makes his move
in search for the UFO.]
That's the UFO!
There it is!
Isn't it that shiny thing over there?
That's it!
[Correct answer!
The identity of the UFO is a car!]
I found it!
[Orange Team succeeds!
Snail Alien Ha Ha arrives at the UFO.]
Is that it?
There it is.
This must be it.
[Minzy also finds their team's UFO after
canvassing all over the park!]
I wonder when the rest of my
teammates will arrive?
I'm the only one here.
[Pink Team succeeds! Determined Alien
Gong Minzy boards her UFO!]
Hey, Minzy!
- What happened?
- What's going on?
- This is our UFO.
- This is the UFO?
- Okay, the search and hunt game is over.
- Okay.
From your team, Lee Kwang Soo and
Park Bom were ousted.
- Minzy was the only one who found the UFO.
- Yes, that's true.
We will deduct an amount of water depending
on the number of people who've been ousted.
[For every member ousted,
two liters of water will be deducted.]
[A whopping four liters of water deducted from
the 21 liters of water they need to protect...]
[Green Team also loses four liters
from their water supply.]
I'm sure we'll get a chance to
fill the water back up.
[Orange Team also loses four liters of water
for having two of their members ousted.]
If she hadn't worn her hair up like that,
she wouldn't have been caught.
[First round results: The Pink, Green,
and Orange Teams all lose four liters each!]
Sandara.
Your antenna is standing straight up.
Sandara!
Your antenna...
Look, it's the LTE hotspot here.
We've got free Wi-Fi.
To all the outer space aliens.
Take yourselves to Han River Waterpark.
Han River Waterpark?
[UFO takes off to take the aliens
over to Han River Waterpark!]
- We want to change our image a bit.
- How do you want to change it?
- Your image right now is great.
- I think we come across as being very scary.
[Their current image is too scary?]
[They do have a very strong image...]
People say that we're too scary
to even approach.
- You guys are so charismatic on stage.
- Tons of charisma.
With your heavy eyeliner and everything.
- That's why I lightened it up today.
- Yes, I can tell.
- We didn't even wear lashes today.
- You look nicer today too, Minzy.
Your eyes look
so nice and kind now.
- Kind eyes.
- Yes, your eyes look kind today.
Minzy really does look like
the girl next door today.
Minzy's eyes look so nice the
way they are today.
- Her eyes are the kind of eyes that I love.
- Please don't try to make a pass at me.
What do you mean, make a pass?
- Why are you trying to make a pass at her?
- I'm not making a pass! It was a comment.
- She got you right on the mark.
- I was just saying that her eyes are pretty.
Bom hit you right on the mark.
- I think you've crosses the line.
- Bom stole the words right out of my mouth.
What do you mean, I crossed the line?
Seriously.
CL has a bit of a bad girl concept.
[CL with her astounding stage presence.]
But now that I've spent some time with you,
you actually seem really nice.
When I first met CL,
I thought she would be screaming out my name.
I thought that she would be
really rambunctious.
Screaming out everything she says.
I thought everything she said
would be really loud and upbeat.
I didn't know that's the kind
of image that I had.
- It's because you're so charismatic.
- I see.
[Han River Waterpark.]
'I don't care... please stop it.'
You have no idea how much
I love that song.
[Alien Jae Suk an obvious fan of 2NE1.]
What's this?
[What is that out on the water?]
Sandara, I can't see what's
in front of me.
I'll just walk alongside you.
Wi-Fi!
[With the Wi-Fi hotspot so close,
the jokes are bound to happen.]
The next time Sandara comes on our show,
please have a convertible ready for her.
- We came here with the sunroof open.
- She could barely even drive.
Since CL came on the show with full makeup on,
know that she's going to be wearing goggles.
[CL has to wear goggles during the water game
since she has her full makeup on?]
- No, it's okay.
- And the thing is...
I'm not even joking about that.
She really is going to be
wearing her goggles.
- Thank you.
- Wow!
No, I don't say things like that.
[CL is unexpectedly very feminine.]
[CL's public image is on
the wild girl side.]
She has a certain way she says her words.
Asking us why we waited so long to ask
them on the show in her tone.
During our drive here,
she sat so demurely like this.
- What is this?
- Listen here.
- She's so demure.
- We're talking about CL right now.
Why are you acting like such
a brat today?
- Why are you acting up so much today?
- They're like my little sisters.
[Just then, they receive a message
from their home planet?]
[Their second mission is relayed.]
[All members from all three teams board
the UFO floating on the water]
[and push the members from the other
teams into the water.]
[The last team to remain standing
wins the mission.]
[Floating Water Battle, Round One-
Starts now!]
[Orange Team:
Gary, CL, Sandara.]
[Pink Team:
Kwang Soo, Bom and Minzy.]
[Green Team:
Suk Jin, Jong Kook and Ji Hyo.]
- Ready!
- Dara, Dara!
Bright Dara!
Sandara Park, fighting!
[Round One- Start!]
- Kwang Soo, move up front.
- Think carefully about this, Kwang Soo.
[Wanting to team up together
to get rid of Jong Kook first?]
You can't be thinking of that, are you?
Wait, let's just wait it out while those
two teams fight it out amongst themselves.
[To wait out the game?]
[Flat out Giraffe.]
Attack!
Minzy, and Bom! Attack them!
[Attack, you say?]
I'm the best...
[Bom is the first to launch
a preemptive strike!]
[She launches herself at
her easiest target, Suk Jin!]
Why are you doing this to me?
[Even her own teammates are flustered.]
[Bom uses her strength to
drive Suk Jin back!]
Why me?
[A close call!]
[Just then, Pink Team's Kwang Soo and
Minzy also join in on the attack!]
[Green Team's Suk Jin- Out!]
[Just then, Jong Kook goes for Kwang Soo!]
[Kwang Soo lets his guard down after the
successful attack and gets ousted!]
[Total chaos!]
[A fierce and chaotic battle.]
[Orange Team's Gary is also ousted!]
[CL gets a tight grip on Bom!]
[CL vs. Park Bom!]
[Huh?]
[Minzy ousts CL along with her
own teammate, Park Bom!]
[No one is safe in her war path!]
[These girls... are scary....]
[Sandara getting pushed off the platform
against her will.]
[In the end...
Orange Team's Sandara gets ousted!]
[Ji Hyo tries to push her off, but... oh!]
[Minzy counterattacks Ji Hyo's attack?]
[Impressive skills by Minzy!]
[What is this move?]
[A brand new way of defense!]
Gong Minzy!
[Making attempts to lift her up
by her limbs...]
[Wow... she easily escapes from
Jong Kook's attempted grab?]
Nice, Minzy!
[Minzy making an attempt at
pushing Ace Ji Hyo off the platform.]
Ji Hyo's expression is
slowly starting to change!
[Ji Hyo slowly starting to get ticked off.]
[Minzy pushing Ji Hyo off with
her monstrous strength.]
[But Ji Hyo sticks it out!]
[Minzy escapes Ji Hyo's ploy
to take her down with her!]
- There's one left!
- There's only one left!
What are you doing?
You should've taken her out with you.
[It's been a long while since Ji Hyo's lost
to anyone in regards to strength and skills.]
Minzy!
You can do it!
It's okay, you can do it!
[What?
He's going to lift her up?]
[Wait, he can't lift her up?]
[Jong Kook is extremely flustered.]
[Everyone watching is astounded
by the sight.]
[The girl next door with
her monstrous strength!]
For the first time since Yoon Eun Hye...
I can't believe how strong Minzy is!
[A female warrior!]
Hey, Jong Kook.
How about you only use one of your hands?
No, just do it.
I think Minzy will be just fine.
[While Minzy momentarily
has her guard down...]
[Now is the chance!]
[Trying to be as gentle as possible,
but in the end...]
[Jong Kook gently eliminates Minzy.]
[Current standing-
Green Team- 1; Orange Team- 0; Pink Team- 0.]
Must be nice for you to have
won against a girl.
- What did you say?
- Good for you!
- Minzy! I can't believe how good you were.
- You're really good.
- You're so strong.
- You're like a female warrior.
Her strength is no joke.
You know who Yoon Eun Hye is,
don't you?
Yoon Eun Hye was the female warrior back
in the day when we used to be on X-Man.
I think you need to take over that title.
Then it means that you and Jong Kook
need to be the new love couple!
What are you doing!
[One man...]
[Once more?]
- My chest!
- What are you doing?
[Erupting in an excited cheer.]
[A cheer fitting of CL.]
[We can't let them beat us!]
- You guys are embarrassing yourselves.
- You may not know this, but we've got...
[Did you see that?]
Come on, Ji Hyo!
Do something!
- You're all dead!
- Okay!
[Floating Water Battle- Round Two.
Start!]
[Only Jong Kook from the Green Team
is coming out to attack?]
Seriously, this old man!
You two take care of it yourselves.
The only thing he ever does is
breathe and walk around.
[Sense of danger with the Tiger
standing his ground.]
- Should we work together?
- What are you talking about?
[Tiger attacks!]
[Starting the attack!]
[Within moments,
Jae Suk from the Pink Team is ousted!]
[Huh?]
[Orange Team's Ha Ha ousts himself
while trying to escape.]
[Orange Team's Gary vs. Green Team's Suk Jin.]
[Orange Team's Gary- Out!]
Let me go up against Suk Jin one on one.
- Let me go up against Suk Jin on my own.
- Not you, but Minzy.
Me?
- Let's go a round.
- Okay, you and Minzy go a round.
No, I can't go up against my father.
- I bet you're close in age to Minzy's mother.
- How old is your mother?
- My mom is 48 years old.
- We're the same age.
- They really could be friends.
- Think of me as your mom's schoolmate.
[Female Warrior not easy to take down!]
Sorry, I didn't mean that.
[Kwang Soo seems to be eyeing Suk Jin?]
If you can't take Minzy down,
I'll take her down for you.
[Giraffe- Out!]
What the heck are you doing?
[Everyday... every day... every day...]
[Why is Kim Jong Kook always
the star of the show?]
[Me too... Me too...  Me too!]
What the heck are you doing!
[What? Suk Jin attacking his own teammates,
Ace and the Tiger?]
- What is he doing?
- Come on!
[Today... I'm the star!]
[Even the staff members can't
control their laughter.]
What are you doing?
[Enraged Suk Jin makes his move on CL!]
[Minzy, who can no longer just stand by
and watch makes her way over.]
I'll meet you out in the middle.
Let's go take this out to the middle.
[Proposing a one on one
face-off with Minzy.]
[Coming out like a man on a mission
after three long years!]
[For this moment at least,
I'm the star of this show!]
I'm not going to go easy on you.
- What's wrong with you all of a sudden?
- What's gotten into you?
[Minzy's dance warning.]
[I'll give you a piece of warning myself!]
[To call that a warning is a bit... hmm...]
[What was that?]
[Shouts of jeer heard from
every direction.]
[What did he have for breakfast
this morning?]
[Now battling face-to-face and
attempting to win by the use of his strength.]
[However, Minzy is not even
budging from his attack.]
I... I'm not going to lose!
I'm not going to lose!
I'm going to win!
I'm not going to go easy on you!
He says he's not going to lose.
[Suk Jin making a move to trip her over
with his leg?]
[Moves out of his way!]
[Avoids the leg tripping attack!]
[Minzy starts to push Suk Jin!]
[Succeeds in countering
Suk Jin's cold and calculated attack!]
[Pink Team wins the second round!]
[Jae Suk's celebratory performance.]
[Deserving her new title of female warrior!]
I'm warning you, don't show yourself
around Seongsu Station.
[Thus, yet once again,
he didn't become the star of the show.]
If the Green Team is okay with it,
can all four members of the other teams join?
- No, they can't.
- It's the last round, so let us do it.
Have you seen what Minzy's been doing?
- We're at a disadvantage.
- She's ferociously strong!
Come on, let all four of us play the game.
Minzy's on the same level as Jong Kook.
No, I'm not.
[What is he doing?]
[I have to get some rest.]
What is he doing just sitting there?
I'll come out when Minzy comes out.
[Floating Water Battle- Round Three.
Start!]
Stick close to me.
I said stick close to me,
not pin me down!
Don't pin me down!
[A nuisance no matter where he goes?]
You told me to stick close to you!
[Just then!
Kwang Soo launches a surprise attack!]
[Everyone jumping into the cluster,
and fighting with all their strength!]
One, two, three.
[First is to get rid of
the root of their evil.]
[Minzy put in charge of eliminating him.]
Gong Minzy!
I'm going to get my revenge!
[Why are you running away after declaring
that you're going to get your revenge?]
[Capture Ji Suk Jin!]
[Green Team's root of evil,
Ji Suk Jin is out!]
[Giraffe sees his chance
and rushes in to attack!]
[Giraffe attacks Haroro!]
[Orange Team's Ha Ha is out!]
[The ladies attempting to attack
each other.]
[Pink Team's Jae Suk and Orange Team's Gary
are ousted simultaneously!]
[What should I do...]
[Three to four people are all
clustered together!]
[Kwang Soo, Jong Kook, and Ji Hyo
all ousted by Minzy all at once!]
[Now that they're out of the way...]
[Only ones left now are
the four 2NE1 members!]
[Just then!]
[Bom attacks Sandara!]
[Absolute chaos!]
[If the Pink Team wins this round,
they win the Floating Water Battle mission!]
[Will Minzy take care of
this situation again?]
[Joins Bom to help eliminate Sandara!]
[CL eliminates Bom and
Sandara with one push!]
[Sandara and Bom- Out!]
[The last two fighters left remaining-
Pink Team's Minzy and Orange Team's CL.]
Show us a real battle!
First, I want each of you to show us
a popping dance move.
- Show us your dance moves.
- A dance battle!
Let's go!
Let's see your dance moves!
Let's see a dance off!
[Getting excited himself?]
[Minzy breaking out her dance moves!]
[Female warrior's popping warning!]
[CL responds with her 'Bad Girl'
dance moves.]
Okay, let's go!
[Adrenaline pumping through his body.]
[Slowly starting to use their
strength on each other...]
[CL overpowering Minzy?]
[This is now a battle of their pride!]
[Minzy gets behind CL...]
[A close call,
but CL makes it through the attack!]
- Minzy!
- Come on, let's go!
If you lose now,
I'm going to become a joke!
You have to win, Minzy!
[Even a headlock move!]
She's got her in a headlock!
[Minzy pushing CL off the platform...]
[But CL has a tight death grip on Minzy!]
[Wow! Minzy escapes CL's clutches
and pushes her off into the water!]
[Pink Team wins the
Floating Water Battle mission!]
[She is...]
[Pink Team wins!]
[All thanks to
the young female warrior.]
- Who's the winning team?
- Us.
- The Pink Team will not lose any water.
- Okay.
- The other teams will lose some water.
- Look at how big that container is.
[Green Team loses two liters of water
for having come in at second place.]
[Orange Team loses five liters of
water for coming in at last place.]
- Wow, there is a difference.
- There is a huge difference.
[Must obtain some water at the next round
to have an advantage!]
[Off to their next location.]
[YG Headquarters in Seoul, Mapogu.]
[The birthplace of world famous stars.]
[The heart of YG Entertainment.]
- I wonder if Hyun Suk will come down.
- Is CEO Hyun Suk here?
- No way.
- I doubt it.
This is the center base of
the YG building.
Scattered throughout this building
are various types of hints.
You must find these hints
and solve the riddle
and the first team to arrive at the final
location will be the first place winners.
I bet that'll put the Green Team
at a big disadvantage.
That's why a special...
[Special?]
[Big Bang's Taeyang!]
It's Taeyang!
Hey! You remember me, right?
I'm Gae-yang.
[Green Team earning a seasoned
veteran into their team.]
[Now that Taeyang has joined
Green Team...]
[Solve four separate riddles that'll lead you
to where the transport, UFO is hidden.]
[A yellow envelope?]
- Where's the pen?
- Pen? I think they're inside the envelope.
[First level- A crossword puzzle!]
- What's your brother's name, Sandara?
- Cheon Doong.
[Sandara's younger brother,
Cheon Doong of MBlaq.]
[The space aliens slowly
working their way through the puzzle.]
[Taeyang working hard to solve
the riddle as soon as he arrives.]
Number eight... something
that Lee Kwang Soo doesn't have?
Something that Kwang Soo
doesn't have?
Number eight, that's loyalty.
The thing I don't have is, loyalty.
[Coming up with his own answer.]
- You don't have any loyalty?
- No, I don't.
- We're done!
- Let's go!
[Already finished solving the puzzle?]
- Finished.
- We're finished.
- This way, Minzy!
- We got it done so quickly.
[Checking all the answers.]
[Pass]
Go check under the table.
Under the table?
Why did you give us such
a hard puzzle?
[Another puzzle?]
[A special meaning in these
marked spaces?]
[Lee Ha Yi?]
- Did you get it?
- Let's hurry!
[Green Team also completes
solving their puzzle.]
- Can't we take the elevator?
- It's too slow.
[Green Team also finds another puzzle
underneath the table to solve.]
[Checking the puzzle as they make
their way inside.]
Rascal musician!
[Rascal musician?]
- Where's their practice room?
- It's on the third floor.
- It's on the third floor!
- Thank goodness we have Taeyang!
[Taeyang providing a crucial
piece of information.]
- Let's hurry!
- Up to the third floor.
[The Pink Team also receives
their second puzzle.]
- What's this?
- Rascal something?
Ah!
Rascal musician!
[Pink Team is off on their way
to find the Rascal Musicians!]
Let's go find them.
- Okay, this is it.
- Wow, it's so cool.
Isn't that Big Bang?
[Decorated with
cute props all over the place.]
[Arrived at the recording studio
on the third floor as Taeyang mentioned.]
- There they are.
- They're here!
[Discovers the Rascal Musicians.]
- Hi!
- Do you know who we are?
[The winners of KPop Star Season II-
The Rascal Musicians.]
[Brother and sister duo who shined on stage
with their fresh powerful songs they wrote.]
The final winners are...
The Rascal Musicians!
[Signs the contract with YG Entertainment
after having won the season two trophy.]
- You have something for us, right?
- Excuse me?
- We have a mission for you.
- Okay.
Okay, what's the mission?
We're going to sing you a song
but there are several songs mixed into
that one singular song.
So you need to guess how many songs are
mixed into it and the titles of the songs.
- Should we go inside?
- I haven't been to a studio in ten years.
I can't believe I'm here
at YG recording studio.
- Where is it at?
- I need a break.
- What's this?
- It's a giraffe.
[Even YG has giraffes lounging around.]
Where are the Rascal Musicians?
There they are!
[Greeting the next group
just as politely.]
- Hello.
- The sister. I really love you guys.
Look at those guys out there.
Hurry up and sing it for us.
- We got here first!
- You have to sing it for us first.
- Excuse me!
- It really must be sound proof.
Hey!
- I think they play it for us here.
- Yeah, I think it's done out here.
[Name the song titles that are heard
in this one song.]
[We invite the viewers to play along.
There are three songs mixed into this song.]
Lee Seung Chul's 'Don't say hello.'
- It's a mix of that song with something else.
- Right?
Then what else is mixed in there?
- Can we listen to it once more.
- Just a little bit more.
[We invite the viewers to play along.
There are three songs mixed into this song.]
Keep it down.
I think I hear Koyote in there.
What is that one song by Koyote?
Pure Love or something...
[Easily remembering all the lyrics.]
What's the name of that song?
[We invite the viewers to play along.
There are three songs mixed into this song.]
- Ah! This is going to drive me crazy!
- Why? What is it?
[He can't seem to be remembering
the title of the song either.]
- You know that song?
- Ah!
- Unconditionally!
- Yes! Unconditionally!
[But there's more than one song
mixed in there...]
[How many songs are mixed in there?
And what are the song titles?]
- Lee Ha Yi!
- Where are we going? Recording room?
- I think that it's here.
- Is it the practice room?
Yes! We found her!
Yes, there she is!
[Finally found Lee Ha Yi!]
[K-POP Star Season I,
runner up winner, Lee Ha Yi.]
[Signed on with YG Entertainment since and
is a new artist with a successful new album.]
- Hello.
- Okay, tell us what we need to do.
Okay, what do we have to do?
As you see in front of you,
there are 3 and 5 liter water pitchers.
By utilizing these pitchers only,
you have to somehow make four liters of water.
Then you'll get the hint as to
where your next location is.
- Wait, can you repeat that?
- I don't get it.
So we have to use these two
to make four liters.
This is three liters and this is five liters.
So if we use the three liter pitcher
to pour it in there...
What does that mean?
[This is hard...]
Can you play it for us one more time?
[It seems as though they figured out
that 'Unconditionally' is in there?]
How do you know that song?
- Unconditionally!
- Unconditionally.
- Park Sang Chul's 'Unconditionally'.
- Oh my goodness.
Then what are the titles of the
three songs mixed in there?
Unconditionally, Don't say Hello, and...
Why can't I think of that title?
No, I don't know.
[Yoo Hyuk trying to cheat.]
If you happen to know any of
the Rascal Musician's songs...
- Of course, I know!
- Then I'll tell you a letter to the answer.
Yes, of course I know their songs.
Jae Suk, that's not it.
[That's a CM song...]
- You know that's not the right song.
- But that's a very famous song.
Famous or not, it's wrong.
[Rascal Musician's 'Attractive'.]
I can sing the chorus for you
if you can sing it.
[Wanting to sing a duet with Soo Hyun?]
Why does your singing sound
so lecherous?
- The way you sing it sounds lecherous.
- What do you mean, lecherous?
He is acting very lecherous lately.
Bom already gave him two warnings today.
- He keeps trying to lure Minzy.
- I'm not trying to lure her!
Why do you keep doing that?
She's should be like your younger sister.
You two are seriously trying to
drive me up the wall, aren't you?
- Yeon.
- Yeon In! (Celebrity)
- Celebrity.
- Are you sure?
- Sil Yeon! (Broken hearted).
- Yes, Sil Yeon!
- Sil Yeon!
Then tell me the names of all three songs.
Unconditionally, Don't say Hello,
and Broken Hearted!
[Could that be the correct answer?]
[Lee Seung Chul- Don't say Hello.]
[Koyote- Broken Hearted.]
[Park Sang Chul- Unconditionally.]
- That's the correct answer.
- Yes!
- Now that you've got the correct answer...
- Yes?
- The hint is within the answer.
- You have to rearrange the letters.
[Don't say Hello... Broken Hearted...
and Unconditionally...]
Is it the choreography room?
- The first letter of everything is that.
- That's it, let's go.
- It is the choreography room.
- Thanks, Soo Hyun.
- Thank you!
- Bye!
- We'll see you later!
- Thanks, we'll see you later.
Off to the choreography room.
We can't experiment around by
pouring the water into something else, right?
We can only use these two pitchers?
- I got it?
- You got something?
- I got it!
- What is it?
- Can you explain it us?
- Yes, explain it to us.
[The two kids feeling frustrated.]
[First fill up the five liter to the brim?]
Fill it up like this,
and pour out three liters.
- Then there are two liters left.
- Yes, and you throw it out.
- Throw out the three liters.
- Okay, throw this out.
- Then, we pour the two liters into this.
- Okay, I get it.
[Pour the remaining two liters
into the three liter pitcher.]
Then you fill up the five liters again.
That's exactly what I was about to do.
Okay, fill up the five liters.
Okay, I got it!
If you fill that up and dump one liter to fill
up the three pitchers, then you got it.
- That's right.
- Wow, bravo.
- You actually understand her?
- Okay, watch this.
- See how this has two liters?
- Yes, and this has five liters.
So if you dump one liter into this one,
then four liters remain in this pitcher.
[Four liters left remaining?]
- She's so smart!
- Bravo!
[To check the results,
the pitcher is set atop a scale.]
Go, go, go!
This is the most we can do for you.
[Correct answer]
You're a genius!
Hey, you really are a genius.
- The choreography room.
- Okay, the choreography room.
- Fighting! Goodbye.
- See you later. Thanks.
- CL is so smart!
- She's awesome.
I'm going to sign up to be your fan.
- Why do we have to solve riddles all day?
- I know.
[Up and down all over the hallways
of YG Entertainment.]
- It's on the second floor, right?
- Yes.
[This is the choreography room.]
- Is it the right room?
- This is it.
[Step counters?]
[Orange Team also arrives
soon thereafter.]
From five liters...
[One person who still can't seem to
understand the liter problem.]
[And the Green Team is the last
to join the group.]
I think we're going to have to
wear these step counters.
[What's the mission that awaits them here?]
First, you just have to move and dance around
as much as possible to the beat of the music
then you'll find out what
your mission is going to be.
You guys look like you're here to watch us
audition while you're sitting there like that.
- And you guys look like trainees.
- What did you say?
- You're not trainees?
- We're your seniors.
- We're just here to watch you.
- I'm the Ace of our team.
- I have no competitive streak.
- Shall we do this?
- Okay, cue the music.
I wonder what the mission is?
[Music- Start]
I'm great at dancing to this song.
[Fantastic Baby- Big Bang.]
[Ace trainee who specializes in
his shuffle dance moves.]
[This man has been dancing the same dance
for the past three years.]
- How is that 'The Fantastic Baby'?
- Aren't I just like Taeyang?
- How are you the same?
- Don't I dance just like him?
[Watching his dance moves in the mirror.]
Show us what you've got, Minzy!
Show us your dance moves!
[Dancing machine, Minzy.]
That's right, Minzy!
Those are the moves!
[Her groove is still alive.]
That's right, Minzy!
Those are the moves!
[Minzy's amazing dancing skills enough
to impress anyone that is watching.]
Bom!
Come on, Bom!
You have to show us your moves now.
[Park Bom's dance time.]
Let's go!
[That's just embarrassing...]
[Giraffe dance.]
You really need to work on
coming up with something new.
- You dance the same way every day.
- Show us something new.
[Dancing the same way no matter
what song is playing.]
What's this all about?
Look at the camera in front of you,
and call out what your number says.
I wonder what those counter are for?
I have 96.
[Kwang Soo- 96.]
Mine says 62.
Mine says 429.
- Wow, that's unbelievable!
- Wow, Jae Suk!
Mine says 118.
[Kwang Soo- 96, Bom- 62,
Jae Suk- 429, and Minzy- 118.]
[Down?]
Down?
[If it's less than their total sum of 705...]
[Then it means that hint number
is less than 705.]
We'll end our practice session here.
[Ace trainee Yoo Hyuk is stopping
his practicing for the day?]
- We'll just stop it here for now.
- What are we going to practice now?
Since I have the chance to dance with
others who can follow my rhythm...
[Dancing fool feeling totally
energized by dancing with the pros.]
I'm able to dance with them since
our rhythm is so well in sync.
[The Green Team's turn at the challenge.]
- Taeyang has to show us his moves.
- Show us your moves, Taeyang.
[Wait, this song is?]
[2NE1's debut song, 'Fire'.]
- Kim Jong Kook, what are you doing?
- What?
[Dance] [Exercise?]
Show us your moves, Taeyang!
- Show us what you've got!
- Show us your moves!
[Taeyang's dance time.]
[His dance moves making others
widen their eyes in amazement.]
[Letting his body go wherever
the rhythm takes him.]
[Yoo Hyuk writing something on the floor?]
[Can't shake the rhythm out of his body.]
[Time for some cuter dance moves.]
[Quickly picking up the new dance moves?]
Get away from me!
[Taeyang's dance time
kicking up the energy.]
- Taeyang, you're doing so great.
- What about you, Jong Kook?
Come on, Jong Kook!
[Imitating President Yang?]
[Showing some power moves with his muscles.]
[Next up is Blank Ji.]
[A stony expression.]
How about the Hot Issue moves?
- Wow, Taeyang's such an amazing dancer.
- I learned a new move from Taeyang.
- Taeyang, seriously...
- That was so much fun.
[Time to check the counter numbers.]
134.
200.
100.
Exactly 100.
254.
We weren't supposed to get
such high numbers.
- What?
- We need to get close to the number we need.
- What's our total?
- 688.
- So that is it.
- Suk Jin, that is it. We're all set.
I told you that was it.
This is what we needed to check.
- Music!
- Start!
[Dancing with moves that utilize the
arms their counters are attached to.]
Shake it!
That's our Sandara!
Sandara!
[Flings off her counter
from all the excitement.]
- Hurry!
- You have to do it!
[Back to shaking!]
Sandara!
[Matching their dance moves!]
My arm hurts!
We matched our ending pose.
I'm sorry to tell you this,
but I think you need to join another team.
[Only the other three are
going to make the debut?]
Who are you?
Just who are you?
I'm the Ace.
I'm the Ace of this choreography room.
- You need to join another team.
- I've been here for over a year.
I've been here for 30 years.
[Dance Ace, Yoo Hyuk having been
practicing here for over 30 years.]
- Tell us what your number is.
- 156.
131.
- I'm so tired.
- 124.
156.
Your current total is 567.
[Less than their total count of 567?]
Is the hint different for
all the teams?
[The hint number is different
for all the teams.]
It means that the location for each
of the teams is different.
[The hint number means a location?]
It means that the location for each
of the teams is different.
[One of the rooms from all these
countless number of rooms?]
[These aliens seems to know something
pretty definite.]
[Guessing which one of the many room numbers
their number is indicating.]
We've already been to the second floor,
and third floor is the studio.
And on the fourth floor...
there's nothing on the fourth floor.
[2NE1's 'I'm the best'.]
[Dancing Ace seems to like
so many different songs.]
[Breaking out his new moves that
he learned from Taeyang.]
What is that?
It's Taeyang's dance!
[Dance moves that are angering
the other dancers.]
I just learned this move from Taeyang!
[Ah... this is what you mean?]
We're so in sync.
[Yoo Hyuk totally enamored with
dancing with Minzy and Bom.]
[30 year dancing ace veteran
who can't contain his excitement.]
You need to start going out to clubs
and learn some new moves!
[Can't hear you!]
It's not time yet!
[Total laughingstock.]
[Minzy showing others
the correct dance moves.]
[Giraffe's pumping is all wrong.]
[Totally excited.]
You need to start going to clubs.
You say you've been here for 30 years?
Get out.
Stop embarrassing yourself here.
[Getting kicked out of the choreography room
after 30 long years.]
69.
49.
- I came down too much.
- Don't you know what a middle ground is?
[The reason why is...]
[He was shaking the arm without
the counter attached to it.]
[Must have been too excited.]
I didn't do very many of these moves.
But this may not be a bad thing.
It's more than 251.
[Must be above the total count of 251.]
I brought it down too much.
- How are we supposed to get this?
- We all brought it down too much.
[Big Bang's 'Fantasy Baby' once more.]
[Dancing Ace back up on his feet.]
[30 year veteran
quick to pick up on the moves.]
[Giraffe unable to get the rhythm.]
[He's Taeyang only in his heart.]
[Is he boxing?]
What is he doing?
He's boxing!
[Are you fighting?]
What is he doing right now?
He looks like some thug at a club.
I think we're done.
I think I got the count up too high.
I think I did too much shadow boxing.
I did too much shadow boxing.
[It's above 454.]
- Let's try it.
- What we thought of earlier?
- This is it, right?
- It's 503.
- Do we have to guess the number?
- Wrong.
- That's not it?
- That really isn't it?
I knew it!
I knew that wasn't going to be it.
No, that's not it.
[No, that's not it.]
What are you doing?
[Clap your hands together!]
[Getting the crowd fired up!]
[A lively dance party!]
[The music winding down to an end.]
No!
My hands are trembling.
I told you, it's just a hand tremor.
I have 110.
- I think that mine's broken.
- Please show it to the camera.
- This thing is broken.
- It's broken?
No, it's not broken.
- You have to shake it up and down.
- I must've done it side to side.
- 50.
- But can we still guess the answer?
- It's above 392.
- That's too bad, I should've gotten more.
I've got the answer.
[What's the answer that
the Orange Team came up with?]
[Correct answer.]
You are a bad girl!
[Thanks to CL who knows the building well,
they succeed in guessing Room 501!]
[Orange Team is off to Room 501!]
[Room 501 is a fitness center.]
[Find the clue from this room,
and go on to your next location.]
Okay, let's try lifting up the weights.
I bet there's something in here.
[Where could the clues be hidden?]
- No, there's nothing.
- Nothing?
- Your total count is 524.
- It's more than that. I think we got it.
In that case...
[Taeyang seems to know where it is?]
- Lets go with that one.
- That's all we've got for now.
- Should we go with that one?
- Yes, let's go with that one.
Is this it?
Correct.
You may be on your way.
[Where could it be?]
Here it is.
What's this? This thing here.
- Isn't this it?
- That's what you found?
[A safe?]
[Green Team arrives at Room 604.]
Look at this.
What's this?
[Another safe?]
Is this normally here or not?
[Even Taeyang doesn't know if
it's normally there or not...]
This is odd though.
Why would the safe be here?
- Let's look for clues.
- And this is locked.
[The 30 year veteran is still
dancing away.]
[Couple dance unable to find their rhythm.]
Lift me up!
[Fiercely determined
dancing veteran and Giraffe.]
[Is Giraffe trying to develop
some new dance moves?]
[We won't count that as dancing.]
It's down.
[Less than their total count of 460.]
If it's on the fourth floor,
then it would be the manager's office.
- What's your guess?
- Room 403.
We're going to choose Room 403,
and the reason for that being...
What do you mean, 'shut up'?
[Pulling the Giraffe's leg with
every chance that he gets.]
- Correct answer. You may go.
- We got it!
[403 is the correct answer!]
- What could it be?
- What could the clue be?
- Look for something with the 'R' sticker.
- What do you think this is?
I found this.
[A sheet of music?]
- Oh, what's this?
- That also says February!
February, number two!
[Discovers a calendar.]
[This is also left on month, February!]
- Was this originally here?
- I don't think that this was originally here.
[Could the lock code for the safe have
something to do with the month, February?]
- Wait a second...
- It has to have something to do with two.
Can anyone read this sheet of music?
[Singing out the scale.]
But take a look at this.
Why is this the only thing marked in red?
- I think that means something.
- Right? This is the only thing marked in red.
[Only the first four music notes
are marked in red.]
Look at this.
This is the only thing marked like this.
The music sheet is titled 'February'.
- And the notes are marked in red.
- Could it be 0222?
- Why are only these four notes marked in red?
- Then what does this mean?
All the pages are the month of February.
The way I see it,
I think the number is within this page.
Yes, I'm sure.
[Pink Team having arrived in Room 403.]
- Running Man!
- The computer says 'Running Man'.
- This is our clue!
We need the password for it.
Could it be in this calendar?
[The calendar in this room
is also turned to the month of February.]
- It's Do, Mi, Mi.
- Do, Mi, Mi, Mi?
- I'm really bad at things like this.
- I can't do it either.
- I'm confessing that right now.
- I'll confess too.
I'm usually good at this,
but this is pretty hard.
- It has something to do with number two.
- It has to do with the number, two.
Don't you think that it also has something
to do with this treble clef?
This is in red, and so is this.
What if it's like this?
In this order?
[Could there be a correlation between the
sheet music and the calendar?]
[Following the musical notes...]
[Could it be 8-2-3-4?]
[It opened!]
[The door to the safe is open!]
[Numbers 8-2-3-4 matches the
placement of the musical notes!]
I just got goose bumps.
The musical sheet really was the
clue to solving it.
Just who are you?
CL... Master C.
[She definitely is Master C.]
I like you.
- I'm going to confess that I like you.
- How did you do that?
I need an intelligent woman like you.
[Rooftop outdoor garden.]
[The Pink Team is also trying to compare and
match the music sheet to the calendar.]
Do you know what you're doing?
8, 2, 3, 4?
- 8, 2, 3, 4?
- 8, 2, 3, 4.
8, 2, 3, 4!
[Rooftop outdoor garden.]
[Pink Teams also earns their hint!]
Bom did it!
[The final location-
YG's rooftop outdoor garden.]
[Orange Team is the first to arrive.]
[Orange Team will not lose any water
from having been the first team to arrive.]
Wow, by the split of a hair.
[Second place winner, Pink Team
loses two liters of water.]
I know.
[Last place winner- Green Team.]
- I don't think I'm much help today.
- But you helped us navigate around.
[Green Team loses four liters of water
for having been the last to arrive.]
But it's still not too bad.
We have to drink all this water?
- We have the least amount of water.
- No, it's okay.
[Off to the final location!]
[The final water gathering location!]
[Space aliens, find the water jugs that are
hidden throughout the area...]
[and the first team to completely fill up
21 liters of water is the ultimate winner.]
[Moving all the water that each team has
in their own container first.]
[As soon as their containers are filled,
they must be on their way to find the water.]
[Current water level standing-
Pink- 15 L; Green- 11 L; Orange- 12 L.]
Where could they be?
Why is it so hard to find them?
It's like a treasure hunt.
[Unable to find any of the water jugs.]
Minzy, have you found any?
No, not yet.
I haven't found any yet.
[Water jugs hidden deeply away.]
I don't see any!
[A two liter water jug!]
I found it!
She must've found something.
Did you find one?
Help me!
Behind me!
[Their enemy, Big-nose Brother
appears out of nowhere!]
Run!
[She's caught!]
[Water jug snatching!]
[Fortunately,
their guard Gary jumps on to help!]
[Sandara gets her water jug back.]
Watch out for Bom.
Give the jug to Gary.
[Passing the jug over to Gary.]
[Gary's powerful escape.]
Dong Hoon!
[Gary and Ro-Ro's water jug pass play.]
[Oh no... spills all the water!]
Let's wring out our shirts.
Here, wring it out.
[There was this method to consider!]
Should I go dunk myself in the water?
We should gather up all of the
water in the jug.
You can really gather the
water like that?
No way!
Yes, it really works.
There's a lot of water here.
[Who knew there was a method like that?]
I already searched around
all the likely spots.
Where are all these water jugs?
[Unable to find any water jugs.]
I've looked everywhere,
but I can't seem to find any.
Have you checked over here?
[Could it be among all the bikes?]
I didn't search very thoroughly.
Let's look through once more.
Something could be here.
- Kwang Soo...
- You found it?
[Water discovered!]
Don't show it to anyone!
What do I do?
[Precious jug of water from
their desperate search.]
[Yoo Hyuk running over to help after seeing
them making their discovery from afar.]
We have to come up with a plan.
- Minzy...
- It's a really big jug.
- What do we do?
- Put it in one of the bags.
Or should we go over there
and try to distract them?
- Minzy, stay over here for a minute.
- I'll come with you.
Ji Hyo saw you.
[Did they find any water?]
What do I do?
- Let's go back.
- Act natural.
Just act natural.
[Something feels suspicious.]
- Let's not go back there right now.
- What?
[This area is still bustling with people.]
You're such a cheater!
[Big-nosed Brother totally immersed in
gathering up the water.]
[We have to seize this opportunity...]
[Yoo Hyuk picks up an empty jug
to use as a decoy.]
[This is it...]
[Decoy Giraffe is first to go in.]
[Will Giraffe and Yoo Hyuk be able to
create enough of a diversion?]
- I have water.
- It's a lie.
I think that Jae Suk really has it.
[Yoo Hyuk, the second decoy.]
I think Jae Suk's for real.
I think he really has the water.
[Just then!]
[Young female warrior Minzy moves in!]
[I've got the real jug right here!]
[Young female warrior Minzy's
frontal move!]
[Succeeds in bringing the water home!]
[Defending their container with their lives!]
It was all a ruse!
[Young female warrior not even budging!]
- Okay, we got it.
- Wow, that was amazing.
She's so unbelievably strong!
- You were a decoy, weren't you?
- I was just a decoy.
Yes, I was the decoy.
[Hurray to the young female warrior.]
[Their goal is 21 liters.
Only about two liters left to fill.]
- Why do you look so angry?
- Why are you saying that I look angry?
I can't seem to find any
no matter how hard I look for it.
[Finally finds a water jug!]
- Stop Jong Kook!
- Get out of my way!
[Completely empty water camp.]
Stop Jong Kook!
[Pulling all sorts of moves
out of desperation.]
- Stop Jong Kook!
- What are you doing?
[Mr. Capable not even budging an inch.]
- Are we good?
- You got it all in there.
[Green Team only needs
about three more liters!]
Hey, you have to be careful not to spill!
Why did you pull down my pants?
Have you lost your mind?
- We have to save every last drop.
- Wring the water in there.
Do you think that you're even
strong enough to wring that towel out?
Hey!
[Easy Brothers' dropping all sense of loyalty
to one another for a single drop of water.]
Good job!
You did good!
I hope that you get struck down
by lightning.
[Not stopping in his attempt to
gather up any spilled water.]
Yes, we're going to have
a grand opening soon.
I have to clean up around here so that
it's clean for our potential customers.
There it is!
What's that?
[Nice catch!]
[Even reduced down to stealing the water
from a wrung out dish towel.]
Let go!
I said, let go.
I dropped it all.
It could've been over.
I barely wiped up the water
that Gary spilled.
See?
We have to save every drop of water.
[Water delivery Tiger making
a beeline for the water stand.]
It's Jong Kook!
- It's Jong Kook!
- Where?
It's Jong Kook!
[Touchdown?]
I thought you were some football player
coming in with your touchdown or something.
- It's a touchdown!
- What the heck was that?
[Running back for their team?]
[Getting to wiping down
the spilled water right away.]
[Stealing the water from
the wrung up towel.]
[What are these two doing?]
[Showing no signs of an end
to their stupidity.]
What are you two doing?
What are you doing?
What are you doing right now?
- I'm going to win.
- We love our nature.
[Water loving aliens...]
[Huh?]
[Gary's sudden ambush move!]
[Still in need of a bit more!]
- It wasn't enough?
- No! And I dumped everything in there.
[Spilled water cleanup crew on the move.]
What are you doing?
What are you doing!
[Making a desperate attempt to save
every last drop of their water.]
[Saving up the spilled water
is becoming popular.]
If it starts to rain,
catch the rain with your shirts.
We have to wring out our clothes.
That's the only option we have left.
That's the only way for us
to win right now.
[Giraffe finds a water jug.]
Look... look at Kwang Soo.
[Are they drinking it?]
[A sip for each of them.]
We have to take it from them.
[Even if our water jug gets stolen,
they can't steal the water in our mouths.]
[The Pink Team now only needs about
one liter of water.]
Kwang Soo is a decoy!
He's going to drop the water.
[Avoiding their attack,
and moving to the back of the line.]
[Attempting a full frontal attack!]
[Succeeds in dumping in the water
both from the jug and his mouth!]
I think we got it!
[Pink Team's water container
in need of a little bit more!]
That's still not enough?
How are we supposed to fill this thing up?
[Time to wipe up the spilled water.]
[Every single last drop is precious.]
- You're very good at cleaning.
- I don't even clean like this at home.
- Wring out everything you can.
- We just need one more jug of water.
[A water jug behind the boulder?]
[Water jug in hand!]
He found one?
There he comes.
It's all over now.
[Water delivery Tiger on his way!]
Jong Kook!
[Opening up the lid
and getting ready to pour!]
[This one last jug could mean
Green Team's victory!]
[The Tiger on his way!]
Jong Kook!
[Mr. Toad man?]
[Blocking off the Green Team's container
with this body?]
[Nice going!]
[The Tiger unsure of what to do.]
[Kwang Toad Man blocking off
the container.]
- Lee Kwang Soo, seriously.
- What do you think you are, a toad?
- Hurry up and start tickling him.
- You can endure it, Kwang Soo.
Everyone take the jug away
from Jong Kook!
Take it from Jong Kook!
[Young female warrior Minzy's attack.]
Over here, Minzy!
[A desperate attempt to steal
the water jug away from him.]
[Kwang Toad not budging from his post.]
[Which team will the jug of water go to
and determine the final winner?]
[All the water's been spilled!]
[Bom who had been waiting with
the towel in hand!]
[Heading off to Pink Team's container
with her soaking wet towel!]
[Wow!
Succeeds in filling up the 21 liter mark!]
[Pink Team succeeds in filling up
their 21 liter mark!]
- It's a UFO!
You can take that back to your planet.
Jae Suk, there are four pieces
of gold on it!
[Four pieces of gold ornament on it!]
You can give it all
to the 2NE1 members!
[Really?]
They really did work so hard
to do their best on the show today.
They made it fun, and did their best
all day today.
To our aliens!
- You didn't even ask me for my opinion!
- I'll ask now. What do you think?
Even Lee Kwang Soo seems to
agree with the idea.
- I saw him nod his head.
- Yes, he nodded his head.
Subtitles by DramaFever
[In the waiting room
on the day of the incident.]
- What is that?
- What is it?
[The waiting room suddenly
cloaked around in secrecy.]
Someone just hit me.
Case number 157-
A blow to the back of the head.
[The witnesses confused
by the four possible suspects.]
[The suspects born with suspicious images
are all gathered on the stand.]
They are all to be indicted
as co-principles of the attack.
- He's the culprit!
- What did you say?
[A fiery battle breaking out
in the courtroom.]
If you talk, you're dead.
If you lie, you're dead.
Gary!
My clients are denying the charges,
and would like to declare their innocence.
[Find the evidence and determine
who the real culprit is.]
[Prosecution Team vs. Plaintiff Team]
[A breathtaking, nerve-wrecking game
of cat and mouse.]
[Only those whom find the clues
can find out the real truth.]
[The criminal always leaves a trail...]
[And that trail shall lead you
to the truth.]
[Next Week's Running Man-
Courtroom Head Case.]