Subtitles by DramaFever
[Lee Kwang Soo's hide and go seek?]
[Just why does Kwang Soo
have to hide?]
[The story of a man who must
stay in hiding.]
[I really want to go home.]
['S' shopping mall in Incheon.]
Okay, what do we have here today?
[Huh? Something feels amiss?]
Kwang Soo said he can't come until later on
because of his drama shooting schedule.
Why is he pulling this stunt when
he's not even on the show much?
- So Kwang Soo's not coming today?
- He's coming later on this afternoon.
[The opening scene is a little quieter
without Kwang Soo on set.]
He said if he doesn't make it big this year,
he's just going to stick to variety shows.
- Really? This is his last year?
- Yes, he promised me.
- Then he doesn't have much time left.
- Your guests are making their entrances.
[Wow! A fancy van that only the
top stars are known to ride around in.]
- I have a feeling that it's an actor.
- Whoever it is, they're in a nice van.
- It's got to be a top actor.
- Could it be an idol?
[Just who is the top star that's making
their entrance in this van?]
Kwang Soo usually runs up there to
open up the door for them.
Yes, he usually does that.
- Someone is about to step out.
- It's not going to be Kwang Soo, is it?
[Actor, Son Hyun Joo- The man
known for his amazing acting skills!]
[Actor Son Hyun Joo who needs
no other words of introduction.]
It's Son Hyun Joo!
[Actress, Moon Jung Hee-
Actress with stellar acting skills.]
[And top star, Jun Mi Sun-
Making waves on the screen.]
[The two actresses who can stir up
the emotions of the audiences are here.]
[A shopping mall that has suddenly turned into
a film set with the appearance of these three.]
- Son Hyun Joo is here.
- He really is here on the show.
He's wearing his mic like he
would wear a gun.
[First time seeing a guest wear the mic belt
on top of his clothes.]
[Because he's so new to
guesting on variety shows...]
It doesn't really matter if you
wear it over your clothes.
You look cool no matter what.
[If Son Hyun Joo wears it that way,
then it becomes instant fashion trend.]
We've really been hoping to
see you on the show.
Yes, we've really been anticipating it.
Whenever we've had other guests like
Sang Joon, we always asked for you.
- Yes, I saw the episode when he was on.
- Oh, you watched it?
Sang Joon really got his share of betrayal
when he came out on our show.
- He was pretty weak.
- Weak? That's funny.
You have no idea how long we've
waited for you to be a guest.
Are these three going to be
our guests for the day?
- Let me tell you about today's race.
- Okay.
It's a 'numbered
hide and go seek race'.
[Today's race-
Numbered hide and go seek race.]
You will each receive a number that
will be placed under your name tags.
You won't know which number will be
affixed on your backs either.
[Even they themselves won't know which
number will be put on their backs.]
[They will start to come out one by one
to receive their number for their backs.]
[They each have now chosen a number
between one and ten.]
This game will not be played in teams,
but it will be played individually to the end.
- And only one person will be the winner.
- Just one person?
At the completion of each mission,
the person who won that mission
will be given a hint that will help them
figure out which number is on who's back.
[Winner of each mission will be given clues
to help them figure out who has which number.]
Hints as to which number means what,
and the like.
An example of a clue is, 'People with these
numbers are all actors.'
- Ah, okay.
- Those are the types of clues.
So while you're participating in the race,
you have to deduce who has which number
and make your way to
the final location.
So at the final location, you eliminate each
other by guessing which number they have.
So you eliminate each other
by the use of their numbers?
The last person to stay alive
is the ultimate winner.
Okay, I understand.
You have to judge for yourselves whether
sharing the clues you received
with others will be advantageous,
or disadvantageous to you.
But Kwang Soo won't be able to
join us this morning.
- He should be here by this afternoon.
- He's shooting his drama right now.
- I'm pretty close with Kwang Soo.
- Really?
He talked about Kwang Soo
the whole way here.
Just wait a little bit longer, and
you'll get your chance to order him around.
You might become
closer to us than him.
He should be here right around lunch time.
[But...]
[The atmosphere... feels suspicious?]
[There's someone who stayed hidden and
witnessed this whole scene unfold...]
[Kwang Soo?]
They're here, they're here.
[What is Kwang Soo who's supposed to be
on his drama set doing here?]
[One hour prior to the opening scene.]
[In one of the rooms in the shopping mall...]
[Kwang Soo making
his appearance all by himself.]
[Wait... what is going on here?]
Hello.
[Unable to contain his excitement.]
It's been a while since
you've done this, hasn't it?
It's practically my first time!
What do you mean, 'it's been a while'?
Am I really going to be
doing this alone today?
Here.
[Passing off the mission.]
Lee Kwang Soo's Hide-and-Seek?
[Mission-
Lee Kwang Soo's Hide-and-Seek.]
Then does this mean...
that I'm the star of this episode?
Well, if that's the way you want to think,
you can think of it that way.
Come on, just tell me!
Rather than saying that you're the star,
since you're so tall in stature...
I'm the star of this episode!
My dear viewers!
At long last!
Thank you!
I promise...
that I won't disappoint you today.
Let me tell you the details
of your mission.
[Yes! I'm the star!
I'll do whatever you ask of me!]
[Ah... the mission is...
that's a little...]
[Wow... I'm in big trouble.]
- Hello!
- Kwang Soo! What are you doing here?
- Hello, Jae Suk.
- Hello.
[All of the members coming
onto the scene.]
- Kwang Soo, when did you get here?
- Hello.
- You got a mission, didn't you?
- Everyone come have a seat.
- I smell the filthy stench of betrayal.
- What do you mean, smell of betrayal?
[Everyone suspicious at the sight of
Kwang Soo waiting for them in the room.]
- What's going on here?
- Why are you here before us?
- Please come in and have a seat.
- What's going on here?
Everyone have a seat and be quiet.
- Do you have a presentation to make?
Don't tell us to be quiet.
- What's going on here?
- He's been given some kind of a mission.
Are you hosting the show today?
No, not exactly hosting it.
Can you read this out loud for us?
- Lee Kwang Soo's Hide-and-Seek?
- Yes, that's correct.
The first mission is...
Lee Kwang Soo's Hide-and-Seek!
- That doesn't sound like any fun.
- Why not?
- Why are you saying that?
- Are you hiding, or will we be hiding?
- That really sounds lame.
- You're not going to do this then?
I have to explain this to you guys.
You're going to be shocked once you
find out how important my role is in all this.
- What is it?
- Today...
- There are going to be three guests.
- Really?
And also, the first mission is going to have
a subset of four smaller missions.
Of those four missions, those who come in
first through third place will pass.
Ah, pass?
And amongst those...
while you're doing those
four missions...
- You really are bad at explaining this.
- You're horrible at it!
Wait, hang on.
Give me a little time.
- You really are horrible at explaining.
- Give me a minute!
- Come on, and just get to the point!
- How long is your explanation going to take?
- Why are you so horrible at this?
- You're really frustrating us.
Once the three people pass the mission,
we'll go on to the next round.
There are four missions altogether.
And during the time it takes us
to complete those four missions
I have to complete my missions secretly.
- What does that mean?
- We're all on the same side.
All of you have to help me,
and if I end up getting caught...
then the mission ends right then and there.
And the scariest thing is...
we'll have to go into filming overtime.
The scariest thing about this whole thing
is that you're the star of this episode!
- That's the scariest thing of all!
- We all have to work together!
You have to succeed the mission before
the three guests pass their missions?
If I'm caught, it's all over.
- Feeling anxious, and the need to...
- Reasons to feel anxious?
There are game zones.
Other than myself...
What happens after this?
[Stuttering MC Kwang ultimately hands over
the explanation portion to the PD.]
I have no idea what he was talking about.
There are four floors in this
shopping mall.
You're going to have to pass through
all four floors
by playing a different game
on each floor.
Each game can only be played
in that specific game zone.
Each floor has its own game zone.
You can only play those games
within that specific game zone.
But in order to start playing
those games
you have to find the tools needed
for each game.
So while you're looking for those game tools,
and while you're playing those games...
Lee Kwang Soo has to pass those games
without getting caught by the guests.
- Okay, I think I finally get it now.
- Now it makes sense to me.
You all understand now? We have
to make sure that I don't get caught.
- Lee Kwang Soo can't be caught.
- Kwang Soo's greedy for the star role.
Because of that, he's always
trying to make himself stand out.
Greedy to be the star?
How about this? Why don't you
wear something over your head?
No, that'll just make him stand out
even more.
And you can't keep moving around either.
You have to stay in one place somewhere.
If I was just going to sit still,
then I'd be sitting still at home.
Since you're so tall, you need
to crawl around on your knees.
You know where you should hide?
In a dark place somewhere.
[Suggesting that he stays in a dark place
where the camera can't even capture him?]
- What I meant was...
- Listen to what he's telling him.
He should only come out when it's
time to do one of the games.
When it's time for you to hide,
just stay hidden so that we can win.
- Yes, that's what I meant to say.
- Come out when it's time to play the game.
Then I'll just go home and wait,
and you can call me when it's my turn.
You know what I'm trying to say here.
Okay, the guests have arrived on scene.
- We should get going then.
- You have to do a good job with this.
We're going to start with our opening.
We're going to do the opening
without Lee Kwang Soo.
Kwang Soo, if we're going to get these hints,
you have to make sure to do a good job.
[Lee Kwang Soo's Hide-and-Seek]
[His grudge over never having starred in
a drama will now be fulfilled here.]
[On the other hand]
[The guests have no clue that
Kwang Soo is watching from hiding.]
We're going to start our first mission.
[Heading inside the building to start
their first mission.]
[At last, Kwang Soo's
Hide-and-Seek starts!]
- This must be the game zone.
- What is this game zone?
- This is the game zone.
- What are we going to do here?
Are we going to be playing
some kind of a game in here?
Welcome, everyone.
After we play a game on the first floor,
which is where you're all standing right now
we're going to move up to the second floor
to play the next round of games.
Your first mission is,
The Gold Medal Empire.
- What's that?
- What is that?
You're going to need props
to play all of these games.
For example, since we're all
on the first floor right now
the props that you'll need
to play the first game
are hidden throughout the first floor.
You can only go around on the first floor
to find the props that you'll be needing
and come back to the game zone where you're
currently standing to play the game.
To those that come in at first through
third place in each of these games
you will be given a gold medal.
Okay, we're going to start playing
the game on the first floor.
The first floor game is...
- Gonggi game.
- Ah, gonggi?
Then I guess we need to go
find some gonggi.
[Wait...]
[How is Kwang Soo at gonggi?]
Ah, it's gonggi?
Where am I going to find
those tiny things?
I'm just going to have to rely on someone
else to find and bring them to me.
Gonggi pieces are hidden throughout
the first floor.
The objective is for you to find them,
bring them to the zone and play the game.
You have to get through all five levels
of the game without making a single mistake.
- Everyone must succeed to pass.
- Do we have to play with one hand?
Of course, with one hand.
Gonggi is usually played with one hand.
[Gonggi is usually played with one hand...]
No, you can't play it like that.
Okay, let's get started.
[Kwang Soo...]
[You have to do a good job...]
[Round One- First Floor Game.
Gonggi Game- Start!]
[Kwang Soo's game of hide-and-seek
also begins!]
[Right from the beginning,
rummaging through the garbage cans.]
Are all five pieces together?
Why aren't you saying anything?
Can't you just tell me if you know?
You're taking this game way too seriously.
So we just start searching without
anyone giving us a hint?
Without knowing anything?
I don't see any.
[Here they are...]
Where's Kwang Soo?
- We need to keep our eyes open.
- We need to find them as quickly as possible.
- Should we? Just find them first?
- You don't know where they're at, do you?
No, I have no idea where they're at.
He just has to stay in hiding.
[Kwang Soo, where are you?]
It's Dong Hoon!
I just heard something.
- Hey.
- Dong Hoon.
[Finally succeeds in their search for him.]
- You look so pitiful.
- Dong Hoon, do I look obvious?
I can totally tell it's you.
[Anyone can tell that it's Kwang Soo.]
We'll find the gonggi pieces
and get them to you, okay?
And you know those mannequins
that are dressed up in armor?
You should hide in there.
How can I hide in those?
[Do I look obvious?]
Where's Kwang Soo?
He needs to start making his moves.
[Kwang Soo must pass the game of gonggi
before three other players beat the game!]
He's in there right now.
In there.
He's in that room over there.
[Ha Ha's alerting others of
Kwang Soo's hiding location.]
- Get the pieces to him if you find them.
- We need to find the pieces for him.
[Discovers the gonggi pieces!]
[He must now hurry and get
these pieces over to Kwang Soo!]
Did you find them?
- Did you find them?
- No, I didn't!
Did you find them?
Kwang Soo!
[Secretly passing the gonggi pieces
off to Kwang Soo!]
Is there anyone at
the game zone right now?
[Now's the chance!
The game zone is empty!]
Hurry!
Hurry up and do it!
[Must rush over to the game zone
to successfully pass the gonggi game!]
Hurry up and run!
Hurry, hurry!
[Rule: Even Kwang Soo must play
the game only the game zone.]
Don't you dare fail.
[Ha Ha keeping watch in case
any of the guests approach.]
Calm down, and relax.
There you go.
[Succeeds through the second level!]
Okay, you're doing good.
There you go.
[Succeeds the third level!]
[Ah...]
Hey, take it slow and do it calmly.
I feel like I'm the one
who's going to go crazy.
[Just then, Hyun Joo on his
search mission...]
[Hyun Joo discovers the set of
gonggi pieces!]
[Hyun Joo rushes off to the game zone!]
Dong Hoon, is anyone coming?
Come on!
Come on, please!
Ugh, hurry up and go back into hiding.
Over there.
Go over there.
Hey, Hyun Joo found the pieces!
Really?
[Hyun Joo arrives at the zone
by the split of a hair difference.]
- I just found some too.
- Really?
- You found them?
- Yes.
[A crowd is slowly starting to gather
at the game zone... what to do?]
[Kwang Soo goes back to hide
in the dressing room.]
I'm usually really good at gonggi.
I'm normally very good at the game.
[Giraffe disappointed at having
lost a good opportunity.]
Here's another person.
You found some too, Gary?
Three people need to succeed, right?
[If all three of the guests succeed,
then Kwang Soo's hide-and-seek is over!]
[We have to stop them!]
You have to go and find yours too.
- Aren't there only these three sets?
- No, there are more out there.
He's really good.
[Hyun Joo surprising them with
his unexpected gonggi skills.]
- That one is going to be a bit hard.
- You're really good.
Don't let them get to you.
[We have to stop them!]
[He's already at the fourth level!]
I'm sorry.
That was so close.
[Hyun Joo fails the game with
Suk Jin's interference.]
[What a relief...]
It's Gary's turn now.
- It's Gary's turn.
- Okay, Gary.
[Failing on purpose to buy
some more time.]
[Kwang Soo is inside that store
to the right.]
- Ugh, this game is hard.
- It is pretty hard.
[Blank Ji sneaking away to meet Kwang Soo
in order to come up with a plan.]
Kwang Soo.
- Do you have the gonggi pieces?
- I have the pieces.
- You have the pieces?
- I got up to the second level.
Who's up on the stage right now?
Who's over at the game zone?
They're all there.
Son Hyun Joo is over there right now.
What am I going to do?
Just wait here for now.
They're all over there right now,
and the members know that you're here.
I have to get back and finish this.
That looks like a lot of fun.
It's all over now.
[No!]
[Getting ready to interfere with the game
by moving the tablecloth with his foot.]
[Success!]
- What are you thinking?
- I'm so sorry, Hyun Joo.
[Hyun Joo starting over from
the fourth level.]
What are you doing?
[An obvious... sneeze interference.]
Sorry, but I suddenly had to sneeze.
What are you guys doing?
[Hyun Joo's gonggi pieces that
fell on the ground...]
[Ha Ha steals them and runs away!]
My... hey!
Hey!
[Now's the time!]
Toad!
[Blank Ji calls Toad Kwang out of hiding.]
[No one is at the game zone!
Now's another chance!]
[But Hyun Joo gets his gonggi pieces
back in the meantime and is heading back!]
Hyun Joo is going to try again.
Hey!
[Shock]
Hyun Joo is going to try it again!
Hey!
[A split second late in his reaction,
and he would've been discovered!]
[Now what...]
[The crowd has gathered
back up in the game zone.]
Gary's good.
He's very calm and serious about it.
The lighting is in my eye.
- I'm going to have to try it from here.
- He has a hard time with this level.
It's kind of hard because you keep
grabbing onto the tablecloth.
- I got up to the second level earlier.
- You're on the third level now, right?
Which level did you get up to, Hyun Joo?
- I almost got all the way though.
- Wow, he's almost all the way through.
He's at the final catch round.
[Why is he trying so hard to do well?]
He's going to ruin it at this last moment.
[Gary passes through the fourth level.]
[What is he doing?]
You have to get at least three pieces.
[Must get a minimum of three pieces
in this fifth level.]
[Huh? Gary passes the first
gonggi mission in first place!]
[What are you thinking passing the mission
even before Kwang Soo passes it?]
[Oops...]
[That idiot...]
Gary... good job.
[Anyway, Gary passes in first place,
and therefore wins himself a gold medal.]
If two more people succeed
it's the end of this round,
and we'll move on to the next round.
[If two more people succeed,
the whole mission is over!]
Gary succeeded?
What is Gary thinking winning
the round like that?
[It's now gonggi master, Hyun Joo's turn.]
- No, I was told that it's okay.
- You can't do that?
- Don't talk to me.
- I don't think you're allowed to do that.
[If he keeps going at this rate,
he's going to succeed too.]
He's really good at this.
Do you have a lot of sisters
or something?
[Jae Suk 'kidnaps'
Hyun Joo's gonggi piece from midair?]
What is this?
Unless you go catch Jae Suk,
there's no way for you to win.
[He must get the gonggi piece that
Jae Suk stole, back in his hand.]
For example, if Ji Hyo was to take
this piece and run off with it?
No, you can't do that!
[Running Man members becoming
bold in their attempts at interference.]
Pass it to me, Ji Hyo!
[Kwang Soo seizes this moment to
approach the game zone.]
[Gary takes a piece of Jung Hee's gonggi,
and runs away!]
[Huh?
Wow... such a close call!]
Jae Suk.
I've always liked you, Jae Suk.
What were you thinking, beating
the game like that?
- What did you say?
- How could you succeed like that?
- I just got on a roll and forgot about it.
- Who cares if you were on a roll?
I just got swept up in the game
and totally forgot about it.
- How nice it must be to have your gold medal.
- No, it's not like that.
Wow, look at her.
[They must get Mi Sun
far away from the game zone.]
Are you sure you have all five pieces?
Let me see.
[Jae Suk steals one of Mi Sun's
gonggi pieces and makes a run for it!]
What do I do?
I'm not wearing running shoes!
[Now it's Mr. Capable who steals Hyun Joo's
gonggi pieces and makes off with them!]
- You have to hurry and get them back.
- You should hurry.
[That's what you call desperation.]
[A signal to let Kwang Soo know
that the game zone is empty!]
[Kwang Soo infiltrates the
game zone again!]
[Going under the table?]
[Level one complete.]
Please do it right!
Come on, and hurry!
[Level two complete.]
He doesn't even make a single mistake!
Look at him.
[All the guys are busying themselves
trying to distract Hyun Joo.]
- You have to get at least three.
- It's has to be at least three.
[Mi Sun and Jung Hee are almost
at the game zone!]
[Level three complete!]
Slow down.
[Level four complete.]
[Gets exactly three pieces
on top of his hand!]
It's totally over if you don't
catch them.
[Wow! Kwang Soo secretly passes
the first round of gonggi game!]
He did it.
He got it done, Jong Kook.
[But he must not get caught
for being under the table!]
[He'd better not even breathe...]
- You're really good.
- Fighting.
- Level two.
- You're really good at this.
I think level two is the hardest.
[Secretly sneaking a bottle of water in
to Kwang Soo for his job well done.]
He caught it, he caught it.
He's here.
Hyun Joo is here.
Why are you knocking me
out of the way?
Why are you trying to interfere
with my game?
But he may be able to succeed this time.
[I can't let them catch me under here!]
- That's good.
- He's good at it.
[Suk Jin flying through the levels
now that he can play in comfort.]
[Running Man's Suk Jin easily passes
the round in second place!]
[Suk Jin did it!]
- Why did you try to interfere?
- You already got through it anyway.
[Suk Jin wins himself a gold medal for
coming in at second place in the first round.]
- But, Hyun Joo, didn't you do it earlier?
- You got it done earlier.
[Gonggi master Hyun Joo's serious turn.]
He's a master at this.
- I bet he did this a lot when he was little.
- I can't believe how good you are at this.
[Passing through all four levels
in one try!]
You have to catch them all
if you want to pass.
You have to catch them all.
No one touch him right now.
Let's see if he can do it.
[Guest Hyun Joo completes the round
by coming in at third place.]
- He's really good.
- He's very competitive.
[Completing it so easily without any
interference from other members.]
[Hyun Joo also wins himself a gold medal
for coming in at third place.]
Is this real gold?
Just this little portion?
This part?
Seriously?
[Running Man protecting the table that
Kwang Soo is hiding under to the end.]
Okay, the first mission,
gonggi game is now over.
As I told you earlier, we will now head up
to the second level for your next mission.
- Yes.
- You may now all go up to the next game zone.
- Let's go.
- I need to win myself a medal too.
I'm usually pretty good at this game,
but I don't know what happened this time.
Okay, let's go.
I'm going to play a practice round
to see how I do.
[These two remaining behind to protect
the table until everyone else is gone.]
- Hyun Joo.
- I want to try playing a round before I go.
No, I just came back to get you.
Let's go up to the second floor.
- Jong Kook.
- Yeah?
[Are they gone?]
Should I go now?
Is it okay for me to come out now?
They're all gone.
[The poor thing... having to dress
like that in this hot weather.]
[Plan is to disguise himself as a
VJ with the camera in hand.]
[The missions are just going to keep
getting harder and harder.]
[Will his plan of keeping himself
disguised keep working?]
Okay, the next game is, the jaeggi game.
[Round three- The jaeggi game.]
- Jaeggi game?
- I'm good at this game.
Men and women alike have to
kick it five times.
- Okay.
- Five times?
- We just need to kick it five times?
- Five times.
- Then we have to go find them?
- You must go find them now. Go!
- Okay!
- Isn't this one?
[On their way to find the hidden jaeggis
that are hidden throughout the third floor!]
You startled me.
What is it?
Oh, here's one!
[Ha Ha already discovers one?]
Sorry, I was lying.
[Ha Ha's little tricks.]
I think you've been tricking me nonstop
for the past two hours now.
[Huh? Did he really find one this time?]
I'm sorry, Hyun Joo.
[Seriously...]
Why are you so easily tricked?
I want you to go away.
[Succeeds in buying some time.]
[Gary is the first to discover a jaeggi!]
I found one.
Go give it to Kwang Soo.
How am I the star of this episode right now?
[Kwang Soo hears the calling sign
for him to come down to the game zone.]
[The game zone is still empty!]
[Kwang Soo can pass this round if he can
kick it at least five times.]
- What are you doing?
- Hurry up and don't make any mistakes.
Hurry!
[Is it really that hard?]
- You have to worry.
- There's someone there.
- No there isn't. It's just Suk Jin.
- Is that Hyun Joo?
Come on, please!
Get it right!
Set, go.
One, two, three.
[Three this time.]
Come on!
You have to calm down.
[Ouch...]
One, two, three, four... one more!
[Four!
He just needs one more!]
[Misses the kick.]
[Ah... to lose such a good and
easy opportunity as this one...]
[On the other hand,
right around the same time...]
[Guest Hyun Joo discovers a jaeggi.]
[Now off to the game zone to
try his turn at jaeggi kicking!]
Calm down and do it.
[This isn't the right time to
be doing this.]
- One, two, three...
- He's headed this way.
- Can I rest for a bit?
- What do you mean, rest?
You have to try to finish this
while we've got the chance.
- I'm about to lose my mind.
- Hey, hey, hey!
You have to run and hide!
[Danger!
Someone is headed their way!]
[Hyun Joo is heading in their direction
with the jaeggi that he's found!]
[That could've been big trouble.]
- Are you finished?
- No, I'm still trying.
Okay.
One, two, three, four...
Why did you push me, Dong Hoon?
[As soon as Hyun Joo got up to four,
Gary automatically interrupts the game.]
- You can't use both feet.
- No, you can't use both your feet.
- You can only use one foot.
- Okay.
- You're not allowed to use both feet.
How about I use both my feet,
but I'll do ten kicks?
- Ten kicks with both feet?
- Ten kicks.
Is there anything that you can't do?
Okay, Hyun Joo is going to kick ten
by using both his feet.
- Ten?
- Go.
- We'll keep it simple.
- He's going to kick ten using both his feet.
[Everyone agrees to having Hyun Joon
kick ten with the use of both his feet.]
[Got up to eight!]
Your turn.
You need to be more cautious.
You almost hit yourself.
If it wasn't for me,
you would've hit yourself in the nose.
- You could've really hurt yourself.
- You have to try it again.
You almost bruised yourself in the nose.
[So many different ways of interfering.]
- It's Gary's turn.
- Okay, Gary.
- You almost hit me with that thing.
- You almost really did.
- It could've been dangerous.
- That was dangerous.
Do I just drop it like this?
- Oh my.
- See? I can't do it.
- If you've never done it.
- I've never done it, so I don't know how.
[Huh? He's right in front of them?]
- How am I going to do this?
- You can't do this?
[What do we do?]
- In that case... let's all take a break.
- Why don't we take a moment first?
[Proposing that everyone walk around once
and come back and do it in order of arrival.]
Okay, how about we do it in
the order of arrival?
[Why do we have to
do that all of a sudden?]
[The plan is to give Kwang Soo a chance
to try his turn while they walk around.]
Since running is too tiring,
how about speed walking?
Running would count as cheating.
- We have to walk like this.
- Speed walking?
Ready, set, go.
Okay, men have to walk on their heels.
[The guests giving it their all
without even knowing the reason for it.]
[Running Man members are moving
at a much slower pace.]
[Now is his chance!]
Just do it now!
[He only needs to kick it five times...]
- Make sure that no one comes.
- No one's coming, so hurry up!
- One, two, three, four..
- You have to concentrate.
[On the other hand, Jung Hee's
proving herself to be quite fast!]
This is quite a distance.
Why is it so far?
My legs are going to give out on me.
My legs are already so exhausted.
What's wrong with you?
Hey, Kwang Soo.
You're the star of this episode.
I'll throw it to you.
One, two, three.
Hurry!
[Just then, Suk Jin yells out to
signal danger heading their way.]
Come on, you can't run!
- I'm not running.
- Yes, you're running!
- No, this is running.
- Yes, you're running right now.
- Were you running?
- No, I wasn't running.
No, I wasn't running.
I was just speed walking.
No, all three of us are done.
- Really?
- Yes, all three places have been taken now.
[Huh? Did Jae Suk just succeed?]
I succeeded.
I just got my five.
[What's he doing?]
Really?
[Jae Suk wins the gold medal for coming in
at first place in the jaeggi game.]
[Sending the guests off again.]
[It's another chance for Kwang Soo!]
- Come on, hurry!
- What are you doing?
[If he doesn't succeed this time,
he may lose his chance to succeed at all!]
Hurry up and just go.
[Sending everyone else away
so that they don't draw any suspicion.]
What is it that you're doing?
[Can't seem to get past three.]
Just go.
Seriously... hurry up and do it.
[Oh? He may get it done this time?]
[He just needs one more!]
[Kwang Soo succeeds round three game
of jaeggi in secret!]
[No time to celebrate.
Back to disguising himself as the VJ!]
Okay, we did it.
[If Kwang Soo can pass the next game,
only the RM members will gain the clue!]
[Mr. Capable's turn!]
[So easy! Succeeds in
getting five kicks in right away!]
What the heck?
[Kim Jong Kook comes in at second place and
wins himself a gold medal in Round Three.]
- Let's go.
- Okay, let's go.
[Round three of the jaeggi game
is now over.]
[Jaeggi King Gary no longer pretending
to be bad at the game.]
[It looks like he can keep it up all day.]
[Kwang Soo has to secretly go on to
the next location for his final mission.]
This is too nerve-wrecking.
Don't they even find it suspicious to see
someone walking around dressed this way?
They don't find it strange when it's
so obvious that I'm wearing a disguise?
I'm walking around dripping sweat, covered up
in a coat and a hat, but they don't notice?
[It's a relief that they don't suspect the VJ
who's walking around dripping sweat.]
I don't think I can do this anymore.
This is too hard.
You told me that I was going to be
the star of this episode.
This is your fourth and final game
for the gold medal.
As you can see,
this is the limbo game.
Even though it's a limbo game, there's
something that you still have to find.
- What do we have to find now?
- This isn't your average limbo game.
There are various animal masks
that are hidden throughout this floor.
You can only make an attempt at the
limbo bar when you have the mask on.
- Wow...
- But those masks are huge!
It'll be big trouble if we find
the giraffe mask.
[Big trouble if the mask that they find
ends up being the giraffe mask.]
[Kwang Soo also must have the mask on
before he attempts the limbo challenge.]
But I can't use that as part of my disguise.
Unless you're a complete idiot,
what VJ films with a mask on?
How am I going to get this done?
I'm going to have to complete this quickly.
I need to do it before
the others find their masks.
[Making his way over to find
an animal mask.]
[Kwang Soo discovers the giraffe mask!]
How am I supposed to pass under
the limbo bar with this thing on?
[Of all the masks out there to find,
that's the one you find?]
How am I supposed to do the limbo
with this thing on?
[He's tall enough as is to begin with,
but limbo with the mask?]
If the limbo bar is tall as this one...
[Making his attempt with the clothes rack.]
This shouldn't be bad.
[Oh!]
I should be able to get it done
if it's this height.
[As expected, the giraffe mask is
making it practically impossible!]
[This isn't going to work!]
[I'm going to have to
think of another solution.]
[Hyun Joo on the search for a mask
in another store.]
Isn't this one of them?
This is a mask too.
Isn't this a mask?
It is!
I found one right away.
Look, I found one right away.
[Hyun Joo is first to arrive.]
[He just needs to pass under
the limbo bar with his mask on!]
[His first time wearing an animal mask...]
You have to do a good job, okay?
[Hanging the strap on his nose?]
What is he doing?
[Unable to make it through and crashes.]
[Mi Sun making her attempt with
a rat mask on her head.]
[Oh? It looks as though she may
pull it off!]
You're going to make it!
[No!]
You got it!
[I'm sorry, Mi Sun.]
- Aren't you pretty athletic?
- I don't think that's going to matter at all.
[Moon Jung Hee, known for her dance skills
is taking her turn with the dog mask on.]
- Oh my...
- See? Look at her.
[Fails from Jae Suk's quiet interference.]
Wow... you're very flexible.
[Kwang Soo making his way to the game zone
with the mask on his head.]
He looks like his mask.
[Jae Suk takes his turn with
a rabbit mask on.]
This is the way you approach the bar.
You have to spread your legs apart a bit.
[Hm... backs up again.]
[If he thinks that he won't make it,
he backs up a few steps again.]
[Finally making his appearance is...
Horse Beckham Ji.]
He looks a little like Beckham.
[It looks rather good on you.]
[Hyun Joo takes his turn after having
picked up Jae Suk's method.]
There you go.
You're doing pretty well with that.
[Also learned the trick of backing up
when things aren't looking very good.]
You learned that skill fast.
[And if it seems that he still can't do it...
time to back it up.]
Nice.
That's nice Hyun Joo.
[Lowering his stance to give it
another try.]
[Leaning to the side a little bit
and reproaching the bar.]
- Okay, this is hard.
- Who's next?
[The fact that he can hide himself behind a
piece of cardboard is fascinating in itself.]
Ji Hyo!
What do I do?
Where did you find that giraffe mask?
You can't wear that.
[Scolding him as soon as
she sees the giraffe mask.]
This one doesn't even have a chin.
- But if I'm not going to win anyways.
- Hurry up and take it off.
I'm going to do this one.
I'm the Giraffe!
We have to succeed this mission
in any way that we can!
Hurry up and put that on.
- I don't like the impala mask.
- Just hurry up and put it on!
I'll just get really close to the zone,
and get in there and do it.
[Suggesting that he barges in to just do it
before they realize that it's Kwang Soo?]
Then I'll pretend to be one of the VJ's
and go near the zone.
Yeah, I think that would be better.
[Hyun Joo is still in the midst
of making his attempt.]
That's like his basic move now.
That's the best.
That's the best position to take for this.
He's really good at everything.
[Gary's sly interference.]
[Flexible Jung Hee's turn.]
- You got it.
- You're there, and you got it.
- You got it!
- You did it!
[Oh? Success!]
- The gold medal that you wanted so badly.
- Thank you.
Look at Hyun Joo practicing by himself
in the corner over there.
Why does this look so low?
I don't know if I can do this.
My legs are exhausted.
I would think that you'd be good at it.
[Mi Sun easily succeeds the mission!]
[Now... only one more...]
[Mi Sun wins the gold medal for coming in
at second place in the last game.]
[No more time!
Must hurry before someone else succeeds!]
[Hyun Joo makes another attempt
with fierce determination.]
But your position...
Don't stick out
your lower body too much.
Bend your head back.
Hyun Joo, you have to bend your head back.
Bend it back as much as you can.
[Like this?]
That's right.
Now tilt your head to the side a bit.
- This really isn't as easy as it looks.
- Did you see the way he was shaking?
- Why don't you try it?
- I'll pull it up 5cm.
[Everyone agreeing to lift up the
bar by 5cm.]
- Then I'd be able to do that.
- That's not going to be very hard.
[If Hyun Joo succeeds this attempt,
then Kwang Soo's hide-and-seek is over.]
Tilt your head to the side.
[Will he be able to do it this time?]
[Kwang Soo finally makes his way
near the game zone.]
If you're not playing anymore,
can you step off to the side?
[Silently staying hidden.]
[What do we do now?]
Can my VJ do it for me instead?
- My VJ is the best at this.
- Yeah, he really is good at this.
Can we get someone else to do it?
Hey, come over here.
[Running Man members trying to get Kwang Soo
who's disguised as a VJ to give it a try.]
Why don't you try it?
Let's have him give it a try.
You know that tall VJ?
Why don't we try to get him to do it?
- Soo Chul is really flexible.
- No, I want Ki Jin to try it first.
[Soo Chul?]
[VJ Kwang Soo Chul...]
[VJ Ki Jin to go first as their guinea pig.]
Is that your own VJ?
[Now that everyone is into the game...
calling VJ Soo Chul to the front line!]
[Attempting to hide the face of VJ Soo Chul
by putting on a mask over his face.]
- Come here, let him try.
- Why don't we have Soo Chul try it?
[Curious...]
I heard that he used to be really good at
sports while he was still in school.
[He hasn't been caught yet.]
- Give it another try.
- Try it again.
Didn't you tell us that you used to
play quite a few sports in school?
[Turning his face away from others
so that his face can't be recognized.]
Hey! I thought that
you said you played sports.
[The guests still unaware of
VJ Soo Chul's real identity.]
[As Jung Hee makes her way over
so that she can see his face...]
[Jae Suk attempts to keep
Kwang Soo's face hidden.]
- Hang on, wait a minute.
- Give it another try.
Here, you really have to get down.
Why don't you try this?
[Attempting to hide his bashful face
so that people can't know who he is.]
Soo Chul, why don't you give it a try?
[My knees!]
[This guy is funny.]
[VJ Soo Chul unable to even lift up
his head out of embarrassment.]
- Come on.
- Let's hurry up and do it.
[Fails for going under the bar
during a fall.]
[Do you think that man is okay?]
[He could be caught if he tries to
drag this out any further!]
Why don't you just show us how it's done?
Come on!
[Nice and easy... sliding.]
[Because he fell down,
it's another fail!]
Let's count that as a success!
That should count as a success.
- This should count as a success!
- Soo Chul! Soo Chul!
[Even the guests are joining in
on the cheer.]
Soo Chul!
[Don't do that!]
I told you not to do things like that.
[VJ Soo Chul trying to take his
jacket off from being too hot.]
Soo Chul, no.
Don't take that off.
Get your head on straight.
No, you can't take that off.
Soo Chul!
Look at all that sweat.
Come on, Soo Chul.
We got the point.
Ready.
Soo Chul... go!
Put your leg towards the middle.
- How about you take your shoes off?
- There you go!
[Taking off his shoes!]
- There you go, Soo Chul! You got it!
- Soo Chul! Soo Chul!
[Lowering his stance!]
[Just a little bit more!]
[He did it!]
[VJ Soo Chul does it!]
- He did it with his shoes off.
- Taking his shoes off helped.
He did it, right?
He's Ki Jin's rival.
[Back to his position as a VJ
with a gold medal around his neck.]
- You have to take the camera back.
- Take the camera.
- Soo Chul.
- Hurry up and get going.
[Depleted of all energy.]
- You have to get back to filming us.
- Get back to your position.
- Say thank you.
- Say your thanks and get out.
- Thank everyone.
Hey, Kwang Soo!
[Finally realizes that it's Kwang Soo!]
- You really didn't know?
- So you really didn't know?
You didn't recognize him as he was out
here the whole time as Soo Chul?
- This is Soo Chul!
- We've just been calling him Soo Chul.
Actually, the true mission
for the day...
was Kwang Soo's Hide-and-Seek.
- It was Kwang Soo's Hide-and-Seek.
- Seriously?
Remember when we were
playing gonggi earlier?
- He was under the table the whole time.
- Oh my goodness.
[All the pieces of the puzzle
are finally starting to fall into place.]
Kwang Soo had to do everything that we did
without any of you finding out about it.
Kwang Soo had to do all the missions that
we did without the three of you finding out.
So that's why we've been working all day
to interfere in your attempts.
[Everyone did seem to be acting
a little strange...]
We were thinking that you were
acting very strange.
[Cannot get rid of the rage bubbling
inside of him over being deceived.]
- You didn't know?
- You really didn't know?
If you said, 'Kwang Soo', 'Hey, Kwang Soo',
or 'What are you doing, Kwang Soo?'...
If you had said anything that indicated
that you recognized him
then it would've been the
guests' victory.
However, since that didn't happen
Running Man members succeeded in helping
Kwang Soo succeed all his missions in secret.
You participated under the condition that
you'll gain the hint if you succeeded.
Thus, all the members along with Kwang Soo
succeeded this mission.
Today's race is,
Numbered Hide-and-Seek.
This will be an individual race to the end.
And the winners of each mission will be given
hints about the numbers on the backs.
[Numbered Hide-and-Seek]
As I mentioned to you earlier,
you'll now be given your hint.
As I said, this isn't a team effort today.
But this is going to be an
individual race.
So all of the hints will be different
from each other.
So it may be to your disadvantage
to share your hints.
Okay, each of the Running Man members
can each take a hint.
[Everyone receiving hint with
the exception of the three guests.]
Even though I feel bad for Hyun Joo,
Min Sun, and Jung Hee...
Okay, you may now change into your uniforms
and we'll move on to the next location.
[And thus... Kwang Soo's Hide-and-Seek
comes to a grand close.]
[Off to the next mission location!]
I was told what to do.
If Kim Jong Kook mentions tiger,
then I was to mention a rabbit.
Wow, that's pretty nice.
[Her kids requested for her to do
the infamous 'cross' chant.]
- Then do it.
- Tiger!
- Rabbit!
- Cross!
That's pretty good.
If you don't mind, I'm going to take
a quick peek at my hint.
Okay, but I'd like to...
[Numbers 8, 9, 10 are Running Man members,
and each of them has one offspring.]
Wow.
You know this is a little...
[Numbers 1 and 9 use a stage name.]
- But this is still...
- This is unbelievable.
- Really?
- This is a very conclusive hint.
- Don't you think?
- This really is conclusive.
What do you think our hints are?
- Since this is an individual race...
- I can't look at it, right?
[Since it's an individual race,
to share the information is a bit...]
- I wonder what mine says?
- Does it relate to anything?
Just tell me what it relates to.
[Numbers 1, 2, and 9 are singers,
and numbers 8, and 10 are comedians.]
- Do you think you get it?
- I see what this is.
[Numbers 1 and 3 have something
to do with Mondays.]
There's numbers in my hint too.
There are some numbers.
So you have to figure it out from
those hints, and deduce a guess
and the person to figure out who those
numbers belong to is the ultimate winner?
I'm not quite sure about how it'll
all end, but I think the numbers...
It sounds like you're trying to
get us to tell you something.
Like what our hints are.
We haven't seen our hints yet,
so we don't know what they are either.
Should we take a quick peek?
[Numbers 1 and 2 are unmarried.]
My hint is amazing.
[Numbers 4 and 5 are in a drama that is
currently airing on Mondays and Tuesdays.]
I know that it can't be easy for you to come
on our show while currently in a drama.
- No, I've always wanted to come on this show.
- Really?
My son really loves the show.
What's his name?
- Son Hyung Suk.
- Hyung Suk?
Hyung Suk, at the rate things are going,
I don't know if your father will win.
I don't know what'll happen in the second half
but I want you to keep watching, okay?
- You have to cheer him on.
- Yes, you have to cheer your dad on.
- Will this get on air?
- Of course, it will.
Hyung Suk.
Dad will do his best on Running Man
and come home, okay?
My pretty daughter, keep watching, okay?
Your father doesn't have a very good chance
of winning at the moment.
But you still have to support your dad, okay?
- You have to keep cheering him on.
- I want you to keep watching too, honey.
I won a gold medal earlier.
[Incheon Park]
It's the acupuncture mat again.
- We used to play this when we were little.
- I see what it is.
[Wait, this is?]
[A hop scotch game made entirely
out of the acupuncture mat.]
I'm really good at this.
- Wait, I think I know this.
- Isn't this a game of pool?
[No! It's the traditional kid's game
of hop scotch.]
- This is hop scotch.
- What are you talking about, Kwang Soo?
- I think I know this game.
- This looks more painful than usual.
- This one is even more pointy.
- Don't you think this is too much?
[Upgraded acupuncture mat!]
[Pick a number to throw a stone on and
all the members must get through to win.]
- What's the time limit?
- It's 30 seconds.
If there are four people in your team,
then only three of them can participate.
Yes, I understand.
Can we wear socks or no?
No, take off your socks.
Anyone participating has to take them off.
- Fine, take off the socks.
- Yes, take off the socks.
- Let's see who can handle this.
- Take off the socks.
Let's all take them off and see how we do.
- Wow, they're serious.
- Fine, let's just see who handles it better.
[Merciless first experience with
a variety show.]
- We're not ruthless, Hyun Joo.
- No, we're not like that.
Wow, this is...
This really is something else.
[The power of the acupuncture mat.]
This is a whole different level of pain.
If I were to describe how it feels,
it feels like your feet will be bruised.
Let us just feel it on our own.
- What did you say?
I'm just trying to let them know
what this is going to feel like.
I'm going to feel it myself soon enough,
so why are you telling me?
- I'm just trying to help them out.
- Seriously.
Why are you so argumentative?
Why are you only yelling at me?
- Hyun Joo is on our team.
- You're on the same team?
- He's a little weird too.
- How is he weird?
Since our team was the first to arrive,
can we go first?
- Okay, go ahead.
- Hyun Joo, pick one.
[Blue Team to start them off.]
- Jumping on this is going to hurt.
- Number six would be best.
Number one!
[Number one.]
[Son Hyun Joo, Jae Suk and Ji Hyo
to participate first from the Blue Team.]
This is the part that we should step on.
I'm sorry, but can you
take your foot off the mat?
- What did you say?
- Can you take your foot off the mat?
What are you talking about?
He's the head of this clan.
[Will it be possible for all three people to
make it through within 30 seconds?]
Okay, why don't you go first?
[Blue Team's first participant-
Charismatic Son Hyun Joo.]
[Son Hyun Joo, the god of acting.]
[This terrifying acupuncture mat...]
[Screaming bloody murder.]
- What are you doing?
- What are you doing, Hyun Joo?
[His charisma crumbles to pieces
on top of the acupuncture mat.]
[This is embarrassing.]
- What are you doing?
- This isn't that hard.
That's not how you do it!
- You have to jump on both feet.
- Okay, he made it through.
[Hyun Joo unknowingly entertaining
others with his physical gags.]
- At the rate that she's going...
- You have to jump on both feet.
Have you never played this before?
- Hey! You give it a try!
- You can't step on the lines.
- On both feet!
- It's okay, Ji Hyo.
Seriously...
what's so difficult about this?
What's so difficult about this thing?
[Why can't you do it better?]
What is he doing?
Wow! That is no joke!
I feel like my feet are on fire!
Ugh, it's so hot!
Why is it so hot on this thing!
[Once he's gotten through the acupuncture mat,
he steps on the blue sun-baked mat.]
- Hurry up and get back!
- This is so hot!
[The power of the acupuncture mat
making them scream out in agony.]
That really hurts.
I don't know how we can do that.
[Blue Team- Fail.]
[Red Team's turn.]
- Wow, that's really painful.
- This looks like a liver.
It looks like a liver.
- Why don't you pick it? Pick a good one.
- I don't know if I should be picking it.
- I'm not good at things like this.
- You should've chosen with more care.
- Number four.
Whatever it is that you're imagining,
it's so much more than that.
[She did a good job throwing the liver!]
[Acupuncture mat is the worst
nightmare come to life for your senses.]
[Starting over in a calmer manner.]
[She's doing great.]
You're doing great.
- You won't be able to pick it up.
- You have to pick it up from space five.
You have to do it on one foot.
[Determined Mi Sun.]
- She's like Moon Geun Young in her 40's.
- She's really good.
[Complete!]
- You did really well.
- My feet are killing me.
- This mat...
- Doesn't it hurt?
[First time playing this game in 30 years.]
- You have to run around now.
- Jump on both feet.
You have to jump on one foot now.
One foot. You have to do it on one foot.
You can't walk like that.
Back up and start off again
with your right foot.
- Like this?
- That's right.
[A rush of blood flowing to his feet.]
- This really hurts.
- Let's do this right.
- How are we going to do this?
- This time, it's Gary, Ji Hyo and Hyun Joo.
- That looks really painful.
- Pick a number, Hyun Joo.
I'll pick one for you.
I hope it's number six.
Number four.
- Ji Hyo can go first.
- Fighting.
[Ji Hyo to go first.]
[Where are you going?]
[Emergency treatment of his feet.]
Is it number four?
- There you go.
- Go!
[Must get to these three spots
only on one foot.]
- What's IC?
- Were you just swearing, Ji Hyo?
[Reverting to her brutish Ji Hyo ways with
the wave of pain from the mat.]
- Don't get angry.
- I'm sorry.
- I told you that Ji Hyo used to play around.
- It's too late for an apology now.
[Passing it off to Hyun Joo for his turn.]
[Going without any hesitation.]
[Moving around naturally as if
he's playing the game on a flat surface.]
Doesn't it hurt?
[Amazing]
- Here, Gary.
- It's your turn.
[Ah... this is Gary's first try...]
This feels really different
than the last time!
[Blue Team- Fail]
That's impossible.
That really hurts.
Son Hyun Joo completed it
in nine seconds.
- In nine seconds?
- That's not an easy feat.
Hyung Suk, I think your father is
quite determined to win today.
You need to cheer him on, Hyung Suk.
[Hyung Suk... your father is doing great.]
- Number five.
- Number five?
- It's not bad, right?
- It's not that good.
- Numbers one through three are best.
- Number five isn't a good pick.
- You have to go all the way through?
- That's not a good number.
Do you know how much
Actress Moon likes to dance?
Time to dance!
- She really loves to dance.
- I told you please not to do that!
She really likes to dance.
[Actress Moon's love for dance that knows
no boundaries in time and the locale.]
She loves to dance, but can't sing.
But she'll dance anywhere.
- Time to dance!
- Look at this!
[Dancing machine]
- Actress Moon is a good dancer.
- Yes, she is.
Okay, Suk Jin.
You can do it, Suk Jin!
- You have to do it faster!
- Move it!
- Mister, what are you doing?
- What are you doing there, Mister?
Are you drunk or something?
- You were stumbling out there.
- Is it my turn?
[Passing it off to
Dancing Machine, Jung Hee.]
You got it!
You have to keep doing it on one foot.
[It seems as though she's doing
much better than the Easy Brothers.]
Can I do it like this?
Is this not right?
- That's not right.
- You can't do that.
- Just tell us if you want to give up.
- Just do it however you want to do it.
- No, you did fine. Do better next time.
- What were you doing out there?
You just do it however you
want to do it.
[Yellow Team- Fail.]
I was doing it with my teeth gritted,
but I still can't seem to do it.
This is impossible to do
even with your socks on.
[Red Team picks number one.]
[Chooses number one which is
one of the easier spaces to pick.]
[Ha Ha in the midst of trying to
get himself mentally ready.]
- I know that I can do this.
- Okay, I got it.
I can guarantee that you'll get a beating.
[Psyching himself up?]
[Screaming out loud to motivate himself?]
[Able to conquer the acupuncture mat pain
by screaming out his own encouragement?]
You just stepped on the line.
Darn!
I'm dead now.
[Already predicting his future?]
Mister, you stepped on the line.
I'm sorry!
[Agonizing apology on top of
the acupuncture mat.]
I'm sorry.
- Just come back here.
- What I did was wrong.
I'll do better next time.
All of the aces from our team are
going to do it this time.
[Only the ace players will participate
from the Blue Team this time?]
I'm going to stay out of it.
- Then you're the one of the aces?
- No, I'm staying out of it.
- Number four.
- It really does hurt, doesn't it?
It really hurts.
Okay, number four.
- Hopping on one foot is the hardest part.
- Okay, you got it.
Hyun Joo, are you okay?
How did you jump on the mat like that?
There's no need for you
to do all that.
- You can take it easier.
- Why are you doing that to yourself?
[Even though he's psyched himself up,
the agony is starting to overtake him.]
Why did you start off like that?
- You have to get back!
- You didn't have to start out so hard.
[Falling down onto his knees.]
Why did you start off so hard?
[Son Hyun Joo gives it another try.]
[Falling back down onto his knees.]
[Overly eager in his attempt.]
Let him have one more try.
He started off too hard.
That would've hurt even on a flat surface
without being on this acupuncture mat.
Hyung Suk, I don't think he's going to
be able to come in at first place.
[Hyung Suk...
your father still tried very hard.]
That really hurts.
We have decided to give you extra time
and make 50 seconds the new time limit.
- Number two!
- Okay.
[Red Team chooses number two.]
You can do it as long as Ha Ha can do it.
Okay, let's do this.
Number two, right?
- Number two, right?
- He's so annoying.
- I just wanted to make sure.
- We can do it this time.
[Screaming out the battle cry again
to help forget about the agony.]
[Completes the course within seconds
as if running a 100m dash.]
- I think they may do it this time.
- One, two...
[Mi Sun doing surprisingly well at this game.]
[It's the problematic Ha Ha's turn.]
[Screaming out the same battle cry
that his teacher has taught him.]
Hurry!
My feet hurts!
[Will they succeed this time?]
[Huh?]
[Landing on both feet?]
[Is this your first time playing this game?]
What!
[Turning right around to do it again.]
He can't do that.
- On one foot!
- You have to do it on one foot!
You have to do it on one foot from there!
Hop on your right foot!
- Just on your right foot!
- On one foot!
[He lands on both feet again!]
- I did it. Come on!
- I told you to hop on your right foot!
- Come on, I did it!
- It's okay. Do it again!
Come on, just do it again!
[Heads back out again.]
I don't think I can do this.
You guys can't do it because of him.
You won't be able to pass this.
[Red Team unfortunately fails.]
You could've passed this course if
you had been on one foot.
[One person who still can't seem to
comprehend the rules of the game.]
Don't you even know how to play this?
You have to do it on one foot.
You were still within your time even
with Ha Ha's second attempt.
Can't you just let us pass then?
Hey, you practically made it through.
You just needed to hop on one foot.
[Time for reflection with Coach Kkuk.]
[Explosion of his nonstop nagging.]
Just because you're screaming out your
battle cry doesn't mean you're finished.
It's not just about screaming,
but you have to think as you go.
[Not muttering a sound,
and only responding when spoken to.]
Aren't you even sick of being scolded?
Just get it done for once.
Okay, I'll do it.
[Blue Team makes another attempt.]
Fighting.
He's going to do it.
He's really good at this.
[A real man on the acupuncture mat,
Son Hyun Joo.]
[Flying through the mat again without
any sense of hesitation.]
[The god of acting's
determined one footed hop.]
[Just like Park Ji Sung's feet that've seen
glory on Europe's infamous field.]
[Just like Ballerina Kang Su Jin's feet
that touched the hearts of the whole world.]
[Son Hyun Joo's feet that brought tears
and shock to everyone on the acupuncture mat.]
[Son, are you watching this?
A show of your father's determination?]
[Hyung Suk... are you watching this?]
[After his explosive run through the course,
he's trying to pull himself back together.]
He's jumped through all these spaces
hopping on only one foot.
[Gary seems to have acclimated himself
to the feel of the mat somewhat as well.]
- You're doing great.
- I'm determined.
You got it.
[Now as long as Jae Suk can get through it!]
[Huh?]
[Jae Suk lands on space seven
on both feet.]
Hurry up and come back!
[Must rush back to start over.]
Hurry!
[You Hyuk ultimately
brought down to his knees.]
- I don't think I can do this.
- Can you make it a minute? It really hurts.
Just one person from each team can wear
one sock on just one of their feet.
- The time will remain the same.
- Just one person?
50 seconds?
[Blue Team who started off first gets to
have a try under the new rule.]
But if we can succeed this time,
the game's over, right?
I think that the Blue Team
is going to do it then.
You're going to do it now without
wearing the one sock?
- Okay, then.
- Go ahead.
- We have to give it a try too.
- Why are you making that decision for us?
- You need to discuss it with us.
- You didn't even ask for our opinion.
Why are you insisting on doing this
when we've been told we can wear socks?
- He said we can wear socks.
- She said she can't do this anymore.
- Blue Team is going to succeed next time.
- Yeah, Jae Suk is their only problem.
We need to give ourselves a chance to win
before Blue Team gets to go again.
We'd be more inclined to follow you if
you had shown us something.
Just do it!
Just do it, okay?
[Letting his hand fly at the disagreement.]
- Look, I picked number two.
- You look like a leader.
- Suk Jin has leadership.
He's only like this when he's with me.
Okay, I'll go first.
[Yellow Team takes their turn
without the added bonus of a sock.]
[Actress Moon is the first to
start off the game.]
- I think they may do it this time.
- We are going to do this.
[Going through the whole course without
crying out one single time.]
[Actress Moon gets through the course.]
You have to make sure that you do this!
Don't forget to hop on one foot.
If you don't succeed this time,
you're dead. Okay, Suk Jin?
[Actress Moon's frightening words
of encouragement.]
You have to get through it.
- There you go! Bend down and grab it.
- Grab the stone now.
Okay.
Kwang Soo, fighting!
[It's already down
to the last player, Kwang Soo.]
Kwang Soo, fighting!
You can do this!
[Going through at top speed with the added
boost of Actress Moon's encouragement.]
[Pass]
- How many seconds?
- What's our time?
Success.
[Yellow Team succeeds!]
I'm sorry, Hyung Suk.
It's all my fault.
I'm sorry.
I had no other choice because
it just hurts too much.
I'm sorry, Hyung Suk.
Your dad did really great though.
You finally got yourself a hint.
Yellow Team just earned themselves
the highest level of clues.
[Yellow Teams gets the best clue
for having come in at first place.]
Once you see this hint,
you'll be able to guess a few.
[Top level clue just as it's labeled.]
- And also...
- What is he talking about?
You can figure that out by yourself later.
Don't you know what yours is?
So you didn't even know what you were
reading off that card earlier?
Next, Red Team will receive
a mid-grade level clue.
And Blue Team will receive the lowest
level of clues.
Yes, I understand.
[Next mission-
Public hide-and-seek.]
[One member at a time from each team must
infiltrate a crowd of people in public.]
[Must complete their mission and get out
without being recognized to succeed.]
[Hyun Joo's mission-
Eat a snack without getting recognized.]
You have to buy the fried chicken,
eat the snack at the stand
and get back out to pass.
[But Hyun Joo succeeds his mission!]
[Jae Suk and Ji Hyo's mission.]
[Make it through the market with the torn
umbrella without being recognized.]
[Disguising themselves as a couple?
Succeeds the mission.]
[Kwang Soo's mission-
The village idiot...]
[Actually, the real mission is to buy a
wineglass and get back before he's caught.]
Look at all those people following him
right now.
I just want to go home.
[Kwang Soo fails.]
- Do we get another hint?
- Look, we get another hint.
[Another hint is handed out.]
- This is another clue?
- Are they all this obvious?
[Everyone seems to have figured out
who has which number?]
[On their way to the final location.]
- Can't you tell me what yours says?
- What about you?
- Then me yours first.
- What does yours say?
- Let's all reveal it together.
- Okay, together. One, two, three.
See?
It's the same hint.
Such and such numbers are actors,
and such and such numbers are singers.
- Is yours something like that too?
- Ones I know for sure are Jae Suk's, yours...
[Will they be able to guess
their own numbers?]
[Numbered Hide-and-Seek Race-
Final location.]
[Aqua studio]
[Find the 'R' flag!]
What is this?
[Here's the flag!]
Okay!
[Yoo Hyuk is the first to arrive!]
This is an individual race.
Yoo Jae Suk is in first place,
and Lee Kwang Soo is in second place.
[Everyone to stand in line
in the order of their arrival.]
[Hyung Suk's dad trying to piece all the
clues together in midst of all this.]
- Ddak-ji king is Jae Suk, right?
- Jae Suk is one of them.
And Jong Kook too.
It's Jae Suk and Jong Kook both.
[Is he trying to be sly and cut in line?]
Okay, this is the final
individual mission time.
I hope that you've gotten an idea of who
has which number on their backs
by piecing together the clues that
you've all been given.
You will all be climbing atop that structure
and sitting on top of it.
[What?
On top of that structure?]
While seated on that structure,
you'll have to guess who has which number.
If you guess it correctly
the person who has the number that
you guessed will fall
and if you get it wrong, the person who
took the guess will fall.
So going first isn't necessarily
a good thing.
Wow, the water is so deep.
- What if I get it wrong?
- You have to get lucky with the number.
This is all about the luck of the draw.
Okay, everyone may now climb up there.
[Everyone is seated
in the order of their arrival.]
I'm so nervous!
- Okay... raise them up.
- What? We're being raised up?
- You're going to raise us up?
- Is this being raised? What is this?
- This is going to be raised up?
- You're raising us up?
We're not getting dumped from here?
- Stop!
- What do you guys think you're doing?
How far are you raising this up?
- Stop!
- This is enough! Stop it!
[Wow... this is high.]
[All the members are now seated
in the midair chairs.]
Yoo Jae Suk will start off with his guess
since he was the first one to have arrived.
I didn't know that arriving first
would mean having to do this.
Judge Go Dong Wan will draw a number.
Don't look when you pick the number.
[The number he's going to have
to guess is...]
[Number one.]
- Number one.
- Number one?
Yoo Jae Suk must shout out the name of the
person who he believes to be number one.
If he guesses correctly, then
that person will be dumped in the water.
But if he guesses wrong,
Yoo Jae Suk himself will be dumped.
[Guess right, then he survives.
Guess wrong, then he gets dumped.]
- Being up front isn't good.
- Being first isn't a good thing!
[Who's number one?]
Number five.
The king of all animals.
And Monday, Tuesday drama.
Number five is Kwang Soo, right?
I think number four is Hyun Joo.
If number five...
If number four is Hyun Joo, then
five would definitely be Kwang Soo.
Numbers two and ten are ddak-ji kings.
Then would mean it's either me
or Jong Kook.
[Numbers two and ten would be either
Jong Kook or Jae Suk.]
But...
[Then who is number one?]
I'm not quite sure who it is.
I'm just going to have to guess.
[In one word...
he's going to have to take a guess.]
[Numbers 3-7 are actors and 2 and 10
are Jong Kook or Jae Suk.]
[Then that means...]
[Number one has to be either
Ha Ha, Suk Jin, or Gary?]
I have to take a guess.
[Jae Suk having to guess between
the three.]
On the count of five,
you have to shout out the person's name.
Five, four, three...
[Which one of these is number one?]
I don't know who number one is!
Gary?
[Jae Suk guesses Gary to be
number one.]
Gary!
[Did he guess correctly?]
[Or is he wrong?]
[Wow! Number one is Gary!]
This is so scary!
- Gary.
- Stop!
Stop this!
- Gary.
- Stop!
[One person in need of a rescue.]
This is driving me crazy.
This is so annoying!
Why am I the first?
I knew this was going to happen!
Okay, Yoo Jae Suk guessed correctly
and Gary is number one.
[Number one was Gary.]
He's received an award in the past
for his dancing.
And numbers one and three has
something to do with Mondays.
Number one... is Kang Gary.
I'm...
number one.
[He himself knew what his own
number was.]
[That's why he looked so distressed
right before he took his dive.]
[And then took the plunge.]
This is really scary.
Gary's empty chair looks so scary.
- Look at this chair.
- So that's what happens.
That's too scary.
I don't remember any of the numbers
that I thought about.
Second person to have arrived,
Lee Kwang Soo.
We will not pick the number that
Lee Kwang Soo has to guess.
[It's Kwang Soo's turn to take a guess.]
You think you'll get it?
[And that number is...]
Number ten!
[And that number is... number ten.]
- Number ten.
[Panic]
- You have to shout out the person's name.
- You told me that I was the star today!
You will be given five seconds.
[Who could number ten be?]
When I looked at all the clues
back in the car...
I think that number ten...
Number ten wears glasses.
- Would that be Jae Suk?
- I've known him for the past ten years.
That much I'm sure of.
[Number ten has to be either
a singer or a comedian...]
I can see someone sitting very
stiffly in their chair.
Look at how stiff he looks up there.
The poor thing!
[Telling him to prepare himself?]
Five, four, three, two, one.
Number ten is Yoo Jae Suk!
[Number ten is Jae Suk?]
[Correct]
- That chair is so scary.
- Lee Kwang Soo!
I survived!
- Lee Kwang Soo, that was low!
- Everyone's ultimately alone in this life!
I'm so scared!
I'm so scared of getting dumped.
We will now choose the number that
Moon Jung Hee will have to guess.
Number eight.
- Number eight.
- I don't know!
[She doesn't look so sure...]
Number eight.
- I'll count to five.
- Kim Jong Kook!
[She chooses Jong Kook to be
number eight.]
- Jung Hee!
- Number eight is Kim Jong Kook?
[She picks Jong Kook as number eight.]
[Is number eight... really Jong Kook?]
[Number eight isn't Jong Kook!]
Wow, that's really scary.
I'm so scared!
All my friends are now gone!
- Where did all my friends go?
- They're all disappearing one by one!
Why did she pick me?
- It's not him?
- Are you okay?
[What's going on here?]
[Suk Jin with the hint about
someone else's line of career.]
Number eight is a singer too, right?
It's a singer, right?
[Playing ignorance.]
- Why are you acting so serious?
- Then Jong Kook is number eight?
[She guesses Jong Kook to be
number eight.]
[But Suk Jin's clue says...
'Numbers 8 and 10 are comedians.']
[Jung Hee totally fell for Suk Jin's trick.]
No, you can't take it off.
[Jung Hee can't reveal her own number
since no one has guessed it yet.]
Next is Ji Suk Jin's turn.
Please let it be a number I know.
- Please!
- Number nine.
[The number he must guess is number nine.]
This is a 50/50 chance.
[Who is number nine?]
- Please shout out the person's name.
- Don't say my name because it isn't me.
I know everyone and their jobs.
Number one, two and nine are singers.
And number ten is a comedian.
One thing that I know for sure...
is that number one is Kang Gary.
So number two is either Ha Ha
or Jong Kook.
And number nine is also
either Ha Ha or Jong Kook.
This really is a 50/50 chance.
[A 50/50 chance!]
[Is it Jong Kook or Ha Ha that's
number nine?]
Number nine is... Ha Ha!
[Could it be?]
Wow!
I got it right!
[Guesses correctly!
Number nine is Ha Ha!]
This actually makes me feel better.
I actually feel much better!
Wow, I feel so much better.
[It was a 50/50 guess,
and he guesses correctly!]
It's Mi Sun's turn.
[Next up is Mi Sun.]
[The number she has to guess is,
Number eight.]
I think I know this one.
It's not me, right?
It's not me?
[Who could number eight be?]
- It's not me, right? I'm not number eight.
- Five, four, three, two...
Two, one.
Number eight is... Ji Suk Jin!
Ji Suk Jin!
[Number eight is Ji Suk Jin!]
You've been tricking everyone all day!
You deserve it!
I knew all the answers too!
[Big-nose having taunted everyone
all day that he knows who everyone is.]
It's Kim Jong Kook's turn.
Please pick the number.
- What's left?
- Number three.
[The number he has to guess
is number three.]
Number three.
- Five, four, three...
- Seriously!
[He doesn't seem to know?]
I don't know who numbers three, four,
five, six and seven are.
My number is... number two.
[Of all the numbers to pick,
he picks the one that he doesn't know.]
[Hint- Jong Kook is not number two.]
[So the chances are one out of five.]
[Of these that are left...
who's number three?]
Seriously!
Number three is Song Ji Hyo!
[Could Ji Hyo really be number three?]
Seriously?
[How can this be?
Ji Hyo really is number three?]
Really?
[Mr. Capable beats the odds!]
I totally guessed!
- That was a guess!
- That was a good guess.
[Darn...]
The odds are shrinking.
I think that maybe I can win.
We're checking to make sure
that Ji Hyo is number three.
- Number three.
- She really is number three? I just guessed!
The chances of winning for the remaining
players have gone up significantly.
[Only four people are left.]
We will now choose the number that
Son Hyun Joo has to guess.
[The number he has to guess is,
number five.]
[Why the sudden laughter?]
Number five!
I will count to five.
Lee Kwang Soo!
- Lee Kwang Soo!
- Me?
It's not me!
Is it me?
I'm number five?
- Bye.
- Bye!
- I'm number five?
- Bye, Kwang Soo.
I'm number five?
[I'm the star of the show today...]
Seriously?
- That's more like it.
- I thought I was number six!
- Seriously?
- Yes, it's Kwang Soo.
Number five is the king of animals?
Wont that be Lee Kwang Soo?
Yes, I saw that episode.
Giraffe becomes the king.
[Hyung Suk's dad happened to see
that specific episode.]
Kwang Soo is number five.
[More people aboard the float.]
So one of those three
is going to be the winner.
It's Jun Mi Sun's turn once again.
[Back to Mi Sun's turn.]
[The number she has to guess is,
number four.]
[The odds are, one out of four.]
I will count to five.
[Including Jung Hee and herself...]
[If Jong Kook's taken out of the equation
according to this hint...]
[That means number four would be either
Hyun Joo, Jung Hee or herself.]
Number four is.. Jun Mi Sun!
Jun Mi Sun!
[She picks herself out to be
number four!]
[Is she right?]
[Mi Sun isn't number four.]
[Now there are only two people left...]
I don't care if I win,
but I'm just so nervous!
It's Kim Jong Kook's turn now.
Number four.
[Number four]
Number four!
[It wasn't Mi Sun...
and he's number four...]
Jung Hee's number hasn't been
verified yet either, right?
[So that means that number four has to be
either Jung Hee or Hyun Joo!]
So if Moon Jung Hee's number four...
then it means that I won't
get dumped, right?
Stop talking so much!
Hyun Joo, are your number four?
You need to stop talking,
and you'll have five seconds.
[Who's number four?]
Number four is Moon Jung Hee!
[Chooses Jung Hee to be number four.]
[A 50% chance-
Did Mr. Capable get it right?]
[Jung Hee is not number four!]
[Hyung Suk's dad wins!]
[Ex-salsa dance instructor Jung Hee
is number seven.]
Thus, the winner is...
Son Hyun Joo!
[Winner is, number four,
Son Hyun Joo!]
Hyung Suk!
Jung Min!
Honey!
[The god of acting wins!]
Hyung Suk, your father won.
He didn't even know his own number.
[Handing out the prize.]
[Three 'R' rings!]
Some people are just born with luck.
Thank you so much, Running Man!
[The man who remained so poised even when
he received the best acting award...]
We should come back on the show.
Subtitles by DramaFever
[One bright and sunshiny day...]
[All the cute couples resting in quiet...]
[Relaxing and enjoying the peace.]
What is your father doing?
[Battle for the lives of these
new couples.]
[Only those couples who really
know how to play!]
[Play your heart out for the gold!]
[Next Weekend's Running Man-
Strongest Couple Race.]