Subtitles by DramaFever
[Jackie Chan is coming!]
[The legendary treasure hunter!]
[The eternal superstar of Hong Kong.]
[The star of action comedies that
swept the globe!]
[The legend, Jackie Chan!]
[To find the mysterious treasure,
he's coming to join the cast of Running Man!]
Myungdong, Namdaemun,
Dongdaemun...
It's so pretty.
[Now that we've gotten to know him,
he's an adorable treasure hunter?]
These are the members.
Running Man...
Running girl.
[I need to be cautious of this guy...]
[It's been a while, Grasshopper.]
[Are you all ready to go on a search
for the treasure with me?]
[Jackie Chan, the treasure hunter!]
[7 a.m. - Namsan historical village.]
Namsan... Namsan tower!
Seeing the Namsan tower is reminding me
of the Macau tower.
What is this all about
so early in the morning?
[You guys are talented treasure hunters.
Solve the secret cipher first.]
[Treasure hunter?]
[Trying to decipher the morning riddle.]
What's a treasure?
Treasure... what's a treasure?
[At this rate,
solving the secret password will be...]
[Treasure]
That's what treasure means?
Treasure hunter...
Ah, that treasure?
[Asia's Prince isn't very
versed in foreign languages...]
If you put it like that,
it's not very easy to understand.
I know English very well.
[Huh? This is...]
[And a pencil holder?]
What is this?
[Is this the cipher?]
[What kind of a cipher is this supposed to be?]
By gathering the strength of seven men,
to find the seven treasures...
find the treasure that's been
lost to time.
Let me look at this closely.
I wonder if it's a coded message?
[Just how are they supposed to solve this?]
What is this?
Why are we being given school supplies?
Why is there a glue stick in here?
In Running Man...
there's always something.
This isn't what's needed.
This is it.
[Just the pencil holder?]
I bet there's something hidden in here.
[Ah... I guess we didn't think of that...]
[In front of 'D' theater]
[Oh... a Hallyu Idol star, Choi Si Won!]
[With exaggerated reactions...
and a peculiar speech pattern.]
[The man who's extreme reactions
serve as his trademark...]
[Why was he brought here?]
[Si Won also received a mission card.]
This is my third one.
You guys are talented
treasure hunters.
[Si Won is another treasure hunter!]
- The secret password is contained in this.
- In this?
[Si Won also receives the mysterious cipher.]
Solve this by the end of the day.
Fascinating and royal...
The treasure...
What the heck?
What is this?
Royal... and fascinating...
[You're just supposed to read it...]
Numbers?
Do I need to replace them with numbers?
[Unable to comprehend]
I don't get it.
[If you want to decipher the message,
go to these three places.]
[A hair salon, a kimbap restaurant,
and a children's amusement park?]
I'm going to start by
going to the hair salon first.
I have no idea what this is.
[Heading off to the locations where
the clues are kept waiting for them.]
I'm hungry,
so I'm going to the restaurant.
[Nonstop muttering from the get-go.]
[What does this have to do
with the treasure?]
[Hair salon]
Even this early in the morning...
people are in here getting their hair done?
[This early in the morning...
people are here getting a perm?]
You're not rolling the hair right.
I'll roll it up nice and neat for you.
- A wide roller needs to be used for this.
- Really?
[Wait, their conversation is...]
[Kind of strange?]
Of course, I can roll it up.
Roll it outwards?
Wide rollers, and rolled outwards...
[Having listened to the conversation,
it's about rolling... and rolling...]
[Kimbap restaurant]
I'll take the vegetable kimbap.
[Starved Mr. Capable
orders a vegetable kimbap.]
Yes.
Two rolls of vegetable kimbap, please.
- Two rolls, please.
- Okay.
[Wait... they're saying 'Roll' here too?]
[Roll?]
You guys are all here?
[Starving family members all
gathering at the restaurant.]
I'll take some kimbap too, please.
Roll two more kimbap, please.
[You're saying 'Roll' again?]
He said 'roll' a little bit ago, and
now he just said the word, 'Roll' again.
- Roll up two kimbap, please.
- You're right.
He keeps saying the word, 'Roll'.
I think there's something
to that word, 'Roll'.
- Roll?
- Yeah.
Seriously stop what you're doing.
Why don't you just keep it to yourself
and just solve it on your own?
- Jae Suk...
- Seriously...
We have to talk things over
so that we can solve this.
- You're such a chatterbox!
- The owner kept saying the word, 'Roll'!
There was no need for him
to keep saying that word.
Roll...
Roll it?
That hurts.
Ji Hyo, that hurts.
[Asia's Giraffe getting his mane rolled?]
You look so pretty!
- This is...
- Customer...
- I think you did this for fun, but...
- Look at how wide your forehead is!
[Full exposure of his forehead
thanks to a morning perm service.]
Okay, let's roll it up.
How should I roll it up?
Don't you think that we need to solve it
before we start rolling it up?
If you roll it up like that...
[He wraps it around his finger...]
[After he wraps it around...
'Carefully'?]
[Fascinating how the words are
starting to form...]
I don't know,
but this kind of makes sense...
[No way...]
[Wrapping it around the magic marker
that was in the pencil case.]
[Si Won also arrives at the restaurant.]
- You came!
- Si Won, good to see you!
- What are you doing here?
- I came to find the treasure.
- You're searching for the treasure too?
- You know Si Won, don't you?
Of course, we do.
[Imitating Si Won's reactions.]
[Just then...]
Jung-gu...
Shindang-dong...
- There's got to be something here.
- I know. We need to roll it up.
Look at this.
Look at what happens when I roll it.
I got 'Jung-gu Shindang-dong 777'.
It says, 'Jung-gu Shindang-dong 777'.
[Jung-gu Shindang-dong 777]
I'm going to head out first.
[Is this the address to
where the treasure is?]
- Why can't we all go together?
- I should wrap this around?
[He's already leaving?]
[The surprised look on his face
is pure Si Won.]
Jung-gu Shindang-dong 777...
is that right?
I think it's right.
Jung-gu Shindang-dong 777.
[Kkuk and Ro-Ro get in a cab.]
Can you please take us there?
777...
[It exists! 258 meters away!]
It exists!
Wow... it exists.
This is awesome.
Don't cut it.
No, don't do it!
[Blank Ji cutting Kwang Soo's paper
in case it ruins the one she has.]
I was barely able to glue it back together,
and I can't believe you cut it again.
You rolled up my hair earlier too.
Then what was I supposed to do?
Undo my hair?
[Blank-Kwang siblings bickering with
one another first thing in the morning.]
[Let's roll it...
with Kwang Soo's paper...]
[Having rolled it up...]
[Jung-gu Shindang-dong 777]
[Did Blank Ji notice something?]
[The commonality between those that
solved the cipher... awkwardness...]
- Where are you going?
- I don't know yet.
[Little brother Giraffe having noticed his
older sister's suspicious behavior.]
- I just want to get out of here.
- Can you lock down the doors?
You can't go anywhere.
- You just keep looking at that, okay?
- Where are you going? You can't leave.
[Blank-Kwang siblings farewell...]
- Never mind where I'm going.
- Call the cops!
[Sister!]
Call the cops.
Report her to the police!
Hello.
Mister, can you take me to
Jung-gu Shindang-dong 777?
[With the exception of just one person,
everyone is on the move.]
What am I supposed to do by rolling it?
I don't get it.
This is the place.
[Arrives at the children's amusement park
for another clue.]
[Roll-Roll's attack?]
Why?
Why are you doing this?
[Asia's Prince being chased after
for no reason.]
Why are you doing this?
Wait a second... why?
What is this?
[Having become a giraffe roll within
a blink of an eye.]
What is this?
[Everyone get it?
This is the final hint.]
This is the place.
Yeah, this is the address.
[A Chinese restaurant on the sixth floor?]
[Being first to arrive will prove
to be advantageous!]
Sixth floor!
[This building... to the sixth floor!]
[Run!]
No!
Running Man!
[Sprinting as soon as the flag is spotted!]
[Just who will be the first person
to arrive on the sixth floor?]
[Destination-
Chinese restaurant on the sixth floor.]
[Arrives at the final escalator.]
- You can't run! No running.
- Jong Kook, wait!
- You can't run. It's dangerous.
- Wait, Jong Kook!
[Off to the Chinese restaurant setup!]
[Who will be first to sit down on the chair?]
[Kkuk is first to sit on the chair
by the split of a hair.]
Why don't we all take a seat first?
What happened to Kwang Soo
and Ji Hyo?
- It's Ji Hyo.
- Ji Hyo!
Miss Blank!
- Where have you been?
- You all figured it out?
- We figured it out right away.
- Hello.
Go sit down next to your boyfriend.
Next to your Monday boyfriend.
- I saved a seat for you.
- Seriously...
Ji Hyo, look at Gary's hat.
- What's with the KISS?
- K.I.S.S.
K.I.S.S?
- Kwang Soo... he's here.
- There he is.
- Hey, Kwang Soo!
- Hello.
- Did you get your hair rolled nicely?
- Yes, I did.
I thought you were some French actor.
[The Giraffe all of a sudden looks like
a French actor with his morning perm?]
- There's an actor who sort of looks like him.
- I think he was on 'Notting Hill'.
[Maybe he was on the 'Notting Hill'?]
[The character actor, Rhys Ifans?]
- Come on, that's a little harsh.
- That's right on the money.
It's not Notting Hill,
but Gae-tting Hill. Gae-tting Hill!
[Gae Grant, Blank-lia Roberts,
and Rhys I-Kwang Soo?]
[Today's race - Treasure Hunter]
The special mission will be shown on screen.
Please take a good look at the screen.
[Oh... on that screen is...]
[Jackie Chan?]
Hello, Running Man.
[Jackie Chan is on the screen!]
- Do you remember me?
- Of course!
- Of course, we do!
- Jackie, do you remember me?
You saw me in Hong Kong.
[I saw you in Hong Kong.]
[Jackie Chan having relayed an important
message to him regarding the mystery.]
It really is Jackie Chan.
I have another request to make to
all of you today.
Please recover my lost treasure for me.
- You want us to find you your lost treasure?
- Of course, we'll find it for you!
In order to find the treasure, you'll have to
hit a bulls-eye with the golden dart.
To do that, you'll have
to pass all the missions first.
It's difficult for me to find
the treasure all on my own.
Grasshopper,
you'll help me, won't you?
- Of course, I'll help you!
- We'll all help you!
Everyone... all together!
- All of us together!
- Let's go find the treasure!
Yes, I understand!
Don't worry about it.
No problem, no problem.
[Let's find the treasure!]
[I'll put my faith in you.]
- We'll handle it.
- I love you!
- Wait!
- Where are you going?
Where are you going?
What's 'promise'?
[I don't know either?]
Hi!
[Wow!]
[How... can this be?]
[Jackie Chan in person!]
[A shocking appearance!]
Jackie!
[Happily greeting all the members.]
- Oh my God!
- Jackie Chan! Jackie Chan!
Jackie, I'm such a huge fan!
[With a nose as prominent as
Big-nosed Brother's?]
Are they the same?
They're not the same!
[They're different!]
Why are you talking about your nose
to Jackie Chan?
- You win!
- Seriously, Suk Jin.
His nose isn't the same!
[Huh?]
[Attempting to take a picture.]
[Wow... it's Jackie Chan!]
[Me too, me too!]
[Huh?]
[Even his sense of playfulness
is world-class.]
[A proof of photo is more important
than chatting with him for now.]
My face isn't in the shot.
- Yes!
- Jackie Chan!
[Proof-aholics...
Aren't you going to work?]
Let's all give him a huge
round of applause.
What in the world is this?
Jackie Chan is here!
[Jackie Chan really is here!]
To have Jackie Chan on the
show like this...
- Seriously...
- I loved him in Rush Hour.
[Countless film titles he's been in...]
- How about the 'Drunken Master'?
- That one...
There's been a lot!
[So many - Over a 100 movies!]
I never imagined in my wildest dreams
that he'd come walking out that door.
By the way, do you know Si Won?
- Hello.
- Remember this guy?
Ask him if he remembers.
He's very famous in China.
- Me too! Very famous in China!
- I haven't seen you.
[Ruthless Jackie Chan.]
- You should just stay quiet.
- What are you doing, Suk Jin?
You're all popular in China.
But not this guy.
[Jackie having figured out the
dynamics of Running Man already.]
Jackie Chan knows all of us already!
- I can't believe it.
- This is so surreal.
- You look very young.
- Am I? I am young!
- 39?
- Suk Jin, it's over. He says he's young.
- 40... I'm 40.
- 40?
- Yes, I'm 40.
- You're 40 years old?
- Then I'm going to say I'm 20.
- Okay, I'm 41.
[What a sense of humor...]
Your pronunciation is that of a Korean!
I saw the 'Drunken Master'
when I was in elementary school!
- But that would make you...
- Hey, what are you doing?
Okay, fine.
I'm 45 years old!
[Unbelievable energy-
Unbelievably youthful looking Jackie Chan!]
The five people that I believed could protect
the earth when I was younger...
consisted of Superman, you
and a few others.
- You were one of my heroes.
- Speak in words that he can understand.
- But I don't know...
- You are our hero... forever.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
What do you think he meant by
that 'thank you'?
It means he doesn't want to
talk to you much.
Why are you saying things like that?
[How did he know?]
Why don't we all take a turn and say a
few words we'd each like to say to Jackie?
Jackie...
Can I have your phone number?
[What's your phone number?]
- Why not?
- You're not a woman.
A woman...
[Blank Ji is okay?]
Not this woman.
No, no, no.
[Let's do this!]
[His sense of humor really is...]
He's saying giving his phone number
to girls is okay... what a joker.
The next time we're in Hong Kong,
we'll come see you and hang out.
- Yes, do so. I'm serious.
- Seriously?
Come to Hong Kong and give me a call.
- Let's all grab dinner together.
[Dinner with Jackie Chan?]
You can... pay.
Okay, I'll pay.
Jackie Chan is treating us to dinner.
Jackie Chan says he's going to
buy us dinner.
Okay, we have Jackie Chan
on our show today.
[Today's treasure hunter special]
Today's race is to get a bulls-eye with
the golden dart and find the treasure.
Hence 'The treasure hunter'.
With each mission that you pass,
you'll be receiving a dart.
Gather all those darts, and the team that hits
the bulls-eye on the golden dartboard
will become the treasure hunters
that will receive the treasure.
[The treasure to be earned!]
[Hm?]
- Kwang Soo, can you translate?
- Dart... the gold dart?
- Yes.
- Good.
[Extremely rudimentary giraffe-English.]
[Starting to sign language?]
[Why don't you try translating this?]
- You're seriously embarrassing.
- What are you doing?
[Hello Vietnam. Why is he popular?]
- I know, I know.
- You know?
- Your English is good.
- Thank you.
- He's so good at our language.
- His Korean is so good!
I used to be good in the past,
but my Korean now is...
- Your pronunciation is so good though.
- You really are very good.
- The first person to have arrived earlier...
- It was Jong Kook.
[What's being handed out to Kkuk?]
Why don't you open it up?
[A dart!]
What is this?
This is for me to use later on?
When you succeed a mission,
you'll be given a dart to use later.
And you'll use it later on to
throw a bulls-eye on the dartboard.
The more darts you win,
the bigger advantage you'll have.
Then if you don't have any darts,
you won't even be given a chance?
You will be divided into teams now.
Two two guests will choose
the members they want on their team.
And that's how the teams will be
divided into two different teams.
Two people...
- Please.
You!
[Chooses Asia's grasshopper, Jae Suk.]
Package.
We come in a package.
[Huh?]
[Trying to persuade him.]
- Fair... fair game.
- One plus one.
One man and one woman.
[Also selects Blank Ji.]
What was this that you were doing
showing him your arm?
[Fails to get selected with
his muscle show.]
This... your brain needs to be good.
This is no good.
Then this is the first team.
Si Won, it's your turn to pick your team.
In that case,
I choose Mr. Capable, Jong Kook.
[Gym enthusiasts partnering together.]
[Choosing to go with
Si Won's reaction style.]
- And...
- My big brother and I are a package.
Gary.
[And at times Mr. Capable, Gary.]
[Si Won, Jong Kook and Gary are a team.]
This team really is... a traitor's club.
That's actually kind of dangerous.
You guys are all dead now.
- We'll show you what betrayals are all about.
- You're in for it now.
Everyone can get changed into
your team uniforms now.
And we will start
the non-stop race right away.
I understand.
[Slate]
[Nice and easy?]
You have to say, one, two, three.
One, two, three!
[Treasure hunting race - Start!]
[Non-stop race]
[Changing into the team outfits
right away.]
[The opening location to be
the location for their first mission.]
[Stage 1]
Are you tired?
No, I'm okay.
He understood when I asked him
if he was tired.
He understands everything.
One, two, three.
[Teasing the Giraffe and
making fun of him.]
The non-stop mission means that
we're not going to stop until the end.
[The first mission is...]
- Read it out loud.
- What is this?
[Cola and cider-
Get the cap on the finishing line to pass.]
Where's the finish line?
- Over here.
- The line is over there.
- The one who gets closest to the line...
- Ah, that!
- We used to play that a lot.
- Cola and cider!
We used to play that a lot.
Flick the cap and
get it closest to that line.
- Over here.
- Without it going over.
The team that wins by getting it
closest to the line without going over
will get to leave for the next
location immediately.
Jackie, you get how it's played, right?
You understood what he said?
It's all about getting the feel for it,
which we're very good at.
- Jackie is like a master at things like this.
- Of course, he is.
Since it's all about instinct.
[What kind of a man is Jackie Chan?]
[Just the number of things he's thrown in
his life alone are countless.]
[His accuracy and ability to hit things
right on target is an amazement.]
[His faster than lightening action sequence
that requires no dialogues?]
[The legendary Jackie...]
[The unbelievable mission with
the legend starts now!]
- Say rock, paper, scissors for us.
- Rock, paper, scissors.
- Rock, paper, scissors, you start.
The three of you do it.
Three of you play rock, paper, scissors.
- Rock, paper, scissors!
[Lost...]
I guess he's not good at everything.
Rock, paper, scissors!
[Suk Jin wins]
[Friendship doesn't apply today!
Traitor's club out for the win only!]
[He is getting upset?]
Ji Suk Jin can decide the order
of who will go when.
- Suk Jin will?
- Okay, then we'll go last.
And you can go first.
[Red team to start the game.]
- You're doing great!
- Suk Jin is the best!
[Red Team- Blue Team- Green Team]
Jackie can understand
everything that we're saying.
- Si Won...
- You have to hit it harder than you'd think.
[Reaction man, Si Won to start off.]
- You only have one chance.
- Hit it just like that.
- You only get one chance.
- That's good!
- It's okay, it's okay.
- It's okay, I'll go next.
[Next up is Jae Suk of the Blue Team.]
- Jackie, fighting!
- Fighting!
Jae Suk, fighting!
[Huh?]
[Oh my goodness...]
- What are you doing?
- Are you joking right now?
Jae Suk, why did you do that?
- Jae Suk, why did you do that...
- He asks him why he did that.
[Kwang Soo from the Green Team's turn.]
I really wanted to show Jackie
how good I can be.
- I can't believe that happened!
- Asia's Prince, Lee Kwang Soo!
[Asia's Prince, Kwang Soo]
Kwang Soo!
[In one clean shot, out!]
[Familiar result]
[Kkuk from the Red Team
takes the challenge.]
Here I go!
Hurry up and play it.
[Hm?]
[The bottle cap coming up way too short.]
He's really horrible at anything that
requires detailed work.
- She's our ace.
- I thought I'd be good at this!
Just think of me.
I said, just think of me.
- Just keep your mouth shut.
- It's because he's always thinking of you.
- You two are seriously...
- That's too strong of a hit!
[Oh!]
[Si Won's cap is closer to the line
by the split of a hair.]
It's okay, we have Gary.
Gary's good at things like this.
[He really is good...]
Get it all the way up there.
[Impala of the Green Team's turn.]
Good luck, Suk Jin.
Good... good!
[What!]
[Passes between the other two caps,
and gets ahead!]
[Impala currently stands in first place!]
You can hit it out of there.
- Okay, I can do this.
- You can do this.
- Since I've always been an outsider...
- That's right.
[Gary's preparing to hit it from
the outermost spot?]
[Oh!]
[Closest to the finish line!]
- Yes! Yes!
- Yes, Gary!
[Showing his sometimes Mr. Capable
side of him again today!]
[At last, it's Jackie's turn.]
Fighting!
[Blue Team's last ray of hope.]
Jackie...
[Will Jackie...]
[Get past all those bottle caps
to win the battle for his team?]
[All those countless items he's
thrown in his lifetime...]
[With the same feel for it
that he had back then...]
[Oh... it's getting close?]
[Ah... too bad!]
[Misses getting first place by a margin!]
You just beat Jackie Chan!
- You just beat Jackie Chan!
- I won! I just beat Jackie Chan!
Dong Hoon, just hit it.
It doesn't matter if you fall off.
[Will he get closer to the line
than Gary's?]
[Huh?]
[What in the world?]
[Hits Jackie's in his path,
and hits his own cap off the table?]
[He just helped in pushing Jackie's cap
closer to the finish line!]
[How can this be...]
[An event that can't repeat even if he
was to practice it a hundred times!]
[Panic]
This is the power of Jackie Chan!
[Jackie's bottle cap noticeably
closest to the finish line.]
That's the power of Jackie Chan!
- Good!
[Jackie Chan power?
Thanks to Ha Ha, Jackie lands in first place.]
- You can get going to your next location.
- Let's go!
What just happened?
It really felt like something out of a movie!
[As a sign of his gratitude, he
agrees to giving him his phone number?]
[Not forgetting to show his gratitude...]
Jackie, you really are the best!
This is why he's Jackie Chan!
How do you say...
- He says you're a spy.
- Spy... spy.
[You're now Jackie Chan's spy?]
[Treasure Hunter- Go up to the rooftop.]
[Off to the rooftop!]
- Then do we play between us?
- Ha Ha, thanks!
Ha Ha, thanks!
[This is Jackie Chan's power!]
- You're the best!
- So lucky!
We were seriously so lucky!
[Wins three darts.]
I can't believe that happened!
[Heading up to the rooftop.]
[With Jackie on their side,
it all seems like something out of a movie.]
What is this?
- What is this?
- What is all this?
[Stage 2]
[In middle of the rooftop...]
[A shiatsu mat?]
[Could this be...]
- What this this?
- Could this be that thing...
[If you can jump rope at least 10 times
on the shiatsu mat, you pass the mission.]
[Drunken Master - 1979]
[Jackie, who's not known to walk
evenly along a flat surface with his moves.]
[Countless number of jumps he's made
throughout all his years.]
[Something so simple as jump roping on
top of the shiatsu mat would be a cinch?]
Jackie, this is...
[Taking their shoes off...]
This hurts.
[Good for the blood circulation.
Sending shocking sensations along their feet.]
[Toe separating socks...]
Jackie... Jackie's socks...
Look at Jackie's socks.
You're so cute!
Jackie, you're so cute!
This hurts.
Ugh, this hurts.
[Jump roping on this mat...]
- How are we supposed to...
- How are we supposed to do this?
[Unable to even walk straight.]
This hurts!
[And downstairs...]
[Haroro this time...]
[Out!]
[Red Team wins!]
- Give me the darts!
- He has skills.
Let's go!
Let's go, let's go!
How did Jackie...
[No matter how much they think about it,
what happened with Jackie is amazing?]
[Red Team wins themselves two darts.]
[Satisfied with winning second place.
Now up to the rooftop!]
Jackie... let's stand like this
with Ji Hyo in the middle.
- Okay.
We have to do it standing like this.
Move, let's change spots.
We're good at things like this.
[Muscles on the bottom of his feet too?
Walking with confidence.]
We can start and Ji Hyo will jump in.
That's when the counting will start.
- Oh...
- Jackie has toe separating socks on?
[Will they be able to jump rope
more than 10 times on the mat?]
- Are you ready?
- Yes.
Set... go!
[Sending waves of shock throughout
their whole body!]
[Even Jackie, the action star
cries out in pain!]
[The shocking sensation of
the shiatsu mat.]
That hurts!
- It hurts without shoes.
- That really hurts!
[Green Team also arrives on scene.]
- It's a group jump rope.
- Jackie, you have to stand here.
How do you do this?
I don't find it painful.
- You don't find it painful?
- No.
- Jong Kook, I'm okay too.
- Right?
[No problem!
The brothers feeling no pain.]
It feels okay to me.
[They're no joke.]
I should've worn thicker socks.
[the brothers who feels no pain
up to take the challenge.]
One, two, three, go.
[Will they...]
[Huh?]
[Not really feeling the shock,
but steps on the rope...]
[Fail...]
The moment you wind the rope, it's over.
[Even though they argue it was practice,
they fail to convince others.]
There are no practice swings.
[Darn...]
I was just practicing!
This isn't just a joke,
but with Jackie and his toe socks
he totally feels like a member of our team.
[Jackie's appeal that makes him seem like
he's just an older brother to everyone.]
He just seems so friendly!
- You want me to jump in?
- No, I'll jump in.
[Traitor's club taking their turn.]
- Why?
- I find this side more comfortable.
Why do we have to go with
your comfort?
- Kwang Soo, you can turn around then.
- You're younger than me!
- Like this?
- That's right.
[What is this?]
[What kind of a starting position is this?]
[Jackie breaks out into laughter.]
Jackie started laughing too.
[Even the world star finds the comedic antics
of the traitor's club entertaining.]
You really think this is going to work?
Set... go!
[What is that...]
[Deformed strategy that's hard for
a normal person to understand.]
[Fail]
I can't do it that way!
[Screaming out in pain again after
piercing the palms of his hands.]
The space is too tight.
You have to make more room for me.
[The Blue Team makes their second attempt.]
- That really hurts.
- Jackie, we have to endure the pain.
- That's some serious stuff.
- Let's do it slow.
Slow?
Okay, I got it.
- One, two...
- Three...
Jackie just said to me, 'Slow...'
Jackie, I got it.
Don't worry.
I'll go slow.
[The two appearing to have
become quite close.]
- One.
[Huh?]
[The hand and feet coordination is...]
[Listen to me!]
Jackie, seriously!
I really didn't take him
to be like that!
- One.
[Ah, like that?]
- We can't?
- We can't!
- We can't do it like that.
- Okay.
I just figured Jackie out.
He wants to do it like this.
Jackie wants to jump once, and rest.
Two and rest...
[Okay, I get it.]
We'll stand up front,
and then you'll come in.
Come up right next to us.
And then we'll jump like this.
- Ready, start. One, two, three, four...
- One, two, three, four...
It hurts!
It really hurts!
[Strict mock practice run.]
Just a light jump, okay?
We're going to go, okay?
When do I come in?
[Start... huh?]
[Drops the rope!]
Jong Kook!
[Get off!]
Get off!
[The Painless Brothers' distress over
not knowing how to jump rope properly.]
- They don't know what they're doing.
- Seriously!
[Comedy act Green Team's turn once again.]
- So that we don't trip over it.
- Set, go!
[Oh?]
[They're actually good?]
- Five, six, seven, eight...
- Hurry up and come in!
Hurry up and come in!
Hurry!
[Fail...]
[May have jumped over 20 times already?]
They were going way too fast!
Don't you think they were going too fast?
[Getting a huge laugh from the world star.]
That's the only team Jackie laughs at.
I think he likes us.
[So funny!]
Jackie and I really are getting close!
[Chan and Jae Suk making another attempt.]
Like we practiced.
[Slowly like they planned earlier.]
One, two, three!
One, two...
One, two, three...
One, two, three, four, five...
What are you doing?
[Explodes]
- What are you doing?
- I was trying!
Jackie has a bit of a temper.
- Why...
- Here...
[Jackie starting to give them
a lesson in how it's done.]
- One, two...
- One, two, three!
[Matching their steps to the speed.]
Five, six, seven, eight...
[Me too!]
Set, go.
[Painless Brothers making another attempt.]
[Their feet not feeling any of the shock.]
There's no room for Gary to get in.
[Now if only Gary can jump in...]
Hey!
You could've just jumped in!
- Jong Kook, there wasn't any room for me!
- How many times so I have to spin the rope?
Hey! There wasn't any
room for Gary to jump in!
[Continuing to jump rope without giving
Gary any room to jump in.]
What do you mean, there wasn't any room?
There was plenty of room for him!
He could've just jumped in like this!
- There wasn't any room for Gary!
- Yeah, there was no room for Gary!
How was he supposed to
jump in there?
Even Jackie wouldn't have been
able to jump in between you two!
This team doesn't look like they feel
any pain on the bottom of their feet!
If you think about how it's good for
your health, it doesn't hurt a lot.
['If you think of it as being good for
your health, it's not painful.'- By Kkuk]
It hurts me. I'm just enduring it
because of Jong Kook.
- Are you ready?
- Yes.
- Fighting!
- Ready...
[Trying to match up their pace.]
One, two...
[What?]
I'm sorry!
- You did that.
- I'm sorry!
You're the one who did that.
Jackie, you're the one who
messed it up.
It hurts... it hurts.
Five?
Just five is okay.
There's no way we can get ten.
Just five.
- Just do five.
- He says ten is too many.
- Five?
- Jackie is trying to get everyone to agree.
- We have to get ten!
- Yes, we'll get ten.
Ten, ten... we need to go for ten.
No!
Just get five.
- Ten, ten...
- Okay, seven.
- Seven. Just go for seven.
- No, let's go for full ten.
- Seven... just go for seven.
- Okay, we'll settle for eight.
- Then let's do seven.
- Okay, seven.
[Settles on seven jumps as the new goal.]
Okay, seven.
Let's settle on seven.
- Four without the socks?
- Five without the socks.
Five?
Let's take them off.
- You're taking off your socks?
- Let's take off the socks.
But taking off the socks
is really going to hurt.
[Even though it's reduced down to
five without the socks...]
Taking off the socks is
really going to hurt.
- That's going to hurt.
- Oh my gosh... put the socks back on!
Hey, this isn't right!
[The pain being escalated exponentially
without the socks?]
- This is no joke!
- Hurry up!
The pain is no joke.
[Attempting to go for five barefoot.]
[Traitors' club with their sight
set on winning only.]
- Set, go!
- They won't even get one.
One...
[The pain...]
[Barefoot shiatsu mat jump that
makes them double over in pain immediately.]
You look like you're
bowing down to us right now.
[The New Year's Grand Bow
to wish all the viewers a good year?]
- Is it bearable?
- Back on... put the socks back on.
- Is it unbearable?
- We can endure it... we can endure it.
[Painless Brothers and Gary making
the barefoot jump attempt?]
- Wow, that's really...
- We just have to endure five!
- Just five.
- We can do this.
- We can do it!
- Numb the bottoms of your feet.
[What? Numb the feet?]
- Numb the feet.
- Numb it, numb it!
- You have to numb the feet.
- Numb it!
[This is the true worth of Kkuk
who feels no pain...]
- I'm seriously so sick of his antics.
- How is he doing that?
It's not going to be easy.
We know from experience, and it really hurts.
[The goal is to get five.
Will they get it?]
One, two, three!
[Just five jumps!]
[Fail]
[Even the Painless Brothers seem to have
a difficult time enduring the pain barefoot.]
Look at Gary.
Once you start jumping, it's not that bad.
Jackie, we only have to jump five times
if we do it barefoot. Just five jumps.
No, it's okay.
[The Blue Team goes for seven
with their socks on.]
One, two, three...
[They seem to be in sync?]
I'm going to jump in!
[Ji Hyo, now's the time!]
[Must jump a minimum of seven times
for them to succeed the mission!]
[Fail...]
[Jackie finally sits down
on the ground in defeat.]
[The hot packs...]
Hot packs?
You have hot packs on your feet?
- It's okay. For the sake of our health.
- Of course. This is durable.
- You have to forget about the pain.
- One, two.... start!
[The Painless Brothers going barefoot again.]
[Oh?]
[Five jumps is their goal!]
[Succeeds in accomplishing five jumps!]
[Read Team succeeds!]
- They succeeded.
- Sparta!
I can't believe they succeeded.
[Earns themselves more darts!]
You got three?
[Darn...]
[Treasure Hunter-
Go down to the third floor.]
Jong Kook, I think our team is a great fit.
[Red Team earns themselves
three darts.]
Okay...
[The Blue Team's attempt.]
Jackie, are you ready?
You're ready, right?
[Will they succeed getting their
seven jumps this time?]
One, two...
Three, four...
[Oh! She jumped in!]
[Success]
[The Blue Team finally succeeds!]
Ji Hyo, I knew you'd do it!
We did it.
[Wins more darts for their team!]
Where do we have to go, Ji Hyo?
What happens to these three?
[Worrying about the Traitors Club
as soon as he succeeds.]
Jackie, this team has to keep trying.
- Bye!
- Slow! Take your time!
[Blaming each other's feet
for no reason.]
[Earns two additional darts.]
You know that scene with the huge chandelier
in that giant shopping mall?
- You did that yourself, right?
- Yeah.
You don't get hurt doing that?
You didn't get hurt?
Wasn't it painful?
Of course, it hurts!
[It sounds as though he injured
his hands quite a bit.]
[Their next mission location is a
woman's clothing store.]
- Should we sit in the middle?
- Sure.
- Is this coffee?
- Isn't this Caramel Macchiato?
[Non-stop race.
Off to their next mission location.]
Hello.
[Stage 3]
Jackie just showed us his hands real quick,
and they're just covered in scars!
[Marks left by all the action sequences
he's performed throughout his years.]
Jackie is famously known for doing
all his stunt himself.
Your movies always show the outtakes
at the end of the film.
[Extremely difficult and
dangerous action scenes.]
[The warning message not to imitate what's
being shown on screen is also included.]
When I was little,
I thought that you were Korean.
- Me too.
- That's right. Because of the dubbing.
I thought you were a Korean who
just spoke really good Chinese.
Especially because of his name too.
- That why I thought Bruce Lee...
- You thought that too?
I thought Bruce Lee was Korean too
with his last name.
Do you ever get in touch with Sammo Hung?
[Of course, I do.]
- What about Yu Wang?
- Yu Wang too.
- We eat together all the time.
- Really?
- Ah! I wish I could eat with him too!
- You're close to him like our group is!
- Yeah, it's like our dynamics.
- They're close like we are.
What is Sammo Hung doing these days?
He's a martial arts director.
[Sammo Hung is currently working
as a martial arts director!]
What about Duk Hwa?
Is he doing well these days?
Yoo Duk Hwa.
Yoo Duk Hwa...
Yes, he's filming these days.
- Oh, he's filming right now?
- They're all very similar to us!
We film overnight like they do
all the time!
- If we do a fan meeting...
- You guys are all the same!
You guys are all the same!
[How we all work to make a living
is all the same.]
You guys are all the same...
All these world stars eating and talking
while working like us...
- Filming...
- And getting together...
You're right, you're right.
I see...
There's something I've been wanting to
ask Jackie, but I haven't yet.
- About Man Ok, Jang Man Ok...
- Ah, Man Ok...
I really like Man Ok.
Right now...
She's looking for a good script.
He said, she's looking for
a good script.
[Jang Man Ok taking
some time off at the moment.]
Vacation... she's taking a vacation.
It's really difficult these days to find
a script that would be popular worldwide.
Jackie just said it's really tough to find a
script that would be popular worldwide.
- The translator already told us that.
- Yeah, he already told us!
- When did he tell us that?
- He just told us right now.
Seriously, you guys have no sense!
When I see Jackie,
I'm most reminded of 'Drunken Master'.
- But that was from so long ago.
- You're really strange for your age.
You're most reminded of 'Drunken Master'?
You have to be at least 39 years old
to know that movie.
Whenever I open my mouth,
you guys all attack me like piranis.
Piranhas, you meant to say piranhas.
It's not 'pirani' but 'piranhas'!
- You're supposed to say piranhas.
- Jackie, do you see Kwang Soo over there?
How old do you think Kwang Soo is?
- Be really honest.
- 45 years old?
[You're not?]
- Are you being serious?
Okay, 50?
50 years old?
45 years old...
Are you guys all having fun
chatting and talking to each other?
[Alarm talk-
The next game is alarm talk.]
[The game is played by asking and
answering questions to each other.]
[If the alarm sounds,
then the person is disqualified.]
What does this mean?
If Kim Jong Kook was to start the game,
he'd have to set the time to begin.
So it's like 'The Time Bomb'?
[If the alarm sounds like in the movie,
'The Time Bomb'...]
[The person who's holding the cellphone
at that moment is disqualified.]
- Okay.
- This sounds like fun.
This game sounds like fun.
You have to mix-up the seating.
[Team members to mix-up the seating.]
In the end, you and I
get to sit next to one another.
[Hm... no kidding?]
- In the end...
- No kidding? Maybe they're destined.
[Every Monday, they're
drawn to each other like magnets.]
- That's just so strange.
- Just accept it.
You don't have to go in order.
Ask the question to whomever you'd like.
Did you tell Jackie?
Did you explain the game to Jackie?
Did you explain how it's played?
I know!
I'm smart.
[Kkuk deciding what he should set the time for
between 20 seconds and two minutes.]
- Okay, I'm ready to go.
- Show the time to the camera.
[20 seconds!]
He's always doing things like that.
- Suk Jin...
- Yeah?
[Stalling for time...]
How's your business going?
- Business is...
- You have to hand him your phone now.
The business is going really well.
How are you doing?
How's your dating life?
[Huh? Back to Jong Kook?]
[Flustered]
I'm okay.
How are things at home?
[The time!]
[The alarm sounds!]
- He got played by his own trick!
- Can he pass it back to me like that?
- Of course!
- Why can't he?
What the heck are you doing?
[Red Team's Kkuk is eliminated!]
Impala, Impala!
Impala is still alive!
[Impala's counterattack is a success!]
Jong Kook and what he was planning...
I noticed what he was trying to do.
[Jackie's tissue pack...]
[This man really is...]
This really is amazing.
[To be sitting right next to Jackie Chan
like he is right now...]
He's totally fallen
head over heels in love.
I'm so deliriously happy right now.
I love him more than any other woman,
I'm being really serious.
[Hurry up and restart the game!]
He's not even looking in your direction.
[Jackie is too focused on playing the game.]
[Setting the time limit.]
- Hurry up and do it!
- Oh my goodness!
You scared me.
[Between the allotted 20 seconds- 2 minutes,
what's the time limit he set it for?]
Seriously... I seriously admire you so much.
Honestly... how are you so handsome?
- How?
- What?
How can you be so attractive?
Exercise every day.
Exercise.
Do you exercise every day?
Yes.
- I breathe... I walk, I jog, run, you know?
- Good.
Your nose... your nose that you have...
- Your hook nose...
- Hurry!
Is it like your dad's nose,
or your mom's nose?
- Dad... like my dad.
- Your dad.
Why... um... do you have a girlfriend?
[Girlfriend?]
[Hm?]
- No, I don't have one.
- What's your answer, Si Won?
- Are you happily married?
- It's almost a sin how happy I am.
- Kwang Soo...
- Me?
We're on the same team!
[Oh yeah!]
Kwang Soo...
- Who's better looking?
- Jackie...
[Green Team's Kwang Soo - Out!]
- Why did you give it to your own team?
- What the heck?
Impala, Impala...
Impala, Impala!
Impala is still alive!
Why did you do that to me?
- Just come over here!
- Jong Kook...
Can you at least give us a dart
for ousting our own team member?
So I'm not supposed to give it
to my own team member, huh?
Jackie really likes the Green Team.
They're a funny team.
Not the winning team,
but the funny team.
[Big-nosed Brother sets the
time limit again.]
Seriously though, Yoo Jae Suk...
have you met Jackie before today?
Yes, of course.
Starting from the 80's to 90's...
There's not a single movie that Jackie
has been in that I haven't seen.
Starting from the 'Drunken Master' to
'Police Story' to the recent 'Tuxedo'...
Hurry!
- Then Ji Hyo...
- Me?
[A team member picking someone from
his own team again?]
- You're in a new drama, aren't you?
- Yes, I'm starting a new drama soon.
I'll be starting a historical drama soon.
[Everyone seems so relaxed
about the time they're taking?]
You know how I can do my shopping
here right now?
- What's the role you'll be playing?
- Why are you asking the question?
- You can ask when it's your turn.
- I guess I'm just always curious about you.
Kang Gary, if you had to pick...
what clothes do you want to see me wear?
You have to choose the top and bottom.
Why don't you pick the full outfit for me?
- For Song Ji Hyo...
- Hurry up!
There's no need for you to wear
a top or a bottom.
- When it comes to Song Ji Hyo...
- Hurry, Gary! The time's almost up!
- Song Ji Hyo natural beauty...
- I said, it's almost time! Hurry!
- Song Ji Hyo is...
- What are you trying to say I am?
She is just like a flower.
She's a flower...
[Running out of time!]
How tall are you, Ha Ha?
I'm 143cm tall!
- How tall are you?
- I'm 183cm. What about your weight?
69 kg?
How about...
[Green Team's Ha Ha is ousted!]
[The Traitors Club is getting
eliminated one by one.]
Ji Hyo, do you ever think about
dating Gary?
That's a really good question.
Your question about Gary...
I'll think about it later.
[Huh? Later?]
What the heck does that mean?
I'll think about that later.
What about you? Do you want to date me?
What's going on between those two?
Instead of thinking about it later,
can you give me an 'X' or 'O' answer now?
[Passes the phone back to her.]
[What is he saying?]
Can you give me an 'X' or 'O'
answer now?
- What are you two doing right now?
- Might as well get an answer right now!
I'll think about it when you bring me
a three carat diamond ring.
[Huh? That diamond ring
from that other time?]
Keep... okay?
[The diamond ring she asked him
to keep in Macau?]
Keep the name, Kang Gary.
- Kang... Mr. Kang.
- Yes, it's for Ji Hyo.
[If he's to bring the ring that was asked
to be kept for Blank Ji?]
[How much was that again?]
I'll think about it when you bring me
a three carat diamond ring.
- What are you two doing right now?
- The three carat diamond...
[The Blue Team's Ji Hyo is out!]
- Ji Hyo!
- That happened because of the diamond!
- It's because you asked for an answer!
- You should've just quickly done the 'O'.
Seriously, what are these two doing?
[Si Won's reaction time.]
- You thought about it too long, Ji Hyo.
[Red Team- two; Blue Team- Two;
Green Team- One]
[Gary setting the time limit]
My respected Jackie...
when is your next movie?
Can you please tell us about
your next movie?
I'm very curious to know.
Gary... that was kind of cool.
- And...
- You sound like a reporter.
How you're asking the question is...
And the type of movies that you're making,
what are your thoughts on it?
You sound like you're interviewing him!
- It's Reporter Gae!
- I respect you very much as an actor.
And you mentioned that you
work out every day.
How many hours per day
do you work out?
- Those are nice questions.
- Just answer one of those questions, please.
[It seems as though his questions alone
took a full minute to be asked.]
The current movie I'm working on is about
searching around the world for a treasure.
[A nice and short answer
to a very long question.]
How old were you when you started
watching my movies, Gary?
And out of all the movies you like,
list your 10 favorite movies.
List 10 of your favorite movies
that he's been in.
[Retaliating in the same method.]
If you can't list 10 questions,
you fail your turn.
'Rush Hour'...
Rush Hour... Rush Hour!
[Gary, out!]
Jackie Chan...
Jackie Chan is still alive!
- He's the best!
- He's a genius.
Jackie Chan is still alive!
That was the best.
Jackie Chan is the best.
The next time you're in Hong Kong,
let's go grab a meal together.
I'll introduce you to a lot of my friends.
- The next time you're in Hong Kong...
- He called him Mr. Impala.
He said he'll take you out to dinner.
I'd be so grateful!
[Mr. Impala, out!]
Thank you!
Jackie Chan is still alive!
[All of the members of the
Green Team are ousted!]
How do you guys keep coming
in at last place?
[The last three people left remaining.]
[What will he set the time limit for?]
You guys are like his subjects now.
Jackie Chan's subjects.
If we were to work on a movie together,
what genre would you like to work on?
A martial arts or a Kung Fu movie?
- If you're to shoot a movie with him...
- Me too! I want to do it too!
I'd like anything.
Anything would be great.
Jae Suk, who do you think is
the best MC in our country?
[A little difficult of a question to
answer in his position?]
There are so many people...
[Jae Suk, out!]
- That question was..
- That was good!
- I should've passed it on!
- Si Won, that was good!
[We should've heard his answer...]
That was a difficult question
for him to answer.
[The final face-off:
Jackie Chan vs. Si Won.]
Jackie is very good at this game.
Do you have a girlfriend?
[Very good at asking
ambush attack questions.]
[And counterattack questions.]
You have to list the ten movies!
[And Reaction Si Won who's not
an easy opponent to play against.]
[Which one of the two will come out a victor?]
With all the fans you have in Korea,
will you be coming back often?
Yes, yes.
Since I've made all these good friends now,
I'll be back to visit often.
He said he'll be back to visit often
since he's made good friends with all of you.
It would be nice if you took me out
to dinner every time I came to visit.
He says he hopes you'll take him out
to dinner every time he comes to visit.
Of course, of course!
The next time Super Junior sings,
I'd like to sing together with them.
I'd like to sing along to the
Korean songs...
[Not much time left on the clock!]
How many members are there
in Super Junior?
- How many members in Super Junior?
- There are nine of us working.
Are you planning on putting out
an album yourself?
I'll tell you about that
when I return to Hong Kong.
Want to choose a song to work on
together the next time you're in Beijing?
[Running out of time!]
[Si Won, out!]
[By the split of a hair!]
[Pretty amazing!]
Jackie Chan is still alive!
[Wins the team three darts!]
[Treasure Hunter-
Finally off to Stage Four!]
[The first team to collect seven masks
out of 12 is the winner.]
[Time for Jackie's real action!
A real chase mission!]
There are areas designated for
each team to take their position in.
In the four floors below,
including this one.
The first team to collect the seven masks
while evading other teams, is the winner.
[Masks representing the 12 signs of zodiac.
First team to collect seven wins!]
[Red Team finds their position mark.]
So we have to find the masks
and gather them up here?
- They can't take it from there, right?
- No, they'll take it.
Really?
- This is our spot.
- Our team spot.
Once we set them here, other
teams will come and try to steal them.
So we have to stop them while
gathering all the masks we can.
[Huh?]
[No, you have to find a tiger Mask...]
We have to find the masks.
[Green Team also finds their position.]
- Let's go down.
- There it is. There's a mask over there.
What is that?
[Wait... that's...]
[That is a mask, but which one of the
12 zodiac signs is that supposed to be?]
- Is there a rabbit in the zodiac?
- This is a rabbit?
Isn't it a grasshopper?
Just keep it for now.
[That's a grasshopper.
Fake masks are placed everywhere too!]
I don't see anything...
What to do?
[Jackie checking all the stores
with a fine toothed comb.]
[Huh? There's something back there!]
[Blue Team's Jackie discovers
the mask of the Dog!]
[All his detailed searching pays off!]
[Ace Ji Hyo finds the mask of a Ram
from the floor below!]
[Hiding it away from
other team's prying eyes.]
[Jackie also comes back with
the Dog mask in hand.]
[Needs to gather seven to win.
The Blue Team already has two.]
You're the best!
[Huh? Why is he pulling out the
Ram mask Ji Hyo just hid away?]
[So detailed!
Jackie making sure to hide it carefully.]
Two... we have two!
[Giraffe having found a giraffe mask,
which isn't even one of the signs.]
[One of the masks are hidden away?
The Horse mask is up on the shelf!]
[With Giraffe on their team,
tall shelves are not a problem!]
[Giraffe proving himself to be useful.]
- There's no sign of the giraffe.
- Throw away that giraffe.
- I don't want to throw it away.
- Then put it down somewhere for now.
[Love for his giraffe character.]
I want to take this and keep it forever.
[On the other hand...]
[Si Won loitering around other teams' areas
rather than searching for the masks.]
Is this the Blue Team?
[Starting to search the Blue Team's area.]
[Behind that curtain is...]
[Discovers the Ram and the Dog
Jackie and Ace hid away!]
[Feeling smug about stealing the two.]
[Red Teams Si Won succeeds in
stealing away two masks!]
[This is easy.]
It's Jackie!
[Jackie attempting to steal
the Rooster away from Ha Ha!]
[Where did he run off to?]
[Haroro attacking Jackie after
being attacked and stolen from.]
Jackie stole a mask from me!
[Easily slips away from Suk Jin's block.]
Stop it!
Don't come after us!
[Impala and Haroro becoming more
exhausted than Jackie seems to be.]
[Blue Team's Jae Suk bringing back
the Dragon he discovered.]
[Realizes that the masks they hid away
have been stolen!]
Someone stole our masks.
[Jae Suk sneaks up on Green Team's area.]
Kwang Soo, come over here.
[Jae Suk steals the Horse away
from the Green Team!]
No!
[It seemed Jae Suk may get away
with his thievery...]
[But of all things,
he has to run into the Red Team?]
[The chaos... finally ensues!]
[The desperation to steal at least
one more mask for their own team.]
[Everyone scatters after the ownership
of the masks has been changed.]
Give it back to me!
Ji Hyo!
Ji Hyo, hurry!
Jackie, hurry!
[Discovers the Rooster that
Jackie hid away!]
- Jae Suk, where are you?
- Over here!
[It's mine!]
[His own team member Ji Hyo
surrounded by other teams.]
[I'll save you!]
[Making his way through
in the blink of an eye!]
[Throwing Ha Ha's arm out of
the way first...]
[An instant action which shows how
Kung Fu is embedded into his body.]
[Protecting the masks and Ji Hyo by
shoving them both under the table.]
Grab Jackie!
[The evil henchmen!
A group attack on Jackie!]
[At that moment, Si Won from the Red Team
succeeds in stealing away the Snake!]
Jong Kook!
They stole it.
We had it stolen!
We no longer have the Snake.
- How many?
- Two... we only have two.
[Blue Team only left with two...]
[But if it hadn't been for Jackie,
they may have lost all the masks...]
[Okay... you just wait and see.]
[Giraffe walking towards the
Red Team's home turf.]
Where are you going?
Where do you think you're going?
[Mr. Capable forcing him to a stop.
The masks must be hidden here somewhere!]
- Dong Hoon!
- You can't! Si Won!
Dong Hoon, hurry!
[Red Team rushing in
like a bolt of lightning.]
- Hide it elsewhere.
- Suk Jin! Hurry!
[Seeing how he's blocking the stairs,
it seems the masks are hidden upstairs!]
[Getting up there from the front
is not the idea...]
[How about going up from the back?]
[I'll go up the ladder!]
- Jong Kook, it's me... your little brother!
- No, Kwang Soo.
- Why do you keep pushing me away?
- I can't let you go, Kwang Soo.
[Jae Suk succeeds in safely stealing away
the Red Team's Monkey mask!]
What are you doing down there?
- I'm waiting for my turn to steal.
- Okay, hang on.
I got one!
[Green Team stealing away an
already stolen mask!]
[Jackie jumping out of nowhere
to block his getaway path.]
[Big-nose shouldn't be an issue...]
Hey!
Help me!
[Jackie easily stealing it away
using a bit of his strength.]
I was the one who initially stole it away.
[Jackie Chan is still alive...]
[Secretly hiding away the mask in
the store next to their site.]
[Red Team's storage that's been
compromised.]
- Here they are!
- Up there?
[Red Team in danger!
They may be robbed empty at this rate!]
[I should get up there.]
Jae Suk is going up.
- Good job!
- Good job, Kwang Soo.
[A fierce battle between all three teams!]
Throw it down, Kwang Soo!
- Kwang Soo, throw it down!
- Throw it down here!
- Kwang Soo, throw it down here!
- You're doing great!
[Barely gets away to throw it down...]
[Huh?]
[To get stuck up there...]
[Throws it down to Jackie of the Blue Team?]
[Jackie does it again!]
[When it comes to the decisive moment,
he's always there waiting!]
- Jackie is being very Jackie-esque.
- What do we do?
- Isn't he starting to act like himself?
- How do we stop him?
[Red Team having gathered a total of
five masks with Si Won's Snake mask.]
[Hiding it away under a tarp to
stop from all the thievery!]
[The five mask bundle is complete!]
What are you hiding up there?
[I saw everything.]
What are you doing?
Are you running away?
- You're trying to escape?
- Gary...
- What are you doing?
- What are you hiding up there?
- No, I'm not hiding anything.
- You're saying that's not hiding anything?
- What are you saying?
- I see you're hiding things up there.
- It's just so messy up here...
- Really?
- I'm just organizing up here.
- Is that so?
- Gary...
- Hey, Gary!
What are you doing?
[Shoving them down like a bulldozer.]
[Red Team not about to be had
like they were earlier.]
Why are you standing around here?
[Jae Suk and Kwang Soo in the end
turning away from their goal.]
[Firmly protecting their loot.]
I'll bring it down all at once.
I have them all bundled up together.
[Slowly starting to reform their plans
to protect the masks they already have.]
- Jackie, how many do we have?
- We have four right now.
We need to get three more then.
We have four right now,
and we need to go get three more.
[No end in sight to staying there,
and too nervous to go back out...]
[Jae Suk ultimately deciding to
go back out to hunt.]
- Ji Hyo...
- Don't go!
[Nervous Jackie telling him not to go...]
We need three more.
[Huh? What's Giraffe doing?]
Kwang Soo, we'll stand right here.
[Planning on infiltrating
the Blue Team's lair!]
[You little brat...]
[How dare you!]
I'll go down!
I'll just go back down!
[Spectacular punishment.]
I'll never do it again!
[Leaving after being properly chastised.]
[Just then, Ha Ha quietly sneaks up
through the front entrance.]
[Same punishment for this one!]
[Battered and bruised.]
[Giraffe getting another round of beating.]
[Retreating without accomplishing anything.]
[The last line of attack is
Big-nosed Brother.]
[The result is the same...]
- My glasses.
- Ji Hyo, bring the hat down.
I'll give you your hats back.
Come up here.
[Returning the hats and the glasses
they lost in the battle?]
Come here.
[Did you think I'd
give them back to you nicely?]
[That's the Giraffe's hat...]
[It's all up to the person
returning the items.]
[The shocking visuals of the three.]
[And thus the Green Team started planning
their revenge against the Blue Team.]
[The defeated Green Team now makes their
move over to the Red Team for their attack.]
- Jong Kook is there by himself.
- Okay, we can do this.
If one person grabs his legs,
and the other person grabs his arms.
If one of us grabs his arms...
Suk Jin, let's go together.
[Jong Kook starting to set up defense
after hearing their talk.]
[Just come and give it a try!]
[The Red Team's home turf looking
like an iron clad defense line.]
- Don't even think about this place.
- What is all this?
Suk Jin, don't even consider
getting through this.
- The future looks bleak.
- Let's just end this.
[The Red Team makes an offer.]
[If Red Team is to win, they'll
give the Green Team two darts!]
[Green Traitors Team perking up
at the offer they're being made.]
Kwang Soo... let's go.
Let's attack.
[Extremely gullible Green Team!]
[Green Team and the Red Team
uniting to attack the Blue Team!]
[Blue Team in danger!]
[The united teams coming to attack!]
Come down, that's right!
That's good!
Bring her down!
[Si Won pulls Ace Ji Hyo down
from her spot!]
[Suk Jin starts looting
the Blue Team's cache!]
Thieves!
You have to keep your promise!
Don't forget your promise!
You really think they're going to
keep their promise?
You have to keep your promise!
[What the heck is going on here?]
Good job!
Jong Kook!
- Si Won!
- Jong Kook!
[Red Team only needs two more masks
to win the game!]
[Preparations to bring down the five masks
he kept in waiting is complete!]
Hurry up and bring it down!
- Hurry! Run!
- Bring it down!
[With Green Team on the lookout...
the other two makes a touchdown!]
[We're too late.]
Watch out for Kwang Soo though.
- Okay, I'm going to check.
- Yes.
I wrapped them all up in a bundle.
I'm going to check right now.
[Truly the Giraffe of all betrayals.]
[How did he think he'd
get away with it?]
[Just thinking about it himself
seems to bring out a laughter from him.]
[Stage 4:
Finding the 12 zodiac sign masks...]
[Red Team wins!]
[Waiting for the two darts from
the Red Team as they were promised.]
- We can give it to them, right?
- Give them what?
- The darts.
- No, you can't.
But that was the deal we made!
[They only helped because the Red Team
promised to give them two darts...]
- See?
- I told you, they couldn't be trusted.
- We helped the Red Team for the darts.
- We can't give it to them?
[They just helped another team
without any benefit to themselves.]
[Final results of the darts,
Red Team- 11: Blue Team- 10: Green Team- 4.]
Towards the escalators?
I had a feeling that we weren't going to be
allowed to give them the darts.
I knew that he'd be
very cut and dry about that.
I already knew that when I made the offer.
Come this way, Jackie.
- He looks tired.
- He said he didn't get any sleep.
I'm not tired.
- This is fun.
- You're having fun?
- We've been funny all day today.
- Yes, we've been very funny.
[Proposing that they stop being funny,
and get really competitive?]
- We have to be serious.
- Should we really win?
- Really? Should we really do this?
- Let's do it.
- Okay.
- Tr-ai-tors! Cross!
We're really going to win this.
[Disbelieving it themselves
as they say the words out loud.]
Let's do it.
I remember trying to go to a fan signing
Jackie had when I was little.
I begged my mom to take me so desperately.
He was that kind of a hero to me.
[This place is?]
[Today's final mission...
throw the golden dart!]
[Throw the dart and
hit a bulls-eye in the golden zone.]
Is that middle area the golden zone?
[The team to hit the bulls-eye in this
zone first is the ultimate winner!]
This is the final treasure hunter mission.
[To be fair, practicing is not allowed!]
Practice shots...
Ah, no practice!
No practice.
[Jackie throws one before the translator
could even tell him there's no practice.]
- But it's Jackie.
- It's Jackie.
Okay, let's go.
Don't go easy on anyone.
You have to be serious.
If I land it in there, it's over, right?
- Yes.
- First person to hit it wins?
- How many does the Red Team have?
- They have 11.
So they have one more than us.
[Si Won to throw the first dart.]
[I will win by landing it in my first try!]
[If he lands it in the golden zone, he wins!
Will he land it in the zone?]
It's okay, you did good.
[It seems he threw it a bit too hard.]
[Blue Team's Ace Ji Hyo takes a turn!]
No way... I think you may do it.
I have a feeling you may get it.
That's a really high score area.
[Big-nosed Brother
from the Green Team's turn!]
Impala, Impala!
Impala is still alive!
He used to go to dart bars
quite frequently back in his day.
He used to get yelled at all the time
by his wife for not coming home.
Don't listen to him, don't listen to him.
[I'll show you...
my dart throwing skills!]
That looks good.
[That must've been a very
long time ago...]
[Gary of the Red Team's turn!]
[Too much thinking isn't good!]
- This is all about luck and fate.
- That's right.
[It's not good to think
too little about it either...]
You should've thought about it
a little more.
[Jackie of the Blue Team's turn!]
[World action star, Jackie Chan!
Will he land it in the golden zone?]
[So close! But still much
closer to the golden zone!]
[Ha Ha of the Green Team's turn!]
Energy...
[Here, take it.]
[Ha Ha with Jackie's energy, will he?]
You should've thrown it softer.
[Mr. Capable of the Red Team!]
How many darts do they have each?
He's not good, he's not good.
Jong Kook is bad at throwing things.
[Weak skills when it comes to throwing things.]
- Jong Kook, you're not very good.
- It's okay.
[Blue Team's Jackie takes another turn!]
[Wow! So close this time again!
It may happen for sure next time!]
[With the few darts they have,
this is Kwang Soo's first and last turn.]
His first and last chance!
- Jae Suk...
- What? It's the truth.
Tr-ai-tors Cross!
[I like this guy...]
We have to keep making people laugh
since we're the funny team.
We're the comedic relief today.
[Red Team's Si Won takes
another chance!]
[Much more stable stance than earlier!]
- It's over!
- Is it over?
[Wow! A bulls-eye in the golden zone!]
[My goodness...]
[It really is a bulls-eye in the golden zone!]
[You're the best, Si Won.]
For the win today...
Si Won landed the dart in the golden zone.
Red Team is the winner of the day!
[Ultimate winners of Treasure Hunter-
The Red Team!]
[This is today's treasure: The golden boot.]
- Great job.
- Thank you.
More than anything today,
all day since early this morning...
Jackie, who's been with us today.
He really is like a brother to all of us.
[The big brother from Hong Kong, Jackie!]
[Jackie Chan is still alive!]
Seriously... I absolutely love Jackie!
[Still unable to believe that he's
been by their side all day for the show.]
Can you please say a word
to all our viewers out there?
I love you!
- This is our gift to you to keep as memory.
- Really?
Wow, thank you!
[The Red Team even happier to see him
accepting it with such a happy heart.]
These are the words he said...
Thank you so much.
[Jackie likes gold too?]
Ultimately... we're all the same!
- We're all the same!
- We are all the same!
All the same!
[Action star of the world, Jackie Chan...]
[A familiar warmth found within
the world action star...]
[Jackie Chan will forever remain
in our hearts as our hero.]
Subtitles by DramaFever
This is the secret of the nine daggers.
[The expedition that took them all throughout
Asia in search of the nine daggers.]
[The seal of the golden dagger held a
secret no one could ever have dreamed of...]
[Going back to the origin
of the ultimate dagger.]
[Leaving on a search for the temple
hidden in the depths of nature...]
[The story of their brave expedition
is about to start.]
[The person who possesses the dagger
will rule the earth!]
[The secret of the absolute dagger
is about to come to light!]
[The battle to possess the ultimate dagger!]
[Who will become the one to rule the earth
with the possession of the dagger?]
[The secret of the nine daggers...
The prequel.]
You can get some clothes shopping done here.
- This is nice.
- You like it?
Oh, you like that?
You know that scene where he gets trapped
by the truck and he's wearing the suit?
- Want some?
- Yes. Thank you.
Thank you. Wow, thank you!
He's such a caring big brother!
He's our big bro!
Do you... remember me?
Do you...