[I'm G-Dragon]
[Republic of Korea's Fashion Icon.]
[What is it that I'm doing
here right now?]
[The fiercest battle of
Running Man history starts now.]
Ji Hyo!
Subtitles by DramaFever
[One sunny day in late summer...]
[Running Man members all show up
dressed in their finest.]
[It seems as though everyone's here
dressed in their finest duds.]
Why do you look so tall?
- Are you wearing lifts?
- Why are you wearing lifts?
- It's weird to see you looking so tall.
- Gary!
My pants are too big.
[Mr. Gary dressed to the nines.]
You're not playing fair dressed like that.
[It's not your dad's suit, is it?]
- My pants are way too short.
- How are those shoes?
- What do I do about my pants?
- Your jacket is way too long.
- What's he wearing?
- Is he in a marching band or something?
[Huh?
Marching band uniform?]
- What are you wearing?
- You're dressed like Lady Gaga.
- You look great.
- Yes, thank you.
[A jacket with major shoulder padding.]
Do you think that you're a
nutcracker soldier or something?
What about you?
Do you think that you're a security guard?
- Gary put some effort into his outfit.
- Do you have a wedding to go to, Gary?
I don't know how I'm expected to live.
Why did you tell us to come
dressed like this today?
- Is it a prince theme today?
- Where's Ji Hyo?
- That's right, Ji Hyo. Where is she?
- She'll probably come out with female guests.
I see someone pulling up.
It's a big van.
[A black car pulling up just at that time.]
[Who could it be?]
[Who are these guests walking with
ease and confidence down the red carpet?]
[Big Bang's Dae Sung, G-Dragon,
and Seung Ri.]
It's Big Bang!
[With their appearance... one man
looking more pathetic than he had...]
I want to go change my clothes.
How am I expected to keep this on
with those guys on the show?
They all look so great.
[The real princes are here.]
[Man... against man.]
- Hello.
- Look how great Dae Sung looks.
You've gotten so much taller, Dae Sung.
The prince has returned.
- When did you get so tall?
- I went through a growth spurt.
- I will now announce your teams for the day.
- But why isn't Ji Hyo here yet?
Yoo Jae Suk, Gary and G-Dragon
are a team.
[Yoo Jae Suk, Gary and G-Dragon
are a team.]
- All the fashionistas are on one team.
- Yes, you're right.
[Marching band geek, Fashionista, and... ?]
You look so pathetic standing next to him.
Kim Jong Kook, Lee Kwang Soo,
and Dae Sung make up the second team.
[Kim Jong Kook, Lee Kwang Soo,
and Dae Sung are another team.]
- All the best are on one team.
- This is awesome.
[Which means, Suk Jin, Ha Ha and
Seung Ri make up the final team.]
I know what this team is all about.
- I know what your team is made of.
- What?
You're the idiot team.
Kwang Soo, your stupidness
hasn't been up to par lately.
Dae Sung is really good at being stupid,
so you'd better step up your game. Go ahead!
[No one's going to beat me today!]
I'll make sure to keep that in mind.
It's a horse drawn carriage!
It's a pumpkin carriage.
[Just then, a horse drawn
pumpkin carriage is seen pulling up.]
It's a real live horse pulling that carriage.
Why are you doing all that for Ji Hyo?
[Like a story right out a fairytale...
she arrives in a horse drawn carriage.]
- She even has a butler?
- Ji Hyo!
[She is... about to make her appearance.]
Why are you doing this?
Why are you doing this to us?
She actually looks like a princess.
[Here comes Princess Ji Hyo.]
Big Bang's here?
- You just noticed?
- Yeah, Big Bang's here.
You look kind of pretty
all dressed up like that.
Look at how Gary's dressed today.
They look like they're dressed up
for their wedding.
- This is their wedding.
- They look perfect together.
- Gary's just perfect for this role.
- And Ji Hyo's the city bride.
[Wedding for a country bumpkin groom,
city slicker princess bride.]
You two look very good together like that.
[Arm in arm... and hand in hand.]
Your mission today...
Steal Princess Ji Hyo's Heart.
[Today's mission-
Steal Princess Ji Hyo's heart.]
To the team that comes in at
first place with each of the games...
that team will win a big advantage
at the start of your final mission.
To the team that wins the final mission...
they will win something that
Princess Blank has a lot of.
- It's gold!
- It's gold for sure!
Okay, silence everyone.
[They were already being quite.]
None of us were even talking.
[He's just reading from a script...]
Princess Ji Hyo, who's been known for
being the Ace of Running Man...
she was the winner of the golden ball
in the Hong Kong episode.
That's right.
That was the biggest gold prize ever.
She won the gold badge in the special episode
when Park Ji Sung guest starred on the show.
She was the singular victor in Vietnam
in the golden turtle episode
and she took home the golden turtle.
That's right, she did.
She has the highest record for winning
the most gold prizes as a sole victor
and it won't be a stretch to say that she
took home the most gold from Running Man.
Currently, Princess Ji Hyo has enough gold
at home to be dubbed, 'Gold Ji Hyo'.
- That's amazing.
- You are amazing.
If you do a good job today,
I will gift out the gold as a royal gift.
[A job well done equals a golden royal gift!]
[A sincere round of applause
for her generosity.]
At the end of each game,
the winning team of that game
will escort Princess Ji Hyo to your next
location in a luxury sedan.
And the other two teams will move on to
the next location in a very old classic car.
- No!
-Is that the same car from last time?
Before we really get started
Princess Ji Hyo will choose the team who
will be escorting her to the first location
by seeing how well you can dance.
[Team GD- Dance time!]
One, two, three, four!
[Starting off with some flash!]
[Breaking out the moves.]
[Once their choreographed dance is over,
it's time for GD's solo dance.]
[Prince of fashion's dance time.]
[And bringing their dance move
over to Princess Ji Hyo.]
You guys are too heavy!
Just hold still!
Hold still!
What do you mean, we're heavy?
- You guys are too heavy!
- Just hold still then!
- Just hold still, Ji Hyo!
- Hold on!
[Followed by,
Team Seung Ri's dance time.]
[Huh?
They're not really in sync.]
Suk Jin's moves are too fast.
Suk Jin's moving in
the same direction as Seung Ri.
They're not dancing to the same tune.
[The princess is slowly
starting to get into rhythm.]
[Seung Ri... go!]
[Did she like their dance?]
I'm actually pretty displeased
with their dance.
- Why?
- I'm disappointed in Running Man.
Even just looking at all the teams...
There's the winning team,
second team, and we're the loser team.
- What are you talking about?
- That's a hurtful thing to hear, Dae Sung.
[How is our team lacking anything?]
No, that's not true.
- We're not lacking anything.
- Let's get the audience to vote on this.
Over three million of them will say
that we're going to come in at last place.
No one can know anything until
it's all over.
[Then will the self-proclaimed loser team
be dancing to, 'Look at us'?]
[Should I show them what I'm made of?]
[Team Dae Sung's dance time.]
Get out of the way!
[A manly move made by
only Mr. Capable!]
That was just his manly gesture.
- We could carry her all the way.
- Team Dae Sung wins!
Team Dae Sung wins!
[A woman's heart...]
[Totally confused...]
- What just happened?
- Play that song for us too.
Would the other two teams
like another chance?
Ji Hyo will soon realize who it is that
she should be watching like this song says.
We're on a totally different level
than the rest of you.
[Team GD's turn to dance to
the new song.]
[One elegant step taken
deliberately at a time.]
[What?]
[A kiss out of nowhere!]
[Oh my goodness...]
[Look at this man...]
[Congratulations!
Monday Couple's first kiss!]
[How can this be?]
No!
Get away from her!
[What is this now?]
What are you doing? She's mine!
- I said, get away from her! She's mine!
- I can do it too!
[Total chaos out of the blue.]
[And even Seung Ri?]
[A smoldering atmosphere.]
[This is how popular the princess is!]
Kissing her like that wasn't fair.
[Gary looking extremely smug
after his ambush kiss.]
- I heard a smacking sound.
- He really kissed me on my cheek.
He touched my cheek with his lips.
Don't talk to me right now.
Good job, Gary.
Even though everyone did
such a great job...
[Who will Ji Hyo choose
as her first escorts?]
[Team Seung Ri?]
[Team Dae Sung?]
[Team GD?]
- Ji Hyo.
- Kang Gary.
[Princess Ji Hyo chooses Team GD!]
That's not fair!
It's not Team Gary,
but it's Team G-Dragon.
You'd better start dating for real
after all this.
[Today's mission-
Steal Princess Ji Hyo's heart!]
[Team GD rides off in style in the luxury car
with Princess Ji Hyo in the back.]
I can't even stand to look
at them right now.
Then don't look.
GD.
- GD?
- Look at all those guys.
We're riding in this car thanks to Gary.
Come on, Gary.
[One having gotten them the victory,
Prince Gary.]
Thank you.
Wow, this is nice.
- Isn't this a nice car?
- I hope we can continue to ride in this.
[Will they be able to continue to ride
in this car to the end?]
We're to go to a rice paddy field
in Ahnpyungri.
What?
A rice paddy?
[A rice paddy...]
It's already steaming in the car.
Ouch, the seat's so hot!
Ugh, I'm already hot in this car.
Ouch, that's hot!
The outside air is actually cooler,
so let's just drive with the windows down.
[Inside air being hotter than the outside air
is the classic car's special feature?]
Wow, that is some really hot air.
- It's much cooler to have the windows down.
- Yeah, it's much cooler outside.
Ouch, that's hot!
- That's hot!
- Are you okay?
[Be cautious not to burn
your arm on the windowsill.]
- You can't touch it with your leg either.
- I think I just burned my arm.
- Princess Blank.
- Yes?
We really want to be with you all day.
- We're serious.
- He says he wants to as well.
- GD says he wants to as well.
- I really want to stay with you.
[I don't want to ride in the other car.
I really want to stay with you.]
- I get hot very easily.
- Really?
[GD can't stand to be hot.
Worried about how he'd do in the classic car.]
- He said that so timidly.
- I'll be really good to you.
He says he gets hot really easily.
[They all finally arrive
at their first location.]
[The luxury sedan with the princess inside
also pulls up elegantly to the curb.]
Time to get out of the car, Princess.
Let me get the door for you.
Please allow me.
Please watch your step.
[Princess Blank has arrived.
Everyone bow down to her.]
- Thank you.
- Please don't mention it.
[Hat parasol-
G-Dragon protecting the princess' fair skin.]
Does the air conditioner in your car work?
You guys can do better in the next round,
and find out in that car for yourselves.
We're not doing that for the car.
We'll be doing it for Ji Hyo.
Of course.
[But...]
[Not getting a very good feeling
about this place...]
This is...
- What is all this?
- What's going on here?
What is this?
[Welcome to the rice paddy.]
- They purposely filled this with water?
- Yes.
- This is really something else.
- They've got something planned for us.
[In a few moments, the fiercest battle
in Running Man history will soon start.]
Her Highness, Princess Ji Hyo
will make her entrance.
Please give her a round of applause.
- Song Ji Hyo!
- Yeah!
- I love you!
- Ji Hyo!
[A red carpet event...
on top of the rice paddy.]
- You look so beautiful!
- We love you!
- It's an honor!
- I love you!
- Ji Hyo!
- Baby!
[Everyone's calling out their own
term of endearment for her.]
- Wait for me!
- Baby face!
- Baby!
- Beautiful girl!
- Baby girl!
I can't live without you!
[I won't let you beat me!
Crooning out to Ji Hyo.]
Because you're my girl!
- How can you say that she's your girl?
- Ji Hyo!
- I feel like a 10 year old boy right now.
[Big-nosed Brother's cutesy act making others
ball up their fists in embarrassment.]
Okay, everyone.
- Here's your first mission.
- What is it?
Your first mission is...
gather up Princess Blank's flags.
[First mission-
Gather up Princess Blank's flags.]
As you can see, each team has
three flags placed in front of you.
Each of you has to get one flag each
and return to the starting line
and stick all three flags in the
stand that you see behind you.
But...
you are all aware of the rope that is used
to tie around you when you bungee jump?
You will all be tied together with the rope
so that you have to work together as one.
[Everyone will be tied together so that
they're required to work together as one.]
- What are you doing?
- We can do it without the rope.
This mission is more than possible if
you all just work together.
We have done countless tests to ensure
that the mission is more than possible.
- Let's show them how strong we are.
- We're as strong as bulls!
We will run our hardest with
only the princess in our thoughts!
What day is it today?
It's the day that we win.
- It's the say we win.
- Seung Ri! Ha! Ji! Cross!
Okay, everyone.
You've all been tied together with the rope.
[All the preparations are complete!]
At the sound of
the whistle by the Princess...
The winning team gets to ride with me
in the nice car.
[Only the winning team can move on to the next
location in the nice car with the princess.]
We can do this!
Ready!
[Princess Blank's flag race.]
[Let's go!]
[Oh my God!]
[Covered in mud as soon as
the race starts.]
[Team Dae Sung in last place all thanks
to the Mud Kwang.]
[Onward!]
[The bungee cord starting to
drag them back.]
[And the muddy rice paddy field
sucking their feet into the ground.]
[Just then, Mud Kwang races through
and starts pulling his team forward.]
[Giraffe dives to grab one of the flags.]
What is this!
What am I reduced to doing!
[Team GD also grabs one of their flags.]
[But...]
[They automatically fall back from the
unbelievable strength of the bungee cord.]
Someone help me!
[Tries to get up...
just to fall back down on their behinds.]
[Again!]
[The stately prince's third crash.]
[Meanwhile, there's Team Seung Ri,
who has yet to grab a single flag.]
Just a little bit more!
Ji Hyo!
[Team Seung Ri pulling on every ounce
of strength that they have.]
[Gets their first flag!]
[And falls on their behinds
immediately afterward.]
[An impressionable first greeting with
the rice paddy field.]
What are you doing, GD?
[Team GD and Team Dae Sung each completes
getting their first flag into the stand.]
[Blank Ji laughing and feeling bad
for them at the same time.]
[Ha Ha pulling on their cord?]
[Just then...]
[Team Dae Sung races full speed ahead!]
[We won't be stopped!]
[The bungee cord stretching long behind them.]
[Having raced up to the flag in moments
with their monstrous strengths.]
[Only Mr. Capable is left
still standing on his feet.]
[Our turn!]
[Then Team GD gets down on all fours
to crawl the rest of their way.]
[Team Dae Sung makes another attempt!]
[Who will be first to get the second flag?
Team Dae Sung, or Team GD?]
[Simultaneously!]
[Even falls down... simultaneously!]
[Just then, Team Seung Ri
races their way forward!]
[But they're looking the weakest
out of all three teams...]
[Screams that can be heard
from all three of them.]
[GD is getting a full on mud spa treatment.]
Currently, both the Yellow Team and the
Red Team only has one more flag left to go.
[Team Dae Sung vs. Team GD-
Only one more flag left to go for each team!]
We can do this.
You can do this, right?
- Let's do this!
- Let's win!
- Ji Hyo! Make sure that you see this!
- Fighting!
- We're going to win this for you!
- Start on the count of three, okay?
[Princess... we're on our way!]
One, two, three!
Run!
[Screams of their battle cry that
can be heard throughout the rice paddy.]
[The flag is right in front of their nose!]
- We have to stop them!
- Just a little bit more!
[If they can just get this flag,
the victory will be Team Dae Sung's!]
- Ji Hyo!
- We have to stop Team Dae Sung!
Pull!
[Desperately...]
Ji Hyo!
[Rushing off one more time!]
[He grabbed the flag!]
[A fiery will for their princess!]
Great job!
[Team GD just needs one more...]
Just leave me and go!
[Save the soldier from the rice paddy...]
[I want to go home...]
[Team Dae Sung succeeds in getting
all three of their flags.]
Yellow Team wins!
[Team Dae Sung wins!]
- You have to scream out Ji Hyo's name.
- Yes, this is all for Ji Hyo.
[Is that what you're supposed to do?]
If it had been anyone else but Ji Hyo,
we wouldn't have been able to do this.
[They're going a little overboard
with their fervor for Ji Hyo.]
- Ji Hyo!
- Let's go!
It's all over.
You may all go back now.
You can all just go back now.
First round is over.
The Yellow Team won.
The first round?
[You're saying that we have to
do this again?]
- This is only the first round?
- How many rounds are there?
Congratulations to the Yellow Team.
You've won the first round.
[The scary truth that this was only
the end of the first round...]
Okay, here we go.
Okay, this is the second round.
- All the rules are the same.
- Watch us win again, Princess Ji Hyo!
You're doing a great job.
- Okay, let's do this.
- Okay, everyone. Fighting!
Ready!
[This time... we will win!]
[Start the race!]
[In a flurry of movement!]
[No fear of the mud...
A battle between men for Princess Blank!]
[Acclimated to the rice paddy?
Much faster than the first round!]
[Team Dae Sung is the first
to grab their flag.]
[Team Seung Ri and Team GD
get theirs soon thereafter!]
[They need to get the flag into their post,
and come back for the second!]
[Team Dae Sung and Team GD gets back
to the starting line simultaneously.]
[Team Dae Sung's battle cry is still 'Ji Hyo'.]
Ji Hyo!
[Moving quickly forward.]
[Both teams grab their second flags.]
[Yoo Hyuk's legs give out on him.]
[Bull Kkuk passes off the flag to Dae Sung.]
[One more, and Team Dae Sung
wins again!]
[This team is busy pulling
Yoo Hyuk back to the finish line.]
[Team Seung Ri seizes this chance
to grab their second flag.]
- We are... not going to stop!
- We're not stopping! Never stop!
- Fighting!
- For Ji Hyo!
[All three teams are now fighting
to get to their last flag!]
[Big Bang...
with their teeth tightly gritted.]
[Who will be the first...
to get to their Princess Blank's flag?]
[All three teams grab their flags
by the split of a hair!]
[Must get the flag into their posts!]
[Team GD doing a backward stroke.]
[Such a close call!]
[Who will it be?]
[The last spurt!]
[Will it be Team Dae Sung...]
[Or will it be Team GD?]
[Who will be the victor of this
bloody rice paddy field mission?]
[Gary gets to it first!]
[Really by the split of a hair!]
Red Team wins!
[Second round victory goes to Team GD!]
[A day like this may never come
to GD in his lifetime again...]
- The two of us swam over here.
- You two looked very comfortable.
[Backstroking side by side.]
The two teams are currently
tied in first place.
The first team to win two rounds
is the victor of this mission.
Which means, if either the Yellow Team
or the Red Team wins one more round
then the victor will be determined.
What we want the most right now is
for the Blue Team to win this round.
[Too much of a stretch
even just to imagine it.]
- Let's just finish this right now.
- I can't even imagine that happening.
I'm going to win this round!
- Dae Sung!
- Yes?
- You look really fitting of this place.
- I think I'm made to be a farmer.
Yes, you're made to be a farmer.
This is the final round,
and this can determine the winner.
We're going to win this round,
and we're going to go one more round.
- We're Big Bang.
- No!
We're going to finish this right now.
We're going to go for another round
after this one.
- Seung Ri!
- Let's end it for sure this time.
- Fighting!
- Ready!
- Set!
[Just who will be the victor
of this fierce battle ground?]
[Or will there be another round after this?]
[Round three- start.]
[Grim determination of these nine men.]
[First flag is secured!]
[Huh?]
[They've learned a new way!
Backing this way prohibits them from falling!]
Ji Hyo!
[Back towards the flag!]
Fighting!
[Team Dae Sung secures their
second flag at an amazing speed!]
[The return of the backstroke.]
[Team Seung Ri bashes into each other
and falls down to the ground.]
This is wrong!
[Team Dae Sung already gets their
second flag into their post.]
Get it in there, Gary.
[Stay strong.]
[We have to end this now!]
[With every ounce of strength they have!]
[One final flag left to go!]
[Ah! Giraffe takes a dive
at that last crucial moment!]
[We'll get the flag...
even if it's the last thing we do!]
Just a little bit more!
[Just then...
Yoo Hyuk grabs the last flag!]
[Team GD wins as soon as they get
their flag back into the post!]
[Team Dae Sung also grabs
their final flag!]
[Will it be Team GD, or Team Dae Sung?]
[We can't lose now!]
[Who will it be?]
[Team Dae Sung succeeds in getting
their flag into the post!]
[The final score- Team Dae Sung:2,
Team Seung Ri:0, Team GD:1]
No, don't do it.
That's enough now.
[Rice paddy muddy battle-
Team Dae Sung wins!]
- Song Ji Hyo!
- Princess Song!
- Did you come up with this?
- Did I?
Do you want to die?
Why don't you give it a try?
[Team Seung Ri loses it,
and they take it out on Princess Blank.]
Why are you saying all that, Suk Jin?
Ji Hyo's our princess.
- We can't even serve her as our princess.
- You can't speak to Ji Hyo like that.
Princess Ji Hyo.
[Princess Blank making her way to her princes
to bestow the wet tissue upon them.]
Who are you?
Princess Blank.
[Princess Blank, it is I, Prince Grasshopper.]
What are you going to do?
I know you can't handle the heat, GD.
[GD's first shocking experience
with the rice paddy.]
[The truth is, Princess Ji Hyo has kept a
secret trump card hidden with her all day.]
The cards are divided into Top, Middle,
and Bottom, according to their numbers.
The team that came in at first place can
choose a card from the 'Top' level cards
second place can choose from the middle
and the loser team can choose from the bottom.
- Is this how you're really going to do this?
- I actually think that this is really fair.
What do you mean, it's a fair game?
This game was pretty much for you to win.
[Princess Ji Hyo, who knows the numbers can't
aid them during their card selection process.]
- Thank you, Princess.
- Allow me to kiss the top of your foot.
[First place winner- Team Dae Sung.
Choose from the top level cards.]
- Do we pick from this stack?
- You have to pick one of these cards.
- How about this one?
- The one in the middle?
- May we select this one?
[Thanks to the gracious Princess Blank,
they've figured out where the high card is.]
- Let's go with that one!
- Grab it!
- Go on, Dae Sung.
- The middle one!
The one in the middle!
Really?
[Which will it be?]
[Team Dae Sung chooses number 9,
the highest number in the group!]
[This is all thanks to Princess Ji Hyo!]
You have to be good to me, Kwang Soo.
I'm really going to be good to you
from now on.
I won't let him get away with it
if he doesn't.
Even though GD's done other variety shows,
he's never experienced this before.
- You all are so...
- We put everything we had in the battle.
[Putting everything they had on the line
for their Princess Blank.]
Did you see how GD's white teeth got stained
by the muddy water from the field earlier?
- GD...
- With my warmest regards...
[Second place winner- Team GD.
Must pick from the middle deck of cards.]
- Six.
- Go on and choose.
No.
[Choosing their card under
the guidance of Princess Blank.]
[As expected, they pick number 6,
the highest number from their deck!]
- Keep working hard.
- Thank you, you're so beautiful.
[And last, Team Seung Ri.]
- We can't even see, right?
- I really am a huge fan of Seung Ri's.
We'll take number three.
But what Ha Ha said earlier about
me having made up that game...
I was just asking because it was such
an amazing idea of a game.
- It was such a brilliant idea.
- He was out of his mind.
I was just saying that it
was a good idea.
Please just look at
Seung Ri's innocent face.
I just meant that it was a great game.
I'm serious.
- It was a refreshing idea.
- We should play that game every week.
- Let's play that game every week.
- Choose your card.
I will try to be as nice as I can to you.
[Bestowing her kindness upon them
for Seung Ri's sake.]
- I saw that sweet smile on her face.
- She is so kind.
[Which card did
Princess Blank direct them to?]
[The middle number, number two.]
One!
- They want to be number 1, so give them one.
- Pretend that you're happy.
As I always knew...
even your heart is so very beautiful.
What a nice day today is.
I hope that every day will be like this.
- Hey, hurry up and open the door for her.
- Hurry up and get the door open for her.
- We're ready for you, Princess!
- We're ready!
Step on me and get in the car!
Step on Kwang Soo.
Use Kwang Soo as a step to get in the car.
There you go.
Okay.
That was good.
I can't believe you really
stepped on me.
- Why wouldn't she?
- You told me to step on you!
[Princess Ji Hyo's camera falls
down to the ground!]
- Kwang Soo, her camera...
- Yes.
I'll film her myself.
You look very beautiful at this angle.
[What are you filming?
Don't play with me!]
- Kwang Soo.
- Can you switch seats with me?
- Come on, switch seats with me.
- Stop it, Kwang Soo.
Why are you doing that?
You have to take good care of her.
- Aren't you even afraid of the consequences?
- Seriously. Do it right.
Stop filming yourself, and film me.
Don't film yourself.
Isn't this car so much better
than the other one?
- Yes, it's much nicer.
- Yes.
Princess, as long as you're with us,
don't even think about doing any walking.
Do you know what
the final mission is going to be?
Of course she would know everything.
There's nothing that she doesn't know.
Even if she doesn't know,
whatever she says will become the law.
Of course, that's a given.
- Of course, she's the princess.
- Yes, you're right.
Dae Sung is very good at
serving the princess.
- Of course.
- He's very good at serving someone.
I'm a caretaker by nature.
I'm known as the caretaker
amongst all the Idols.
How did that camera ever get so lucky to
be filming you like this right now?
- Wow, that is one lucky camera.
- I really can't do this.
- Dae Sung's really good at things like that.
- I told you that I'm a known caretaker!
- Dae Sung's very good at this stuff.
- Seriously.
[Team GD having being downgraded from
the luxury sedan to the classic car.]
That first game was way too tough.
- You were laughing the whole time.
- I was laughing while I cleaned up too.
He was probably delirious.
You know why he's laughing?
It's because he can't believe what happened.
He was laughing out of disbelief
the whole time.
[Coming up to a toll.]
[He takes the toll ticket,
and sticks it up in the visor...]
[The toll ticket flies out the window!]
Hey.
The ticket flew out the window.
[Driving with the windows down...]
Did it fly away out the window?
[How could something like this
have happened?]
- What do we do, Gary?
- I can't believe we lost our ticket.
What do we do now?
[Just what else awaits this team today?]
[Second mission location-
'D' Gas station in Gyunggido.]
Where?
Where am I going?
[Making a noisy entrance with
Princess Blank in his arms.]
- Carpet! Carpet!
- Put down the red carpet!
- Quickly!
[Rushing to roll down the red carpet.]
- Hurry!
- Unroll it quickly!
- Faster!
- Get it down!
- We're all set!
- Let's go.
[After all the loud fanfare,
Princess finally makes her entrance.]
- Please use me as your step.
- But the chair is over there.
We have to roll this back up!
[Dae Sung truly is a caretaker specialist.]
We have to make sure
that the princess is comfortable.
Move it.
Move!
Princess.
You're looking beautiful as always.
[Team GD follows right behind them,
and enters like a group of gentlemen.]
Princess Ji Hyo, have you had your lunch?
What do I do if that becomes a habit?
[Will it become a habit?]
Go ahead and soak it up.
You've only got today.
I know that it's just for today.
Your next mission is,
Princess Ji Hyo's everything.
[Second mission-
Princess Ji Hyo's everything.]
- There's nothing I don't know about Ji Hyo.
- I know everything about her.
- You know what's to know about her.
- Yes, I know enough too.
You know everything, don't you?
Ji Hyo and I go to the same hair salon.
I even know all the movies,
and dramas that she's ever been in.
We're her number one fans.
57.8 kg.
- You're in big trouble now.
- What are you saying?
You know what he means when
he says, 57.8 kg?
Why do you keep doing this to me?
[Has Kwang Soo forgotten how
generous Princess Blank was to his team?]
- 42.4.
- People are going to believe 57.8 kg is real.
Then are you saying that you're not?
- We'll take care of him.
- I'm sorry!
[Finally realizing what he's done.]
- It's over for you now.
- I'm sorry.
Unless you send him away to another team,
you won't see another good card again.
Or another option for you would be to
leave him behind at this gas station.
[Hateful Giraffe...
What are you going to do now?]
We're going to be asking you questions
that are related to Princess Ji Hyo.
All three of the teams will
have to run out
and find something that is relatable
to the question that is being asked.
So there are things hidden
throughout this place?
[Go find the answer to the questions
that are being asked!]
We can win this one.
[Team Seung Ri's confident in their skills
as long as it's not something physical?]
- Okay, here's your first question.
- Yes.
This gas station is our country's
largest gas station.
You have to go and bring back the food
that Princess Ji Hyo is craving the most.
[A huge selection of food to choose from
since it's the largest gas station.]
[Just what is the menu item that
Princess Ji Hyo craves the most?]
I know what kind of food Ji Hyo likes.
I know.
I know exactly what she wants.
It's nice to be on Gary's team
when it comes to things like this.
Ji Hyo, do you want the same thing
that we shared together last week?
- You know what I'm talking about.
- So you two meet on your own privately?
[Just what is the menu item that she's
craving the most from this place?]
Okay, ready.
- Go!
- Being fast isn't necessarily good.
[The first team to bring back the food
that she wants the most wins!]
- Why are you saying that it isn't good?
- Being fastest isn't always the best.
- Think about it carefully.
- We have to hurry!
Since she's hot right now, she
wants something cool and refreshing.
- Patbingsoo.
- Yeah, she'd like patbingsoo.
And she loves waffles.
She loves sweet rice donuts.
- Or... she also likes steamed potatoes.
- Let's go with the potatoes.
Because whenever we stop by a gas station,
Ji Hyo always gets steamed potatoes.
- Ji Hyo really likes Korean style food.
- You're right. She's Korean food all the way.
- You don't think she'd want Chinese?
- No, definitely not Chinese.
- She definitely doesn't want Chinese.
- Let's go this way.
[Finally enters the restaurant area.]
- Let's get her nangmyun.
- Hurry!
[Team Seung Ri decides on nangmyun!]
Hello.
The water nangmyun.
Let's get her the water nangmyun.
[Team GD also decides
to get her the nangmyun.]
We have to buy it quickly.
Princess!
- We've brought you the menu item you wanted!
- We got it for you!
- It's your favorite steamed potatoes!
- You have to wait.
- You want us to wait?
- Lee Kwang Soo, you wait.
- Wait, she told you to wait!
- Get Lee Kwang Soo far away from me.
[Get Lee Kwang Soo
far away from her as possible.]
[Removing him right away.]
- I'll just call you when we're back in Seoul.
- Why back in Seoul?
- Nangmyun?
- Yes, nangmyun.
[Both Team GD and Team Seung Ri
are waiting for their order of nangmyun.]
They're making ours right now.
Please make it nice and cold.
Ma'am.
Can you give us two orders
of nangmyun?
- You have to wait for your turn.
- Okay.
You have to wait for your turn.
[It's down to which team's nangmyun
will come out first...]
[Only one bowl of nangmyun is out!]
Go away!
[Both teams arguing that it's theirs
and starting a tug-of-war!]
You guys can't do this!
[Just then, another bowl comes out!]
[Which team will be first to
serve their bowl to Princess Blank?]
[GD takes the bowl and runs!]
[Team Seung Ri is right on his tail!]
[Princess Blank, your nangmyun is coming!]
[Team Seung Ri's nangmyun arrives!]
[Even though it spilled onto the tray a bit,
it was a speedy delivery!]
But we got it for you quickly!
We forgot the chopsticks!
[They forgot to grab
the chopsticks in their haste...]
- What happened?
- They forgot their chopsticks.
This is so unfair, Princess Ji Hyo.
We got here first.
Get back here!
Why do you always become such a jerk
whenever you're on Running Man?
- Get back here!
- What happens to you on this show?
Why do you become such a jerk
when you're on this show?
You have to get out of the way!
[Princess Blank enjoying her
bowl of nangmyun.]
- What are you guys doing?
- Can you try our potato?
- She already tried it.
- I had some.
Didn't you even see me eating it?
Just don't even open your mouth!
Keep your mouth shut!
What's wrong with you?
Kwang Soo, you should just grab
a bus back to Seoul.
[That's the best way for you
to help your team...]
We have seen Princess Ji Hyo enjoying this
steamed potato many a times.
We thought that she'd enjoy eating
something simple such as this.
Yes, the potato.
[Could the steamed potato really be what
Princess Blank is craving?]
[Team Dae Sung's steamed potato-
The wrong answer.]
You guys are totally wrong.
Get out of the way.
[Team Seung Ri immediately followed
by serving her their nangmyun.]
We were faster, and they cheated.
[Team GD and Team Seung Ri
both brought her the nangmyun.]
But they spilled their nangmyun
all over their tray.
- They cheated.
- Nangmyun is best on a hot day like this.
If nangmyun is the correct answer,
will you choose between the two nangmyuns?
Okay, I will.
Then both teams, go back and redo it.
- It's not this either?
- No, this isn't it either.
[Team GD and Team Seung Ri-
Nangmyun is not the correct answer.]
She will choose one person that she likes
to give a hint to.
[Princess Blank will choose one person to
give a hint to as to what she wants.]
[If they want to receive the hint,
they have to earn her favor...]
- I've repented for my behavior.
- Princess.
[G-Dragon putting on his best
cutesy act for the princess.]
What are you doing?
That's cheating!
- What are you doing?
- You can't do that!
[Even just gazing upon her
has a powerful effect.]
[Thanks to GD's cutesy act,
Team GD earns themselves a hint.]
There you go again telling me
how much you love me.
Just tell me the hint.
I already know that you love me.
These two really are cracking me up lately.
- It's red.
- Come on, hurry!
- What is it?
- It's ddukbokki.
[Hearing her say the word, 'red'
has him running off to buy her ddukbokki.]
Hurry!
Come on, hurry!
Come on, Jae Suk!
Where is it?
[Red in color- The item
that she wants the most is...]
[The correct answer is, Jjamppong.]
[The gas station food item she wants
the most is, jjamppong.]
Princess!
- Princess!
- What is it? I can't see what it is.
[Ah... ddukbokki...]
It's red in color!
Red in color, wrong!
[To run off so single mindedly like that
without even thinking about it first...]
It's a noodle dish.
I gave you all my hints.
[Red in color, and a noodle dish.
Can they figure it out this time?]
- I think it's jjamppong. A noodle dish.
- Really?
[Oh... Gary's quick to figure it out.]
- Jjamppong?
- Yeah.
Jjamppong?
[Team Seung Ri brings back
buckwheat noodles.]
- Oh no!
- This isn't it?
- I'm sorry, but this isn't it.
- Why are you so picky?
[Oh yeah?]
- No hint for you.
- He was just kidding.
I'm so sorry.
- We want to know.
- It's red.
Ramyun?
Jjamppong?
- It's jjamppong.
- It's jjamppong, isn't it?
[It seems as though Team Seung Ri
has also figured it out!]
Let's just go with jjamppong.
If we have to come back,
might as well be quick.
- Jjamppong?
- Yes, jjamppong.
China.
- China?
- Jjajangmyun in this weather?
China.
It's one or the other.
[One or the other?
Main representative Chinese dish.]
- Ji Hyo likes jjamppong.
- Yeah, she loves jjamppong.
- She likes jjamppong.
- Doesn't she prefer jjajangmyun?
[Even though they eat together often,
they're getting confused all of a sudden.]
- You have to give it to us first.
- No, give it to us at the same time.
You're the best!
I'm sorry, but please keep your eyes forward.
- Ma'am!
- Make it look pretty.
We don't need all that.
- Hurry! We were first!
- Give us ours first!
[Which team will get it first?]
[Sensible enough to give it to the
two teams at the same time!]
[It's now all down to
a matter of speedy delivery!]
Hurry!
[That's it!]
[Team GD's Jae Suk succeeds
in blocking their path.]
[Team GD takes that opportunity
to take the lead!]
[Thanks to Jae Suk's interference,
Team Seung Ri's in danger!]
[Team GD ultimately serves their
bowl of jjamppong first.]
They keep following us and
doing what we do.
- Why do you keep copying us?
- No, we got our own hint.
[Team Seung Ri is one step late
in serving up their bowl.]
Why do we keep doing this?
[Feeding her a spoonful of
broth to start out with first.]
- She tried ours first.
- You won't leave her side.
Princess!
We got the combo that you wanted!
- Your combo!
- Here's your combo!
[Team Dae Sung- Here's your combo.]
- The combo is the best!
- Why don't you give ours a try?
[Unsure of which dish to pick,
they decide to go with both.]
[That's pretty smart.]
First, thank you everyone for your efforts.
- The food that I like is...
- Yes?
Combo, combo, combo!
- Jjamppong.
- Jjamppong!
[The correct answer is, jjamppong!]
Red Team wins one point.
[Team GD wins themselves a point
for being the first to deliver.]
- Okay, here's your next question.
- Okay.
If you look behind you
at this gas station...
there's a playground where
you can bring your dog to play.
There are a total of ten different
types of dogs in there right now.
They are all different breeds of dogs.
Princess Ji Hyo is going to choose the dog
that she likes the most out of that bunch.
So all the men have to guess which
breed it is that she likes the best
and you have to bring that
dog back here.
Isn't it the one that's already here?
'Gae'? (Gae means Dog)
[Which breed is Ji Hyo's favorite?]
Okay, everyone turn around.
Princess Ji Hyo already made her choice.
She chose her favorite dog.
Go!
One dog per person!
It's possible that Ji Hyo doesn't know
the names of the different types of breeds.
See?
There's even a bulldog.
It's possible that Ji Hyo might like
a dog that's rather on the uglier side.
- Yeah, you're right.
- Ugly, yet cute.
[Ugly, yet cute?]
[A black sheepdog?]
[But...]
[You thought that you'd be able to
get these dogs easily, didn't you?]
[Catch the dog inside her heart!]
[Total chaos breaks out all
over the place.]
[This is unbelievable.]
[Please stop!]
Come over here.
What about this one?
Are there any treats around here?
Okay, come over here.
Aren't you a cutie!
[A really huge dog!]
Okay, come with me.
Come this way.
Okay, here you go.
Wow, you're so strong!
You're so cute.
[Ha Ha's selection...]
[A tiny Yorkshire Terrier.]
Come with daddy.
[So adorable.]
[Seung Ri's trying to make friends
with a dachshund.]
[G-Dragon chooses a sleek poodle.]
Did you pick a fashionable dog
because you're a fashionista?
- Don't most women like poodles?
- That's a poodle?
- Why is it so big?
- Look at all the hair on its butt.
That's the one!
[Mr. Capable bringing a bulldog,
which is of his similar build.]
Haru... come on, Haru.
Haru.
[Papillion, Haru-
Not making it easy for anyone to get close.]
Haru.
Come on, Haru.
[Jae Suk really seems to want this dog.]
[Giraffe barges in uninvited.]
Where do you think you're going?
What are you doing?
- What are you doing?
- I've been keeping my eye on her.
Do you know how much work I've
already put in on Haru?
- I've had my eye on her from the beginning.
- What are you talking about?
Haru.
[It seems as though they're both
intent on taking Haru, the Papillion.]
Stop barging in.
What do you think you're doing?
- We've already made friends.
- Haru.
[In the meantime, everyone is carefully
making their way back with their dogs.]
You are so cute.
Here they come.
- This is Lauren.
- She's so cute!
My name is Lauren,
and I'm a Yorkshire Terrier.
- Hi!
- My last name is 'Yo'.
[Could this adorable Yorkshire Terrier
be Ji Hyo's choice?]
I brought one here.
- It was so hard to catch this guy.
- Really?
- But I thought that you'd like him.
- He's so...
Today is his first birthday.
- He just turned one.
- He just turned one?
He's a St. Bernard, and his name is Barry.
Here he is.
[Everyone starting to show up one by one
with the dog of their choosing.]
[Ha Ha's Yorkshire Terrier, Lauren.]
Suk Jin.
- Excuse me.
- Let me show you his face.
[He's trying to formally introduce his dog,
but the dog isn't even budging.]
There you go.
Come on, Barry.
My dog is a St. Bernard... wait.
Sit.
Hey!
[Free-spirited Barry.]
We'll just stay that you're not even here.
You can come back later.
CoCo is a Border Collie.
He's a popular dog among the nobles.
- He originates from Scotland.
- Aren't they used for sheep herding?
He herds sheep and everything else.
- Poodle.
- Poodle?
If anything,
I think the dog is GD's style.
Women loves poodles
because they're so pretty.
This is a poodle.
She's actually a standard poodle.
[A fashionista of a dog that seems
very suitable to GD.]
- This is Sophie.
- And her name is Lauren.
You're in trouble now.
You're starting to pant now.
[It's hot...]
- Your tongue's all twisted sideways.
- Hey!
[I'm leaving if you're not going to
give me any water.]
- Hey!
- If you leave, then you're out of the game.
Can't you just please just sit still?
[Brings out a bowl of water for
all the dogs.]
[Jong Kook's bulldog, Leo is the first to go.]
- You don't think they'll fight?
- No, they won't fight.
[Bulldog Leo not budging from his place,
and lapping up the water.]
You can't drink up all the water
by yourself.
- Guys, get some water too.
- Hang on a second.
[Other dogs aren't able to get water
because of Leo standing in the way...]
- Get your dog out of the way!
- Why? He's just thirsty.
Just leave him alone!
He's just thirsty!
- Get him out of the way.
- There are other dogs waiting.
Tell him to stop drinking up
all the water.
[How is it that he found a dog
that is so similar to him?]
- Don't you see the other dogs waiting?
- Go on and some water.
- Barry, come on.
- Go on and get some water.
[Just then, Kwang Soo finally arrives
with his dog.]
[Russell Terrier, Jay.]
That dog looks exactly like you.
[The dog really does look like him!]
You all did a great job.
[Which of these dogs will Ji Hyo choose
as her favorite?]
- Is your favorite dog here?
- Yes, it's here.
[The dog that Ji Hyo likes the most is...]
- Is your favorite dog here?
- Yes, it's here.
[Ji Hyo's favorite dog is...]
[The bulldog!]
[Mr. Capable's bulldog from
Team Dae Sung is the correct answer!]
See?
I told you.
Why do you think Ji Hyo likes
Gary so much?
I'm starting to feel even more
confident now.
- I feel more confident now.
- So looks aren't your priority, Ji Hyo?
[This is Princess Ji Hyo's perfect style.]
Thus, Yellow Team gains themselves a point.
[Team Dae Sung gains a point!]
[Team GD guesses the last question correctly,
and they are the ultimate winner.]
- I won't give you any hints this time.
- So we just pick one?
[Team GD must pick a card
from the top deck.]
[Team GD chooses number eight!]
Okay, we chose one.
One, two, three.
[Team Dae Sung chooses number five.]
[Team Seung Ri chooses number three.]
['T' waterpark in Yi-cheon.]
What is this now?
- Are we going to be walking on water?
- I see something floating on the water.
- Ugh, the water's so cold!
- It's cold?
The water's cold?
[Huh? They're walking on water?]
That's so amazing.
How is it possible that a human being
can walk on that thin little mat?
[This is the fascinating water mat
that floats on top of the water.]
Come one everyone.
Seung Ri.
What's wrong?
Come on in.
[Unable to find his balance and falls in.]
[Even though they're all wavering,
they're able to remain standing.]
Thank you all for waiting patiently.
Here comes Princess Song Ji Hyo.
[Princess Ji Hyo makes her entrance.]
This is going to end today, right?
She's not going to get a single one
of her toes wet today, is she?
[Blank Ji is having a hard time getting
used to her treatment today as well.]
[I'm Princess Ji Hyo.]
- You look beautiful.
- You really do look pretty.
This game is called,
'Serve Princess Blank Your Rose'.
There are three people per team.
Three people must take turns
and they'll have to jump rope a total
of 30 times from where Dae Sung is sitting.
- On this mat?
- Yes, a combination of 30.
Once you've completed all 30 jump ropes,
one person will run down the length of the mat
with a rose in their hand for the princess
and they'll have to jump and
throw their rose to Princess Blank.
Once the rose is thrown, Princess Blank will
catch the rose if she likes that person.
Or she can avoid catching
the rose as well.
I love you, Princess!
You should've told us from the beginning
that there was going to be a game like this.
Wow, today really is...
today really is a great day for me.
The total time that you have to get the
flower into Princess Blank's basket is...
one minute.
- We're ruined because of Kwang Soo.
- Why?
You have to complete your 30
jump ropes within that minute
and all the members have to
participate in the jump roping.
Okay, we will now start the game.
Okay!
[Mission- Start.]
[Team Dae Sung to take the first turn.]
[This is the water float jump roping.]
[I bet you'll find that it's harder
than jump roping on the firm ground.]
[Takes the plunge into the water.]
- We have to get the rose!
- You do it.
[22 jumps still left to go.]
- Hurry!
- Why is there so much water on this mat?
It snapped!
That's what you deserve!
- The rope snapped!
- Fail!
[Kkuk power- fail.]
I haven't even had my turn yet!
[Team Seung Ri takes their turn
with a new jump rope in hand.]
You should do 28 jumps.
[Poor Seung Ri...]
Ready!
[He's good!]
[He's already done 15 all on his own!]
[Even Princess Blank is surprised.]
You've done 23!
[Current count, 23.]
[Passing it off to Haroro after 27 jumps.]
You have to do it too.
[Passes it off to Suk Jin after one jump.]
- You have to do two.
- I have to jump two.
[The rose can get on its way
as soon as Suk Jin does his two jumps.]
[But he has awful jump rope skills.]
[Are you guys ever going to come?]
[After all the frustration,
he finally completes the 30th jump.]
[On his way to Princess Blank!]
[Seung Ri running and parting the water.]
Hurry!
[Shoots the rose!]
[Too short.]
[Time's Up]
[Team GD's turn.]
[Laying down side by side?]
Why do you guys look so sexy?
[Throw it over here.]
[Wow... 18 jumps!]
[Experienced boxer,
Gary's blinding jump roping skills.]
[Gets the count up to 29 in a blink of an eye
and passes it off to GD.]
You just need to do one!
[Huh?
An acrobatic move?]
[Regardless, completes 30,
and on their way!]
[So close!]
[Could she have done that on purpose?]
Ji Hyo!
[Catch my rose!]
[One more chance at a success rides on GD!]
[Will the rose make it into the basket?]
Red Team succeeds!
[A perfect rose goal!]
[Suddenly, something is starting
to feel off.]
Isn't he supposed to get
back on his feet?
[GD's fall onto his back...
will that count against their success?
- He jumped over the rope.
- But he was lying down.
He didn't get back up on his feet.
In jump rope, you jump off your
feet and land on your feet.
But he landed on his butt
and stayed down.
- How did he jump rope with his butt?
- He sat down on his butt.
He totally sat down.
We all saw that.
G-Dragon fell down like this.
- How can you call that jump roping?
- He really did just sit down.
But he still jumped the rope.
In that case, it's too ambiguous for
the staff to make the call on this one.
We will leave the decision up to
Princess Blank's judgment call.
Okay.
Red Team's win is invalid!
[Do it again.]
[Their complaints succeeded!]
[Celebration breaks out.]
- Okay.
- In that case...
Since the Princess ruled it invalid
the Red Team will get the chance to
make their second attempt first.
[Team GD gets the first chance at the second
attempt from having their win overruled.]
- You can do that for them, right?
- Sure, let them go.
We normally wouldn't do it,
but we'll do it because of G-Dragon.
Ready.
[Boxer Gary to start it off again.]
You're doing great.
[Mr. Random Capable jump roping
at lightening speed.]
[Quickly completes 26 jumps.]
[Easily completes the three jumps.]
[Now it's all up to G-Dragon.]
[Succeeds in completing 30.]
[Are they going to dispute that too?]
That doesn't matter.
[Princess Blank...]
[Please accept my rose!]
[Ah...]
[Next up is, Gary!]
Catch it, Ji Hyo!
[Not even a chance, and fails.]
[GD rushes forward without
any hesitation.]
[The gap having been widened
the width of the Han River.]
- They pulled the mat back! It's too far!
- They can't pull the mat back!
[Their coordinated plan to
ruin the chances of Team GD's success.]
Did you know that the gap now is
over a hundred meters?
They can't pull the mat back like that.
Okay, then... from now on,
no more pulling of the mat!
[Breaking out into the unity song again.]
You're the most hateful one of the bunch!
Ready, set!
[Team Seung Ri's turn.]
[Seung Ri's jump roping skills are
impressive in its own right.]
[Already having completed 20 jumps
without even breaking.]
[27 jumps!]
[Haroro jumps two jumps,
and passes it off to Suk Jin.]
[They just need one more...
will Big-nosed Brother pull through?]
[Easily succeeds.]
[Giraffe, the king of interference.]
[A head on collision with the rolled up mat.]
[Giraffe using all sorts of methods
to interfere in other's game.]
[The rose doesn't even come close.]
[Second runner, Big-nosed Brother!]
[The mat is already twisted around
all thanks to the Giraffe's interference.]
What are you doing?
[Big-nosed Brother also fails.]
[Time over]
Hey, Lee Kwang Soo.
You just wait for your turn.
You did good, Kwang Soo.
It looked like a wave.
[A manmade mat wave.]
[Kwang-seidon calling forth the waves.]
- Do you all have your roses?
- Yes.
One, two, three...
[Gary, the jump roping machine.]
[Unbelievable speed.]
[He's jumping as if
he's jumping on solid ground.]
[Completes 28 jumps
without even breaking a sweat.]
[Wow, he's good.]
[They just need to complete
one jump each.]
[Falls down on his butt again.]
[Success]
[Yoo Hyuk on his way!]
[Huh?]
Seriously!
You guys are going too far!
[Haroro is behind Princess Blank?]
Come on.
[Where is Princess Blank going?]
[Not even close...]
- Ji Hyo!
- No!
[GD's rose is their last chance!]
- What are you doing!
[Fail]
That's too bad.
I thought that was going to make it in.
Let's do it!
No more interfering with each other
from now on!
- No more interfering!
- Let's play a fair game.
[A call for a truce to stop interrupting
that's always in words only.]
You just be quiet.
We'll take care of ourselves.
[You just wait and see!]
Okay.
[Team Dae Sung's turn.]
[Muscle Boy kicking up a lot of water.]
[Trips over the rope at 18.]
Pass it on if you're caught on the line!
[Can't hear you.]
[Completes 28 jumps by ignoring
the Giraffe.]
[They just need one jump each
for them to succeed this step.]
[There's never anything easy with him...]
[Succeeds in jumping 30.]
[Dae Sung makes his way.]
[An aggressive interfering tactic.]
[Next runner, Kkuk.]
[The Tiger's jump.]
- What the heck?
- What was that?
[Now he just has to shoot!]
[The final runner, Giraffe.]
[Time over]
- Let's play it fairly from now on.
- Seriously, no more interference from now on.
[The never-ending battle of interference.]
Since you guys started it,
you guys figure out how to end it.
Okay!
Leave it to us!
- We can stop this ourselves.
- Let me borrow a pair of scissors!
Okay.
Let's just do this for the next eight weeks
for the sake of entertainment.
[They're planning on seeing how far
they can take the battle of interference?]
Make sure that you throw it far
so that Ji Hyo can catch it.
- Please catch it!
- Fighting!
I want to give myself to you!
What's wrong with his voice?
Ready.
[Team Seung Ri- Start.]
[Explosive jump rope skills.]
[Completes 27 jumps and then
passes it on.]
[Ro-Ro to complete the final jump.]
[30 complete!]
[Princess Ji Hyo!]
[Wow! The rose makes the goal!]
[Big-nosed Brother does it!]
[Haroro makes his dash for it!]
[Catch it!]
[What's going on here?
Haroro too? Two goals in a row!]
[Will Seung Ri make it too?]
[Bravo!
All three of them succeed!]
[Unbelievable!]
Blue Team come forward and
receive the top card.
[Team Seung Ri receives the top card
from having come in at first place.]
Thank you, Princess.
[Team GD receives the middle card
for having come in at second place.]
[Team Dae Sung receives the final bottom card
for having come in at last place.]
[Oops...]
[They're happy?]
Let's just go.
[The final mission.]
[Just what is the final battle
that awaits them here?]
[Yi-cheon Art Hall.]
Look at the red carpet.
What is this?
I feel like something really
substantial is going to happen here.
[Princess Ji Hyo is asked to wait outside.]
- We'll see you soon.
- I'll see you later.
[Team GD also makes their entrance.]
There's a door over there.
What is this?
[All three teams gathering at the location
of their final mission.]
[The final competition...]
[Just who will the victory go to?]
[Princess Ji Hyo is seated upon her throne.]
Please have a seat.
[And she's handed four cards?]
This is your final mission.
Each of the teams has received
three cards thus far.
Princess Ji Hyo currently holds four cards
numbered from ten through thirteen.
You will each trade in one of your cards for
a card that she holds in her hand.
[Trade in one of their cards for a high
numbered card Ji Hyo holds in her hand.]
You have trade in your card one at a time
to a total of three times.
Then the team with the final count of
the highest number will be the final winner.
So this is all about luck.
So highest number wins?
If even after all the cards
have been exchanged...
the total count of the cards
that Princess Ji Hyo holds...
is higher in count that the cards
that you all hold in your hand...
then Princess Ji Hyo will be
the sole winner of all the gold.
No!
Stop it with that.
- Are you all ready?
- Yes.
[Round one- Start.]
- The team that won the last round?
- That's us.
Then your team will start
the exchange process.
We have to be careful with
what we choose.
I think this will be the best choice.
[Must choose the higher card from
Princess Ji Hyo's deck for a chance to win.]
[Cards that the Princess holds in
her hands are... 10, 11, 12, 13.]
I hope you pick a good one.
I mixed them all up, so I don't know.
[Which card will Seung Ri choose?]
Is it okay if we look?
We can look, right?
[Their card selection is 11.]
Do we have to mix up all
four cards now?
No, you mix up only the three cards.
[Take out the card they just picked,
and mix up their three original cards.]
Picking last would be the least
advantageous.
[Of these cards...]
[The Princess needs to pick the lowest number
for them to have a chance at winning.]
[Just which one of the three
did she choose?]
[She chooses number seven,
the highest number from their deck!]
It's our turn now.
This is pretty thrilling.
[Time to exchange with Team GD.]
She will now mix up all four
of her cards.
[She can now mix up all four cards including
the one she just picked.]
We really needed to win the last game.
[The later the team gets to pick,
the more disadvantageous it is for them.]
Let's pick a good one.
[GD to choose the card.]
[Is he trying to see through the cards?]
No, I don't think that was the right card.
[Completes his card selection.]
I can guess from her expression.
- What if you took our original card?
- You did fine.
[Wow! He chooses the high card,
number 12!]
[Trying to control his facial expression.]
We're curious to see if it's our card.
Their original cards weren't bad, right?
[It's now Princess Ji Hyo's turn to pick.]
[Please let it be the four.]
[It is now Team Dae Sung's turn.]
Why do I feel so nervous?
Just pick one.
My lucky right hand!
- My right hand!
- Your lucky right hand?
[Which card did Dae Sung's
lucky right hand pick?]
- There's just one card here.
- Don't show anyone.
- There can be only one choice.
- Show the camera your card.
[Huh?
What's wrong?]
[His reaction is a bit...
Is he laughing over a low number?]
Why do you think that I'm
laughing right now?
It can only be one card,
so what's the number?
[Of all the cards in Ji Hyo's hand...
he has to pick 6 of all numbers?]
Maybe your hand is a bit... cursed?
[Thus, Jong Kook takes the cards from
Dae Sung's hand to mix it up himself.]
Pick the highest number.
- That's the right one.
- Wow.
- She picked the high card, didn't she?
- I heard Dae Sung say they're in trouble.
- I feel bad she picked such a low card.
- You can quit the act now.
You can stop it now.
We've already figured you out.
- Round one is now over.
- Yes.
- Fighting!
[It's getting more and more crucial
to choose the right card.]
[Is it an act?
Or is the laughter for real?]
[Wow! He chose a high card!]
[Will she take their low card?]
That's what I thought.
[Team Seung Ri feeling flustered?]
Did they lose the card that
they picked earlier?
[But the truth is,
it was one of their low cards!]
[Their count went to 23 from 16.]
[Team GD's second exchange opportunity.]
[Why are you grabbing her wrist?]
Why are you grabbing her hand?
[He picks her highest card!]
Look at the way he's acting.
He picked a good card.
[His expression that he cannot
keep hidden.]
[It would be amazing for them if Ji Hyo
just picked their number four card.]
What do I do?
You may now exchange your card
with Kwang Soo.
[Princess Ji Hyo starting to feel danger.]
[Kwang Soo from Team Dae Sung's turn.]
He's famous for his failures.
[This could put Princess Ji Hyo
in extreme danger.]
- Please trust me on this one.
- You should pick from the left.
- Two or a six.
- It'll be one of those two.
[Huh... what is it?]
[Figures...]
[Bad luck Giraffe...
He picked the lowest number she had.]
- You can't give each other any signals.
- None of us here has any luck.
[At this rate, they can only hope that
Princess Ji Hyo takes their lowest card.]
Please let it be the low card.
[The card she picked... is one!]
[Could there still be hope for them?]
Okay, round two is now over.
[Team Seung Ri- 1, 10, 11.
A total of 23.]
[Team GD- 4, 12, 13. A total of 29.
Team Dae Sung- 3, 5, 6. A total of 14.]
This is the final round.
[The winner will be determined after
this final round of exchange!
We've got nothing.
Do you have a lot of low numbers?
I don't know either.
I haven't really checked.
[Team Seung Ri still has a
chance at a win.]
[Will he pick her high card?]
Please.
Look at his expression.
[The other teams bursts out in laughter.]
We're all set!
[Just what is the number
that he chose?]
[Their selection will determine their fate.]
- This is really nerve-wrecking though.
- I'm getting nervous too.
[There's only one card that they
want the Princess to take.]
[Just which one of these cards
did she take?]
I don't know, but I'm just going to pick!
[Jae Suk from Team GD's turn.]
[A anxiety ridden moment.]
I don't know what's what either.
To you...
I hope that this got to you.
[Huh? What is
that expression on his face?]
[Are they trying to control
their facial expression again?]
[Or did he really pick a lower card?]
[Just what is the card
that he picked?]
[A good sign for Team GD who's been
in first standing until round two?]
[But they still have two high cards left...]
[His expression is...]
- She just took their high card.
- I knew it!
[Did Princess Ji Hyo really take
their high card?]
Princess!
Let's do this!
[Kkuk's final selection.]
[Is he calling on his psychic powers?]
[It's coming.. the feeling is coming.]
You got it, Jong Kook.
[Checking his card.]
Please show the camera your card.
It's nothing, is it?
I don't think he got anything.
[The work of God?
The number one is back in their hands.]
We got it.
Jong Kook did it.
Jong Kook is Jong Kook!
It's Song Ji Hyo's turn to make
her very last selection.
[Team Dae Sung only has
all the low cards.]
Ji Hyo's going to pick their high card.
I bet they lost an important card.
Okay, all three rounds are now over.
As you can all see,
Song Ji Hyo has four cards.
- So it gives her an advantage.
- Yes, it does.
Thus, the three team must discuss and
agree on which card she must discard.
Yes, that's more fair.
[The three teams must agree on which
card she must discard.]
[One of the men has to pick one of her
cards that she must discard.]
[Gary chosen to choose one of her cards?]
Gary must go in front of Ji Hyo...
and choose which one of her cards
she must discard.
[This selection can determine
who the victor will be.]
[Princess Ji Hyo mixed up her cards
without looking herself.]
[Just... which card will she
have to discard?]
[Gary chooses one of her cards.]
So Gary's selection will
determine Ji Hyo's fate.
It's all on Gary.
I did what I thought
would be best for the princess.
All three teams and Princess Ji Hyo
now have three cards each.
- Yes.
- In that case...
We will now start with Team Seung Ri,
who was first to make their exchange.
Please reveal your cards one at a time.
Please reveal your cards.
[Not a bad number.]
[Already at 17?
Team Seung Ri has a rather high count!]
Ha Ha.
Reveal your card.
You had me scared there for a moment.
This is the level we are.
Team Seung Ri has a total of 19.
[Team GD starts off with four.]
I hope that you continue like that.
There it is!
- I'm sorry.
- There it is!
[The highest card in the game!]
[Team GD, a total of 25.]
Lee Kwang Soo, please show your card.
That card came from us.
That was our card.
[Even their next card is meager.]
They have no chance of winning.
And finally, Kim Jong Kook.
[Oh my...]
What the heck!
They have no chance whatsoever.
[All three cards don't even
add up to 10...]
- You picked this, and made its way back.
- Seriously?
Song Ji Hyo, please show your card
one at a time.
[Time for Princess Ji Hyo to show her cards.]
- Wow... it's 12.
- What is it?
- 12?
- Yeah, she just showed 12.
- That's the first card you show?
- She already has us beat.
- I really had no idea what I had.
- She beat us with just one card.
This really is a stab to our pride.
Please reveal  your second card.
[Next card is, nine!]
[That was originally
Team Dae Sung's card.]
- Song Ji Hyo, please show your last card.
- Let's see what her final card is.
[What is her final card?]
[If the card is lower than four,
then Team GD wins!]
[But if the card is higher than four,
then Princess Ji Hyo wins!]
Wow!
[Her final card is 11!]
- She doesn't have a single low card.
- Which card did she discard?
[The card that Gary discarded was...]
Even her lowest number would've
made her win.
[Number six was her lowest card.]
[An astounding total of 38.]
[Princess Ji Hyo wins!]
[Jaw dropping prize.]
There it is!
Song Ji Hyo!
[Ji Hyo takes the gold yet again!]
There's something with you and gold.
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Madame Go Dong Wan's
family reunion.]
[Running Man's special family reunion.]
[The youngest son, Yoo Ah In.]
[And the nation's leading mom,
Kim Hye Sook.]
It seems that the time has come to pass down
my fortune that I've worked so hard to amass.
There's nothing I won't do in order
to get my hands on that fortune.
[Inheritance project.]
[Just which family member will inherit
grandmother's fortune?]