[Last scorching summer...]
[2012 Running Olympics]
[The ambitious Idol Team wins!]
[A rematch they've been waiting for!
Opening of 2013 Running Olympics!]
[Running Man Team full of revenge vs.
And an even more ambitious Idol Team!]
[The real competition starts now!]
[Running Olympics real face-off!
The terrorizing Bell Race.]
[Running Olympics 2013 - Starts now!]
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Gimpo International Airport]
[2013 Running Olympics]
- If it's Olympics, then it's Idol guests.
- It's the Olympics today?
As you can see behind you...
this is the 2013
Running Olympic Opening ceremony.
Last summer, when it was
Running Man Team vs. Idol Team...
you remember that Olympic competition?
Of course, we remember.
[Ambitious Idol Team vs.
overly confident Running Man Team.]
[Even though they competed with gritted teeth,
Idol Team ultimately wins.]
You will be competing in this winter Olympics
with an even more ambitious Idol Team.
Please turn your attention
to the entrance gate.
[First member of the Idol Team
makes their entrance.]
[Idol stars carrying the weight
of the Hallyu wave on their shoulders.]
[Makes their entrance through the
arrival gate.]
- Is it a girl?
- Who is it?
[The star with a unisex hairstyle
making their entrance.]
- That's a girl.
- No, it's a guy.
- It's totally a guy.
- But the person is walking like a girl.
Hello!
[The perpetual kid, Kwang Hee.]
Hello.
It's me, the trendy Kwang Hee.
[A raucous entrance.]
We've got ourselves a loud one here.
- Kwang Hee...
- Can you be more welcoming?
Why aren't you being more welcoming?
Are there more guys or girls back there?
It's a total guy fest back there.
Really?
- Kwang Soo...
- Yes, Jae Suk?
Kwang Hee plays your role on that team.
Come on, Jae Suk.
What do you mean, my role?
- What is my role?
- Kwang Hee and Kwang Soo.
[A matching role even just from
the 'Kwang' in their name?]
Two 'Kwang's...
We will welcome our next Idol.
Who is it?
[The next Idol member is...]
[Shinee's Min Ho.]
[Min Ho, whose name is synonymous with
'ambition' makes his entrance.]
- Min Ho...
- He's Kim Jong Kook of the Idol team!
- Min Ho is...
- He really is good looking, isn't he?
[Kkuk's gym buddy.]
Min Ho's really athletic,
and his competitive streak is no joke.
- He's the best even among the other Idols.
- Of course, he is.
Min Ho is a Dream Team member.
We have a Dream Team member
amongst us too.
- He's of the past though.
- What do you mean, the past?
- He's the older kid.
- Jong Kook is old now.
[Dream Team vs. Dream Team Classic.]
[Idol Team's next member]
[F(x)'s Sulli]
Sulli!
[An extreme welcome.]
- Yeah... I knew Sulli would be on today!
- It's been so long!
- Get back in line. Get back!
- Have you been well?
- Give it a rest!
- Wait... wait a second.
When I came on earlier, it was,
'Oh hey, you're here.'
But look at how you're all
jumping all over each other now.
It was worse for Kwang Hee, Min Ho.
I got scolded for coming on the show.
- I got scolded.
- Sulli is here!
- Sulli...
- Hello!
You've gotten so much cuter!
The atmosphere around here seems
to have brightened immensely now.
- Yeah, this is much better!
- I feel so much happier now.
[And the next Idol member...]
[Idol Ace, Yong Hwa.]
Yong Hwa's competitive streak
really is no joke.
Why did you post my name tag
on the web?
[Yong Hwa, eliminating Mr. Capable's
name tag just two weeks ago!]
[Proof of Kim Jong Kook's
name tag in his custody.]
- Why did you have to put it up there?
- I know exactly what you felt!
[The taste of posting
Mr. Capable's name on display.]
Who is that now?
[MBLAQ's Lee Joon.]
[As soon as they see his face, all
the nervousness flows out the window.]
We won!
[CN Blue's Jong Hyun]
- What are you doing here?
- We won!
You seemed to be on my level.
- Jong Hyun...
- He and I are alike.
[Infinite's emerging Ace, L.]
[All the players have now
made their entrance.]
- Wow, this is really...
- I think this will be an even match.
- This isn't too match.
- Know this, Jong Hyun. You're me.
Then 'L' is 'Gael'...
(Meaning Gary.)
Good to see you, L.
[Gael and L.]
Are you in charge of looks
for your team too?
[This man's confidence that knows no end.]
But seriously... including Infinite's L...
everyone looks so, wow...
[So... good looking!]
Skipping... Kwang Hee and
after Min Ho on...
[Everyone's so good looking with
the exception of Kwang Hee!]
- Why are you being like that to me?
- You two are like brothers!
Why are you comparing us?
[They're both taking offense to
the comment?]
The teams are like this.
The Idol Team and the 'Kwang' Team.
[Idol Team + Kwang Team?]
I was looking at you earlier and I bet you
looked a lot like him before your surgery.
- I'm being serious right now.
- This is before and I'm after.
Why am I the before?
[Kwang Brothers insisting that
they each are the after results.]
Every member of both teams
are now present.
[Time for the torch lighting ceremony
to start off the Olympics game.]
Our torch lighting ceremony will be presided
by a beautiful queen of figure skating.
[Beautiful Queen of figure skating?]
[Could it be?]
[The world champion, Queen of the ice.]
[Kim Yeon Ah?]
[Go Yeon Ah...]
[His gentle roller moves.]
[Extreme makeup.]
You really are suffering a lot, Dong Wan.
[Haroro unable to watch anymore,
and breaks out his leg flip moves.]
What are you doing?
Leg flip? You flipped him over?
Why are you doing that to a woman?
[Anyways...]
[Torch is lit.]
- So I'm taking Yong Hwa's role?
- Come on, that's not right!
Ha Ha's more like Sulli's level.
Okay, that makes me feel good.
- Ha Ha's Sulli right now...
- Then which one are you?
- I would be Yong Hwa.
- No, you're Kwang Hee.
Why do you all keep treating me
like this?
I didn't take the busy time out of my schedule
to come here to be treated like this!
Seriously, this is so unbelievable.
[In commemoration of today's
2013 Running Olympics.]
[2013 Running Olympics - Start!]
[The first competition location is...]
[Please go to the outdoor
sleigh park in Bucheon.]
- Sleigh park?
There may be a lot of people there
who came to see us.
[Rather than worrying about the game,
he's worried about the crowd?]
- But, when we were at the last Olympics...
- When Siwan came?
When we were here last, you
know when we did the marathon race?
They're really good.
We have to show them how ambitious we are.
We're all really hot right now.
What does being good and being hot
have to do with one another?
What can't we do right now
when we're the kings of K-pop?
K-pop is K-pop,
but this is a game right now.
We're the leaders of K-pop right now.
[Leaders and pioneers?]
Leaders and pioneers...
[Idol Team's unknown fear factor,
Kwang Hee.]
Now that I'm thinking about it,
these guys are better than the last group?
I'll take charge of Kwang Hee and make sure
that he doesn't even make a move.
Yeah, you take care of Kwang Hee.
From what I see, Kwang Hee doesn't
seem like he's very competitive.
- He just wants to get some laughs.
- Yeah, he came on to give some laughs.
He's Kwang Soo.
- Jong Kook, we have to win today.
- I really want to win.
- Let's make sure to win today.
- We have to show them who's boss.
- Shall we?
- Let's win today.
- I think we're here.
- Yeah, we're here.
Where is it? Oh, there it is.
- Okay, let's everyone get out!
- Let's win this!
[Running Man Team determined to win.]
- Let's really shock them.
- Okay.
Wow... it's been so long since
I've been to a sleigh park like this one.
[Sleigh park reminiscent of the past.]
- This is...
- So this is what a sleigh park is like.
I wonder what we'll be doing here.
This is a sleigh park reminiscent
of our past.
Team Running Man should be familiar
with a park like this, right?
- Of course.
- No! This is my first time here.
- We've never done it when we were little.
- You've never done this before?
We've never done it either when
we were little. So this is good then.
- We've never done it before either.
- We don't know how to do it either.
[We're still young!]
There's not much difference in age
between them and myself.
The first competition of
2013 Running Man Olympics is...
It's sleigh ski.
What?
- Sleigh ski?
Instead of using batons,
you'll be passing off your sleigh sticks.
And the team that reaches the finish line
first wins the competition.
Kwang Soo, you're standing too close
to the camera. You need to move over.
[Are you a staff member or an actor?]
- I thought you were our new cameraman.
- I thought he was one of our team members!
[Camera Team eyeing
the Giraffe for his tall height.]
One thing that we're sure of, Kwang Hee,
Joon and Jong Hyun, the three of them...
- They're no worries!
- No, we're not like that.
These are the Idols that we want!
Idols here to give us more laughter!
We're the leaders of K-pop!
Then I'm the leader of hip hop.
You know what Kwang Hee said?
'What if I eliminate Jong Kook?'
You're going to eliminate Jong Kook?
That'll be a hoot.
- I think that would be a real hoot.
- Should we give people some laughs today?
- Joon, what number are you?
- I'm number five.
- I'm the fifth runner.
- Really?
Since Joon's number five,
then I'm number five too.
Jong Kook, which number are you?
- He's the seventh.
- Jong Kook is the seventh runner.
I'm the seventh runner, Min Ho.
Min Ho and Jong Kook go to
the same gym.
Jong Kook mentioned earlier
that he's going to win.
Me too!
[Both showing off
their arm strength and speed.]
[I will not lose...]
[Each player to their positions.]
- Suk Jin, are you number one?
- I'm number one. You are too?
[Suk Jin vs. Kwang Hee.]
I'm not kidding around right now.
- How old are you?
- What?
He was born in 1966.
[Suk Jin of '66 vs. Kwang Hee of '88.]
- Your mother was born in '68?
- She's my junior then.
[Old enough to be his father.
Competition between the generations.]
- Can you give me any tips?
- No, I can't give you that.
How much tip should I give you?
- Come on, any know hows?
- Okay, okay...
We have to win this.
We have to win before we go.
Ready... prepare for your race.
[Prepare for takeoff!]
Fighting!
- Fighting!
- Running Man, fighting!
Fighting!
[Opening competition of
2013 Running Man Olympics.]
[Can't lose when it comes to
the sleigh race!]
[This is my win!
I'm 22 years younger than him!]
I used to do this a lot when I was little!
[Big-nosed Brother making big strides
and gliding forward in his sleigh.]
- I used to ride this a lot!
- Kwang Hee's really falling behind.
- I used to do this a lot when I was little!
- He's so awful at this!
[Extremely nonathletic Kwang Hee
embarrassing the Idol Team from the get go.]
[How can this be?
Big-nosed Brother is in the lead?]
- What's going on here? Oh my gosh!
- Look at him!
Nice!
Suk Jin, you're really doing great!
How far is he about to go?
[Going straight ahead
without any hesitation...]
[Then running off course...]
Where is he going? Hurry!
[An urgent change in his course.]
Suk Jin!
[Must hurry to the second player!]
Suk Jin, you're doing great!
[1966 vs. 1988.
Who will be the victor of the race?]
[Despite getting off course, he's
back on track and is full speed ahead!]
Just a little bit more! Come on!
[Hands off the sleigh sticks
to the second runner.]
[Team Running Man succeeds first in handing
off the sleigh sticks to the second player!]
[But Kwang Hee is still...]
[He definitely is different than the
other Idol members on his team...]
How can you be in such horrible
physical condition at your age?
How can you lose to me?
[Barely able to pass off this sleigh sticks.]
Wow... Kwang Hee really sucks at that.
Hey... you're the first Idol
who's ever lost to me.
- That was really hard.
- He's really bad at this stuff.
[Second players working hard to
glide through the ice.]
[An extreme gap between the two
no thanks to Kwang Hee.]
Nice! Nice! I can't
believe how amazing we're doing!
[Ace Ji Hyo earnestly making
her way forward.]
Ji Hyo, come on.
[Passing off her sticks
to the next player already.]
Here I go!
[Team Running Man's third player,
Ha Ha on the move!]
I think there's almost a quarter of
the rink's gap between the two teams.
Yong Hwa,
show them what you can do.
- Sulli, you have to give me a push.
- Okay, I will.
Get up and give me a push.
It's okay.
[Team Idol's third player,
Yong Hwa gets on his way!]
[The undisputed Idol Ace, Yong Hwa!]
He's so fast!
Ha Ha! He's closing in on you, fast!
[Missing the corner slightly
due to his unbelievable speed.]
[Ha Ha uses the opportunity to pass off
his sticks to the fourth player, Gary.]
I'm off! See you, L!
Gary! Wait for me!
[Idol Team's Yong Hwa hands his off to L.]
[Will L...]
L's coming!
[He's fast!]
[Panic.]
[Uh... a reversal in order?]
Nice!
[What a relief!]
[L closing in on Gary quickly!]
Who is that?
[Just a little bit more...]
[L! You're doing so great!]
Wow! He's catching up to him!
[Fifth player, Jae Suk
starting to feel anxious.]
[Wow! A reversal in the order!]
[L surpassing Gary!]
I slipped! I slipped over here.
[Idol Team is now in the lead!]
What the heck is this?
[Idol Team's fifth runner,
Lee Joon on the move!]
Nice!
[Running Man Team's fifth player,
Jae Suk gets on his way!]
[Good job!]
[Just because they've now taken the lead,
showing too much ease on the ice?]
[Ah! Jae Suk is catching up!]
[In danger from having been
too much at ease!]
Hey! Stop it! Hey!
[Pedaling backwards.]
[Caught up once again.]
It's neck and neck! He's caught up!
Jong Hyun, I'm sorry!
[Handing off their sticks to
the sixth players.]
Nice!
[Sixth players, Giraffe vs. Jong Hyun.]
Kwang Soo! Kwang Soo!
[His moves may not be smooth,
but the Giraffe is still pulling ahead.]
That's our Jong Hyun!
This is exciting!
[Now the final players,
Jong Kook vs. Min Ho.]
[Passing off to Running Man Team's
seventh player, Jong Kook.]
You have to push!
You have to push me off!
[With his foot?]
Lee Kwang Soo kicked him off
with his foot.
[Now it's down to the last two players.]
[Why is he kicking him with
his foot again?]
[A one man Giraffe show on the ice.]
[The final competition!]
[Min Ho vs. Jong Kook racing op top of
the ice with their gritted teeth.]
[The fate of the first game rests
on these two's hands.]
[No...]
No!
[Neck and neck competition!]
[Jong Kook misses a beat
with his push...]
[How could he have made
such a mistake...]
[This is his only chance!]
[The finish line is
right in front of their eyes!]
[Feeling the pressure,
yet continuing to make mistakes!]
No! No!
[Could it...]
[Be another reverse for the win?]
[Idol Team wins!]
[A dramatic comeback!]
How could...
- You have to be careful of the corners!
- That's right!
You can't speed up
when you're rounding a corner!
Jong Kook, have you never ridden
one of these sleighs before?
It's because you kicked him
during the race when he was going!
[Giraffe having broken the rhythm from
having kicked him during the race.]
Did you push me or just kick me?
Half and half.
It was fifty and fifty.
We lost.
[Extremely static Min Ho.]
I thought Min Ho just won a gold medal in
the winter Olympics the way he was acting.
He flew his hand in the air like crazy!
Jong Kook is only Jong Kook
when he wins.
[Thus the first sleigh ski race victory
goes to the Idol Team!]
[Heading right away to the next location.]
Look at how happy he is.
Incheon Town Hall.
Seriously... the first game...
we could've won this game.
- Jong Kook, at the end you really...
- Say something to him.
Jae Suk, that's not it.
I was just going way too fast...
Jong Kook, you're starting
to really decline.
You're getting easier to defeat lately.
My conclusion is that you may be strong,
but you don't know how to use your strength.
['He may be strong, but he doesn't
know how to use his strength']
[Okay, toothless Tiger...]
[I will show you!]
[Just why I'm called Mr. Capable!]
[Mr. Capable, Kim Jong  Kook...]
[He will reawaken in his true form.]
[An epic drama that travels through time.]
[Their true selves from 80 years ago
will resurrect.]
[Resurrection - Coming to you next week.]
Want me to tell you what my one liner
is about you, Suk Jin?
- Yeah, tell me.
- Kwang Hee really is weak.
['Kwang Hee truly is a weakling.'
-Jae Suk@Running Man.]
- Kwang Hee, seriously...
- Kwang Hee really is weak.
I think they're just going to be
making fun of Kwang Hee from now on.
Kwang Hee, you really are bad at this.
Sulli, what did you think when I
wasn't doing so well earlier?
- Did you see Sulli's expression?
- I was totally annoyed!
She said that so sincerely.
I knew that you wouldn't be very good,
but I had no idea you'd be that bad.
Let's do this for real though.
- We can't lose this.
- Don't go easy on us because we're juniors.
I did that on purpose earlier. I
pretended to be a weakling on purpose.
- Then I'll anticipate your next game.
- Okay.
I have an image to upkeep. People
are shocked when I use my strength.
[Kwang Hee's mouth springing to life
whenever he gets back in the car...]
[Incheon Town Hall]
There's something in there.
I think there's something in there.
[Second competition location is the
lobby of the town hall?]
Haven't we been here before?
[The site of 2013 Asian Games.
Incheon Town Hall's special auditorium.]
- What is this?
- Look at the soccer net. Soccer net!
Min Ho used to play soccer!
Running Olympics second game is...
Ice hockey.
[The second game is
none other than ice hockey.]
Do you see the nets?
It's not just any ice hockey,
but it's broom hockey.
That's why we've come up with
a special hockey puck.
- Why isn't the puck going in a straight line?
- What is this?
Why is it going swerving around like that?
Isn't that a robotic vacuum cleaner?
- We have to win this game.
- We have to win this no matter what.
Wow, that uniform is no joke.
[Ice hockey uniform to ensure
their safety.]
Let's see those pants.
How are those made?
This is the front.
[Unfamiliar with the hockey uniforms.]
I think we can just put them on.
Sulli looks so cute.
Stop acting like a brat!
Stop it!
Sulli, you're dressed like the
Electric Shock stage costume.
[Like a stage costume from the future?]
Jong Kook, you totally look like a robot.
Jae Suk...
It looks like you've transformed
into someone else.
- Let's go.
- Can you open the door for me?
You think you can even block the puck
dressed like that?
[Transformer Blank Ji.]
- Transformer...
- Ji Hyo looks like a transformer.
[This is so hard...]
[Idol Team's goalie,
Sulli is in the same boat.]
[The restrictive uniform making it difficult
to take even a single step forward.]
- Does it hurt? It doesn't hurt?
- It doesn't hurt at all.
[Safety gear worth the effort.]
Okay, I will explain the game to you.
Each half is ten minutes long.
And it will be played five against five.
Two people will remain on the bench,
but they can be traded out at any time.
And if anyone plays foul,
and the ref calls you out...
then the player will have to spend
one full minute in the penalty box.
- Yes, we understand.
- I have a request to make.
Please insert it in subtitles
on screen to be sure...
that these safety gear and uniforms are
very sturdy and will keep everyone safe.
[You're all dead!]
Jong Kook...
[Since these uniforms are very safe!]
Make sure that all the viewer's know
that without a doubt, these are very safe...
[We're in big trouble...]
The puck isn't my main objective today.
[Idol Team screaming out their
encouragement to one another.]
[Running Man Team following them
in their actions?]
[A thousand steps to the goal post...]
Are you going to date me or not?
Tell me once and for all!
I said, tell me clearly!
- Hey! Let's do this!
- Fighting!
[Suk Jin and Jae Suk are starting
on the bench.]
Fighting!
Ah... I'm so hungry.
[Oh! Nice pass!]
[And having it stolen from them
right away...]
[A forceful body check.]
[He's not playing around.]
[Just then...]
[Jong Hyun's chance to shoot!]
[She blocks it?]
[Blank Ji scooping it up
to get it out of there!]
Get away!
Nice blocking!
[Thanks to the unleashed Tiger,
getting close to the puck is impossible.]
[Another chance for the Idol Team!]
[She blocks it again...]
[Blank Ji standing firm at the goal post
and blocking off the shots.]
[Fierce Blank Ji.]
[Goalie Ji Hyo's brilliant save.]
Ji Hyo, I can't believe you blocked that.
- Ji Hyo, you're something else.
- What other choice do I have but to block it?
- Keep blocking it. Block it with your body.
- Can you help me with my helmet?
[The helmet keeps...]
You have to get the puck
away from her.
[Kkuk, a specialist when it comes to
physical confrontations.]
Wait... he keeps hitting me
with his broom!
He keeps hitting me with his broom!
[Huh?]
[Yong Hwa slightly moves out of the way,
so he fails to body check him!]
[Did you escape me?]
What the heck is this?
[The Tiger trampling all over
the special lobby auditorium.]
How does it taste to be up
against Jong Kook?
[The fury of Mr. Capable
no one can escape.]
[A fierce battle going back and forth
between the two teams.]
- Why? What is it?
- Who? Who is it?
- Who is it?
- Lee Kwang Soo, one minute in the box.
[A minute in the penalty box
for Kwang Soo?]
[Utter confusion.]
[During the fierce physical battle...]
[Giraffe stealing one of their brooms
and throwing it off to the side.]
[For the next minute... bye!]
- Seriously, what did you do?
- Lee Kwang Soo, what the heck?
He did play foul?
Lee Kwang Soo, seriously...
Dong Hoon, come in
and Suk Jin, get out there.
[When do I get to play...]
[An unbelievable defense by L.]
[And a chance to shoot!]
[Huh?]
[Joon having hit it out of the way
before Suk Jin could even shoot.]
Where did it go?
- Hey!
- What's wrong with you, Suk Jin?
How old are you?
[It may have been a bad move
to trade out the players?]
[Kwang Soo's time in the penalty box is up,
and it's time for him to get back in!]
Lee Kwang Soo! Trade out!
[Trades out for Jae Suk.]
[Kwang Hee finally enters the game.]
Kwang Hee, start running.
I'm sure everyone's starting
to feel tired.
Your chance is now. You have to help them.
I'm sure they're all feeling tired.
[That... that...]
[It's too fierce out there...]
[Will I be able to stand up
to that Tiger?]
[What do I do?]
[Getting down to his knees in defeat?]
What are you doing?
Hurry!
- Hurry! Hurry up and get in there.
- I'm too scared.
[Still competing with 0-0 score.]
[The game now rife with screams
after Kwang Hee joins.]
[Backing up again?]
Go away!
[I'm too scared...]
Oh yes, oh yes, oh yes!
[Here, get a taste of this.]
Kwang Hee... Kwang Hee... you okay?
[Using the moment of chaos...]
[Yong Hwa steals the puck.]
[A chance to shoot a goal!]
[A one on one chance with goalie, Ji Hyo.]
[Amazing! She blocks it again.]
[But then...]
[Jong Hyun having followed behind
gets a chance at rebound!]
[Jong Hyun's shooting is a success!]
- I didn't see it...
- You did good.
[Yay... this is exciting.]
[Idol Team: 1, Running Man Team: 0]
- Who scored?
- Jong Hyun did.
Jae Suk, you have to play better defense.
- I'll play defense.
- Fighting!
- Hurry up while Jong Kook isn't here.
- I'll score a goal while Jong Kook's out.
[This is their chance while
Jong Kook is out!]
[Idol Team not hesitating to attack
with Mr. Capable out of the game.]
You can't just block the puck.
You have to block their bodies too!
[Oh... Haroro's breakthrough.]
[Ah... unfortunately hits
the goal posts and misses!]
[Breaking out in a scuffle
all of a sudden?]
[Instigating a brawl for no reason with
Ace Yong Hwa in his grasp.]
Both of you in the penalty box
for the next minute!
[Acting as though he's furious.]
[Breaking out into another brawl?]
[A deliberate brawl in attempt to get their
opponent's Ace thrown out of the game.]
[Ha Ha goes into the
penalty box for the next minute.]
Do a body check! A body check!
[But the others are still in
midst of the brawl that was started.]
[The whole group jumps into the scuffle.]
[During the midst of all this chaos...]
[The puck having broken free...]
[L's sole chance!]
[Another one on one chance with
Goalie Blank Ji!]
[Shoots with all his might!]
[The puck unfortunately misses the goal...]
[Running Man Team escapes danger.]
Get out of the way!
The big nose is coming!
[What are you going to do
about your pants?]
- Look. His pants fell off.
- Wait! Time!
[A service to the fans?
A prime photo opportunity.]
Here... here!
[Just then...]
[Player Big-nose's one on one chance!]
[L plays defense by throwing
his body in the way.]
[Giraffe boy who hasn't had the chance
to pull up his pants yet.]
[As soon as he returns from the penalty
box, he incites another brawl.]
[Lets you and I both die!]
Both of you in the penalty box.
How many times
are you going to get kicked out?
[Rather than the game itself, deterring
Yong Hwa seems to be his main goal.]
Look... look over there at our
tiger caged up in there.
Look at our caged up tiger.
Guys, he's going to be back in a minute.
- No... no, it's not time yet.
- Look at him. Bite it!
Bite it! Bite it!
[Black hole Kwang Hee not being of any
help and just being a loud distraction.]
[Jae Suk's awesome pass.]
Shoot!
[Kwang Soo's nonstop shoot.]
[What in the world happened?
Kwang Soo?]
[A fantastic team play!]
- That was great!
- Your pants!
[But your pants...]
Kwang Soo, re-tie your pants.
[Idol Team: 1, Running Man Team: 1]
[End of the first half]
Somehow... during the game, a whole crowd
of people have come out to watch our game.
You really are a
high maintenance woman!
- You really are a high maintenance woman.
- You say that to each other often.
- You really are high maintenance.
- You think I can sit down in this?
- Try it.
- How?
- Here, I'll help you down.
- No, I don't have a chair yet!
I don't have a chair yet!
[Due to the uniform she's in, no
other choice but to lay down to rest.]
If we're going to win against that team,
the only choice we have is 'AZ887'.
AZ887...
The AZ887 that my father used
to speak of?
Have you ever thought of
becoming a manager?
I'm a hockey player.
- We can do this. Let's do this together.
- Okay. I know that we can do this together.
[Seems as though he no longer could stand
to see the drama unfolding before him.]
- What perfect timing...
- It was good timing.
[Mannerly Jong Hyun
becoming a backrest for Sulli.]
This looks like an ice hockey drama.
You guys look like you're shooting a
teen ice hockey drama.
She couldn't sit with her uniform on.
[Running Man Team's plan
for the second half is...]
[To keep inciting fouls to be
called into the penalty box.]
[Especially Ace Min Ho and Yong Hwa!]
You have to get both
Min Ho and Yong Hwa out of there.
- This is AZ887.
- AZ887...
How about we get everyone out and
leave Kwang Hee alone with Jong Kook?
- That's a great idea.
- That bad, is it?
Jong Hyun likes things like this a lot.
[Jong Hyun with his
naturally abundant curiosity.]
[Trying to figure out what's going on...]
- What was the name of our plan?
- AZ0885.
[His clumsiness is part of his charm.]
Okay, let's start the game!
[Time to start the second half.]
- Ji Hyo, fighting!
- Fighting.
- Take care of her, Gary.
- Kang Gary...
[Back to the distant goal post...]
You can't go too fast.
[Sulli also arrives at her goal post.]
Put it in my grasp.
- Let's go! Let's go!
- Fighting!
[Running Man's plan for the second half
is AZ887...]
- You can handle it, right?
- AZ887!
Idol... Idol! World leading Idols!
We can't lose!
One, two, three, fighting!
Veterans... they're all old veterans!
[Second half - Start!]
[As planned, starting AZ887.]
[Inciting a group brawl to carry on
their plans to get everyone thrown out.]
[Um... what to do?]
[Weak Kwang Hee just falling down
without any resistance.]
[Purposely starting a brawl with everyone
with the exception of Kwang Hee.]
Out!
[All six people thrown out
into the penalty box!]
[Oh no...]
[Here's the chance...]
[Mission accomplished according
to plan AZ887.]
Wait... Sir, just a minute.
Wait!
- Kwang Hee, fighting!
- Follow the plan!
[As planned, it's down to Kwang Hee
and Jong Kook, one on one.]
[Unable to even get close to the puck.]
[Even hanging onto his back is of no use.]
- You have to block him.
- You have to block him somehow.
[While Kwang Hee's unable to even
get a grasp on his broom...]
- You have to block him.
- You have to block him somehow.
No! No!
[Easily scores the goal.]
[Plan AZ887 is a success!]
Plan AZ887 worked!
- This is a good plan.
- That was good.
[Fine... let's do this.]
[Idol Team: 1, Running Man Team: 2.]
[Within moments, Min Ho gets a chance!]
[Blank Ji blocks it again!]
[But then...]
[L shoots it in the goal!]
[Idol Team evening out the score
immediately!]
[Idol Team: 2, Running Man Team: 2.]
This game is down to the last goal.
[With only a few minutes remaining,
it's down to the one last goal.]
[A fierce battle with the score at 2:2.]
[Big-nosed Brother's breakthrough?]
- Suk Jin!
- Over here!
[Passes through an opening!]
[Will he...]
[Easy Brothers' fantasy team play!]
[Kwang Soo scores another goal!]
[Do you have any interest in giving
ice hockey a try?]
[Get off of me.]
Lee Kwang Soo! Lee Kwang Soo!
[The Giraffe pulling it out...]
It was both our efforts.
Pil-Chok-Cross!
Sulli, you did good.
Sulli, block the shots!
I was trying to block it...
You were trying to block it...
[Idol Team: 2, Running Man Team: 3]
Nice... give it to him.
There are only two minutes
left on the clock!
You have to block him!
[Idol Team's full on efforts.]
[Wall Blank Ji blocking it again!]
Ji Hyo, you're doing a great job.
[Goalie Ji Hyo doing a great job
of protecting her goal posts.]
We have to play defense!
[She's good...]
[Game over!]
We won!
[Crap. We lost...]
Sorry. What to do...
[Running Man team wins!]
[A round of hands to everyone
who gave their best at the game.]
What is it?
Third location for
Running Man 2013 Olympics.
[Go to Incheon Environmental
Corporation's sports park.]
So it's one to one.
[Current score - 1:1]
L was really good.
L worked really hard.
- Ji Hyo was really good.
- You're right.
I'm sorry.
Ji Hyo filled up the whole goal posts.
I can accept Ji Hyo being good, but I
can't accept Kwang Soo making the goals.
[The location of
Running Olympics third event is?]
[Huh? This is...]
[A diving board?]
It's a combination of ski jump and diving.
It's called ski jump diving.
[2013 Running Olympics' third game,
Ski Jump diving.]
Why are you combining those two things?
The distance that you jump from the
diving board will be combined
and the team that jumps the furthest
will win the game.
A combination of all the distance?
And I'm sure there will be some of you who
may be too scared to jump, right?
In case of those people,
you don't need to jump.
However, just know that the combined
distance will get deducted for their amount.
Just jump no matter what.
- Just jump no matter what.
- I don't think I can do it.
He just said we don't have to jump.
The team that wins this game will receive
a huge advantage for the final game.
- It will be an enormous advantage.
- Let's win. Let's win this.
- Kwang Soo is going to jump first for us.
- No, no... there's no way!
Lee Kwang Soo! Lee Kwang Soo!
[Idol Team as always showing
their ambitious side.]
You can just plug your nose
when you jump.
[After shoving it around, deciding
their order with paper-rock-scissors]
[They're so happy it's not them when
they're going to end up jumping anyway.]
[Running Man Team's first player - Gary!]
[Now that he's up on the board,
the 5m height seems so high up...]
[So I just need to jump far, is that it?]
You look so cool up there!
[At times Mr. Capable Gary
with a change in the glint of his eye!]
You look like a Seoul resident!
[Jamsil resident changed
into a Seoul resident.]
For the life that I've lived thus far!
- Let's go!
- 5m! Please get 5m!
[Fails at his attempt to look cool.]
[How far will Gary jump?]
Gary, you're awesome!
[He's going... he's going!]
[With all his might!]
[Did he fall on his face?]
[Wow! Nice distance!]
Gary! Is your face okay?
[Now that we take a closer look, his
face seemed to have turned quite red?]
Is your face okay?
I know that your face is
the money maker!
[My face is my fortune...]
[Gary succeeds at jumping the 5m!]
[Running Man Team's combined distance
total thus far is 5m!]
[Idol Team's first player - Kwang Hee!]
Kwang Hee, don't overdo it!
No, overdo it!
- Aren't you scared up there?
- I am scared!
- Kwang Hee, don't overdo it.
- Don't stand up there for too long.
[Grabbing tightly onto the camera boom.]
Don't hold that! Don't hold onto that!
[Each step is in agony.]
Don't hold onto the rails,
and just run and jump.
[It may sound easy...]
[Will he?]
[A clean submersion!]
[He jumped!]
[More cool that he got up the courage to
jump rather than the distance he gets.]
[But then what is he doing?]
[He can't swim.]
I'm trying to move!
[Swimming in place while standing straight
just like a seahorse... fascinating.]
[Moving forward bit by bit...]
[And finally lands ashore on his own.]
[Feeling great!]
[Kwang Hee's jump distance is 4m 20cm!]
[Idol Team's combined distance total
thus far is 4m 20cm!]
[Running Man Team's
next jumper is Ace Ji Hyo!]
Wow... she's not even afraid!
We're going to win this because of Ji Hyo.
Take a point from her.
- Just jump! Jump from there.
- Just watching you stand there scares me.
- Run to the ledge and then jump.
- That's right!
Stop doing things like that,
and just jump!
- Stop!
- Don't do that!
[This is fun!]
[Courage befitting of our Ace!]
[Ace Ji Hyo gets ready for her jump!]
[A refreshing submersion!]
[Irrefutable Running Man's treasure,
Ace Ji Hyo!]
[Running Man Team's combined distance
total thus far is 8m 50cm!]
[Idol Team's next jumper is
Jung Yong Hwa.]
[Responding to the fans cheering him on
in the swimming pool.]
[Charging up his energy.]
Yong Hwa, jump far!
[After showing us a dashing expression...]
[Idol Team's representatives for two
Running Olympics' in a row! How will he fare?]
Make some noise!
[Fly!]
[Jumping quite the distance!]
[Jumping with all his might!
And submerging with force!]
[Pretty cool...]
[Best record thus far! 5m 10cm!]
[Idol Team's combined distance total
thus far is 9m 30cm!]
[Next jumper for the
Running Man Team is Jae Suk.]
Wow, this is no joke!
[An Idol image with the glasses off?]
- Show us how far the grasshopper can jump!
- Look straight ahead when you jump!
Don't look down, but look straight ahead!
[A person who really hates heights...]
[But the cheer of his teammates
will give him the strength!]
[Let's go!]
[He should've jumped more!]
[But still, not a bad record at all.]
[Running Man Team's combined distance
total thus far is 13m 10cm!]
[And for the Idol Team, it's L's turn!]
Let's jump far. Jump far.
- Fighting!
[Jumping with style without any hesitation!]
[A tie with Yong Hwa
for the furthest distance!]
[Idol Team's combined distance total
thus far is 14m 40cm!]
- Kwang Soo!
- Kwang Soo, fighting!
[Running Man Team, Kwang Soo's turn.]
[Tallest Giraffe, will he jump far?]
You have to jump far, got it?
If you end up falling like that,
you're only going to get 1m!
[Is he tumbles head first,
his record will only be 1m...]
- That's even scarier.
- What you're doing is scarier.
[Trying to gauge the distance in height
by stretching out his arm.]
[It seems as though he left his sanity
back on the ground.]
My stomach hurts.
[Even resorting to prayer?]
This is the only chance you have
to beat Song Joong Ki!
- Five, four, three, two...
- Look out in front of you!
[Oh... the glint in his eye... it's changed.]
- One!
- Let's go! Run!
[What... what is there that I can't do!]
[This is nothing!]
[That's far!]
[Awesome! Giraffe!]
[Did you think I wouldn't be able to do it?]
Come on. Hurry up.
Just because you did that,
nothing's changed.
[The best record!]
[No matter, showing us the cool side of
himself for once... Nice, Giraffe!]
With only one jumper left on each team,
I'll show you the combined score so far.
[Combined score for each team thus far.]
[Running Man Team- 24m 40cm.
Idol Team- 23m 10cm.]
[Running Man Team in the lead with
a difference of 1m 30cm.]
[Running Man Team's final jumper,
Kim Jong Kook!]
[And Idol Team's last jumper is Min Ho!]
[The victory of the game once again
rests on these two...]
[Even though Running Man Team is ahead by
1m 30cm, they still need to stay on guard.]
[A lot resting on last jumper,
Jong Kook's shoulders!]
- Here I go!
- Fighting!
[Let's trust... in my abilities.]
[Even though he submerged after
flying freely into the air...]
[Somehow doesn't seem as though
he got too much of a distance?]
What happened to you?
[The Tiger's record not
meeting the expectations.]
- We needed to get a definite end on them!
- We don't know what's going to happen now.
[If Min Ho jumps more than 5m 80cm,
then the Idol Team wins!]
Fighting! Let's rally him on!
[Idol Team giving all their energy
to Min Ho!]
[He lost out to Min Ho during the sleigh
game in the first round, could he really...]
[Yelling at one another to
bring down each other's energy.]
[Idol Team's final jumper, Min Ho.]
[If he jumps more than 5m 80cm,
then Idol Team wins!]
[For the first time in a long time,
even Mr. Capable seems nervous!]
Min Ho, you don't have to
work so hard!
Even though we're Running Man,
Min Ho is a dream team all on his own.
- Take it easy on yourself!
- Just jump!
[Everything about today's competition may
change depending on his one single jump!]
[Jong Kook vs. Min Ho...
who will win this time?]
[He seemed to have jumped quite the
distance, but will it be enough?]
[What will the results show?]
You did good.
You're lookin' good, lookin' good!
We've got the results.
[Time to reveal the combined score results.]
[Did Min Ho flip the game around?]
[By a 20cm difference,
Running Man Team wins!]
[Running Man Team wins the third game,
Ski diving!]
[Min Ho unfortunately lands at 5m 60cm!]
Now... we have one final game left.
[At last, it's the 2013 Running Olympics'
finale competition.]
[Running Man Team: 2, Idol Team: 1]
Running Man Team will be given an advantage
at the final location when you arrive.
[The final competition that Running Olympic
is known for is now about to start!]
[2013 Running Olympic final location-
Incheon Institute of Biology Resources.]
[Just what is the final game that
awaits them here?]
This is attack and defense again.
[This is...]
[The finale to the Olympics is a marathon!]
[Running Olympics finale is an
alternating chase game!]
[The finale for 2012 Summer Running Olympics
was also the alternating chase game!]
[Alternate the sides every 10 minutes!
The ultimate chase where planning is crucial!]
[A special chance to decide whether
they're going to attack or defend first!]
- Let's attack first. That should be good.
- Let's get rid of Min Ho first.
I'm going to oust every one of them.
I'm not going to leave out a single one.
[The attack team must attach a bell
to their shoe.]
You think they'll be
able to beat our know-how?
[Idol Team has no choice
but to go on the defense first.]
[A change in their position every 10 minutes!
When it's announced, must stop their actions!]
And from where you are at that moment,
you'll change your position immediately.
Do I look cute?
[How like them as Idols to be worried
about how they look first.]
- Sulli...
- I don't know who to put this on.
One, two, three, fighting!
[Game, start.]
[Defense team is given three minutes to hide!]
Where should I go?
- Hide well, kids.
- We're going to get you guys.
Please take good care of us.
- Jong Hyun, hide well.
- Yes.
Sulli, hide well, okay?
Kim Jong Kook!
[Kwang Hee's laughter
bringing down their morale.]
Lee Joon!
Quiet... keep it down!
[Only Joon keeps quiet and hurries along
from having been on Running Man before.]
- Three minutes. we have three minutes.
- I said, keep it down!
- Lee Joon... where do we go?
- Keep it down!
Where... where do we go?
[Best chance at survival is to catch as
many as they can during their first attack.]
[10 seconds left before the attack begins.]
- Let's go!
- There's no time to waste here.
- There's no plan. Just oust them all.
- We need to oust them all unconditionally.
- Oust them as soon as you see one.
- Let's go.
Lee Joon! Where's Lee Joon?
Where did Lee Joon go?
Don't go... don't leave me!
We can't stay together.
[The moment that gives most excitement
and anxiousness at the same time.]
[Attack team- On your way!]
[Prepare yourselves!
We will teach you all a lesson!]
- Where do you think they're at?
- Let's try this way.
[The sound of ringing bells...]
[Discovers L from the Idol Team
running away.]
- Jong Kook!
- Up top! He's up top!
[Sound of Running Man team voices
coming from all around him.]
- Jong Kook! It's L!
- There he is! Over there. This way!
This way... this way!
[This is the know how!
Block his escape route and ambush him!]
[L makes a desperate attempt to flee!]
Lee Kwang Soo! Get him!
[But... this time,
it's Mr. Capable blocking his way.]
[Completely surrounded within moments!]
[Overly ambitious L didn't even hide
and was lying in wait, and of all places...]
- Five of you against one?
- Sorry. there's no other choice.
- Let's go.
- Next. Let's go find the next one.
[As soon as the chase begins,
one member of the Idol Team is ousted.]
[L - Out!
L - Out!]
L - Out!
Don't you think that was
way too quick?
[Searching one room at a time.]
- Jong Kook, do you see anyone?
- There's no one.
Please turn the light off.
No, there's no one.
[Wait! Jong Hyun is hiding in that room!]
Did you check out here too?
Ji Hyo!
[Running Man know-how. As soon
as you're called, you come running!]
Ji Hyo!
[Mr. Capable and Ace...
Finds Jong Hyun in hiding!]
[Came into the room to hide... Who
knew he'd get cornered like a mouse?]
[Within minutes, already two members
of the Idol Team are ousted!]
I'm really sorry.
[Jong Hyun - Out!]
[Still quite a bit of time left on the clock
until their roles are reversed.]
The sound of that bell is no joke.
[Sound of the bells ringing...]
[If they give out any signs of anyone
being inside, it will mean big trouble!]
- Jong Kook!
- Yeah?
- Do you see anyone?
- I haven't seen anyone. What about you?
I think I'm going to head downstairs.
[Luckily, it seems as though they're
about to just pass by the area...]
[They're leaving... they're leaving.]
- Have you found anyone?
- I just have a feeling someone may be here.
You see anyone?
Someone could be hiding in here.
[The office that Big-nose Brother
is being suspicious over...]
[Joon is hiding underneath the desk!]
Someone could be hiding in here.
- But no one's in there?
- No, I guess no one's in there.
I thought someone would be in there.
[Just shaved 10 years off of his life.]
Hey, kids... there's at least
one of you hiding here, right?
[Even though he has his suspicions,
he doesn't actively search for them...]
[Kwang Hee's inside!]
It's just a relief that Jong Kook
hasn't been by yet.
I would've been dead earlier
if I didn't have this.
[A relief that he took the time out
to make a roof for himself earlier.]
Please leave. If someone sees a camera here,
they're going to know that I'm in here.
I think I'm going to hide here later.
Right in there...
[His idea of a good hiding spot is...]
[The place where Kwang Hee is hiding?]
Hey! Over here!
Hey...
Answer this correctly.
Who's your favorite comedian?
- Who is it?
- Ji Suk Jin. Ji Suk Jin!
[Amazing teamwork! Everyone
comes running from Suk Jin's call.]
- This is how we need to work together.
- Why? What is it?
- I like how we're working together.
- Kwang Hee..
- Honestly, I really do like you.
- Thank you.
- Kwang Hee, there's no other choice.
- Gary, just give me one more chance!
- No, I really like you too, but...
- Come on, you know how popular I am lately!
You're popular...
but Suk Jin's popular these days too.
- Just one more chance... just this once!
- We've got no other choice.
[Amazingly, he thinks to make a deal?]
This was going to happen
sooner or later.
[I'm sorry, Kwang Hee...]
- Just give me one chance!
- Seriously...
- Gary, Gary... just one chance!
- We have no other choice. We have to.
[Must eliminate as soon as they're caught,
otherwise the roles may change...]
- Seriously! Leesang is the best!
- Thanks. You're the best too.
Got it, got it... we've got Kwang Hee.
[Now Kwang Hee too!
Idol Team now loses their third member!]
This is Running Man's know-how...
This is a really good hiding spot though.
Leave me here so I can hide here.
[Kwang Hee - Out!
Kwang Hee - Out!]
- I really wanted to give you a break...
- I understand where you're coming from.
- You do, don't you?
- But I really hate Ha Ha and Gary.
- I much prefer having you around.
- Right?
Oh, there you are...
[But I'm too cool to react to that.]
- I heard what you said...
- Since I'm already eliminated...
[One minute left until the exchange.
One minute left until the exchange.]
We have to get them quickly.
Otherwise, we're going to get ousted.
[The time flew by so quickly in the midst
of ousting three of their opponents.]
Hey!
[Discovers Yong Hwa from the Idol Team!]
[Yong Hwa makes a run for it!
There's no time! Must catch him quickly!]
[Must eliminate him before the exchange!]
[They cornered him into
a dead end office for now...]
[The problem is that he's no
easy opponent.]
[Imminent time of exchange!]
We have to end this.
[Stop all movement!]
[Stop movement... now?]
[Time to stop all movement!
Time to stop all movement!]
It's ruined.
[Please exchange attack
and defense positions.]
[10 minutes is up! Time to exchange
attack and defense position.]
[For the next 10 minutes,
Running Man becomes the defense team.]
[And Idol team becomes the attack team.]
[Kwang Soo and Jae Suk in a hot situation.]
What are we supposed to do here then?
- What about us? Look at us...
- You just need to sit still.
What do you mean, just sit still?
[Rule: Must exchange their roles as soon
as cease movement is called out.]
[We're ruined...]
[Attack: Four Idol Team members.
Defense: Seven Running Man Team members.]
[Idol Team with the bells attached
in order to start their attack.]
Seriously... what is this?
Look at our situation!
[Just what is going to happen to
these three in the next moment?]
We can do this.
It's two against one right now.
[But you're not very trustworthy...]
[End of cease movement!]
[Exchange their positions!
Must block Yong Hwa's attack!]
It's two against one... two against one.
[However... Yong Hwa manages to get up!]
[Huh? Giraffe, you're not...]
You're not... you're not by any chance
telling Yong Hwa to eliminate me?
[Giraffe, you really seem like you're
pressing down on Jae Suk right now...]
Jae Suk! Wait...
Yong Hwa! What are you
going to eliminate me for?
Wait! Wait...
Get rid of Jae Suk... Yong Hwa!
Now's your only chance to eliminate Jae Suk!
Jae Suk!
Let go! Let me go!
[Jae Suk gets his revenge by holding
tight onto the Giraffe's pants!]
[Yong Hwa of the Running Man Team
rids Kwang Soo of his name tag!]
[And moving right away onto
his next target.]
Hey!
[Jae Suk - Out!]
Wasn't the plan for both of us to survive?
[Both survive, our butts...
you've both been ousted simultaneously...]
Yong Hwa, you're really lucky.
To get both of us...
A one, two shot like that...
[What one, two punch?]
How could you have told Yong Hwa to
eliminate me and help him like that?
I confused your arm with
Yong Hwa's arm.
You really confused yourself into
thinking you were on Yong Hwa's team?
If you were misunderstood,
I formally apologize.
[Idiots one, two punch.
Two members of Running Man Team, out!]
[On the other hand...]
[Big-nosed Brother looking
for a place to hide.]
Wait... what is this?
You're here. Where were you?
- You opened the door to where I was earlier.
- When?
- I opened the door?
- Yes, I was inside the room you looked into.
- You were there the whole time?
- Yes, I was in there.
- Go on back to what you were doing then.
- Okay.
So I opened the door earlier?
- The manager's office.
- The manager's office?
- Yes. I was in there.
- Then I gave you a break?
- I guess... you could look at it that way.
- Right?
Then you can give me a break too
and just walk on by then.
Isn't it a good idea?
[Is he really going to let him go
as if he hasn't even seen him?]
Go on... it's okay.
- Go on back to your work.
- I am doing my work.
- Yong Hwa!
- Hey!
[Gathering the Idol Team to attack!]
- So this is where you were?
- Yes.
So had I walked in the office,
I would've found you?
- Joon...
- This is where I was.
[Ambitious Min Ho arrives as his helper.]
- Min Ho...
- You do it. I don't know.
- I love you.
- Min Ho...
- I gave you a break, okay?
- Hey! You... Lee Joon!
- I gave you the break that you asked for.
Hey...
[Even to the little lion, Min Ho,
Impala is an easy prey.]
[Suk Jin - Out!]
[Ji Suk Jin - Out!
Ji Suk Jin - Out!]
My heart is pounding.
Race... start.
[Idol Team with a spring in their steps.]
- Hi there, Gary.
- Oh, Joon!
You didn't have to come all this way!
How did you know to come here?
- Okay, I'll see you later then.
- Okay.
Oh my... you all came to see me?
[Even the gentle Sulli joins the hunt.]
Sulli! What's with that glint in your eye?
Sulli! Don't do this...
Give me one more chance, Sulli.
Give me one more chance.
Do you see this? Did you not see that?
[Gary - Out!
Gary - Out!]
[One minute left until the exchange.]
- Wait! Over there!
- Where?
I've been caught.
[Idol Team needs to rush
before their time is up!]
To the left! To the left!
It's time for the exchange soon.
I should get out of here.
Over here! Min Ho, over here!
[Discovers Jong Kook
in the corner of the room.]
- There's not much time left!
- We have to rush!
[Will they be able to get Mr. Capable
in the time that they have left?]
I got him. I got him!
[Mr. Capable with a tight grasp
on Yong Hwa!]
[Cease all movement. Time to exchange!]
Do you know what you call this?
This is an ant hill attack plan!
I showed you my face on purpose!
[This was Mr. Capable's clever plan timed
around the exchange!]
[Idol Team is now on the defense, and
the Running Man Team is now the attacker!]
The moment that I saw Ji Hyo's face...
- I knew I've been caught.
- You knew you were caught...
As soon as the clock starts up,
run like crazy out of here.
Yong Hwa... get them, okay?
- Are you leaving and abandoning me behind?
- You shouldn't exert yourself, Sulli.
It's my fault again.
It would be better for you not to move.
[Cease movement cancelled.]
[An ant hill hell that he can't escape from!]
Let's go get Min Ho! Quickly!
[Yong Hwa - Out!]
- Where? Where?
- This way! He went this way! Come on!
- Go that way... go in that way!
- Jong Kook, where are you going?
[Sound of the bells coming
from all over the place!]
Where is he in here?
[Escaping into the showcase room!]
[The nervousness making his heart
feel like it's about to burst!]
I saw him run in here.
Really? Could he be back where
you were hiding earlier?
[Jong Kook discovers Min Ho!]
[Jong Kook vs. Min Ho!
Their third face-off of the day!]
[The unmerciful battle between
Mr. Capable and Ace!]
[At last, the baby lion's Min Ho's
name tag is eliminated!]
[Min Ho - Out!]
[Min Ho - Out!
Min Ho - Out!]
[The jail getting louder
at Min Ho's entrance.]
Mr. Capable ripped it off.
- Seriously...
- He even ripped my clothes.
[With even the slightest grab,
the sleeves of his shirt is all ripped.]
[I know that feeling all too well...]
I was hiding in there...
and they both rushed in there at once.
Kim Jong Kook has an unbelievable
sense of hunting people down.
Wasn't your plan to get rid of
Jong Kook right from the beginning?
- But we couldn't find Jong Kook.
- I know.
- I bet he went into hiding right away.
- He was probably hanging from the ceiling.
Hanging from the ceiling...
- Jong Hyun just keeps laughing.
- Like he's watching TV.
[Having fun like he's a part of what's
going on in the TV screen.]
[One minute left until the exchange.]
Let me come with you.
You too, Ji Hyo.
- We have to make an ant hill.
- I'm getting really nervous.
We have to make an ant hill,
so we need to find a good spot.
[Trying to plan their second
ant hill attack.]
Someone was hiding in here earlier.
[At last, it's time to cease
all movement.]
[Running Man to become the defense team
and the Idol Team to become the attack team.]
Attack!
[Cease movement cancelled.]
Joon!
Yes? Yes, Sulli?
Over here! Over here!
I think someone is hiding down here.
But where are the rest of the guys?
Everyone's all dead. We're the only ones left.
So we have to oust the rest ourselves.
- They're all dead?
- Yes.
[Will these two be able to oust Mr. Capable,
Ace Ji Hyo and Haroro all by themselves?]
- If we find them...
- We have to figure out what to do.
When I looked earlier, there were
a lot of secret rooms around here.
Rooms like this one...
There are a lot of rooms like
this around here.
Hello.
There are a lot of rooms like this here...
hello.
[All three of them in the same place?]
[Is this the second ant hill hell
that they spoke of?]
- We've been waiting for you.
- Sulli...
Sulli... what do we do?
[Is this really the face of the defense team?]
- What is this?
- We've been waiting for you.
- Come here.
- Where have you been?
[The attack team is undeniably the Idol
Team. Sulli makes her way forward!]
Hey! What are you doing?
[Running Man Team covers each other's
name tag with their hands to protect it!]
[Absolutely impossible for Lee Joon
to approach using his strength alone!]
[Sulli's attack vs. Ji Hyo's defense
over Ha Ha's name tag!]
[Sulli rids Ha Ha of his name tag!]
[Sulli doesn't stop and moves on to
attack Ace Ji Hyo!]
- Don't step on me!
- Sorry.. sorry!
[What is he being subjected to?]
[Sulli now starts attacking Mr. Capable!]
[Ace Ji Hyo blocks her path
with her own body!]
[The bloodiest battle in the
history of Running Man!]
[Absolute chaos!]
Joon! Hurry up and rip it off!
I wish I could... but I have no hands!
My hands...
Look at this!
Don't stab me with your chin!
Ji Hyo, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
[One minute to the exchange.]
- Jong Kook...
- We... lost to you guys the last time.
[Running Man Team trying to get revenge
for having lost at the last Running Olympics.]
I really want to win.
The Idol Team won the last time.
The Idol Team won the last time, Sulli.
It's our turn.
[Mr. Capable shutting the door
and locking them up inside?]
Ji Hyo, I'm sorry!
Ji Hyo, I'm really sorry!
[Escapes to the outside and leave
Ji Hyo locked up with them inside!]
[Their chance to rid of Ji Hyo is now!]
[Ji Hyo - Out!]
Ji Hyo, I'm sorry.
[Song Ji Hyo - Out!
Song Ji Hyo - Out!]
[Cease all movement.]
I had no other choice.
There was no other choice if
our team is to win.
Ji Hyo, I'm really sorry.
- Ji Hyo...
- You locked me in there so you could live?
Ji Hyo, it was for the sake of our team.
- We have to win...
- Did you think...
- That I'd survive in there once you left?
- You did really well though.
But there was only 30 seconds left,
and I knew I had to get out of there.
You'd better win.
And... Sulli's really strong.
Jong Kook...
I'm going to trust you, okay?
[The final exchange for the
Running Man Team!]
[This time... I will end it.]
[I will take responsibility for all
of my team members!]
[Idol Team now on their defense.]
[Cease movement cancelled.]
- How could you...
- Jong Kook, wait...
How could you... how could you...
[The final battle between the
two teams!]
Let go! Let go of me!
Sulli!
[Eliminates Joon so easily!]
[Lee Joon - Out!]
[Now down to one on one!
What will be the result of this match?]
Where would I be if I was you, Sulli?
- Lee Joon!
- Joon!
Joon... it was just you and Sulli?
It's just Sulli and Jong Kook.
- How did you last so long?
- I was surprised myself.
I think... I think I'm good at this.
A tiger and Sulli...
I wonder how it'll end?
[The final battle - Tiger vs. Lamb]
[Even though the difference is
clear for anyone to see...]
[Will the victory of this battle be
determined by the strength alone?]
[Discovered!]
Sulli! Sulli!
[Jong Kook discovers his target!]
Sulli...
- Jong Kook... don't come near me!
- Sulli...
Sulli! Sulli...
Sulli...
[Tiger and the Lamb coming
face to face at last.]
How were you planning on coming after me
later on when you get tired so easily?
I don't know why I tried to escape.
I'm the attacker, so I don't know why.
I'm really sorry. Seriously...
[Little lady Sulli... just what
is the fate that awaits her?]
- Who do you think won?
- I'm really curious!
- I'm really curious.
- I think this is the prize.
[Prize box for the winning team.]
[Tiger vs. the Lamb...
the end results are yet unknown.]
Defense...
Jong Kook is wearing the defense hat.
- What is this?
- Is this a joke?
[What? Sulli's name tag is off too?]
The next time I come on the show,
Jong Kook said he'd be my servant.
What are you talking about?
What do you mean, servant?
- You promised!
- I didn't say servant. I just said I'd help.
We won!
[How did this happen?]
I'll just say that I'll owe you one for this,
and let's just make a clean break...
The next time you come on the show,
no matter what happens... for you...
- I will serve you.
- Really?
- I'm being serious.
- You'll be my servant?
- You're going to be my slave?
- Seriously... slave isn't the right term.
For the whole show,
I will do whatever I can for you.
- For the year?
- Not the year!
[After making her the promise...]
[After eliminating Sulli's name tag,
Running Man Team wins!]
[Time to reveal the prize
to the winning team.]
At the count of three,
please open the prize box.
[It was a gold medal at the last Olympics,
what would it be this time?]
Why is it so light?
- What is this?
- What...
- Wait...
- Is it gold?
- No, it's not.
- What is this?
[The winning prize:
Not gold medals, gold colored name tags.]
[Still a long ways to go before
the gold prizes are brought back.]
- We won.
- Yay, we won.
[Jong Hyun in TV watching mode.]
The next time I'm on the show,
I'm going to eliminate you first.
- Really?
- What a joke. What a joke!
You have to go through us first.
Running Man, yeah!
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Reincarnation]
[1938- The old Seoul Town Hall.]
Get to the city hall immediately.
What are you doing here?
[Find the treasure chest!
A special envoy from seven organizations!]
What is this?
[The battle from that day that changed
the course of the future!]
[But there's a subtle energy surrounding
the group...]
[The treasure chest is empty!]
[Reincarnation.
Resurrected to change the future.]
I've been reborn!
The treasure chest
that was discovered in 1938.
One of the seven from the past has been
holding onto it for all these years.
[But there's a secret from the resurrection
that no one had any idea of.]
[Past and the present.
The reversed destiny.]
This is extremely important!
Going back to their former selves!
[The past 'me' will become
the present 'you'!]
[Fantasy thriller that travels through
the time from the past to the present!]
[Resurrection]