[Running Man's Asian Race]
[Legend of the golden dagger-
The secret of the nine daggers]
[Running Man on a journey to solve
the mystery of the nine daggers.]
[The first location of the epic journey-
Macau.]
[Joining forces with
secret agents in Macau.]
[Gather all nine of the daggers which
are scattered all over Asia.]
[A larger than life mission which spans
all over the globe.]
[Four out of nine daggers are found.]
[Current score of the daggers-
Yellow Team-2: Green Team-1: Blue Team-1]
[And later on that night...]
Here's your mission for tomorrow.
[Five remaining daggers must be found...]
[Three different language speaking people
show up to give their new commands.]
[Choose one of the three to hear
what the next mission is to be!]
You always pick women.
No, he's not Korean.
[Which of the teams will understand
what tomorrow's mission is to be?]
Subtitles by DramaFever
[And so the first night in their
epic Asian race comes to an end...]
['S' Hotel- 6:47 a.m.]
[Is everyone still asleep?]
[Giraffe is the first one awake?]
Is anyone out here yet?
[Giraffe looking nervous for some reason.]
[The reason for that being...]
[The order he heard last night...]
[In Chinese?]
[Pretending to be happy in order to
deceive the other teams.]
[They're screwed...]
Hey, I think I know what that word is.
'Soji' means, 'Young lady'.
Ground... I think she's saying above ground
instead of underground.
We're not going to get what she's saying even
if we stand here listening for the next year.
[Since he has no idea what the mission is, he
got up early to see what the others are up to.]
Is Suk Jin still sleeping?
[None of his own team members
seem to be awake yet...]
Jong Kook!
[Silence]
Don't most of our missions start
before 7 a.m.?
[Even the rooms of other members
remain silent...]
I guess everyone's still asleep.
[Ji Hyo from the Green Team wakes up.]
[What got into Blank Ji this morning?]
Hello.
[Last night...]
Hello, Running Man.
[Green Team's order is given in English!]
Did you have fun in Macau today?
[English...]
In order to get the remaining swords...
you need to go to Vietnam.
So tomorrow morning at 7 a.m...
you need to wake up and be at
the airport by 9 a.m. tomorrow.
- His English is a bit hard to understand.
- I think I sort of understand it.
[By putting together a few of the words,
they get a slight idea of what the order is.]
[Ji Hyo wakes up exactly
at 7 a.m. as ordered.]
Does my makeup look okay?
Where are you going?
[Gets discovered by the Giraffe
who's been out foraging for his prey.]
[An out of the blue chase in the morning.]
[Just a relief that the whole floor was being
occupied by only the members and the staff.]
- What are you doing!
- Be quiet.
Why are you doing this to me?
- What is this so early in the morning?
- Why are you out here?
- What?
- Why are you out in the hallway?
What do you mean, why am I out here?
- Where are you going?
- What do you mean, where am I going?
I'm going to Vietnam!
[Viet...nam?]
- Why are you going to Vietnam?
- Didn't you see the notice?
We all have to get ready and get to
the airport because we're going to Vietnam.
But everyone's still asleep.
What language did your translator speak?
- Chinese.
- She spoke Chinese?
- It's possible that she spoke something else.
- But you were clapping like you understood.
- That looked really natural, right?
- Yeah.
I had no idea what she was saying.
Hurry up and go get ready.
Isn't the mission in Macau?
[Extremely confused and flustered Giraffe.]
Shouldn't you at least let us know
where we're filming the show?
What a joke...
Save me!
- Kang Gary!
- Wait! I don't have any clothes on.
[Dressed or not...]
Don't open the door.
What are you doing up already?
When you're one of the biggest sleepy heads.
- Open the door.
- Lee Kwang Soo's lost his mind. Hurry.
[The door finally gets opened,
and he treats his guests to a morning apple.]
- Why are you up already?
- I went to bed early and just woke up.
I usually wake up early to have
my morning apple.
Just go and tell... your team members
to get up and get ready.
They're all still asleep.
They won't open the door
even when I ring the doorbell.
[Who was it that rang my doorbell earlier?]
We decided to take the bus there.
We were told that if we take the 64 route,
the bus will take us all the way to Vietnam.
You just need to take the route 64
in front of the Macau tower.
- Hurry up and go get ready.
- Seriously, go get ready quickly.
We've just given you a very important
piece of information.
[Giraffe is slowly starting to accept
the fact that they're heading to Vietnam.]
Go get ready.
Go wash up and get ready.
[At the same time]
Did everyone leave already?
[Yellow Team's Jae Suk and Ro-Ro
who are already all ready to go.]
We've been out here waiting for you.
We need to get on the move.
[All ready to go? In which
language were they given the order?]
Hello, Running Man members.
[Their order was given in Korean!]
Did you have fun in Macau today?
In order to find the remaining daggers...
you have to go to Vietnam.
You have to wake up at
7 a.m. tomorrow...
and get to the airport by 9 a.m.
But how... we just got here today.
Each team has to figure out their
own way of getting to the airport.
If by any chance,
you can't get to the airport on time
you won't be able to do the mission together
and will have to return to Korea.
You won't be able to do the mission together
[These people may have to
go back to Korea...]
[They're already on their way,
and Gary's room now sits vacant.]
[Finally understanding
the seriousness of the situation!]
Suk Jin, they're all gone.
- Where did they go?
- Everyone's already gone.
All the other teams are really gone.
No one's in their rooms anymore.
- That's seriously...
- I'm not positive, but we need to hurry.
Hey!
Jong Kook!
- Where is he? What's he doing?
- It takes him two hours to get ready.
[Mr. Capable is still getting ready after
being awoken from the doorbell earlier.]
Everyone's gone.
Where's Hye Jin? I was
told she's down here somewhere.
There they are.
- Where have you been?
- Where were you?
- I was having some breakfast.
- Really?
I needed to get some food.
- Let's go, Hye Jin.
- Okay, let's go.
Over there.
Good morning, Sir.
[Yellow Team is the first
to head to the airport!]
International airport, please.
[Blue Team short on time.]
Wait for me... go at my pace, okay?
[On top of being already late, they
now have an injured tiger to deal with.]
[Guessing ridiculous things from the
Chinese that they couldn't understand...]
[Their answer is to follow the other teams!]
We're really late, Jong Kook.
If we can't catch up to them out there,
it's over for us. We need to rush.
[But just then...]
[Discovers the Green Team
on their way out!]
[Nice timing...]
Don't you think we need to get a taxi
and catch up to them?
- Hey... we need to catch up to them. Hurry!
- Hurry... hurry!
- Excuse me... follow...
- Follow.
That car... follow, okay?
What's going to happen to the Blue Team
if Jong Kook is still asleep?
I'm sure they'll come on their own.
Don't worry about it.
- That's them, isn't it?
- Yeah, I think it's them up there.
Doesn't it feel like we're in
a spy movie?
It's like we're shooting a spy movie
here in Macau.
[The two teams are stopped next to one
another at the red traffic light.]
- What the heck?
- What is that?
They must've followed us.
Are they trying to hide?
- They're trying to hide.
- They're looking away from us right now.
They're not looking over at us.
Hey!
Hey, guys!
Pretend to be asleep.
Let's pretend we're all sleeping.
They're following us!
- Look at how they're acting!
- Look at them pretending to be asleep.
[They call that acting?]
I'm so annoyed!
- I can't believe that team.
- We should've left earlier.
- This is unbelievable timing.
- We did good.
I think we're going to the airport.
This is the airport.
[Are they really heading to Vietnam?]
- I guess we really are going to Vietnam.
- We're really going to Vietnam?
I bet there's a reason why we've been
told to get to the airport by nine.
Are we supposed to do a mission
at the airport?
[Macau Airport]
[Another dagger!]
You're just giving this to us?
[Yellow Team wins the fifth dagger
for being the first team to arrive.]
We have three daggers now.
[Yellow Teams gains their third dagger.]
- I feel a little bad.
- Do we just go in there?
[Will the Yellow Team be able to maintain
their first place position?]
- They're getting out.
[The Green Team and the Blue Team
arrive soon thereafter.]
- They're running.
- They're running?
[Continuing their plan to follow.]
I think we really are going somewhere.
But where?
Where are we supposed to go?
Look... even all our luggage is here.
Aren't you guys our staff members?
- Where are we going today?
- Where are we headed?
Where are we going today?
We're heading somewhere again when
we just arrived here yesterday?
[The staff members are in the same boat
when it comes to feeling flustered.]
- There was a mission.
- There really was a mission.
[One step too late...]
We shouldn't have stayed for breakfast.
- They already took it.
- Took what?
- There was a dagger here.
- There was a dagger?
- Kim Jong Kook...
- You're giving us our flight tickets?
Where are we going?
- Hanoi!
- We're going to Hanoi!
[Hanoi-bound!]
- Where's Hanoi?
- Hanoi, Vietnam!
We're going to Vietnam when we just
arrived in Macau yesterday?
This isn't like going from
Gwangju to Busan or something...
[From Macau to Vietnam...]
[Second day of the Asian Race-
Now to Vietnam to find the remaining daggers!]
- We're going to fly out right now.
- This really is an Asian tour.
We're really going to Vietnam?
Thank you!
[Saying goodbye to their Macau fans...]
Bye.
[The race isn't over yet...]
[Their next location - Vietnam.]
I will explain your next mission to you.
Choose the member from your opposing team
who you think may have the daggers
and switch out a member of your team.
Discuss amongst your own team members,
and decide who's going to be traded out.
[Yellow Team secretly stashes away
their cache of daggers.]
Two daggers in the yellow one.
One here...
and this one is a dud.
Nothing in this one.
[Green Team chooses one member
of the Yellow Team.]
You shouldn't have picked me.
[Jae Suk of the Green Team is
empty-handed.]
[And the member they're going
to kick out is?]
Kang Gary.
- Hey!
- Wow...
Wow... I seriously didn't think
you'd be like this.
- Lee Dong Wook.
- I think he has it!
- Dong Wook!
[The only dagger that the
Blue Team has...]
- Dong Wook had it!
- This is great!
- One, two, three!
- Ji Suk Jin.
Hey!
[Poor Green Team...]
[The Blue Team currently holds
two daggers.]
[They decide to split up the daggers between
Jong Kook and Dong Wook's bags.]
[What?]
[Unlike what they've agreed upon,
Kwang Soo puts both daggers into his bag?]
We played Rock-paper-scissors to decide.
[Jong Kook and Dong Wook's bags
currently have zero daggers in each.]
[Traitor Giraffe has
both the daggers in his possession...]
As for us...
Who are you going to pick?
- Lee Kwang Soo!
- Kwang Soo.
Lee Kwang Soo!
[In this case, what am I...]
[Both the daggers!]
[Giraffe gets traded out to the Yellow Team
with both the daggers in his possession.]
[Mr. Capable explodes with rage!]
That's not it! Dong Wook and I
are supposed to have them!
[Yellow Team gains all five
of the daggers!]
Are you even sane right now?
Are you of the sound mind?
Jong Kook, I really wondered if he would.
Wow, he really is the King of betrayals.
Dong Hoon, I'm sorry to ask this,
but can you send him back to our team?
Can you send him back to our team?
- One, two, three, Lee Kwang Soo!
- You can't do that!
[The moment he's recruited, Giraffe is
immediately returned back to his old team.]
I'm going to...
I'm seriously going to...
- Why did you do that?
- Lee Kwang Soo, you're dead.
[But thanks to his betrayal,
the Yellow Team gains all the daggers!]
- Are these the teams to the now?
- Be quiet!
[Out of pity, Yellow Team
gives one to the Green Team.]
[Second location in their Asia Race...]
[The capital of Vietnam, Hanoi.]
[A beautiful scenic nature...]
[A city that is home to this beautiful lake,
and over 3 million people.]
[Capital of Vietnam, Hanoi-
overflowing with vibrancy.]
[A food haven...]
[A place where nature and
present time coexists.]
[A breathless Asia race...]
[The secret of the nine daggers continues.]
[Hanoi Airport]
[Their first mission in Hanoi is?]
What is this?
[Go to Hoan Kiem Lake and
solve the mystery of the nine daggers!]
[Vietnam Race - Start!]
[Each team has their own taxi
to get them to their destination.]
You guys are so popular.
[Countless number of fans are here
to greet them as well.]
[Fascinated and grateful to all the fans
who came out to greet them.]
You guys are so popular!
- All over Asia...
- What do you think? Want to be our friend?
- I want to join the cast.
- She says she wants to join...
This is our first time here.
- But they're still so welcoming...
- It feels really great.
I'm really worried about today.
- Ji Hyo...
- I almost had a mental breakdown earlier.
Just consider yourself lucky to be on the
same team as us, who care for you very much.
- Do you know how...
- How are we going to win this today?
- What do you mean, what are we going to do?
- You're disrespecting our abilities too much.
- What are we seriously going to do?
- We're trying very hard right now.
[Finally driving into the heart of Hanoi.]
[With countless motorcycles...]
[And full of visitors.]
[Hoan Kiem- The lake serves as a retreat
for the citizens of Hanoi as well as...]
[a popular place for dates,
so it's always bustling with activity.]
[An award theater]
[A huge crowd of people
are already gathered around!]
[In front of a theater where an unbelievable
amount of people have gathered...]
[We're so glad to be here, Vietnam.]
[We had no idea so many fans would be
gathered to greet us!]
[An overflowing welcome.]
[Receiving a world star level welcome.]
[Barely gets into the inside of the theater.]
[To see such a huge gathering of a crowd...]
[An even grander welcoming crowd?]
[The crowd in front of the theater
breaks out into utter chaos.]
[After feverishly screaming out
Jong Kook's name...]
[Lee Kwang Soo!
Lee Kwang Soo!]
[Sights the Giraffe?]
[Asia Prince Kwang Soo's
overwhelming popularity.]
Kwang Soo is like Jang Dong Gun.
Kwang Soo is our very own Jang Dong Gun.
[Vietnam's Jang Dong Gun]
- Welcome.
- What took you guys so long?
- We had to go around the block.
- We couldn't get out of the car.
- Everyone...
I'm really sorry to say this, but
treat Kwang Soo very well from now on.
- Why?
- Lee Kwang Soo is Vietnam's Jang Dong Gun.
- Whatever.
- I'm serious.
- You're just finding that out?
It's seriously no joke.
I was totally shocked.
[Giraffe's Jang Dong Gun.]
[Really... that fascinating?]
- You can't get a big head over this, okay?
- No, it's not like that.
He had his sunglasses on the whole time
we were in the car getting here.
[Sunglasses on the whole time?]
What? On this cloudy day?
So Running Man is Lee Kwang Soo?
- You mean, Lee Kwang Soo is Running Man?
- Lee Kwang Soo is Running Man.
- That's what I meant.
- At least in Vietnam, Lee Kwang Soo is it.
[Their reason for coming
to the Award Theater is?]
We're going to show you a performance which
portrays the secret of the nine daggers.
- Is there a hint in the performance?
- What performance are you going to show us?
[Accompanied by Vietnam's traditional music.]
[The sound of someone singing
heard throughout the theater.]
- Look! There are dolls!
- Yeah... that's what we're supposed to see.
Are there people doing that?
She's singing the songs over there?
- She's singing live.
- She is singing over there.
[100% live performance]
[On the boat is a King and his servants...]
Isn't that Lee Kwang Soo in the back?
It's Kwang Soo!
Kwang Soo's in the back!
[What is the correlation between this
performance and the secret of the daggers?]
And if you don't count the King,
there are three people on that boat.
See? There are three people.
What's it doing?
[The legendary turtle?]
Where did that turtle come from?
It went under!
[Just then, the water starts
to roar again!]
I wonder if that turtle has
something to do with it?
- Don't do it, don't do it!
- Oh my... oh my God!
[Oh! The King's gold dagger!]
No!
[The truth is, the turtle repossessed
the gold dagger from the King...]
[and disappeared
into the depths of the lake...]
- The turtle took the gold dagger.
- He lost his dagger.
[It looks like this is the
legend of the gold dagger...]
[Another roar of the water!]
- What is that? A letter?
- It's a mission statement!
[What? A mission statement?]
It's a mission statement!
[Matching the beat of the lively music.]
[The turtle brings
the mission statement to them.]
[What's on the mission statement
that the turtle has brought?]
[Collect all nine of the daggers and
the gold dagger will be resurrected!]
[Go to where the rest of the remaining
daggers awaits you!]
[When the nine daggers are put together...]
[the gold dagger will be resurrected?]
[Could this be a message notifying
them of the gold dagger's resurrection?]
[Find the remaining...]
[four daggers that are scattered
about on this land!]
[And when all the nine daggers
are gathered together...]
[The gold dagger will be resurrected.]
[Off to find the daggers in Hanoi - Start!]
[From the theater...
to the market in Ta Hien!]
[Ta Hien Street: Largest street tourist
attraction in Hanoi.]
We really are here.
There's a certain flair to this place.
[A long stretch of streets with
a European flair.]
[What's the mission that
awaits them here?]
[Exchanging greetings with PD Myuk,
whom they haven't seen in a while.]
Welcome to Vietnam.
The biggest shopping district in Vietnam
is the 36th street market.
This is known as 'Ta Hien Street'.
You will be carrying out your missions
right in this market.
- Okay.
- What is it?
Move the contents in the basket as quickly
as possible until it's down to zero.
If you win a round of Rock-Paper-Scissors,
you can take out one of the items.
If you lose, then you will have to add
additional items to the basket.
[In the streets of Ta Hien...]
[There are 'R1'- 'R7' stores.]
[In Vietnamese,
Rock-Paper-Scissors is 'mot-hai-ba'.]
[If the team member wins the game,
they can take out as much as they bet...]
[But if they lose, they will have to add
double the amount of their bet.]
Be cautious how much you bet.
I will show you your baskets.
[The baskets they will
have to carry around are...]
[Traditional Vietnamese baskets.]
[Mission - Start!]
We have to start off by betting a lot.
Start off by betting a lot.
[Must get rid of all 20 fruits to pass
and win the dagger.]
We have to bet a lot to get this over with.
Bet three at least.
[Where's a shop with the 'R' flag?]
Up there...
Wow, the streets are so beautiful.
[Can't help but be impressed with the sights
even as they struggle with the baskets.]
It's so pretty.
Ma'am... Ma'am!
[Discovers the 'R1' shop.]
- Ma'am, we're going to bet five.
- Five... bet five.
[Starting off the race by betting five!]
- Paper, rock, scissors!
Paper, rock, scissors!
[Unbelievable... Suk Jin wins!]
[Darn!]
Paper, rock, scissors...
[Jae Suk's turn]
Paper, rock, scissors!
[If Ji Hyo also wins, they
succeed in getting rid of five fruits!]
Mother, paper, rock, scissors!
[Will she win?]
Paper, rock, scissors!
[Blank Ji also wins!]
- We're good.
- I can't believe you won it too!
[Unlike their previous worries,
they're now full of cheer and optimism!]
[Green Team succeeds in
getting rid of five!]
[Off to the next shop]
We should've bet it all.
- Here... here's one.
- Here it is.
[Discovers 'R2' shop]
How about three?
[Agrees to start off by betting three.]
- What should I throw out?
- First...
- Scissors.
- Scissors?
[A round of paper, rock, scissors
with the owner.]
Paper, rock, scissors.
Paper, rock, scissors!
He was late.
He threw it out too late.
- He was late with his throw.
- He was late!
[They all seem to work as one
when it comes to arguing?]
[First one is disregarded.]
Paper, rock, scissors!
[Throws out another scissors and loses.]
You're really bad at this.
You're really bad at rock, paper, scissors!
Move out, move out!
There's one!
[Right onto 'R5']
- Ji Hyo, you do it this time.
- You do it this time.
[Entrusting their success to Ace Ji Hyo.]
Bet five of the big ones.
- Jae Suk, what if we don't win?
- It's okay, just do it!
- You can do it.
- Don't worry, you can do it!
Okay, let's bet five.
Ji Hyo, do it.
[Bets five and challenges 'R5'.]
Rock, paper, scissors!
[She truly is our Blank Ji!]
Okay, we're good.
Suk Jin, you're up.
[Next up is, Big-nosed Brother.]
Rock, paper, scissors!
- What's your deal?
- What the heck? What are you doing?
What the heck are you doing?
Seriously?
[They have to take five more
on top of what they bet...]
This is bad.
[The basket is starting to
get heavier with fruit.]
Thank you.
This is a big problem.
[Their pace is starting to slow down
with every step that they take.]
[The Yellow Team's baskets are looking
just as abundant.]
- Here, here.
- Here it is. There's one right here.
[Discovers 'R6']
- Four.
- We're going to bet four.
[Bets four on the challenge.]
- Should I start?
- Yes.
[Everyone's feeling burdened
to be the first one up.]
- I'm not feeling very good about this.
- Okay, I'll start it then.
[Haroro steps up first
for the challenge.]
High five, high five!
Yes, high five!
Rock, paper, high five!
High five, yes, yes!
High five!
Okay, okay... Rock, paper, bread!
[Aren't you going to do it?]
[Putting a lot of effort into
teasing the shop keeper...]
Okay, okay, let's go!
Okay, rock, paper, scissors!
[Darn...]
[Defeated]
[After all that teasing...]
- He could just give us small ones!
- Small, small!
- Where do we go?
- Should we go straight?
Kim Jong Kook!
They're still saying Lee Kwang Soo
even though you're saying Kim Jong Kook.
What's going on here?
[Instead of Jong Kook's name,
they're chanting Kwang Soo's name?]
[I'm the Giraffe of Asia!]
Lee Kwang Soo!
[Question one:
Is his name just easy to shout out?]
[Question two: Could his name
mean something in Vietnamese?]
[A shocking reaction from the crowd.]
[A fascinating crowd with their
fervor for the Giraffe.]
[Due to their slow pace, the scene's been
transformed into an impromptu fan meeting.]
[It's Jae Suk!]
Ji Hyo...
Ji Hyo, bet it all.
- Bet it all.
- Get yourself together!
- Winning this isn't easy, Jae Suk!
- Ji Hyo, bet it all.
- Get yourself together!
- One... just bet one.
Ji Hyo... my shoulder
feels like it's going to fall off.
- Just bet it all.
- Bet it all.
[With the pain in his shoulders,
he's teetering on the edge of insanity.]
Ji Hyo, bet everything.
Bet one whole basket.
One basket.
Rock, paper, scissors.
- Want me to do it? Should I?
- Do it.
[With one whole basket on the line,
Big-nosed Brother starts the challenge.]
[This time... I will win!]
[No way...]
[Will he win?]
[With one whole basket
hanging on the line...]
Rock, paper, scissors!
[The damned scissors...]
How are we supposed to carry
all these around?
Jae Suk, let's just load up and go
to the shop next door.
- Okay, the shop next door.
- All this fruit...
[Green Team with a whole other
basket added to their load.]
Ji Hyo, let's go.
Let's go to the shop next door.
- All this.
- Bet it all.
[Nothing to even think about anymore?
Going all in?]
- This woman...
- She's the one who's good at it.
She is the master of rock, paper, scissors.
Rock, paper, scissors Master.
- Bet it all.
- Rock, paper, scissors.
- Everything... all in!
- All in!
[No time!
Going all in?]
[Betting all three of their baskets...]
Rock, paper, scissors!
[Jae Suk wins!]
[Oh... not bad?]
Ji Hyo... we're all in.
You have to get it done.
[Ace Ji Hyo's turn.]
Ji Hyo, we're all in.
We're all in.
We're not backing down from this.
[Okay... let's do this!]
[Ace Blank Ji vs.
Master of rock, paper, scissors grandmother.]
Rock, paper...
Rock, paper, scissors!
[Lost again...]
[Defeated after having gone all in...]
They can't even lift all that.
[Green Team's baskets flowing over the top.]
[Bowed to the extreme]
[Enough fruit to open up their own shop.]
Let's go win this thing.
Hey, let's go win this thing.
[Blue Team with 16 fruits still remaining
is going to win this thing?]
[The speed of their movement
is the same as a turtle's.]
Ma'am!
All in!
[Okay, whatever... let's bet it all!]
- All in.
- All in. We're going to go all in!
- 16.
- 16... we're going to go all in!
[Blue Team also goes all in
with their 16 remaining fruits.]
We're going to win this no matter what.
[I don't think so.]
Can you please let us win
just this once?
This is too hard.
Very tired.
Very heavy.
[But still... a win is a win!]
[Starting off with Blank Ji.]
[I will show no mercy!]
All in!
Rock, paper, scissors!
[Oh... Blank Ji wins!]
[Sweeps the first round with a win.]
[Next up is their wild card,
Big-nosed Brother.]
[Being cheered on by the fans.]
Rock, paper, scissors!
[If Jae Suk wins, it's a perfect win!]
- Again?
- Yes, one more.
Rock, paper, scissors!
[Blue Team is also playing
with everything on the line.]
They don't throw out a lot of scissors.
It's usually paper or a rock.
Okay.
[Will Dong Wook's scissors win?]
Rock, paper, scissors!
[Their guess is right on the money?]
[Dong Wook wins the first round.]
- Because we did it so quickly...
- Doing it quickly flustered her.
We flustered her.
Wait, let's think.
- Scissors. Throw out scissors.
- Rock, paper, scissors!
[Just as they guessed,
win with the scissors again!]
We got it... we got it.
[Now if only Mr. Capable can win...]
[And in this team,
Jae Suk is the only one left.]
[With extreme nervousness.]
Jae Suk, we're all in.
Everything's riding on you.
[Dear Lord of variety shows...]
[Mr. Capable and Jae Suk with the fate
of their teams riding on their shoulders...]
You just need to do it this once!
[Throw out the scissors again?]
- It could work.
- No...
[Come on, let's go!]
[Just what is his vision telling him?]
Rock, paper, scissors!
[Will it be scissors? Paper?]
[The fateful rock, paper, scissors...]
[Jong Kook wins!]
[Jae Suk also wins!]
[Green Team and Blue Team
succeeds their missions!]
[All-in's win for win!]
- We did it!
- All-in!
- Thank you.
- Thank you!
Thank you... thank you!
Okay, let's go.
- This is it.
- I'm so beyond elated!
Let's go, let's go.
[Their exciting victory.]
Thank you so much.
[The two teams who were at the risk
of seriously damaging their shoulders...]
[Who will take possession of the dagger
from this mission?]
- Thank you!
- Thank you.
[Green Team]
[Goes to the Green Team who got
to the dagger first.]
Thank you, Ma'am!
[The Green Team wins a dagger!]
We still got second place though.
- We got rid of them all between two places.
- We were good with the analyzing, right?
When it comes to analyzing things,
Jong Kook really is...
Wow... seriously...
when it comes to analyzing...
- We did it.
- We did it. We really did it.
- Lee Kwang Soo, you're something else here.
- It's very impressive.
Vietnam, I love you.
I love Vietnam.
I thought Thailand was your love.
And I love Thailand.
And Hong Kong.
- Macau...
- China and Macau too.
I have very many hearts.
- Very many hearts?
- My heart is yours.
[I guess 'heart' can be used to describe
feelings as well as being an organ...]
Are you telling everyone that
you're going to donate your heart right now?
- How do you get that?
- He's right.
Are you going to donate it
while you're still in a living state?
What are you talking about?
36.
Going all in with 36.
- You know how many that means if you lose?
- Yes.
- Yes!
- 72.
[Their opponent is
the 'R6' shopkeeper from earlier.]
Rock, paper, scissors!
[Hye Jin wins!]
[How long has it been since
they had a win?]
Rock, paper, scissors!
[Gary also wins!]
[Wasting no time at all,
they win one after another!]
[Last one remaining, Haroro.]
Dong Hoon, you can do it!
36... there are 36 of them in there!
[An impromptu performance for their fans?]
[An unidentifiable hybrid of
freestyle dancing.]
[Hye Jin's hidden dancing skills.]
Please...
[One last round with
all 36 hanging on the line.]
- If we lose, it means 72.
- We're going to need another pole.
Okay, one time!
[Will Haroro win?]
[Win!]
[Yellow Team succeeds the mission!]
[Darn!]
- You are the last to pass the mission.
- Really?
- Anyways, leave the fruits with him...
- Thank you, Papa!
[No matter, thanking the shopkeeper...]
There are three locations.
One person from each team
needs to go to those locations.
[One person from each team per location.
1:1:1 competition.]
[A parade of countless motorcycles.]
Hye Jin... we're really popular, aren't we?
- You're really shocked, aren't you?
- I'm shocked not one person said my name.
Don't you think it's because
they didn't know?
It's because they didn't know
about you coming.
- Not a single person said my name.
- It's because they didn't know.
But still, even if they didn't know,
since I'm here now...
Now that they know, they could've said it.
I'm going to win them over.
[Passing through the heart of Hanoi...]
[West Lake- A lake 17 km in length
through the city of Hanoi.]
[A food mecca in Hanoi,
the city of lakes.]
[A place where one can get a true taste
of Vietnamese delicious cuisine!]
[This is... delicious Hanoi!]
[Arriving at one of the restaurants.]
[A famous seafood buffet
restaurant in Hanoi.]
I'm glad we came here.
[A traditional looking restaurant
adding to the ambiance.]
[What's the mission that
awaits them here?]
- Wow, look at this.
- Is this it?
Wow... awesome!
Look at the chairs.
This place is way too nice.
[But... why are there four chairs?]
[Is there a meaning to where they sit?]
Then I'm going to sit here.
[Passing out the mission.]
[The person who eats
the 31st dish is disqualified.]
[The person who remains
to the end is the winner.]
- But why are there four seats?
- Is someone else coming?
We have a special guest here
who will be filling in the fourth seat.
[A special person to fill in the seat?]
[Opening the door and
making his entrance is...]
[The chef?]
- Hi, Chef.
- Chef is joining us?
- Hello Chef.
- Yes... Hello, Sir.
- Hello.
- He is a Chef here.
- He's the chef here?
- He's going to play the game with you.
- Really?
- He is?
So he's the wild card.
- You can eat three each.
- Three?
And the chef can eat as much
as he'd like.
- I have to win this...
- Yes, I have to win this too.
[The food makes its entrance.]
What is this?
- What is it?
- Isn't it dumplings?
This dish is known as 'Buying-kkuon'.
[Buying-kkuon-
Mushrooms wrapped in rice paper.]
It smells a little like vinegar.
[Just what does it taste like?]
I think there's vinegar in there.
[Dong Wook starts off the game.]
[Just one to taste.]
- You're just going to eat one?
- The taste is...
It's really good.
Since you said you were only going to
eat one, just eat one.
[Dong Wook eats two.]
I wonder what this is going to taste like.
Isn't it good?
It tastes unbelievable.
This is really amazing!
This is calling Buying-kkuon?
- Buying-kkuon.
- Buying-kkuon?
[Mouthwatering flavor.]
[Openly staring...]
What are you staring at?
I'm eating!
- What are you staring at?
- What?
- I'm just looking! What?
- Why are you staring at me eating?
What's wrong with looking?
The cameras are watching you too!
- Wow... this is amazing.
- Yeah, it's really delicious.
Since we can only eat three,
you're done, right?
- Good.
Very good.
[Chef who is allowed to eat as much
as he wants takes his turn.]
Chef, good!
[This is the shrimp bread street.]
[Fascinated by shrimp bread,
which they've never seen before.]
[shrimp bread street near West Lake.]
[Hanoi's signature shrimp bread with the
flavors of shrimp permeating the taste buds.]
[What is the mission that
awaits them here?]
This is a really nice view.
The view is really nice.
Here... take a look at what
the game is.
[Guess the Korean song that
a Vietnamese person will be singing.]
- This is going to be hard.
- That's hard.
This is going to be really hard.
[The first team to correctly guess
two questions wins the game.]
- Do you know all the current songs?
- No, I don't know.
-  We're in trouble.
- I don't know them either.
[Everyone seems to be full of concern.]
Guess the name of the song
that they will be singing.
[The person who'll be singing
the song for them is...]
[The owner of this restaurant
with a pleasant smile.]
Please sing it well, okay?
Music... cue!
[First song]
[What... is that song?]
[You're saying this is a popular song?]
[Did Big-nosed Brother figure it out?]
What is this?
- You know what this is?
- No clue.
Baby, baby... is that it?
Um...
- Super Junior's...
- You're so pretty.
Super... she said I'm pretty?
She said I'm pretty?
Can you hurry up and say it?
Hye Jin!
- Hye Jin!
- Hye Jin... you've got five seconds.
[Hye Jin with the owner's hand
tightly grasped in her hand.]
I don't care even if I don't get it right.
It's Super Junior's...
[Super Junior's?]
- I'm sorry, but can you hurry it up?
- You have five seconds.
- It's a really popular song.
- I know, it's that one.
[A very popular song that she can't
seem to think of...]
[Frustrated]
- That Super Junior song?
- Why can't I think of it?
Three, two, one.
Cha cha!
[Huh? Super Junior's 'Cha Cha'?]
Super Junior doesn't have
a 'Cha Cha' song.
What is she talking about?
Answer!
SHINee's 'Ring-ding-dong'.
'Ring-ding-dong'.
That's not right.
[Huh? That's the 'Ring-ding-dong'?]
[Correct answer]
[Was just a guess,
but it was the correct answer!]
[Hyun Woo... your dad got it right!]
[Kind of sounds right...]
- She's right... it really is the song.
- She really is singing the song!
She was singing with an inflection.
Look at how happy Hye Jin is
even though she didn't guess it.
She said she doesn't even need to guess it
since she's been told she's pretty.
- What's that Super Junior song?
- When are you giving us some of that?
- Sorry, sorry?
- Ah, Sorry, sorry...
I'm sorry to interrupt... but she said
that Super Junior song is 'Sorry, sorry'.
- And she called it 'Cha Cha Cha'.
- I couldn't think of it.
The song that she said was 'Cha Cha Cha'...
[Each getting to sample the shrimp bread.]
[Second question]
All the songs really sound alike.
- Super Junior's 'Sorry, sorry'.
- That's what you always say!
[Oh! Correct answer!]
She really got it right?
[Hye Jin guesses it correctly after
thinking everything was 'Sorry, sorry'.]
[Verifying the answer]
[What she was saying was, 'sorry, sorry'.]
[It's time to start worrying
about the numbers...]
[Jae Suk just keeps on going.]
I don't think he's worried about the game,
but is just eating because it's good.
[Looks like he's happy to see
Jae Suk enjoying the dish so much.]
[Only about ten left on the tray.]
Enjoy it and eat a lot, okay?
[Chef with no limit on how many he can
eat, just how many will he eat?]
Stop? Stop?
[Chef doesn't look as though
he's about to stop anytime soon.]
Go, go, go, go!
Go, go!
[Wait? At this rate...]
- Okay.
- Okay!
[Eats another]
[Oh? Look at this guy...]
I have to win... I really have to win.
If you tell him, 'Gae-took',
it means 'stop' in Vietnamese.
Gae-took!
- No.
- No?
- Okay, eat.
Go, go!
We're good, we're good!
[This is good...]
[Inhales]
[I can't be...]
[One last remaining...]
Gae-took!
[I'll stop now.]
How can you do this to me?
- Gae-took?
- Yes, Gae-took.
Eat it!
You were eating so well!
[Ha Ha - disqualified.]
- You're the best!
- That was great!
Gae-took.
I really like that, Gae-took.
Since the game is over for you anyway,
just eat it since it's good.
[Chef who loves to laugh.]
I hope we get another delicious dish.
That was so good.
[Next up on the menu is...]
- It's rice noodles!
- I love noodles!
[Vietnam's representative dish,
rice noodles.]
Rice noodles!
Pho!
[And so, the new groom doesn't get to
taste the flavors of the noodle dish.]
[Asia's Prince, Giraffe
arrives at his destination.]
[An even bigger crowd awaiting his arrival.]
[Vegetarian Giraffe pulling in a huge crowd
everywhere he goes.]
[The mission that awaits them here is?]
You can all read the mission together.
[Blindfold one person and have that person
swipe the hats off the other two's heads.]
- What does that mean?
- Here?
It's like hide and seek.
Two people need to go and hide.
Wait... I can't hear anything right now with
the crowd shouting out Kwang Soo's name.
Can you explain it one more time?
I'll explain it to you once more.
One person will be blindfolded...
[Inside this Vietnamese wrap restaurant...]
[One person is the seeker and the
other two will escape with the hats on.]
[The person who catches the other two in the
shortest amount of time is the winner!]
[Restaurant near the West Lake that
serves up delicious Vietnamese rice wraps.]
- Let's do rock, paper, scissors.
- The winner decides who goes?
Rock, paper, scissors.
[The decision is up to the winner, Gary.]
Going first is disadvantageous.
In that case...
- Kwang Soo, you go first.
- Why me?
No, Kwang Soo, you go first.
You think just because you do that,
things will happen between you two?
She's putting on that pouty face.
Why are you doing this?
What is that?
[Putting on the cute act?]
[Putting on the cute act for him?]
- Okay, then Ji Hyo can go last.
- What the heck is that?
[Ji Hyo is the very last to go.]
- But I don't have a single dagger.
- Kwang Soo will go first.
- Then I'll go and Ji Hyo will go last.
- Yes!
- Kwang Soo, you'll be fine.
- Lee Kwang Soo!
[But the crowd outside are all
Giraffe's fans?]
[Give me strength as
I'm stuck between this couple.]
[Take all the strength you need from us!]
[Kwang Soo the seeker, is first to start.]
Shouldn't you still be clapping?
You have to clap.
[Incites the crowd to scream.]
[Confusing him with
all the screams from his fans.]
Wait! Wait!
Be quiet!
Quiet!
[Asking them to stop chanting his name?]
[If the Prince of Asia tells us to...]
[The crowd falls into silence.]
[Asia's Giraffe concentrating with
all his might.]
[Gary in danger!]
[Gary barely able to make his escape.]
[Giraffe's moves definitely becoming
more clear than earlier.]
Kwang Soo!
[Gary - out!]
[Just one more.]
[Ji Hyo tries to joke around...]
[and totally gets caught by the Giraffe.]
[Ji Hyo - out!]
[All hail, Lee Kwang Soo!]
[Feels like the whole neighborhood
is celebrating!]
[I am the Giraffe!]
[But seriously... why is he so popular?]
[Everyone has each guessed
one question correctly.]
[This song will determine
the direction of the dagger...]
[Totally clueless...]
What are you singing?
'Unbelievable sorts' by Yook-gaksu!
- How could you think that?
- That's what she was singing!
Is it a current song?
It's not a very recent song, right?
- Sorry to ask, but do you have any clue?
- I have no idea.
- Can you give us a hint?
- I don't know about Hye Jin...
[With her singing so well,
no hint will be given!]
[Does Hye Jin have a guess?]
- Park Hyun Bin's 'Sha-bang, Sha-bang'?
- No way...
I doubt it's a trot.
[Wow! Correct answer!]
[Hye Jin wins this mission!]
[A joyful dance time with the owner.]
[Hye Jin brimming with excitement.]
[Wasn't I good?]
[After having heard it once,
it sounds very similar!]
- She sang that one part several times.
- Yes, she did.
[An unlimited challenge
at the seafood restaurant?]
[The next dish is a fruity dessert
known as, 'Jjaerayo'.]
[Since the Chef has been disqualified,
it's now between Dong Wook and Jae Suk.]
- How is it?
- It's totally your style.
I bet it'll be unbelievable.
- Stop.
- Already?
What are you going to do?
What if I leave just one?
[You're not really going to eat
28 all at once, are you?]
We still have more show to tape.
I don't think I'll be able to
eat that many.
- Because it's so sweet...
- With a sour after-taste.
Stop.
What are you laughing about now?
[Master of laughter]
[He seems to find their pronunciation
of the word, 'Gae-took' funny.]
Do you find my pronunciation funny?
[Competition with
the dagger hanging on the line.]
Four.
[Inhaling his fourth one.]
He just laughed over Dong Wook saying four
instead of the word, 'Gae-took' this time.
Gae-took.
[Only 12 remaining...
Should I end the game here?]
Stop.
[Unsure of what to do
with only 11 left remaining.]
[The sweet and tart fruit...
can he really eat 10?]
[Eats one first.]
Gae-took.
Do you like it that much
when they say Gae-took?
[Seems to be enjoying watching these
two struggling with their decision.]
One, two, three, four...
[The person who eats nine of them
will be the winner...]
[Nine left to go.
Jae Suk starts off by eating one.]
Gae-took.
[An explosive reaction.]
[Dong Wook's turn to ponder.]
[Starting off with one!]
[Oh... two!]
Maybe he'll eat all of them.
Keep going, keep going!
Look at him go!
Kko-ren, Kko-ren!
-Kko-ren...
- Kko-ren!
[Dong Wook seems to be on a warpath.]
I think this is over!
Doesn't it feel like it's going to be over?
Kko-ren.
Finish it.
Gae-took?
[Is it going to be Gae-took? Or is it...]
All the saliva is pooling
in my mouth...
Okay, I see what you're
made of now.
[Four left to go for the win.]
Jae Suk, I think...
- Kko-ren!
- Kko-ren! Kko-ren!
[Is it hitting him?]
Kko-ren?
Gae-took...
[Two left for the win.]
[Will it be 'Kko-ren' or
will it be 'Gae-took'?]
[Kko-ren...]
Kko-ren?
[The tart and sweetness
exploding in his mouth.]
[Will he really gae-took with
one left to go?]
Gae-took, Gae-took...
[What will Dong Wook's decision be?]
[He goes for his last one...]
[An explosive reaction.]
- I can't believe I lost...
- Kko-ren, Kko-ren...
He ate them all!
[Only one left remaining.]
Gae-took.
[Dong Wook's victory.]
I'm so disappointed.
Since this is Gae-took anyway,
I'll give it to Ha Ha.
- Okay.
- Okay, try it.
This really is good.
I feel like I'm about to start tearing up.
Dong Wook, you did good.
[Dong Wook's spurt of action.]
I thought Dong Wook would
only eat one.
I can't believe he ended
the game like that though.
[Presents with the dagger.]
Thank you.
- Thank you. Thank you so much.
- Okay, thank you.
- He won his dagger.
- I finally did it.
[He won the seventh dagger.]
We have two and they have five.
You don't have any?
No, we don't have any.
- Because of Kwang Soo...
- This team needs at least one.
Thank you.
[Takes home the eighth dagger.]
You've got 10 seconds left
to catch Kwang Soo.
[If he can hold out for another 10 seconds,
Kwang Soo wins for being the fastest.]
Eight... seven...
[Kwang Soo being backed up
into the corner.]
Four...
[Please...]
One!
[With the strength of his height...
he wins!]
Kwang Soo wins.
[A fervent reaction from the crowd.]
A round of applause, please.
- His height won it for him.
- It's cheating.
Here is your prize.
[Tall Kwang Soo wins his dagger.]
[And here's the ninth dagger.]
[You did good.]
Go away!
[All nine of the daggers are
now found.]
[Their next destination is...]
[Hanoi Landmark Tower]
- Thank you!
I wonder who won at the
other locations?
I feel like the Prince of Asia
would've won his.
With the energy from the crowd?
[Right on the money.]
[A nonstop scream from the fans greet
The Prince of Asia with his newly won dagger.]
[Gary awed by Running Man TV's celebrity,
Asia's Giraffe, Lee Kwang Soo.]
There are about three million motorcycles
following Lee Kwang Soo to his next location.
I've always wanted to come visit Vietnam
ever since I was a little kid.
- So you've realized your dreams?
- Yes.
[Giraffe realizes his dreams.]
Lee Kwang Soo is seriously
stuck in a quandary right now.
He's wondering if he should be changing
his nationality to Vietnamese...
- He's thinking very seriously...
- It's only because of Running Man!
[Even though seeing motorcycles alongside
a car is a common sight in Vietnam...]
[A sign with Gary's name on it, which
they haven't seen all afternoon.]
[But as soon as she sees Kwang Soo,
she changes the sign to Kwang Soo's?]
[This is the power of Asia's Giraffe.]
- Vietnam...
- It's unreal.
A place where everyone else's sign gets
switched out for Lee Kwang Soo's.
It really must be an honor.
Can everyone see what's behind us?
[Even behind them is a parade
of motorcycles.]
About 2km behind us right now...
A parade of motorcycles are trailing
behind us that is about 2km long.
[Truly a spectacle.]
We have a staff member here who's been
living in Vietnam for about five years now.
Have you ever seen anything like this
in Vietnam before?
- No, I haven't.
- You haven't?
- Lee Kwang Soo's been turned into an Idol.
- Come on, it's for all of us.
[Final mission location at last.]
[The pride of Vietnam-
Hanoi Landmark Tower.]
[Everywhere they go, they're
greeted by a grateful welcoming.]
[All the Running Man members start
to arrive at the final location.]
[The final journey to find the gold dagger.
What kind of a mission will they find here?]
72nd floor... that's high.
- Is this it? This building?
- Yeah.
It was supposedly built by Koreans.
[Our country's skills, and capitol.
Pride of Vietnam built by Republic of Korea.]
[At a height of 350m and 72 stories,
it is the tallest building in Indo China.]
Do you know this?
This building is the tallest in Indo China.
That's what I just said.
[Entering the hotel where the chase will
be taking place between 62-72nd floors.]
- Did you win it?
- Of course, I won it.
[Most reliable member of the
Yellow Team, Hye Jin.]
You really are like Joan of Arc.
[Variety show's Joan of Arc?]
One, two, three, four!
[To celebrate winning the dagger,
breaks out into a celebratory dance.]
Koreans built this building.
Even when you look at it from the
outside, your neck just...
Lately... the term, 'Blank' that you've been
entitled with seems to be at its peak...
Jae Suk, my mind has been a little
all over the place today.
[After traveling all over the place for the
past few days, her mind is a little...]
- This is insane.
- Its a relief we can't see anything.
[The roof deck at the top of the building.]
- Come here.
- Wow... this is so scary.
[A different sort of fright
from the Macau Tower.]
Anyway, that aside...
you didn't win a dagger?
[But they're still the only team
made of all men.]
[The victory... will ultimately be ours!]
Hello, Running Man.
- Hello.
- Hello, Running Man.
- Yes.
- Hello.
- Hello!
Those of you who've gathered the most
daggers in the past two days...
This mission will be the most advantageous
to the team with the most daggers.
Your final mission to solve
the mystery of the daggers is...
elimination of the name tags.
[Final mission:
Name tag elimination mission.]
So it's the name tag elimination?
The team with the final surviving member
is the ultimate winner of the mission.
But the important factor here is...
only the people with the daggers in hand
can participate in the game.
- Wow! That means we can all participate!
- Wait...
- What?
- Only those with daggers can participate?
Only those with a dagger?
If there are any teams that only hold
two daggers within their team...
Only two members of the team can
participate in the name tag elimination.
Then what about the rest?
[Unfortunately,
for the last remaining member...]
[They will be escorted off to jail
as soon as the game starts.]
[If the team only has two daggers,
one will have to go off to jail...]
No, there are two teams
with two daggers.
You can exchange the daggers in for
just as many name tags.
[Same number of name tags will be exchanged
for the number of daggers handed in.]
[Total number of name tags one single person
can trade their daggers in for are two.]
Five... I bet those guys are happy.
And, one more thing...
Hidden throughout this place...
are shields.
[There are shields
hidden throughout the place.]
If you find one of these shields...
figure out how to use them,
and we hope that you use them wisely.
In this case, since the other team has
five daggers, all of them can participate.
And two of them are going
to have two lives.
- We'll give Hye Jin two...
- We'll give her two.
And you can have two.
I think people are going to think that
I'm going to be one with two lives.
- I understand.
- In that case...
- I'll go in.
- To jail?
Since... since I'm a little injured...
- No, Jong Kook. I'll go in.
- Kwang Soo, get your head on straight!
Kwang Soo...
- Get your head on straight. I'll go in.
- No.
[Is this an act? Why are they
all of a sudden acting loyal?]
Don't be like this.
This is boring.
You have to remain strong, Kwang Soo.
[Since they're both volunteering to go,
I'm not going to stop them.]
Kwang Soo, you have to remain strong.
This is said to be the tallest building
in Indo China.
You and I will be able to work together
again in the future. Kwang Soo...
So I guess I'm going to get to participate?
Seeing how those two are right now?
Okay, I'm in.
Somehow... somehow, I'll find a way!
Find a way somehow,
and bring me in later on.
I understand.
Just wait a little while.
[I'm so bored...]
I'll put my life on the line to find a way.
- Okay, Kwang Soo.
- Jong Kook!
Kwang Soo!
[Beautiful...]
[Just go on to jail...]
Do you really have to do it like this?
- This is really...
- This is so cruel.
Hurry up and go, Suk Jin.
We have to get on with the show.
- You guys have to make sure to win, okay?
- Of course.
[Only two daggers. Ji Hyo and
Jae Suk are the only participants]
One more thing.
If the two of you are caught together
by the protectors of the daggers...
you're going to be separated
right away.
- They can even eliminate your name tag.
- I understand.
Stay sharp and survive this, okay?
- Let's stay sharp.
- Okay.
[For the teams that are short on men,
finding the shield is their priority!]
[Who will be the ultimate victor
of the nine daggers?]
[Mission - start!]
We can see everything from here.
[An easy way to see everything thanks to
an open floor plan on the guests' floors.]
Find the shield.
[Green Team's Ji Hyo is on the search
up on the observation deck.]
The clouds are coming my way!
Look! It's the clouds!
[The clouds really are
right in front of her eyes!]
This means that we're up high
in the clouds right now!
[But...]
[Aren't you scared at all?]
[On the other hand,
Yellow Team with their two extra lives.]
There... I see it, I see it.
Over there, over there.
I can see him over there.
[Making her approach slowly
as if she really is the Joan of Arc.]
[Discovers each other!]
[Yellow Team's Hye Jin vs.
Blue Team's Dong Wook!]
[Yellow Team's first life in danger!]
Hey!
Be careful!
[Kwang Soo takes off to help Dong Wook
after hearing all the shouting.]
[Hye Jin lying down to stick her back
down on the floor.]
[If anything, it's the two men who are
struggling against her.]
Ha Ha!
[Starts to attack her way through!]
[After figuring out which floor she's on...
he's off!]
Ha Ha!
[Hye Jin uses her legs to attack Kwang Soo!]
[What a spectacle...]
No, no!
Rip it off!
Rip off her tag!
Hurry up and rip it off!
[Yellow Team's Hye Jin...
Loses one of her two name tags.]
I'm sorry. Sorry.
[Gary arrives one step too late.]
- They ripped it off.
- You got ripped off?
- By whom?
- Kwang Soo... and Dong Wook!
I told you! Kwang Soo
doesn't care if you're a girl!
Seriously... I didn't take Kwang Soo
to be like that, but really...
[Yellow Team's name tag count-
Hye Jin:1, Ha Ha:2, Gary:1.]
- I should call him on the transmitter.
- That I'm on my last one.
[Hye Jin attaches her last
name tag on her back.]
I think I need to tie my hair back.
A ton of my hair got ripped out.
[Fine, no more nice girl...]
[Blue Team taking a sigh of relief
after eliminating one name tag.]
Hye Jin... she's really strong.
[But Yellow Team still has the most advantages!
Must continue their attack...]
It's Dong Wook!
[Discovers Ha Ha from the Yellow Team!
Starts his chase!]
[Green Team's Jae Suk discovers Ha Ha
from having been on the same floor!]
[The Blue Team and Green Team succeeds
with the ambush attack!]
[Dong Wook starts to run
without any hesitation!]
He has two lives!
[Eliminates Yellow Team Ha Ha's name tag.]
Working together like that...
[Yellow Team's Ha Ha
loses one of his two lives.]
I'm mad.
Do you know that they
attacked me together?
They're working together.
[The targeted Yellow Team
plans their counterattack!]
[Having lost all their extra lives,
it's now onto the real face-off!]
[Dong Wook attacks Ha Ha again
after having followed him!]
[If Ha Ha's name tag gets ripped off again,
he'll be ousted for good!]
[Seriously attacking each other.]
You can't bite me.
[A real battle without any mercy!]
My hair, my hair!
[Dong Wook eliminates
Ha Ha's name tag first!]
[Yellow Team's Ha Ha loses both his lives
that he traded in his daggers for!]
[Ha Ha, Out!
Ha Ha, Out!]
[At last? The Yellow Team
loses a team member.]
[We had the biggest advantage...]
[You just wait and see!]
[Once in a while Mr. Capable Kang Gary...
focused and determined!]
[Discovers Kwang Soo
entering a room just then.]
[Approaches the door of the room
Kwang Soo just entered.]
[Hye Jin also heads in the same direction...]
- Where is he?
- I think he's in there.
[Discovers Kwang Soo!]
[Instead of backing down,
Kwang Soo comes out attacking Gary!]
[No matter who it is,
one of them is going to get ousted!]
[Today's battles becoming more fierce
than any other previous battles!]
I'm about to get eliminated!
Lee Kwang Soo, out!
[Eliminates Kwang Soo's
name tag in its entirety!]
Wait...
How is she going to survive on her own
if I get eliminated?
- I would be so frightened...
- I know.
With his long arms...
I saw Kwang Soo's facial expression.
He looked like he was about to kill me!
[Blue Team Kwang Soo's
name tag eliminated!]
Kwang Soo!
I think I call you more than
I call my own mom.
[Lee Kwang Soo, out!
Lee Kwang Soo, out!]
[I'm the only one left on my team?]
I need to escape for now.
[If he's caught, he's dead!
Going into hiding for now...]
[He's at a disadvantage!]
[Finding the shield has to
be the solution...]
[Both teams shocked by Gary's counterattack
concentrate on finding the shield!]
[Hoping to bring the victory closer
by finding the mysterious shield!]
Why are they all already open?
All the rooms are already open!
[But detailed Dong Wook
still goes on with his search.]
Did I go in there already?
So this is what Running Man
does to you...
It turns you into an idiot.
What floors was I on?
Where was I?
[The shield!]
[Blue Team's Dong Wook
discovers a shield!]
[Was told to read the instructions carefully
if he were to find one...]
[Can oust the person
who ripped off your name tag.]
[Or resurrect a member of
your team.]
[Choose one of the two options.]
[Should he use it as a reflector
to protect himself...]
[Or bring in a comrade by
resurrecting one of his team members?]
[Two members on each of the other teams,
while he's the only one left on his team!]
I'm going to summon Mr. Capable.
[Dong Wook chooses to use
the shield for resurrection!]
[The second power of the shield-
Resurrect a team member!]
A shield has been discovered.
- A shield has been discovered.
- Someone found a shield.
- Who did it?
- Who found a shield?
- Was it one of ours?
- In the name of the shield holder...
Kim Jong Kook has been resurrected.
[Blue Team's Mr. Capable,
Kim Jong Kook is resurrected!]
Kim Jong Kook is resurrected!
Kim Jong Kook is resurrected?
[Like a bolt of lightning to the
remaining survivors...]
I'm seriously about to go insane!
You can't do this!
[The flow of victory
being shaken from the core.]
If you can find one more shield,
it's all over!
I think I'm going to go with speed.
I'll just rip off all the name tags.
[Will the once doomed Blue Team
be able to take their victory now?]
The tiger is finally going to get unleashed
to come after us.
Ji Hyo, we're in big trouble.
[Yellow Team, Blue Team, and Green Team
each left with two survivors.]
[Yoo-ruce Willis makes his way towards jail.]
Too late... you're too late.
Who are you trying to contact?
[Yellow Team's Gary fixed on
Jae Suk as his target.]
[The recently targeted Yellow Team
starts their counterattack!]
[Hye Jin starts her approach first!]
[And Gary closes in from the other end!]
- Where are you? Where are you?
- Right here!
[Yoo-ruce Willis barely breaks through
their ambush attack!]
[All three facing off in the lobby!]
[Yellow Team targets Jae Suk!]
[Jae Suk eliminates Hye Jin in a flash!]
[Yellow Team's Hye Jin
loses all her lives!]
[Han Hye Jin, out!
Han Hye Jin, out!]
[In the midst of her attack,
gets counterattacked instead...]
[Ji Hyo arrives one step behind
the action.]
[Green Team's Jae Suk and Ji Hyo
vs. Yellow Team's Gary!]
We have to get Gary.
[If Gary gets ousted,
Yellow Team is destroyed!]
[A bloody hand-to-hand combat!]
[Gary eliminates Green Team's Jae Suk!]
[Green Team's Jae Suk loses his life!]
This is starting to go our way,
Dong Wook.
[The victory can easily become ours!]
Ji Hyo, you have to
think very carefully about this.
Jong Kook and Dong Wook
are still left alive.
Until we can oust one of them...
Promise. Let's promise each other.
[Must oust one of the Blue Team
members together!]
They're watching us.
- What are they doing?
- They saw us making the promise.
Are you guys holding hands?
We just promised each other that
we'd go grab dinner together.
[What a joke of an excuse...]
- We just said we'd grab dinner later.
- I know that.
We just said we'd grab dinner together.
We're having dinner together later.
How is it Jong Kook would see us
right at that moment?
We were just promising each other to
have dinner later, right?
- I think the protectors are going to come.
- Okay, let's separate for now.
- He coming. Gary, he's coming.
- Be careful. Don't go in his direction.
[The Green and Yellow Team
agree on working together for now!]
We have no other choice
in this situation.
[At a disadvantage in strength!
Must find the shield...]
If I can't find a shield...
[Must find a shield to get the
victory leaning back towards his side!]
[Green Team's Blank Ji is searching for
the shield with the same thought in mind.]
[Everyone else in jail is starting
to cheer on their team mate.]
Dong Wook is really good too.
[Hye Jin having been surprised by
Dong Wook's skills earlier.]
I got my hair pulled.
- Dong Wook did it.
- Really?
A shield has been discovered.
So there was more than one shield?
[Someone else discovered a shield?]
[This is big trouble...]
I guess they're not going to
announce anything.
No announcements about the shield?
[Kim Jong Kook's resurrection was announced,
but why no announcements this time?]
[Now that he thinks about it...]
[There was the ability to reflect too!]
The shield could be used for something
else other than resurrect someone.
It could mean an extra life for someone,
or it could be used as a reflector.
[Precise deduction from experience?]
Jong Kook, I know this much from having
found the shield myself...
and you're right.
There's the reflector power.
See? I knew it.
It's not necessarily about resurrection,
but it could be a reflector too.
I feel like it's Ji Hyo for some reason.
Then what should we do?
Should I eliminate Ji Hyo?
[Which one of the two found the shield?]
- Did you find the shield?
- No.
[They're both denying it was them...]
You didn't find the shield?
You were so good at acting for a while,
but what happened?
What acting?
[Just from their facial expressions,
it's hard to guess who has the shield...]
- From the back.
- Dong Wook is going in!
[A live broadcast segment.]
- Dong Wook is going in.
- Dong Wook! Be careful.
Where?
Where is he?
[Dong Wook vs. Gary and Ji Hyo]
[Imminent face-off]
Who found the shield?
- Seriously, who found the shield?
- I don't know. I honestly have no idea.
[No Mr. Capable in sight...]
[In that case, Dong Wook...]
You're trying to eliminate me right now?
Jong Kook!
[Did something happen out here?]
Where the heck is this guy?
He hasn't been any help
since I brought him to life!
That's why you should've
resurrected me.
[Come on, that's a little...]
[Gary is on the ball today!
A face-to-face battle with Dong Wook!]
[Mr. Capable seeing an opportunity
to attack!]
[Blue Team's Dong Wook in danger!]
[Combo play!
Each grabbing one of his arms!]
[Gary eliminates Dong Wook's name tag!]
[Ah... misses it by a beat.]
[Dong Wook - Out!]
You're ousted?
[Gary is the real killer today!]
[Gary immediately follows it up
by eliminating Ji Hyo!]
[Nothing on her back!]
[That means the person who found
the shield was...]
[Gary!]
[Gary having searched through
the restaurant earlier...]
[Discovers a shield!]
[What luck for Yellow Team's Gary!]
Can oust the member who rips off
the name tag... reflector!
One option is to resurrect
one of the team members.
[Gary's choice is...]
[Reflect!]
[Try your best to eliminate me...]
[Gary has the reflector...]
- Remember when you got resurrected?
- Hi, Gary!
Remember how you were resurrected?
[If he's ripped off, he wins.
If he rips off, he still wins.]
Why don't you get out there?
[Our team is ruined...]
Don't push yourself when your foot is hurt,
and just step over this way.
[This is what you call
a slap in the back of the head.]
You know very well what this is.
Or you could just try ripping mine off!
- I know...
- Jong Kook, just rip it off!
[Can't do this... or that...]
- You know exactly what this is!
- Great job! Great job!
Besieged!
[Fine! If you want it, then I'll rip it off!]
[Shield activated! Reflect!
Jong Kook, out!]
[The ultimate victor for having gathered
all the swords together, Yellow Team!]
[At last, to where the golden dagger
awaits in its slumber...]
[The Yellow Team with all nine daggers
finally gathered together in one place.]
- Congratulations!
- Congratulations.
[With Gary's killer skills,
the game comes to an end.]
Each take three daggers in hand,
and stick them into the turtle.
[Stick all nine of the daggers that
have been found into the turtle!]
I've always wanted to do
something like this.
- What is that?
- It's our calling. To make us rich.
I'm going to stick it from this end.
[Each of the nine daggers
into the turtle...]
For the golden dagger!
[At last... the final dagger.]
[The final dagger being stuck
into the turtle...]
[The legend of the golden dagger
about to be revealed...]
[Korea, Macau, Vietnam...
The epic journey...]
[The nine daggers that will reveal the
mystery are now gathered together!]
[The turtle of the gold dagger...]
[is opening?]
[The ultimate gold dagger
being released from within!]
[This is the legendary ultimate golden dagger!]
That really is no joke!
That's awesome!
[Yellow Team going up to the dagger
for having solved the mystery...]
- This is amazing!
- Let's all grab it together.
[Resurrect the gold dagger!]
[Running Man,
resurrects the gold dagger!]
Hye Jin, Gary and Ha Ha are the winners!
[The heroes who have resurrected the
dagger are Gary, Ha Ha and Hye Jin!]
- What an honor.
- You should hang that up at home.
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Going back to the origin of
the sword's legend.]
[A long time ago, an expedition comprised of
9 explorers set out in search of the dagger.]
[In the beginning, all nine of the daggers
were scattered all over Asia...]
In the name of...
[The story of the nine brave explorers who
set out to find the hidden temple...]
[The one to hold the golden dagger
will have the power to rule the earth!]
[The secret of the spell
surrounding the ultimate dagger!]
[The ultimate dagger revealed!]
[In two weeks, the story of how they
rescued the world from chaos will be told!]
[And next week]
[Our ultimate action hero!]
[Jackie Chan is coming!]
[A real action race with
a world renowned star!]
[Running Man closing in on Jackie Chan!]
I love you!
[Next week,
Jackie Chan on Running Man!]