[2013- The year of the snake.]
[Spirit of the snake
flowing through Jangsado.]
[First of the year special-
Twelve signs of the zodiac race.]
[The battle of the twelve signs
of the zodiac starts now!]
[Find the snake, the symbol of 2013!]
[Twelve signs of
the zodiac protecting the earth...]
[Please watch over me!]
Subtitles by DramaFever
[The symbol of 2013.]
[A morning on the island full of hope.]
[Running Man dormitory nearby Busan.]
[Running Man's sleeping style.]
[The big brother sleeping alone
in the bed.]
[While the little brothers
sleep on the floor.]
It's a new morning in 2013.
It's still 2012.
- Please come out to the front lawn.
- Front lawn? Is there a front lawn?
[Productive Jae Suk is the first
to get up.]
[So sleepy...]
Come this way please.
[Starting the first morning of
the new year in utter confusion.]
This is the first broadcast of 2013.
Please say hello to the viewers at home.
Viewers at home...
I wish you a new year full of
joy and laughter.
We will all work hard to bring you
laughter in the new year.
I wish you all the best of luck
in the new year.
This is your first mission for
the new year.
Choi Ji Woo is asleep in the 'C' building,
and Ji Hyo is asleep in the 'D' building.
You just need to choose
one and go in.
[All I need to do is choose?]
I feel a little uncomfortable
just walking in there.
[Just a little while ago.]
[Ji Woo's room in 'C' building.]
[Looking beautiful even
this early in the morning.]
Good morning.
I'm here to give you your morning mission.
[Presenting Ji Woo with her morning mission.]
[Team selection:
Team Ji Woo vs. Team Ji Hyo.]
Please await your team members
that will be headed your way.
[This means...]
I have to be chosen?
[Anyone she's hoping will come find her?]
I just don't want Ha Ha to come.
[The one who antagonized me so much
last week, Ha Ha... you!]
[Ji Hyo's sleeping quarters in 'D' building.]
I wish everyone nothing but the best
in the new year.
[Starting off the morning with a
new year greeting to the viewers.]
[New year money?]
[Team selection mission - Start!]
[What will Jae Suk's selection be?]
[Will it be Ji Woo whom
he deceived yesterday...]
[Or will it be Blank Ji who's like
a part of his own family?]
This is really...
[Huh? Ji Woo's dorm...]
Why am I asked to do something like this?
[Huh? Already?]
- Choi Ji Woo's in the 'C' building?
- Yes.
What's wrong with him today?
[The camera Director.]
What did you guys feed him
yesterday?
[Okay... two people.]
Choi Ji Woo is in the 'C' building.
And in the 'D' building...
[Heading off to 'C' building without
even the slightest bit of hesitation.]
I'd like to building 'C'.
I'd like to join Choi Ji Woo's team.
Why are there so many here?
[Ha Ha... you!]
[Are they all still asleep?]
[Why isn't anyone coming?]
[Gary makes his appearance.]
Come out here.
That's Kang Gary's voice.
[Oh! 'D' building is Ji Hyo's building?]
[Is he headed over here?]
You come here.
[Is he logging in for the new year?]
- Are you starting already for the new year?
- It can't be helped.
Don't try to escape it.
We're starting over in 2013, okay?
- Why isn't anyone here?
- No one came.
Anyways, it's good to see you, Gary.
[No matter, thanking Gary for selecting her.]
[Fitting in right away
to start the couple wave.]
Best of luck in the new year.
[A busy atmosphere in this room as if
everyone's come to visit their family elder.]
[A grand bow to their big brother.]
Kwang Soo, stop
with your attempt at a love life.
And you should lose some
of your muscle.
[Bright and lovely.]
I feel like I'm joining
a neighborhood convention.
You look so beautiful
even this early in the morning.
- Did you even get any sleep?
- Why are you here?
[Please forget the things
that happened last year...]
Both teams, please come outside.
Hurry up and get out here.
Just know that none of you are getting
anything from me in the new year.
It's not like you've ever done anything
for us in the past.
[Everyone's attention is turned to the left.]
[Everyone rivets their attention
towards Ji Woo immediately.]
- Hello.
- Hi.
- Good morning.
- Everything's such a drama.
The expression on Ji Woo's face right now...
it's as if she's on a country getaway.
She looks like someone who's here
on vacation from Seoul.
Lady from Seoul whose heading off
to the market in the morning.
[Heading off to buy cereal in the morning?]
And this one looks like a country bumpkin.
And now, you are all
divided into two teams.
But since there are so many on our team,
would some of us have to go to the other team?
That's why we have prepared additional
team members to join the other team.
[Additional team members have
been prepared?]
[And they're in this grand lucky pouch.]
[Could they be inside?]
Why are they talking so
much out there?
[Who could be waiting in there?]
Look at how happy she is.
- Why are you being like that?
- You're being too much!
You're being really mean
right now... mean.
- Are you trying to betray us now?
- You... out.
[Trying to rid of her members at the news
of there being other additional members.]
If you shout out,
'I hope your 2013 is awesome'...
your awesome gifts will come
out to greet you.
- I hope they're not very awesome.
- I bet they're inside that thing.
- Let's shout it out together, Gary.
- Okay.
- One, two, three... I hope...
- 2013...
[Tsk tsk... you barely logged in as a
couple for 2013, and already?]
- We wish you an awesome 2013!
[We wish you an awesome 2013!]
[Just who's waiting as their awesome gifts?]
- We wish you an awesome 2013!
[The identities of their guests who
are currently hiding in the giant pouch.]
[Oh... four beautiful boys!]
[CN Blue's Jung Yong Hwa.]
[CN Blue's Lee Jong Hyun.]
[Beautiful smiles.]
[Supreme Team's Simon Dominic
a.k.a. Ssam-Di]
[Beast's Lee Ki Kwang.]
[Beautiful F4 members, all in one place!]
[No... way!]
Yong Hwa... Ki Kwang!
Hello! Hello!
- Ji Woo... you have us though.
- Why did you guys have to come?
[Hot temper flare up.]
[I'm so happy!]
[The truth leaving her mouth
gaped open.]
What's wrong with us?
- Why? What's wrong with us?
- What do they have that we don't have?
All you guys are so scrubby!
[Extreme aggravation]
[Not being able to hang out with those
beautiful boys to start the new year...]
- You're being really harsh with your words.
- We don't lack anything compared to them.
You're not being reasonable. When
we get cleaned up, we look like that too.
It's only because we haven't done anything.
Let us get made up too then.
[They want to be made up?]
Let us do the hair too! The hair!
[Requesting for a hair and
makeup change!]
[Just your average street guys without
the hair and the makeup.]
[Ji Woo joining on in their demands.]
- We can be as good as them.
- Give us a chance too!
What am I supposed to do with them?
You can just act as those guys' manager.
What's next on their schedule?
In commemoration of our first broadcast
of the new year 2013 in Busan...
We have asked Busan's F4
to join us today.
I will admit that they're all flower boys,
but not Ssam-Di!
I will admit that those three are it,
but why is Ssam-Di included in there?
Jae Suk, if Gary wasn't standing there,
Ssam-Di would be the manager!
Why would he be included in there?
You should just be a part of our team instead.
I'm still in my twenties.
We have someone in his
twenties here too.
- That's right! I'm in my twenties!
- You're still in your twenties?
I'm a lot younger than I look!
[Utter shock?]
[1985 born Giraffe shocking
Ji Woo into silence.]
- I'm the youngest one on the show!
- Come on...
He's Song Joong Ki's friend.
He's Song Joong Ki's best friend.
You're putting me on!
- He really is 27 years old.
- Really?
Yong Hwa's like a part of our
Running Man family already.
I've been on the show
seven times now.
Yong Hwa really does honor us
by coming on our show frequently.
- Jong Hyun, this is your first time, right?
- Yes, this is my first time.
Jong Hyun recently wrapped up
filming a drama.
[Acted the role of Jang Dong Geun's son
in the drama, 'A Gentleman's dignity'.]
Ah, that's the guy?
[Big-nosed Brother
finally recognizing who he is.]
- I really loved you in that drama!
- Thank you.
- He's part of CN Blue.
- He's from CN Blue?
Why didn't you bring on any female guests
when those guys are here?
We do have a female guest.
Ji Woo's standing right here.
[What did you say?]
I'm standing right here.
Am I not enough?
[Am I not enough here?]
- Am I not enough for you guys?
- Ji Woo, you're more than enough!
Right?
Ji Woo doesn't get just a little annoyed,
but she gets really annoyed.
She has some anger issues.
After getting to know Ji Woo for a day,
I noticed she tends to get in your face.
She totally does.
- Are these the two teams then?
- The two teams have now been decided.
[Team Ji Hyo vs. Team Ji Woo.]
2013 is the year of the snake.
It's the year of the snake?
To start off the new year of the snake,
this is the 12 signs of the zodiac race.
- Dragon, snake, horse, sheep...
- rat, cow, tiger, rabbit...
You will come out one by one and pick a card
which has a picture of a zodiac sign on it.
Please come up front to
choose your card.
You will each choose a card which will
determine which animal you'll be representing.
What's important about this portion
of the selection...
is to see which one of you will
select the card with the snake drawing.
[Year of the snake!
Snake card is what's most important.]
The person to oust the person with the
snake card will become the ultimate winner.
So this is the point of this race?
So the snake is King in this race?
Every time you pass a mission on
your way to the final destination...
you'll be able to gain a hint about
the person who has the snake card.
- I hope all of you give your best efforts.
- This sounds like fun.
- Doesn't it sound fun?
- It sounds fun.
- Really fun.
- Listen to you guys.
- You guys all sound lively.
Why are you following our speech?
An amazing prize awaits you
at the end of this race.
And in the name of the winning team,
it will be donated to those less fortunate.
- That sounds great.
- That's great.
[Card selection.]
Do I just pick whichever one?
[Each of their animal sign
is being determined.]
[Just which one of them is the snake?]
[Go to Wa-heon Beach and
find the Running Man landmark.]
We have to go to the beach again?
[Just which one of them has
the snake card?]
[They must win the game in order to gain the
hint about the person with the snake card!]
[But what could be the hint pertaining to
the person who was chosen by random?]
Snake or not,
we have Kim Jong Kook on our team!
Yeah, that's what matters.
What's there to worry about when
we have Kim Jong Kook on our team?
Hey, I heard earlier...
that Jong Hyun won the gold medal
in Busan for Judo?
- How old were you when you won the medal?
- Third grade in middle school.
- Third grade in middle school?
- Yes.
Then I bet you'll be able to
go up against Jong Kook.
In that case,
you can take charge of Jong Kook.
You have to take care of him
no matter what.
[Guh-ga Bridge. Spanning 8.2 km
between Busan and Guhjae-Do.]
[The beauty of the south seas
bringing out their delight.]
- It's so beautiful.
- It looks like something out of a picture.
[Heading towards Guh-jaedo
through a scenic drive.]
There it is.
[Beautiful scenery everywhere they go.]
[Team Ji Woo arrives on scene.]
[Fascinated by the Running Man's landmark.]
[Beautiful shore of Wa-hyun Beach.]
[The blinding beauty of the southern sea.]
Run with the opponent's queen
on your back.
The opposing team?
[Run with the opponent team's queen
on your back.]
How are they going to carry me
on their back?
- Wouldn't you like that?
- But I'm too tall.
It's a good thing though.
That's better for our team.
- Don't make it easy on them.
- But I feel so bad!
You have to just hang on their backs
and make it hard for them to carry you.
Hello.
This is really... now that we're back home,
our popularity here is no joke!
- No, it's no joke.
- It's no joke here in Gyung-nam.
You can't take any pictures.
I'm sorry, I apologize.
[Manager Gary refusing
their pictures to be taken?]
Look at Gary.
He's being their manager.
[Manager Gary protecting his
Flower Boy Idols.]
- Gary, you've finally found your profession?
- Yes, I took care of it all.
- How do you say 'So cool' in Busan dialect?
- It's a killer.
It's a killer. It's tally killing.
- Killer...
- It's a killer.
Lookin' good.
Lookin' good?
You guys aren't lookin' so good!
Jae Suk, you ain't lookin' so good!
Jae Suk? Ssam-Di!
[This is my home ground...]
Ain't lookin' good... totally ain't!
The mission in this game is to run with the
opponent team's queen on your back.
- While carrying them on our backs?
- As in a piggy back ride?
- Really?
- It's not good.
[Happier about carrying Ji Woo around
than at wanting to win the game?]
- This is so fascinating.
- What's so fascinating about that?
[A Hallyu Goddess that even the
idols find to be fascinating.]
- You want me to get you her autograph?
- What's wrong with you guys?
[A relay race around the 'R' marker.]
If you were to carry Ji Woo on your back
and pass her off to Ki Kwang...
all of you will have to help her
move onto his back to make it go faster.
- Do you understand what I'm saying?
- Yes, we understand.
Look at Ji Hyo over there.
She's the captain of that team.
We have to win this, got it?
[Humbly listening to her commands.]
Look at the glint in her eyes.
You can do this, right?
What is this?
A female General training her people?
One, two, three... fighting!
[Sir Ace... fighting!]
[First round - Yong Hwa vs. Suk Jin.]
- I'm heavy. I'm heavy.
- It's okay.
That's good, Ji Woo! That's great!
- You have to be heavy!
- It's because I feel bad for him!
You have to go limp on his back and be heavy.
[Surprised at her touching him?]
- Sit down.
- Okay!
- I said, okay!
- Ji Woo... I'll just call you that, okay?
- Sure!
[Idol Ace Yong Hwa losing his
concentration over the Hallyu Goddess.]
- You have to get your head on straight!
- Ji Woo can't get that smile off her face.
[Start!]
[Ace Ji Hyo's overpowering strength.]
Ji Woo!
- Ji Woo!
- Hurry up and get going!
[Wrapped up in happiness...]
[I'm carrying Ji Woo on my back...]
Ji Woo!
[On top of the glaringly bright
white sand...]
[Running in the rose tinted light
with Ji Woo on his back.]
[However the fun of the game
is right here.]
Look at her! She's so awesome!
Are you seriously going to be like this?
[Great job, Ace.]
I can't do that... I can't do that.
- You can't do that!
- Ji Woo, lean back!
You're not supposed to lie so
calmly against his back!
My love will always come back to me!
[Totally immersed in the
male lead's role in a love drama.]
[Already ready to be passed off
to the second runner.]
[During the time that Ji Woo tries
to delay the time of getting on the way.]
[This team also is being passed over
to the second runner already.]
[Run!]
- Stand up straight!
- Straight your body! Make it hard for him!
She's way too heavy!
[Sapping the fighting spirit out of
leg flip specialist, Ro-Ro.]
This is no joke!
- Come on... come on!
- You're almost there! Almost!
What the heck is this? Come on!
My legs... my legs!
[Ji Woo can't hold in her laughter.]
Her legs are twice the length of yours.
[Barely making it back to the starting line.]
Hey! Song Ji Hyo!
[Is this the white sand rodeo?]
[Horse Jae Suk trying to calm down
the angry rider on his back.]
Ji Woo!
What did you have to eat this morning?
What did you eat this morning?
Hey! This is no joke!
It's Ki Kwang's turn!
[He did manage to get her
on his back...]
Why aren't you getting on my back?
Please just get on my back.
I can't see!
[Plans to blindfold her horse?]
[Fourth runner, Ki Kwang gets on his way!]
Ki Kwang! Hurry!
- I can't see!
- Lee Kwang Soo!
Lee Kwang Soo!
Where are you going?
[Where is Giraffe Kwang Soo going?]
Keep going straight. Keep going.
[Giraffe having walked off course.]
Turn, turn. Turn around here.
- Straight. Go straight.
- Go where?
[Wait... if he keeps going that way...]
You just need to take about
another 10 steps.
- Where are you going? That's the ocean!
- Three, four...
[What to do...]
Lee Kwang Soo!
[Giraffe heading towards the ocean...]
[No!]
[An unbelievable spectacle to the crowd
members gathered here to watch the game.]
- Hey, you stupid!
- Wait...
- Hurry up and turn around.
- Hurry up and get over here.
[Last runner of Ji Hyo's team,
Jong Hyun gets on his way!]
Look at Jong Hyun!
[Busan's gold medalist
running towards his goal.]
[Where do you think you're going?]
Hang on his back! Lean backwards!
I can't! I'm trying, but I can't!
No! No!
[Ji Hyo's desperate resistance.]
[The final runner, Mr. Capable.]
[Desperate Blank Ji pulls out
her hair pulling tricks.]
[At the Goddess' pranks, the
white sand becomes a sea of laughter.]
- Carry her. Just carry her.
- Just carry her.
- Look at Jong Kook.
- You're going to drop her!
[Using his monstrous power to carry her.]
[Come on... the win is
right in front of your nose!]
[Ji Hyo not being able to use her
air pulling skills on him anymore.]
[In that case...]
[Pinch!]
[Even resorting to
desperate pinching methods.]
[Utter chaos.]
Jong Hyun!
You have to bring her! Now!
[Busan gold medalist
sapped of all his energy.]
[Come at me!]
[What do I do...]
I thought you said you were in Judo?
- I thought you were in judo!
- Just come over here.
[Ace Ji Hyo firmly keeping ground.]
[Since her plan didn't work out,
Ji Hyo throws her whole body into resisting.]
[Please...]
[Hanging onto his pant leg out
of desperation.]
Hey! Just roll her! Roll her in!
We have no other choice!
What is he doing? What is he doing?
[The judo master's confidence
coming to a crumble on the beach.]
- No, you can't...
- Please...
I wish I could!
If it was up to me, I wish I could
jump into your arms and help you.
- Jong Hyun, hurry!
- Did you say he was in Judo?
Jong Hyun! Hurry!
[Full power once more!]
[No!]
[Will this...]
[Huh?]
[A little short of the full power strength.]
[Jong Hyun makes an attempt
at his full power.]
[Will he be able to make his goal
by carrying her across this way?]
[Jong Hyun... hurry!]
[Team Ji Hyo wins!]
[We won!]
- Seriously... hey!
- Jong Hyun beat you.
- Jong Hyun beat you!
- You were right in front of the finish line!
- You were almost there!
- Let me help you up, Ji Hyo.
Jong Hyun... what happened to you?
[Jong Hyun having used enough energy
to last him for the rest of the year.]
I bet he's really exhausted.
What do we do?
We won this game because of Ji Hyo.
The winner of this game...
is Team Ji Hyo.
- Mr. Jae Suk...
- Mr. Ssam-Di!
Because Team Ji Hyo won the game,
the hint will be given to them.
[Team Ji Hyo gains the hint
for winning the game.]
[Ji Hyo is a total gambler... a gambler.]
- She was the best.
- She's the reason why we won.
[Saw my skills, right?]
That is our Captain.
A round of applause!
- Leader Song! Leader Song!
We got ourselves a hint.
[The first hint regarding the person
who selected the snake card is...]
I'll read the hint for everyone.
[Kim Yeon Ah]
[Kim Yeon Ah?]
[The Goddess of the ice rink-
World figure skating champion, Kim Yeon Ah.]
[Just how is the person who selected
the snake card related to Kim Yeon Ah?]
- It's me.
- Why?
[What? The person who has something
to do with that hint is Yong Hwa?]
- I said Kim Yeon Ah is my ideal woman.
- Really?
I'm serious. I mentioned it on a show,
and there was an article published on it too.
- Seriously?
- Yes.
- Who's your ideal woman?
- Kim Yeon Ah.
[After confession his feelings...]
[All these articles got written up about it.]
[Did I select the snake card?]
And I'm the only one here
who's zodiac sign is the snake.
- Really?
- Seriously.
- Are you really that influential?
Hey!
- Kim Yeon Ah's my ideal woman too.
- I'm a fan of hers too.
- Me too.
- Isn't she every man's ideal woman?
[Is she?]
[I doubt... the writers
would make it that easy.]
Or it could be someone that
Kim Yeon Ah likes?
- That's a good point.
- That would be me.
Yong Hwa?
- Are you sure?
- I have a feeling.
I just have a feeling...
[Just who...]
[Did Yong Hwa pick the snake card?]
[If not, then who did?]
[Second mission location-
Arrives in Gujora village!]
[What is the hint that awaits them here?]
We have to be cautious of the hint.
We can't let anyone know, okay?
We have to be careful with the hint.
It's so nice. This really is an island.
[A pretty village with murals on the walls
everywhere they look in this seaside village.]
[A picturesque village of Gujora.]
Isn't it so nice here?
I bet this is something.
Look, it's the yogurt lady.
[But...]
[Everywhere they look in the village,
yogurt ladies and men are all over?]
[Who are these people that are seen
walking all over the village?]
I bet this is a mission.
[Team Ji Woo also notices
something strange is going on.]
- Why are they all dressed alike?
- They're the yogurt ladies.
[Just what is this mission about?]
'Yogurt ladies... please give me a yogurt.'
[Singing the song from the yogurt commercial.]
[F4 boys brimming with enthusiasm.]
Kang Gary!
- What is it?
- You're not part of the F4. Come here.
We're the F5! What are you saying?
Why do you keep trying to take part
when you're not even a part of the F4?
[Ignores them to continue their singing.]
[Me too! Me too!]
Ji Hyo! Come up here and
sing the yogurt song with us!
- Come on!
- You have to be our center.
One, two, three, four!
[Leader Song, Blank Ji joins in
on the yogurt song singing.]
If you don't have a yogurt,
give us the yogurt juice instead.
This is fun.
Who's Gary?
- She just asked who Gary is.
- Lady! Gary is right here!
She just asked who Gary is.
[The name Gary drawing curiosity
no matter where he goes.]
I'm sorry for not being
recognizable enough.
[Passing over the mission envelope.]
What is it?
[First team to find the opposing team's
yogurt queen and take their hat off wins.]
This is the yogurt village.
One of you has to become the yogurt queen
and avoid getting caught by the other team
and if you find your opponent's
yogurt queen, then you win the game.
The queen doesn't have to
be a woman.
For this mission, you have to find the queen
on the opposing team and get their hat off.
[Just who will be chosen as
the queen in Ji Woo's team?]
It can't be Kwang Soo.
He would be too noticeable.
I can't even hide because I'd stick out.
I think Kwang Soo and I both
would stick out too much.
I wonder if it should be someone
who's a fast runner.
Since the other team is so
knowledgeable in things like this...
I don't think being a fast runner
is what's important here.
Yes, I understand.
[Everyone listening to
the command of Leader Song.]
No matter how fast you can run,
Jong Kook will still be able to catch you.
Our opponents could think that
we'd choose Yong Hwa as our queen.
- Don't you think?
- You're right.
If anything, we should trick them
and have Ki Kwang be our queen.
Let's start by disguising him first.
Here, put your clothes on.
[Disguising their queen.]
Wow... he's starting to look
really pretty.
[Yogurt Queen Ki Kwang, who seems
to be so well suited for his makeup.]
[Flower boy]
[Yong Hwa and Ssam-Di
getting bored on the sideline?]
[Playing around and taking pictures
with the wig on their heads.]
[Having too much fun.]
- What are you guys doing?
- Are you guys here to play?
Ssam-Di, you look hilarious!
- We're trying to disguise him here!
- That looks like fun.
We have to disguise our queen!
Kang Gary!
[What?]
[My face is true hip hop.]
- He looks like the definition of hip hop.
- How does he make that kind of an impression?
[Definition of hip hop.]
There seriously can't be
anyone else like that.
His face is so totally hip hop.
[Even Leader Song take a moment from
her nagging to take a picture.]
I'm an eight ton truck with
a broken handle!
My life is always so crooked...
About to enroll in this
school of life!
Want to meet up once a month?
I'm so happy being around you guys!
[F4 and Gary brimming over with
enthusiasm.]
- Are you finished with the disguise?
- Yes, we're finished.
[The yogurt queens to enter
the village first.]
[Will be entering the village at the same
time as the opposing team's queen.]
You have to stay well hidden, okay?
- Stay well hidden.
- One, two, three... fighting!
[The queens gets on their way!]
I think I need to research the village
in the map a bit first.
[A map on the wall...]
[Huh?]
[It's a map of all of Geojae-Do!]
The team from the other team is
on the move too, right?
You really can't tell me apart, right?
- You didn't recognize me?
- No, I didn't recognize you.
Then we're halfway towards winning.
[Then the Yogurt Queen for
Team Ji Woo is none other than...]
[Big-nosed Brother.]
Since I have a sense of feminine aura
that flows from me unconsciously...
I was chosen to play the role.
[We've never seen anything like that
in the past two and a half years...]
[Yogurt Queen mission - Start!]
[The search starts now?]
You will be playing the toss game.
Play the yogurt container toss game and
the person that makes it in first
will join in on the mission.
- Yes, we understand.
- We drink before we get to play?
The yogurt tastes better when you
drink them upside down.
- You have to bite off a little hole.
- Yeah, and you need to freeze it too.
- Yeah, and freeze them.
- Is that how kids these days drinks these?
[Afro Gary envious of their
Busan speech?]
[The more they look at him,
the more he reminds them of Ki Young.]
[Checking the wind.]
- So we have to keep drinking the yogurt?
- That would be trouble.
Yes!
[Fail]
[Even though it was a good throw,
he still fails to make the goal.]
[Jong Hyun is up next to pitch.]
I think you're going to make it in.
Ssam-Di... Ssam-Di!
[Oh!]
[Seems overly excited.]
Get your head on straight. You're
the oldest. Show them how to succeed.
[Will he be the first to succeed
being the oldest brother on the team?]
[Not a chance...]
A little more to the right, Ji Hyo.
This needs to be a little...
Don't speak in fancy Seoul city talk.
Don't say things like 'This needs to be'
but say 'This gotta be'...
I think it would be better to crush it
a bit before throwing it.
[Idol Ace Yong Hwa,
throwing the pitch after crushing it.]
I'm smart too.
It's not going in!
[So close, but hits the rim and misses!]
Can't you just count that as a goal?
Count it as a goal!
[Ah... you want us to count it as a goal?
Is that what you said?]
[Team Ji Woo also in the midst of
doing the challenge.]
We have to throw it
when the wind isn't blowing.
Ugh... that's too bad.
You have to make it in this time.
[Giraffe drinking the yogurt juice
for Jong Kook instead.]
I've already had six because I had to
drink Jong Kook's on top of my own.
- I already had five myself.
- I'm going to make it in this time.
I'm going to make sure to succeed
so Kwang Soo's efforts weren't wasted.
[Ro-Ro succeeds!]
- I'm going. I'm going to go.
- You made it in? Go.
- Hurry up and go.
- Go and find the queen, okay?
- Hurry up and find the queen.
- I can just go, right?
[Haroro goes to search after succeeding
in making the yogurt container toss.]
I'm sorry. Excuse me.
You're not it.
Excuse me. I'm sorry.
I don't think their queen would be walking
around on a major street like this, right?
Let's go over that way.
[Idol Ace Yong Hwa succeeds!]
Jung Yong Hwa, you're the best!
[Big brother Gary wanting to do everything
that the little brothers are doing.]
- I was born to be on Running Man.
- Jung Yong Hwa, fighting!
Please put a subtitle on the screen here.
That I was born to be on Running Man.
They're going to put
the subtitles in Busan dialect!
A man born to be on Reun-ning Man.
[A man born to be on Reun-ning Man?]
Go! Hurry up and get out of here!
I'll see you all later!
[Team Ji Hyo's Yong Hwa makes
his entrance.]
Yong Hwa cam.
[Jong Hyun also succeeds!]
- Throw towards the back... the back.
- That was awesome.
- Back?
I made it in.
[Jae Suk also makes it in.]
- Did it go in?
- It went in.
- Hurry up and catch the queen.
- Okay.
I'll be back, okay?
[Ji Woo's turn.]
- Oh!
- What do you mean, 'Oh'?
I totally missed it.
[Ki Kwang doing a good job of
staying hidden and avoiding detection.]
I bet others started
making their moves, right?
[Where is their queen?]
I don't think the queen will be
walking around on the main roads.
I bet the queen is staying hidden
in one of the side streets.
[Maybe not?]
I feel like someone is going to
show up suddenly in front of me.
[Did he see someone?]
I just saw Jae Suk!
That totally startled me!
[Did Jae Suk see Ki Kwang?]
[Please...]
[Oh... right there...]
Oh... it's not Yong Hwa?
[It seems as though Team Ji Woo really
guessed Yong Hwa to be the Queen.]
- I thought you were going to be the Queen.
- Hello there.
- Hi, Yong Hwa.
- Who is it?
- Huh?
- Who's your Queen?
You know I can't tell you that!
[Team Ji Woo's unknown Queen.]
This is really hard.
I have to make sure that I'm
not noticeable.
I'm scared.
[Oh... my team member.]
You scared me.
- It's my team member.
- Go hide and stay hidden.
Stay up there.
You have to stay hidden.
Don't come out.
[Just then!]
[Did Ro-Ro witness this scene?]
[So that's where you're hiding...]
Are there a lot of people up there?
[Jong Hyun coming face to face
with Ha Ha.]
[Extreme nervousness]
Jae Suk is...
[Losing his ability to breathe.]
[Jong Hyun making it way too obvious
that something is going on.]
- You're acting suspicious.
- What?
- Why am I suspicious?
- Okay... I'll see you later, okay?
- Yes.
Jae Suk!
[Ro-Ro requesting for a backup.]
- Over here, Jae Suk.
- What is it?
[Jong Hyun stuck in a difficult situation.
The Yogurt Queen, Ki Kwang.]
[What do I do?]
Jong Hyun, why are you blocking
this alley?
[Definitely heading towards
that house...]
- There he is!
[Yogurt Queen Ki Kwang is found!]
[Jong Hyun's lightening quick defense
to help Ki Kwang escape!]
Run! Run!
Make your escape!
[Ro-Ro on the chase!]
[Team Ji Hyo in extreme danger!]
[Jong Hyun bringing Ro-Ro
to a stop.]
[Ki Kwang making his escape thanks to
Jong Hyun's quick defense moves.]
[Of all places, he makes his escape
to a house with a guard dog...]
[Please stop barking...]
[These three still not able to
make it in the goal.]
[Gary succeeds!]
I'm going to go in there.
Good luck guys.
- Good luck.
- Don't think about anything as you throw it.
[You first, Leader Song.]
Okay, go. Throw it now.
[Ji Woo feeling more desperate
inches her way forward?]
I can't really see very well.
[Disappointingly fails.]
[Kwang Soo succeeds.]
[Jong Kook succeeds.]
- I'll see you in there.
- We'll see you soon.
Ugh... seriously!
I'm seriously not good at
things like this.
[Thanks to Jong Hyun's work,
Ki Kwang made his escape far away.]
- Are you going to keep following me?
- What?
Why do you just keep following me?
- That's because you're...
- Come this way!
He ran off this way.
Dong Hoon!
[Oh no... Mr. Capable now in the mix?]
The feeling I get...
I don't think he's walking around
on the streets.
- Jong Kook...
- I think he's hiding somewhere.
Why is that dog barking like that?
[Ro-Ro... his senses are
sharp today!]
[No kidding...]
The barking means that
there's a stranger around.
You're right.
[I'm in big trouble.]
[What do I do?]
I keep hearing a dog barking around here.
Why would the dog be doing that?
There must be a reason why
the dog would be barking like that.
[One... two...]
[Ki Kwang making yet another
escape!]
[Jong Hyun uses his whole body
to aid his escape once again!]
Catch Lee Ki Kwang!
[Defender Jong Hyun - Using
his whole body to block the gate?]
[If the others walk around
to the other end...]
Watch out! Watch out!
[Discovers Ki Kwang.]
[Yogurt Ki Kwang completely trapped
without room to escape!]
Catch him!
[Team Ji Hyo's Yogurt Queen
captured in the end.]
Catch him.
That's...
You really do look beautiful!
- Ki Kwang... you look beautiful.
- He's beautiful.
[The hat...]
[Come off... and Team Ji Woo wins!]
[Team Ji Woo wins the game!]
Mr. Ssam-Di!
You still haven't made the goal?
Ha Ha was really on the ball today.
- I kept hearing the dog barking.
- Really?
That was a sure sign to me
that he was there.
Ssam-Di, Ssam Di...
you totally ain't lookin' good!
Ssam-Di, you still haven't
made it in the basket?
- We threw it like a hundred times.
- You drank this many?
You need to crumble this up a little bit
before you throw it.
- What were you guys doing?
- Ssam-Di, why couldn't you get it in?
The wind is blowing really hard today.
[Due to the strong winds blowing, the
game's over before he could even join?]
- I wonder if Suk Jin is still hiding.
- Suk Jin...
[Just where is Team Ji Woo's Queen?]
I bet you it's Yong Hwa.
I think it's Yong Hwa.
[I need to let the others know.]
[I have to quickly alert my team
that it's Yong Hwa...]
[Why isn't anyone coming?]
We will deliver the hint to your car.
Please get started on your way.
We'll see you later,
Jong Hyun and Ki Kwang.
It's okay. We're tied right now.
No need to worry.
Since your team won the game,
the hint will be given to you.
What is it?
- Yoo Jin?
- That's our hint? Our hint is Yoo Jin?
Winter Sonata's Yoo Jin?
The main characters name is
'Winter Sonata' is Yoo Jin, right?
Isn't that too obvious?
[Then does it mean that Ji Woo
is the snake?]
- It's Ji Woo?
- I think it's Ji Woo.
[Is the card that Ji Woo picked this
morning the snake card?]
They don't usually make it so
obvious though.
Yoo Jae Suk, Ji Suk Jin?
Ah... Yoo Jae Suk, Ji Suk Jin. Yoo Jin...
Ah... Yoo Jae Suk, Ji Suk Jin?
Or could it be Ssam-Di's given name?
What is Ssam-Di's given name?
Ssam-Di's given name is Jung Ki Suk.
- Ki Suk?
- His given name is Ki Suk?
[Not even close to Yoo Jin...]
It's such a relief that we didn't
lose this game too.
[The third mission location
Running Man teams have arrived at.]
[A small branch of school in the village
with a total student body of 13 students.]
Hi, kids.
Are all the students here?
[Trees of hope who came out to
greet the Running Man members.]
- I'm in sixth grade.
- Sixth grade? You must be the oldest.
- Hi... hi.
- Hello!
[Mr. Capable showing
his kinder side to the children.]
I'm a huge fan of Running Man.
I know that we've mentioned this before,
but the scenery around here is amazing.
- Yes, it's beautiful.
- The scenery is just stunning.
The color of the ocean... what's it called?
The Jade ocean?
[Jade colored ocean.]
[Gorgeous scenic views from
the southern seas.]
- Each team has one hint each...
- Yes.
Here is your next mission.
[What is their mission here?]
- Kwang Soo, have some manners.
- Come on, Kwang Soo.
- Didn't you see Ji Woo running up there?
- Seriously...
[Queen of dodge ball....]
[If you hit the opposing team's Queen,
then your team wins the game.]
If your team's Queen is hit,
then your team is immediately out.
However...
There's bound to be one man who's
going to remain guarding the Queen.
And that man can't be ousted
no matter how many times he gets hit.
[Last man left will become invincible!]
[The last man left will have to use his
whole body to protect the Queen!]
[And the team that wins two games
out of three will gain the final hint!]
- Put Ji Woo in the back. Behind all of us.
- I'm really bad at Dodge ball.
- It's a very fast moving game.
- You have to avoid the ball.
- Fighting!
We have to protect Ji Woo.
[The team to run out and grab the ball at
the sound of the whistle is the offense team.]
The team to grab the ball is the
first to be on the offense.
Jong Kook! His foot is over the line!
The kids are watching you guys.
Play clean.
[Trying to cheat when these precious
and innocent kids are watching?]
Sorry! I'm sorry.
- I'm sorry, kids!
- Come on... seriously!
- Let's play fair, okay?
- Ready...
[Queen Dodge ball - Start!]
You have to oust him! Oust him!
What are you doing!
[The point of the game is to protect
their Queen to the end.]
Look at you standing there
all by yourself.
Are you going to throw that my way?
[Team Ji Woo's Kwang Soo is ousted
in the blink of an eye!]
[Gary definitely shows his strengths
when it comes down to the wire.]
- We have to oust someone over there.
- Yeah, since one of our own is already out.
Catch it.... catch the ball.
Maybe it's better that he's ousted.
[What are you doing?]
What is he doing?
[Wow! It worked!
Ssam-Di is out!]
- Why did you just stand there?
- It worked! I got him!
[Kwang Soo's spin shot worked!]
Lee Kwang Soo! Lee Kwang Soo!
[He's having a field day.]
[Team Ji Woo's Jae Suk, Out!]
[And immediately following,
Team Ji Woo's Suk Jin, Out!]
[Team Ji Hyo still has
plenty of men survivors.]
Over here... here!
[A hit on Jong Hyun.]
[Team Ji Hyo's Jong Hyun, Out!]
- It could be better to be on the outside.
- Didn't you see how he was ousted?
- Yeah, it may be better to be outside.
- Get it back to me.
[Team Ji Woo quickly making the pass
back to their own side.]
Quickly! Make the pass!
Pass the ball! that's right!
[Team Ji Hyo's Ki Kwang, Out!]
[Jong Kook is ousted
while trying to protect Ji Woo!]
[Final man left standing on
Team Ji Woo, Haroro.]
[Rule - Final man left remaining is invincible.
Protect the Queen no matter what it takes.]
Ha Ha! You have to oust Ji Hyo
before they're down to one man!
[Team Ji Hyo in danger!]
[Hong Hwa throws his body in the way
and protects his Queen Ji Hyo!]
Ultimately, it's down to Gary and Ji Hyo!
[Queen Ji Woo's bodyguard, Ha Ha.]
[Queen Ji Hyo's bodyguard, Gary.]
- Pass it! Pass it!
- Kwang Soo! Over here!
Kwang Soo! This way!
[Their plans of confusing their opponent
by passing the ball quickly around.]
Kwang Soo!
- Kwang Soo!
- Ha Ha!
[See ya!]
[No!]
[Another opportunity!]
[Ji Hyo must be protected!]
[In a dangerous situation...
using his head to make the block!]
[Going back to the plan of trying to
confuse Team Ji Hyo once again.]
[Impossible to predict who will be
making the throw!]
You guys are too fast!
[Gary barely makes the block
with his arm!]
[Uses his body to make
the block again!]
[And the offense changes side!]
[You just wait and see.]
Let's just see how this goes!
[An opportunity!]
[By the skin on his teeth!]
Do you remember me?
- Take your best shot.
- You cannot be forgiven.
A short stature!
[Another shorty besides
'Dodge ball Tong-Ki'.]
Dodge ball Ton-ki...
Ha Ha! Ha Ha!
[What the heck was that?]
[Utter disappointment.]
- He was trying to channel Ton-Ki.
- He should've thrown it better.
[Team Ji Woo continues their plans of
confusing Team Ji Hyo with their passes.]
[Just then!]
[Jae Suk eyes the space between
Gary's legs and takes his shot!]
[Hits Ji Hyo directly on her foot!]
[First round of Queen Dodge ball
is Team Ji Woo's win!]
[Queen Dodge ball - Two out of three.
Team Ji Hyo: 0, Team Ji Woo: 1]
Let's win this.
Let's finish the game right now.
- Let's win.
- Let's win this round.
[Team Ji Hyo making a vow to
win the round.]
Fighting!
[Just which team will receive the final hint?]
We have to get the hint.
I'd like to be clear that
once you get this hint
the person who chose the card will
know for sure that they're the snake.
[Very possible for the person who chose the
snake that they're the one with this hint.]
You guys watch yourselves.
Jong Kook is going for the ball this time.
We're not guaranteeing your
safety anymore.
I'm warning you. It's possible
I may even break your teeth.
- Be careful, got it?
- We've given you fair warning.
- You watch yourselves, got it?
- I'm being nice by giving you this warning.
[Prepare for the second round...]
[Overflowing with eagerness.]
[Gets hurt for running out on the field
like a crazy man all by himself.]
None of those guys ran out.
Why didn't any of you
guys come out?
- Don't you guys think you were too much?
- You have to compete for the ball!
[All they did was not run out to the field
in case they may get hurt in the process.]
Didn't you see him run out with his teeth
gritted in an attempt to beat you guys?
Look! My pants are torn!
There's a rip on my knee!
[While even tearing up his pants.]
Ugh... he's so embarrassing!
- You're embarrassing us.
- We'll take a picture of this spot.
[Is this the scene of a car accident?]
[Clear tire marks.]
[A light fender-bender caused by
some skidding on the slippery road.]
We all need to be careful of slippery
roads with these winter conditions.
[Running Man Campaign]
[Driving in icy conditions -
Let's become slow as turtles.]
- Everyone, please drive safely.
- Drive slow on the roads.
- Use caution.
- I can't believe they didn't come out.
[Queen Dodge ball, Second round starts now!]
[Jae Suk on the attack is a
figure of terror.]
[But when he's on the defense... huh?]
[Staying in safety by using
Giraffe as his shield?]
Let go! Let go of me!
Nice... this is nice team play!
[You call using someone else as a shield
in order to survive, team play?]
[Giraffe becoming a sacrificial lamb
for the sake of his own team.]
[Team Ji Hyo on the attack.]
[Team Ji Woo's counterattack!]
[Out! Yong Hwa fails to catch
the ball and drops it.]
[Gary responds to it by
firing the ball immediately!]
[Directly hits Giraffe on the face.]
[Giraffe bursts out in anger.]
[Unsure of who threw the ball at him.]
Gary! Hey, it was Gary!
[Discovers Gary!]
I can't believe you have two hot packs
on just so you can stay warm by yourself!
[Shouldn't have taken off your clothes.
Now you just look like a cheating scoundrel.]
You should've shared one with
Suk Jin and Ji Woo!
Forget it! Here.
[Anyways, Kwang Soo from
Team Ji Woo is out!]
[Oh no! They now realize they let
their guard down way too much!]
[Team Ji Woo's Jong Kook is ousted!]
Oh my... that scared me!
[You can't even catch that?]
[So close...]
[Almost got into big trouble no thanks
to the mistake on Mr. Capable's part.]
- Where's Ji Woo? Keep an eye on her.
- I'm back here.
- Watch Ji Woo!
- Oh no!
[An opportunity!]
[Jae Suk instinctively throws himself to
protect his Queen and is ousted!]
Okay... good!
[This time, Ha Ha
aggressively protects Ji Woo!]
[Nice moves, Ha Ha!]
[Wait... then this means...]
What... I'm the one left remaining?
[The last man left remaining for
Team Ji Woo is Ji Suk Jin?]
Big-nose! Big-nose! Big-nose!
I'm your bodyguard.
You hit me in the jugular!
[Becoming the neighborhood
beating drum.]
- Keep throwing it!
- Don't stop throwing it!
You're doing great!
[Team Ji Hyo's Ki Kwang sacrifices himself
to give his team the chance to attack.]
[Of all places to take the hit...]
It's okay! It's okay!
It's okay!
[Team Ji Woo slowly starting their
plan of confusion with the passing.]
[Then stops for a sudden attack!]
[Team Ji Hyo's Ssam-Di is out!]
I thought Gary was going to be
ousted with that hit too.
[Big-nosed Brother's opportunity
to attack!]
[A direct hit on Jong Hyun's hand!]
[Once again, Gary is the last man
remaining on Team Ji Hyo!]
[Guard Gary vs. Guard Big-nose.]
[A hit like that is no longer
a big deal.]
[Tries to further the attack
by confusing his vision. However...]
[The one gets the short end of the stick
is once again, Big-nosed Brother.]
[It seems as though he's just
been hit at the same spot again.]
[It's not even as if he can lie down
in pain with the kids watching.]
[Team Ji Woo is once again
back on the attack.]
[Already at the point of exhaustion?
Falling while trying to get the ball...]
[Anyway, Big-nosed Brother proving himself
to be a better blocker than expected!]
[What is the Tiger and the Giraffe
up to all of a sudden?]
Are you about to do what I think
you're about to do?
I have been waiting for this movement.
- Come at me, Kang Gary!
- Is it the move that stops my heart in fear?
Lightening... shoot!
[Fails at the blast off from
the lack of teamwork.]
What was that just now?
[Second attempt at the lightening shot.
This time, The Tiger gets down on his knee.]
Lightening!
Don't step on me too hard, okay?
[Game or not, Giraffe is on full out assault
from all the built up resentment and anger.]
What are you guys doing?
[But just then!]
[Killer Jae Suk targets the legs again
and makes his throw!]
[Wow! A direct hit on
Queen Ji Hyo's leg!]
[Queen Dodge ball, Two out of three.
Team Ji Hyo: 0, Team Ji Woo: 2.]
[Into the cries from the crowd.]
[A nice play toy for the children.]
[Third mission,
Queen Dodge ball - Team Ji Woo wins!]
[The final hint regarding who chose
the snake zodiac sign is given to the team.]
- Wow... it's radish california rolls.
- Yum...
Enjoy your meal!
[The original taste of the california rolls
being enjoyed in a classroom setting.]
[An unbeatable taste combined with
spicy radish kimchi, squid and calamari.]
I thought it was just some calamari
and radish in there... but squid too?
[Team Ji Hyo is also enjoying
their delicious lunch.]
[Checking the hint they just gained
in the middle of their lunch.]
[Just what does their final hint say?]
[Min Hyo Rin.]
[Team Ji Woo's second hint, Min Hyo Rin
following their first clue of Yoo Jin.]
[Either she was in the same project as
the person who chose the snake card...]
[The only person who's been in the
same project as Min Hyo Rin is Ji Hyo.]
- The snake could be someone on our team too.
- Yeah, you're right.
We have to stop thinking that it could
only be someone on the other team.
[The deduction continuing on
after their lunch.]
I looked up some stuff.
I started the search by
looking up Min Hyo Rin.
After trying Min Hyo Rin with some others,
and when I did Min Hyo Rin and Lee Ki Kwang...
the search results showed
that they once did a kissing scene.
Was that all?
- What about Yoo Jin?
- I searched Yoo Jin and Lee Ki Kwang.
And when I did, singer Yoo Jin had
a song with Ki Kwang as a featured artist.
But don't you think that would
make it way too simple and obvious?
- That's true. That could be.
- I searched other guys too.
- When I searched Yong Hwa, I got nothing.
- So Ki Kwang got the most hits?
[For the moment, Ki Kwang has the
highest likelihood of being the snake?]
I don't think it's Ki Kwang.
I wish that it was Ki Kwang.
- I don't have the slightest clue.
- It's not you, is it, Ji Woo?
- Right? You and Min Hyo Rin...
- Any association between you and Min Hyo Rin?
I have nothing to do with her
whatsoever.
If you think that you may be, you
have to tell us so we can protect you.
[Team Ji's main suspect, Ki Kwang.]
You don't think Ji Woo did any
figure skating in the past, do you?
I doubt it.
What about 'Stairway to Heaven'?
- In 'Stairway to Heaven'...
- Was there skating in there?
There's a scene where she's
figure skating.
- Really?
- Ji Woo skates in 'Stairway to Heaven'.
[Now that they think about it,
there was this scene...]
Then, wait a second...
For now... let's focus on Ji Woo for now.
[Team Ji Hyo focusing on Choi Ji Woo
as their main suspect for now.]
What if they're using Kim Yeon Ah
as a hint for 'Winter Sonata'?
Then that would mean Ji Woo...
[Ki Kwang's guess is Ji Woo.
Is one of the two the snake?]
[Final mission location - Jangsa Island]
[With 400m in width and 1.9 km of roads,
the resemblance to a snake gave it its name.]
[Snake island... The perfect place to
greet 2013, the year of the snake.]
We will now start our final race.
If you can last the entire hour
that is given to you...
then the team that lasts during
the time given will be the winning team.
Otherwise...
without any regards to who gets ousted
the moment that the snake gets ousted,
it's game over.
- Yes, we understand.
- But was that it for our hint?
- You're not giving us any more hints?
- It sounds like you don't know who it is?
[Team Ji Woo - Yoo Jin and Min Hyo Rin.
Team Ji Hyo - Kim Yeon Ah.]
[Attaching the animal that they each chose
earlier on their backs under their names.]
[Just which one of them chose the snake
and now has the snake on their back?]
Once you already rip it off,
it doesn't stick as well again.
We're all set now.
[All the members with the animals they chose
now attached firmly to their backs!]
[Trying to determine whether the snake is
on their team or on the opponent's team...]
[Team Ji Hyo decides to protect Yong Hwa and
Ki Kwang while attacking their opponent.]
Let's protect them while we attack
the other team at the same time.
[Final mission starts now!]
The important thing is...
[Team Ji Woo brimming with confidence from
their knowledge at how the game's played.]
[Find the snake!]
[The Tiger and the Giraffe's
sudden cutthroat sparring.]
- Look at you... you've learned.
- Of course... I can even attack now.
[Breaking Kwang Soo's zipper.]
- You always take playing around too far.
- You attacked me first and I just countered!
But you're warmed up now, right?
Loose and warmed up.
[Tiger and the Giraffe overflowing
with eagerness in the new year.]
For some reason, I feel like the snake
is one of our own team members.
- Wow... this is unbelievable.
- This is amazing.
[The beauty of our ocean seen
from atop Jangsa Island.]
[Like a painting that shows the blue sky
meeting the sparkling ocean in the horizon.]
Wow... this is so amazing!
- This is just amazing.
- Doesn't it look like a picture?
[Losing themselves in the beauty
of their surroundings.]
[Soaking in the energy of 2013.]
- This feels so spiritual.
- Doesn't it feel amazing?
[No matter where they look,
everything looks so picturesque...]
[Suspect Ki Kwang slipping away while
everyone else is busy sightseeing.]
- I just hope I don't run into Jong Kook.
- You're going to run into him sometime.
If we run into him,
we have to make a deal with him.
Suk Jin!
How about we make a trade?
- Hey...
- Trade what?
- The hints.
- Let's trade.
- Should we trade? What is it?
- Yes, let's trade.
- You have to tell us one first.
- Why? Then let's play Paper-Rock-Scissors.
- It's because we only have one.
- We'll have to pick which one to give you.
Wait! I'll tell you.
- Give them the first one.
- I'll let you know one. It's Yoo Jin.
I'll give you one. It's Yoo Jin.
Yoo Jin?
[Team Ji Hyo trying to make a deduction with
their two clues, Kim Yeon Ah and Yoo Jin.]
- Yoo Jin. What's yours?
- It's really Yoo Jin?
- Are you being honest?
- Yeah, it really is Yoo Jin.
We told you already! It really is.
- Let's both say it at the count of three.
- One, two, three!
- Yoo Jin!
- Kim Yeon Ah!
Kim Yeon Ah?
[Team Ji Woo's hints -
Yoo Jin, Min Hyo Rin, Kim Yeon Ah.]
What does Kim Yeon Ah, Yoo Jin and
Min Hyo Rin have to do with one another?
[Team Ji Woo falling into
state of greater confusion.]
- What is it?
- Did you figure something out?
[Did Ji Woo figure something out?]
Min Hyo Rin and Kim Yeon Ah
both skate.
- Min Hyo Rin was in a skating drama.
- You're right! She was in 'Triple'!
- She was in 'Triple'.
- What else?
Min Hyo Rin was in 'Triple'.
Min Hyo Rin was in a drama about skating
and Kim Yeon Ah is a skater.
- What about Yoo Jin?
- Yoo Jin? I don't know about Yoo Jin.
They're both the same age.
- Ki Kwang and Kim Yeon Ah are the same age.
- They were both born in the same year.
This is part of the hint.
Even though we were confused earlier...
Kim Yeon Ah and Ki Kwang are the same signs.
- And...
- And there was the kiss scene.
- Hyo Rin had the kiss scene with him.
- And Yoo Jin had a song featuring him.
[The suspect for having the snake card
definitely is Ki Kwang!]
Let's go get him first.
- Hey... I think it's 'Winter Sonata'.
- Why?
They just said Yoo Jin, right?
Ji Woo's character was named Jung Yoo Jin
in the drama, 'Winter Sonata'.
And in my opinion, Kim Yeon Ah is a sort of
a word play on the title, 'Winter Sonata'.
- I think that's what it is.
- I think you're right.
[Team Ji Hyo is confirmed that the suspect
of having the snake card is Ji Woo!]
- For now, let's...
- What's the other clue?
- They didn't tell us the last one.
- They didn't tell us.
- I wish there's a way we could find out.
- We shouldn't have told them what it was.
- We should've told them it was Son Yeon Jae.
- Yeah, you should've told them Son Yeon Jae!
[We shouldn't have been honest and
told them that it was Kim Yeon Ah...]
[Maybe I should've told them
that it was Son Yeon Jae...]
But they were being honest with us...
But we don't know if they were being
honest with us about it being Yoo Jin either.
- You think they lied to us?
- What's the point of thinking that now?
- But they could've lied to us.
- We're ruined.
[Feeling as though they got the raw end
of the deal for having been honest.]
Anyway, let's start off by ripping
the name off of Ji Woo first.
- Let's oust Ji Woo first.
- Call.
There's no need to be considerate.
[Still unsure of who the snake
could be...]
But Kim Yeon Ah...
[Anyway, Team Ji Hyo suspects Ji Woo,
and Team Ji Woo is targeting Ki Kwang.]
[Imminent nerve-wrecking moment.]
[If they make a wrong move,
the mission could end this moment!]
Ssam-Di... Ssam-Di...
[Team Ji Hyo starting to
squeeze in on them.]
[Targeting Ji Woo and moving in on her.]
[At this rate,
they're going to get had!]
- What should I do? Should I run?
- Run... run!
[Team Ji Hyo starts their attack!]
[A surprise ambush - Attack Ki Kwang!]
[The name tag is in Jae Suk's hand!]
[Jae Suk eliminates Ki Kwang's name tag!]
[At the same time, Jong Hyun rids
Ha Ha of his name tag!]
[Which one of the 12 animal signs
does Ki Kwang have on his back?]
- What's Ha Ha?
- Monkey. He's a monkey.
[Ha Ha is a monkey.]
[Is Ki Kwang really the snake?]
[If Ki Kwang truly is the snake,
then Team Ji Woo wins!]
- What's Ki Kwang?
- A rat?
- He's a rat?
- He's not the snake?
[Ki Kwang is not the snake!
Ki Kwang's chosen card is the rat.]
All this time, we all thought it
was Ki Kwang.
[It seemed a sure thing that all the hints
pointed to Ki Kwang. How could this be...]
- This makes no sense!
- How can this be?
- What if it's one of us?
- It's not Ki Kwang?
I was sure that it was Ki Kwang.
You and Min Hyo Rin...
[Mentioning Min Hyo Rin
which Team Ji Hyo isn't aware of...]
[You idiot!]
Wait... why are you telling him that?
- Make sure that he doesn't say anything.
- Keep quiet on your way to jail.
You can't say anything, okay?
Min Hyo Rin! Min Hyo Rin!
Min Hyo Rin!
Hey! You can't tell them that!
- What are you doing?
- Min Hyo Rin!
[Ki Kwang passes on the hint that he got
from Kwang Soo to his team members.]
- What are you doing?
- Min Hyo Rin!
Min Hyo Rin?
You can't tell them that!
What the heck?
[Min Hyo Rin?]
It's all your fault!
Why did you have to tell him that?
Just what in the world is the
matter with you?
- I was just asking if he and Hyo Rin...
- Why would you say that?
- You told him that?
- You really did ruin it all.
Seriously!
Why did you tell him that?
Then doesn't it mean that the snake
could be a member of our own team?
[Now the suspect as to who the snake
could be once again is up in the air.]
Even though it is the name of
a celebrity...
couldn't it mean something else
other than a person's name?
There's Kim Yeon Ah...
- She's an athlete.
- It could not be the people we're thinking.
[It could not be the same people
that they're thinking of?]
- But Min Hyo Rin...
- I've never seen Yoo Jin skate.
[Not able to think of how all three
hints are related to one another.]
Even if I do think of how the three
hints are connected...
I don't know how the hints would be related
to one of the people on the other team.
[How the snake suspect and the hints
are related are what's most important.]
I seriously have no idea.
[Team Ji Hyo still eyeing Ji Woo.]
Who's down there?
Why can't you figure out who it is
even though you have all three hints?
They have no relation with one another.
No matter how we look at it,
we can't think of anything.
- We really can't think of anything.
- In that case, tell us your final hint.
- We can't do that.
- No, we can't do that.
No, not that.
[Tiger and the Giraffe stepping up
to the front lines.]
[Retreating for now.]
We need to corner them.
[Another imminent danger!]
Wait... wait...
[Everyone gathering around
the wide open space.]
- Are you guys on the offense or defense?
- We're on the defense.
Give us a chance...
to make our own deductions too.
But we can't...
come up with a guess ourselves either.
- No matter how we look at it, we can't.
- Really?
[Team Ji Hyo inching their way
towards Jae Suk?]
- Are you suspecting me right now?
- No... no.
[Just then...]
[Kwang Soo breaks out into
attack mode on Ji Hyo!]
[Ace Ji Hyo avoiding his attack
by sidestepping his move!]
[Instead... it's Kwang Soo
who comes into danger!]
[Kwang Soo, Out!]
[At the same time,
Gary attacks his target, Ji Woo!]
I got her! I got her!
[Ji Woo's not the snake either!]
[Jong Hyun is the rabbit.]
[And Kwang Soo's the ox.]
What? We still haven't found
the snake yet?
Seriously?
[Just which one of the remaining
survivors is the snake?]
No, this isn't it.
If the hints aren't talking about people...
[Thinking since earlier that the hints
may not be alluding to real people.]
I think I'm starting to get something...
I'm starting to get an inkling.
Wait...
- What if...
- Yeah?
What if the names Kim Yeon Ah, Yoo Jin,
and Min Hyo Rin are names in dramas?
- What if they're characters in a dramas?
- Drama?
What if they're characters in either
a drama or a manga book?
- You think?
- Look up all three names then.
Then could it be Yong Hwa?
- We don't know that.
- Were they in a drama?
Yoo Jin...
- Look up all three.
- If not Yong Hwa, then Ji Hyo?
- Then it wouldn't be one of us.
- No, it wouldn't.
If it has to do with a drama,
then it wouldn't be one of us.
Let's just check this avenue out though.
It may not be someone real we're thinking of.
Ki Kwang shouted out Min Hyo Rin
before he was taken away earlier.
- He shouted out the name, Min Hyo Rin.
- But think about what was said earlier...
The PD said the one who chose the snake
would know that the clues meant them.
Then let's put it all together.
Min Hyo Rin, Yoo Jin, and Kim Yeon Ah...
I don't know.
- I don't even have the slightest clue.
- I can't think of anything either.
CN Blue's Jung Yong Hwa confesses that
his ideal woman is Kim Yeon Ah?
- That probably isn't it, right?
- No, I don't think that's it.
No matter how I think about it,
I don't have a clue either.
Do you have any idea?
[Oh? Wait...]
- I wonder of it's me?
- Why? Tell us why?
- My character names!
My character names!
- You just gave me the chills.
- Why? What is it?
[Song Ji Hyo's... character names?]
What were some of your
character names?
Jae Suk! Jae Suk!
Jae Suk!
- Could it be me? It can't be me.
- What were some of your names?
- Yeon Ah...
- Why are you telling us that now?
- Why did you wait until now to tell us?
Was the last name Kim?
Yeah, the last name was Kim.
[2011 movie, 'I love you'.]
Yeon Ah. My name is Kim Yeon Ah.
- What else? What about Min Hyo Rin?
- Does it even matter?
Goong!
- What took you so long?
- How did you take so long to figure it out?
[2006 drama, 'Goong']
The most beautiful and talented
ballerina, Min Hyo Rin.
Song Ji Hyo... the role of Min Hyo Rin.
Song Ji Hyo played it?
It's Ji Hyo?
- I never even dreamt it would be Ji Hyo.
- Ji Hyo could've known all along.
Then who else?
It's me!
Yoo Jin... 'Some'!
I can't believe this!
[2004 movie, 'Some'.]
This is Seo Yoo Jin reporting in live
from Seoul Police Station.
[The animal that she picked
earlier this morning.]
[Snake.]
[The hints were different characters
that she's played.]
[Ji Hyo is the snake!]
I played Yoo Jin in 'Some'.
It's you! You're the one!
What have you been thinking all day?
[Definitely our Blank Ji.
To figure it no after all this time...]
[Even she is feeling
embarrassed herself.]
- I'm positive they know who it is.
- How can they not know?
It's all Kwang Soo's fault for mentioning
Min Hyo Rin earlier.
- What is it?
- Look at this.
- What? What is it?
- Min Hyo Rin... Song Ji Hyo.
[Did the figure out who it is
in jail as well?]
- What is it?
- Same clothes, but a different feel!
[Same hints, but different explanations...]
I think we need to reposition ourselves
into a defense mode right now.
- But we still need to attack a little.
- Why didn't I know it was me all this time?
[No kidding...]
[Attack the other team while protecting
Ji Hyo in the time that they have left.]
[On the other hand,
Team Ji Woo is planning their attack.]
- There's not much time left on the clock.
- You're right. We may only have one chance.
[As long as they can oust Ji Hyo in the
time they have left, it's game over!]
[Searching for Team Ji Hyo
to make their approach.]
- One shot...
- We only have one shot at this.
[When everything hanging on the line,
there's only one chance at an attack!]
[As long as they can oust Ji Hyo in the time
they have left, Team Ji Woo wins the race!]
[Oppositely, as long as they can protect
Ji Hyo in the time they have left, they win!]
[They're here!]
[The clock keeps on ticking!]
[Neither team able to back away
from this battle.]
Is it one of you guys?
No, it's not one of us.
Do you even know who it is?
- Of course, we do.
- You know? How did you know?
- How did you figure it out?
- You got it from two hints?
[What are you talking about? We
got it thanks to Kwang Soo's mistake.]
Jong Kook's glint in his
eyes looks strange.
Jong Kook's eyes always
look strange.
Jong Kook's eyes are always strange!
- He's going to snap.
- Yeah, he's going to snap all of a sudden.
There's not much time left now.
I'm not sure what's going to happen,
but there's only about 10 minutes left now.
Then how about waiting out the 10 minutes
and leaving it all to fate?
- You know we can't do that.
- Why not?
[We just need to hold out
a little bit longer...]
[No one is making the first
move to attack.]
Why don't you start?
[It's on!]
[Jae Suk locks in on Ji Hyo as his target
and springs into action!]
[Danger! Left unprotected!]
[Guard Gary coming to rescue!
Protects himself into rescuing her!]
[Everyone throws themselves
into the melee!]
[Yong Hwa trying to drag out the time
by detaining Jong Kook.]
[Total chaos.]
[Just then!]
[Gary, Out!]
[Ji Hyo's guard, Gary is ousted!]
[And simultaneously...]
[Jae Suk is also ousted!]
[Gary, Out!
Jae Suk, Out!]
What am I?
Am I the dog?
Gary is... the horse.
Gary's the horse?
I'm the dog.
[Jae Suk is the one who picked
the dog.]
[But the battle isn't over yet!]
[One of them will have to go...
Mr. Capable vs. Yong Hwa.]
[An inevitable face-off
in order to end the battle.]
- Then let's do it one on one.
- Want to?
[Determining the outcome of the
battle by going one on one.]
- No!
- Let's do this one on one.
[Will Yong Hwa be able to
cross this mountain?]
[Competitors... to the stage.]
[I'm going to take you down
and go for Ji Hyo!]
[I can't allow that, Jong Kook!]
[Don't worry.]
[Battle of wills begins!]
[As predicted, not as strong as
Mr. Capable.]
[On top of that...]
[Big-nosed Brother is slowly
starting to close in on Yong Hwa!]
[Just then!]
[Ssam-Di shoots in for Suk Jin who
was starting to close in on Yong Hwa!]
[Jong Kook vs. Yong Hwa vs.
Suk Jin vs. Ssam-Di and Ji Hyo!]
- Hurry! Hurry!
- Rip off his tag!
- Get it!
- Rip off his name!
[Suk Jin, Out!]
[Not much time left! Mr. Capable
suddenly getting desperate!]
[The final battle!]
[Yong Hwa pushing through Jong Kook...]
I got it!
[Yong Hwa eliminates
Mr. Capable's name tag!]
- Which animal am I?
- Let's see.
You picked the perfect one.
I can't believe you picked that one.
[Of all things to pick,
to pick his own character the tiger...]
I dedicate this honor to my parents.
[Team Ji Hyo's ultimate win for
protecting their snake Ji Hyo!]
Today's victory goes to Team Ji Hyo.
[Team Ji Hyo's victory won
through their teamwork!]
[Feeling a little disappointed with the loss
after having figured out who it was.]
[Full of disappointment from
not having won the race.]
Let's see what the prize is.
[Just what is the gift that will be
donated in the name of the winning team?]
[One ton of rice to be donated to
the less fortunate in the neighborhood!]
[100 bags of rice has been donated to
the orphanage in Busan.]
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Gently charismatic Park Shin Yang.]
[Confident little princess, Uhm Ji Won.]
[Korea's ultimate A-list actors...
with their 100% A-list comedic abilities!]
- There will be a special bonus.
- We have to pay for everything.
[Running Man will treat generously!]
['Man may leave scars,
but money leaves interest.']
[Will they be able to protect
their new year's bonus?]
[Next week's Running Man,
The Money War.]