[It's Shanghai!]
- Ji Sung!
- Captain Park!
[Together with Captain Park and Evra...]
[Getting to set their feet down
once more on the field of dreams!]
There's Jong Kook!
['The tips of my toes...
is where my dreams will start.']
Your self-confidence is through the sky.
[Entering a tough battlefield
full of competition.]
[Captain Park Ji Sung vs. Captain Gu Ja Chul]
[Captain Park Ji Sung vs. Captain Gu Ja Chul-
Their rigorous training is about to start!]
[The fierce competition of pride
bubbling up between the two captains.]
That kid!
[Captain Park vs. Captain Gu.]
Park Ji Sung... right?
Yes, I guess you're already
well aware.
[The day that the truth of Park Ji Sung's
relationship became public.]
My brother!
- Sung!
- Ji Sung!
Captain Park!
Ji Sung!
- Ji Sung!
- Sung!
[After a year...
he makes his return on Running Man.]
[The eternal captain of soccer.]
The worldwide soccer superstar,
Park Ji Sung!
[Making his return after a year,
worldwide superstar, Park Ji Sung!]
[A man who showed us last year that there's
nothing that he can't do in variety land.]
Being on Running Man was
truly enjoyable.
[Now with a new love in his life...
he's made his return to Running Man.]
[An enthusiastic welcome.]
- Ji Sung is here!
- Ji Sung.
[Captain Park makes it on time even with the
breaking news of his new relationship.]
Let's all give a round of applause
to welcome our Captain Park.
- He's made his return after a year.
- The heart of Republic of Korea.
He's our eternal captain!
But as for today...
Since Ji Sung's got a lot
going on today...
Ji Sung told us that he'll still give it
his best and that we shouldn't worry.
Ji Sung always comes to support us
whenever we're going through a tough time.
- Yes, you're right.
- To give us a fresh breath of life.
Please give a greeting
to our viewers at home.
Hello, my name is Park Ji Sung.
I'm so happy to be back on the show
after a year has gone by.
And today...
What about today?
Why don't you send her a video message?
I will run with everything I have
for the special woman in my life.
I heard that you've got
very good news to share with us.
Something very significant
has happened in my life.
[A very significant event in the life
of Captain Park!]
Captain Park Ji Sung and SBS announcer
Kim Min Ji's relationship has gone public.
- Your relationship has gone public.
- Yes... it just happened that way.
[Congratulations, Captain Park.]
You're like a part of the SBS family now.
SBS, I love you.
And also... Sulli will be joining us
on our trip to Shanghai.
Thank you.
Please take good care of me.
I doubt he even notices that
she's standing there right now.
No matter who's standing next to him
right now, he's not going to notice anyone.
I'm sure there's just one person
that he's missing right now.
- This is so Ji Sung.
- You went out for chicken last night, right?
Yes, it was delicious.
Have you been watching our show
lately at all, Ji Sung?
Yes, I haven't missed a single episode.
Any episode that really stuck with you?
Any episode that you found to be
especially entertaining?
- Something from the past year?
- It could be one of the earlier ones too.
- It could be any of the episodes.
- None was as funny as the one I was in.
None was as funny as the
one that I was in.
- Wow... that was awesome.
- Why didn't I think of that myself?
[One step above Running Man.]
As you may already all know
the reason why we're
all together again this year is...
the Asian Dreamcup will be taking place
in Shanghai.
It's the dream of all soccer games.
Then will we be participating in
the soccer game again this year?
That's why all of you
are gathered here today.
I bet we'll be playing to determine
who'll be playing in the game.
- I really want to play in the game.
- I want to stand in the lineup.
- I can do this.
- You have no idea how fast I can be.
That's why we have prepared something.
Why don't we all take a look?
Let's all take a look.
I really hope it's not
the clip from last year.
[Of course, it is!]
[Player number 1-
Last year's Dream Cup player, Kang Gary.]
[A player that resembles Jung Dae Sae.]
[Captain Park's pass over to Gary!]
[Kang Gary Analysis I-
Lacks in improvisation.]
The ball was just too fast!
It was just way too fast!
[Kang Gary Analysis II-
An awful center ring.]
[Kang Gary Analysis III-
An unbelievable miss of the pass.]
You idiot!
[Refusing any interviews after the game.]
- Now that we're watching that...
- He didn't have the basics.
I had no idea that he'd be
that pathetic.
- Is it Kim Jong Kook now?
- That's when I first went on the field.
[Next player analysis-
Self-proclaimed soccer pro, Kim Jong Kook.]
[Captain Park's explosive footwork.]
[A perfect pass over to Jong Kook
in front of the goal post.]
[The captain grabbing
and shaking him by the neck.]
- That was so pathetic.
- I couldn't not grab him at that time.
He lost such a great chance.
[Reckless personal moves.]
[Following up with acts of violence?]
- I was left alone on my own!
- What were you doing out there?
I was just trying to help out
and make a heel pass.
It was just a simple mistake.
I normally don't play like that.
- Just do a good job with a regular pass.
- His conceit is through the roof.
What happened to him?
He's gotten so mean!
- Why has he gotten so mean?
- You're right on with that analysis.
What's wrong with you?
Skill wise, I expected the
most from him...
but he wasn't really
mentally prepared.
[Is he telling him to get
his head on straight?]
What happened to you?
When did you get so mean?
Seriously!
What happened to him?
[Even his wit is world class.]
Thus... Park Ji Sung will be one
of the captains for the day
and he will choose his own teammates
from the Running Man cast.
From having seen your soccer and
otherwise athletic abilities thus far
we have ranked all of you from
A-rank all the way down to D-rank.
[Running Man soccer skills ranking.]
- First, please pick someone from the C-rank.
- Is this the C-rank?
I'll just pick with my eyes closed.
[C-rank: Suk Jin vs. Ha Ha-
Chooses Ha Ha with his eyes closed.]
- Hey!
- That was such a smart choice!
Suk Jin, you've ultimately
been left abandoned.
Okay, pick one person from
the B-rank.
- What are you doing?
- I want to show him my toenails.
That's because he's always wearing
shoes that are too small for him.
Okay, thanks for showing me your toenails.
[Just put your socks back on.]
It's because women step on you with
their heels when you're out at the club.
- It's because you get stepped on.
- Now, pick someone from the A-rank.
- You two should close your eyes.
- I know he'll pick me.
We all know who he's going to pick.
[The eternal rivals-
A-rank's Yoo Hyuk vs. Kkuk.]
Be cruel and shove one of them aside
and take the one that you want.
Don't make him do such mean things!
- Okay, here I go.
- Okay.
[Once again...]
[For once...]
That's right!
- That's right!
- I haven't picked yet.
What's wrong with you?
[Captain Park's earnest touch?]
Don't you know how this goes?
That's what I thought.
It just happened too easily.
I'd rather have Jae Suk on my team.
[Just which one of the two
will get shoved aside?]
I'm sorry!
[Captain Park chooses
Yoo Hyuk from A-rank.]
- You made the right choice.
- Jong Kook nags so much.
I was going to show him some new moves
that I've been working on.
[What? But aren't you a singer?]
That's why I didn't choose you.
That's why.
I didn't want to see your new moves.
So as you can see,
Team Park Ji Sung has been chosen.
[Team Park Ji Sung- Ji Sung, Jae Suk,
Sulli, Ha Ha, and Gary.]
Now the opponent team's captain,
who's here to rescue them...
[Another captain?]
[Here to face Captain Park...]
[Is another captain clouded in mystery!]
- He is...
- Who is it? It can't be your average guy.
Okay, let's invite him out here.
Please come on out!
- Who is it?
- It can't be just your average guy.
Gu Ja Chul!
[Soccer player, Gu Ja Chul.]
It's Gu Ja Chul!
Gu Ja Chul!
I can't believe it!
It's Gu Ja Chul!
[Captain Gu, he is here!]
[The new captain who led the team
in the 2012 Olympics!]
[A dignified leader...
and a man of fearless spirit.]
[The new leader of Korean soccer,
Captain Gu Ja Chul!]
Gu Ja Chul!
[Yes, it is I!]
[Second enthusiastic welcome!]
Sorry.
Wow, it really is Gu Ja Chul!
[Kkuk's extreme protectiveness.]
[The crowd gathers around the soccer
star whom they're meeting for the first time.]
Look, we left Ji Sung back here all alone.
You get away from us!
- I can't believe...
- Get away from him!
- Don't even touch him.
- Are you trying to go over there?
[All the members fascinated by
the sight of Ja Chul.]
Excuse me, Ja Chul.
It really is great to meet you.
- Keep your distance.
- Yes, okay.
I'm sorry, but you're blocking my camera.
Just pay attention to Ji Sung.
You just pay attention to your own team,
and we'll take care of our own.
Ji Sung's really good with
the things he says on the show.
- He's our MC.
- Didn't you know that he's MC Park?
He's very good at making us laugh.
- Why don't you say hello to the audience?
- Introduce yourself to the audience.
Hello, my name is Gu Ja Chul and I'm currently
a member of German's Bundesriga team.
Gu Ja Chul!
[Persistent fan getting adamantly denied.]
That was a really quick response.
Jong Kook was so fast.
I can't believe that they're both here.
[The former and new captains of
Korean soccer are both here!]
- He's getting married soon.
- When are you getting married?
- The day after tomorrow.
- We'll be there!
- You have to do it back to me.
- Oh, okay.
- Hey!
- Why wouldn't you do it back to him?
[Not even responding back to
what the show's fan is doing...]
He's trying to do what you always do
with you right now.
Do it right this time.
[With Gary?]
No, I'm not the right one for it.
Want to be Monday Couple with me?
If it's you, I don't think I'd mind it.
- This is going to be a good game.
- This is going to be fun.
Yes, I think this is going to be
quite a game today.
What's going on today?
What will we be doing?
The weak performance that our Running Man
members have shown at the last Asian Cup...
- Come on, we were good at times.
- We weren't that awful.
Let's forget about the past.
We're going to improve on our skills,
and re-enter the game with better skills.
We'll be playing various games today,
and go through rigorous training
to choose a total of four players who will
participate in the upcoming dream cup.
Ji Sung, four people?
Maybe we should think
about that again.
- What are you saying?
- We'll be fine.
- No, we'll be fine.
- We'll start with a Korean selection match.
Then a selection match in Shanghai.
There will be a total of two selections.
The captain of today's winning team will be
given two votes to nominate players.
[The winning captain of the game today will
be given two voting tickets.]
We're going to start the training right now.
Please go and change into your team uniform.
[Asian Dreamcup-
Player nomination training- Start!]
[Captain Park vs. Captain Gu]
[Captain Park vs. Captain Gu...
A face-off between the two captains.]
[A super match between the two captains
without any concession.]
[Super match between
Captain Park vs. Captain Gu.]
[Now that they're in their team uniforms,
it's time to go train!]
[Instincts different than
those of other people.]
[He's not Captain Gu for no reason!]
It seems as though the name tags
are harder to take off than it looks.
Why don't you try it?
- He's good.
- He's good at ripping that off.
But when you try to do it for real,
it doesn't rip off as easily.
And when Ja Chul comes to get me for real,
I'd avoid his attacks like this.
I wouldn't let him come get me,
and I'd avoid it like this.
What do you think?
Aren't I fast?
That's the way he gets himself ousted.
Why don't you try it
for real this time?
[Yoo Hyuk's moves making it even easier
to get himself ousted.]
Yeah, his moves will get himself ousted.
I know this because
I've been ousted many a times.
Is it foot volleyball?
[Referee Go]
[Captains of both teams exchanging
greetings with Referee Go.]
- This is your first training session.
- Yes.
This is a four against four foot volleyball
match with world famous stars.
You'll play a total of three sets
which will be played four against four.
You'll be playing for 11 points per set.
- 11 points? Okay!
- That's no big deal.
Have you ever played this game before,
Ji Hyo or Sulli?
- No.
- But I've seen others play it.
- No, they haven't.
- Since they haven't, they can try it today.
- I've seen it played many a times.
- Because you've never played...
Ji Hyo and Sulli will be
given a pair of gloves to wear.
- They get to wear gloves?
- They'll be given goalie gloves.
- But they can't grab the balls.
- Ah, just use the hands to swipe the ball?
[Not able to grab the balls,
but able to swipe the balls away.]
[Time for the players to
greet each other.]
[Team Gu Ja Chul vs. Team Park Ji Sung.]
[A super match without any concession
from either of the teams.]
- Sulli... fighting.
- Be careful not to get hit by the ball.
Good luck.
Republic of Korea!
Fighting!
[Four players per team with unlimited
number of chances to switch out players.]
[No touching of the net!]
Good job!
[Team Park Ji Sung serves the first ball.]
[Oh... better skills than expected!]
[Oh...]
[Self-proclaimed soccer player,
Coach Kkuk misses the ball.]
What are you doing?
Only thing you know to do is talk!
Take him out and put me in!
[Huh?]
[A warning.]
- That was your warning card.
- One more mistake, and you're out.
[Team Gu Ja Chul- 0
Team Park Ji Sung- 1]
- There you go.
- Use your hands, Ji Hyo!
Use your hands.
[Blank Ji misses.]
The ball just went over my head.
- It's okay, it's okay.
- No, it's okay.
- The ball just went over my head.
- It's okay.
- It's okay, Ji Hyo.
[Team Gu Ja Chul- 0
Team Park Ji Sung- 2]
Ji Sung hasn't even played the game yet.
Okay, you go in.
[Park Ji Sung finally comes in the game.]
[The former and the new captain
facing off at the foot volleyball net.]
[Captain Park's serve.]
Be careful,
Park Ji Sung is in the game now.
[Letting the ball slip away
right within his reach!]
That's not what I meant to do.
That's not what I meant.
[Signing for a player swap?]
Swap, swap.
Time to swap out a player.
Kim Jong Kook, you're out.
- Swap, swap out.
- Kwang Soo, you're out.
[What?
Kwang Soo is swapped out?]
- Why am I being swapped out?
- He's doing good though.
- No, it's time to trade him out.
- He just doesn't like me.
[Team Gu Ja Chul- 0
Team Park Ji Sung- 4]
[As predicted...
Blank Ji totally gets the hang of the game.]
- Leave it, leave it.
- Jong Kook, get it!
Okay, send it over!
[Gu Ja Chul's chance to kick it
over the net!]
[Darn...]
Nice!
- Maybe Ja Chul should be swapped out.
- You should've spiked it!
Seriously!
Hey, Ja Chul...
Gu Ja Chul and Kim Jong Kook are
the big black holes of that team.
If it wasn't for Gu Ja Chul or Kim Jong Kook,
they'd win the game.
Just because it's you, Ja Chul...
don't think that you won't get swapped out.
[Team Gu Ja Chul- 0
Team Park Ji Sung- 5]
[With the game totally leaning towards
Team Park Ji Sung's win...]
Come on, Ja Chul!
[The team continues to toss their ball
towards the middleman, Ja Chul.]
[Again...]
- Ja Chul!
- You okay?
What?
What!
- What!
- Are you okay?
- One more time.
- Let's do it one more time.
- What are you doing?
- Let's do that one more time.
One more time.
Let's do that one more time.
[Team Gu Ja Chul- 0
Team Park Ji Sung- 6]
[Passes it off to Ja Chul again!]
[He makes a good pass over the net,
but Yoo Hyuk blocks the ball!]
[Ji Sung gets his chance.]
[Succeeds with a spike!]
[Scores with the chance that he's given!]
If you spike the ball on your first try...
what does that make me?
[That's what you call
the power of experience.]
[Team Gu Ja Chul's scores three points-
Team Gu Ja Chul- 3: Team Park Ji Sung- 7]
- It's okay. Take it easy.
- You can pass it over.
[Huh?]
[Captain Gu having been kicked off
to the cheerleading team?]
- Nice!
- There you go!
[Giraffe's spot on kick!]
[Team Gu Ja Chul scores!]
[Team Gu Ja Chul- 4
Team Park Ji Sung- 7]
- There you go.
- Nice serve.
[Sulli's super receive.]
- It's not over yet. You did fine.
- Good job, Sulli!
- There you go!
- Mine!
- My ball.
- Nice!
[Nice heading!]
[Bitter...]
We're doing so much better without you
in the game, Ja Chul.
I don't know what's
really going on here.
- Things are going so much better now.
- Ja Chul...
The score is going up and up without
Ja Chul in the game now.
Fighting, fighting!
[Annoyed Captain Gu going over to
cheer on the opposing team?]
Ja Chul is really good playing
that symbol though.
- No kidding.
- Maybe he should've gone into music instead.
Yeah, maybe he should've gone into music.
Okay, come in the game.
Trade Sulli out, and put Gary in.
[Team Gu Ja Chul-
Ja Chul finally back in the game.]
Here, I'll kick it your way.
There you go!
Good job!
[Ja Chul gets his chance...]
Nice!
[Pushing the ball off to the other side
of the net with a slight head hit.]
[Wow- Gary saves the ball!]
- Nice!
- Ja Chul!
[Tosses the ball directly over to Ja Chul.]
[Will he be able to do it this time?]
[Awesome spiking of the ball!]
[Finally evening out the score-
Team Gu Ja Chul- 7: Team Park Ji Sung- 7]
[The score is currently even.
Nervous energy at an all-time high.]
- Gently. Kick it gently.
- Nice!
[High up into the air!]
- That's going to be hard to catch.
- Watch out up front.
[Giraffe of misfortune.
Of all the places to get hit...]
[Where?]
I'm so sorry!
Don't look at me, Sulli!
[Team Gu Ja Chul- 7
Team Park Ji Sung- 8]
This is so much fun.
We haven't played this game in a while.
I got it, I got it!
- There you go.
- Get it, Suk Jin.
I meant to pass the ball to you.
I didn't realize the ball would go over.
[A perfect toss over to Jae Suk.]
[Oh!]
[A direct hit over in the corner!]
That was an awesome attack.
It's all about the corners.
Corner attacks are what it's all about.
[Back to even score-
Team Gu Ja Chul- 9: Team Park Ji Sung- 9]
[Total concentration as the score gets
closer and closer to eleven points.]
I got it, I got it.
- Ja Chul!
- Get it, Ja Chul.
There he goes!
[A ferocious kick!]
[Captain Gu having found his rhythm.]
[Team Gu Ja Chul- 10
Team Park Ji Sung- 9]
[The mood on the court is that of a
foot volleyball world cup.]
- I'll get it.
- Kick it to Ja Chul.
[Team Park Ji Sung luckily saves the ball.]
Get it, Jae Suk.
- There you go.
- Get the ball!
[The chance is back to Ja Chul!]
There he goes!
[Fierce!]
[Wow!
He saves the ball!]
Get up!
- It's in!
- Keep going! Keep going!
[The rally continuing on.]
[Kwang Soo's mistake...]
[Team Park Ji Sung bringing the game
to a deuce.]
[Team Gu Ja Chul- 10
Team Park Ji Sung- 10]
I'm so nervous.
Deuce.
Wow, this is really
nerve wrecking.
- There you go.
- Take it easy.
[Because the game is at a deuce,
there must be a two point score for a win.]
Okay, this is it.
- Okay.
- I got it, I got it!
[Huh?]
- I thought you got it?
- 'I got it!'
- He said he'll get it.
- He'll get the ball.
I thought you said you'd get the ball.
['Kim- I got it' makes a huge mistake.]
[Team Gu Ja Chul- 10
Team Park Ji Sung- 11]
[If Team Park Ji Sung wins this point,
they win the first set of the game!]
I need someone to catch this pass.
[With no one in the middle to
catch the ball!]
I need someone to come
and catch this pass.
[Flies in like thunder!]
[Huh?]
[Flies in like the wind to
drive himself into the net.]
[A full out quarrel.]
What a nice greeter you are!
Hello!
- Who were you bowing down to?
- No, that wasn't it.
- I thought Suk Jin was in the way.
['Kim-leave it' greeting is catching on
to become the new way of greeting people.]
No one else was stepping up to get the ball.
Let's just swap for now.
- It was because the sun was in our eyes.
- That's right. It was because of the sun.
[Team Park Ji Sung wins the first set!]
I'll give you one minute
to plan your strategy.
- Good job, Sulli.
- But I didn't even do anything.
No, you did great.
[Captain Gu, who's gotten the feel for it
is strategizing the game for his team.]
- Over this way?
- Yes, this way. Then I'll take care of it.
[His plan is to take care of all
the scoring for the team.]
[Have you forgotten all the mistakes
that you've made?]
[In the meantime, Blank Ji delivers bottles
of cold water to her teammates.]
- This is the last round.
- Get away!
What are you doing here?
Since Jong Kook is left footed,
we have to kick over to his left.
[Attack to his left!]
- This is a great strategy.
- Avoid passing it to the right.
- This is what you call strategizing.
- That's right!
This is what you call strategy.
Figuring out their lefts and rights.
They haven't figured out yet that
we're going easy on them, have they?
No, they haven't noticed.
- That's a relief.
Do you think they've noticed that
we've been going easy on them?
- No, they haven't.
- Of course not.
[Captain Gu acting as shameless
as the other team.]
You're quite sneaky.
- He's quite sneaky.
- Didn't you know his nickname is Sneaky Gu?
The current set score is one to one.
This is the final winning set.
- Who's serve is it?
- Tell them to do it.
- We'll take the serve.
- Tell them to take the serve.
[Team Gu Ja Chul's serve
starts the final set.]
Gu Ja Chul, fighting!
Nice, nice... we got it!
[Yoo Hyuk, the attacker scores a point!]
I'm so sorry!
[Due to the popularity of 'Kim-leave it',
the court is full of mannerly players.]
[Team Gu Ja Chul- 0
Team Park Ji Sung- 1]
[Huh?]
[Kim-Leave it missing the ball again?]
[Team Park Ji Sung in high spirits.]
- Don't you think we need to swap positions?
- I didn't know where I was running to.
- I didn't see where I was running.
- You need to apologize.
[A deep bow of apology.]
I'm sorry.
Sorry, Ja Chul.
[Team Gu Ja Chul- 0
Team Park Ji Sung- 2]
I got it.
Leave it, I got it.
There you go.
Careful, be careful.
[Fierce offense and defense plays.]
There you go.
Take the ball.
[Kim-Leave it's mistake...]
[Making fun of Kim-Leave it is
the newest trend to follow.]
Why did you use your foot?
You should've hit it with your head.
- This really is...
- Has he always been like that?
- No, he's much worse.
- What's your deal, Kim Jong Kook?
Ja Chul!
[An automatic apology]
- One, two, three... fighting!
- What are you doing without me?
[Team Park Ji Sung- 3
Team Gu Ja Chul- 0]
[Kim-Leave it receives
the ball successfully this time.]
There you go!
[Ja Chul's attack succeeds!]
[Team Park Ji Sung- 3
Team Gu Ja Chul- 1]
Get the ball!
That's the most important spot.
There he goes!
[Concentrating their attack on Kim-Leave it
who's proving to be their black hole.]
- There you go!
- Behind you!
[The rally continuing on without
any sings of it ending soon.]
[Tall Giraffe's ambush heading attack.]
[What?]
[Wow- he saves the ball!]
[A fantastic team play!]
[Team Park Ji Sung- 4
Team Gu Ja Chul- 1]
There you go!
That was nice!
[An ambush kick towards
Big-nosed Brother!]
What kind of a kick was that?
You didn't have to kick it that hard.
[Easy... go easy!]
Sorry!
- I'm sorry!
[Team Park Ji Sung- 5
Team Gu Ja Chul- 1]
Nice, nice.
[Attacker Yoo Hyuk spikes the ball
towards the corner again!]
You're really good at this.
- That was out.
- He hit the ball out of bounds.
Why?
Why!
['Why?' Breaking out
his own popular saying.]
Wow!
I saw him doing that on television!
[Team Park Ji Sung- 6
Team Gu Ja Chul- 1]
Someone has to stay close
when I receive the ball.
- There it goes.
- Get it.
[Huh?]
[A hit to the face.]
[Ah... right in the face
that he's so proud of...]
That was hilarious!
That was really...
I was just trying to make
you guys laugh.
It's okay, I'm fine.
[Team Park Ji Sung- 6
Team Gu Ja Chul- 2]
Here I go!
[Thus the fierce play continues on.]
[Team Park Ji Sung- 9
Team Gu Ja Chul- 9]
There you go!
[Both team with their full
concentration on the game.]
Pass it over to Ja Chul, Kwang Soo.
You have to pass it over.
There it goes.
- That was so cool!
- Nice shot!
Nice!
[The heading attack is a success!]
[Team Park Ji Sung- 10
Team Gu Ja Chul- 9]
[One more point,
and Team Park Ji Sung wins!]
Come this way, Kwang Soo!
- Shoot it over.
- Ja Chul!
There you go.
He's the black hole of that team.
[Trying to save the ball?]
Jae Suk is going to hit it out of bounds.
[Shooting the ball far... out of bounds.]
- Why...
- Where were you kicking the ball?
[Succeeds at confusing 'Kim-Leave it'.]
- I know you were trying to confuse me.
- We're good. It's a deuce now.
[Team Park Ji Sung- 10
Team Gu Ja Chul- 10]
- Nice.
- This is tough.
We have to win this.
[A tight and nerve wrecking energy
out on the court.]
I got it.
Leave it, leave it!
There you go.
Ja Chul... show them!
[Ja Chul's kick!]
[Yoo Hyuk receives the ball?]
[Showing some skills in the game.]
There you go.
Kick it  over the net!
[Another killer kick!]
[And the ball is received again!]
That's going to be out of bounds!
[Out?]
[Ah...]
How did that happen?
That was supposed to be out!
- I told you to just leave the ball alone.
- Our team is so good.
That's so awesome.
[Team Park Ji Sung- 11
Team Gu Ja Chul- 10]
Let's do this!
Thank you.
[Team Park Ji Sung- 11
Team Gu Ja Chul- 11]
- Leave it, leave it!
- Isn't it out?
[Giant Giraffe saving the ball that was
headed out of bounds.]
I got the ball!
[The headshot making it impossible
to predict which way the ball will go.]
Aren't you even embarrassed?
Please just leave it.
I'll get the ball from back here.
- I can get the ball from back here.
- I can't trust you with the ball.
I'm back here,
so don't worry about it.
[Team Park Ji Sung- 13
Team Gu Ja Chul- 13]
- It's over the net.
- Nice shot.
[Giraffe's ambush heading is a success.]
- One more, we need one more.
- We just need one last shot!
Let's get the last point!
[Team Park Ji Sung- 13
Team Gu Ja Chul- 14]
Get it, Jae Suk!
[The ball right in front of the net.]
[Spikes the ball over.]
[Captain Gu saves the ball.]
Nice, nice!
Leave it, leave it!
[Unbelievable rallying of the ball.]
- Nice, nice.
- Get out of the way.
Out, get out of the way.
There you go!
Here, Ja Chul.
You take the ball.
That ball is out!
There you go!
[Captain Park's cheap shot
towards the empty corner!]
[Saves the ball!]
[In?]
[Or out?]
[Which is it?]
[Ah... by the split of a hair, it's out!]
We lost?
[Team Go Ja Chul wins the
foot volleyball super match!]
We will now move on to
the next competition.
It feels like we're in the world cup.
Wow, that was unbelievable.
We could've won that game.
- That was so much fun.
- I haven't played that game in a while.
- You guys were amazing.
- Really?
- Yes. Maybe too good.
- How amazing were we on a scale of 1 to 10?
On a scale of one to ten?
Guys like hearing things like that.
Just how cool were we on a number scale?
You were just really cool.
When Sulli showed up in that
white dress earlier today...
- You looked like an angel.
- You looked so pretty.
- No, not at all.
- No, you looked so pretty today.
We're serious, Sulli.
Maybe we can dub ourselves 'Sul-Sa-Mo'.
[We love Sulli.]
[That sounds a little...]
Sul-Sa-Mo.
We love Sulli.
It sounds like we have diarrhea.
('Sulsa' means diarrhea in Korean.)
No, that doesn't sound quite right.
Ji Sung's thinking about
something else right now.
Ji Sung right now is...
Ji Sung has that interview tomorrow.
[Captain Park facing an interview
after taping Running Man.]
- They look very good together.
- Yes, they do.
- She was on this show before.
- Yes, we know.
When Ha Ji Won was on our show
before for the Olympics.
She came on as
the announcer for that episode.
This is the first time I realized how much
fun foot volleyball could be.
His competitiveness is no joke.
He's really competitive.
- Jong Kook is the most competitive of us all.
- It's not really that.
He's being nicer to you and not scolding you
because it's your first time on the show.
No, I'm usually nice.
Ja Chul, were you really angry when you
were screaming 'Why' in his face?
I forgot what was going on then.
What happened again?
That actually stemmed from the 2011 match
that Ji Sung played in.
Remember when Ji Sung scored in Saitama
and asked everyone to stay silent?
[Staring at the Japanese audience in silent
mutiny for their hostile jeering and hissing.]
[That day's ceremony was testimony of
Korea's dignity.]
During the first half of the game,
Ji Sung was facing off with Nagatomo
and Nagatomo stole Ji Sung's
ball away from him.
And even after Ji Sung fell down, he chased
after him and tackled down the ball.
[Tenacious Ji Sung chases him down to the end
to tackle him down for his ball.]
And when he chased behind to tackle
the ball like that
I was actually sitting out
on the bench at the time.
And when I saw the expression
that he had on his face...
I thought to myself,
'Wow... that person really is amazing.'
[Surge of emotion and respect when he saw
Ji Sung's expression on his face.]
I was in a game last year against Japan
where a player stole the ball away from me...
and as I fell down from his attack,
I felt so insulted and humiliated.
And I was suddenly reminded of Ji Sung,
and thought to myself, 'You're dead'.
[Just like he did two years ago...]
[I'll run just as hard!]
[I'm Park Ji Sung's junior!]
When you're on the same team...
you feel like you're all part of the family.
Especially since you look
upon him like your older brother.
[Thus the place these two honorable
Captains have arrived at is?]
[A lunch table?]
We get to eat?
[Unexpected lunch time.]
We can eat?
Relax and enjoy your meal while
conversing with one another.
What's going on here?
I know that you wouldn't
just be feeding us.
I know something has to be up.
[Everyone's suspicious of
the offered lunch.]
- Wow... this looks so good.
- Enjoy your lunch, Ja Chul.
- Yes, please enjoy your lunch.
- We won the game all thanks to you.
Remember the show with
IU last year?
- Sulli!
- Yes?
Is there anything that you want?
- Something I want?
- Yeah. Jae Suk likes to give out gifts.
- Ah... a car!
- A car?
- Jae Suk!
- You know about it, Sulli?
- Sulli knows about it.
- I want a house.
A house.
[Sulli's big dream of owning a house.]
- A house?
- House?
If Jae Suk buys you a house,
I'll wallpaper it for you.
Ja Chul says he wants you to buy him
a house for his wedding gift.
- You're have to take care of all of us.
- Ji Sung should be getting him that.
I think it would be much more fitting for
Ji Sung to get him that gift.
- I can do that.
- Really?
In exchange, I want him to get me one
when I get married.
Then you can buy each other a house
for your wedding gifts.
Why? Are you getting
married sometime soon?
- Ji Sung?
- I'm sure I'll get married sometime.
- Jae Suk.
- What?
Ja Chul doesn't have an officiator for his
wedding yet and wants you to do it.
- The day after tomorrow?
- Yeah.
He still doesn't have an officiator
when it's the day after tomorrow?
Jong Kook's agreed to sing a song
at the wedding for him.
- Really?
- Of course.
- What are you going to sing?
- 'You're so lovely'.
And he's going to sing topless.
That sounds nice.
If things go well for Ji Sung and he ends up
getting married, we'll have to do something.
Gary can catch the bridal bouquet.
[Gary will catch the bouquet?]
What are you going to do
for him, Ja Chul?
Me?
I'll sing him a congratulatory song.
You will?
Are you a good singer?
- When Kwang Soo gets married...
- He'll never get himself married.
- Kwang Soo will be alone forever.
- He'll never get married.
I'm only 29 years old.
You're such a liar.
- Why won't you believe me?
- You do look younger, but how old are you?
- Ja Chul was so shocked earlier.
- Why?
He was so shocked when he found out
Kwang Soo is friends with Joong Ki.
- Really?
- What?
- They're friends?
- Yeah, they're friends.
What?
They're really good friends.
Ji Sung.
Is your girlfriend a good cook?
Come on, tell us how you two met.
Let's ask him in a more casual setting.
Let's turn off all the cameras.
Okay, so how did you two meet?
[Camera back on?]
[So full of sense.]
[Cameras off]
How did you two meet?
[Why turn off the camera?]
Jae Suk, you try doing something.
Ja Chul, did you not know about it?
- No, I didn't know.
- Really?
I felt so happy because she's
such a nice woman.
- Do you know her well?
- What?
Do you know her well?
[Captain Park's shot at
Suk Jin's statement.]
- Do I have to know her personally?
- Answer the question.
- Do I really have to know her, Ji Sung?
- Suk Jin, you're something else.
I was just saying that I have a feeling
that she's a really nice person.
- Is that right?
- Yes, I just have a feeling that she is.
I could just tell by the way she looks
that she's a really nice person.
Have you proposed to her, Ja Chul?
You don't think he's proposed to her when
he's marrying her the day after tomorrow?
[Getting criticized for
every little thing he says.]
- Actually, I never did propose to her.
- You haven't proposed yet?
- Why don't you propose to her right now?
- No, that's not what I meant.
- Just propose to her right now.
- What do you mean, propose now?
Why don't you propose to her
through a video message?
- What are you talking about?
- He'll never get a chance like this again.
Go ahead and propose to her.
We'll make sure that she gets it.
I'm going to do it tomorrow.
- What? Tomorrow?
- You're proposing tomorrow?
- Really?
- You're proposing to her tomorrow?
Why don't you ask Jae Suk to
do the proposing for you?
How did you propose to your wife?
- What?
- How did you propose?
- He's really not good at things like that.
- I'm horrible at things like that.
I did it very simply in the car.
He doesn't have much style
when it comes to stuff like that.
He doesn't know anything about doing
any surprising events or anything like that.
You'd think that women would like him, right?
Not at all. He's actually repels them.
If I repel them,
I bet you're even worse!
I bet whomever I end up marrying will
become best friends with your wife.
Because they're going to have
so much in common.
- I think Eun Hye's still waiting.
- Who?
- Yoon Eun Hye.
- Ah, Eun Hye?
[Ah... this person?]
Wow, Eun Hye...
I really do miss her.
- Eun Hye, are you doing well?
- Come on, stop it.
- It's been so long since I've seen you.
- Come on the show sometime, Eun Hye.
In all the times I've seen the show,
I've noticed they never edit that out.
They're never going to do that now either
because of what you've just said.
- Ja Chul.
- Yes?
- How are you going to propose?
- Have you planned a special event?
- We've been dating for six years now.
- Wow... really?
- Yes.
- Since you were 19 years old?
- Wow, you've been dating her that long?
- So the six years that we've been dating...
- Various episodes of your relationship?
Like our first meeting, and our first kiss...
Moments of danger... and getting
over those dangerous moments.
And like the time when I've made up my mind
that I wanted to marry her and asked her...
I've arranged for two people to perform
a musical to play out those moments.
[Wow... so romantic!]
- Really?
- Who are you using to act that out?
- We could be good at that too.
- Why not use Jae Suk?
- Why don't you use me?
- How about using Jae Suk and Ji Hyo?
Me and Ji Hyo?
- Why don't you do it with her?
- It should be me and Ji Hyo!
- Then how about Gary and Ji Hyo?
- You can use Gary and Ji Hyo.
- I can even make her tear up.
- I bet that would be really touching.
- That's very cool.
- That's so romantic.
What about location?
Where are you doing it?
I've only been on the receiving end
for the past six years.
- That's why I wanted to do something for her.
- I think I'm going to start tearing up.
- So you felt bad for it?
- My style is a bit more like Jae Suk.
I'm not good at things like that.
But...
- You know what I mean, don't you?
- Of course, I do.
- Yes, he does know.
- Just continue to be on the receiving end.
- What's wrong with you?
- Just thank her for it...
Thank her for it, but just continue to
receive whatever she has to give.
- Has everyone finished eating?
- Yes.
We're going to play
a very simple game right now.
- You know what the game will be, don't you?
- Is it a question game?
This is a question game.
Like a relay question game.
We'll start asking question
and whomever the question goes to
when the alarm ends loses the game.
- Do we have to answer the question?
- You have to answer the question.
[What's the allotted time?]
Ready, go.
Are you happy?
Of course... I am.
Does being married make you happy?
It makes me so happy that I'm not sure
if it's fair for me to be this happy.
- You're that happy?
- I can't even express how much.
- Here. Where are you going to propose?
- You have to ask your opposing team.
[Don't you know the rules?
Pass the alarm to your opposing team!]
- Why are you passing it to your own team?
- Don't you even know how to play this?
- The proposal?
- Where are you going to do it?
At a small theater.
Ji Sung, I'm sorry, but...
Why did you go to Han River?
I went to Han river to have some chicken
after seeing a soccer match.
But I didn't know so many people
would find out about it.
Who's your favorite soccer player?
[Asking Sulli who her favorite
soccer player is?]
This is Park Ji Sung's question?
You've got Park Ji Sung and Gu Ja Chul
sitting next to you.
I'm curious to see what she'll say.
[What will Sulli's answer be?]
Ji Sung is the best.
That's because she's on
his team right now.
- What kind of an answer is that?
- Ja Chul is sitting right next to you.
- Are you okay?
- Look at Ja Chul sitting next to you.
- What kind of a question is that now?
- She asked you if you're okay.
I gave her a look
as soon as I saw her earlier.
But I guess you didn't see that.
Aren't you getting married
the day after tomorrow?
- Get your head on straight!
- Aren't you getting married?
- What kind of a response is that?
- You need to get your head on straight.
[Team Gu Ja Chul-
Jong Kook and Ji Hyo are currently out.]
- You love your wife, don't you?
- Of course, I love her very much.
Can you send your wife a
video message?
- Make it short! A short one!
- I love you!
- There you go!
- Forever!
- Hurry up!
- How about a video message?
- To whom?
- To your lady.
- Hurry up and to it!
I love you!
- Hurry.
- I love you!
- Kwang Soo.
- Yes, Ji Sung?
If you were put in the match,
do you think you could score a goal?
- I think one goal would be possible.
- What a load of crock.
Sulli.
Can you tell us the ranking of best looking to
worst looking of all the men here right now?
You're in last place.
[The worst looking of all the Running Man
members according to Sulli's ranking.]
I didn't eat any breakfast yesterday.
- Dong Hoon.
- Yeah?
Hurry, hurry.
- Hurry up and ask.
- Do you truly want to run in the game?
Yeah, I really want to run. You've
dated a celebrity before, haven't you?
- Nice! Nice question!
- Have you or not?
Does he even have to answer
that question?
- Have you dated one or not?
- Hurry up and answer.
[Out!]
[Why is he getting so overexcited?]
- There's no way that you have.
- Why not? He could've!
Why are you getting so
flustered, Kwang Soo?
You could've just said, no.
- You could've just answered, no.
- Hurry up and get out of there.
- Get out of there, Kwang Soo.
- Kwang Soo can't lie about stuff like that.
Are you doing well?
[Time over- Kwang Soo is out!]
- Suk Jin.
- Yeah?
Your wife isn't your
first love, is she?
No, the thing is...
I really don't remember.
But it's very possible
that she was my first love.
What about you?
- Is your wife your first love?
- Everyone knows the answer to that.
She may not be my first love,
but she's my last love.
How about a video message
to your first love?
[A video message to Suk Jin's
first love?]
Are you doing well?
[A video message that's
years... past due.]
You're well, aren't you?
[Time's up with his video message.]
What's your reasoning for saying that
Park Ji Sung is better than Gu Ja Chul?
- Yeah.
- I want to hear your answer to that.
- Yeah, I want to hear it.
- I'm curious to know.
What is it that our Ja Chul is lacking?
- Why is Ja Chul...
- First, Ji Sung is the captain.
- Okay, Park Ji Sung is the captain?
- Yes.
What the heck is this?
Ja Chul is a captain too.
- Who's better looking?
- When it comes to looks...
Well... both of them...
- Both of them?
- You have to just pick one.
- What are you talking about, Sulli?
- What if you had to pick one?
How old were you when you started
playing sports?
When I was... 12 years old.
Do you not know that I'm
also a captain?
- Ah... really?
- Yes, he is!
- Yes, that's right, he is.
- I had no idea. I'm sorry.
[Time over- Sulli, out!]
What do you think the possibilities are
of our country rising to
at least sixteenth in ranking
at the next world cup competition?
That's a great question.
As long as people will put their faith in me,
I guarantee 100% that we'll be up there.
[Determined to make it 100% as long as
people put their faith in him.]
Captain Park.
Do you have any interest
in coming back?
[Coming back to his home team?]
[The alarm chooses to go off
right at that moment!]
I can't believe the alarm went off!
We didn't even get to
hear his answer!
I wish we could've heard his answer!
Could you have given us a
warning on that?
Wow, I was so curious to
hear his answer.
Ji Sung, that last question really was...
[The question that they're all very curious
to hear the answer to.]
I was so eager to hear
what your answer was going to be.
But I could tell that Ji Sung
was just about to answer that question.
I was just about to answer it
when the alarm went off.
Can you text us the answer later?
- I can tell you guys the answer now.
- Then tell us.
Can you tell us?
This is going to be broadcasted
later on anyway.
Well, unfortunately...
I don't think it's time for me yet to...
I don't have the intention of going out
to the world cup as a player yet.
- Not yet?
- No.
[No desire to play in the world cup
as a player himself yet.]
Even though many people have
mentioned it to me...
but there are other players who haven't had
the chance to run yet, like Gu Ja Chul.
When players like that play the game,
then it'll change the team as a whole.
[Wanting to give the chance at the honor
to his juniors...]
I don't think this is the right time
for me to make that comeback yet.
I'm different than the person
I was two years ago.
[On top of everything else,
he's different than he was two years ago.]
But still,
if you really want to talk it out...
even though you may feel that way now,
once you think about it some more
you never know how you'll feel later on,
and you may change your mind down the road.
- That's true.
- I'm sure Ji Sung will make the right choice.
We just want to
see him back, that's all.
That's what the people of
this country feel.
Just having him back would
make us feel so much more confidant.
[No matter what you decide,
we'll stand by your decision.]
[Korea Polar Research Institute-
The last training session!]
- You need to work on your soccer skills more.
- Aren't those name tags?
- What's that?
- Those are name tags.
That's how we're going to
oust each other?
Ah... that's how we're going to do it?
Ah, do we have to hit the ones with our
own name on it to get it on our backs?
I think that's how we get the name tags.
I'm going to get Ji Sung's name and oust it.
[Name tags of various different sizes
on the goal post looking set?]
If you get the big one,
then you're pretty much out.
Yeah, you're as good as out.
This will be your last mission
of the night.
Song Ji Hyo, and Sulli.
Please step forward.
[Ji Hyo and Sulli asked to step up front.]
These two ladies will get to go first.
[The two to enter first?]
- Good luck.
- Wait for us.
- What are we going to be doing in there?
- I guess we'll go in and just wait for them.
- Don't you think?
- I guess.
We'll have to wait for them?
Your last mission is...
'Rescue your Queen'.
[The next mission-
Rescue your queen.]
Ji Hyo and Sulli will enter the building and
will be placed somewhere inside the building.
They'll be placed separately
in two different rooms.
We have to stay in hiding until our own
teammate comes to rescue us?
I'm scared.
- Can our opponents oust us?
- Be careful, Ji Hyo.
- See you later, Sulli.
- Okay.
[Not knowing where they're being led to
with their eyes blindfolded.]
Guys...
I feel like I'm going to bump
into something.
It's so dark!
This is really scary.
The rest of the men cannot
enter the building right away.
- Do you see your name tags up there?
- Yes.
Everyone must kick a ball to hit one
of the name tags that are stuck up there
and when that name tag falls off,
you'll enter with that name tag on your back.
- What if we get someone else's name?
- Wait, what if...
What if I kick the ball,
and I get Gary's name?
- Then Gary will enter the building.
- Ah...
- Seriously?
- It doesn't matter who's team you're on.
The person's name tag your ball kicks off
gets to enter the building right away.
- Ah, I see.
- How am I supposed to get my name?
- Only two people here can control their aim.
- The most important thing is...
If your team's queen gets ousted,
then the rest of the team is ousted.
- Okay, I understand.
- At that point, the game is over.
- So the quicker we get in there, the better?
- We have to get in there quickly.
You have arrived on the ninth floor.
Ninth floor?
[By a stroke of luck, she
finds out which floor she arrives on.]
[Queen of Ji Sung's Team is placed
in the waiting room on the ninth floor!]
Since I don't know if my team,
or the Yellow team will arrive first...
It's not like I can stay in here
with the doors locked either, can I?
What if I open the door to peek outside,
and get caught by a Yellow Team member?
Then I'd be ousted, wouldn't I?
I can see from here like this.
[The current location of each queen.]
- Hey, Ja Chul...
- You're going to kick first?
- Then do you want to kick first?
- Why would you kick first?
[Ji Sung to kick off first
for Team Ji Sung.]
- It's okay.
- Here I go!
- What are you looking at?
- Which name are you targeting?
The way I see it, I think
Ji Sung is going after his own name.
- That's right. His name tag is small.
- I hope he kicks my name tag first.
- Or kick Kwang Soo's.
- There he goes. Fighting, Ji Sung!
[Ji Sung kicks!
Who will be the first player to enter?]
- What was that?
- What are you doing?
[Huh?]
[Wait... Park Ji Sung...]
- Ji Sung!
- What are you doing?
[His junior not even able to
lift his head up?]
What the heck was that?
- Ja Chul, what was he doing?
- I think he's too embarrassed for him.
Ja Chul, are you that
embarrassed for him?
- What was that?
- Maybe he slipped.
- He could've made a mistake and slipped.
- How? All he does every day is kick balls.
I don't kick balls every day.
Show him how it's done, Ja Chul.
[Next up is the captain of
Team Ja Chul's turn.]
Where are you aiming?
Which one are you hitting?
- Are you going to hit the small one?
- You can't just aim for the big name tags.
Pick either your small one,
or the opposing team's big name.
[Locks in his own small name tag
as his target.]
- Okay.
- Okay, go for that one.
Okay, Ja Chul.
Ja Chul.
[What's going on here?]
- He did that to be nice.
- He has a very big heart.
- It was for Ji Sung's sake.
- He did that to protect Ji Sung.
[Junior's everlasting brotherly love.]
- Okay.
- Ja Chul is so nice.
- I'm going for my own small name tag.
- Gary will get it.
If you make a mistake though,
you'll get Ja Chul's big name tag.
That won't be good.
Here I go!
It didn't fall down.
[The panel must fall off completely
for it to count.]
It has to fall off.
- How is that going to fall off?
- I'll go next.
- Okay, Kwang Soo. You go in.
- If that wasn't enough to make it fall...
- How did that not fall off?
- You have to kick with your instep.
Lee Kwang Soo's big name tag
should've fell down.
[Kwang Soo's big name tag-
He could've been in trouble...]
Challenge.
How about right there?
Between Kim Jong Kook and Yoo Jae Suk.
- Is it that hard to kick it on the name?
- Even we didn't get it.
- Is it that hard?
- I guess I'll have to show how it's done.
Challenge.
- You're just going to kick, aren't you?
- Anyone could be a target.
- I should've kicked harder.
- See?
[How is it not a single person
can kick it right?]
Are we even going to be able to
get this done tonight?
I'm going to kick towards that corner with
Yoo Jae Suk, Gary, and Gu Ja Chul.
Here I go.
[After all that big talk,
will he be able to get it done?]
[Homerun!]
[Humiliation]
What is it that
you're actually good at?
What can you actually do
when balls are involved?
All you've got is your brute strength.
- Come here. Just get back here.
- I kicked it too hard.
This isn't easy for any one of us.
[Captain Ji Sung's turn once again.]
[Perhaps he'll kick it more accurately
with it being his second try.]
We're all watching you!
[A direct hit on Gu Ja Chul's name!]
[Roaring out as if
celebrating a huge goal!]
[I'm ruined...]
You hit Ja Chul's big name tag!
[Sending in the captain of the opposing team
with the large name tag on his back.]
- Ja Chul, you've got the big name tag.
- I can't believe you got that.
[Here's your large name tag.]
[Ja Chul of Team Ja Chul enters
with the big name tag on his back.]
- Good luck, Ja Chul.
- We'll see you in there.
- You have to protect Ji Hyo.
- I'll be right in, so wait for me in there.
Now that Ja Chul's going in,
I need to get in there too.
Hurry up and kick.
[Kim-Leave it of Ja Chul Team's turn.]
Where are you going to kick it?
Are you going to kick it up there?
No, I'm going to kick it over there.
We know that you like soccer.
- You're just a spectator of the sport.
- We know that you like to watch soccer.
You just like to watch soccer.
Fighting.
[Huh?]
[A large name tag for his own
teammate, Ha Ha?]
Me? Ha Ha?
- That was the big name tag.
- Big name tag?
You kicked off my big name tag?
I'm going to rip off your name tag
as soon as I get in there.
[Jae Suk bringing disadvantage
to his own team...]
I was aiming for Jong Kook's name.
[Ji Sung Team's Ha Ha enters the building
with the big name tag on his back.]
Jae Suk, Jong Kook and Gary's names
are all bunched together.
Ji Hyo?
Ji Hyo, can you hear me?
- Ji Hyo?
- Hello?
It's me, Gu Ja Chul.
- Gu Ja Chul, hurry up.
- Where are you right now?
I don't know where I'm at.
I was blindfolded when they took me.
- But I'm in... a lab or something.
- A lab?
- Okay, okay. I'll be right there.
- Okay.
Wait just a little bit longer.
Fighting.
Thank goodness for Gu Ja Chul.
So I have to search through this
whole place for her?
When am I ever going to find her
in this bid place?
A lab?
Lab, lab...
How fast can you run a 100m dash?
I run that in 12 seconds.
Will you be okay with that?
Gu Ja Chul!
How?
How did you find me so quickly?
[Ja Chul meets up with his queen, Ji Hyo!]
- Is no one else here yet?
- No, no one else is here.
[Gets lucky enough to find her
as soon as he enters the building!]
You were too easy to find
as soon as I got in here.
- Can we move you to a different place?
- Yes, I can move. Let's go.
- We should move before someone else comes in.
- This spot isn't a good hiding spot.
This isn't a good spot?
Where are you, Sulli?
- It's me, Ha Ha. Where are you?
- Ha Ha, I'm on the ninth floor.
Okay, I got it.
I'm on my way right now.
- Sulli.
- Yeah?
I'm on the ninth floor right now.
Ha Ha... I'm in a room.
Come and find me quickly.
It's okay for you to come out right now.
No one else is here.
Where are you?
- Ha Ha.
- Where are you?
- Ha Ha!
- Ha Ha, I'm right here.
- Where are you? I'm coming.
[Ha Ha and Ji Sung Team's
queen, Sulli meet up!]
I'll show you my spin kick.
Just show us your regular kick.
Here's my spin kick.
I'm sure it'll go out that way.
I don't even need to see that.
- Why? What's even the point?
- All I have to do is kick up a little.
I just need to kick it up a little.
Okay, I got it.
Okay, here I go.
[Will he be able to do it?]
Didn't I tell you?
I told you he'd kick it off to that side.
Yeah, you were right.
How did you know he'd do that?
- I almost had it.
- Just get back here.
[Will Jong Kook be able to hit
any of his targets sometime today?]
- I know where to kick it now.
- Challenge.
Challenge.
- Needs to kick it hard enough for it to fall.
- I have to get in there quickly.
[Almost got Jong Kook's big name tag.]
Hey!
You almost made mine fall!
- What's wrong with you?
- Ji Sung, hit Jong Kook's.
No, he can't do that.
[Ji Sung's turn once again
with his spot on kicks.]
Wait, wait.
[That's Kwang Soo's name tag?]
[Doing nice things for others...]
He hit the small one.
Ugh, that really is too bad.
- Must be nice for you.
- Thank you.
[Kwang Soo enters with a small
name tag on his back.]
Lee Kwang Soo of Gu Ja Chul's team
makes his entrance.
[A direct hit on Gary's small name tag!]
Gary is a nice hit.
Good to get Gary in there.
Gary's good.
[Gary enters with the small
name tag on his back.]
Can I go a little to the right of the line?
- Is he allowed to do that?
- I'm not moving up or anything.
I just won't go up in front of the line.
Why?
Where in soccer have you ever seen a
penalty kick kicked off from the side?
You know he's right.
- You have to kick it from the white line.
- What he's saying is right.
[What he said isn't wrong!]
Kick a little more to the right
than what you're thinking.
Since your kicks keep going to the left,
kick more to the right than you'd think.
I'm going to shock you with my kick.
You just wait.
- Okay, please do.
- You just wait.
He's going to kick that way again.
[Ji Sung is right on once again!]
Ji Sung keeps saying that way.
I wonder why that is?
Can't I move the ball over a little?
That spot would be perfect for me.
Gary of Park Ji Sung's team
makes his entrance.
Sulli.
It's Gary.
Which floor are you on?
Gary, come to the ninth floor.
We're on the ninth floor.
Ninth floor.
Okay.
Kwang Soo.
Which floor are you on?
Kwang Soo,
Ji Hyo's on the second floor.
Let's meet up on the second floor since
no one else from the other team is here.
[Suggesting that they meet up on
second floor where their queen, Ji Hyo is.]
Ji Hyo is on the second floor.
Which floor on you on, Ja Chul?
What?
Eighth floor?
[With the bad reception on the walkie-talkie,
mistakes second floor for eighth floor.]
[Giraffe heading up to the eighth floor.]
Where are you?
Ji Hyo.
Kwang Soo, where are you?
- I'm on the eighth floor.
- Are you coming to second floor or not?
Are you going to come or not?
Tenth floor?
- Okay, just stay right there.
- I'll go up to the tenth floor.
[Giraffe heading up to the tenth floor.]
[But the problem is...]
[These guys are on ninth floor.]
Are you alone?
[This is the chance!
Get the Giraffe while he's alone!]
[What luck is this!]
[Giraffe making his escape up
onto the roof.]
[Queen unsure of what may happen,
and goes back into hiding.]
One, two, three.
Ja Chul, come up to the roof.
They're all up here. To the roof.
[Receives Giraffe's call for help.]
Okay, the rooftop.
Just stay right here.
[Ja Chul off to rescue the Giraffe!]
Wait, I'll be right there.
[Giraffe in extreme danger!]
I don't know what to do.
[Giraffe with quick moves!
Handling the two on his own rather well!]
[Giraffe showing superhuman strength
succeeds in escaping from them!]
[The two kiddos very disappointed
at having lost their chance!]
This is our chance to get him.
[Huh? Giving up their
chase on the ninth floor?]
We have to protect Sulli.
That's too bad.
When did he get so strong?
- I can't believe he got away.
- Sulli.
- Where did she go? Sulli.
- Yes?
I think we're going to have to run, Sulli.
[Really good at hiding...]
We're going to have to
move our hiding spot.
- Let's move elsewhere.
- Let's hurry.
Thank goodness you two survived!
- You can't die!
- Okay, don't worry.
We survived, but we didn't get him.
Ja Chul!
Where have you been?
I just almost got eliminated!
[Barely having made his escape.]
Those two are walking around
together right now.
What's Jong Kook doing?
He was pretending to be so good at soccer.
- What's taking him so long?
- All he does is talk about how good he is.
- We have to last until he gets here.
- I know.
[Have to make plans to survive
until Jong Kook comes in.]
Okay, this time... if not Suk Jin,
then it'll be Jae Suk's name.
- Or Ji Sung's big name.
- Get the one on the left.
Okay?
Here I go.
Challenge.
[Another homerun...]
You're nothing but a soccer spectator.
If he can't get his name,
then he can't go in, right?
- Yes, that's correct.
- Then no need to get Jong Kook's name.
- Then there's no need to get his name.
- Hey! I can get my own name!
- Just hurry up and kick it?
- We don't have to send him in then.
[If it's left up to him to get his own name,
then he may never actually make it in.]
- He won't ever get his own name.
- To the left is either Jae Suk or Ji Sung.
[What's the point of looking and
strategizing all night?]
I didn't say, 'Challenge'.
- You scared me for a moment.
- You're so honest. You don't have to say it.
[ You don't really have to say it...]
Good. That's a good looking setup.
Nice.
[A direct hit on
Yoo Jae Suk's small name tag!]
[A direct hit!]
[Jae Suk of Ji Sung's Team entering
with the small name tag on his back!]
We needed Ja Chul to stay here.
Jae Suk, should I get my own name tag
to get in there or what?
- You want me to get Jong Kook's name?
- Yeah, get Jong Kook's name.
- No, Ji Sung. Don't do that.
[His next target is
Jong Kook's big name tag.]
Hey, Ji Sung.
Can't I kick just one step to this side?
Come on, you can't do that.
Challenge.
[The ball is heading towards
Kim Jong Kook's big name tag!]
[So close!]
That's not very nice of you.
I have to get that.
I have to get that for it to be fun.
I'll take care of it being fun
on my own.
- Challenge.
- Go.
- You don't know where Ji Hyo is?
- No.
[All of Ji Sung's team having
found each other.]
- Ji Hyo went in the opposite direction.
- Really?
If I came this way...
then Ji Hyo went in the opposite direction
at a ninety degree angle.
I remember hearing her voice as
we were saying goodbye to each other.
- Then Sulli, why don't you stay here?
- She can't stay here, can she?
Guys...
- You have to stay alive.
- Of course, we will.
- Sulli, keep yourself hidden back here.
- Contact us if anything happens.
- Eliminate everyone.
- Okay.
I feel safe with all of them out there.
It's going to be really hard
to find Ji Hyo.
[Team Ji Sung out on their search
for Ji Hyo, the queen of Team Ja Chul.]
There's someone down there.
I see you hiding down there.
I can see you guys down there.
[What do we do?]
[Imminent face-off!]
[Sulli will be in danger
if they get through us!]
[We're outnumbered!]
Come and get us!
[The chase is on!]
[Team Ji Sung trying to use the fact that
they have more people to their advantage!]
[Facing off in a
wide open space.]
[A menacing move from Ja Chul!]
Look at his moves.
- He looks menacing.
- Ja Chul has the big name tag.
[Ja Chul has the big name tag...]
[Corralling Ja Chul and Giraffe
back into a corner.]
[Ja Chul initiating an attack on Jae Suk?]
[Just then!]
[Kwang Soo's back is exposed!]
[Kwang Soo's name tag is eliminated
in the blink of an eye!]
[How can this be...]
Get him!
Get Ja Chul!
[Team Ji Sung seizing this chance
to chase down Ja Chul!]
Wow, he's so fast!
[Literally having disappeared from
their sight in the blink of an eye!]
[Already having escaped their grasps!]
[Having left his own VJ behind as well
to make his escape on his own.]
[Ja Chul had ten years
shaved off of his life.]
Jong Kook needs to get
in here quickly.
Kim Jong Kook of Team Gu Ja Chul
makes his entrance.
Okay, we're all set now.
We're all set.
[Mr. Capable, Jong Kook!]
[Huh?
That's a giant sized name tag?]
Just look at you.
You can no longer say anything to me.
What else as I supposed to do when
Ji Sung kept targeting me like this?
[How did Jong Kook get to make his
entrance with that on his back?]
- I think I can get it next time. Seriously.
- Challenge.
- I'll get Ji Sung's.
- No!
No!
[And thus...]
[With the gigantic name tag on his back...]
Ja Chul, where are you?
I'm right here.
- Ja Chul!
- I'm right here.
- What do we do? My name tag is big too.
- Ji Sung did it, didn't he?
That Ji Sung.
He kept targeting me.
Ji Hyo is down that way.
That's where she's hiding.
[Telling Jong Kook where their
queen is hiding out first.]
- They're up on the third floor.
- Okay, I see them up there.
- I see them.
- I see all three of them up there.
Look at all three of them together.
We're in trouble.
- Look, they're together.
- They've found each other.
[Verifying that Jong Kook
and Ja Chul have found each other.]
Go Ja Chul and Jong Kook
have already found each other.
Make sure that you keep yourself
very well hidden.
Okay.
Those three guys walking
around together...
They're so cute!
They can't even approach
the other team.
- Are they on the fourth floor?
- Gu Ja Chul and Jong Kook together is scary.
[Even the sight of them together
is enough to frighten them.]
Team Park Ji Sung's
Park Ji Sung making his entrance.
- Okay.
- They're on the third floor now.
Jong Kook is on the third floor now.
[At last...]
[He... is here!]
Challenge.
[Kicking...]
[His own small name tag!]
[His class... everlasting.]
Bye, Suk Jin!
[Who's going to send me in?]
Jae Suk.
Where are you, Jae Suk?
We're on the third floor.
I think they're looking for you right now.
- You're on the third floor?
- They're on the second floor right now.
Is this the second floor?
It's Ji Sung.
[Ji Sung is right by them!]
- Where on the third floor?
- Ji Sung! You can't go that way!
Go to the right.
You have to go to the right.
- Over to the right!
- You have to move over to your right!
Right here!
We're right here!
We have to go after him!
[Team Ja Chul on the chase!]
Ji Sung, you have to run!
Run!
[Team Ja Chul on his chase!]
[Must hurry to help Ji Sung!]
Ji Sung, you have to run!
Run!
[Capture Park Ji Sung!]
No, Jong Kook!
[Ji Sung being clever and
escaping up the emergency stairs!]
[All of Team Ji Sung is now
gathered together!]
- They all have big name tags.
- Really?
Jong Kook and Ja Chul both
have big name tags on.
[Revealing that Jong Kook and
Ja Chul both have big name tags on!]
[Then shall we go face them?]
- There they are.
- They're looking at us right now.
I feel so much better with
you here, Jong Kook.
There they are.
I see them together.
They're all together right now.
I heard that you both have
big name tags on your back?
I'm sorry to tell you this,
but Suk Jin's still kicking out there.
I don't think Suk Jin is
going to make it in here tonight.
It's four against two right now.
But why am I still so scared?
They can't approach us very easily
right now because there are four of us here.
[Even though there are just two of them,
they're still a dangerous duo.]
- Where's Ji Hyo?
- We have to protect Ji Hyo.
[But the chances of winning with
their big name tags is...]
[Jong Kook...]
[Let's make a run for it and
go find Sulli!]
Okay, let's go.
Go up.
Let's go up.
[Their best bet in their situation is to
go find the other queen, Sulli!]
They ran away.
They can't find Sulli.
They're on the fourth floor right now.
Sulli, they're looking for you right now,
so keep yourself well hidden.
Okay.
I don't think this is going to work.
We have to go after them.
- I feel so bad for Suk Jin.
- Why?
He's still out there kicking the balls.
Suk Jin is still out there?
- What's he still doing out there?
- After I sent Jong Kook in...
I got my own name and just
came in here.
Challenge.
I'm at least kicking it
in the right direction now.
Challenge.
It's not like I'm preparing to
go out in any competition here.
[If I had studied this hard
when I was younger...]
Yoo Jae Suk.
I can do it!
- We have to switch out our tape.
- Okay.
Hit the slate.
What?
One, two, three.
Did you use up all your tape?
[With a fresh roll of tape
and new determination.]
[I'm going to lose my mind!]
[Oh... oh!]
[Team Ja Chul's Suk Jin hits his own
big name tag on the mark!]
Why does it have to be that one?
I don't know if I should be happy or not.
[Even the staff members who've been bored
out of their minds cheer in excitement.]
Ji Suk Jin!
[Set Team finally able to go home!]
Ji Suk Jin! But I really
don't know if I should be happy.
Wow... of all the name tags,
I can't believe I got that one.
[Team Ji Chul's Suk Jin finally gets to
enter with his big name tag.]
Ji Suk Jin of Team Gu Ja Chul
makes his entrance.
I finally did it.
Ji Suk Jin of Team Gu Ja Chul
makes his entrance.
- Suk Jin!
- Where are you?
Where do I need to go?
You have to be careful.
Suk Jin, they're all lying in ambush.
They're all lying in ambush.
I'm coming down. Just wait there.
You have to be careful!
They're coming down?
[Message crossed.]
[Ji Sung's team having waited in ambush!]
[Starts to chase down the Impala!]
Run, Ji Sung!
Run!
[Ji Sung is hot on his heels!]
[Moving in on Big-nosed Brother
before he even notices it!]
[Barely escapes the attack!]
[Getting attacked...
from every which direction!]
I just got in!
I just got in here!
Please, Ji Sung!
I just got in here.
I just got in here after kicking
the ball for the past two hours!
[Poor thing...]
I just got in here.
I've been kicking out there
for two hours, Ji Sung.
- Are your legs okay?
- My legs won't stop shaking.
- I just got in here.
- And that's what you wore in here?
That's what I kicked.
Ji Suk Jin, out.
Wow, that's too funny.
Ji Sung...
I can barely walk as is right now.
How could you have eliminated me
when I can barely even walk right now?
- Did you see him run?
- You really are...
I'm sorry.
- I'm going to get some rest now.
- Ji Suk Jin, as soon as he enters...
Ji Suk Jin, out.
- Ha Ha.
- Yes?
Why don't you take Sulli and hide?
I'll come find you later.
Okay, then let's do this.
Hiding team, search team,
and attack team.
But Gary... you have to eliminate Ji Hyo
as soon as you see her.
Okay, I got it.
You have to promise me.
- You can't weaken your heart.
- You think I can do it?
You have to do it instead of
asking me if you can.
I have to get my mind straight.
- You really have to eliminate her.
- Okay, I will.
- Gary, you have to eliminate Ji Hyo, okay?
- Okay.
- I can do it, don't you think?
- Of course.
Since we're out there looking for Ji Hyo,
but that Gary...
I don't know if Gary will be able to
eliminate her though.
That's what I'm saying.
What if he loses his sight
in front of her again?
You, Kwang Soo or Suk Jin would be
perfect for a job like this.
Suk Jin never gives anyone a break.
Ji Hyo.
Song Ji Hyo.
[Even the tone of his voice when calling out
her name is that of a lover...]
Ji Hyo.
[She's right behind that door!]
I hear someone right by here.
Someone is here right now.
Someone come over here right now
and help me!
Ji Hyo.
- Kang Gary, are you here alone?
- Yeah, I'm here alone.
Are you going to eliminate me?
Hang on, I don't know what to do.
- Come here.
- Hang on.
Are you going to eliminate me right now?
If you keep asking me like that,
I don't know...
I don't know if I
can eliminate you anymore.
- Can you turn off the lights?
- Why are you turning the lights off?
Why are you trying to set the mood?
- Are you going to eliminate me?
- No, I'm not sure.
[Already looking discouraged.]
It's just the two of us right now.
I made a promise that I'd eliminate you
as soon as I saw you.
- Who did you make that promise to?
- With my team members.
Stop staring at me like that.
You're going to weaken my resolve.
[Who knew a situation like this
would come find them again?]
Do you remember that rainy day
out on the field a long time ago?
Yeah, I do.
[This is the situation we were in...]
[The man who had to
capture the woman...]
[The woman who begged for
the man to save her...]
You can't do this to me.
- Don't tell Jong Kook that I let you go.
- I'll tell him that I ran away from you.
You have to give me your
number, okay?
- Okay.
- Promise?
[And thus...]
[He set the woman...]
[Free on that day.]
[The first time that the man
self-sacrificed himself for the woman...]
Remember when I let you go?
- Remember?
- Yeah.
[The man caught in the
same dilemma once again...]
I've been hiding under here all this time
without even being able to lift up my head.
Why?
Have you even eaten yet?
You haven't even eaten yet?
[You all ate together earlier...]
I wish I could order you
some jjajangmyun or something.
Don't you think that if I were to eat here,
that I'd be totally caught?
But you still have to eat.
Listen, Ji Hyo.
[The man and the woman...
how will today end for them?]
[Hello?]
[Ja Chul arrives to help Ji Hyo!]
Wait, Ja Chul!
Ja Chul!
You, Song Ji Hyo!
[Sorry!]
[Gary of Team Ji Sung is eliminated!]
You should break up with her now.
You could've waited five minutes
to eliminate me!
She and I were talking about
our past memories!
Gary, out.
- Where's Jong Kook?
- He's alone right now.
I have to go, Kang Gary.
- Forget it. I'm mad.
- Don't be mad.
It's always been like this.
For three and a half years now.
- Let's make up.
- Forget it. Not today.
Come here.
Let's make up.
Can you play the song that you played
for us the very first time?
- 'A woman that you can't break up with...'
- For three and a half years now?
[A man who can't leave that woman
for three and a half years now.]
- Where are they?
- We have to go over to the other side.
Over there.
You see them over there?
- I see them coming this way.
- It may be better to stay here.
Ji Hyo, the guys are here now,
so you have to stay hidden, okay?
[Contacting Ji Hyo to tell her
to stay deep in hiding.]
I'll go back to where I was earlier.
[A habit that he's formed since
having been on Running Man before.]
Ji Sung... did you see us on the sixth floor
when you were with Sulli earlier?
I saw you with Sulli.
I even made eye contact with her.
I saw her earlier up there.
- There's Jong Kook right there.
- Yeah, I see him.
You know I'm fast.
[Four of the strongest having
all gathered in one place.]
Hang on a second.
[Imminent battle]
Why are you always hiding in the corner
when you're the strongest of the bunch?
[This is the survival instincts of
being a Running Man.]
Why are you getting so startled?
[Ja Chul startling his senior, Ji Sung.]
I've never seen you act like that.
This little kid...
[Now that we get a better look,
he's a rigid senior?]
Ji Sung, you're funny.
Should we go and help them?
Maybe we should?
[Ji Sung vs. Ja Chul and
Jae Suk vs. Jong Kook!]
Be careful, Ja Chul!
Time.
Hang on.
These two guys look like they're
in a little kid fight or something.
What? I keep hearing
all the slapping noises.
What are you two guys doing?
What's all that noise?
Are you okay?
[Soccer players aren't very good at
using their hands...]
What's this that they're doing?
Give us some space.
Come on, give us some space.
Where are you...
[Ji Sung attacks Ja Chul!]
Ja Chul...
[Ji Sung now moves on to
attack Jong Kook!]
[Ji Sung gets a hold of
Jong Kook's name tag!]
[This time gets his hand on
Ja Chul's name tag!]
[Jae Suk and Jong Kook eliminates
each other simultaneously!]
- Are you okay?
- I'm fine.
Are you okay, Ja Chul?
[Jong Kook and Jae Suk
are both out!]
[Team Ji Sung's survivors-
Ha Ha, Ji Sung, and Queen Sulli.]
[Team Ja Chul's survivors-
Ja Chul and Queen Ji Hyo.]
Ha Ha is still alive, isn't he?
You have to be careful.
You have to go right now!
You have to finish the battle
between you guys right now.
No, I have to oust Ha Ha first.
- Ha Ha.
- Go find Ji Hyo!
You have to oust Ha Ha.
You can't handle both of them by yourself.
[Ji Sung going off to find Ha Ha
to get his help.]
Ha Ha, where are you?
- Who got ousted?
- Ji Sung and Ha Ha are still alive.
- I'm the only one left.
- Really?
- Ja Chul... and Ji Hyo.
- That's it?
It's just the two of them left?
So it's three against two.
- They're on that side of the building.
- Really?
- They're over there.
- Let's go find them.
- We have to go find them first.
- I bet they're hiding right now.
We'll win as long as we eliminate Ji Hyo.
You and I together will grab her like this
and eliminate her.
Ji Hyo... our target is Ji Hyo.
Whatever Gu Ja Chul decides to do,
our goal remains Ji Hyo.
Okay.
Ja Chul, are you watching us right now?
Gu Ja Chul!
Are you watching us right now?
[All the survivors of both teams
coming face to face!]
Wow, this really is...
[Once the queen is ousted, it's game over!
Have to protect the queen no matter what!]
[Queen Ji Hyo is getting ready to
attack on her own behind Ja Chul.]
- Yeah, grab his arms.
- Be careful.
[Ji Sung and Ha Ha each grabbing
one of Ja Chul's arms!]
[Just then, Sulli moves in to
attack Ji Hyo?]
Hurry!
Hurry, Sulli!
[Ji Hyo turns and counterattacks Sulli!]
[Ja Chul rushes in to help,
but Ji Sung blocks him from moving in!]
[Even Ha Ha moves in to attack Ji Hyo!]
[Sulli eliminates Ji Hyo's name tag!]
[Team Ja Chul's Queen, Ji Hyo is ousted!]
That really won't come off!
I think he glued it on here
with superglue.
Oh, I guess it does come off.
[It looks like it falls off
easy enough to us...]
- What happened?
Those guys won.
[Protect the Queen-
Team Ji Sung wins!]
Ja Chul still didn't get ousted?
No, Ja Chul didn't get ousted.
Since Team Park Ji Sung won,
his team gets two nomination cards.
[Team Park Ji Sung wins two entrance cards
for having won the race.]
We should've won the race.
I can't believe Ja Chul came on the show when
he's getting married the day after tomorrow.
- Seriously.
- Thank you so much.
The Asian Dream Cup is the day after
the wedding...
But I won't be able to attend since
I'm getting married the day before
so I'm a little disappointed myself.
That is disappointing.
I really hope that everyone goes to support
Running Man and the team at the tournament.
That's our Captain Gu.
[The moment where the sincerity of
Captain Gu's love for soccer is felt.]
- He's very loyal.
- He is a great guy.
That is one loyal guy.
I really wish Ja Chul the happiest
of all marriages!
[Congratulations on your nuptials!]
Everyone will now head off to the airport.
Off you go!
[Off to 2013 Asian Dreamcup in Shanghai!]
Running Man, fighting.
Gu Ja Chul, fighting!
One, two, three!
[A few days later-
Incheon International Airport.]
[Off to Asian Dreamcup!]
[Entering city of Shanghai with
high expectations!]
[And the meeting of the two men
as if destined by fate.]
As expected, he and his best friend,
Evra are in perfect sync.
He and Evra...
they're sharing their joy together!
[A brother to our own country, Evra!]
No, you're stupid.
Republic of Korea, I love you.
[With high energy,
and overflowing with wit and humor.]
[Korean sense of humor which
isn't very easy to get a hang of...]
[Evra meets it head on!]
[His sense of mischief is
like none other!]
[God of variety has blessed him
every step of the way!]
- Evra...
You're scary funny.
I have to go to the bathroom.
Maybe I should've gone to the bathroom.
You're going in.
I'm going in?
What do I do?
[Next Week's Running Man-
Shanghai Dream.]
Subtitles by DramaFever