[He made his return last week.]
[Our eternal captain, Park Ji Sung.]
[And our proud new captain, Gu Ja Chul.]
[Two captains of Republic of Korea-
A super match with their pride on the line.]
[A national draft match with the chance to
join the Dream Cup on the line.]
[At the end of a hot match on
one summer night...]
[Team Park Ji Sung wins two
entry tickets to the game!]
[One hot punishment
awaits the loser team.]
[And today...]
[Running Man stands
on the field of dreams once more.]
[Battle of the manliest of all men.]
[Running Man takes their spot
in the midst of that field.]
Kwang Soo!
Subtitles by DramaFever
[One day before the Asian Dream Cup-
Incheon International Airport at 7 a.m.]
[Antarctic fashion hitting the airport
in the middle of the summer.]
There they come.
I can see those guys heading this way.
- There they are.
- Look, it's people from Antarctica.
Hey, we're over here!
Ji Hyo looks pretty nice.
[A worker from the Antarctic,
and a model from Moscow.]
I bet they're going crazy.
They've got to be crazy hot in that.
[A look that makes even the onlookers
break out in a sweat.]
[What are they doing?]
- I bet they're miserable right now.
- Hello!
- Hi.
- Hi, Sulli.
[I'm doing fine,
but I don't know about you...]
We're not embarrassed whatsoever.
Suk Jin, that's the best look I've
ever seen on you so far.
- Me?
- Yes.
- You look like G Dragon.
- It really does suit you.
[Call me 'Ji-Dragon'...]
Hey, don't you think that
Ji Hyo looks pretty nice?
- You look pretty good.
- Ji Hyo looks pretty in anything she wears.
Ji Hyo looks like she just stepped
off the pages of a fashion magazine.
Not many people look good
in earmuffs.
- Does it look okay? I can't see myself.
- No, they look good on you.
I'm sure you remember, but that's the
punishment from losing the game.
You four were the winning team,
and these four were on the losing team.
This is their punishment for losing.
If you don't take off any of your clothing
until you board your plane for Shanghai...
you can be freed from your
slavery duties.
Slavery duties?
You're the winning team's slaves.
[Complete your mission and rid the clothes,
and escape from the slavery duties!]
[Only when completing the mission given
by their masters, can they shed the clothes.]
Since we're evenly numbered,
we've assigned each of you a master.
- Can you tell us who?
- Hang on a minute.
- Since you're a slave...
- Isn't Jong Kook Sulli's slave?
Just hang on a minute.
Therefore... Sulli will be your master,
and you'll be her slave today.
And Gary will be in charge of Ji Hyo
and will be ordering her around today.
I actually happen to be wearing a denim
button-down shirt underneath this like Gary.
[Master Gary happy with the idea of
a couple look with his slave, Ji Hyo.]
- I really am wearing a denim shirt.
- What is this between you guys?
- They seriously are fated to be.
- Okay, I'll pick the first one.
I really need to take this coat off.
I'm burning up underneath all this.
- This is for all the slaves. Oh my!
- Oh my...
[Buy jippo (dried fish) in order.]
What?
What does that mean?
Where are we going to find that
at the airport?
- I don't have any money either.
- I have no money either.
- You have to figure that out for yourself.
- Don't you want to take off that fur coat?
- I'm starting to sweat in this thing.
- Where are we going to find jippo?
Walk so that you don't sweat and this is
a first come first serve type of thing.
- I'm really starting to sweat in this.
- Where's jippo?
Who sells jippo in here?
Who knew that I'd ever be looking for
jippo at the Incheon airport?
- Do you sell jippo here?
- No, but we have dried squid.
Okay, thank you.
- Is there a convenience store in here?
- Over there in that direction.
[He definitely is the brain!
Big-nosed Brother heads off to the store!]
[All the slaves heading off in the direction
of the Big-nosed Brother after seeing him.]
Suk Jin found it!
[Too busy paying for the jippo
to even think clearly.]
Please hurry!
Get away from me.
Let go!
Let go of me! It's over there.
[Everyone grabbing the jippo
by the handful.]
- You can get the change.
- What?
- You can get my change for me.
- Hey!
[Arriving back in a rush
to appease their masters.]
- I'm so hot.
- You can take this off for now.
- I'm so hot in this right now.
- You can take off the scarf.
[Ji Hyo gets to take off her scarf
for having completed her mission.]
I like my caramel macchiato
in the mornings.
I need my caramel macchiato.
What are you doing, slave?
Hey, Song Ji Hyo!
Don't get too close to me!
You're going to make me weaken my resolve.
- You can take off your scarf.
- Thank you.
- Sure, you can take off the scarf.
- Kwang Soo, take off your panties.
What?
How can I take off my panties?
- I want a cola.
- Look at Jong Kook.
[Jong Kook having arrives at last,
and delivers the food to Sulli.]
- You can take off your scarf.
- Sulli's such an angel.
She's such an angel.
You have to have a good master.
It makes the life so much better.
I'm going to be so loyal to her.
- What else can I do for you?
- Didn't you say that you were thirsty?
- You can talk to him in casual speech.
- In casual speech?
- Speak to him in casual speech.
- This is your chance.
- You're just playing a game.
- Think of me as one of your friends.
- In that case...
- Think of me as being younger than you.
Just order him by his name.
Kim Jong Kook!
Yes, Master.
- Orange juice...
- Yes, I understand.
- 'Get it for me'.
- Will you get it for me?
'I really want some right now'.
- I really want some!
- Yes, I understand.
What kind would you like?
Would you like it in a can?
Or what other kind can I get for you?
- Tell him to use your own judgment.
- You can make the call.
Yes, I understand. Why do
you keep telling her what to say?
I didn't say anything to her.
I'm just talking to myself.
Why do you keep feeding her
the lines?
Here's the caramel macchiato.
[Blank Ji Hyo's speedy service
to her master.]
That looks really refreshing.
I told them to make it extra good because
Kang Gary was going to be drinking it.
- You can take off your coat, Ji Hyo.
- Thank you, Gary.
You're not going to eat it?
You're not eating it?
Then should I throw it away?
Wow... look at how well
he treats Ji Hyo.
- There's nothing you won't do for her.
- I knew a day like this was going to come.
- What? Are there two straws?
- Of course.
Here. How about you and I
each take a sip?
That sounds good.
Aren't you going to drink it?
You're not drinking it?
[You just wait until we get to Shanghai...]
Then you can keep your coat on
until we get to Shanghai!
One sip for Ji Hyo!
- I haven't seen that in a while.
- Been three years since they've done that.
- You two look so comfortable doing that.
- We've played the stick cookie game twice.
You two look so natural doing that.
As if that's a no big deal.
You can take your coat off, Ji Hyo.
- Wow... he's so nice to her.
- Thank you.
Thank you so much.
- There you are.
- Maybe I shouldn't have worn this.
- Wow, that was good.
- Can I take my coat off?
No, but you can take
your scarf off.
[Kwang Soo is allowed to take off
his scarf for completing the mission.]
[I want to take my earmuffs off.]
Shout out, 'I want you, Kang Gary' five times
loud enough for everyone to hear.
[Ugh, my head...]
Loud enough for
those people to hear you.
Why aren't we heading off
to Shanghai yet?
- Ji Hyo's about to do her mission.
- Really?
[As soon as the last item comes off,
she escapes her life as a slave.]
What?
That she loves Kang Gary?
[Fine. It's no big deal...]
Everyone!
Are you guys going public
with your relationship?
- Please make room for her announcement.
- Yes.
Aren't you going to do it!
[Will she say it?]
I'll make my confession
here and now.
You have to say it five times.
Ready, go.
- I want you, Kang Gary!
- One.
- Not loud enough, is it?
- Yes!
-  I want you, Kang Gary!
- I don't think Shanghai can hear you yet.
Are you feeling shy?
Everyone, please join in.
I want you, Kang Gary!
[Ecstatic]
- You all heard her, didn't you?
- I want you, Ha Dong Hoon!
- I want you all to tell the whole world!
Hey!
You've just humiliated me.
[After their arrival at the airport,
everyone completes their mission.]
- Wow, it's so hot.
- That was too funny.
We will be leaving for Shanghai soon.
There are only two tickets to participate
in the competition.
Four of you will have the honor of playing in
the Asian Dream Cup through a nomination.
Everyone will now board
the plane for Shanghai.
- Let's go!
[Heading off to Shanghai
with all the cheerful farewells!]
Thank you.
[Asian Dream Cup...
We are coming for you!]
[This is Shanghai!]
[Second capitol of China.
This is Shanghai!]
[A place where the global culture
and tradition lives in coexistence.]
[Running Man arriving
at the press conference.]
[A passionate welcome.
The start of their press conference.]
[What are they predicting
the final score to be at the game?]
I'm not sure how it's
going to turn out.
It all depends on how well
the Running Man Team does for us.
[Huge burden]
[If the Running Man Team participates, then
there's a higher chance Shanghai will win.]
He's not the same as he was last year
when we played on the same team.
One, two, three.
Fighting!
[Here's to fair play at the upcoming game!]
[The morning of Asian Dream Cup]
- What is this?
- What's going on in here?
What's this?
I guess we'll be sitting
with our own teammates.
Director.
[Captain Park joining
the Running Man Team.]
- Let's sit over here.
- Come here, Sulli.
How is your condition this morning?
- Are you doing well?
- I got a very good night of sleep.
- Yes, I slept very well last night.
- Jong Kook didn't sleep very well last night.
From what I can see, he hasn't
been able to recover his condition.
- He's not adjusted to the time difference.
- What is he talking about?
There's only an hour difference.
- There's only a one hour difference.
- But there's still a time difference.
Anyway, since our Captain Park is going to
choose who'll be in the game...
Would it be possible for all of us
to participate in the game?
- All of you?
- Yes.
No, that's not going to happen.
[Predicting that he won't
be in the game?]
[That actually makes him feel
more at peace...]
I will now reveal to you
your Shanghai mission.
You will play a total of two mission to
choose two players for the game.
At the end of each mission,
one player will be picked for the game.
- One team currently has no captain.
- I think he nominated himself as the captain.
Give us a captain too, since
Gu Ja Chul isn't going to be on today.
- Give us a new captain.
- This person has strong leadership skills.
- Who is it?
- He's a world famous soccer player.
- A world famous star?
- Call out to him in English.
- In English?
- Excuse me!
Is he an American?
[A manly man with dignity...
waiting behind the closed doors.]
- Welcome!
- Come in please!
Welcome to Running Man!
[Another captain makes his way
into the room!]
[Patrice Evra!]
Evra!
[Ji Sung's other half, Evra is here!]
[French floating wingback currently
playing for the Manchester United.]
[Known as Ji Sung's other half
during Ji Sung's days on the team!]
[Park Ji Sung's best friend,
Patrice Evra!]
He says that I'm stupid.
- My brother!
- Evra!
- My brother, Evra!
- His face is so small!
[Happy to see each other again even though
they met at the press conference.]
- Come shake his hand.
- Greet each other.
- Evra is here.
- Hello.
- I can't believe that he's here.
- Evra, this is Sulli.
- Hello.
- Hey, Evra.
[Greeting Ji Sung with familiarity.]
- Evra.
- This is your name tag.
[Running Man name tag on
his own back!]
- I have to put this on your back.
- I'm not stupid.
- Oh, you're not stupid?
[The very first Korean word
that he learned from Ji Sung.]
This is all because of you!
[Welcome to Running Man!]
Evra is like a member of our own family.
He's so familiar with all of this.
Why don't we all give him a
round of applause?
[Another world famous star making
his appearance on Running Man!]
- Thanks, thanks.
- 'Thanks, thanks'...
- Isn't he good looking?
- He's really good looking.
- His eyes twinkle.
- You're so handsome.
Thanks, thanks.
[Am I good looking?]
Has Evra ever watched Running Man before?
Does he know about the show?
Have you ever seen this program?
- Yes, and I want to greet the Korean people.
- He says he wants to greet the Korean fans.
Republic of Korea... I love you.
[Lighting fire to the atmosphere
with one simple statement!]
- We love you too!
- Me too! Me too!
[Pay attention to Evra's entertainment
skills that we'll be showing in a little bit.]
Can you ask how old he
thinks Suk Jin is?
- What?
- My age...
- Yes?
- You guess my age.
- Ah, your age?
- Thirty...
- Dirty?
- Thirty eight.
- Ah, thirty eight?
[What? This face?]
[Then what about Kwang Soo?]
I think he looks 42.
42.
[The old man...]
It's because you're big.
- Evra, let's you and I be friends.
- Evra, that was great!
But that was too much.
It's so nice for Evra to come join us in
the little free time that he has.
He is amazing as our new captain.
- He's better than Ji Sung.
- Jong Kook... are you going to take that?
How can you say such a thing?
You may not get to run even if
you're picked to join the game.
[Park Ji Sung is the one with the liberty
to decide who gets to join the game.]
Come on, you can't do that.
I'm prepared to do whatever it is
that you ask of me to do.
I played mostly the One-Top position
when I played soccer.
[Say what?]
[One-Top= The highest offensive position.]
Why wouldn't I know?
Why wouldn't I know what One-Top is?
When I told him that you may be playing,
Evra just said that we'll lose if you do.
No. It's not going to
be like that, Evra.
You should see how well I can run.
I'm very well suited for One-Tops.
Okay, then.
Let's see how well you do.
- What will you do, Jong Kook?
- I'll do whatever is ordered of me.
In that case, a jjajangmyun...
[You just said that you'll do
whatever is ordered of you.]
Just order it for us.
[Kindly translating even
the jokes to him.]
What about you, Kwang Soo?
What are you going to do?
- I too am...
- Why don't you just cheer?
- I can do whatever I'm told.
- You should do this...
You can play second base.
[Isn't that baseball?]
- You're telling me to be a ball boy?
- A ball boy.
We will now conduct a variety of training
sessions to determine the last two open spots.
Okay, we'll start off with
the first training.
It's called, Shanghai Marble.
[First player nomination mission-
Shanghai Marble.]
[If it's Shanghai Marble...]
- What are we going to have to do?
- Isn't that Dong Wan?
[The king of disguises, Dong Wan!]
[Disguising himself into the famous
game character...]
- He's a man?
- Yes.
[Evra bursting into laughter.]
Evra really seems to like
Dong Wan's getup.
He looks better than
either of these two ladies.
[Seriously?]
He says that Dong Wan is
the prettiest in here.
[You're the best!]
What you're looking at right now is
the Shanghai Marble board.
Do you see the board pieces
for your team?
Park Ji Sung and Evra's faces are on
top of each team's piece.
You will move the number of spaces on the
board that you roll on the die for a mission.
[Must complete the mission
that you land on.]
If you fail your mission, you have to
pay Go Dong Wan's Shanghai bank
a toll fee of 1,000 Yuan.
But if you succeed your mission
you don't need to pay the fee,
and get to roll the dice again.
- Okay, I understand.
- Each team will be given 3,000 Yuan.
- 3,000 Yuan?
- 3,000 Yuan.
The captain that wins the Shanghai Marble
will earn one slot for their teammate.
- Evra, you can roll the die.
- Right here?
[Evra taking the first turn to
roll the die on the board.]
- Two.
- Two!
The lucky key.
[Landing on the Lucky Key?]
- Aren't we supposed to go that way?
- Doesn't it usually go that way?
[That's not the direction
to move the piece...]
[Moving two spaces in the right direction.]
No, no.
No, this way.
No, I'll just go.
He's annoyed now.
- Seoul.
- I bet Seoul would be better.
[Shanghai Marble- Seoul Mission.
Ddakji.]
- It's a ddakji game?
- The first Seoul mission is...
- What is it?
- It's 'Beat the ultimate ddakji'.
[Beat the ultimate ddakji!]
You have to hit that and flip it over.
[Must beat two players of the other team
to pass the space!]
[Demonstrating the game to Evra
who's never seen ddakji before.]
- I have to turn that over?
- Yes.
You've got to flip it.
You should tell Evra that he needs to
hit it right in the middle.
- It's not flipping over.
- Is it really hard?
- Yeah, you try it.
- Let me see if I can help it.
- He's good.
- He's got the feel of it.
[Oh? Showing some skills in the game?]
Good.
- Ji Hyo, show them what you've got.
- You've only got one chance, okay?
Hey, hey, hey...
- She only has one chance.
- Evra wants you to be quiet.
There you go!
[Reacting like an elder would?]
- Evra, that's Kwang Soo.
- Kwang Soo.
- Giraffe.
- Come on, Kwang Soo.
He's a long guy.
He's a comedian.
42. He's 42.
I'm 29!
I'm 29 years old!
- No, no. You 18 years old.
- He's 18?
[Since he's on his own team,
flattering him by telling him he's 18.]
We have to beat two people.
- You need to flip one, Suk Jin.
- I know. I need to get one.
I get another try since I caught it.
[Anther try for catching it?]
[A new rule?
Catching it gives you three tries?]
- Catching it gives you another try.
- One more?
What kind of a rule is that?
[He catches it again!]
[Is this Big-nosed Brother's secret skill?]
How did Suk Jin catch that?
[Anyways, this will be his last try.]
- Don't think about it too much.
- You have to slam it down harder.
You have to hit it in the middle.
[Now it's Ddakji King, Mr. Capable's turn.]
Ddakji King.
He's Ddakji King.
Hey, hey.
That's me.
[I'll show you how it's done.]
[Two out of five people must flip it to pass.
Evra Team's Jong Kook easily succeeds.]
How about a round of applause for Evra!
[Evra of Evra's Team is the final player.]
[His first encounter with ddakji...
He must flip it over for his team to pass.]
This is going to be difficult.
[There he goes!]
[Evra flips over the ultimate ddakji!]
[My goodness...]
[Evra's Team passes the Seoul ddakji mission
in the Shanghai Marble game!]
That's unreal.
Unbelievable!
- Thanks.
- What does 'unbelievable' mean?
Thus, Evra's Team can go on to the next round
without having to pay the toll fee.
Okay, it's Park Ji Sung's turn.
- Is it my turn?
- Okay, Captain Park!
- Get number two.
- Just throw the die!
We're good at the second one.
We're good at the ddakji game.
Number three!
Okay, Sao Paulo!
[What will Sao Paolo mission be?]
Okay, Sao Paolo!
- What's that?
- We have to play it with our feet?
Come on, that can't be done
with your feet.
That's the first time I've heard
Ji Sung say anything like that.
Ji Sung normally doesn't say
things like that.
Just one of you needs to succeed
for you to pass this mission.
- Just one person?
- Challenge!
Challenge.
You have to get the ball a little higher
to get it in the goal.
You have to get a clean shot for it
to have a chance of making it in.
- You're good at foot volleyball.
- But that's not going to be as easy.
With it being so high, it won't be easy.
Challenge.
[Ah, it unfortunately
bounces off the rim!]
[That's not going to be easy.]
It can't be that hard.
My foot must've lost its mind.
[Everyone's focus is on the open slots
for the player nominee.]
You seem to be very
stressed out by that.
- You seem to be very stressed by it.
- Challenge!
- You can do it, Sulli.
- I can do this.
Good job.
You looked pretty doing it.
He told her that she did good
because she looked pretty doing it.
- What is that supposed to mean?
- Your face looked pretty when you did it.
- Then that's all that matters.
- Challenge.
- Gary may make it.
- He's good at things like this.
- He's good at stuff like this.
- Gary can do it.
- If it's Gary...
- Challenge.
[Captain Evra correcting his stance.]
- This is a difficult shot.
- Are you trying to teach me?
[I can be strict.]
[The ball goes in and bounces back out!]
Wow, that was such a close shot.
I thought that was going to
make it in for sure.
[Ji Sung Team's last hope,
Captain Park!]
- That's harder than it looks.
- Come on, Ji Sung.
Please, Ji Sung.
It definitely is hard.
- You didn't say, 'challenge'.
- No, I didn't say that.
[One more chance for not having said,
'challenge'?]
[Captain Evra coming out to call foul.]
Okay, okay.
I got it.
- He's really strict.
- Tell him not to step on the line.
Since I'm already mad...
seeing Kwang Soo's face over there
is making me want to hit it.
Why would you want to do that?
Challenge.
[If he makes the goal, then the
team passes the Sao Paolo mission!]
[Team Ji Sung fails
the Sao Paolo mission.]
[Having Evra give it a try?]
I really thought that Ji Sung
and Gary would make it in.
I don't think it's going to be easy.
[Immediately going into his acting mode?]
Did he say that it was because
his foot was hurting?
- He's so funny.
- Evra really is so funny.
Why is he so funny?
[Evra succeeds in scoring the ball!]
- Evra!
[Captain Evra full of
confidence and cheer.]
[How did he do that?]
- That's awesome.
- How did he do that?
- It was easy.
- What were you doing?
What's wrong with you, Ji Sung?
[Amazing... succeeds at
ddakji and the ball scoring?]
- That was shocking.
- Seriously.
[Team Ji Sung must pay 1,000 Yuan in
toll fees for failing their Sao Paolo mission.]
He's frighteningly funny.
[When did he learn to say that?]
Frighteningly funny?
- He sounds just like one of the guys.
- Evra feels like one of our regular members.
- Four!
- What is it?
- One, two, three, four.
[Lands on the Lucky Key!]
- He's bringing something.
- What is that?
Pick one.
- Do we rip one?
- No, just pull one out.
Captain vs. Captain competition.
- What's that?
- Captain vs. Captain competition.
[Ji Sung Team's Ji Sung vs.
Evra Team's Evra.]
- Ji Sung vs. Evra.
- It's captain vs. captain.
It'll be a competition
of captain vs. captain.
If Evra beats Park Ji Sung...
then his team wouldn't pay a toll fee.
But if Park Ji Sung wins,
then the team would pay the toll fee.
- Then this isn't a lucky key.
- Yes, it is lucky.
- What kind of a game is it?
- Then he has to beat Ji Sung?
[What is the game that Evra will be
playing against Ji Sung?]
[What's this?]
- What kind of a goal is that?
- Do they have to blow it?
Is it scoring by blowing with the straw?
- It's straw soccer.
- It's straw soccer game.
[Straw soccer!]
I'm tired.
I'm frighteningly tired.
Totally, frighteningly tired.
[Captain vs. Captain.
Best out of three straw soccer game!]
- You have to win, Ji Sung.
- Show him how it's done.
You have to win this, Evra.
[At last, a battle between
two best friends!]
- It's a game between Evra and Park Ji Sung.
- Between two world famous athletes.
- Competition between best friends.
- This is nerve wrecking.
Even though you may have played
video games like this together
I bet this is the first time you've
played something like this together.
First time playing this kind of a game.
- Are you ready?
- Yes.
[Just who will be laughing
at the end of this game?]
[Kick-off!]
Wow... look at them go.
No!
There you go!
[Ji Sung loses his first goal!]
[Acting as if he just scored a
real goal out on the field!]
Goal!
A goal for Evra!
[Ji Sung- 0: Evra- 1]
[It's not over yet!]
Thanks, thanks.
Thanks, but I'm tired.
Evra, how about restarting it?
[Shaking hands in goodbye
on his way out?]
[Even shaking hands with the camera?]
[Reconfirms that's it's a
best out of three!]
- Okay, one more for the win.
- This is my ball.
Yes, it is.
Blow real hard.
To the end!
That's so loud!
[Blowing the whistle
right next to their ears.]
- This is a sports arena.
- Take it easy with that.
[If he loses another round,
then it's game over!]
[Then let's do this!]
Goal!
I'm tired.
I was too tired.
[One more goal left for either teams.]
[Ji Sung steals Evra's ball!]
- Penalty!
[Adamantly protesting the move!]
- Admit that you cheated!
[Admits their breaking of the rule-
Going into a penalty kick.]
You have to block it from here like this.
Ji Sung Park can block it.
[If he scores the ball,
then it's Team Evra's win!]
[Will Ji Sung be able to block the shot?]
You're my captain!
[Misses his penalty kick.]
[The saying goes, the person who
kicks is the more nervous one!]
[Receives another chance at
the penalty kick.]
[Ji Sung blocks it!
He succeeds with his defense move!]
Evra!
[Taking his anger out on the referee.]
Evra.
- Water, water.
- Water.
Water, water!
[Both teams requesting a time out
for rest and strategizing.]
Evra!
[Both teams dispersing
back into their corners.]
[Special treatment for Captain Evra who
seems to be frighteningly tired.]
- Evra.
- It's just a game!
[All the team members fawning
over him.]
- Water, water.
- Get him some water.
- Here, Evra.
- We need some water too.
[Feels like a rest time for the UFC players.]
- Ji Sung, you ready?
- You're my captain.
[Putting his water bottle
in front of the goal post?]
I never knew that
straw soccer was this fun.
[One more goal, and this match is over!]
[Ji Sung dribbling the ball
as soon as the whistle sounds.]
[A close call for Evra,
but he blocks the goal!]
[So realistic with the real players
playing the game.]
- Evra's ball.
- Give both captains a hand.
[Cheering on the two captains with
a round of applause.]
[The writer trying to readjust the camera.]
[I need to borrow your hat.]
[Forceful dribble from Evra!]
[Evra protesting that his ball
hit Ji Sung's hand!]
- Penalty.
- He needs a penalty kick.
No penalty.
[Everyone reacting extremely sensitively.]
- He hit it with his straw!
- His hand got in the way.
- Penalty.
- No, no.
- No hang, no hand.
- Penalty.
[Finally agreeing on a free kick
instead of a penalty kick.]
[Putting it right in front.]
[Ji Sung trying to
block off the goal already?]
- That deserves a penalty!
- One palm length.
Okay, one palm.
- One palm.
- I feel that.
[Feeling to check and make sure
that Ji Sung isn't blowing on the straw.]
[How will Evra do this time?]
[Bouncing off the goal post!]
Tired, so tired.
[Time for Ji Sung's counterattack?]
[Slowly brings the ball closer,
then bam!]
[Good dribble tactics!]
[A dazzling score!]
[Recreating the 2002 winning ceremony
against Portugal!]
[A love and hate relationship.]
- We won!
[Straw soccer game-
Team Ji Sung wins!]
[Still thanking his teammates for cheering
him on even though he lost the match.]
That was good.
- That was so funny.
- That really was funny.
Seriously... that was too much fun.
[Team Evra ultimately hands over
1,000 Yuan in toll fee.]
Here, Evra.
[After Team Ji Sung's win,
it's now Team Evra's turn.]
- Four, four.
- Four!
- Bangkok.
- Bangkok!
- What is it?
- Massage jump roping.
- What's that?
- What is that?
- Ah, the acupuncture mat?
- What? I don't know.
- Bring out the mats!
- Evra...
- Bring out the acupuncture mat.
[Acupuncture mat that even
Jackie Chan had experienced...]
Everyone must take off their
shoes and socks.
This game is called,
'Loyal massage jump rope.'
[Shanghai Marble, Bangkok mission-
Loyal massage jump roping.]
This is our weakest game.
- 50.
- What?
[Five team members must complete
50 jump ropes.]
- How are we going to do 50 jumps?
- Jong Kook, you give it a try.
I can do this.
You know that I can handle it.
[Even though Running Man members
have experienced it before...]
No, no, no...
[Loyal massage jump roping-
Elder Kwang Soo to start off.]
You have to jump higher, okay?
One, two, three, four...
[Watching him with respect
glinting off of his eyes.]
Six, seven, eight, nine... nine!
[Goal is a combined count of 50.
Kwang Soo completes nine jumps!]
His toe got caught on the rope.
- It was his toe.
- He did a lot. He got nine jumps.
Okay, Ji Hyo.
I don't think Ji Hyo will even get one.
Ji Hyo, ready...
your team currently has nine. Set, go!
- I got it, I'll do it.
- Set, go!
- Just be quiet.
- Just let me do it.
- You should've done ten.
- But he only got nine.
- It didn't go the way I wanted.
- You can do it, Ji Hyo.
- Ji Hyo just needs to do two.
- Of course, that's all she needs.
10, 11, 12, 13, 14...
17, 18, 19, 20, 21, 22...
23, 24, 25.
[Ace completes 18 jumps!]
[Using the corner of the mat to
get himself used to the pain.]
- How many more?
- 25 more.
- 25.
- Challenge.
[Hits Kwang Soo in the back.]
[Icon of misfortune
no matter where he goes...]
[Ultimately, Big-nosed Brother
contributes 0 to the score.]
Why were you standing
back there!
Why are you yelling at me when I was
just standing there quietly!
Why were you standing back there?
Just get out of the way.
You just get in the way.
I was just standing in my spot!
- They need 25 more, right?
- 25.
[How will Evra do on his first
experience with the mat?]
[Who is that guy?]
[Does he have an acupuncture mat
at his home in France?]
[Continuing to jump!]
[Now that the mission is won...
the pain comes to find him!]
[You are something else...]
[Captain Evra is the icon of success!]
Evra did it!
[It's good for your health...]
Wow, Evra!
Are you okay?
[Shanghai Marble, Bangkok mission-
Massage jump roping is a success!]
- It's a success.
- Okay!
Evra's really entertaining.
[How about joining the Korean
entertainment industry once you retire?]
[Team Ji Sung's turn to roll the die.]
One!
What is it?
[What will be the Lucky Key's
mission be this time?]
It's another Captain vs. Captain game?
- What is it this time?
- It's a heading competition.
Each captain must head the ball to his teammate
and the team that does the most wins.
- Gary would be the best.
- Let Gary do it.
We choose Gary.
- Why don't you go first?
- You want us to go first?
- It's just one try, right?
- Let's practice it once.
Yes, it's one single try.
One, two, three, four, five, six...
He's good.
[While dancing?]
[Good job, Gary!
Feeling a win coming their way!]
- Good job.
- I can do that while dancing!
- I think Kwang Soo can do it.
- You try it, Kwang Soo.
[Team Evra-
Captain Evra and Elder Kwang Soo.]
We can do this, Evra.
Let's show them!
[Kwang Soo's pretty good himself?]
- There you go!
- Stop.
[This team is good too!]
- You just need to put your head out there.
- Okay, Gary!
- Shall we go first?
- Keep your eye on the ball.
[It's for real this time!
Which team will win?]
- We have to win this round.
- This is nerve wrecking!
Hey!
Don't touch.
This is nerve wrecking.
[Team Ji Sung-
Start the heading relay!]
One, two, three, four, five, six...
[Oh... can he make it?]
Seven...
[Ji Sung tries his best
to receive the ball...]
[Team Ji Sung scores nine!]
[Did so much better
during the practice round.]
Relax and calm down.
[Team Evra needs to beat nine to win.]
You get really nervous when you
start playing for real.
- Don't be nervous.
- Let's go!
Evra!
One, two, three, four...
Five, six, seven...
[Will seven be the end for them?]
[Receives the eighth shot!]
[If they get one more!]
Eight!
Nine, ten!
Seven, eight, nine, ten!
[Team Evra wins the heading relay game!]
[Hurray, Captain Evra!]
Evra!
[Shanghai Marble-
Team Evra is the ultimate winner!]
[Even celebrates with Dong Wan.]
Captain Evra just won himself a spot for
one of his members in the game.
[Finally making their move to the arena!]
Time to hit the slate.
One, two, three.
[Shanghai Hongkou stadium]
[Entering the stage where the
Dream Cup will take place in three hours.]
- It's really hot out here.
- It really is hot.
Who would've ever thought that I would be
walking up behind Evra like this?
This is so cool.
[Half excitement, and half nervousness.
Stepping onto the field of dreams...]
Okay, everyone.
This is Shanghai Hongkou Stadium.
This is amazing.
There's only one spot left to fill.
Team Ji Sung has two spots,
and Team Ev has one spot.
What do you mean, Team Ev?
It's Team Evra.
You will play a very simple game to determine
which team will get the last remaining spot.
[Starting their second training session to
determine who'll get the last remaining spot.]
[Free kick photo zone.]
[As the opposing team kicks the goal,
have to stand in front of the goal and smile.]
- Oh my God...
- On top of that...
The ball can't make the goal
in order for you to succeed.
So block the ball while we
keep the smile on our faces?
Let's go!
[Final mission-
Free kick photo zone- Start!]
- Is this the penalty kick?
- Yes.
- This is the official penalty kick spot.
- But how are we going to make this?
No, we can't make that.
Okay, I'll try kicking it.
I'll try to make the next goal.
[Yoo Hyuk shoots!]
[Even though Captain Park blocks it,
the ball still makes it in!]
You can't just kick it carelessly.
[Mr. Kim-Leave it makes his attempt.]
Let's see how Jong Kook does.
[Hmm...]
[As previously stated,
he just really loves the game.]
[Captain Evra tying his
shoelaces for him?]
Can I kick it?
[Team Evra takes the first challenge
in the Free Kick Photo Zone mission.]
You have to smile big.
You're getting your picture taken.
- You're getting your picture taken.
- I'm so scared.
Smile nice and big and
don't pay any attention to the ball.
How can we not pay any attention to it?
You try standing over here.
Okay, here we go.
Smile!
[Their hearts are about to
beat out of their chests.]
Okay, we're going to take the picture.
One, two, three.
[Ji Sung's kick.]
Kwang Soo, I'm sorry!
[Captain Evra getting
frighteningly angry.]
It's because you're just too tall.
It's because you're too tall.
[Ji, you just wait...]
Song Ji Hyo was the only one smiling.
[Picture shows that only Blank Ji
had a smile on her face.]
[Both eyes shut tight with
his teeth tightly gritted.]
Okay, I'm going to take the picture now.
- One, two, three!
- I'm going to kick it real hard.
[What did you say?]
[Extremely fierce kick!]
- Wait! Is he allowed to do that?
- What is he doing?
[Captain Evra breaking out in rage
for the second time.]
[You just wait and see, Ji...]
[Oh?
But they were all smiling?]
[With the exception of one.
Kangaroo?]
[Sorry.]
[Team Ji Sung's turn.]
Ji!
Come on, come on.
Wait, hang on.
- Revenge.
- I hope he takes it easy.
[A terrorizing fake shot.]
Jae Suk just turns his back.
- I don't know if I can do this.
- It's so scary.
[Oh? He makes the goal.]
I thought I was going to take
the ball in my face.
[Even though it was a fail because
the ball made the goal...]
[He still manages to protect his face
that he's so proud of.]
- You really are so ugly.
- He's a scaredy cat.
It's not like this is the first time
that I've acted this scared.
[Team Ji Sung's second try.]
Okay, I'm going to take the picture.
[Too scared to give a big smile...]
[Makes the goal again.]
[Just ends up guarding his face again.]
- Jae Suk...
- What are you doing, Jae Suk?
Why does he keep doing that?
[Putting up his guard?]
[If Yoo Hyuk had just smiled...]
[Team Evra steps up to
the challenge again.]
Kwang Soo, be careful, okay?
[Targeting on Kwang Soo?]
That's it, Ji Sung.
There it is.
I saw the expression on his face.
[There it is!
Scaredy-Kwang Soo's expression.]
[Everyone with a big smile on their faces...]
[Frog Kwang?]
[Adding ten additional chins to his face.]
- You have to relax.
- Okay.
Smile.
[Tea, Evra's second attempt.]
- One, two, three.
- Even Evra seems a little nervous.
[Frog Kwang makes his
return once more.]
[The ball didn't make the goal...]
[Even though everyone
managed to smile...]
[Frog Kwang only looks like he's crying.]
[Frog Kwang getting criticized
for his expression.]
That's how I normally smile.
[Giraffe's smile.]
I'm going to smile for real this time.
Evra, I'm going to smile for sure this time.
[Okay, you just give it a try.]
[Another hurray.]
[Throwing up his arms to guard his face
no matter what happens.]
The ball isn't even coming our way.
[I have to put the guards up.
My face is very precious...]
Okay, fine.
Let's get it done this time.
Come on, smile.
[Captain Evra concentrating on
black hole, Kwang Soo.]
[Don't do that.]
When did I do that?
I didn't make an expression like that.
[Big brother Evra not able to
put his trust in the Giraffe.]
- Want to try kicking the ball, Gary?
- Yeah, why don't you try it?
- It's okay, I can do it.
- No, no, no...
[Refusing his turn at the free kick.]
Come on, Evra.
Okay, I'm going to take
the picture now.
One, two, three.
- That felt so good! That felt so good!
- Kim Jong Kook!
No, no, no!
I smiled!
[Picture verification.]
[Shocked expression once again.]
[Frustrated]
That was a scare tactic.
[Sulli is the next kicker?]
[Realizing that Sulli can do it too
after seeing how scared they get?]
One, two, three!
[A hard hit to his long legs.]
Change!
[Ah... there's the Frog Kwang again...]
What now?
He's kicking it?
Here I go!
[The amateur kicker for Team Evra is...]
[Uncertain kick by the soccer loving
Mr. Kim-Leave it.]
[Huh?
Blank Ji?]
[Huh?]
[Since it was a fake tactic...]
[Captain Evra starting to get a headache.]
[Luckily fails it...]
Sorry.
[Telling her to leave the field?]
[Cold Captain Evra.]
- It's Suk Jin's turn.
- I'll kick it.
I don't know where it's going to go.
[Next kicker is, Big-nosed Brother.]
[Huh?
They may have succeeded...]
We got it.
[Ji Suk, Jae Suk and Gary succeeds...]
[Huh?]
[His eyes are closed, right?]
That Ha Ha...
Doesn't that count as a smile?
You have your eyes closed.
[That's his smiling expression?]
[Even though he tries to argue that
his eyes were open... Fail.]
Let's succeed this time.
Come on.
[Telling each other to get the timing right.]
One, two, three.
[Ji Sung's ball goes over the goal post.]
- I think we got it.
- I smiled.
[Blank Ji, Evra and Big-nose succeeds
in getting a big smile.]
[What about Frog Kwang?]
[Smile!]
Blue Team... success.
[Team Evra succeeds the
Free kick Photo Zone mission!]
Evra!
We have now completed all the player
nomination rounds for the Shanghai Dream Cup.
Park Ji Sung has two votes,
and Evra also has two votes.
[Team Ji Sung and Team Evra each
has two spots open for the game.]
Park Ji Sung can nominate two players
from his own team
and Evra can nominate two players
from his own team.
Make sure no one sees what you write down
and hand it over to us for us to announce.
[Who will be the members to step their foot
onto the 2013 field of dreams?]
Take it easy and
think about it carefully.
All I want to say is that
experience could be an important factor.
I just want to reiterate that I was
known for my One-Tops...
[After telling him to think comfortably,
everyone is quick to add their two cents.]
[Mr. Kim-Leave it showing off
his sloppy footwork.]
Evra's not watching you right now.
[His love for soccer reaching its peak.]
[Everyone gathering in to add
their final comments and opinions.]
You have to choose two players.
Look at me!
[Yoo Hyuk's kick hitting Evra
on his back.]
Change, change.
[I'm so sorry.]
[The two captains complete their
recommendations for their two players.]
[Who will the four slots go to?]
We can just cheer them on if
we don't make it in.
- The first player is...
- It's our team?
The first player for
Team Park Ji Sung is...
The first player is...
[Nervous... energy.]
[Who's the first player that
Captain Park has nominated?]
It's Yoo Jae Suk.
[Yoo Jae Suk]
- He's so lucky.
- I'll give it my best.
The next player is...
- It's an honor just to be here.
- It's an honor.
- Me too.
- I believe the experienced player should.
[Making courteous comments
that they don't really mean.]
Maybe it should go to someone
who's never done it.
But I really hope that it's me.
Second player from Team Ji Sung is...
Ha Ha!
[Second player- Ha Ha!]
Ji Sung!
I so badly wanted to play!
I wanted to play so badly!
I'm going to make sure to score a goal!
[Gary and Sulli unfortunately
don't make the cut.]
- Since you were in the game last year.
- Of course.
I feel even worse now that
Gary didn't make the cut.
[It's Team Evra's turn to make
the announcement of the players.]
Evra made the decision himself.
I didn't choose the players.
[Two players that Evra himself
chose to be in the game.]
I didn't have anything to do
with the decision that he made.
Time to announce the players
for the Blue Team.
[Who will be the first player for Team Evra?]
Lee Kwang Soo.
Yes, Evra!
My brother!
I'm your big fan forever!
- Forever.
- Thank you!
- He told Evra about Jong Kook's neck disk.
- Jong Kook's neck disk?
[Evra made aware of Jong Kook's
slipped disk on his neck?]
- You have medication patches on your neck.
- It's okay.
See?
I'm fine.
No, I'm fine.
Okay, the last player to participate
in the 2013 Dream Cup is...
[The final player for
the 2013 Asian Dream Cup is...]
Kim Jong Kook.
[Kim Jong Kook]
[Emotional...]
Thank you, brother.
The four of you who will be
playing in the game
will follow Park Ji Sung and Evra and go
prepare yourselves for the game.
[2013 Asian Dream Cup participants-
Jae Suk, Ha Ha, Kwang Soo, Jong Kook.]
We'll be cheering you on.
Good luck.
- Fighting.
- We'll see you later.
- See you later!
- We're proud of you!
- Make sure you win!
- Fighting!
[I should be in that game...]
[Off to the field of dreams!]
[One hour before the game.]
[Player locker room.]
[All the famous players that they've only
seen on TV are all in one place...]
[Seeming so out of place...]
[Swallowing in nervousness.]
[About to have a mental breakdown from
the thought of really being out on the field.]
[Camera flashes going off
to capture that moment.]
Captain Park.
Can you tell us what
the strategy for the game is?
4-3-3, or 4-3-2?
The formation is going to be 4-2-3-1.
Jae Suk, it's going to be 4-2-3-1.
[Earning a crucial piece of evidence.]
What did you say?
- 4-2-4?
- 4-2-3-1.
I usually get a lot of One-Tops.
[Craving attention
even during a soccer match.]
What's that on your thighs?
Are those medicated patches?
You're supposed to do this.
[Kim Bo Kyung]
He looks a lot like Kim Bo Kyung.
[Taking a picture with his twin,
Kim Bo Kyung.]
[Goldfish bread]
They really do look alike.
[Yoo Hyuk and Bo Kyung amazed
at their own likeness.]
[And one more couple.]
[Kim Dong Won and Giraffe, Kwang Soo.]
[A brief time to practice.]
[Stadium already full of audiences.]
[A bright greeting
at their eager welcome.]
[Practicing to loosen up their limbs.]
[- There are so many people here.
- I know.]
[Park Ji Sung.
All following him around?]
[All trailing behind Captain Park.]
[Do whatever Captain Park is doing.]
[Wanting to be just like Captain Park.]
[Evra catching sight of the scene.]
[Initiates Jae Suk in a playful play.]
[End of practice.]
One more minute.
[At last...]
[The moment to take their step
onto the field of dreams.]
[Running Man members full of
nervous energy.]
Kim Jong Kook.
[Jong Kook is called in!]
[How can this be?
Kim Jong Kook in the starting lineup!]
Good luck out there.
[Kkuk blinking his eyes out of
amazement and nervousness.]
- Fighting!
Good luck!
[Making their entrance at last...]
[The unfortunate mistakes
from last year...]
[Will show off his true skills this year!]
[Entering the stadium.]
[Cheers of welcome for Jong Kook that
can be heard throughout the stadium!]
[Ceremonial picture of the
starting lineup.]
[Let's do this.]
This is unbelievable!
[The remaining members heading
towards the bench.]
[But where are the rest of our members?]
[Everyone with their eyes fixed on
the image of Jong Kook out on the field.]
[They're right in there.]
I should be standing out there.
Jong Kook doesn't look as nervous
as he did last year out on that field.
- Here's the news article in Korea.
- What does it say?
That Kim Jong Kook and
Ji Dong Won are Two-Tops.
[There really is a news article...]
Is media play even allowed?
That'll be Kim Jong Kook's first and last
sports news article.
[Today's game being
broadcasted live in Korea.]
[Jong Kook's name on the lineup list!]
Everyone has their eyes on Kim Jong Kook.
He has to be the ace player of the day.
If Kim Jong Kook doesn't pull his weight,
it'll be tough for his team to score a goal.
That's correct.
Wow... he has an impressive build.
[The first half finally starts!]
[All of the world famous players are running
around kicking the ball on this field!]
[And Tiger Jong Kook running with
confidence amongst them!]
Jong Kook's build
looks like any other players.
[Blank Ji seeming to be
more nervous than he is.]
He and Ji Dong Won are the Two-Tops.
[Fellow members with their eyes following
Jong Kook's every move.]
[Captain Park's impressive footwork!]
There it is!
[A chance for Jong Kook!]
[Jong Kook moving into where
the ball was passed!]
[If he can receive the pass...]
[But the ball unfortunately
goes out of bounds.]
[But Kkuk shows that
he can make the right moves!]
[A 2:1 pass!]
[Kkuk showing his great passing skills
alongside Lee Chung Yong!]
- Jong Kook made a nice pass.
- Yeah.
[Number 38, Kim Jong Kook...
showing a different side to him this year?]
Look at the expression on
Jae Suk's face.
[Frightened Jae Suk.]
[His heart is about to beat
out of his chest.]
It's so nerve wrecking to
be sitting here.
[Getting more and more nervous seeing
the big crowd and all the players.]
I wonder how nervous Jong Kook is.
What do I do if they pass
the ball to me like that?
[Having less and less to say
from their nervous energy.]
[Shocking... To know that
he could actually be silent.]
[Only 15 minutes having passed
in the first half.]
[Evra's light footwork.]
[Just then, a pass is made over to Kkuk!]
It's Jong Kook!
[A slew of defense raining down
on him to his one side!]
[Will he be able to break through?]
[Missing his aim!]
[Oh no!]
[His sloppy footwork missing its mark!]
He missed his aim.
[Evra encouraging him on.]
[You'll have the ball stolen from you
if you try to do it all by yourself.]
[Captain Park's accurate long pass.]
Evra!
Evra shoots!
[Just then!]
[A chance for Kkuk to shoot!]
[Ah...]
[Kkuk having wasted a golden opportunity.]
- Oh no!
- He missed the pass!
He really isn't good, is he?
He just likes the sport.
He's just chasing the ball around.
[Chasing after the ball like its shadow.
Soccer lover, Mr. Kim-Leave it.]
If Jong Kook is playing that bad,
what hope is there for us?
[Full of worries.]
You're going in at the 25 minute mark.
- Who? Me?
- I think he meant you.
[Giraffe Kwang Soo being told
to warm up.]
Good luck, Kwang Soo.
[Minho of SHINee also nervous from
having been told to go warm up as well.]
- What? What do I need to do?
- You're going in.
[I have to go out there?]
[Nervousness is increased.]
[Giant Giraffe warming up.]
Please...
- Is that Lee Kwang Soo?
- There he is. He's coming out.
- Way to go.
- Kwang Soo!
I'm getting nervous for him!
- Why am I getting so nervous?
- I'm getting nervous for him!
Kwang Soo!
[Kkuk is being traded out.]
Good job.
[Giant Giraffe goes in!]
Now everyone will get a chance to see soccer
being transformed into a variety game show.
What if Kwang Soo makes a goal
with a headshot?
Lee Kwang Soo!
Look at how tall he looks out there.
[With his impressive height,
a headshot is definitely possible.]
Kwang Soo needs to spike in a goal.
[Captain Park ordering
Kwang Soo on where to go.]
[A corner kick chance!
Off by the goal post!]
[Even showing off some rough
playing skills.]
I think Kwang Soo's going to be good.
He gets rough out there.
[Amazed by Kwang Soo's aggressive moves.]
[Similar vibe as
England's Peter Crouch.]
Made a heading goal, Kwang Soo.
[A chance for a headshot?]
[Giraffe Crouch missing his timing.]
[But tall Giraffe still giving off the vibe
as if he may pull something off.]
- He's playing aggressively out there.
- With his tall height, the Chinese players...
[Gritting his teeth and sticking to
his spot by the goal post.]
[A pass made in the Giraffe's direction!]
There it is!
[Jump]
[Will he pull it off?]
[Ah... where's the ball?]
[Landing his headshot on the ground.]
[Oh no!]
[But you still did good!]
- He crashed.
- Even in sports, that's how he ends up.
[But still aggressively making his
attempt at making the headshot.]
Maybe he's trying too hard?
Is Kwang Soo okay?
- I bet that really hurt.
- That had to have hurt.
Evra steadies the ball and passes it.
Lee Kwang Soo!
He had the chance, but didn't
jump very high given his height.
[He didn't jump very high
given his height.]
[His long legs spiraling out of control
out on the field.]
[Bringing tons of laughter
to the crowd.]
Kwang Soo!
[Heading it with the side of his head?]
[Giraffe Crouch not performing
as well as expected.]
[What are you doing?]
He almost took that shot face first.
But he's still doing great.
[Giving the chance at a
free kick to Kwang Soo?]
Is Kwang Soo going to kick it?
I think Kwang Soo is kicking it.
Oh my gosh, Kwang Soo's kicking!
Don't do it!
Don't do this to our Kwang Soo!
- Please!
- Kwang Soo!
[Free kicker- Number 42,
Lee Kwang Soo.]
[20m to the goal... Can he make it?]
[Runs up to the ball
without any hesitation!]
[Will he make it?]
[Shooting the ball straight to
the goalie without any power behind it.]
[Chastised by Captain Park.]
But that was still a very effective kick.
- Does that count as a shot?
- Yes, it does.
[In one of the Chinese newspapers
on that same day...]
[This is the shot that made the papers.]
Kwang Soo, make a headshot.
[Giraffe Crouch still running
with everything that he has.]
[Another headshot?]
[Ji Sung's headshot bounces off
the post and misses the goal!]
- I should be out there!
I would've kicked it better than that!
All he had to do was kick it in.
[Giant Giraffe traded out of the game.]
- Great job, Kwang Soo.
- At least you didn't humiliate yourself.
- Good job.
- Good job, Kwang Soo.
- How was it out there?
Is it that bad?
Ji Sung nags at you so much.
- Like what?
- 'What are you doing!'
You even made some headshots,
and got to do a free kick too.
You are the only person on Running Man
who got to do something like that.
There appeared to be three balls
while I was out on that field.
I thought I was going to lose it.
I chose one of those three balls in my vision,
but that wasn't the real ball.
[Chose one of the three balls in his vision,
but that wasn't the real ball.]
[Start of second half!]
- Is Minho in there?
- Huh?
[Captain Park sitting on the bench?]
Evra said he wants to run
for another 15 minutes.
[Frighteningly tired Evra...
What a marvel!]
Nice!
[Evra with the ball!]
Nice.
Shoot!
[Ah... the goal post!]
[So close!]
[The score is still at 0:0.]
You need to warm up.
I said, you need to warm up.
[The time has come...]
[Ro-Ro finally heading in to warm up!]
- There's Ha Dong Hoon!
- Where?
There he is!
I'm nervous for you!
I really should be out there.
[So nervous...]
[Huh? What's that underneath?]
Both my shirts came off.
They both came off.
[Showing off his Iron Man shirt
to everyone.]
[Jae Suk also heading
into the warm up area.]
There's Jae Suk!
- Jae Suk!
- Ha Ha!
- Ha Dong Hoon!
[So nervous!]
[Just then!]
[Goal!]
[Captain Park scores a goal!]
[That's our Captain Park!]
He truly is the Captain of Asia!
[Ha Ha trades Minho out!]
[Ro-Ro finally stepping out onto the field!]
Is he ready?
[Ro-Ro being stationed off to the side.]
[With Ji Sung's goal,
the score is now at 1-0.]
[Haroro running all over the field
with his short little legs.]
[Winger Haroro showing off his sloppy
foot skills no matter where he goes.]
Oh no!
I can't bear to watch this.
Ha Ha stands out on the field with
his blond hair and short legs.
But he manages to move
fairly quickly, doesn't he?
- Yes.
- He slightly resembles Lee Geun Ho.
- No, I was wrong
- Yes.
[Jae Suk heading off to
take his position.]
I'm not good at soccer.
- How do you feel?
- What?
What are you doing?
Are you shooting this?
Do I look like I can even think
of what to say right now?
- I'm going to go crazy.
- You have to score a goal.
You're telling me to score a goal when
even this professionals can't score one?
[So easily startled...]
You're going to trade out
with Nam Tae Hee.]
He's in the center right now, so you'll
be a Two-Top with Suk Hyun Joon.
[Two-Top?]
- I'm playing the Two-Top position?
- Yes.
[Neighborhood One-Top position...
and now a real Two-Top position.]
- You have to make the goals.
- I'll do my best, but...
But I've never done that before.
[Ro-Ro doing well in his position
in the sideline.]
[Passing off to the open player.]
Shoot!
[Blocks off the goal.]
[But it was still an amazing attack which
started with Ro-Ro's move.]
I was told I have to take off my glasses.
I'm not going to be able to see the ball.
[Jae Suk finally getting ready
to step out onto the field.]
- Please!
- I'm so nervous for Jae Suk.
- Come on, Jae Suk.
- He took off his glasses.
Can he see?
What if he can't see?
The bigger problem is that he looks
so ugly without his glasses on.
[More worried about how his
bare face looks rather than his vision?]
[A chance at a penalty kick!]
He came out of nowhere!
[Sulli getting upset for him.]
[What?
Giving Haroro the chance to kick?]
- Ha Ha!
[How is he...]
Ha Ha's getting the chance
at the penalty kick!
Don't give him the ball!
[It really does look as though he's
going to make the penalty kick.]
- Stop tormenting our Ha Ha!
Don't torment him!
[Just then, Jae Suk trades
Nam Tae Hee out!]
[It's Jae Suk.]
[What? Telling Jae Suk to kick the
penalty kick as soon as he comes in?]
I can't see anything!
[Even though he begged and told them that
he can't see without his glasses...]
Jae Suk is about to kick off the penalty kick!
Let's cheer him on!
[How can this be?]
As soon as he goes in the game...
Jae Suk...
You have to score the goal!
[Readying himself to kick the penalty kick
as soon as he comes into the game.]
A penalty kick as soon as
he's in the game!
[How will Yoo-ames Bond fare?]
[Torrential rain picks just that moment
to start pouring.]
[Especially not being able to see
without his glasses...]
[Will he be able to make the penalty kick?]
[Please...]
[Mightily kicking the ball!]
[A good kick...]
[Hits the goal post!]
It hit the goal post!
- What the heck!
- That was still great!
[A strong reaction even from
the players.]
But that was still a great kick.
Yoo Jae Suk getting ready to
kick off the penalty kick!
- It hit the goal post and bounced off.
- Yes, it's too bad.
- That was looking pretty good though.
- It was a nice kick. It's too bad.
[Such a close call!]
- This is so cool.
- Watching them playing in the rain is cool.
I'm getting goosebumps.
[The rain falling heavier by the minute...]
Nice!
[Yoo Hyuk running with
everything he has!]
[Ha Ha getting past one of the
opposing players!]
Ha Ha practiced that move
all night last night!
He learned that move from Jong Kook
and practiced it all night!
[Just then!]
Pass it off to Jae Suk!
There you go!
[A perfect pass of to Jae Suk!]
[Too bad...]
[That was good!]
[A brief moment of friendship
out on the field...]
[Haroro making a perfect pass
off to his friend, Jae Suk.]
What are you so happy about right now?
You two haven't done a thing.
- What are they happy about?
- Why are they high fiving each other?
What is...
what's that high five for?
Why are they high fiving each other
for making a pass?
[If a goal was made, then they would've
carried each other on their backs...]
[The game is still at 1-0.]
[Goal!]
[Suk Hyun Joon's awesome goal!]
[Celebrating his amazing goal.]
[Game over]
[Park Ji Sung's team wins with
the score of 2-0!]
Our Running Man Team took part in
this game and the game was won.
Our Running Man members didn't get
in their way and cost them the game.
[Unable to even think...]
[Sad at having missed the goal.]
[His members greeting him brightly and
chasing away his blues.]
Jae Suk.
- You should've scored that penalty kick.
- I couldn't see anything.
- I didn't know you took off your glasses.
- I thought I was going to die.
[Great job!]
- Great job!
[Exchanging greetings with other players
for a game well played and won.]
Yo, brother.
Minho.
Why didn't you kick the penalty kick?
[Just then, Evra gets up and...]
[And wipes off Jae Suk's glasses
off for him.]
Captain Park...
Thank you for everything today.
[Captain Park's final greeting
to the viewers.]
Thank you everyone for coming today,
and for all your hard work.
[The man who returned with
a huge new event in his life.]
[Breathtaking face-off with
his junior, Captain Gu.]
[A crackling match
with his best friend, Evra.]
[And even the field of dreams,
the Dream Cup.]
[The honor of having stood out
on the field with these men...]
[A bigger honor than anything else
they could've hoped for.]
[With that image fresh in our minds...]
[Number 7, Park Ji Sung-
You are our eternal captain.]
Subtitles by DramaFever
[A transfer student moves into
Running High School's junior class.]
Suzy!
[With the pretty new student and our
graduation ahead of us, we were so happy.]
This letter is written to
our future selves.
[And sent letters to our future selves in
a time traveling mailbox as a joke.]
[Then at the school reunion five year after,
we received those letters.]
[Fate- Life or a situation that was
predestined for you before your life started.]
There's a fateful couple that was destined
to be together unbeknownst to your knowledge.
[Mirror, mirror on the wall,
am I a part of the fated couple?]
I'm so scared!
We're the fated couple!
[The one who changes the fate,
and the one who controls the fate...]
[Anyone who looks behind them will die.]
[The nightmare that followed the
joke that they played five years ago.]
[Find the terrorizing truth that
links the past to the present.]
[The fateful tie that became a nightmare.]
[Next Week's Running Man-
You two are a fateful pair.]