[Spring 2013]
[Days full of joy and laughter.]
This is breaking news from SBS.
[But...]
[A dangerous strain of...]
[Rage virus was spreading
all over the world.]
Rage virus...
[The world fell into a fit of rage...]
[and the world lost its ability to laugh.]
[A world full of rage.]
[Laughter must be returned to humanity.]
[Virus]
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Three days after the rage virus outbreak.]
[Running Man members - All gathering
somewhere on the western shore.]
Hello.
This is pretty early in the morning.
[Full of curiosity over what's about
to happen so early in the morning.]
Once everyone arrives...
I will make a major announcement.
What major announcement?
[A major announcement to be made once
all the Running Man agents are gathered.]
[A major announcement?]
Okay, everyone...
[All Running Man members
are now present.]
Right now, the whole world...
has been exposed to
the outbreak of the rage virus.
[The rage virus outbreak has
spread all over the world!]
[Rage virus' surprise attack.]
Once infected with this rage virus
the person infected will lose
their ability to laugh forever.
- No wonder I felt so angry this morning.
- No!
This can't happen!
I don't want to hear it!
This could prove to be especially fatal
to people in the entertainment industry.
Of course.
But luckily, none of you are infected
by this virus yet.
But our staff members...
are already infected by the virus.
Is that why none of you
are smiling or laughing?
[Stoic]
Look at his expression.
He looks really scary right now.
- Did you just smile?
- I think I just saw him smile!
- I can see you smiling.
- I can see some of you smiling.
Look at the scary expression
on his face.
Is that why Gwon Yeol isn't smiling?
[VJ Gwon Yeol having lost his ability
to smile his trademark smile.]
That's pretty good acting.
Let's wait and see if you can
hold off smiling all day.
You're still not smiling?
[Remaining focused and
stoic through the opening.]
He refuses to break out into a smile.
[Everyone except for Running Man members
have lost their ability to laugh or smile.]
[A grand scale:
Bring the laughter back to humanity!]
That's why you're not seeing
anyone on the beach right now.
[As you can see for yourself,
the beach is devoid of any life.]
[A desolate beach scene.]
As you can see, there are seven cars
that are waiting out here.
Get into your own separate cars,
and get to your next destination on your own.
As for where you need to go,
you'll find the instructions in your car.
Please review the instructions
and get on the road.
- Don't run!
- Why are you running?
Why is he running like that?
[Rage virus...]
It's not that I'm afraid.
There are just three things in
this world that I'm scared of.
Bugs...
Zombies...
and my mom.
[I hope my mom hasn't been infected
by the rage virus!]
Hang on.
Running Man emergency disaster headquarters.
Must pass the agent test. What is this?
Go to the rest stop in Seocheon and pass
the agent test for emergency situations.
Okay, got it.
[On their way to pass the agent test.]
Rage virus?
The Earth devoid of laughter...
I will save it from its despair.
I will... find the laughter that's been lost
and return it back to humanity!
Rage virus?
I think this may be for real.
I think it really must be the rage virus.
I don't see anyone around.
It's almost nine in the morning,
and I don't see anyone around.
I keep...
I keep feeling surges of anger!
In a world that's already lacking in love,
and consideration for one another...
if we keep breaking each other down,
and hurting each other...
this isn't the world I want to live in.
[A world that's been filled with rage...]
[Will they be able to
bring the laughter back?]
Seocheon rest stop.
Do not get out of your vehicle.
What did you say?
You don't want us to get out?
You may risk getting
infected by the rage virus
so do not get out of your cars.
What the heck is he talking about?
Myuk PD is the one who's about to
make me break out into a fit of rage.
This area is now the rage virus zone.
So please hold your breath until you can
move to the safe green zone area.
[Move over to the safe green zone area
while holding their breaths.]
You may get out of the car now,
and hold your breath as you move.
- We have to get out?
- Everyone, move out!
This area is full of the rage virus strain!
[Doing whatever they can not to
get infected by the rage virus.]
- Move!
- Why?
[Thus, they escape into the safety
of the green zone area.]
What is this?
This is the green zone. The only
area left where you can still laugh.
- We can laugh now?
- I'm going to laugh as much as I want now!
You will now be tested to see how well you
can handle an emergency situation.
Since the rage virus strain has already
spread over this rest area...
- Really?
- Is that why no one is laughing?
If you get through the virus to buy food
from the gas station to bring back here
I will use the items of food you bring back
to judge if you're fit to become an agent.
[Emergency situation agent testing.]
[Survival skills test: Bypass the virus,
and secure the food items listed.]
We have prepared happy helium gas
that will help ward off the rage virus.
Inhale the happy helium gas, and bring back
the food you're assigned from the station.
But if your voice doesn't emit the sound
of the happy helium gas when you return
then you fail the mission.
- We have to do it very quickly then.
- Helium gas never really works for me.
- This is simple.
- That's way too easy.
- I have water.
- What is this?
- I have dried squid.
- I have to bring back miso soup?
Ddeok kalbi bibimbap.
[Survival skills test:
Buy the appropriate food - Start!]
Can we get started now?
[Rule: Must inhale the happy helium gas from
the green zone first before starting.]
You want us to inhale it now?
We're supposed to inhale this, right?
So this is what your voice sounds like
when you inhale the gas.
[The ability to make anyone happy is
the power of happy helium gas.]
Hurry, hurry!
Let's all hurry!
I'm full, I'm full.
Wait, I think I inhaled way too much.
[Overindulging in the happy helium gas.]
You have to shout out what you have
to buy before you get on your way!
- Ddeok kalbi bibimbap!
- Sweet potato sticks!
[Shouting out the items they need to
buy before getting on their way.]
Bottled water.
[Must hold their breath for as long as
possible to retain the helium gas.]
How much is this?
[Darn...]
Do I have to go back?
I need one Ddeok kalbi bibimbap, please.
- And I need a seafood tofu soup.
- A clam miso soup for me.
- You sound so funny.
- How much is it for the bibimbap?
Clam miso soup.
6,000 won?
[Infected with the rage virus?
A very stoic expression.]
[Agent Ro-Ro and Agent Gary on their
quest to buy ham toast and dried squid.]
Ham toast.
- How much is it?
- Dried squid. I need one dried squid.
How much is it?
Do you have sweet potato sticks?
How is the voice going to last all this way
after inhaling it just once?
I'm starting to feel the rage.
Toast.
- It's 1,500 won.
- Here.
- Did your voice last all the way there?
- This is ham toast.
[Voice tampering - Fail.]
Why?
Thank you.
- How are we supposed to...
- This is how you do it, Suk Jin.
You just keep visiting the
recharge stations like this one.
You have to go get the food first
before you can charge back up.
[Agent Jae Suk making his way
with abated breath.]
[An out of the blue grand bow?
Is it for the sake of laughter?]
- Why are you bowing down to us?
- I'm fine.
[Taking quite a while to
prepare the dish.]
[Ddok kalbi Bibimbap is finally ready.]
Thank you.
[Heading back to the green zone
with abated breath!]
I don't think I have what it takes
to become an agent.
This isn't going to work.
[Did Blank Ji make it?]
- She's won't make it.
- No. She took a big breath.
Ddok kalbi bibimbap.
I brought the water.
I said, I got the water.
[Obviously faking the voice.]
Suk Jin... that's
Detective Colombo's voice.
But I brought the water.
This is impossible!
[Returning at an unbelievable speed.]
- Dried squid!
- He didn't make it.
I got it!
- Dried squid. I got it!
- He didn't make it.
Seafood tofu soup.
[Will the Giraffe pull it off?]
- You have to tell him.
- We have to verify.
Seafood tofu soup.
[Fail]
My voice wasn't like that a second ago.
This is absolutely impossible.
[With his breath held tight...]
Seafood tofu soup.
You're disqualified.
Are you able to do this, Jong Kook?
It's impossible for me.
[Tiger with his mouth sealed shut
to prevent himself from breathing.]
[Tiger not even budging at the teasing.]
Ma'am...
Please cancel the clam miso soup.
[It's already done...]
Seafood tofu soup.
An order of seafood tofu soup.
An order of the
seafood tofu soup, please.
[Mute Agent Tiger receives his order.]
You're still not going to say anything?
[Looks as though he plans on remaining
silent until he reaches the green zone.]
[Even through the cheers
from nearby fans...]
[Just remain focus on task at hand
while greeting them with his eyes.]
[Did Agent Kkuk pull it off?]
Clam miso soup.
[Wow!]
[Success]
[Agent Kkuk is the first to pass the test!]
- How did you do it?
- How do you do it?
Agent Kim can proceed with his meal
now that he's passed his test.
Yes, I understand.
I will change out your food for something
that is a bit closer in distance.
[Exchanging out the food for the agents
left behind with their weak lungs.]
- What is this?
- Walnut cookie!
Fire grilled burger.
You can't breathe at all?
Let's just not breathe at all.
A chicken skewer!
[Blank Ji with her breath held is
on a mission to find her grilled burger.]
- Here you go.
- How much is it?
An order of popcorn, please.
Popcorn, please.
[Taking the opportunity to recharge
themselves after having bought their food.]
[Back to the green zone!]
You're done for, Kwang Soo.
You didn't pull it off.
Squid on the stick.
[The happy helium gas not very
compatible with the Giraffe.]
- So funny
- Squid on the stick.
[Did Blank Ji do it?]
Fire grilled burger!
[Success]
- I thought I was going to die!
- Come on, Ji Hyo!
[As always, Mr. Capable and Ace
are the first two to get the job done?]
- Did you run back here?
- I ran back as fast as I could.
- You are now in the second place.
- Here comes Suk Jin.
[Impala finally makes his way back.]
Here's your popcorn.
- Here's your popcorn.
- Wow!
[Success]
You are now in third place.
You may go take your seat.
[The ease of having succeeded
their mission already.]
[Only three of the four left remaining
will get to become agents.]
Sweet potato sticks.
[Success]
[This won't do!]
Where are you going?
Gary, where are you going?
[The happy gas is effective in
making them extremely happy.]
[With his breath held...]
Sausage on a stick.
[Success]
I guess it is possible.
- Kwang Soo...
- Yes?
- Chicken skewer.
- He did it.
[Success]
- You passed.
- Chicken skewer!
[Gary is the sixth one to succeed.
Then that means...]
Mr. Lee Kwang Soo, who didn't pass
the agent endurance test...
You weren't able to make it back
to the safety of the green zone
and therefore have been infected
by the rage virus.
[Infected by the rage virus!]
- Then Kwang Soo can't come with us?
- Don't come!
Already?
Now that you are an infected carrier...
What do you mean, infected carrier?
Why are you treating me like a disease?
Why am I already going to jail?
I'm ousted already?
[Oh no... showing signs of
the rage virus already...]
[Lee Kwang Soo a.k.a. Giraffe,
Infected by the rage virus.]
The rest of you fortunately passed
your agent test
and were able to make it back to
the safety of the green zone.
[Luckily survives in the green zone.]
- Tr...
- There's no 'Ai'.
Ai!
[Where is rage virus infected
Kwang Soo being taken off to?]
[Kwang Soo is no longer able to smile
now that he's been infected by the virus.]
I'm getting so angry!
I can't control this rage!
[The Giraffe is already full of rage.]
Where are you taking me?
Wait!
[Where is the rage virus infected
Giraffe being taken to?]
Once you're disqualified,
you become one of the infected.
The rest of you will now head off to
your next mission location.
Just like when you got
out of your car
you have to hold your breath on your way
back to your car until you're safely inside.
- Are you going to keep doing this to us?
- How can you say that with a straight face?
You guys are humanity's last hope
of finding back the lost laughter.
We have to do whatever we can to
bring the laughter back to humanity.
I will save the future of humanity.
- But why are blue ropes in the green zone?
- Just hurry up and leave.
- The ropes aren't green though.
- What does that matter?
His face is starting to look
more and more like a robot.
[Moments later]
Find the last remaining vial of the
laughter vaccine which is being kept at...
Find the last vial of the vaccine,
and save all of humanity.
There's only one?
[Laughter vaccine?]
[The last remaining vial of laughter vaccine
that could save the race of humanity!]
[Only facility to escape the infection-
National research center.]
[Will they be able to stop the rage virus
from its path of destruction?]
[Chungnam, Seocheon-
National biological research center.]
[The place that holds the last surviving
vial of the laughing vaccine...]
[that could save the human race
from the rage virus!]
[What? Who are all these people
in this facility?]
[Agent Kkuk is the first to infiltrate.]
From this moment on,
in order to save humanity
that has been infected by the
rage virus strains
you have to find the one last remaining
vial of the laughter vaccine.
[Find the last remaining vial
of the laughter vaccine!]
Inside this biological research center...
is the last remaining safety zone which
has not been infected by the virus strain.
But the enemy has found out that
this center holds the laughter vaccine
and they're trying to infiltrate the
center to get their hands on the vaccine.
[Avoid the scientists and the security
agents to find the laughter vaccine.]
The vaccine is believed to be in a vaccine
storage room somewhere within this facility.
In order to pass through
the entry of that room...
you need the I.D. badge
of one of the scientists.
You have to find one of the I.D. badges
as soon as possible to retrieve the vaccine.
[The person who finds the vaccine will be the
sole winner to save the fate of humanity!]
[Who will be the one to restore
laughter back to humanity?]
[Mission to reclaim laughter for mankind,
Start!]
Look at all this cacti... wow!
Where do I find the I.D.?
It's pretty hot in here.
This area is really hot.
Wow, it's scorching!
[Are those people... scientists?]
Excuse me.
- There it is.
- Intruder! It's an intruder!
I see security agents.
That one person had the I.D. on him.
It's an intruder!
[Big-nose is also discovered by
the security agents.]
[In order to get their hands on the ID card,
they must avoid being sighted by the agents!]
- Intruder!
[Humanity's last hopes are too busy being
chased around by the security agents.]
What?
I think we have to rip the name tags
off of the scientists' back.
- Their name tags?
- It's just a feeling that I have.
The reason being,
they all have a name tag on their backs.
I see what you're saying.
Instead of just taking it from them?
Get over here.
You keep exposing our location.
- So instead of just taking their ID cards...
- That's what I think.
And once we rip off the name tag,
with all these scientists around...
that's how I think we figure out which
of the scientists has the ID cards for us.
- That's just my guess, anyway.
- I think you're right.
There would be no other reason for the
scientists to have name tags on their backs.
- That's exactly what I was thinking too.
- What a joke!
Hey... our earth has lost all
its ability to laugh right now.
If I could crack a joke and
make someone laugh, that's great.
You just stole the words
right out of my mouth.
- Thanks for relaying my thoughts for me.
- You really are so shameless.
- What do you mean, shameless?
- How did you get to become so shameless?
I just said that you stole the
words right out of my mouth.
I was going to rip the name tag off of
one of their backs earlier.
No, you can't go through there now.
Come over here.
I said, come here!
[Now that they take a look...]
[All the scientists with the ID cards...]
[Have a name tag on their backs.]
Ha Ha! What is this?
What's going on here?
- What are you...
- You startled me!
- Did you rip off any name tags?
- What?
- I asked if you ripped off any name tags?
- I have to rip off their name tags?
We can get the ID's
if we rip off their name tags.
- Really?
- Rip off their name tags.
[Agent Ha Ha also thinks that ripping off
the scientists' name tags is the key.]
[Mr. Capable targeting
the scientists' name tags.]
Intruder!
Intruder alert!
[Surprise attack on the scientists!]
[Bingo! The scientist faints as soon as
the name tag is ripped off!]
[Agent Ha Ha gets his hand
on the scientist's ID badge!]
I should've asked you this
while you were still conscious.
But where's the science lab?
Huh?
Where is the vaccine being kept?
Can you hear me?
Please answer me.
Hey!
[Agent Jae Suk is also on the hunt
to get his hands on the ID badge.]
Here are some scientists.
- Scientist!
- Intruder alert!
I need your ID badge.
Thanks.
[Mr. Capable springs an ambush attack.]
[Mr. Capable immediately escapes after
getting his hands on the ID badge!]
Now I have to find where the
vaccine is being kept.
- Suk Jin!
- Ji Hyo...
I'm going to go crazy with
all these people chasing after me.
Where did Ha Ha go?
He was with me just until a moment ago.
What's over here?
I don't know what that is.
- I haven't been in there.
- Hey! Hey!
- What is it?
- It's the vaccine storage room.
[Vaccine storage room is discovered!]
Don't you think?
[Verification pad for the ID's.]
Have you seen this?
It's the vaccine storage room.
[All the members gathering around at the
news of the vaccine room being discovered.]
- Did you see this vaccine storage room?
- Is this it?
- You're right!
- This is the room.
Where is it?
- So if we bring the ID badges...
- You can get through if you have the ID.
I think you're right.
[You think someone will open the door
if you knock on it?]
[Everyone eyeing each other down
even though they all have their own ID's.]
I was just looking at
the vaccine storage room.
[Haroro waiting for everyone to
leave from his hiding spot.]
You're not just a fox,
but the sneakiest of all foxes.
- No, I'm not!
- What do you mean, you're not?
- Yes, you are.
You seriously think that blank expression
is going to work on me right now?
[Are they all gone?]
[There's no one around, right?]
[Just then, Jae Suk heads towards the
vaccine storage room with an ID of his own.]
[Wait... Jae Suk is...]
Wow, Suk Jin...
- I have one too!
- No, I have one!
[The emergency alarm starts going off!]
[After they all pretended not to
have an ID on them...]
[It seems as though they're not able to open
the door with the ID's they currently have.]
- How many ID's did we try?
- You all had one?
Pretending not to have one
when you did...
[The trickery Running Man members
are known for.]
[The emergency alarm sounds again!]
Intruder!
Intruder alert!
[With the alarm going off again,
the security guards rush in!]
Over there!
He went that way!
[Ultimately gets captured
by the security guards.]
Seriously, come on!
Aren't you supposed to give me your ID?
Give it to me. Hurry up and give it to me.
Come on.
- Give it to me quickly!
- Catch the intruder!
Let go of me!
[Just as he finally gets his hand on one...]
- Do I have to give this back?
- This is just too funny!
They're going to take this back?
This is mine.
[Forced outside of the building once
captured by the security agents.]
Gary...
[Members getting kicked out one by one.]
Why didn't they give me the badge right
away when I ripped off their name tag?
Huh?
You have to take it from them.
I have to take it from them?
How many people are they
going to kick out?
Kang Gary, you were hilarious.
All I could see was your face.
I can't believe they didn't
burst out laughing.
[No matter, they have now realized that the
ID pass to the storage room is elsewhere.]
If you scan a fake badge, it sounds the alarm
and those security agents' runs over.
- You think?
- And the real one will open the door.
What I think is...
I bet we have a guest today,
and the guest is hiding in there.
[Their imaginations are running amok.]
[The four members are looking for an open
entryway after having been kicked out.]
[Will they be able to save humanity
by the end of the day?]
[On the other hand...]
[Having escaped the situation earlier,
Haroro heads towards the storage room again.]
[Wait...]
The color is different.
Look, the color itself is different.
All the rest have a silver sticker on it,
but this one has a gold sticker on it.
[After a closer look, only one
has the gold 'R' sticker on it!]
[The door is opening!]
State the password.
[There's another door that needs
a secret password to get through?]
The one who controls time!
[Incorrect password]
Haroro is the best!
I want you to be the love of my life.
Intruder!
Intruder alert!
[The security devices sound off!
The security agents rush in again.]
Intruder!
[Haroro barely escapes their clutches.]
[The security pass for the first
entrance gate is now in his hands.]
I have to find the passcode now.
The passcode.
[The security code for the second doorway
is hidden somewhere in here...]
Intruder!
Yeah... I'm the intruder!
How are we going to find
the vaccine at this rate?
[Will they really be able to find
the vaccine at this rate?]
Let's go!
[Rage virus carrier Kwang Soo
being transferred to the facility.]
Let go!
Let me go!
[The effects of the virus?
Inexplicable fits of rage.]
You've been seriously infected.
Infected?
Infected, my butt!
Restrain him.
[Rage virus infection rate testing.]
[First phase - Dog weed tickle test.]
[As guessed, no fits of laughter.
Showing signs of rage.]
[Rage virus infection rate testing.]
[Second phase - Testing the response to
having air blown into his nostrils.]
[Chaos]
[Rage virus infection rate testing.]
[Third phase - Testing the response to having
the bottom of his foot tickled with a feather.]
[Laughter? Rage?]
So angry!
I'm so angry!
[On the brink of insanity from all the rage!]
I'm so angry I could die!
[Starting to get fed up from
being chased nonstop.]
Hey!
Did you find anything?
[Why does he look so busy?]
I don't think I can keep doing this.
[Is that you hiding?]
Three... four... five.
[Gary finding and gathering up as many
ID badges as he could get his hands on.]
If it's not one of these,
I'm going to give up on saving humanity.
Please!
[Rushing to test out his second badge
before the security agents rushes in.]
The door's opening!
[It opened!]
It opened!
State the passcode.
What's the passcode?
Running Man!
[Incorrect passcode]
Laughter brings good luck.
What is this?
Roll-Roll!
Where am I supposed to
get the passcode?
That's really cold.
Intruder!
I want to participate in the race.
I want to participate in the race!
I want to film the episode!
I want my face to be on TV!
[The more the infection sets in,
the more violent Giraffe becomes.]
Intruder Kim Jong Kook is now infected.
Quarantine measures to be taken.
What did he just say?
What does this mean?
What does...
[What is this sudden...]
Intruder Kim Jong Kook is now infected.
Quarantine measures to be taken.
[He's been... infected?]
[Mr. Capable...]
[is now infected by the rage virus!]
[Intruder Kim Jong Kook is now infected.
Quarantine measures to be taken.]
- Gary.
- Hey!
- It's a water gun.
- What?
- Where's the water gun?
[Water gun?]
[Ha Ha calls everyone over to him.]
- Jong Kook.
- What?
- What about Jong Kook?
- His back.
Something just got shot on his back.
- Really?
- Jong Kook?
[His back's been shot by something?]
[Evidence of water gun shooting
on Mr. Capable's name tag!]
He's been shot by something on his back.
- Really?
- Jong Kook did?
Hang on.
[The agents starting to become
suspicious of one another.]
I don't have anything.
Be careful.
Everyone needs to be careful.
- Everyone scatter about for now.
- What is it? Tell me what you know.
- Did you see it happen?
- No, I didn't see anything.
- Where did you see Jong Kook?
- I got a glimpse of his back.
Now that Jong Kook's been infected,
we're finished.
- Where did Jong Kook go?
- I think he's been taken off to jail.
[But...]
[This was just the beginning of
a bigger conspiracy.]
Ha Ha...
But how did you see the water gun?
I didn't see the water gun, but saw
the mark of it on Jong Kook's back.
You saw it on Jong Kook's back?
I saw some sort of watermark on
Jong Kook's name tag on his back.
[Watermark?]
Yoo-ames Bond?
Yoo-ames Bond.
[When it comes to water guns...]
[Yoo-ames Bond...]
[Yoo-ames Bond secretly ousted everyone
with his water gun a year ago.]
I didn't want to say this because I didn't
want any suspicions cast my way, but...
I won't suspect you.
Tell me what it is.
But it's Mid-April.
[Around the same time last year was
part two of Yoo-ames Bond story.]
Part two we had last year...
I recently watched that episode again
so that I don't get tricked again this year.
You really are one frightening woman.
You watched that again so that
you don't fall for it?
I watched it thinking that it's possible
for that to happen again.
But that was some time in Mid-April.
I don't remember the exact date,
but it was in April.
Remember how cold it was at night?
Let's just keep this in mind,
and get on our way.
[Could Yoo-ames Bond be the culprit?]
[Unauthorized ID pass.]
This one isn't it either.
I don't even have the energy
to run around anymore.
Why did Jong Kook get ousted?
I don't know, Jae Suk.
[Face to face... with Agent Blank.]
Jong Kook...
I wonder why he got ousted?
I heard he was shot with a water gun.
- Water gun?
- He was shot by a water gun.
Who told you that?
- Ji Hyo, it's not me.
- Wait, Yoo-ames Bond, wait.
- Is it time for part three?
- Ji Hyo...
- Wait! Don't come any closer!
- Okay, I'm not getting closer.
It's not me.
This is entrapment.
[Jae Suk vehemently denying that
he is the culprit.]
- How do I know you're not?
- It's not me!
- Ji Hyo! It's not me!
- There's a water gun being played.
I'm about to lose my mind.
- Ji Hyo, it's not that!
- There's a water gun!
- Ji Hyo...
- In the past three years of this show...
Water gun meant Yoo Jae Suk,
Yoo Jae Suk meant water gun!
That's why right now...
this is seriously so frustrating.
- I'm telling you, it's not me!
- Jae Suk...
Think about it this way.
You said being shot by the water gun
would infect that person, right?
If I really am being Yoo-ames Bond
like you say that I am
I wouldn't use the expression,
'infection'.
Why would I infect anyone?
Isn't that why?
I'm making sense, aren't I?
Even I can see that what I'm saying
makes perfect sense.
I'm really glad that I pointed that out.
Yoo-ames Bond wouldn't use the
expression, 'infection'.
- I'm a little unsure now.
- See!
See that?
If I'm the culprit, I wouldn't say, 'infect'.
I'd use the word, 'oust'.
But you never know!
I told you, it's not the case!
Yoo-ames Bond is not that
type of a person!
Do I really have to get into all this?
- Yoo-ames Bond isn't that type of a man!
- Then what kind of a man is he?
Yoo-ames Bond doesn't resort to taking
cheap shots like that.
I don't play like that.
I'm saying, Yoo-ames Bond
isn't your culprit.
- Yoo-ames Bond?
- Yoo-ames Bond.
- And water gun?
- I know Yoo-ames Bond means water gun.
But I'm saying that isn't the case this time.
I'm positive... that someone
else is working on the inside.
There's someone amongst us.
Using the water gun to frame
Yoo-ames Bond.
[A culprit to frame Yoo-ames Bond through
the usage of water gun?]
- I understand, Jae Suk.
- Understand?
[On the other hand...]
[Agent Ha searching around to find the code
for the second entrance to the vaccine room.]
[A string?]
There's something down here!
[An 'R' marked file attached at
the other end of the string!]
[What has six faces with 21 eyes?
The answer to the riddle is the passcode.]
This reminds me of the clue
that we had to find in Macau.
[That's how he found one of the hints
at the Macau Tower as well.]
I think it's time for me to
put on my thinking cap.
I feel like I'm going to lose my mind.
What's the point of finding this
when I can't figure out the answer?
Patient Lee Kwang Soo.
I've got the results to your test.
It's more serious than we thought.
You're past the point of any treatments.
[Bolts right out of his bed.]
For now...
Weren't you going to treat me
so that I could get better?
We can't treat you.
Don't try to escape,
and just stay right here.
There's nothing we can do for you.
Let me go!
I'm perfectly fine!
I'm normal!
This is absurd.
This is just absurd.
I'm going to escape out of here.
I'm going to escape.
[Carrier Giraffe attempting to escape
out of the infirmary.]
I have to get out...
I have to get out of here.
[I'm out of here!]
[Giraffe on the loose!]
[Giraffe's desperate escape.]
Kwang Soo!
What are you doing here?
- I escaped.
- What are you doing?
What are you doing around here?
Tell me what you're up to right now.
- What are you?
- I keep feeling so angry.
- Why are you getting angry?
- I just escaped out of there.
- They're coming!
- Tell me what you're doing?
- I escaped.
- What are you doing?
- I escaped from their clutches.
- Hey, Lee Kwang Soo!
[Agent Jae Suk also discovers the Giraffe.]
Please... save me!
- Jae Suk, I escaped from them.
- What are you doing?
Please make me laugh.
I just feel...
I just feel so angry!
[Enraged Giraffe's urge to
attack is activated!]
- Why are you out here?
- What?
Why are you out here?
Why are you asking me that?
Aren't you even glad to see me?
I thought you were taken away.
I broke out of there.
Intruder!
Catch them!
[Escaping from the situation first!]
- Hey...
- Huh?
[Even Ha Ha seems surprised to see
the Giraffe out and about.]
- How are you out here?
- I escaped from them.
- Why are you here?
- I broke out of jail.
Go back in there.
You can't break out of jail.
[No interest whatsoever in
seeing the Giraffe out of jail.]
What the heck is this?
I don't even know what I'm doing today.
Then just get back to jail
and stay there.
- We'll make sure to make today fun.
- I worked hard to break out of there.
- You're a carrier of the virus, aren't you?
- Yes.
What's going on?
Why are you being like this?
[Special characteristics of a carrier
that he momentarily forgot about.]
- What are you doing?
- You're not sure yourself, are you?
No, I don't know.
- I just keep feeling angry.
- Where did you just come from?
You're smiling.
You're smiling right now.
Where were you?
Kwang Soo, where were you all this time?
In the examination room.
- They kept poking and testing me...
- Who was examining you?
- Nurse Go Dong Wan.
- What did you say?
Look, he's smiling again.
[Instant fit of rage.]
What the heck is all this?
- Are you good at solving riddles?
- Yeah.
What is it?
[Trying to borrow their thinking caps
in order to solve the riddle for the code.]
Let go of me.
Let's just share the information.
- What did you find?
- Tell me what you found.
[Riddle - What has six faces and 21 eyes?]
- What has six faces and 21 eyes?
- What?
We have to keep this
between ourselves.
[At the same time]
[Unauthorized ID]
Seriously... are any of these even real?
These are all just a bunch of fake ones!
Who are you going to catch?
Who do you think you're going to catch?
Who do you think you're going to get?
[Where did his sudden surge of
self-confidence come from?]
This is my third year of doing Running Man!
[Oh... he's pretty fast!]
- Kwang Soo!
- Ji Hyo!
Come here! There are
agents back there! This way!
[Avoiding getting caught by
the scientists and the security agents.]
- Kwang Soo...
- What is this? Is this for sterilizing?
- We're looking for the vaccine.
- What's going on?
I...
- I feel so angry right now.
- Why?
[Fits of rage bubbling up constantly
without any prior notice.]
What's wrong with you?
I don't think I should stay with him.
You startled me!
[Erupting in rage at the staff member
put in charge of the CO2 tank.]
[That must be the rage virus...]
Okay, why don't you just stay here
and keep getting angry?
What is today about?
What are you guys doing today?
I think it's something to do
with water guns.
All I heard was that a water gun
is somehow involved.
- Water gun means Jae Suk.
- Right?
Don't you think finding the person with
the water gun would mean we could win?
Then we'd have to rip off
everyone's name tags.
Let's do it.
Let's rip off everyone's name tags.
[Sorry]
[Jae Suk on the other hand is searching
for the clue to the second passcode.]
Nothing in here.
[The 'R' folder containing the hint!]
Seriously...
What the heck is this now?
[What is the missing letter in this sequence?
O, T, T, F, (_), S, S, E, N, T.]
This is driving me nuts.
O, T, T, F...
[Hint for the correct passcode.
What is the alphabet in this sequence?]
[Another person trying to find
an answer to the mysterious puzzle.]
[Six faces with 21 eyes?]
Paper-rock-scissors?
No, that can't be.
Six faces...
Dice!
One, two, three, four, five, six sides.
There are six faces, and a total
of 21 dots if you count them all.
[Dice with six sides and
a total of 21 dots counting from 1-6!]
[Agent Ha convinced that 'Dice'
is the correct answer to the riddle.]
What has six faces and 21 eyes?
Dice!
[Finally succeeds in infiltrating
the vaccine storage room!]
[Carrier Giraffe never even having seen
what an ID badge looks like all day.]
I need to rip off the name tag
of at least one scientist.
My illness... is something I myself...
[Why not find your way back in first?]
Intruder Ji Suk Jin has been infected.
Quarantine measures to be taken.
[This time... it's Suk Jin?]
What does this mean?
Someone else has been ousted?
But how is that possible?
How do you oust someone?
What's going on?
How can this happen?
Intruder Ji Suk Jin has been infected.
Quarantine measures to be taken.
I'm a carrier?
Intruder Ji Suk Jin has been infected.
Quarantine measures to be taken.
Where are you taking me?
[The culprit behind all these events is...]
Gary...
I think...
What happens to ousted members?
And what is going on around here?
You know what the real big problem is?
[Carrier Giraffe having donned a clean room
garment in fear for his life?]
Why are you pant legs all ripped?
What is today about?
[Still unaware of what's going on today.]
Why isn't Jae Suk here?
- Why do you think he's missing?
- Jong Kook and Suk Jin are out, right?
What the heck is that noise?
[A mysterious bird sound that can be heard
all over the biological research facility.]
[We heard it once before
a little while ago...]
- Isn't it a bird sound?
- Bird?
[There's no way this is happening
for no reason...]
[What is the meaning of the bird noise?]
- Kwang Soo!
- Yes, Ha Ha?
[The agents trying to figure out the
meaning of the sudden bird noises.]
- Maybe it's a signal alerting the time.
- That's what I think too.
- When the bird sounds...
- Do you know this?
- Who's the worst enemy to bugs?
- Birds.
Grasshopper... that's a bug.
[Therefore, it's an enemy sign
to the Grasshopper?]
The sound means that it's getting close for
Jae Suk to accomplish some kind of a mission.
[A warning sign of some sort for Jae Suk?]
- Then Jae Suk...
- The culprit...
is Jae Suk.
I knew it.
The one who took away your livelihood,
and your laughter...
Why is Jae Suk doing this to me?
Why did he steal away my laughter?
Why do you think that is?
I can't believe this.
I have to stop him.
I have to make Jae Suk wake up and
realize what he did to me!
The only person who can stop this...
there is only one person.
And that's me.
You have to help me.
Get yourself together.
We have to do this!
But why would Jae Suk do this?
[What is Jae Suk's real purpose?]
It's hot in here again.
It's really hot in here.
It's a desert in here.
Gary...
- Hey.
- Jae Suk, did you find anything?
- I haven't found anything.
- I'm being serious.
- I am serious.
- I have no idea what's going on.
- I've just been wandering around like this.
- Have you been in the room yet?
- Where?
- The vaccine room.
- I have been in there.
- I've been in the room too.
- You had to know the passcode, right?
- Yes.
I don't know what the passcode is.
- Why did Jong Kook get ousted?
- I don't know.
- It's the water gun.
- Really?
Who shot him?
When it comes to water guns, it's you.
- You're always with the water guns.
- It's not me.
You know that shooting with the water gun
means the person is infected.
It's not me.
It's eliminating the person anyway.
Yoo-ames Bond is not a bad person like that.
He just ousts people with the water gun.
Either way, it's not me.
Hey... it's not me.
- Gary, it's not me.
- Something not right.
It really isn't me.
[Giraffe wanting to be able to laugh again
goes out in search for the vaccine.]
[Gains an ID badge.]
[Solely focused on gaining the ID's.]
Thank you.
[The rage virus is
bubbling under the surface.]
Oh my goodness!
[Gathering up all the ID's one by one.]
[Heading towards the storage room in
search of a way to save himself.]
[Coming face to face with Agent Jae Suk
in front of the vaccine storage room.]
Jae Suk, I've found three
of these badges.
Kwang Soo...
What is it?
Did you find something?
Having that...
isn't going to get you anywhere.
[Jae Suk...]
[You... are behind this, aren't you?]
- What the heck is this?
- The sequence...
[Clueless as to what the passcode is.]
Don't you feel angry at all, Kwang Soo?
He keeps doing this to me.
- Why would he get mad?
- Whenever I try to do anything...
Why would he be feeling
angry right now?
For the past eight hours,
he's been doing this to me all day.
[Making the infected carrier keep bursting
out in anger as symptoms indicates him to.]
Whenever I take a break from getting
angry, and try to get something done...
[Constantly showing fits of anger
whenever he was prompted to do.]
- It's annoying!
- Let's try to solve this.
- Should we try to solve it?
- Yeah, solve it.
[Jae Suk telling Kwang Soo he should
try using his ID's for verification.]
- I'll try out my ID's right now.
- Okay.
But that's...
- I'll check to see if this works first.
- Try it.
Try it and see if yours works.
Go ahead and see if it works.
[Something feels off...
I can't let my guard down.]
That one didn't work.
- Yours doesn't work?
- The second one didn't work either.
- How many do you have?
- Three.
I'm really serious about this right now.
- Why have you gotten so strong lately?
- You should be careful too.
[What?]
[Water gun!]
[That is without a doubt, a water gun!]
[He shoots Kwang Soo's name tag
with the water gun!]
[What in the world!]
You should've at least been a little
more covert about it.
How could you do this again?
[Exploding in a real fit of rage!]
[Is it really... Yoo-ames Bond?]
[The clear green water gun mark left on
these ousted members' name tags...]
[Does it mean that they were all a result
of Yoo-ames Bond's actions?]
[Infected carrier Giraffe being
taken away.]
Kwang Soo!
What is it?
What's going on?
[Automatically bursting out in rage
without being prompted by anyone.]
[Everyone's just standing by watching this
scene with a shocked expression.]
You should've made it less obvious
than this water gun.
This is just total entrapment.
[Entrapment?]
Who is it?
Who could it be?
This is really getting more and more...
I really don't know what's
going on now.
[Is he searching for someone?]
[What is going on?]
[What does any of this mean?]
[Two hours ago]
[Jae Suk having arrived at the facility in
search of the laughter vaccine with others.]
Only the person who finds the
laughter vaccine will be the sole winner.
I have no idea what you're
talking about.
Go Dong Wan!
[The place Nurse Go Dong Wan
leads him to is...]
[A secret door inside the closet?]
[The same door through which Bond received
his secret mission during parts one and two!]
[As guessed, a secret door!]
Yoo-ames Bond, Yoo Jae Suk.
You are about to get framed.
- You're about to be framed.
- Why am I getting framed?
Someone on the outside...
is shooting people with a water gun
to mark them with green fluid...
to infect the members with the virus.
That's the tip we've just received.
[Yoo-ames Bond, find out who's
framing you!]
[Yoo-ames Bond's trademark,
water guns are on display!]
Use these water guns...
to shoot the name tag of the real culprit
who's trying to frame you.
By which you'll infect the culprit,
and oust that person.
I'm going be had without
any choice on my part.
But if you get shot by the real culprit
instead of shooting the culprit yourself...
or your gold bracelet gets stolen,
you'll be ousted so be careful.
[If shot by the real culprit's gun or
the gold bracelet is stolen, he's ousted!]
Find out who the real culprit is,
and oust that person.
Then retrieve the last surviving
laughter vaccine to save humanity.
I encourage you to become
the ultimate winner and savior.
- What are you saying?
- This is your mission.
I don't think it's going to be
easy this time.
[An uneasy feeling that this mission
won't be so simple.]
- The real culprit is executing the mission.
- I know.
The real culprit is using green fluid.
The person is out there trying to
frame you for their crimes.
Where are you taking me?
What's going on?
Intruder Kim Jong Kook is infected.
Quarantine measures to be taken.
What does that mean?
Just who's going around doing this?
Who is the culprit?
I'm infected now?
[Comrades having taken the fall
without even knowing what's going on.]
Intruder Ji Suk Jin is infected.
Quarantine measures to be taken.
[The culprit... just who are you?]
[Yoo-ames Bond... he's been
searching for the real culprit!]
[Thinking that Kwang Soo could be the culprit
since he's already an infected carrier.]
[That's why he was shot down
without even any hesitation.]
[But he wasn't the real culprit
who stole the laughter vaccine away.]
[Sorry... I'll make sure
to catch the real culprit.]
It's someone on the inside.
It's one of us.
[The real culprit...
is one of these members.]
[The culprit who infected my comrades,
and took laughter away from humanity...]
I will get you!
[Framed Yoo-ames Bond vs. Real culprit.
The real battle starts now!]
[What is the next letter in this sequence?]
[Did he figure out the answer?]
One, two, three, four...
You know this, don't you?
You knew this, didn't you?
[Rushing over to the
vaccine storage room.]
This is the answer to the passcode clue.
F.
[The answer if 'F' for five.]
[Finally entering the inner room
where the vaccine is kept.]
This is seriously too much.
This is too hard.
What the heck?
[It's empty?]
The culprit already took it.
[The laughter vaccine, the culprit
seems to have taken it already.]
What I think is...
I don't suspect you.
I think it's Jae Suk.
[Yoo-ames Bond picks the perfect
time to make his appearance.]
Jae Suk, how far have you gone?
What do you mean, how far have I gone?
Are you suspecting me right now?
The glint in your eye tells me that
you guys suspect me right now.
We are suspicious of you.
To be honest...
Is it okay for me to search you?
- Go ahead.
- Okay.
Put your hands on your head.
I find this really offensive.
I can't do anything about it.
[He's going to get framed even more once
Ha Ha discovers his water gun.]
Prove to us that it's not you.
- What are you doing?
- That's not it?
- You scared me!
- Does he have something?
[Starting to become more and more
wary and suspicious of one another.]
- Can I search you too?
- Yes. But I'll go first.
Let me search you first.
- I'll do it first.
- No, I'll search you first.
- No.
- After hearing what Ji Hyo said...
Don't even think about using that
to oust me right now.
[Haroro aggressively targeting Jae Suk.]
- I can't believe all this distrust.
- Hang on a second.
[Yoo-ames Bond starting to get
backed up into a corner.]
- Do you really have to be like this?
- Yes. Let me see your belt.
[How will Yoo-ames Bond get himself
out of this danger?]
- Turn around.
- I can't do that.
It's back there, isn't it?
Is it in his waistband?
[It's possible that the real culprit
could be Ha Ha or Ji Hyo...]
- It's not me.
- And actually...
Jae Suk recently washed his hands.
I can smell the soap on his hands.
No, that's just because I've been
touching everything and they're dirty.
He recently washed his hands.
You know why?
It's because he had watercolor
on his hands. Why?
[Haroro takes the chance and
corners Jae Suk even further!]
How does it feel to be taken down
by Ha-lock Holmes?
Hey, look at him!
He's reaching back for something!
His hand's reaching for something!
You brats!
- Wait! Wait!
- I told you that it's not me!
[Escapes danger by threatening them.]
This is driving me crazy.
This is a big problem.
What do I do?
This is getting more and more
complicated.
Is it Jae Suk?
Are you sure?
I think it is.
I think it's him.
[He's about to get ousted by his comrades,
let alone catch the real culprit!]
I just helped frame myself even further.
Who is the real culprit?
[Just who is the real culprit that's
pushed Yoo-ames Bond into the corner?]
Ha Ha... it's Ha Ha!
It's Ha Ha.
It's...
The culprit is one of those three.
[The real culprit is either,
Gary, Ha Ha or Ji Hyo!]
[There's only one chance!
Must figure out who the real culprit is!]
It's Ha Ha.
I'm sure it's Ha Ha.
Ha Ha...
He tried to corner me
too aggressively earlier.
Ha Ha was the only one who saw
everyone getting ousted.
Gary!
Water gun.
It's the water gun!
[The only witness to comrades
getting infected was Ha Ha!]
Jong Kook...
Suk Jin...
Ha Ha saw them both.
No one else saw them getting infected.
[Is Ha Ha the real culprit as
Yoo-ames Bond is guessing it to be?]
You're coming to get me, aren't you?
- What?
- You're coming to get me.
- No, I'm not.
- Seeing the two of you together...
[Gary and Ha Ha approaching
Agent Blank.]
I think we need to start
trusting each other.
Let's show each other our ankles.
Okay, don't come any closer.
I'll show you my ankles.
- My ankles?
- They're so slim.
- Show us your shoes.
- You're not going to jump me, right?
No, I won't. Then let's all
sit down and do it together.
- You sit down too.
- Okay.
- What are we doing?
- Sit down and show us.
- We don't trust each other right now.
- It's not me.
It's not me either.
I'll be the judge since it's not me.
What are you saying?
I'm telling you, it's not me.
I'm serious!
Fine, let's do it.
I'll do whatever you want.
What do you want me to do?
[Why is Ha Ha getting so upset?]
Why are you getting upset?
- You're acting strange.
- Okay, then search me.
Guys... if we can't find the vaccine...
humanity is going to lose
their ability to laugh forever!
Do you want to lose your livelihood?
The Monday Couple will be no more!
Haroro will disappear, and
Running Man itself is going to disappear!
- I think you're acting suspicious.
- Okay, let's go.
[Jae Suk witnessing this whole scene.]
Gary, it's not me.
It really isn't me!
- Jae Suk!
- The real culprit is amongst you guys!
- What are you talking about?
- The real culprit is in your group.
One of you three stole the vaccine
and is infecting everyone.
- Infect? It really isn't me.
- Jae Suk...
[Just which one of these three
is the real culprit?]
Be careful.
You have to watch out for Ha Ha.
- Don't believe him.
- You have to listen to me.
- I swear it's not me.
- Show us your arms.
[Requesting Yoo-ames Bond to show
his wrist to confirm devoid of any bands.]
I'm being honest.
I'm serious, it's not me.
[Luckily the band is inside his pant leg!]
Jae Suk, why did you kill Kwang Soo?
Why did you kill Kwang Soo?
- I had no choice but to eliminate him.
- How did you kill him?
- I killed Kwang Soo with a water gun.
- How did you kill him with a water gun?
But I didn't say that I killed Kwang Soo
by infecting him, did I?
What did the announcement
say about Kwang Soo?
- There was no announcement made.
- Right?
See? He wasn't infected.
But why do you have a water gun?
- And why don't any of us have a water gun?
- One of you three...
I don't know which one of you,
but I have to oust one of you.
That's my mission.
- You're lying!
- Intruder alert!
- Gary...
- Jae Suk.
What's going on?
I want you to be honest with me.
I...
I've been watching what's going on.
I think Ha Ha is the culprit.
- He's acting very suspicious.
- I'm suspicious of him too.
[Gary is also feeling suspicious of Ha Ha.]
Ha Ha wouldn't show us.
After hearing what's going on,
I think you're acting a little suspicious.
[Ji Hyo is also starting to get
suspicious of Ha Ha.]
- You saw everyone getting ousted.
- Yeah.
I wasn't the only one who saw it.
- Then who else saw it?
- We saw it together.
- With whom?
- Gary.
Gary didn't see both.
He only saw one getting ousted.
I saw one by myself.
What I...
What I was surprised by was...
after thinking about it carefully
HaHa is the only one
who saw everyone getting ousted.
- You're right.
- Except Kwang Soo, because I ousted him.
[Is Ha Ha, the only witness to everyone
getting ousted by the real culprit?]
- Really?
- He showed me Suk Jin getting dragged away.
It's Ha Ha.
Jae Suk... is your water gun the only
way of eliminating Ha Ha?
[Yoo-ames Bond's water gun is the only means
of getting rid of the culprit, Ha Ha!]
[But if Jae Suk's guess is correct,
then Ha Ha also has a water gun!]
You're acting suspicious too.
You can't be this clueless, can you?
You're Song Ji Hyo!
Why? I'm not allowed to
remain clueless?
You're the Ace!
Don't you think it's too weird?
What is?
Let's not get swept away by
what Jae Suk is saying.
I feel a little unsure.
- I'm uncertain right now.
- Really? Then let's go our own ways.
I'll do it my way,
so you do things your own way.
Okay then.
- Okay.
Bird sounds...
What does the bird sound mean?
[When Blank Ji, Gary, Ha Ha and
Kwang Soo were all together...]
[And even when Blank Ji and the Giraffe
were together, the bird sound was heard.]
Whenever Ji Hyo and I are together,
the bird sound goes off.
- Okay.
Jae Suk... Jae Suk!
Find him and bring him to me!
[Gary to lure Ha Ha over to Jae Suk,
for Jae Suk to eliminate with his water gun!]
I'm a carrier...
and whenever a carrier and Ji Hyo are
together, the bird sound goes off.
[That means...]
[Green watermark on Ha Ha's name tag!]
Intruder Ha Ha is infected!
Quarantine measures to be taken!
Intruder HaHa is infected!
[What?]
Why?
No!
I'm the star of the show today!
This can't happen!
I'm too close!
Wait... wait!
It was Song Ji Hyo.
Song Ji Hyo...
I was with Song Ji Hyo last,
and she got me.
[The woman no one ever suspected...]
Rip off the name tag and
let me see it.
[Five hours ago]
What's that sound?
[A mysterious USB in Blank Ji's car.]
Miss Song Ji Hyo?
The International Angry Group has
a special and important mission for you.
We can't stand to watch the world
be so happy anymore.
Steal the laughter vaccine
and hand it over to us.
The one and only vaccine left in this world
is kept in the vaccine storage room.
Use the pass key and the lock key
that are included in the case provided
which will aide you in your attempt to
steal the vaccine for us.
Laughter vaccine.
[The pink fluid is the laughter vaccine.]
And the green fluid is the rage virus.
[The green fluid is the rage virus.]
In order to ensure that you can safely
get the laughter vaccine to us
infect all the members with the rage virus
provided and have them quarantined.
If you use the water gun to shoot the
virus strain on the opponent's name tag
you will succeed in infecting them.
[Spray the name tag with the virus,
and the person will be infected!]
[Mr. Capable and Big-nose getting infected...
were both works of Blank Ji!]
- I didn't do anything!
- You did something, didn't you?
All I was doing was following behind you.
- Really?
- Really. I didn't do anything.
[I'm sorry, Suk Jin.]
But one thing to remember.
Who is the one person you think of
when green fluid is mentioned?
That's none other than
Yoo-ames Bond!
If you frame Yoo Jae Suk,
it'll be easier for you to infect others.
- It's not me.
- But Jae Suk, you're Yoo-ames Bond...
- Is it time for part three?
- Ji Hyo...
- Yoo-ames Bond is not that kind of a man!
- What kind of a man is he?
Yoo-ames Bond doesn't resort to infecting
people with his water gun like that!
He doesn't resort to
filthy tricks like that!
I wasn't going to say this because
I didn't want anyone to suspect me...
[Certainly an actress! With tight acting,
works to frame Jae Suk for her actions!]
[Ha Ha fell for it hook, line, and sinker.]
You really are one scary woman.
That was sometime last April.
If you either refuse this mission,
or fail to carry it out...
you will immediately be infected
by the rage virus.
So make sure to find the vaccine,
and hand it over to us.
[This is how Blank Ji had no choice
but to accept her mission.]
Jae Suk...
I'm sorry for what's about to
happen today.
I think you're going to have to
take the fall for me today.
Let's do this.
[And as soon as Ha Ha started suspecting
her, she infects him immediately!]
[I'm the real culprit of the day!]
Intruder Ha Ha is infected!
Quarantine measures to be taken!
[That means... Ha Ha isn't the culprit?]
[Then that means?]
[Gary - Out!]
Wait!
I knew this was going to happen!
Song Ji Hyo and Gary.
It's Song Ji Hyo and Gary.
[Having ousted Gary from having thought
of the Monday Couple to be the culprits!]
[Jae Suk having been brought down by the
Monday Couple during the zombie episode.]
Those two... framing me like that...
They almost had me fooled!
[But all these events were
the work of Ji Hyo alone!]
[Real culprit Ji Hyo,
casually taking a look around.]
I need to find Yoo Jae Suk.
[Spots Yoo-ames Bond!]
Come in.
Come in here.
[A real final battle with each of them
with a water gun of their own.]
[She's here...]
[The distance is starting to close in...]
[Ji Hyo, stepping out...]
[Now!]
[Yoo-ames Bond shoots first!]
[Has Ji Hyo's name tag been marked?]
[Bulls-eye]
- Why?
- Check her name tag.
[Finally... the real culprit,
Song Ji Hyo is ousted!]
Song Ji Hyo, Kang Gary,
do you think I'm dumb?
Huh?
- Song Ji Hyo, Kang Gary!
- Kang Gary isn't a part of it!
- What did you say?
- It was me by myself!
Hey, I thought it was Ha Ha
in the beginning.
But after thinking about it...
When we did the zombie special,
it was you and Kang Gary!
- I seriously...
- There's the vaccine.
[Yoo-ames Bond gets the
laughter vaccine in his possession!]
Seriously... Kang Gary isn't in on this.
He doesn't know anything.
He really doesn't know?
He wasn't in on it?
You think you can just take the cake
after I put in all the work?
Seriously...
Really? It was just you?
Then Ha Ha and Gary weren't anything?
I feel really bad towards Gary now.
[Yoo-ames Bond succeeds in finding the
laughter back for all of mankind.]
I'm grateful to be able to return
laughter back to mankind.
Even though I didn't really know
what I was doing...
I just happened to come across it...
But I somehow did it.
What's that?
Why are you giving that to me?
[Yoo-ames Bond... Never Die.]
[And thus...]
[With Yoo-ames Bond's unintentional
accomplishment...]
[Humanity was able to rid
themselves of their rage...]
[and find their way back to laughter.]
[And Running Man members got to
keep their jobs.]
Subtitles by DramaFever
[In the peaceful prairie...]
[lived one not so bright giraffe.]
[A place where all the animals
live in harmony with one another!]
[Running Animal Kingdom.]
[From the beasts of prey...
to the herbivores...]
[A peaceful animal kingdom.]
[A wild and bloody battle to determine who
will be the king of beasts will soon start.]
[The tiger being the king of beasts
is a saying of the past...]
[Any of these animals can become
the new king of beasts!]
[A fierce battle between the food chains
to determine who will take the throne!]
[Next week on Running Man-
King of Beasts.]