[Sweet]
[Frightening]
[To become the top couple
in the kingdom of Running Land...]
[The three princesses must train the fools.]
[Foolish idiots and the peaceful princess,
the fairytale...]
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Park Min Ha of Giraffe classroom
at Running Kindergarten.]
[The story Min Ha chose today is...
'Foolish idiot and the peaceful princess.']
Once upon a time, in the Running Kingdom,
lived six foolish idiots.
You guys are... foolish idiots.
[What?]
See? This is why I said it's not good for me
to stand next to you during the opening.
I'm immediately subjugated as a foolish idiot
because I'm standing next to Kwang Soo.
- Why are you saying it's because of me?
- I'm made to be an idiot because of you!
- You really think this is because of me?
- I'm even wearing green because of you!
When you ask an idiot to be an idiot,
it can be very insulting.
You're not supposed to tell
an ugly person that he's ugly.
- But being idiots doesn't really suit us.
- That's what I'm saying.
Being an idiot really doesn't suit me.
Everyone in the kingdom made fun
of them and teased them for being idiots.
[Jumping right into their
foolish idiotic behavior.]
[Getting immersed in their idiot role play
as if they've been waiting for this moment.]
[Hey... this is fun!]
I can't see anything.
- Do you know how to do this?
- I can't see the persimmon in front of me.
Is this better?
Kwang Soo...
Make sure that you hide it very well
so that even your hair strand doesn't...
[Idiots...]
Mommy!
[Everyone's immersed in
their foolish idiot act.]
You look so funny right now.
[What are you doing?]
[They're doing so well...]
Everyone in the kingdom...
called them idiots...
Idiots...
They all called them idiots.
[On the other hand...]
[Running Kingdom's front court garden]
[King Go Dong Wan of Running Kingdom had
three daughters who were all of marrying age.]
I, King Go Dong...
It has been 15 years since
I've started ruling this land...
But I have not raised my
daughters right.
One day, King Go Dong called his
three daughters to him and told them this...
My eldest daughter...
[Eldest daughter - Plump Princess?
Princess Sa Yeon.]
Plump Princess...
Yes?
Why do you eat so much?
This country's treasury is
hitting rock bottom because of you.
What are you going to do about it?
My second daughter...
Blank Princess.
[Second daughter,
Blank Princess, Blank Ji.]
Your blank expressions...
are known all around the country, and
I'm so ashamed I can't even lift up my face.
My third and youngest daughter...
Peaceful Princess.
[Third daughter, Peaceful Princess.]
My youngest daughter...
the Peaceful Princess.
[Peaceful Princess, Uee.]
Your beauty is your sin.
You take after me.
For your own sakes...
I've taken drastic measures.
Do you remember what I told you girls
whenever you upset me while you were little?
That I would...
marry you off to foolish idiots.
[Married off to idiots?]
Sa Yeon, say something!
What did he just say?
[Maybe even her ears have
gained weight...]
It's because you eat too much!
- And I'm just too pretty.
- What were you again?
- I'm just blank...
- Because you're always spaced out?
Snap out of it and
get yourself together.
- What about you?
- Because I'm pretty...
- Because you're pretty?
- Yes.
There she goes pissing me off again.
Pretty ones are the problem!
Be quiet!
I'm taking drastic measures...
and marrying you off to idiotic fools.
[Find yourself your own foolish idiots,
and marry them!]
Father... please consider it again!
Father, please!
I'll stop eating so much!
- There it is!
- Where?
[Having to marry these idiots...]
[Look at them...]
[There's no way!]
[Dad... anything but that!]
- Father! Not that!
- Father... please, no!
I'll stop eating altogether from now on!
- Father!
- Be quiet!
Find yourselves your own foolish idiots...
and train them to become the
ultimate generals of Running Kingdom.
Then I will forgive you.
- Father!
- Father...
[Resolute King Go Dong]
- What do we do?
- It's because you always eat too much!
Then what else am I supposed to do
when I never feel full?
The biggest joy I have in my life
is to eat all the food I want!
[The three getting angry and
pushing the blame on each other.]
- Your problem is that you're too pretty!
- It's because I'm nothing like dad.
What do we do?
We're ruined!
[And thus...
King Go Dong's three daughters...]
[were kicked out of the palace
to search for their own foolish idiots.]
Sa Yeon!
[Plump Princess barreling down the path.]
[With lightening fast speed...]
[She led the way to find herself
her own foolish idiot.]
Wait for us!
- Sa Yeon, wait for us!
- Sa Yeon!
Wait for us!
Sa Yeon, wait for us!
[Heading towards the woods where
the idiots are rumored to live...]
[The fools are deeply immersed in
playing their roles as the village idiots.]
Jae Suk... what are you doing?
- Why are you acting like this?
- Good boy... good boy.
What do you mean, good boy?
Do you think I'm your dog or something?
-Six times two?
- 50,040.
Four times two?
Three trillion.
[About to burst out in laughter.]
Seven times one?
Sign of the boar.
[Surprise attack!]
[Idiot Giraffe falls for the trick.]
I'm not doing anything
and just standing here.
- Seriously...
- Oh?
What is it?
Who is that?
[Blank Princess is heading their way...]
What is it?
Who is that?
It's no one.
No, it's nothing.
[Foolish idiot... are you there?]
Let's not look like idiots.
Let's try to appear really cool.
[This is looking cool?]
You two really are idiots!
This young lady's got it all wrong
when it comes to us.
Listen, young lady...
- Even though we may look like this...
- We're foreign exchange students.
[Unbelievable...]
Get yourself together!
- We're very educated people!
- What are you talking about?
- I have a black belt in karate!
- And I used to be a bodyguard!
It's humiliating to just
even be standing next to you!
Listen to this young lady...
You didn't by any chance come here
to get us, did you?
- Me?
- Yes, you.
- I'm the fair princess.
- Fair?
- Yes, I'm the fair princess!
- Oh please...
[Over there, someone is...]
[Oh no... it's Sa Yeon!]
[Whenever she comes on the show,
she depletes them of their energy...]
My fair princess!
I love you!
Please accept my love!
Hi, guys!
I love you, fair princess!
Sa Yeon!
[Proving that they're idiotic fools.]
[Blank princess... please accept us.]
- Oh my, you're here!
- Hello, Sa Yeon.
- Why are you guys dressed like idiots today?
- No, we're not idiots.
- We're not idiots.
- No, we're not.
We may be dressed like this,
but we're really not idiots.
- You're not the idiots?
- Us? No, we're definitely not.
What brings you here today?
I'm going to marry myself
an idiot today.
- I saw them over there.
- What?
- No idiots here...
- My father...
My father... he told us to find ourselves
foolish idiots to marry.
Really? Is that what he said?
But we're not idiots.
[They're not?]
- It's been awhile.
- I wish we were marrying you.
Finally at this age...
I finally get to play the role of a princess.
It's making me feel really happy.
And just this past summer,
you played the role of a tuna.
[A recent summer tuna...]
- I lost some weight since then.
- You have?
[After her fishing incident,
she's lost some weight.]
- I'm serious.
- Your clothes seem a bit loose.
I purposely wore something bigger.
[Just leave?]
- Are you leaving?
- Yeah.
In that case,
we'll see you in a little bit.
[A cool farewell?]
Want to come with me?
[Will Sa Yeon be deterred
this easily?]
Sa Yeon, I think they're okay.
We have something to talk
to Ji Hyo about.
If you're going to do something like this,
pick someone with better brains.
I doubt Kwang Soo is it.
[His explosive idiot act.]
- In that case... I'll just come back later.
- Okay, then we'll see you later.
Goodbye, Sa Yeon.
[Safely... passes on Princess Sa Yeon?]
[Whew...]
I knew that was going to happen.
Whenever there's a race involving
queens or princesses...
it's pretty much a given
that Sa Yeon will be on the show.
[Blank...]
[Idiot Gary and idiot Ro-Ro
infatuated with playing their idiot roles.]
Come here!
Dried persimmon, you come here!
Give me back my dried persimmon!
Hey!
Hey, my dried persimmon!
[Where are all the idiots?]
[I have to meet an idiot and turn him into
the ultimate general of Running Kingdom.]
Meet yourselves a foolish idiot...
and turn them into the ultimate general
in all of Running Kingdom.
Then I will forgive you.
- Sa Yeon... you didn't even eat that much.
- That's what I'm saying.
Father is so weird.
Just because I was born weighing 4.8kg,
he keeps holding that against me.
- And you've lost all that weight recently.
- I know, I'm nothing but a bag of bones now.
What do we do?
Our father really is...
Look who's here!
[Finds Idiot Kook and Idiot Big-nose
deeper in the woods.]
Is that a man or a woman?
[Could that person be...]
[Sa Yeon the tuna?]
You two wait right there.
- Not here, we're not here.
- We're not here.
[Immediately goes into hiding.]
We're not here!
Who's this?
- She can't see us...
- I don't think she can see us.
- Idiots, let us see your faces.
Idiot Kook!
I will be your fair princess!
[You two are my foolish idiots.]
- No, we can't!
- There you go!
Sa Yeon...
[Blank Princess is extremely popular today.]
- You're much better.
- You're better.
Forget it!
I'm not going to be your fair princess!
- You're better... stay with us.
- I'm not going to be your princess.
[Forget it!]
Come on, let's go.
Hurry up and come on.
You two...
I'm going to train you very hard.
I think someone's coming.
Right?
It's Uee!
[Wow... Princess Uee!]
At last!
- Uee!
- I miss you!
Uee!
- Uee!
- What is it? Who's making you cry?
You have no idea how much
I've been searching for you!
[Seriously?]
- Uee!
- I miss you!
- We missed you!
[At last, their long awaited
'Uee, I miss you' project is fulfilled.]
- I've missed you.
- Uee...
Many times on the show,
we always said...
[Her name was shouted out
like it was a force of habit.]
- Uee..
- I miss you.
I want to go somewhere else.
[With the way their dressed,
it's understandable...]
- Why are we made to wear this?
- What's the deal with our outfits?
I really want to go somewhere else.
Seriously... why didn't you tell us sooner
that Uee was going to be on today?
I should've came dressed
in my suit today.
We're just dressed like this right now
because of a shoot we had earlier.
- Really?
- I'm going to change into my suit now.
- Does this mean Uee and the two of us...
- I'm...
your Fair Princess.
[Seriously?]
[A Uee-Brothers celebration.]
It's a celebration!
Do you want a dried persimmon?
Foolish idiot!
[Idiot Gary putting the moves on
Princess Ji Hyo?]
I have to train you to become
the ultimate General.
Let's have a dried persimmon
before we do that.
[In that case, Princess Blank is...]
Let's go, you foolish idiots.
[Chooses Idiot Gary and Idiot Ro-Ro!]
[Idiot Ro-Ro being a very good listener....]
- Let's go!
- Hey!
You two look very good together.
I saw Kwang Soo earlier,
and he really does look like an idiot.
When did you see him?
[We're scared that we may see
these guys in our dreams.]
Our brave princess has to lead and
teach our foolish idiots...
and have them become the
ultimate winners at the final competition.
The team that wins each
of the missions...
will be given a princess
name tag that they can use
at the final battle.
[Orange idiot team gains a name tag
for being the first team to arrive.]
[Quenching their thirst first.]
Let's see where we have to go.
Go to the 'D' spa in Yongsan.
- Hey!
- This is so embarrassing.
[Extremely embarrassed at having to
walk around with these two.]
What did you say?
You idiots!
- Is that you, Gary?
- You look like a movie star.
[The idiot act in full bloom.]
- Gary... this is Ki Bum.
- You parted your hair down the middle?
[More awful they look
the more you look at them.]
Aren't you the doctor from Astro Boy?
Wait, you weren't wearing the glasses
that's attached to the big nose?
- Your nose wasn't fake?
- What are you talking about?
- This is my nose!
- You're lying!
My nose!
Are you okay?
Who hit my boy?
Show yourself!
- Who hit my stupid idiot?
- I hit him!
- I'm the one who hit the idiot!
- Come out here immediately!
He's my idiot!
Don't touch him!
- All of you, get out!
- Oh my goodness...
- Go away... go away!
- Go away!
- I said, go away!
- Go!
What is it that you keep
saying to her?
[What is it that he's saying?]
You stupid idiots...
Our brave princess has to lead and
teach our foolish idiots...
and the team that wins at the final battle
will become our ultimate winners for the day.
- Is that right?
- She has to teach us?
- We're on our way!
- Let's go.
- Uee!
- I miss you!
We really did miss you.
[Finally able to tell the real Uee
that they miss her to her face!]
- Uee!
- I miss you!
[I'm the reason for their famous saying!]
[Uee's finally here! Yay!]
- Where are we going?
- We're going to the 'D' spa in Yongsan.
Idiot, I can't pull this.
You're not supposed to pull this.
You're supposed to turn it.
One shot?
Okay, let's go.
[The Green Idiot Team is
also on their way!]
Go go, go!
Keep it down back there.
Uee, you have to make sure
not to fall for this.
If you two team up together,
and gang up against me...
You have to make sure not to get
roped into his little ploys, okay?
[The 21st century idiots and the fair princess
proceed along in their car...]
[Blank...]
What are you looking at?
Why do you keep glancing back at me
and laughing like that?
It's so scary up here too.
Uee used to be a swimmer.
Do you want to get hit by
her backstroke?
Do you really want to get beat
by her backstrokes?
Move back a little! You want Uee
to beat you with her backstrokes?
- What do you mean, with her backstrokes?
- Backstrokes... beat like this!
And butterfly strokes are like this!
Pull your face back a little!
Your face is up so close...
[Idiot Giraffe making it feel
burdensome to look at.]
Hey, look up here.
Look at how you're showing up
in the front camera... look here.
[Take a look at your face...]
You look like a dog
that I'm taking home in my car.
Come on!
- A dog? How can you say I look like a dog?
- Look up here... look at how you look.
[His looks are a little difficult to believe
that he's just another human being...]
- Seriously...
- Kwang Soo, the light...
[Repugnance]
Listen to Uee... she wants to
know what the heck you're doing.
- You were saying that to me?
- Of course she was, who else could it be?
[You thought that would be funny?]
I'm doing this because there's no
other light in the back.
[I don't like him.]
You really don't know anything
about women!
[I agree.]
[Hm...]
[Look at how strong my jawline looks...]
[He seems to like his idiot makeover?]
[Cutie pie rapper...]
Is there any tissue in here?
I have tissue right here.
Do you need to wipe your nose?
That's not right.
[You like it too?]
- It's over there.
- I see it.
[Arrives at their destination.]
- I see it. I see the Running Man.
- The yellow clothing.
The name tag... Running Man.
We're here.
[Princess Uee Team also arrives
at their destination.]
Look, it's a sauna.
[- What is he doing?
- Pretends not to notice anything.]
[Yongsan, 'D' spa.]
[With the steam pouring out...
wow, an outdoor hot tub!]
[What kind of training will
the foolish idiots have to face here?]
- This is really nice.
- The water feels so warm.
The water's warm!
- The water's warm.
- This is nice.
[Princess Sa Yeon seeming happy
with the location.]
[Today's first mission will take place in
an outdoor hot tub to melt away the frost.]
Since all the foolish idiots
have met their fair princess...
will be a water purification game.
[Water purification?]
The idiots and the princesses went to the
fountain of knowledge to test their skills.
[Fountain of knowledge...]
It's making me nervous to see
the water cannons in front of us.
[But this fountain of knowledge
comes with water cannons?]
We've prepared something
special for you.
Once all the idiots are sat upon the balance
beams that you see in front of you...
The princesses will have to answer the
questions we'll ask of them in our quiz.
The princesses have to grab the spatula
and answer our question correctly.
If the princess give us the wrong answer
to the question asked...
the idiots of that princess' team...
You saw what's in front of you, right?
You'll be shot with a stream of water.
Ji Hyo's really bad at answering
quiz questions!
That's so not fair!
Her nickname is Blank Ji Hyo because
of her inability to answer quiz questions!
I'm not good with quizzes!
She's the idiot princess!
Idiot princess!
You idiot... did you just call me an idiot?
- You know what I mean!
- Got it... I got it!
- Okay, I got it!
- Hey!
I'm already bad at this game but I'm
going to lose on purpose just for you!
No, Ji Hyo... I didn't mean it.
But if the princess answers
the question right
the other team idiots will
be shot with the water stream.
[If one of the team gets the right answer,
the other teams will be shot with the water.]
- Okay, let's do it. We're cold!
- We're getting cold!
Okay, here's your first question.
In soccer terms...
[Soccer?]
[Blank...]
What do they call, 'Three against two'?
[What... is he... saying?]
What do they call, 'Three against two?'
[The correct answer is derived from a
famous Brazilian soccer player's name...]
['XX score!']
[Uee, you know this, don't you?]
- You can't give out any hints!
- Brazil... Brazil!
Five... four... three...
[Blank Princess going to
grab the spatula.]
Don't do it!
- Three to two?
- Three to two.
Just sit down if you don't
know the answer!
[Already preparing himself?]
Three wins!
[Powerful jets]
[This is the power of the
extreme water cannons.]
- What did you say?
- What answer did you give?
Three wins?
[Princess Sa Yeon takes the challenge.]
Parlay!
Parlay.
[It's not 'Parlay', but 'Pelle'.]
[Correct answer- 'Pelle score'.]
[The phrase which refers to the most
exciting score, three to two in soccer.]
I'm so scared!
Three to two?
I'll repeat the question.
What's the soccer phrase that refers to
the score being at three to two?
[Pelle... Pelle!]
[Blue Team caught cheating!]
Any team that cheats will be
blasted with the water cannon.
[All three of the princess'
are still clueless.]
- It only refers to three to two score?
- Three to two score.
- Uee...
- Please!
You can do this!
- It only refers to three to two score?
- Three to two score.
- You can do this.
- Win?
[You can just mute their screams.]
[Oh no...]
[Not likely these princesses
would know soccer terms...]
Don't you have any easier questions?
- Uee, you can do this.
- Ji Hyo!
Please!
- Parlay?
- What did you say?
[These idiots are learning to take a beating
before honing their knowledge first.]
[I guess that's not the right answer.]
[Please...]
Winner?
Wow... I'm seriously about to
lose my mind.
[Soccer maniac idiots are feeling
extremely frustrated by the situation.]
Sa Yeon, I'm sure you had to have
heard the term somewhere.
Sa Yeon, you can do this.
Pelle score.
How did you know the answer?
Earlier, Ji Suk Jin...
Disqualified!
[Giving out the answer is cheating!]
[Huh?]
[This forceful blast of the water cannon...]
[Kkuk-inator]
He's the terminator!
He didn't fall off!
[Oh my...
we're sure that he's just a singer...]
As mentioned earlier, since Ji Suk Jin gave
you the answer, this round doesn't count.
Pelle... Sa Yeon, Pelle.
[Pelle?]
[Can't you give me a break?]
Here's your second question.
Meaning, actively engaging in defense mode
even while in the attack mode...
what is the soccer term that also
means 'freedom' in Italian language?
[The idiots already know the answer!]
- Uee!
- You know this answer!
It's a soccer term?
[Blank...]
- Song Ji Hyo!
- Uee, get up there!
[Oh... Sa Yeon thinks she knows?]
She knows!
Ferrero?
- Ji Hyo, you know this answer!
- Uee, you've heard the term before!
You can't shout out the answer.
Freedom?
Free...
[Save this giraffe's life!]
It sounds like there's a waterfall
behind us right now.
[Total chaos back where
all the idiots are kept.]
- Ji Hyo!
- You can do this, answer the question!
Ji Hyo, hurry up and say the answer!
Are you spacing out on us?
Okay, I'll repeat the question.
Meaning, actively engaging in defense mode
even while in the attack mode...
what is the soccer term that also
means 'freedom' in the Italian language?
[The correct answer: 'Libero'.]
[Player Hong Myung Bo dubbed as
'The eternal liberator'.]
Freedom... it means freedom!
[Freedom?]
Forever!
[Forever is not quite the
same meaning...]
Forever!
[That's not the right answer?]
[Eternal = Forever!]
Forever...
Where is 'forever' coming from?
What's the word that comes
after 'eternal'?
[Could Blank Princess know the answer?]
Forever field?
[It seems as though she was meaning
to say 'Midfield'.]
How is it we know all the answers...
the idiots knows all the answers!
[Rather than the princesses helping
to grow the idiots' knowledge base...]
[The idiots are helping to grow
the princess' knowledge base?]
How is it that the idiots know
the answers better than all of you?
What kind of princess' are you three?
- You can do it!
- Uee, it's three syllables!
You can do it!
Felice!
[What in the world is...]
I seriously have no idea.
Sa Yeon, that's just the name
of an Italian restaurant!
[Is it?]
Is it an Italian word?
I'll give you a hint.
Hong Myung Bo.
[Oh! Princess Sa Yeon...]
[Oh... could she know
the right answer this time?]
Libero!
[Wow...]
She got it!
- Sa... Yeon...
- Is beautiful!
[Cross!]
You've earned your first point.
We all knew those answers!
All us idiots know all those answers!
[Soccer questions sure aren't easy
for these ladies...]
- This is big trouble.
- I'm in trouble.
- Uee...
- We're cold!
- Blank... Ji!
- Blank...
Here's your next question.
- You have to get this one!
- Okay.
- In tennis...
- It's a tennis question!
[When the score is calculated
in a tennis match...]
[What is the term that refers to
no scores on the board?]
Sa Yeon, you know what this is!
It's a beautiful word!
Zero!
[Oh? Blank Princess
shoots out of her seat?]
Love?
[Correct answer]
[Feeling of death warmed over.]
- Love!
- Ji Hyo!
[Blue Idiot Team wins one point.]
Uee... stay strong.
[Sports questions are so hard...]
Here's your next question.
[In a basketball game...
right before the game is over...]
[What is the term that's used to describe
a shot scored right before the end?]
- You know what it is!
- Right before the end!
The shot that's scored
practically when the buzzer sounds!
Strike!
[It seems she's a fan of bowling...]
She said 'strike'...
How can that be a strike?
Ji Hyo, you know this!
[What is it... what is it?]
What do I do?
I think I kind of know what it is...
Just give it a try.
[Did Uee remember the answer?]
- Uee's got it!
- Uee!
Time out.
[At last, is it a question that
Uee knows?]
- Buzzer bit.
- That's right!
What is it?
[So close, yet still wrong...]
[It's not the 'buzzer bit',
but the 'buzzer beater'.]
It's similar... it's very similar to that!
Hurry up and grab it!
[If it's similar...]
Buzzer beast?
Last chance!
- Uee! You're almost there!
- Buzzer...
bead?
Buzzer ball.
Is it four syllables?
- Sa Yeon, don't do it!
- Free throws.
[Throwing out anything
that comes to her mind.]
Sa Yeon... are you sure you're not
an idiot yourself?
- Sa Yeon...
- Stop saying whatever!
Sa Yeon, it's four letters!
Why are you saying 'ball'?
[Uee takes another stab at the challenge.]
- Uee... you're almost there!
- Almost there?
Am I really almost there?
Buzzer beacher.
[Buzzer beacher]
- Sa Yeon, it's really similar!
- It's similar!
Ji Hyo! You can do this!
It's very similar to that!
I really want to grab it!
[The correct answer is
staring at them in the face!]
- Uee!
- Hurry!
You got it right up to 'Buzzer be-'
I said every word I know that
starts with 'be'!
Buzzer Beju?
Buzzer Beju.
[Buzzer Beju...]
[That's not it?]
Okay, let me think... wait.
- Be...
- Uee, take a guess!
- Guess?
- It's similar!
- It's very similar!
- Buzzer beazer.
Buzzer beazer.
- Oh my goodness...
- Ji Hyo!
- Save us!
The character the last letter starts
with is 'T'.
- Uee!
- You can do this!
- You know this! Say it!
Buzzer beater.
[Finally gets the correct answer.]
- Uee!
- I miss you!
But you keep giving us sports questions,
and we're very weak in that subject.
Stop giving us sports questions.
Give us food-related questions instead.
[Exhausted]
Just hurry up and do it!
- Stop stalling so much!
- Kang Gary, you're so handsome!
Really?
[Immediately breaks out into a smile.]
It's okay then!
We're going to start with
our next question.
- Uee!
- I miss you!
This time, it'll be the idiots that will
be answering the quiz questions.
The way we're going to do this is...
is when I ask the questions, the princesses
are going to come grab the spatulas.
Then the men on the same princess' team with
the spatula will have to answer the question.
- Even though we may not know the answer?
- Just grab the spatula no matter what.
Ladies, all you have to do is...
if you think your teammates will know it,
just come out and grab the spatulas.
- Sa Yeon... just grab it.
- Just grab the spatula.
- Jae Suk, I'll grab it, okay?
- I wasn't going to mention this...
but you all know that Uee is
a swimmer, right?
- What does that matter?
- Do you mean that tiny distance?
Swim up there!
- Uee...
- Sa Yeon is a good fighter!
- Swim up there!
- Ji Hyo... then you can ride the wake board.
Okay, here's your question.
The soles...
The sole and the heel is connected...
The sole...
- What?
- The sole and the heel...
What do you call the style of ladies shoes
where the sole and the heels are connected?
[What style of ladies shoes has the sole
and the heel part connected together?]
What style of ladies shoes has the sole
and the heel part connected together?
[Ji Hyo knows right away?]
[That's...]
- High heels!
- Hey!
- Uee, I know it!
- Okay... Ji Suk Jin's good with this.
[Most of women would know this, right?
Correct answer - Wedge heel.]
Horseshoe?
- What is it?
- What could it be?
- Do you think you know?
- Ji Hyo, we think we know.
- Correct answer.
- Stilts!
Hey!
You might as well just say lifts!
Uee, go grab it!
[It seems as though Idiot Suk
may know the answer?]
I believe in him!
Loafers.
High boots!
[Naming every kind of shoe
that they've heard of.]
- Jae Suk, hurry!
- Uee, I don't know!
[If you don't know...]
- The answer is... it's an English word.
- English? Answer!
- Fur boots!
- No!
[That's just fur...]
[The difference in men and women
becoming evidently obvious.]
- Jae Suk... say the answer.
- Aladdin shoes!
What?
- Aladdin shoes.
- Aladdin...
[Giraffe's creative answers.]
- You don't even know that answer?
- Is it an English word?
- It's an English word!
- High...
- Like a tall hill...
- Heel boots!
Wedge heel, wedge heel!
Wedge heel is the answer, you stupid idiots!
Wedge heels, wedge heels!
[Wow... she shouts out the answer.]
- Wedge heels, wedge heels!
- Wedge heels?
- That's right!
- She shouted out the answer!
What do we do now?
How frustrated do you think we had to be
to shout out the answer ourselves?
This is the first time I've ever heard
'Wedge heels' in my whole life.
[First time these idiots have ever heard of
the term 'wedge heels' in their life.]
- This is the first time I've heard of it too.
- To us...
they're all just dress shoes.
- All the shoes are the same.
- And soccer is just soccer to us.
- Uee... we'll get it right this time!
- Okay!
- Don't worry... and just grab it!
- Go grab the spatula!
- Fighting!
- Ji Hyo, don't worry!
As the most popular way
of dying hair in 2013...
what is the hairstyle that's become popular
due to many idols sporting it?
What is the hairstyle that's become popular
Partial decolorization!
[Correct answer: Two tone hair.]
[Hairstyle where the top and the bottom
portion are dyed different colors.]
That's not it?
Hair dye!
- Why don't you guys try and answer?
- Root dye?
- What?
- Fin.K.L perm?
- It's very popular right now.
- Sa Yeon, is it an English word?
- It's in English.
- It's an English word?
- Jae Suk and Kwang Soo are...
- Rainbow color!
[Answers that are varying
as the colors of the rainbow.]
What kind of hair is it?
[Hint: 'XX- hair'.]
- Is it a two word answer?
- Think about it simply!
- What did you say?
- Think about it simply.
- It's what kind of hair?
- Easy hair!
Simple hair?
Simple hair!
[Is she giving out hints with
her hand?]
Here... something hair!
[Signaling 'two' for 'two tone hair'.]
- Here! What kind of hair is it?
- Brown hair!
[When she says it's some sort of hair...]
[All the princesses are signaling
'two' or a 'v' with their fingers.]
- English!
- What are the two words, Sa Yeon?
We can't understand the hint.
Fashion hair?
Grab it!
Two tone hair!
- Two...
- Two tone!
[Correct answer]
[Finally!]
[Current score- Blue idiot Team- 1,
Orange idiot Team- 1, Green idiot Team- 2.]
The next question is extremely easy.
[An extremely easy question
even for the idiots?]
- Sa Yeon, just grab it.
- Just grab the spatula first.
[I will get it this time!]
[What do you call the method where the feet
are cleaned up and the toenails painted?]
What do you call the method where the feet
are cleaned up and the toenails painted?
[Wow, Princess Ji Hyo's
lightning fast moves!]
Nail art!
- Nail art!
[The other two teams have a chance!]
[Princess Uee grabs the spatula.]
[Now the chance goes to
the Green Team!]
Pedicure!
- Pedicure!
[Correct answer]
[Final score- Blue idiot Team- 1,
Orange idiot Team- 2, Green idiot Team- 3.]
I thought it was nail art too.
- How could you not have known the answer?
- Why are you scolding your princess?
I came on the show because I got to
be a princess, but what the heck is this?
- Sa Yeon, I'm sorry.
- Sorry, Sa Yeon!
Okay... Team Princess Uee wins!
[Green Idiot Team wins!]
[Wins the mission, gains
another Princes Uee name tag!]
[The Grasshopper and Giraffe's
ceremonial butterfly strokes.]
Princess Uee and the Green Idiot Team who
gained the strength of knowledge first
set foot on their travel
around the world.
[Next up is a trip around the world?]
We won first place.
- Wow...
- Wow.
- You guys did great.
- That was really...
How well did we do?
What was so cool about what we did?
She was just saying it.
How cool could we have been?
Jae Suk was really cool.
You were really cool.
Why were you guys so bad at it?
- Ah... I knew that it was pedicure.
- It was pedicure.
- You didn't know the pedicure..
- And the wedge heels.
- We didn't know the wedge heels.
- You guys should study some more.
- Wedge heels...
- And what else... what's popular?
Okay, we have to go to Itaewon.
We're told to go to Itaewon.
- Itaewon bound!
- Yes!
[Itaewon... a trip around the world.]
(Where many foreigners in Korea lives.)
You said nail art earlier, right?
[This team is still in review mode.]
But when it comes to feet,
it's known as pedicure.
I have big toenails.
So they can draw a whole
picture on there.
So they can draw a whole landscape
on your big toenail?
[Landscape painting on her big toenail?]
- That's why it costs me so much money.
- Landscape...
And with my big face,
it costs me a lot for makeup too.
Uee, do you have a boyfriend?
If I say anything right now, I feel like
you're going to hook me up with Kwang Soo.
I'd never do that,
so don't worry about it.
Uee, we don't do things like that anymore.
We're very cool about it now.
- Really?
- Of course.
Kwang Soo, what kind of a man are you?
Don't feel burdened with Uee here,
but tell us in fine detail.
- In truth, at first glance...
- Tell us about yourself.
- I'm not very specific.
- Okay...
People may not get your
attraction right away?
No, people would have no idea.
No clue whatsoever.
If you're going to be a damper
on things like this...
- When I...
- Forget it.
You two aren't going to work.
I told you, I was right.
- We should see it through to the end.
- Seriously...
Whether I get slapped in the face,
or things work out, let's see where it goes.
I told you, she's going to beat you
with her backstroke.
[The three princesses and their idiots'
trip around the world.]
[Place of destination... Itaewon.]
[Green Idiot Team and their princess
are first to arrive.]
[What is their mission that will
take them on a trip around the world?]
[All of the idiots will go to different
stores separately on their own.]
[You must beat two missions when your
princess finds you in order to proceed.]
Over there, you'll see a Thai restaurant.
For America, it's the handmade
pizza pie shop right behind you.
That pizza shop? Didn't we do a mission
at that same shop in the past?
If you mention me,
I'm sure the owner would know.
- Jae Suk...
- The Chef and the owner in there...
they know me very well.
So mention me when you get in there.
- Where?
- Boss!
Boss!
[Oh! That's a familiar face!]
Gary... let's go!
How you been?
Hello, Sir!
[Edward, whom they've met when they came
to do a mission here previously!]
- You look younger.
- Really?
You too!
Nice to meet you.
[They didn't notice it before, but the
store next to it belongs to him also?]
Here, here, and there.
- Rich guy!
- This owner here...
This is my ally.
- Congratulations.
- Are you guys talking about something funny?
Thank you very much, Sir.
[No matter,
this is a fateful encounter as well.]
- Happy new year.
- Yes, goodbye.
[The idiots must choose between the Thai and
American restaurants and make their move.]
In order to further strengthen their idiots,
the fair princesses separated them...
to test their hearts.
[Just what are the two missions
that await them at these restaurants?]
[A flower adorned limbo bar
at the Thai restaurant?]
What is this?
We're in trouble.
- I'm not good at limbo.
- Why are you doing this to us?
Why...
While shouting out 'Princess, your highness',
sit up and down five times.
and follow through by passing under
the limbo bar
and shout out, 'All hail Princess,
your highness' to win the mission.
Five times?
What did you say?
I have to hold and carry the princess?
[Hopeless...]
This is really worrisome.
[Weak Suk Jin to carry Princess Sa Yeon?]
- Since he has to carry me...
- Our knees can't touch either?
- Of course, they can't.
- Then how can we pass?
We can't jump over the bar, right?
[Jae Suk can't participate this round because
Princess Uee isn't at this location.]
Then I'll proceed with the game.
In that case...
Suk Jin, why don't you start?
Hey...
Just because it's not your legs
at stake here...
- Just because they're not your legs...
- Well, I have nothing to lose here.
[Proceeding without any hesitation since
he's not the one having to lift anyone.]
But Sa Yeon... this is no joke,
but Sa Yeon's lost a lot of weight.
- Sa Yeon was very sick for a while.
- My husband told me I was nothing but bones.
- I'm serious.
- You're no longer the tuna here then.
- You really have lost a lot of weight.
- I miss our Tuna Sa Yeon.
[Anyways, Orange Idiot Team
is the first to step up to the challenge.]
I've had to carry Sa Yeon twice
in our past missions...
It was difficult for two people
to carry her together.
[Back in Sa Yeon's tuna days?
The memories still fresh in his mind.]
- How much do you weigh?
- What?
- How much do you weigh, Suk Jin?
- I weigh 76 kg?
- I see...
- How much do you weigh?
There's not much difference there.
[Adorable Sa Yeon, how will it go this time?]
[The moment he lifts her up... crash.]
- Hey!
- Sa Yeon, are you okay?
[Come on, that's just too...]
I really am trying my best.
I wasn't joking around,
but I was really trying.
The viewers are going to think that
Sa Yeon's really heavy now.
- I wasn't kidding, but was trying hard.
- Sa Yeon, I'll do it.
- Here, let me lift you up.
- One, two, three.
- You got it. One, two, three.
- You said I got this?
Let's go.
One, two, three.
[I can't...]
What do you mean, one?
Sa Yeon, I don't think I can do this.
[Even setting her back down
is no easy task!]
[Drops her to the ground.]
Why are you guys so weak?
[Will the Orange Idiot Team be able to
lift Sa Yeon Princess for the mission?]
[At the same time,
at the American pizza place.]
[What's the mission here?]
[What's the mission that makes her smile
like that as soon as she sees the card?]
- What do we do?
- Why?
Play the stick biscuit game...
- This game? Really?
- I...
[Play the biscuit game with the princess and
if there's less than 1.5 cm left, you win!]
[Since his princess is the only one present,
only Kwang Soo and Uee can play the game.]
Why?
How can you do that?
Then there's no reason for me
to be here right now.
[You have to play the game when your
Princess Ji Hyo comes to the restaurant.]
Kwang Soo, come up here.
Kwang Soo...
[It's just a process that any idiot has to
go through so why do you look so...]
Challenge.
I'm so nervous.
- That's not the nervousness she means.
- Why are you nervous?
That's not the nervousness
that she's referring to.
Do you have any heart calming medicine?
This is just a game.
- Challenge.
- Okay, challenge.
[Green Idiot Team's Uee and Kwang Soo.]
Is Uee making the move?
Kwang Soo, why do you keep backing up?
No, no I'm not.
Let's do it again.
[Unlimited chances until they succeed.]
- Kwang Soo, you can't back up, okay?
- Okay.
[Uee is confidently playing the game,
so why is Kwang Soo...]
Challenge.
I don't think I can do this!
I can't do this!
Wow... that's a beautiful scene.
[Fails with a whole 6 cm!]
What happens if the whole thing disappears?
[Huh? In order to make it disappear...]
I was just curious.
[On the other hand...]
But Ji Hyo is pretty muscular...
[Blue Idiot Team's Ha Ha and
Blank Princess step up to the challenge.]
You can definitely do it.
[Definitely heard something breaking...]
Go Eun!
Go Eun, I'm sorry!
[How could such a sound be heard
when it's not like he lifted up a boulder?]
It sounded like a tree breaking.
What the heck is this?
[Orange Idiot Team's second attempt.]
- Sa Yeon, you're light as a feather.
- She's not that bad, and you can do this.
I'm a pretty light person.
I really did lose a lot of weight.
[Big-nosed idiot fails from the get-go again
in his attempt to lift up Plump Princess.]
What is this?
Sa Yeon, give it one last try
and if it doesn't work again...
go over to the other restaurant to do the
mission with Jong Kook, then come back.
- Okay, I think I'll do that.
- Can you help lift up her legs?
[With Jae Suk's help,
Suk Jin attempts to lift up Sa Yeon again.]
Set, go.
[Sit up and down five times while
shouting out 'Princess, your highness']
Your highness...
Princess...
[Suddenly bursts out into laughter
without even knowing the reason why.]
Why are you laughing?
He just keeps laughing.
Are you okay?
- Sa Yeon...
- This team has no chance.
Just hurry up and go see Jong Kook.
- This is really starting to make me mad.
- It's because Suk Jin's too weak.
You're really not that heavy.
- Sa Yeon, it's not because of you.
- I really have become much lighter.
[Brief rest time while tape reel
is being replaced.]
- You really want to do it?
- Yeah, for real.
I'll do the slate.
- One, two, three.
- She's so strong.
[Is Big-nosed Brother losing to Sa Yeon
in arm wrestling?]
- Are you doing this for real?
- Why are you dangling like that?
[Idiot Big-nose really can't
even budge his hand!]
- This is just absurd!
- Suk Jin, you really can't move her?
[That means he's already pretty much
lost the game...]
Did you win your mission?
[Plump Princess having made her way over
after teaching Idiot Big-nose a lesson.]
What game are you playing?
I need to win the game quickly
and take Jong Kook back with me.
[Planning on taking Jong Kook back
with her after winning this mission.]
- Why does Kwang Soo look like that?
- Why are your hands gripped in a fist?
No, you can't do it like that!
With your teeth... yes, like that!
[Green Idiot Team fails for having stopped
in the middle of their attempt.]
[Giraffe still playing the game
with his feelings worn on his sleeve.]
[This is a nice mission.]
- Sa Yeon...
- Let me wipe my nose first.
Why is your nose running?
[Don't misunderstand,
it's just that she has a slight cold...]
- You want me to hold onto it?
- Go ahead. I'm too nervous.
Isn't it nerve wrecking?
[Worry about the nervousness later,
and just concentrate on the game first!]
[Must complete the mission here first...
and hurry back to the limbo mission.]
- Okay, let's do a god job.
- Okay, I'll bite onto it.
- She says, let's do a good job.
- Here we go.
[Plump Princess coming out aggressively.]
[Blue Idiot Team's Blank Princess
makes her way over here first as well.]
Sa Yeon looks way too eager.
[Working hard!]
[Wow! That looks really short!]
Here it is!
[Almost nothing but crumbs left
of their biscuit!]
- Hey!
[Idiot Giraffe destroys the evidence of
Orange Idiot Team's work!]
Have you lost your mind?
[Quickly destroying the evidence because
it looked as though they succeeded!]
- That was it!
- That was our piece!
Ah... so that was the piece.
Ah... sorry, I'm sorry.
It doesn't count if we can't
measure it with our ruler.
[Mission failed due to the writer's rules.]
[Plan success]
[Blue Idiot Team's Blank Princess
and Idiot Gary's turn.]
[Now that we think about it,
this is the Monday Couple...]
- You want to eat the chocolate?
- No.
- Say 'challenge' before you start.
- Challenge.
- Let's do this in one try, Ji Hyo.
- One try.
Now that I'm really about to do it,
I'm getting nervous.
I really am nervous.
[Even more awkward for two people who knows
each other so well to play the game together.]
Are you going to close your eyes?
- We have to let each other know.
- Why?
What's so important about that?
I don't know.
You're not going to lean your head,
are you?
Okay.
- Where are you looking at?
- Looking at the ceiling because I feel shy.
Okay, go for it.
[They're so sweet and adorable.]
[The Blue Idiot Team's Monday Couple
starts their challenge at last!]
[Riveted]
You have to turn your head.
Why?
[Blue Idiot Team's Monday Couple - Fail.]
- He has to grab you. If he doesn't...
- It's just too shaky.
[It would be easier to grab
the other person's head...]
That shocked me.
[What did they score?
Fails at 4.3 cm.]
Gary, I think I can do it.
I think I can do it this time.
I think Gary looks more nervous
than Ji Hyo is.
- Can we go right now?
- It's our turn.
It's our turn.
Can we just continue shooting
the scene on our own?
We're going to keep shooting, okay?
[He's unstoppable...]
- Let's just end this.
- Okay.
[At the same time, at the Thai restaurant...]
[On suspension with all the
Princesses on a trip over to America?]
- Suk Jin, was that arm wrestling for real?
- No.
What do you mean, no?
You were hanging on for dear life.
- I was just reacting to it to be funny.
- Even your toes were tightened up.
- It was all just part of my reaction.
- I think you're lying.
No, come on...
did my acting look natural?
Seeing just how natural it was,
we know it wasn't acting.
When you look natural,
that means it's for real with you.
- Because you're a bad actor.
- You really are a horrible actor.
I really made it look natural, didn't I?
[Orange Idiot Team's challenge.]
[If the Giraffe hadn't crushed their biscuit,
they probably would've passed by now.]
[A fragment fell on the plate!]
[Amazing!]
- My neck feels stiff.
- I'm sorry to tell you this, but...
You can pick whichever one you want
to measure.
Oh my, oh my...
Look at how short this one is.
[Time to reveal the results...
exactly 1 cm.]
[Orange Idiot Team succeeds
their America mission!]
Seriously... having no feelings
really is the best.
You guys aren't able to do it
because there are feelings there.
You're just pretending that you don't
have any feelings, Sa Yeon!
- Let's go, Sa Yeon.
- You're going with her, Jong Kook?
- Of course. I can go with her, right?
- You only have one mission left to go.
[Orange Idiot Team is on the clear!
Off to Thailand they go!]
Kwang Soo, just relax.
This is nice.
- Sa Yeon, where do we go now?
- We have to go to the Thai restaurant now.
- Thailand... let's go to Thailand.
- Yes.
That's too long.
[Must be less than 1.5 cm to succeed!
Green Idiot Team fails at 2 cm.]
Kwang Soo, I'll come to you.
Why are you acting like
nothing's going on?
[It's now the Monday Couple of
Blue Idiot Team's turn.]
[Forget about any feelings
just like Sa Yeon said?]
It's short.
[What will be the Monday Couple's result?]
[Succeeds at 1.2 cm!]
Success!
I'd like to go for a 7mm challenge this time.
[Blue Idiot Team must also hurry to Thailand
to complete their last mission.]
Challenge.
[Since the Green Idiot Team is late,
they must hurry to succeed this mission.]
- Uee...
- You want me to say my own name?
- I miss you!
- Kwang Soo, I think I can do this.
- Okay.
I know I can do this.
I believe in you, okay?
Why do you keep doing that?
[Everyone's gathering in Thailand.]
They're here.
What is Kwang Soo doing with
Uee over there?
[An armload of handmade pies
after completing their America mission.]
It didn't take long.
[Having been hungry,
everyone taking a piece to share.]
- Break it off.
- Sa Yeon...
You shouldn't be eating right now
when you still have to do this mission.
- You shouldn't be eating.
- Why?
You can't lift me up anyways,
so what does this matter?
Just hand it over.
[But I'm hungry...]
After... you can eat after the mission.
[Princess Uee and the Giraffe still at it
when they were first to start the mission.]
[That's short!]
[Sure of their success this time?]
[At... 1cm. Success!]
- Is it this way?
- Here... it's right here.
- Hello.
Kwang Soo!
- Jae Suk, I'm so sorry!
- What do you have to be sorry about?
[But the sight of them walking together
is a bit...]
Why do you two look like you're just
returning from your honeymoon?
Telling me that you're sorry...
what do you have to be sorry about?
[Bearing gifts with their blushing faces...]
- I oppose this!
- What?
- Why are you opposing this?
- I oppose this marriage!
I second that!
No way!
It's too big of a loss for Uee!
Why are you so harsh with your words?
[Anyway, since all three teams are here now,
we must hurry to complete the mission here.]
[Green Idiot Team to take the first turn.]
- Uee... you're on the lighter side, right?
- What?
- You can keep that on.
- Keep it on?
- Of course.
- One, two, three.
Wow, Uee...
- What are you doing?
- Why are you rolling her over?
- Uee, why did you fall off?
- Are you okay?
[Maybe she slipped, maybe he dropped her,
maybe she's too heavy, or he's too weak...]
She's like a marble rolling around.
Uee... Uee is acting weird.
[A bit different feel than his prediction
of her being light as a feather?]
Oh my goodness...
- Kwang Soo, you want to try?
- Okay, I'll give it a try.
I'm going to give it a try.
I'll get it done for real.
- What?
- Let's do it.
- Uee!
- I miss you.
[Reaffirming their team bond
by shouting out the team's battle cry.]
We can do it too!
- Blank.. Ji! Blank...
Let's do it.
One, two, three.
She's not quite what you think.
It's a little different.
- But it'll be okay.
- So this is what you were talking about?
Uee's not quite what you think.
- Uee feels different.
- Princess...
- Princess, your highness...
- That's right... you're doing it.
- It's okay.
- Uee and Suzy are very similar.
[With his teeth gritted tight...]
I know you want to put her down,
but you have to endure it.
You're going to want to put her down,
but you have to get over that hump.
[Must pass through the limbo bar with her in
the arms and shout out, 'All hail princess!]
Okay, that's good.
You're getting the feeling that
you can't do it, right?
You have to try again.
Gather up your strength again.
You have to get a feel for it.
That's right. Kick off your shoes.
Okay...
[Getting back into position once again.]
And... okay... here you go.
All the feelings you have for Uee are
all coming at you right now...
- Okay...
- Kwang Soo, when are you going to move?
You're feeling it right now, aren't you?
Here it comes...
- Kwang Soo...
- That's right, slow...
- That's right Kwang Soo...
- Kwang Soo, you're going to touch your head.
Kwang Soo...
[Almost touched the limbo bar
with Uee's face.]
I'm sorry.
- I'm sorry, but stay still.
- Kwang Soo...
Don't move.
- I'm moving bit by bit.
- Hey...
- You have to take off his hat.
[Uee's made it through,
now just Kwang Soo needs to...]
- Are you okay, Kwang Soo?
- I think you're going to do it.
[About to make his pass through the bar!]
- Little bit more...
- I almost have it.
- Kwang Soo, you're...
- Just a little bit more.
[Backtracking once again.]
[It's all in the state of mind...]
[His head is through,
now only his body is left!]
You have to move your
right foot a little.
Wow, I'm seeing Kwang Soo with
a whole new set of eyes.
- Kwang Soo, just a little bit more.
- You can't backtrack now.
- Kwang Soo looks really cool.
- You can't move back right now.
[Backtracks again.]
You can't come back here.
You really can't come back here.
This is so embarrassing.
[Idiot Giraffe gathers up his strength
for his fair princess...]
All hail the princess!
[Losing all the strength in his legs at
the last minute and stumbles on his words...]
What are you doing right now?
[Feeling bad and humiliated.]
[Green Idiot Team fails their attempt.]
Hang on...
I'm just going to sit here for a minute.
It's okay, Uee.
It's not because of you.
Isn't Jong Kook going to try?
[Orange Idiot Team-
Capable Idiot's attempt.]
I lost some weight.
[Sit up and down five times while
shouting out, 'Princess, your highness'.]
- Princess, your highness.
- Four.
- Jong Kook is the best!
- Princess, your highness.
[Immediately moves over to the limbo bar.]
Your leg... stretch out your left leg.
[Carefully getting into position.]
I think you're going to do it.
Her arm is about to touch.
- Sa Yeon arm...
- It's about to touch her arm.
- Pull your arm out, Sa Yeon.
- No! Don't move that arm!
No, not that arm!
[He barely found the balance, but now
is about to crumble with her moving!]
Jong Kook, why are you
shaking like a leaf?
- Look at how you're shaking!
- I've never seen Jong Kook's legs tremble.
- I'm slipping.
- What is that?
[Orange Idiot Team - Fail.]
I've never seen you shake like that.
Sa Yeon makes even Jong Kook
shake in his shoes.
[Strong Sa Yeon making even
Mr. Capable tremble in his seat.]
- The feeling I got...
- That was so close.
We're going to make our attempt.
[Blue Idiot Team switches out
the player to Idiot Gary.]
[Monday Couple continues on after
succeeding the biscuit challenge.]
- This is the lover's game.
- Okay...
- Did you loosen up?
- I'm ready.
I seriously...
I wonder if I'll be strong enough.
Ji Hyo...
[Five times while shouting out,
'Princess, your highness'.]
- Princess, your highness...
- Look at Ji Hyo smiling.
- How many times was that?
- Five.
- It's limbo time.
- I think he can do it.
[Moving off to the limbo bar
without any hesitation.]
[Posing like something out of a movie,
and let's go!]
[Easily passing through.]
Don't move. Stay just like that.
Stay real still.
- Your shoulder...
- Don't even say anything.
Just think... just think about
what you're having for dinner.
[Gary almost makes it through!]
[Now all he has to do is shout out,
'All hail princess' as he gets back up!]
All hail princess!
[Monday Couple keeps on rocking today!]
All hail... all hail!
[Very cool, Idiot Gary!]
[Blue Idiot Team wins another name tag.]
Princess, your highness...
[Even though there are no more name tags,
the princess' training continues on!]
[Idiot Giraffe also finally succeeds!]
- There you go!
- You made it through...
Okay, you're through!
[Capable Idiot succeeds this time!]
[The idiots and the princesses complete their
fun journey and finally faces their last mission.]
Go to the fitness center in Yongsan.
Yongsan fitness center?
[Fitness center?
Could there be a fiery competition ahead?]
Yongsan fitness center...
We're here.
- Gary...
- Yeah?
I think we're going to be boxing.
Boxing?
[Chilling... This place was about to see
a great fight take place inside.]
[The idiots' final passage...]
[Boxing center!]
[The ultimate idiot will be determined!]
[Enters the ring with trepidation.]
[Gary with manners.]
- Kang Gary...
- Isn't this what you're supposed to do?
[Blue Idiot Team completes their entrance.]
[Orange Idiot Team also completes
making their grand entrance.]
But isn't boxing...
[Idiot Jae Suk already starting to feel
nervous as he makes his entrance.]
[Could their last mission
really be a boxing match?]
[And Green Team brings up the rear,
and completes making their entrance.]
[Mount a blindfolded idiot, and
eliminate the opposing princess' name tag.]
Mount a blindfolded idiot, and
eliminate the opposing princess' name tag.
[The first team to have arrived
moves on to the final round.]
- Final round?
- Yes!
[Blue Idiot Team moves on to the final round
for having been the first to arrive.]
[Each team currently has
two princess name tags each.]
Since the idiots can't see anything,
the princesses will have to guide them.
While riding your idiot, you have to
eliminate the other princess' name tag.
[Teamwork between the idiot and
the princess is the most crucial thing!]
[The princesses will have to target each
other's name tag while on idiot's shoulders.]
[All the idiots firmly believed that their
own princess would win the battle.]
[Practicing their boxing skills while
the film reel is being changed.]
[Gary and Jong Kook boxing in earnest
with their authentic boxing skills.]
Fighting.
Uee!
She's literally mounting
Suk Jin right now.
[Green Idiot Team's Jae Suk and Uee vs.
Orange Idiot Team's Suk Jin and Sa Yeon.]
- You're nice and light.
- Not bad, right?
[Real princess and the idiot general
will be determined here!]
[Who will take the glory?]
[Preliminary first round - Start!]
[A real fight right off the bat!]
[Uee almost having lost the battle!]
[Ready]
[Princess Sa Yeon attacks again!]
Right... to the right!
No, to the left!
[I feel like death...]
Left!
To the left!
[Uee attacks Sa Yeon's back!]
[In the battle between the princesses...
the idiots are suffering quite a bit.]
Jae Suk!
You have to move away!
Jae Suk, you have to turn!
[Princess Sa Yeon dismounted.]
What happened?
[Crumbling down in shambles
within moments.]
- Wait...
- What happened?
- Sa Yeon, why...
- Why did you fall off?
[A they pull off their blindfolds to look,
Sa Yeon is sitting in a heap on the floor.]
[There was a definite sound of something
crashing to the floor...]
I heard something fall to the ground.
[Time for Coach Kook's pointers.]
I'm seriously not just going to
let you get away with this.
[Idiot Big-nose being scolded worse than
he would be by a real boxing coach.]
Turn... Sa Yeon, turn your body a bit.
[Realistic practice with Coach Kook.]
You have to turn now.
[Getting ready to start off after
being severely coached on how to play.]
[First round reconvenes!]
[Suk Jin treated like an idiot for
having turned in the opposite direction.]
[Sees another chance!]
[Uee moves in!]
[To the front lines!]
[A golden opportunity!]
[Green Idiot Team strikes like lightening
as soon as they see an opportunity!]
[Princess Sa Yeon takes it out on
Big-nosed idiot for his mistake!]
[What a pathetic sight...]
That's not it... but when Sa Yeon told you to
turn, you presented her back to Uee!
It's been at least 30 years since
I've been grabbed by my hair.
[Orange Idiot Team. One of their
two name tags are eliminated!]
[Thus onto the second preliminary round!]
Okay, put your blindfolds on.
Jong Kook, this isn't our fight.
[Each team's idiots stepping up
to test the waters.]
- He's not even putting on his blindfold.
- It's okay, it's oaky.
[Giraffe provokes the Tiger.]
Good, Kwang Soo...
that's good.
- Kwang Soo, you better watch yourself.
- It's okay Kwang Soo. There are cameras.
[With all the cameras around,
it's safe to make his attempt?]
- You've got the cameras, Kwang Soo.
- Since we're just checking each other out...
[Orange Idiot Team's Jong Kook and Sa Yeon
vs. Green Idiot Team's Kwang Soo and Uee.]
Okay, put on your blindfolds.
We need to win this so that we
can move on to the final round.
[So you've got your blindfold on now?]
[Take that!]
[Even blindfolded,
Tiger is still a tiger!]
Is there just no way?
Just what does one have to do...
how can he ever be beaten?
The one chance at Jong Kook I'm
waiting for is his 70th birthday.
So I have to stay alive until then.
I'm living to see his 70th birthday party.
- I'm waiting for his 70th birthday.
- Even old, he'd still be scary.
Just what state will I be in when
Kim Jong Kook turns 70?
[Even when he turns 70,
we're guessing he'd still be all muscle.]
Okay, Kwang Soo...
[If the Orange Idiot Team loses again,
they're out of the competition!]
Whatever you do,
you can't drop your princess.
Okay, round two!
- To the right, right...
- Left! Turn to the left!
[Capable idiot definitely quicker
on his feet than Big-nosed idiot.]
[But the idiots are still suffering
just the same.]
[A bloody battle ensues once again
between the two princesses!]
Don't go... don't!
Move back.
[But the princesses and the idiots
are impressively working in sync.]
[The princesses have each other's
name tags in their grasp!]
[Who will get to it first?]
[Princess Uee of the Green Idiot's Team
moves in like lightning and rips it off!]
[Orange Idiot Team loses both their name tags
and is thus eliminated from the competition.]
[Green Idiot Team moves on
to the final round!]
- Uee!
- I miss you!
Oh my gosh, the whole thing ripped off!
I ripped it all off.
Can we just try it on our own?
Without getting on someone's back.
[Please have mercy on me!]
We can't?
[She would've been dead if I didn't
have to be on an idiot's back...]
[Green Idiot Team in final battle
with the Blue Idiot Team.]
[Will the Monday Couple be able to
dominate this race too?]
Just destroy the other team, okay?
Once this season is over,
you two can get married, okay?
You two can start dating for real, okay?
Get yourself together, okay?
Uee... we'll just leave those two to love,
and we'll take home the gold!
And then we can just leave them,
and never see them again!
And you don't really have to see
Kwang Soo again.
You can just see each other
on TV from now on.
[Let's win the gold together today, and
only see each other on TV starting tomorrow!]
It's just weird that you two haven't
dated at all in the past three years!
Don't worry about a thing.
Both the teams looks like
you're having a lot of fun.
You guys look like a father, mother,
and the boss.
This is my place...
and my parents came to visit me today.
But you look very young to have
a son his age.
[Too young to have a son his age?]
[Final round:
Kwang Soo and Uee vs. Gary and Ji Hyo.]
- Get your head on straight.
- How much is this event costing to watch?
Okay, this is the final round.
[At last, start!]
Left... no, Kwang Soo.
You're moving backwards right now.
Wait... waiting is a good thing.
Front... to the front, Gary.
[Princess Ji Hyo starting off by
training Giraffe idiot first?]
What is going on?
Scary, isn't she, Uee?
That's Song Ji Hyo.
[Counterattack!
Uee attacks Gary's headgear.]
[Finally, a battle between
the two princesses!]
Kwang Soo, turn!
Let go... just let go.
[But to let her down like that...]
I couldn't let you go.
- I couldn't let you down like that.
- Ji Hyo...
You can see the old Ji Hyo coming out
to play right now, can't you?
Let go, let go right now, Kang Gary!
[The bully Ji Hyo?]
Let go... Let go, Kang Gary!
I thought my upper body was going to
break off from my lower body.
- Is the bully going to make an appearance?
- You should talk it out instead.
[You should just talk it out...]
This really looks like a battle
between lovers.
The game is starting to get
a little more heated.
[Final round reconvenes!]
- No, don't move!
- Your move earlier was pretty good.
[Ji Hyo once again tries her
training tactics on the Idiot Giraffe.]
[Ace not letting the Giraffe off easy!]
Ji Hyo really is something else.
Kwang Soo bit me!
Lee Kwang Soo!
[Carnivorous giraffe not letting
go of his meal.]
How dare you bite your older sister!
This is an entertaining final round!
- Uee! Fighting!
- Fighting!
[Full of energy and ferocity
just as a final round should be!]
- Concentrate.
- To the right... move to the right.
Kwang Soo, to the right a bit.
[Princess Uee directing in a calm manner.]
- Gary, to the right!
- Wait...
[Ace Ji Hyo moves in like lightening
to get a grasp on Uee's sleeve!]
[Uee not being able to use either of her
arms is in extreme danger!]
Turn... Gary, turn.
There she goes!
[Uee counterattacks with
Ji Hyo's name tag in her grasp!]
[In a blink of an eye, Ji Hyo also gets
Uee's name tag and attacks simultaneously!]
[Who'll be faster?]
[That's our Ace!
Blue Idiot Team's Princess Ji Hyo wins!]
[Awesome, Monday Couple!]
[The ultimate final round.
Current score is even at 1:1.]
[The fate of the victory
rests on this final round!]
[Green Idiot Team's Jae Suk and Uee vs.
Blue Idiot Team's Ha Ha and Ji Hyo.]
[One of these two teams will become
the ultimate Idiot General and Fair Princess!]
[The fateful final round - Start!]
- Hang on.
- Turn to the right.
[Princess Ji Hyo attacking as predicted.]
Turn to the left!
[The battle could come to an end
at any moment!]
- Jae Suk, to the left!
- Ha Ha, move!
[So close! Almost had it,
but falls down instead.]
What the heck is going on with me?
I'm supposed to be a princess today!
That's why we're the idiots.
[Now that we think about it,
the men are the idiots...]
[For one last time,
restart the final round!]
Okay, I'll guide you.
Jae Suk... to the left.
[Both teams are being more cautious
this time around.]
- To the left... go to the left.
- Almost there.
To the right... go to the right.
[The two princesses are at it!]
[Strength vs. strength!]
Jae Suk, take one step forward.
Just take one step forward.
[At the same time again!]
[Both start ripping it off
exactly at the same moment!]
[Unbelievable... Uee gets it first!]
[Green Idiot Team's Princess Uee wins!]
- She's not to be messed with.
- You're a champion, Uee!
Yes, we won!
[The Fair Princess and the Green Idiot Team
finally wins the long drawn out battle.]
[In midst of all that happiness,
the fair princess was caught in a quandary.]
[Because she had to pick just one
idiot between her two idiots.]
Princess Uee can go on and
put her ring on first.
[Princess Uee puts her ring on first...]
And you can choose your idiot,
and put the ring on him yourself.
[Who will she give the other ring to?]
- Jae Suk, no matter who she chooses...
- Of course!
- Let's be cool about this, okay?
- Of course, we will.
- Be happy for the winner?
- What else would we be?
Uee...
Why are you being like that?
This is an important moment for us!
Stop being so creepy,
and just stand still.
[Putting on what they think to be their most
attractive expression on their faces.]
[Who will be the ultimate Idiot General?]
[Who will Princess Uee choose?]
[After thinking long and hard,
Princess Uee...]
[Puts the gold ring on Idiot Kwang Soo!]
[The fair princess chooses idiot Kwang Soo!]
What happened, Uee?
The fair princess... chose...
Idiot Giraffe...
[Idiot Kwang Soo and the Fair Princess who
became the fairest in the Running Kingdom...]
[lost their sight to greed over
the gold rings...]
[and soon went on their own
separate ways.]
Mom...
This fairytale book is weird!
Subtitles by DramaFever