Running Man
[All secrets are hidden in the numbers.]
[Five numbers cloaked in secrecy...]
[Get it wrong... and you'll disappear.]
[Must solve the secret behind the numbers.]
[There's only one chance.]
The answer lies within today's mission.
[The answer lies within today's mission?]
- I think we need to look at the numbers.
- 14357?
[In that case...]
[The number that has been
stamped on their hands...]
Make sure to remember that number.
What if I add all the numbers together?
[Plus 11...]
[One by one...]
What are these numbers?
Do I pick one of them?
[Bicycle locker within the train station.]
[The number that they spent
all day chasing after...]
[That number is none other than...]
[But I was still unaware until
this morning.]
[Just what fate awaited us...]
['S' Sports Center in Sangam
this morning.]
He looks like he used to when he first
started making his appearance on X-Man.
[The Golden Prince of the Variety World
makes his comeback.]
[Seung Gi seems to have gotten younger
since the last time they've seen him.]
- I can feel the muscles in your arms.
- I just have a thick layer of clothes on.
I wore a lot of layers
because it's so cold out.
[Let me check Kang Gary out too.]
[Shapeless older brothers getting handsy
with their shapely younger brother.]
- Kang Gary is really soft, Jae Suk.
- Really?
- He's really soft.
- It's because I have a soft heart.
[Soft bodied and soft hearted Gary.]
I feel a bit nervous since
I haven't been on the show for so long.
- Why are you saying that? So unlike you.
- There's no need to be nervous.
- It's been a year since he's been on.
- Has it been a year already?
[Last visit was the 007 special episode.]
To be honest,
I still don't understand this show.
I still have no idea
how the 007 episode ended.
It's not just you, Seung Gi.
That episode is a mystery to us all.
Who's that?
[Just then...]
[Another bashful guest makes
her appearance.]
- She looks very beautiful.
- Hello!
[Sistar's Bora.]
[Bright as sunshine Bora is here!]
It's Kwang Ja!
She must have seen last week's episode.
Kwang Ja has more fans
than I do these days.
That was awesome.
What is this?
What's going on between you two?
- Are you two dating?
- You guys are dating?
- I'm jealous.
- What's going on?
Sistar is one of my favorite girl groups.
I also asked her to join me onstage for
a segment at my recent concert as well.
- Did you dress up as a woman?
- No, I didn't dress up as a woman.
- Isn't that what you did?
- No, I didn't do that.
I stopped doing things like that.
No, I'm not doing that.
You should just give me a call.
My Sistar imitation is awesome.
- He's unbelievable.
- Jong Kook is another Sistar member.
- Jong Kook could be another Hyorin.
- Yeah, I could be Hyorin.
Do you like dressing up like a woman?
- You never used to be like that.
- I never used to, but...
Seung Gi... he's very different than he
used to be during the X-Man days.
- Bora and Seung Gi are our only guests?
- Are these two it?
- There's another one?
- We have another guest?
[There's another guest?]
She's pretty.
[Han Hye Jin- Returning as a new bride.]
[Making her return as a woman trying to
protect her family from harm in 'Warm Words'.]
Congratulations on your marriage!
- Congratulations!
- Congratulations on your marriage!
[Though a little late, we sincerely
congratulate you on your marriage!]
- It's been awhile.
- So good to see you!
Madame!
- Mrs. Ki!
- It's been so long.
- Seriously...
- We haven't seen you since Vietnam.
[Hye Jin joined them on a week-long trip
to Vietnam for the special overseas episode.]
It seriously has been so long.
- Seriously.
- Your husband is well, right?
- Did you see him in the recent game?
- Yes, he was great in it.
- He's a great soccer player.
- I saw your initials on his soccer cleats.
That's old news already.
Why do you always do that to me?
You drive me nuts with that.
[Candidate for youngest best entertainer
in history- Prince of Variety, Lee Seung Gi.]
[2012 Best actress award winner-
Goddess of spitfire, Han Hye Jin.]
[The girl who is as bright as sunshine,
no amateur to variety, Bora.]
[The ultimate race against the undisputed kings
of variety athletes is about to start now!]
What are we doing today?
Are we going to be divided into teams?
- The phone's ringing.
- I'm dying of curiosity!
- Tell us what we're doing.
- Is it a mission?
[With the sudden ringing of the phone,
men clad in all black make their appearance.]
[Pulling them away without any explanation.]
Let go of me!
You can't take me away!
I haven't done anything wrong!
[Just where are they being
taken away to?]
What is this?
[Wait! That is...]
[Morning Flying Chair.]
What is this now?
- Come on!
- You're really going to start this?
- What are you doing?
- I had my makeup done this morning!
- This is too much this early in the morning.
- Do you all see the flying chairs?
Two people need to get on those chairs and
play a round of rock, paper, scissors.
- Then what?
- The loser will be eliminated.
And the next person will take over
the empty seat to continue the game
and the person who survives to the end
without being thrown in the water wins.
So this is an all-kill method
we're playing?
Then we will now designate the order of
who will sit in the chairs first.
[Designating the order of who'll go first
through draw of the paper.]
[Who will be unfortunate enough
to go first?]
The last person will only
have to beat one person.
[Number one- Jong Kook vs.
Number Two- Seung Gi.]
- I'm so nervous.
- Seeing you nervous is making me nervous!
[Extreme nervousness.]
- The dizziness is making me dizzy.
- I feel like I'm going to get flown off this.
Just hurry up and play the game.
Are you both ready?
[Just who will be the first person to get
flown into the water by the flying chair?]
[They both throw out paper.]
If they tie,
shouldn't they both be thrown off?
That's not a bad idea.
Again.
Rock, paper, scissors.
[Kkuk loses.]
[Immediate flight into the air.]
[Kkuk demonstrates the flying chair.]
[Ten years shaved off of his life.]
[But, just then...]
[A man clad in black appears
out of nowhere again...]
- What is that?
- He's being taken away.
- Why is he being taken away?
- Where is he being taken to?
- Why?
- He's being taken away somewhere.
- Is he being dragged away?
- He's being dragged away somewhere.
Where are you taking him?
[Hauled away the moment
he's catapulted into the water.]
Are we teamed up with those guards?
- Where are they taking me?
- They're taking you away somewhere.
[Just where is he being led away to?]
I want to stay and watch!
- Where is he being taken away to?
- Bye!
This really is like a mystery theater.
If you're going to do this,
make it so that we never see him again.
[Number four- Kwang Soo.]
Why did you do that?
[He was just trying to
help you onto the platform...]
Good job, Seung Gi.
I'm going to bet everything I have
on winning this round.
He's always betting
everything he has these days.
That's because Kwang Soo doesn't have
all that much to his name yet.
I want to beat Kwang Soo at least
before I'm thrown into the water.
[Seung Gi showing an unusual streak of
competitiveness against Kwang Soo.]
Kwang Soo tends to be
a bit of a dirty player.
- You have to watch yourself, Seung Gi.
- No hesitating to test me, okay?
Okay.
Let's play like real men.
[Huh?]
Okay, I'm ready.
- Didn't you already do it?
- No, we're going to start now.
[What just happened?]
No, that was just me showing you
that's how the game is going to be played.
- No, that was our game, and you lost.
- You guys already played your hand.
[Kwang Soo loses.
Plenty of witnesses to testify.]
- No, we didn't see it.
- Yes, you did!
- Rewind the tape.
- There's no need to rewind anything.
- What just happened?
- We didn't see what happened.
No, but we didn't give you the cue
to start playing rock, paper, scissors.
[Excited and relieved Giraffe.]
Fine, then instead of rock paper scissors,
let's play mook-jji-ppa.
[What?
All of a sudden?]
I was going to say that from the beginning,
but you interrupted me.
Seriously... you don't know how to play
a fair and clean game, do you?
Where have you been?
You know I've always played dirty.
Let's just be honest here.
I told you that he plays dirty.
- Let's just go for it since you admitted it.
- Okay, thanks, Seung Gi.
[Agreeing to play mook-jji-ppa
for this round only.]
Okay, here we go.
Rock, paper, scissors.
[It would've been Seung Gi's win if it
had been just plain rock, paper, scissors.]
Mook, jji!
[Giraffe's forceful attack is making
Seung Gi's hand shake in fear.]
[Seung Gi loses.]
[Ah...]
[I, in the end...
fell for Giraffe's dirty ploys.]
[Tricky Giraffe wins!]
That's too bad, Seung Gi.
It was your win in the beginning.
I really wanted to beat Kwang Soo.
- Sorry, Seung Gi.
- I really wanted Seung Gi to win!
[Next up is Number Five, Hye Jin.]
I'm really nervous!
[So nervous!]
The marriage has made her weak!
You're not normally like this, Hye Jin.
- You're going to have to re-train yourself.
- I have a family to think about now.
What is she saying?
[All-kill flying chair,
Hye Jin vs. Kwang Soo.]
Wait!
Wait a minute!
Let's just do mook-jji-ppa instead, please!
[The most entertaining moment
we've seen in rock, paper, scissors.]
Rock, paper, scissors!
[Hello, Toad Kwang.]
Toad Kwang made his comeback.
[Right around the same time...]
[The first victim of the flying chair
has been dragged out of the building.]
What's going on here?
What is that?
It's not like we're at a club or something.
What's this?
14357?
- Make sure to memorize it.
- This number?
What is this?
What's 14357?
What's the meaning of this number?
[What's the hidden mystery
behind these numbers?]
Make sure to memorize those numbers.
Your mission today
revolves around those numbers.
[Their mission for the day is
related to those mysterious numbers.]
[The five digit number that is
surrounded in a cloud of mystery.]
[Their path starts with these numbers.]
Do you see the doors in front of you
that are marked with the numbers 1,4,3,5,7?
Pick one of those numbers, and
go wait behind the door of your choosing.
Go.
What could these numbers mean?
14357?
[Pick one of the numbers,
and wait behind the door.]
Do I just pick whichever one I want?
You have to think carefully
about your selection.
[What is the meaning behind those doors?
Must be chosen with caution?]
[Jong Kook chooses door number five.]
I...
I choose number three.
[Ji Hyo chooses door number three.]
What is this?
Is this how our teams are chosen?
[Items necessary to carry out their missions
are found in each room?]
No matter how many times I come on this
show, I still can't seem to figure it out.
Rock, paper, scissors!
[Hye Jin is in the midst of experiencing the
flying chair for the first time in her life.]
Are you okay, Hye Jin?
[Frozen as ice.]
- Hye Jin, are you okay?
- Is he the lifeguard?
She's back.
She's back after being dumped in the water.
[The old fearless Hye Jin makes her
comeback after getting dunked in the water.]
This is seriously driving me crazy.
Why is Suk Jin on such a winning streak?
I'm going to do this today.
- Let's do this!
- Let's end this!
[Will it be Suk Jin with this
feisty spirit of late...]
[Or will it be Ha Ha,
who just needs a win?]
Let's do this!
Rock, paper, scissors!
- What is it?
- What?
- It's a draw.
- What the heck!
[Their hearts are about to drop
from the level of anticipation and anxiety.]
I'm going to throw out the 'rock' again.
I shouldn't have said anything!
I'm just confusing myself!
Take it back.
I'm taking it back.
[Starting to show some strange behaviors
from extremely high level of anxiety.]
What are you doing there by yourself?
Rock, paper, scissors!
[Biting down... with all their might.]
[Another draw!]
- I really hate this!
- Just send one of us flying already.
I don't even care if I win anymore.
[The winning of the Flying Chair game will be
given an unbelievable advantage to the race.]
[Let's really finish this right now!]
Rock, paper, scissors!
[Number ten, Haroro is the ultimate winner!]
I did it!
I won!
- Thank you.
- You are going to be given an amazing hint.
I have never seen my coordinator
looking so happy before.
Come here, Sung Chan!
Come on!
[An emotional hug with his coordinator
over his unexpected win.]
Ha Ha, you can go off to the dressing room
on your own without an escort.
Yes, I understand.
Thank you.
[Rendered speechless from his excitement.]
Why are we being
dragged around like this all day?
[Meanwhile, Kwang Soo like others
is being dragged away...]
[There he goes again...]
Kwang Soo.
- You chose number four?
- Yes.
- Why don't you come in?
- What's going on here?
[Kwang Soo and Seung Gi in
the same room.]
What is all this?
- I don't know either.
- What are we supposed to do with this?
- You should know better than I.
- I don't really know either.
What is all this on the table?
[Since there are two of each item,
it's probably two people per team?]
Why are you acting all secretive?
Did I catch you doing something?
No, it's not like that.
- Did you get stamped too?
- Yes, I got stamped with the same numbers.
[Just what is the meaning behind the numbers
14357 that are stamped on their hands?]
I don't even try to know anymore.
- Is it money?
- Yes.
It's 20,000 won.
- Isn't that quite a bit?
- 20,000 is quite a bit for them to give us.
Do we need to go somewhere far
or something?
- With 20,000?
- You don't think?
Since one of us has to be
the leader of this team
how about since I'm the
older one here...
Of course, you should be the leader.
I felt like you were being really
rude to me earlier.
- The way you treated me...
- Are you kidding?
No, I wasn't being rude to you.
I was just saying that you're not
so easy to trust sometimes.
- Kwang Soo.
- What is all this anyways?
Why are they dragging us around
everywhere?
14... I think we should both memorize this
just in case it gets wiped off.
14357.
All these rooms look like
they're all taken already.
[It's time for Bora to
make her selection now.]
Since my name is Bora,
I'm going to go with purple.
Bye!
What is this?
Hurry up and come in since
you've already made your choice.
- What just happened?
- I was so startled.
- Were you started?
- Yes, I was.
I had no idea that someone
would be hiding in the corner.
I can't believe it's Bora.
I really must have something with Sistar.
[Following the Star of Idols episode,
he's teamed up with Sistar again.]
[Fifth member of Sistar,
Voluptuous Muscle Boy.]
[New housewife Hye Jin starting off by
checking the money in the envelop first.]
Don't you think that
this amount is too little?
Wow... look at this.
This one.
[Jae Suk picks door number one.]
[Inside, he finds Hye Jin!]
- Good luck with the mission.
- The victory will be ours.
Hye Jin's really good at doing
the missions.
[The goddess of competitiveness,
Madame Han.]
Hye Jin's competitive streak is no joke.
- I won the last time.
- You did?
I'm going to go with the pink door.
Pink.
Ugh, you startled me!
You really startled me!
It's you again?
[Unbelievable...
Monday Couple is teamed up again.]
- Why did you choose this door?
- What is this?
Since I came in at first place,
should I choose door number one?
Or should I pick lucky number seven?
Since I came in at first place...
I'm going to go with door number one.
Hello!
[Two people per team-
But all the other rooms are already filled.]
What is this?
[First place winner, Haroro keeps on being
refused admittance to all the rooms.]
- Lucky number seven!
- Come in.
- Wait.
- Hey!
- What is this!
- Come in!
This is the only spot left available.
Hey, I just got done experiencing
the same thing that you did.
This is the only room left.
- Today?
- Today is the day.
[Now that they think about it, they're the
1st and 2nd winners of flying chair game.]
- Seriously!
- Okay.
Has everyone finished equipping yourselves
with the items that you have been given?
[All the teams have been now chosen.]
Here is today's race.
Today's race is, The Number.
[The Number Race.]
You may start off to your next location with
the number you've been given and a keyword.
Once you succeed the mission that
you're given at each location...
you will be given the keyword
for the next location.
- Really?
- You have to complete the mission...
to get to the final location
as quickly as you can.
The member who came in at first place
during the Flying Chair Game...
and also the member who came in
at second place...
Up to the third place winner
will be given a special hint.
[Special hints to be given out to
Ha Ha, Suk Jin and Gary.]
[The keyword to help them find
their way to the first location.]
This is so disappointing.
You don't have any hints for people who
went first, second or third?
- Nothing for fifth place winner?
- No, nothing.
You may now try to deduct your guess,
and find your way to the next location.
14357?
[What is the third place winner hint
that Gary and Ji Hyo have been given?]
[Bus]
[Bus?]
Could it be a bus number?
All the buses are numbered.
- Bus station?
- Is that what yours says?
[Second winner hint- Station.]
[First winner hint- Bus station.]
- This is the best hint.
- All we needed was your hint.
[Prime hint- It seems as though 'Bus Station'
is the only hint they need!]
Let's go.
[Suk Jin and Ha Ha are on their way
with their hints!]
[14357... and Bus Station?]
Suk Jin... let's just sneak away
right now.
Let's just sneak away before
anyone notices.
[Married Men-Cross!
Sneaking away in the midst of confusion.]
- Bus station.
- Is that what you have too?
[An extreme advantage over all the others
with the hints that they've been given.]
- If others notices that we're leaving...
- What if they try to take it away from us?
- That team is leaving.
- They're leaving? Then let's go too.
[Jong Kook and Bora are trying to
follow in their trail.]
Is Running Man changing their theme
to using their brains now?
No, not at all.
- 14357 is the hint to the next location?
- That number sounds so familiar to me.
- I know.
- Me too. That number sounds familiar to me.
[The number sounds familiar to them?]
Isn't 14357 the number to our
Foreign Cultural Administration?
- I don't know if it is or not.
- There you go acting all smart again.
Where are you getting the
Foreign Cultural Administration from?
[Gary and Ji Hyo head off to the bus station
with the hint that they've been given.]
- What could it be?
- Where did everyone go? Ugh, it's so cold.
- Bus?
- Could it be a bus?
[Bus number, 14357?]
[Carefully scanning the bus directory list.]
[Why do things like this keep
on happening to them?]
Why do you mean, skills? What skills are
required in rock, paper, scissors?
We have to be careful.
[Run!]
[But the couple on the chase seems
to be full of ease.]
[Immediately flags down an empty cab.]
- Can you turn around?
- Yes, please turn around.
- Can you follow that taxi?
- We have to follow that car.
What could 14357 mean?
That's the car up ahead.
Just follow that cab.
You have to stay right on their tail.
[Meanwhile, these two couples are walking
around aimlessly without a single hint.]
But seeing how we were given
the bus card...
[Now that they think about it, the bus card
was given out with their money...]
I think it's a bus number.
- It's a bus number.
- You think?
[Anyone see a bus numbered 14357?]
I doubt it's that simple.
- Does it mean take bus 14 three times?
- Maybe it's bus number 143?
[Zero hint group thinking of
everything they can think of.]
We have to put our heads together since
none of us know anything.
I feel like my mind goes blank
whenever I come on Running Man.
My mind just stops working.
We're always doing these tough missions
whenever Seung Gi comes on the show.
- It's always a mystery.
- Seriously.
14357.
- Should we go ask the city office?
- Should we?
Whether or not there's a bus
with that number?
- The office is right there.
- What?
The office is right here.
- Is this the city office?
- Is that what they said?
- You're from Yongsan, right?
- Yes.
Then you can't go inside the
Mapo City office.
Do you think...
you think they'd be that petty?
Excuse me.
I'm sorry, but is there an office where we
can find out different bus numbers?
- Yes, we can look it up.
- Can you look it up on the internet for us?
- 14357.
- We can't, but they can look it up, right?
[Rule- Even though they can't look it up
themselves, they are allowed to ask for help.]
[What would searching '14357' result in?]
[Something seemed to have popped up?]
- I think it's a bus station number.
- Bus station in Sangam-dong?
[The mystery behind 14357...]
[The number to a bus station?]
- Maybe it's the bus station we were by?
- It's the bus station in Sangam-dong!
Come take a look, Hye Jin.
[As guessed, they make a run for it!]
Thank you!
Excuse me!
[14357 is the public bus station
in Sangam-dong?]
- Are you sure?
- I'm sure! Want to take the cab?
- I'm sure!
Can I ask you something?
- Where's Sangam-dong bus station?
- You're asking everyone in sight?
- You have to go that way.
- That way?
[Asking nearby pedestrians where
the bus station is located.]
They're already going!
- Thank you!
- Run!
[It's quite the distance...]
You know how to work those women.
[Could it be from his most recent trips
with older women?]
- They cussed me out the whole time.
- Seriously?
Jae Suk, I thought you said it was
Foreign something or other?
[Yoo Hyuk's know-it-all personality becoming
a subject of laughter for the new bride.]
I thought you said it was
the Cultural Heritage something.
I thought it was the number of some cultural
artifact item that we needed to recover.
[That's 74434...]
- I think we have to cross over.
- How do we get to the other side?
There's goes Seung Gi with
his questions again.
- Yes, thank you.
- Why are you asking so many questions?
- Didn't I tell you that I was the leader?
- Huh?
[It seems to be reversed.
Team member Seung Gi leading Leader Kwang.]
If you have a question,
then just come to me and ask.
The subordinate has to bring
the leader useful information
and you can make the final decisions.
- Where's Sangam-dong bus station?
- Sangam-dong Center?
- No, the bus station.
- Oh, that's over that way.
Thank you.
- Make sure to keep this in mind.
- Okay.
You have to tell me everything and
get my approval before you do anything.
- That's going to take too long.
- What?
Then why... then why am I even the leader?
You're the one doing everything,
and I'm just following you.
You're the leader of this team.
Have you ever seen the captain out in front?
The captain always stays behind his men.
I'm going to ask one other person where
the station is. Hang on a minute.
[Questioner Seung Gi off to ask
someone else.]
I told you to consult with me
before you go off, didn't I?
Wow, you're so good looking.
Why do you act like they were
only talking to you
when they were saying handsome?
Weren't they speaking to both of us?
- They could've just been talking to me.
- Yes, you're right.
[Gary and Ji Hyo are still mindlessly
staring at the bus terminal directory.]
[Wait... those numbers...]
Look at the bus station number.
It starts off with a 14.
[The bus station number starts off with 14!]
Then that means we need to find a
bus station with the number, 14357.
Should we call the office of transportation?
Yes, we're in front of the World Cup Stadium,
and we need to get to station number 14357.
- That team just needs to follow us.
- I know, it's so annoying.
It's so annoying.
[Taking a close look at the bus terminal
numbers as the hint indicates...]
[Easily able to depict that the hint, 14357
is the number to a bus station!]
- We have to go to 14357.
- We need to get to 14357.
- 14357. We need to check all the stations.
- Please take us there.
- 14... that's 146.
- We need to keep going.
We need to find 14357, but that's 14164.
[14357 has to be around here somewhere...]
How about... we call Dasan Call Center?
- We can try calling them.
- They can tell us anything.
- Yes, we're in Sangam-dong right now.
- Is that... 14344?
Yes, I was inquiring about the bus stations.
What do the numbers 14-357
stand for at a bus station?
That's the Sangam-dong
Community Bus Center ID?
[When all the hints 14357, bus, station
are put together...]
[It stands for Sangam-dong
Community Bus Center ID!]
[The two weakest couples of the group are
still searching for Sangam-dong Bus Center.]
- Gary!
- This isn't it.
What's that?
Why are you standing there?
Ji Hyo and I were just
taking a break and talking.
- Who were you talking to?
- Just a friend.
[Gary trying to lie about having been on
the phone with the Office of Transportation.]
- What are you guys doing here?
- Nothing.
They said they're going to
call us back.
Yeah, they're going to call us back.
- Where are we supposed to go?
- We don't know either.
[Leader Kwang questioning Gary and Ji Hyo
who was given a hint to the location.]
- We seriously don't know.
- You still haven't figured out 14357?
- No.
- We don't know.
What is that?
You got a call.
What are you doing, Leader Kwang?
[Team member Seung Gi coming around
to urge on his Leader Kwang.]
What are you doing?
Are you a minion or a leader?
What do you mean, a minion?
Thank you. Then can we
take the bus from this station?
Yes, thank you.
- What did they say?
- Sangam-dong Community Bus Center.
[Having figured out where to go from
having called the Office of Transportation.]
Does this bus go to
Sangam-dong Community Bus Center?
- Are they leaving?
- No, we're trying to see what we can find.
[Monday Couple getting on the bus and
trying to thwart the other team.]
We don't know what's going on,
so let's just try to figure it out first.
[Clueless Kwang Soo and Seung Gi
are unsure of what they should do.]
[Sangam-dong Community
Bus Center- Bus station.]
- Thank you.
[Could this be the scene of
the mysterious 14357?]
- Do I just swipe it here?
- Yes, you're all set.
- Our plan succeeded, Bora.
- Jong Kook.
- Let's seriously work together to the end.
- Yes, that's what we'll have to do.
- Let's work together.
- Until we're the last two teams standing.
You still don't know for sure where
we're supposed to go, right?
Where is it?
[There it is!]
[This must be the place!
There's the mission envelope!]
- What's the hint?
- We don't know it yet either.
- Everyone grab one.
- What's the hint?
We have to figure this out.
[They joined alliances just a moment ago,
but they're already suspecting each other.]
- What does 14357 stand for?
- That's the number of the bus station.
- Look here. 14357.
- You can see the number 14357 right here.
- There's a dash.
- I do see the dash now.
[They found it!]
- They're all the same, right?
- I think all the hints are the same.
[First keyword- Plus 11.]
[What does the keyword, plus 11 mean?]
- How do we find out?
- There's another way of finding out.
- Want to pay for our cab?
- You'll tell us in the cab?
- Are you going to pay for our cab?
- Okay, we'll pay it.
- Okay, deal.
- You'll pay for our taxi?
- You're dead if it turns out to be nothing.
- What do you mean, nothing?
[What could 'plus 11' mean?]
[Could it be that plus 11 means 14-368?]
This is unbelievable.
He's getting a free ride.
Seriously... this is really unfair to us.
Yes, hello.
14-368... Can you tell us where that is?
It doesn't exist?
[A dead-end.]
Then... how about 25-357?
Where's 25-357?
- 25 dash 357.
- Yes, does 25-357 exist?
- It's in Kangdong-gu?
- Kangdong-gu?
25-357 is Kangdong-gu?
[If it's Kangdong-gu...]
[It's 30km away in the opposite direction.]
[How are they going to get themselves
out of this impasse?]
Hey, this is 14-980.
[Jae Suk and Hye Jin having gotten lost
on their way to the mission location.]
Can you tell us where Sangam Bus Center is?
It's across the street from
the elementary school.
Ah, across the street from
the elementary school?
- It's too far to walk, right?
- Yes, it's far.
If we were to get in right now,
would you be able to take us there?
- You have to go across the street.
- Across the street? Okay.
[It seems to be in the opposite direction.]
You didn't even ask if he could take us,
but you asked if he'd turn the car around.
Then he replies back by telling you
to go across the street.
[Cool enough to tell them to go
across the street.]
I thought that he'd give us
a ride for sure.
[Monday Couple also having gotten lost
on their way to the station.]
Thank you.
- Are you not going to buy any oranges, Gary?
- You want some?
Can we have 13 of those oranges?
[Busy buying delicious looking oranges.]
Since I'm a fan of Ji Hyo's...
I'll give you extra as a bonus.
[Giving Ji Hyo extra oranges
for being her fan.]
- Thank you.
- Just get married.
- Excuse me?
[He seems to think that they make
a good looking couple.]
That's what she wants right now.
- Please stay healthy this winter.
- Thank you.
[Monday Couple's never-ending popularity.]
[Running into Jae Suk and Hye Jin
who are also lost.]
You two are acting like newlyweds.
Some elder just told us to get married.
But... oh, it's here!
Where are you going?
Let's go together!
[Taking the taxi to go somewhere?]
Sorry, please excuse me.
[Monday Couple feeling
the urgency of the situation.]
Please take us there.
[Kwang Soo and Seung Gi having arrived
at Sangam Community Bus Station.]
We're paying Dutch next time, okay?
I want some sweet fish bread.
Want to get one?
Want to each get one?
- Is it possible to get 1,000 won worth?
- 1,000 won worth?
- It's just for the two of us.
- Thank you.
- I'll treat.
- Okay.
- There you go.
- Thank you, and good luck selling.
- Wow, that's really good.
- That's good.
[The deliciousness that melts
all the chill away.]
Where's the station?
[But where's the Sangam Community Center?]
What's this?
It's 14-286.
But our number is 14-357.
Look at what happened from me
having listened to you.
You're the one who said we had to go
to the community center.
But this is the community center.
- Do you know where 14-357 is?
- I'm sorry, excuse me.
Can you look up something on the web for us?
We're not allowed to search for ourselves.
Bus station number 14-357.
[Looking up the bus station location
with the number 14-357 once again.]
- Thank you, we can't do that ourselves.
- It shows up as Sangam Community Center.
[Giving away a sweet fish bread as
a token of their appreciation.]
I'm the one who gave you the bread, but
you're giving all your attention to Seung Gi?
- Where is it?
- I'm the one who gave you that bread.
Hold on, Kwang Soo.
- Did you just shush me?
- No.
- It seems to be that way.
- Right? We have to go up a bit more?
- No, is it that way?
- Yes, it's that way.
That way, right?
Thank you so much.
- That way?
- Yes, thank you.
- Enjoy the sweet fish bread.
- Thank you.
Kwang Soo, that was the piece with
the most amount of red beans in it.
- Really?
- Yes.
Wait, sorry!
[He's going back?]
Can you break it off in half
and let us have a piece?
Giving something away and taking it back
is the worst thing you can do!
[Ultimately takes back half the bread
that he initially gave away himself.]
- There really is a ton of red beans in this!
- Did you get half of it back?
I just asked him to give me the tail half.
I never knew that all the bus stations
had their own ID's.
Me too.
This is my first time seeing it.
Here it comes.
There's Gary and Ji Hyo.
- So we're not very late ourselves then.
- I think so.
Too bad.
- We're heading to the next mission?
- Seriously?
Taking the bus made you late.
You should've taken a taxi.
- Really?
- Yes.
- We're okay.
- We don't worry about things like that.
- Are you eating oranges?
- They stopped by for oranges?
- We stopped by to have some oranges.
- It's over that way.
[Starving Leader Kwang
going after the oranges.]
- Where did you say it was?
- No, they haven't done the mission yet.
What are you doing, Seung Gi?
[What... what are they doing?]
What are you guys doing!
- My hands were too dirty.
- After what you did with me last week?
- Why are you getting jealous over this?
- I don't know, but I'm jealous.
This is the place.
[Finally!]
- What is it?
- This is it.
What is this?
[Plus 11]
- Do we add?
- 14357!
68.
Then isn't it... 14-368?
[As others before him,
his guess is 14-368.]
- 68.
- Then is that where we go?
- There it is!
- Jae Suk!
[Jae Suk and Hye Jin finally making their
way over to 14-357.]
- I can't believe we all ran into each other.
- Why are our three teams constantly together?
[Plus 11...]
I don't know where to add
the number.
Let's just get on that bus.
- We can just take another taxi then.
- Okay.
[Their plan is to grab a taxi
whenever they feel lost.]
[Hye Jin counting up the stations.]
[Could it mean 11 stations away at
Chongkiwa Gas Station?]
Excuse me, but can I ask you a question?
We're trying to look up different
bus stations on the internet.
Can you look it up on the internet for us?
- I see a bus coming.
- 14-368.
There's a bus coming.
- Do you see it?
- No, it's not popping up.
Then how about 25-357?
- Does that not exist either?
- No.
Then this must not be it.
- Okay, thank you.
- Thank you!
We should get on too.
Excuse me, coming through.
- Let's go to the eleventh station.
- Eleventh station?
What are you guys doing here?
[The two couples are back
together again.]
Let me tell you why we're here.
We got some help from others,
and we tried adding 11 to the ID.
- But nothing turned up.
- Meaning it's not a bus station.
Since we told you guys that,
why don't we work together now?
We were going to go to the
eleventh station anyway.
You guys seem to be doing this scientifically,
but we're going by our gut feeling.
If we get somewhere and feel that it's wrong,
then we get on a taxi right away.
But whether it's scientific, or by gut,
we seem to be on the same path.
But you know what's really fascinating?
We all move separately...
We're all moving on our own, but how
do we always end up together again?
I guess it means that we're all along
the same intelligence level.
I guess none of us
are especially smart.
- There it is!
- Where?
- You can let us out here.
- There it is!
[Chungkiwa gas station bus stop-
There's an 'R' box at the station!]
[Ten minutes prior.]
Is it eleventh from where
we're standing?
[Jong Kook and Bora having added 11
from station 14-357.=
Isn't that it?
Chungkiwa station?
[Having decided to check out
Chungkiwa Station first.]
- Chungkiwa Station.
- Why don't we start from there?
Okay.
Let's go.
Did you guys figure anything out?
- Get out of my way.
- Why? I thought we were working together.
- Follow us.
- Hurry up and get in the car.
Follow them!
[The Purple and Yellow couple...
Sniping and being helpful at the same time.]
Wait, then is it 368?
That would be 368 if you add 11 to 357.
- Do you see it?
- Yeah, we see it.
[Having found their way to
the right spot!]
It's yeot!
- Wow, that looks good.
- That look so good.
- There it is!
- Where?
- I don't see anything!
- No, it's here.
- It's not there?
[Discovers the mission envelope.]
Guess the number of people that will be
getting off from the arriving bus.
One person must do standups while holding the
other in the amount that they guess wrong.
You have to guess the number of people
getting off from the arriving bus.
- Do we have to do it in order of arrival?
- In order of arrival?
[Guess the number of people who will be
getting off at this bus station.]
You must be carrying the other
person while you guess.
- Really?
- Seriously?
- Sorry.
- No, it's okay.
- Want to play for it?
- No, just get on.
- I'll do it next time.
- Are you on my back yet?
Okay, jump on.
One, two, three.
Okay, tell me your guess.
- Zero.
- One person.
- I think it's just going to pass us by.
- Someone's going to have to get off.
There it is!
One person.
It's stopping.
I know it's stopping,
but just keep going now.
[Just how many people will
get off the bus?]
[Just how many?
It seems like some will be getting off...]
[Both teams are wrong!
Four people get off the bus!]
- I think I've got it figured out now.
- Okay, I know now.
[Penalty for having gotten it wrong is to do
stand and sit ups five times.]
Three.
Four.
Okay, just one more!
- Five!
- Okay.
- Let's go with two next time.
- Two?
[Jae Suk, Hye Jin, Kwang Soo, and
Seung Gi are still on the bus.]
Hye Jin told me that she was already dating
her husband when she went to Vietnam with us.
- Really?
- That's right.
She told me that she would be on the phone
while the rest of us were sleeping.
That really makes me mad.
- I had no idea.
- Even though she's tired, she won't sleep.
I remember. You would
always fiddle with your cellphone.
I'd always just wait for the moment
when the rest of you would fall asleep.
[But why is he getting angry?]
- Did you like Hye Jin?
- No, that's not it.
[It must've been a dream of his?]
-Then did you make a confession?
- No, I didn't do that.
I remember him paying extra
attention to Hye Jin back then.
- I remember he was Vietnam's Prince.
- That's right.
When all those Vietnamese people were
constantly cheering Kwang Soo on
I remember him always
looking towards Hye Jin.
[Seems as though his random popularity
made him believe he had a chance.]
There was a time back when I had the chance
to play soccer with Ki Sung Yong once.
- Yeah.
- It was just for a moment.
He's really good, and he's really big.
[That's because he's a soccer player...]
- What are you talking about, Seung Gi?
- He was really good at it.
- He met you guys before too.
- You're right.
- Look at Ji Sung.
- He played with you once in China.
- I remember that.
- When you missed your penalty kick.
Why do you have to bring that up?
- You missed your penalty kick?
- He missed that easy shot.
I missed by hitting the goal post.
I didn't completely miss it.
They took my glasses away and I couldn't see.
I'm lucky I was even able to get that close.
He was so nervous that his face
literally shrunk in on itself.
He was so nervous.
- Should I show these guys the picture?
- Let us see.
It's a picture of Kwang Soo that
was published in the newspaper.
Look at that, Seung Gi.
- Your husband was standing behind me.
- Did you get hit on the head?
[Looking as though he was hit
pretty hard in the head.]
- There's Ki Sung Yong.
- I see that.
How did you get your face to do that?
I've never paid such close attention to the
number of people getting off the bus before.
- Here it comes!
- Zero!
- Two people!
- Zero people.
- See? There's no one on the bus?
- No one's on the bus?
[Just how many will there be?]
[Zero- No one is getting off!]
Zero!
[Married Men- Cross!]
- Zero? Want to go with that again?
- Okay, let's do that.
- Give us your final answer.
- Zero people.
This is where we're supposed to go?
[Ha Ha's shop]
- Let's go.
- Let's hurry.
- Call us!
- Purple-Yellow Team are as one!
What should we do, Bora?
[How many people will get off
the bus this time?]
- No one!
- There's no one!
[No one's getting off this time!]
- We succeeded.
- You can let me down.
Your next stop is Chungkiwa Station.
This is it.
I see it.
I see the red box.
We have to swipe our card when
we get off.
[Swiping their card on their way out
of the bus as well.]
Thank you.
Guess the number of people
getting off the arriving bus.
[Guess the number of people
getting off the arriving bus?]
- With the other person on the back.
- Get on.
[Get your teammate on your back.]
- They're about to get off.
- Take your guess now.
- Red Team can guess first.
- Two.
- One, two, three.
- One.
- Please.
- You have to stay in that position.
- In this position?
- You have to stay like that.
- Okay, take a look.
- Okay.
[Huh?]
[Of all people, it had to be Gary, Ji Hyo
and their staff getting off.]
Why did it have to be you guys
and the staff members of all people?
[These two have no idea what's going on.]
[Time for the penalty.]
Three, four, five.
Why did it have to be our staff members
of all people?
- What do we have to do?
- Guess the number of people getting off.
That's why the name of the game is,
in the order of arrival.
[Expert in guessing things like this.
Was this game created for Gary?]
Ji Hyo's gotten much lighter.
- I've gotten lighter?
- Yeah, you've gotten much lighter.
- On the count of three, Song Ji Hyo.
- Two people.
- Show with your fingers.
- How many are you guessing, Hye Jin?
[Jae Suk and Hye Jin- One.]
[Kwang Soo and Seung Gi- One.]
- Here it comes!
- Please!
- Please let it be two!
[One couple wanting two,
and two couples wanting one.]
- Please, just one!
- Is no one getting off?
- Oh!
- No!
[Just how many people will be
getting off?]
[There's one...]
[And one more person.]
[Two people gets off the bus.]
[Gary and Ji Hyo guess correctly.]
[Time for the other two couples to do
their penalty for getting it wrong.]
What are you doing?
You have to go down lower.
[Gains the next mission card.]
We have no luck.
You guys at least switch back and forth.
- Want to switch?
- No, it's okay.
[Seoul Mapo district.]
- Is it here?
- Yes, thank you.
[Suk Jin and Ha Ha arrives
at their next destination.]
Thank you.
Let's go quickly!
- We're here at the right place.
- We're here.
What's this?
They're boiling something.
- What's this?
- What is this?
It's the menu.
What is it they're boiling?
[Hold hands and with your free hands,
peel the boiled potato.]
I bet it's hot.
I bet it's real hot.
[Probably]
We did this once back in the day.
[Nice and warm potatoes.]
- How are we going to do this?
- We'll be better at this than they will.
- Since they're first, it'll be hotter.
- Should we go?
- One team at a time.
- But we're the same team.
- Why don't we do it together?
- Purple, Yellow! We are as one!
[Suk Jin and Ha Ha are up first.]
[What are those cards for?]
[Huh? 1.4.3.5.7?]
- This.
- That one? Okay.
[Chooses number five.]
- Number five.
- You have to eat five within a minute.
- You're joking, right?
- How can we eat all that?
How are we going to eat five?
[Trying to see through the camera
lens reflection?]
No, I didn't see.
I swear that I didn't see anything.
[Can't ever let your
guard down with Mr. Capable.]
- I can't see anything.
- We really can't see anything.
- Pick one
- Wow, that's really hot.
[Seven]
How are we going to do this?
[Suk Jin and Ha Ha- Five vs.
Jong Kook and Bora- Seven.]
[The two team are in the midst
of a very hot challenge.]
Let's really do it this time, Hye Jin.
Mr. Ki... you owe me dinner for this.
Mr. Ki.
[Slippery Leader Kwang.]
- You fail if you fall off.
- Fall off and you fail!
- You fail if you fall off!
- Seung Gi!
[Questioner Seung Gi barely
managing to hang onto Kwang Soo.]
- One person, right?
- Yes, one person.
[Both teams chose one person
as their answer.]
- Just one!
- One person!
[Just how many will there be?]
Don't get off!
Hye Jin... I know you wanted only one,
but you can't tell him not to get off.
[But to ask him not to get off...]
[Both teams fail.]
- Two people.
- We're going with one.
[Time for their penalty.]
- What are you doing?
- What are you doing, Seung Gi?
I feel like we'll be better with the next
challenge no matter what it is.
It would be better for you to just
give up hope of winning altogether.
Come on, Jae Suk!
Someone's about to get off.
[Current guess-
Red Team- Two vs. Green Team- One.]
Two people!
[The doors are opening...]
- Get off!
- Get off the bus!
- Please!
- One more person!
- Get off!
- Please!
[One person for now...]
[Please... just one more!]
One more person!
[Only one person gets off the bus.]
Thank you, Ma'am!
[Completely lost.]
[Darn...]
- We're ruined.
- Thank you so much!
- Thank you, Ma'am.
- Thank you.
- Have a good day.
[Kwang Soo and Seung Gi pass.]
We'll see you later, Hye Jin.
We don't know when we're
going to leave here.
[Ha Ha's shop]
- His restaurant?
- I think we may be here all night.
I'm going to take a picture.
[A picture?]
- Kwang Soo.
- Yes, Jae Suk.
[Taking revenge on all that he's had
to endure up to now?]
- Kwang Soo.
- I'm taking a picture.
Can you give me a wave or
something?
We have to get going, Kwang Soo.
- Thank you, Jae Suk.
- Okay.
Leader!
[The taxi leaves without them.]
[Leader Kwang misses the cab
from his horsing around.]
- Come on, Leader!
- Sorry, Seung Gi.
- We missed the cab.
- I'm sorry.
- Here's another one!
- Here it is.
[On to Ha Ha's shop!]
I want some potatoes.
There were five cards to begin with.
What did you pick earlier?
You chose seven, right?
We picked five at first, right?
- It means, it's 14357.
- Ah, 14357.
That means that there's
a card marked with one.
So we have to keep doing this
until we choose the one card.
[It will be to their advantage to choose
the number one card.]
You have to hold hands,
and only use your free hand.
Ready.
[Ji Hyo and Gary chose four.]
Ouch, that's hot!
We have to peel and eat this?
[Not just hot, but very hot.]
- No, it's too hot.
- Just eat it.
[Taking a huge bite with the
skin still on.]
I feel like we're seeing what we must've
looked like during the first round.
[The potatoes definitely taste
the best when they are still hot.]
Here, Ji Hyo.
Ouch, that's hot!
[The potatoes are
even hotter than their love.]
Open wide.
[Ouch, that's hot!]
That's hot.
They're getting used to the heat now.
[The heat that can be felt
throughout their whole body.]
See?
They're doing the same things that we did.
[Still wrestling over their first potato
out of four.]
Stop.
[Fail]
- Was it the same for you guys?
- We were the same way.
[Back to Jong Kook and Bora.]
It's this one.
Why aren't you letting it go?
What is it?
[Seeing them that happy means...
Could it be?]
[They only have to eat one potato!]
What are you doing?
What are you guys all doing?
[Trying to pick out the biggest
potato for them.]
- Okay, let's go with that one.
- You have to eat that at least.
[So jealous]
[Jong Kook and Bora only have
to eat one potato.]
[Even though it's just one potato,
it's still hot as ever.]
[Shoves it into his mouth.]
[Mr. Capable is knocked out
by the heat of the potato!]
30 seconds left.
- One is too easy.
- They have to succeed this time.
[If it's only one...
you can muster through it.]
[Kkuk taking care of the last piece for Bora.]
[All they have left to do is whistle.]
Ten seconds.
I don't hear any whistling.
- He has to do it again.
- I heard it.
[The sound of his whistling sounds similar
to the owner of the restaurant's voice.]
Success.
[Jong Kook and Bora succeed their mission.]
[Jong Kook and Bora win lunch money.]
After all the potatoes we just ate?
It's lunch money?
But what kind of lunch money is this?
[But something feels off with
their lunch money envelope.]
Since our theme starts with 14,
you get 1,400 won each.
Okay.
- You can give it back if you don't want it.
- No, we're very happy with it.
[Bicycle locker at the train station.]
[Just then, Kwang Soo and
Seung Gi arrive.]
- Are you hungry, Seung Gi?
- I'm starving.
[Still unaware of what the mission is,
and only focused on the eating part.]
- You're giving us four?
- You chose number four, right?
[Kwang Soo and Seung Gi pick
number four for their first draw.]
Good luck, we're going to get going.
[Jong Kook and Bora leave from
having succeeded the mission already.]
[When are we ever going to
get to leave?]
Ouch, that's hot!
Wait, Kwang Soo.
- What is this?
- Do we just eat?
[Must finish all four within a minute.]
We just eat it?
[Takes a huge bite without any hesitation.]
[Foolish Kwang Soo taking a huge bite
of the steaming hot potato.]
[An exact reminder of the giraffe
from their zoo episode.]
That's what happens.
You're going to start crying in a bit.
[Seung Gi is taking his time eating
while blowing on it to cool it down.]
[Why did you take such a
big bite like that?]
He is so odd looking.
[Just then, Jae Suk and
Hye Jin finally arrive.]
[Greeted with an odd scene
as soon as they arrive.]
[Kwang Soo and Seung Gi's
second attempt.]
[Please Kwang Soo]
[He picks the one card!]
[Leader's Kwang Soo's big contribution.]
We have to pick the biggest one.
There's no method to it,
and we just eat, right?
- We just eat, right?
- Did Jong Kook already leave?
Squish it down.
Potato pancake.
Let's turn it into a potato pancake.
[Plan is to turn it into potato pancake.]
[Plan is to thinly spread it out
so it cools down faster.]
It's so hot!
[Half breath... half spit.]
- Okay, eat it.
- Can you eat it like this?
[Pancakes are done,
and it's time to eat!]
[It seems as though they did a decent job
having cooled it down.]
[No... it's still hot.]
[But it's much more feasible now
that they only have to eat one.]
I think we can win this
on our first attempt, Hye Jin.
[In order to win during first attempt...
their only hope is to pick the one card.]
There are still some crumbs left.
[Scraping up every last bit
of the crumbs.]
He's not able to do it.
Kwang Soo can't do it.
[It's Kwang Soo's turn to whistle.]
58 seconds.
[Kwang Soo and Seung Gi succeeds!]
[Won by Kwang Soo's pick of the card,
and Seung Gi's smart plan.]
When you do it like that,
there's no need to chew.
[Did all the chewing with their fists,
so all they had left to do was swallow!]
- Not bad, right?
- That was good.
That was all Seung Gi's planning.
Then Seung Gi is the leader then?
[It seems as though
the real leader is Seung Gi.]
That's hot!
[The team in the last place still trying to
battle the potatoes' hotness.]
[Dancing machine trying to alleviate the
pain through dancing.]
[I doubt that these people... will even look
at another potato for a long while.]
[Quite a while later.]
[The two teams have arrived to share
lunch after completing the potato mission.]
Why don't you tell us something
about Mr. Ki?
- Oh, he's in Dubai right now.
- He's in Dubai.
- For the big match against Russia.
- I didn't know that.
[This episode was filmed a few days
after Korea's win again the Swiss.]
- You like Key that much?
- Yes.
[Ah... Key.. as in Sung Yong?]
- It's not 'Key', it's 'Ki'.
- But they pronounce it 'Key', right?
- In England they do.
- Yes, Key.
Can't you ever let Suk Jin
just say something?
[Even though what he's saying is right,
when it's Big-nosed Brother saying it...]
When you say, Key, it makes us
think of a SHINee member.
Then you guys were in total honeymoon
phase while you were in England?
- Yes.
- Just the two of you, right?
- I heard they were in the northern part.
- Ah, northern?
- It's cold over there.
- Yes, it's cold.
[Mr. Big-nose a.k.a. England Expert.]
- Here comes the food.
- Thank you.
You two can just snuggle together
when it gets too cold.
- Why don't you do that with your wife?
- My house is too hot.
There's no need to say that
because my house is always hot.
- It's snowing.
- Really?
- It's first snowfall.
- It is!
[Delighted by the first snowfall of 2013
during the shooting of this episode.]
You have to make your wish now.
- It's snowing.
- It's snowing!
It's first snowfall!
I can't believe you're the one I'm with
during first snowfall.
- Awesome.
- I can't believe this sudden snow.
[DJ Seung Gi taking it upon himself
to start playing Christmas carols.]
What did you say?
[Kwang-vatar speaking his special Avatar
language for the first time in a long time.]
I can't believe it's the first snowfall.
- You have a decent voice.
- This is so nice.
[The first snowfall is as beautiful
as Kwang Soo's voice.]
[Excited Giraffe.]
- I'm going to dance for a minute.
- Go ahead.
You have to pay him more for doing this.
He needs to be paid more for this.
He really does move around a lot.
Keep on moving.
[If the amount of movement is what counts,
then he's the best Korea has to offer.]
[It's a bit tight in here...
but it's still fun!]
- It's the first snowfall, Gary!
- This is first snowfall?
This is first snowfall of the year.
I'm going to make a wish.
What are you wishing for?
Don't say something about me being single,
and asking me to get married off.
I'm single too.
[Driving through the snow while
making their own separate wishes...]
Shinchon Train Station.
[Jong Kook and Bora are the first ones
to arrive at the train station.]
What is this?
[Are those hoola hoops tied up
to the bicycles?]
You have to go pick three people
out of the crowd.
[Pick three people out of the crowd.]
- Hello!
- It has to be someone light.
[Could it be a mission where a man's
strength could become useful?]
- Can you help us?
- You're so pretty.
[A sturdy looking man to
help with their mission.]
Any athletic person here?
[The sun comes back out again...]
[All five members of the team must jump
through the hoola hoop to succeed.]
- Like this?
- This?
[All five people must jump
through the hoop.]
[But then why are the hoola hoops
strapped onto the bike?]
- Okay, we'll do this one.
- Want this one?
Do you want us to unlock it?
I bet the code is 14357.
[Will that be the right number?]
[Wow- Bora unlocks the lock
on her first try!]
Do you see him getting ready?
He's tightening up his shoelaces.
[I'm ready.]
[Monday Couple is the second team
to arrive.]
[Kwang Soo and Seung Gi arrive
soon thereafter.]
Are there any thin men out here?
- You think you can do it?
- Yes.
- You think you can jump?
- Don't worry.
It's going to be a rough game.
[Thank you to all the fans who came out
on a cold day like this.]
We're going to practice.
[Team Jong Kook and Bora goes first.]
- Fighting.
- Fighting!
- Here we go.
- Okay.
[Oh... they're pretty quick.]
[No way... could they really
succeed on their first try?]
[Giraffe interrupting at a crucial moment.]
[Jong Kook and Bora fail.]
[Good job... my leader!]
One, two, three.
Challenge!
[Team Gary and Ji Hyo's challenge.]
[Even though it's a bit weak,
the hoop is going down a precise path.]
[The Giraffe sneaks in again.]
[Oh my God.]
That really could've been bad, Gary.
I was looking out for him.
There was a camera over here.
[Giraffe was just trying to
protect the camera?]
[Leader Kwang is number one when it comes
to interfering in others' success.]
- Let's get this done, Seung Gi.
- Everyone move up just a bit.
Everyone run towards the hoop
and jump with all your might.
All of you rush forward
towards the hoola hoop.
- Challenge.
- One, two, three.
- Challenge!
- Challenge.
[Ah... challenge...]
[Totally off sync right from the start.]
One, two, three.
Challenge.
Jump!
[Leader Kwang's energetic coaching.]
[Why aren't you jumping?]
[Kwang Soo and Seung Gi fail.]
- I don't think I should be coaching.
- What kind of a leader are you?
- No more interrupting.
- Okay.
He really won't interrupt this time, Bora.
I'll make sure of it.
- You promise?
- I promise.
If he interferes, then I'm not
singing with you at your concert.
Okay, I got it.
Don't make scary comments like that.
Don't make scary comments
like that to me.
What is this?
[Jae Suk and Hye Jin also arrive.]
[First and Fourth place teams seeing
each other for the first time since opening.]
- What have you guys been up to?
- We've been coming in at first place.
[Jong Kook and Bora's second attempt.]
[Oh... off to a nice start.]
[Will they really succeed this time?]
[Enraged Tiger!]
I really didn't do anything!
- I really didn't do anything!
- Yes, you did!
[Giraffe's existence is
an interference in itself?]
Let's just get this done in one shot.
[Even Jae Suk and Hye Jin unlock the
lock in one try and gets their hoop.]
[Team Gary and Ji Hyo's second attempt.]
Don't do anything funny, Kwang Soo.
[Yes... I'll try.]
[Ji Hyo runs off to stop Kwang Soo.]
[Extreme injury]
[Mr. Gary... you poor thing...]
[Delinquent Ji Hyo rears her head.]
[Trying to rehabilitate himself?]
Yes, I'm okay.
[It's just my nature.
What am I supposed to do about it?]
I apologize for my team member.
Let's try this again.
[Team Jong Kook and Bora's other attempt.]
Challenge.
[Top speed.]
[Could they succeed this time?]
[Foreigner coming to his rescue to
stop the Giraffe from interfering.]
[Jong Kook and Bora succeeds!]
[Jong Kook and Bora finishes first again!]
I'm sorry, but can you take
a picture of us?
- Take a picture of us.
- You want me to?
- Take a picture for us.
- I'm working right now.
- Seriously.
- Just three pictures.
- One, two, three.
[Thank you to all those that came out
to help us on this cold day!]
[The 'R' warehouse on the way to Ilsan.]
We need to get to Ilsan.
Can you take us to Ilsan?
[Flagging down a taxi to get to
their final location as quickly as they can.]
It feels really good
to come in at first place.
- The ending is what's important though.
- Seriously.
Things like this happen a lot.
You can start off in first place
then you lose at the end.
I feel like they can catch up to us
very quickly from that mission.
As long as they're not interrupted.
We almost succeeded several times,
but because of Kwang Soo...
He really is a strange one.
- 14357!
- 14357?
[Everything began with 14357.]
[Running Man members having started with
the number to begin their missions...]
[Just what kind of secret awaits them
at the final location?]
[Final mission location-
Arriving at the warehouse in Ilsan.]
[This seems like the warehouse...]
- Come this way.
- That way?
- What's that line for?
- Why is there a line?
- Is it distance jumping?
- What is this line for?
- You're the first ones to arrive.
- Yes.
This is your bonus hint mission.
- Do you remember the numbers you were given?
- Yes.
- What is it?
- 14357.
14357.
Therefore, it's 1.3m plus 3.57m.
What's the total?
Then that's four...
No, you have to start adding
from the back.
You have to start adding from the back
to carry the number up front.
- Then the decimal...
- You have to carry it up.
Then... is it 4.97?
4.57.
Yes, you've got it correct.
- I'm sorry.
- Didn't I tell you?
Let's not let others say that
athletes are ignorant idiots.
- I have a natural science degree.
- But I did the math in my head.
- I graduated with a natural science degree!
- I did too!
[It's nice to meet you,
fellow natural science graduate.]
You see how it's marked at 4.97?
You have to take off your shoes at
where the 'R' mark is.
If you can shoot the shoe into the goal
then you can immediately enter the final
location without having to wait for others.
This isn't hard.
Okay, just like this.
[Oh... that's pretty accurate
for his first try.]
That's right.
That's how you do it.
[Just then!]
[Kwang Soo and Seung Gi
also arrive at the warehouse!]
[Jong Kook and Bora get to re-try
by the split of a hair.]
[His true nature making him want to try
interfering their game again.]
[If he can't interrupt...]
[Then it's time to pay defense!]
[Bora beats him down to the ground!]
What did I just do?
[Jong Kook and Bora
succeeds the hint mission!]
[He's better at this than soccer?]
We won!
[Matter of urgency!
Seung Gi and Kwang Soo's turn.]
[Jong Kook and Bora enter the
final mission location.]
[How can this be?
Kwang Soo succeeds in his first attempt!]
[Kwang Soo and Seung Gi
must hurry into the warehouse!]
[Kwang Leader seems to be on
a lucky streak today!]
You're the best!
You are a true leader!
- I told you to just trust me!
- You are a true leader.
Wow, what is this?
You've made it to your final mission.
- Do you all see the number panel up there?
- Yes.
You have to go up one at a time,
and you'll only have one chance.
If you press the number, and you get it right,
then the door in front of you will open.
[A numbers riddle in front of them-
Team to guess the number correct wins.]
If you get it wrong...
just stand by and see what happens.
Okay, here's your final hint.
The answer...
is within today's mission.
[Final hint-
The answer lies within today's hint.]
[This is it... the final set of numbers
we have to guess correctly.]
- This is really hard.
- The answer lies within today's mission.
If we can it wrong on our first attempt,
can we make another attempt?
- No.
- We only get one try?
[Only one chance...
Guess the number, and your team wins!]
[Number that started with 14357...
And all the missions they've completed...]
[Just what is the final and ultimate number?]
[Meanwhile, the remaining three teams have
yet to make it inside the warehouse.]
This is all about luck.
[Jae Suk and Hye Jin succeed the mission
on their first attempt.]
He's always good at things like this.
That's unbelievable.
[Jae Suk and Hye Jin enter
final mission location.]
Okay, we're going to go in now then.
Don't think about it too much, and just do it.
You have to bounce it off the wall.
That's what I was trying to do.
I just succeeded the mission in one try.
Yes, and this is the first time we've
escaped coming in at last place.
It's very possible for you to turn this around
and become the winner.
- 14357.
Here's your final mission for today's race.
- What is it?
- It's the... Final Number.
[Final number-
Guess the correct final number!]
The answer...
The answer lies within today's mission.
[The answer lies within today's mission.]
You can go up as soon as you're ready.
[All five teams are discussing and trying
to figure out what the final number could be.]
This is crazy.
I'm not good at things like this.
I'm not good at this either.
We need to call Sherlock Holmes.
- Wow, this is hard.
- I think it's a number from 14357.
But this is really odd too.
they could've just given us the address.
Doesn't this look like they purposely
put those words in here for some reason?
[Odd looking mission cards?]
But I don't think
it's about adding the numbers.
[Jae Suk and Hye Jin trying to
make sense of all the numbers.]
I never knew numbers could be
so confusing.
It has to be one of these two,
or I've got nothing.
Excuse me.
We're going to make our attempt.
[Blank...]
What are you two thinking about so hard?
- 14357.
- Try adding 11 to 14357.
14368.
What do we do with your shop?
Could there be something with numbers?
Even if there is, others won't know.
[Could the addition in previous mission
cards be one of their crucial hints?]
If it's not this one, then it has to be this.
[Jong Kook and Bora having decided
that it's a two digit number.]
- Challenge.
- Challenge!
[Order of attempts are
on first come first served basis.]
- Seung Gi did all the work, didn't he?
- No, leader did everything this time.
- I showed him what being a leader is about.
- If we get it wrong, then it's his fault.
But we're going to guess it right first.
We have two possibilities.
[Jong Kook and Bora are first
to attempt to make their guess.]
- Fighting!
- Fighting.
[Jong Kook steps up to the
metal door first.]
[Guess the number correct,
and the door shall open.]
Here I go.
- Bora.
- Yes?
- Fighting!
- Wish me luck.
Okay!
- You're going to get it.
- Right?
- That's kind of like ours...
- Very similar, I think.
[Having pressed 1 and 4 so far.]
[Could Jong Kook and Bora's
guess be correct?]
We started off with 14357,
then we were told to add 11 to it.
Then the penalty was five sit ups when
we got it wrong at the bus mission.
Then we were give one minute to eat
during the potato mission, so that's one.
And we were asked to get three helpers,
so we chose the number three.
So we've added all those numbers together.
[All added together is 14377.]
[Jong Kook completed inputting 14377.]
We didn't get the seven.
[Other teams seem to have
differing answers.]
As long as Jae Suk isn't thinking what we are,
then we really may have a chance to win.
[Could the number be 14377?]
[He disappeared beneath the ground!]
- What is that?
- What just happened?
- What's the big idea?
- That really scared me!
- That's too scary.
[If you get the number wrong,
then you'll disappear beneath the floor!]
I think I'm going to be too nervous
to do this mission.
You need to think about it
some more, Bora.
Why? Why do I need
to think about it some more?
- What's the need?
- Do whatever you want.
[Jong Kook and Sistar's Bora-
Making her attempt at the correct number.]
[Pressing down the numbers
without any hesitation.]
I'm going to add these numbers.
Jong Kook is going to try 14377,
which is an addition of all the numbers.
But if that's wrong, then I'm
going to take the 1 potato out of it.
[Then could the number be 14377 minus one?]
[Could the number be
14376 like she thinks it is?]
14376!
[The number isn't 14376 either!]
Are you sure that's safe?
Are you sure it's even possible
to get the answer?
- She's crying.
- I'm fine.
I'm fine.
Hye Jin, do you want me to go first?
[Time for Jae Suk and Hye Jin's turn.]
Actually, why don't you go first?
Hye Jin, input this number, okay?
- You know the number, right?
- Yes.
[Hye Jin going up first to make
her attempt at guessing the number.]
[This team hasn't been able to come up
with more than one possibility.]
Challenge.
If you fall through,
then we're ruined, Hye Jin.
[Stepping up to the door with confidence.]
Please shout out the number clearly
once you're finished inputting it.
[Just what is the number that
she's thinking of?]
11?
I see what they're doing.
I see.
[Just how did Jae Suk and Hye Jin
come up with their number?]
11... then 5.
Then it was one minute,
then lastly, it was three people.
If it's not 11513...
Then could this be it?
11513?
[Jae Suk and Hye Jin's guess is 11513.]
How did they come up with
that number?
- Shout it out.
- 11513.
[Could their number be correct?]
- 11513!
- Please.
- That was so scary!
- Wasn't that startling?
Isn't it totally scary?
Yoo Jae Suk!
I don't think this is it.
Hye Jin!
- Hey Jin!
- Yes?
- This doesn't seem right, does it?
- I don't think it is.
I'm going to go think this one through.
- I'll go first.
- Lee Kwang Soo!
[Next up is Kwang Soo and Seung Gi.]
[Jae Suk either has to take his turn now,
or go to the back of the line.]
This is driving me crazy.
I'm going to go to the end of the line.
Director, we only have one guess.
If I fall through,
then go to the back of the line.
I'll just go home instead.
Challenge.
[Kwang Soo and Seung Gi-
Leader Kwang makes his attempt.]
We only have one chance.
I will show you what being a leader
is all about!
This was your idea and your leading.
So if you get this right,
then you really are a true leader.
Are you just trying to thwart your
share of the responsibility on me?
No, that's not it.
You were the one who came up with it all,
and I had nothing to do with it.
You're already digging yourself
out of this, aren't you?
No, this is your moment to become
a true leader.
Okay, I'm going for it!
- 14358?
- They only added one?
- Why?
- There was plus 11.
Seriously?
Seung Gi!
Can I become a true leader?
Please!
Please let it be right!
14358!
What could it be?
[Leader Kwang seemed to have
thought of something...]
I honestly got chills right now.
I seriously got chills.
Let's go with that one.
[Chilling guess?
Could 14358 be the number?]
Please let it be right!
14358!
[The doors are lighting up?]
- Can I open it?
- Try opening it.
[The door opens up...]
[And inside...]
[Completely wide eyed.]
[The door opened!]
[Kwang Soo guesses the correct number,
and opened the door!]
Come in!
Come in through the door!
[Even though he's afraid,
he crossed through the threshold.]
[Kwang Soo and Seung Gi did it!]
Leader Lee!
[Crossing back out the door
with the prize in hand!]
I'm the true leader!
- Good job, Kwang Soo.
- Good job.
- How did you come up with it?
- He said the answer lies within the mission.
So we lined up all the missions in the
order we were given the cards.
We couldn't come up with an answer no matter
how hard we looked at the numbers.
- Then our Leader Kwang all of a sudden...
- That leader would be me.
He looked at the mission cards
and noticed something.
When we just looked at the first letters,
it said, 'Plus one'.
Wow... I really didn't even fathom that.
So the 14357 that we were given
from the beginning...
[How did someone like him ever
figure out this riddle?]
So we added one to
14357 and came up with 14358.
[The number is 14358.]
The leader shines his true light
in the end.
This was your last?
Oh...
[Today is Kwang Soo's last show?]
[Leader Kwang wanting to shine
in his final moment...]
What are you guys all talking about?
- What are you talking about?
- Kwang Soo.
This was a very casual way
for you to back out of the show.
[Winning the mission turned into
a sudden exiting from the show?]
- You're leaving as a leader now.
- Watch what you say!
Well, there's nowhere for you
to climb now.
What are you talking about?
Then is there an opening for
a new member?
[Wanting to take over Giraffe's
empty spot?]
Bora wants to take his spot.
Anyways, today's winners!
Team Lee Seung Gi!
[Today's winner- Team Seung Gi!]
Subtitles by DramaFever
[You are a suspect]
[Suspected of setting women's hearts on fire-
Suspect Gong Yoo!]
[Absolutely killer charisma-
Suspect Park Hee Soon!]
[Their last chance to escape
their false charges!]
[Hot action sequence!]
[Tearful meal time.]
[Race to escape their false charges.]
[If you don't catch them...
you'll be the one who gets caught!]
[Action, Thrill, Drama.]
[Next Week's Running Man- Escape.]