The one who dominates food.
[Welcome to eating board Jumanji.]
[Eating Board Jumanji.]
Subtitles by DramaFever
Eat it quickly!
[The new era of food opens today!]
[A new way of going on a food trip
that nobody has seen before.]
[A sci-fi food fantasy full of
extraordinary things.]
Enough!
[Eating Board Jumanji]
Kyunggido, Gapyung, Jara Island.
The weather was good every day.
Why today of all days?
Why are you getting angry?
I feel angry.
Why are you getting angry
on a day like this?
He's getting angry at the weather.
You're getting angry at even
the weather now?
Weather... do you want to
get in trouble?
- When he opens his eyes he gets angry.
- I know, right?
We continuously had good
weather but today..
You should meet a woman, too.
I'll take care of it.
Stop bothering Kwang Soo and
find someone.
What are we doing today?
I will tell you today's mission.
The mission, already?
Please open it.
- Meal?
- Meal as in eating?
- Indiana Junfari.
- What is it?
- It looks like Indiana.
What are we doing with that?
That is a board game,
an eating board game.
[Jumbo Eating Board]
We are going to have an
eating board game race.
Eating board race?
- We will introduce the guests.
- Where are they?
What is it?
It's noisy.
They are out.
- I see them!
- What is this?
Why did you bring him?
It's Jun Ha?
This is some piece of work.
These things scare me.
Who is this?
What brings you here?
So Yi Hyun!
[Only one is receiving a great welcome.]
Hello.
[Eating Master, Jung Jun Ha.]
[Cute Actress, So Yi Hyun.]
Why are you showing such
disappointment?
- Why are you disappointed?
- Why did you come out?
Her face is so small.
You. Go away!
Go away!
Why are you guys showing such
disappointed faces?
You are going to really have
to act stupid today.
[Giraffe who is in charge of acting
stupid is facing a crisis.]
You are finished!
This place is awesome.
He is the stupidest person on earth.
This is really frustrating.
Today's main game is the
Saturday fool vs. the Sunday fool.
- Satfool vs. Sunfool?
- Satfool vs. Sunfool.
- Why are you so nervous?
- About what?
It's because you guys are
fooling around so much.
Are you going to
have a love line today?
He's expecting it again.
- What are you talking about?
- Why is your face getting red?
What do you think about Kim Jong Kook?
I saw him have a love line
with Geun Young.
- That's right.
- What's he going to do?
It's all over now.
I am good friends with Geun Young.
It's fine...?
Your love line's over.
- Totally over.
- Finished!
I will tell you today's mission.
Today's mission, as you have
seen behind you...
Today's mission is an Eating Board Race.
[Eating Board Race]
Eating board race?
You know the movie Jumanji, right?
Yes.
There's a movie about a
magical board game called Jumanji, right?
- By throwing dice.
- That's right.
When they throw the dice, things like
elephants and rhinoceros pop out.
- There was a movie like that, right?
- Yes.
The board game from the movie
has been made in real life.
It's the eating board Jumanji behind you.
When you roll the dice and
the team's piece moves
then a magical statement will appear.
If you win the statement then you will eat
Gapyung's delicacies instead of elephants coming out.
[The statement and Gapyung's
great dishes together!]
These people are...
Don't do this to me.
You can only clear the game if
you finish all the food that's given.
This looks good.
The one who arrives first has
a greater chance of winning.
So finish the eating board Jumanji
quickly and come.
Eating is...
- This is the real food show.
- That's why they called me.
To feed you.
I will announce the teams.
Jung Jun Ha, Yoo Jae Suk,
and Ji Suk Jin.
You are one team.
- This is the worst team ever.
- His nagging..
If you have him on your
team you win.
- What do you mean win?
- When eating, he is the "The Commander."
The one who dominates food.
The one who dominates food!
You don't have to worry. You don't
have to worry about anything.
Jun Ha watches us a lot.
- He watched a lot.
- I do watch a lot.
And So Yi Hyun...
What is it?
It's going to be an
uncomfortable situation.
Love always starts out uncomfortably.
Kim Jong Kook,
and Lee Kwang Soo are one team.
Why are you making me uncomfortable?
You are going to be uncomfortable.
And Chun Yang, Lee Mong Ryong,
and Bang Ja.
That's what it is traditionally.
What is that?
Beef set?
Isn't it liver?
This is...
the board.
Other way around.
Look at this.
[Portable eating board Jumanji]
Where are we putting it?
- We can put it anywhere?
- Yes. Anywhere.
Just do it here.
You must be tired.
I got it.
[Move 2 places.]
It must be working.
Those who conquer their fear
dominates the high altitude.
High altitude?
Sky diving?
What are you doing?
Why are you doing that?
I saw this a lot.
He really watches a lot.
There's going to be a huge
light shining from it.
You're right. You're right.
- You have to be like this.
- One, two, three.
[Battle of the fools?]
[Participant No. 1
the Saturday fool, Meal Brother.]
[Participant No. 2
the Sunday fool, Unfortunate Giraffe.]
- That face.
- That face?
[Blank Ji throws the dice!]
- Move three spaces.
- Look at this.
I knew this would happen.
[Move three spaces.]
Something's coming out again.
[Fussing again.]
- What is that?
- That fool.
I'm just trying hard.
I did it to try to do well.
[Eating board race. Start!]
- Since you came out you need to win, right?
- Yes.
Let's try our best.
- Are you competitive?
- Competitive?
I think she is.
Her physiognomy looks like
she is competitive.
My physiognomy looks competitive.
She kind of does.
You will get scolded a lot today.
You should be prepared.
I won't scold her.
You like small and fairy-like girls, right?
- No I don't.
- How did you know?
I'm not like that.
- It's not that he doesn't like you but...
- No, it's not.
I know it for sure now.
It's not like that.
What do you mean you know for sure?
I don't have anything like that.
I'm just doing my best..
The Sun pine nuts?
The pine nuts here must be...
I'm talking. Why are you talking about
pine nuts when I'm talking?
You don't listen to us when we talk.
- Do you not listen to other people?
- You should listen to the whole sentence.
You are the selective hearing type.
Once one person finishes talking the
other person starts to talk.
Jun Ha really met an angel.
[Newlywed]
I don't normally say this but...
I'm so thankful to her.
He's the same.
Him too. He really..
How did you find someone that
pretty with your face?
- With your face, really?
- It's sunlight to your face.
I really...
- Really?
- Hey, with your face
a pretty son like Ji Ho?
You really...
I'm very thankful to her too.
I know that I should be.
Do you know how tacky you were
when you were a rookie?
I couldn't bear to look at his face.
I couldn't look him in the eyes.
It was really horrible.
It wasn't horrible.
I was ugly. I was ugly but it wasn't
to the point that it was horrible.
When I first met you in 1997
you were a dried fish.
[His face looks like a dried fish.]
It was like a dried pollack.
Dried pollack is a little too much.
[Red team headed to R2.]
Gapyung's pine nut porridge.
Just put a little bit of salt in it
and if you put spicy kimchi on it then
you just...
Just stay still.
- Really?
- Why are you so noisy?
How delicious is that?
That haejang soup.
The pint nuts of Myungsan.
[Every sign makes them drool.]
Table d'hote of salted fish and
rice wrapped in greens.
Marinated duck.
Duck with spicy sauce.
You put garlic on it and wrap it.
- [He already had two meals via mime.]
- Boodae stew.
The corn here tastes really good.
The corn. The corn..
[He bought it.]
- It tastes good, right?
- It looked really good.
It tastes good because it's
not too sweet.
Look at the steam.
[It's good.]
It tastes good if you eat it like this.
You hold it like this and..
[He is really into it.]
You can just see it!
He looks like he was never really
good at studying.
I remember this place too.
[They have to eat a lot later
but they have already started.]
What is this?
That's..?
- Is it bungy?
- It's that. No, I really can't do this.
- It really is that.
- It really is.
I want to just go. I'm sorry.
I wish the best for Running man.
I came here before.
I stayed here for 24 hours.
On the top.
Give that to me.
The youngest has to hold it.
Really?
Really? This place I really..
You are really in for it now.
I don't like this.
Hurry up.
- This is scary. I know because I've been on it.
- Hurry up and get on.
- Come here.
- I'm not here like this because I'm not scared.
- It's not scary.
- You can see everything from the inside.
What is wrong with you?
I want to hide too.
[Going up 55 meters!]
I really can't look. It's opened up.
Just look.
Just look down.
This is really high up!
- It's really high!
- It's no joke.
Jun Ha, just don't look.
- Just don't look.
- We're here.
We're going out now.
It's opened up.
What? Why are we up here?
What are we doing up here?
What is it?
[What is this?]
[55 meters up...]
[there's a net?]
- This is really..
- Why are you doing this to us?
- We really hate high places.
- We really do.
Stand on this side.
Stand over there.
Stop shaking.
I can't stand on this side.
Stand over there.
What are you doing?
What? What do we have to do?
This is shaking. This is shaking.
- It's not shaking.
If you beat me in badminton..
You know that I'm the president of
the celebrity badminton club.
But it's 3 to 1.
You need to connect each
other's hands.
Only the two hands in the middle
can hold the badminton.
Only the two hands in the middle then..
I'm left handed so you have to be
on this side to my left.
Since I'm left handed.
Stress!
Come to this side.
But I'm left handed. If we do this I can't..
Don't do anything.
If I want to play where should I stand?
My nickname is Jungminton.
Stand over there.
Fine. I'll stay still.
I'll do as you say.
What should I do?
-What?
-Why?
[The two hands together.]
-It's over there.
-Is it here?
We are here.
[A restaurant famous for
bowls of acorn jelly.]
Why is there a car here?
I think we have to find the
key to open the car.
What's with those balloons?
This mission...
is the "bowl of acorn jelly" mission.
One person needs to eat the
bowl of acorn jelly.
Two people need to hold the
balloons and get into the car.
At first only the two people
will get into the car.
But people will get into the
car continuously.
You succeed if the balloons don't pop
until the person finishes the bowl.
It's important to eat quickly.
Do we need to use chopsticks?
I don't think we are using chopsticks.
It looks good.
[Toothpicks]
- How can we do this?
- How are we supposed to eat this?
- Someone's here.
- What is this?
- It's similar to when we had the watergun game.
Look at this.
Acorn jelly! Acorn Jelly! Acorn jelly!
Acorn jelly!
[The Acorn Jelly Army appears!]
What is this?
Acorn Jelly! Acorn Jelly!
[They are scheduled to ride
the car with them.]
The person in the back is the best.
They are all Jong Kook.
[The people in the back look like Kook?]
[Smile!]
[What...]
I'll try to eat really fast.
- Fighting!
She can do well.
[Determined]
[If I don't eat it quickly we will
really be beaten to a pulp...]
Mission start!
Acorn jelly! Acorn jelly!
My position..
What is this?
Don't do this to me.
Don't do this to me..
[They are finally holding the rackets.]
Can't you give this to us after
we cross the line?
Really?
You should've given it to us after we crossed
the net. How are we supposed to cross now?
Next time when you make teams put only
one person like them per team. These two...
- I really can't handle..
- Be quiet.
[Yoo Jae Suk is going through the
troubles of being the youngest one.]
This is dirty.
Why did you make us come through
this way?
Come in quickly.
Your body is so big.
It's high.
At least we are not bungy jumping.
- We just need to make the first 5 points?
- 5 points.
Stop pushing me to this side.
[Badminton 55 meters above. Start!]
You can rest for this one.
I'll do it.
- No. Stay still.
- Stay still.
I'm the president of the
celebrity's badminton club.
You're not even that good at it.
Do it quickly.
I told you to stay still. Stay still.
What are you doing?
- Really?
- Stay still.
- It's because we both moved.
You are bad at this, right?
- I'm good at it.
- Just stay still.
- You stay still.
- Let go.
- Let go of this! Let go of this!
- Take your hand out! Out!
- Yes, like this.
- Do it like this.
Don't use any force. Just stay like this.
Just leave your hand on top of mine.
- Just leave your hand on top.
- You are bad at this!
You are bad at this!
I'm the president of the
celebrity badminton club.
What are you doing?
I told you not to use any force.
Don't do anything.
Can't I play alone?
He's really bad at badminton.
- Don't play. Just stay still.
- Stay still.
- Stay still. Let me have the racket.
- Why?
You keep giving him points.
Give it to me.
Stay still.
Stay still. Let go of the racket.
Let go of it.
- Let go.
I told you to let go.
Stop it.
I'm the president of
the celebrity badminton club.
Don't touch me.
- Let go!
- Don't touch me. Let go of it.
- Let go.
- Let go of this.
- Let go!
Why are you doing this?
Just leave your hand on top of mine.
Stop it.
They are telling me to leave my
hand on top of everything.
Just leave your hand on top.
Just leave your hand.
Don't put your strength into it.
That's right. You're doing well.
Return Chance?
I told you to let go of it.
That was mine.
Why were you trying to hit it?
It was mine.
It was coming in my direction.
You weren't ready for it.
I was like this.
I went in for it in the right position.
Why are you drooling so much?
Hey. That's right. Let go.
Really?
- I told you to stay still.
- He did it.
- I won, right?
- Yes.
You can challenge me again if you go
up and down three times while shouting:
"If we work together, we live!"
- We can do it again?
- That's right.
You two decide who's going to
be in the middle.
I can't do it anymore.
We have to say,
"If we work together, we live!"
The three of us have to do it together.
Together. Ready? Start.
Start.
If we work together, we live.
Why are we doing the wave?
[Disharmony]
Wait.
Judge. Judge.
Come here for a moment.
Come here for a moment, Judge.
Please put me into another group.
I think I'm going crazy.
I can't do it anymore with them.
Forget about the team.
Please let me go down as quickly as possible.
This is the problem right now.
- Start. If we get together..
- We did it already.
We already did it three times.
We did it already.
Listen to the judge.
You come to the middle.
Why am I in the middle?
I'm a lefty so I can't use my hand if we do it like this.
We don't want you to use it.
I'll be in the middle so you go here.
I'm going to really...
You go.
This is so frustrating.
I'm a lefty.
I'm a righty.
He doesn't have to do it.
We'll just do it like this.
We'll play like this.
This is so frustrating.
I'm the president of the badminton club.
Why are you like this?
You only go out twice a year.
What do you mean president?
Just put your hand in.
Why are you taking that out?
- Why are you holding onto it so tightly?
- Just put your hand on top of mine.
[When can they go down...]
I think I'm going to go crazy.
[Blue team's turn at R3.]
We have to position ourselves well.
You don't have to hurry..
- There is no need to hurry, Dong Hoon.
- You have to take your positions.
There is no need to hurry, Dong Hoon.
[Before the balloon pops because there
are too many people in the car...]
[finish all of the delicious acorn jelly!]
Start!
Acorn jelly! Acorn jelly!
[The acorn jelly army
forcing their way in.]
Don't do this to me.
Don't do this to me!
Look at Gary.
Don't do this to me.
Why are you doing this?
Ji Hyo.
- Ji Hyo!
- Think of it as alcohol and just drink it.
It is the alcohol that you like.
Think of it as alcohol.
- Please.
- Please think of it as alcohol.
This place is a club.
They are both really ugly.
Ji Hyo. Sorry. I can't hold on.
I have no more strength in my arms.
Don't finish it!
Fail... Gary's balloon popped.
What is this?
Acorn jelly! Acorn jelly!
I feel crushed.
[Oh no...]
[There was still some acorn jelly left.]
This is not a joke.
Dong Hoon! Doesn't he look like the
actors from "Surprise"?
The foreigner.
Oh My God! Surprise!
You look like the actors from "Surprise."
Truth or false?
[Truth or false?]
[He's eating the leftover acorn jelly
as soon as he's finished.]
- What is he doing?
- I'm going crazy.
They are too strong.
I'll eat.
Wait a minute.
[Rather than becoming pulp in the car...]
- I understand how you feel but..
I'll eat. I'll eat quickly.
Are you going to eat it?
- I will..
- I will eat it.
- Fine. You can eat it.
- You can try first.
- Really? Okay.
- It's really good.
Why is our balloon so big?
Our balloon. Wait.
So Yi Hyun!
- So Yi Hyun!
- Yes?
Listen to what we have to say!
Don't just focus on the food!
We are having a hard time.
Look at our balloon!
This is the balloon. It's too big.
It is.
[An answer with no soul...]
- She really doesn't care.
- Should we do it?
You have five seconds.
Let's get in first.
[Eating already?]
Can she eat already?
Is she allowed to eat already?
She's cheating.
She's a cheater.
Even before it started she..
I understand that you want
to eat it but, eat it after we start.
She's so greedy.
Are you playing the game or are
you just hungry?
I only ate a little bit.
You ate this much, Yi Hyun.
- Are you ready?
- Yes.
Those guys are really scary.
This is really.
Lock the door.
Acorn jelly! Acorn jelly!
Press really hard.
[Eating acorn jelly... Start!]
Acorn jelly! Acorn jelly!
[Strong pressure]
More. Press harder!
They are really ugly.
Distorted tiger.
He's really ugly.
Acorn jelly! Acorn jelly!
Eat it quickly!
Hurry!
They are withstanding this!
Jong Kook is really not a human.
His face is turning red!
They're withstanding this?
Relaxed?
Don't appreciate the taste!
Eat it quickly!
Yi Hyun, you'll get indigestion if
you eat quickly.
Hurry!
Yi Hyun, where do you live?
Yi Hyun, what's your dream?
Oh no!
Give her some water.
Yi Hyun!
What are you doing? Push!
This is the end!
Push!
Push more!
She's almost done.
Stop it!
- I'm done.
- No you're not.
-No!
-You guys can do this!
Really?
It popped!
Oh no! It popped...
- Kwang Soo.
- Hey!
Yes?
We just started.
Yellow team. Fail.
And there's a handle. You should've
used it to your advantage.
You should've put it underneath it and...
That's right.
You should've put it in and...
This team has no such thing as teamwork.
- They keep fighting.
- It's zero.
They have no teamwork.
- Ready?
- Yes.
I'll eat quickly.
You don't live alone in this world.
Acorn jelly!
Acorn jelly! Acorn jelly!
[You're doing well!]
Everyone! Let's try a little harder!
Push harder!
What should I do?
My head. My neck.
Hey you!
It popped! I swear..
I swear that
I saw him pop it with his hands.
You did it with your hands, right?
I saw it.
[It's been a long time since we
have seen Bad Ji Hyo!]
I was withstanding it.
They lost their success due to
uninvited guest, Giraffe.
Kwang Soo, I'll forgive you for
what you did before.
Come here.
This time you really have to do it.
- Fighting!
- Say it seriously!
- Look at us when you say it!
- Look at our faces.
- Fighting!
This time the balloon got smaller.
This time it's for real.
[Open it and...]
[Acorn jelly army gets in together.]
Acorn jelly! Acorn jelly!
Acorn jelly!
Jong Kook's balloon has extra space.
You can put in one more.
[Inhumane strength]
- Hurry!
- No!
Wait a minute!
I think we can succeed this time!
It's time we succeeded!
It's time to succeed!
What are you doing?
What's going on?
Hurry!
- So Yi Hyun, what are you doing?
- Hurry up and eat!
- She's almost done.
- Wow, Jong Kook..
- Hurry!
- Please...
No...
Wait.
Haroro's interference strategy starts.
Wait a minute. You can't do this.
How can you do this?
Wait.
Bad Ji Hyo helps.
My nose!
Wait. Wait!
- Don't take pictures! Don't take pictures!
- Nice to meet you! Nice to meet you!
Don't take pictures!
You need to preserve moments
like these.
Don't take pictures!
Thank you.
Please!
How can he look like this?
Zoom in!
[Giraffe from planet of the apes.]
How can he look like this?
Please! I can't hold on any longer.
[Yi Hyun is finishing up!]
So Yi Hyun has a really
good appetite.
Let's just wait a little longer.
A little longer.
No! No!
Push! Push!
Really?
Since she finished,
she just needs to whistle.
No! No!
I don't know how to whistle.
You have to blow it.
She doesn't know how to whistle.
- That's good.
- Wait.
It didn't come out.
She doesn't know how to whistle.
Finished, finished!
Finished, finished! I did it.
[Whistle, success!]
[Yellow team, success!]
[A mess.]
They can't be happy even after succeeding.
[I'm full.]
Yi Hyun, you should tell us
that we did well.
Yi Hyun?
Don't say that you're full.
We succeeded together.
- Do you not see us?
- Hello?
- Yi Hyun, we are a mess right now.
- Do you know how hard we tried?
- We are a mess.
- Don't just say how full you are.
I know you did well but...
Say stuff like, "You look so tired.
What should we do?"
This is you.
Yellow team can roll the dice first.
I can't walk.
[She's ready to roll dice alone?]
Should I roll it?
- This team, really..
- We have to do it together.
I heard that he exercised a lot.
Thank you, Gary.
I want to become a guy with manners.
You did well. Thank you.
No. It's okay.
[Move 2 places.]
[Gather all your senses and survive.]
What is this? It's weird.
- You come out.
- What are you doing?
- Just come out.
- We have to win first.
- Wait. Let me do this first.
Let me do this first.
That's your right hand.
Try it with that hand.
Put your right hand in.
- Like this?
- Yes. Like that.
- It's perfect now.
- This works.
- Do it like this?
- Yes.
- This is good.
- Why didn't we think of this earlier?
It works like that too...
- It works.
- The fool taught him this.
- Ok.
- Nice.
[Yoo Hyuk's smashing is a success!]
[The ball hit him, so out.]
Serve.
You serve.
- That's right.
Did you see?
- Don't put any strength into your arms.
- I didn't. I'm not doing anything.
It's shaking.
- I almost forgot we were up here.
- Yes.
[Yoo Hyuk's surprise serve is a success!]
4 to 1.
We just need one more point to succeed.
Match point.
Nice.
- That's right.
[Ah... the net!]
That's right!
5:1 Red team wins!
They finally succeeded.
You did well.
You really..
[R2 is a success so time for food.]
Awesome!
[Famous noodles]
We just need to eat it
before going down.
It looks really good.
This is awesome.
[God of eating, all at once?]
What is he?
Are you done eating already?
I think we have to give him
another bowl.
He's already done.
It looks really good.
He really finished.
Already done.
Let's go.
He finished?
Why do you eat so quickly?
He went out in an eating contest
and came in third place.
It's delicious.
[Time to roll the dice.]
- Who's rolling it?
- Should I?
- Three.
My eyes!
What is it?
[Gather all your senses and survive.]
All your senses.
Sight, touch, smell...
Do you understand how
tired we are now?
I was eating so I couldn't really see
what was going on.
After we finished you didn't
even show excitement.
Usually when two people
had a hard time...
- I understand you had a hard time too but..
- Usually..
they come and go like this and
ask if we're all right.
They say something to the opponent
about being too harsh and..
Even at this very moment she's
doing something else.
She's touching her fingernails and..
Why did you put such shiny things
on your nails?
Because I heard I was coming
out on television.
That's why I had my nails done.
It's a street market.
There's a lot of middle-aged women here.
[They said to gather all our
senses in one place...]
We have to concentrate.
Let's go. Fighting.
- Fighting!
Fighting!
[Full of generosity, agriculture
and marine products.]
It smells good here.
-There are a lot of places here.
-Thank you.
[Figure out the food that touches your ear.
Buy it and bring it back.]
They said to figure out the food
that touches your ear.
With only the touch of your ear...
figure out what it is
- and here.
- What is this?
Only let your left ear out
of that hole.
This is driving me crazy.
- Like this? Like this.
- Only let the left ear out.
And please stand in a single line.
Take you ear out like this.
Your ear.
Kim Jong Kook nags too much.
What's wrong with you?
Excuse me.
- We are doing such weird things.
- We really are.
The first object.
It's kind of scary.
- Let's start with Kwang Soo.
- Wait.
Kwang Soo it can be something weird.
Wait. Wait!
- Why? Why?
- Kwang Soo, it can be something weird.
Give me a sign after saying 1, 2, 3.
What is this? I heard a sound!
What is this? It made a sound!
[It's definitely not something normal.]
[This is?]
[It's a sea cucumber.]
What is it? It made a sound.
It's probably not something normal.
It's not a normal object.
Why?
Yi Hyun's in big trouble.
Stop!
Why?
What is this?
- What is it?
- Why?
Tell me.
You have to tell us before you do it.
It's Kim Jong Kook's turn now.
Wait! Wait.
Why?
The person who is doing it gave me a signal
but then it made a really weird sound.
- I heard something.
- Listen to that sound very well.
- Kwang Soo, it made a sound.
- Don't miss the sound.
- This is really scary.
- We have to finish this at once.
Look at your muscles.
Wait. I'm ready.
Don't avoid it.
-Again.
It's making a sound.
What is this?
You can do this.
What on earth is this?
What is this?
It felt like a tongue.
I heard this kind of sound.
We'll go now.
What are you doing?
Oh my God.
- You have to endure it.
- What is this?
- What are you doing to the ear?
- It's nothing much.
Miss So.
Am I done?
What is this?
Stay still.
[Her ear...?]
What are you doing Jong Kook?
- We saw everything.
- Are you starting a love line?
- That's not it.
What are you doing?
- She can take it off on her own.
- Why are you doing it?
That's not it.
Let's go.
They have to buy it and
come back.
The yellow team heads for
the market first!
I think it's rice cake.
It was black.
That's not it. It was green.
Poop.
It stinks.
It always happens to you.
You are really unlucky.
I'm right, right?
- He's really unlucky.
- You're right.
Isn't this what they put on our ears?
Isn't it this?
We are going to put it on
your ears now.
Are you ready?
[It's deodeok that's good for your body.]
- Stop overreacting.
- Why are you overreacting?
- Wait. Wait a moment.
- It's too scary.
Why are you making such a big fuss?
- Wait a minute.
- We are going to start now.
What's wrong with you?
Really?
I have no clue what it is.
What is this?
Feel it well.
What is it?
I don't know. Do it one more time.
What is this?
Turn around.
- What is it?
- I don't know.
What is it?
- Is it alive?
- Wait.
Did you put it on?
- I know what it is.
- What is it?
[You know what it is?]
You just have to buy it and come back.
Didn't it feel like dried calamari?
I'm not sure.
Dried calamari?
- To me..
- It was hard.
- To me it felt like...
- What?
It was hard.
Wasn't it hard?
- The head of a pig.
- The head of a pig?
It wasn't that soft.
What is it?
Hello.
- Hello.
Look at the cutlass fish.
Hello.
It's really thick but it's only 10,000 won.
Look at the crab.
It's crabs.
It's a conch, my favorite.
- It looks really good.
- Look at the shrimp.
- The shrimp is as big as my arm.
- Hello.
- This is good too.
- This is really good.
Isn't it this, fried kelp?
- It felt like mugwort rice cake.
- Pounded rice cake.
If it's mugwort rice cake, it's awesome.
I saw the other team but
they didn't get surprised.
It's here.
Because there is powder on it and there was
water on our ears it might have felt like that.
Boss, can I try one of these?
It's all wrapped but you want to try it?
- We have to buy it.
- Hello.
Can I have one bite?
It's 2000 won.
Thank you.
Should we put it on our ears?
It's similar!
Put it on his ears.
- It's similar.
- It's similar, right?
It's similar.
- But it doesn't get on the ears.
- It doesn't but..
Let's try this first.
The pupae look good.
Can I get some pupae?
- Eat it if you want.
- It could be pupae.
- It's not pupae.
- Just eat it.
It could be pupae.
How much is it for one cup?
Should we buy dried calamari?
I thinks it's dried calamari.
Don't you think that it can be garlic?
What are you eating?
You're eating rice cake.
It's because I was hungry.
You bought rice cakes?
You shouldn't eat it like that.
Watch me.
Pupae.
Stop eating.
The pupae is mine.
My pupae.
I can't hear you.
Where is the money? Give it to me.
[Frugal Miss So.]
I really don't know what it is.
[The red team is still clueless.]
- What is it?
- Hello.
[What is it?]
[The deoduk that is the answer...!]
I think it's this.
- Try it.
- Feel this.
I think it is.
Let me see.
Do they succeed just like this?
It wasn't this.
It wasn't this bad.
[He's totally wrong...]
- It wasn't that.
- It was this.
I'm saying that it wasn't.
[Maybe it's not...]
[Stupid]
Thank you.
Maybe it's something like this.
Yes.
Let's try this.
Let's buy this.
It could be this.
Fish?
It could have been it's tail.
That's right.
- If this is right then it's awesome.
- Of course.
Yes.
When I say 1, 2, 3 you open it.
If you're right then you pass.
If you're not right then we do it again.
Like this?
1, 2, 3.
Open it!
It's rice.
But what they felt with their
ears before was...
a sea cucumber!
It was this?
You put this on our ear?
- But we really thought it was that.
- That's right.
[Yellow team fails!]
[The blue team is headed to R6.]
- What I think is..
- Straight, straight.
Straight, straight, straight, straight.
Straight, straight ,straight, straight.
You don't know it?
The straight song?
I don't.
I'm going to go crazy.
Go... go... go crazy!
- Straight, straight, straight, straight.
[R6 Pension]
[Something is making me really
nervous right now.]
[A brazier]
[with roasted sweet potatoes.]
[Nervous...]
While eating the roasted sweet potatoes
look at the camera without blinking your eyes.
This is my habit.
- When I smile, I smile with my eyes.
- Me too.
- I'm famous for it.
Let's peel it.
- Let's first try it.
- I'm peeling it.
- I'm going to peel it first now.
- Wait. I'm not ready yet.
Just hold it like this and push it
into our mouths.
- Okay.
- Let's do that.
What if it doesn't come out?
[Forcing their eyes open.]
Start.
[In one bite?]
[Looking forward while moving
their mouths.]
It's hot.
It's gone bad.
The sweet potato has gone bad.
[What?]
Do I have to eat the sweet potato?
It's gone bad.
I was so surprised.
The sweet potato has gone bad.
I ate it.
- I ate it.
- You failed.
Why?
Everyone else blinked.
Then you should have told me so
that I could spit it out.
What are you doing?
I already ate it.
I told you that it had gone bad.
Can you give me some water?
Did you get it?
How did you get it?
We got it right.
- We got it right away.
- At once?
- We got it.
- Here.
We got this.
We decided on this fish.
We'll open it now.
1, 2, 3.
[Deoduk]
I told you.
I told you that it was this!
- I told you that it was this.
- You said it wasn't.
Why didn't you do it then?
I told you it was this.
- This...
- Everyone.
First of all, it doesn't smell.
Would they do something
that smells?
I told you it was that.
It was this.
This smells. If it was this you would've
smelled it right away.
I said it kind of felt like dried calamari.
This is dried calamari?
It didn't hurt this much.
It was this.
[They really talk a lot.]
- Let me see.
- It is this.
How would you know?
Mister.
- It is this.
- You are really thick skinned.
Why are you acting like a gangster?
What?
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, sir.
I'm really sorry, sir.
This guy here is
a bit drunk...
He's pretty dim-witted, too.
I'm sorry.
- I'm sorry.
- Why are you doing this, seriously?
If you're going to be on
this show, do things right!
- Stop it!
- Why are you being like this?
You want to get hit again?
Why are you nibbling on that rice cake?
Calm down!
Don't lose your temper.
He's a bit slow and lacking.
Please let him go.
Goodbye, sir! And thank you.
Hey, what did you tell him?
Stop, that's enough.
Hey, Joon Ha.
Your ear is really sensitive.
Do I have to put my ear
against something again?
Darn, my ear's not good at this.
I can't tell with my ear.
Then which body part of yours is strong?
[Figures...]
That's true.
So that's it.
Oh, a mackerel!
- It has a smell.
- It smells!
Here we go.
I get scared of these things.
What is it?
Aw, what the heck is this?!
- What's the matter?
- Stop overreacting!
What is this?
What is it?
- Don't overreact!
- Move aside.
What is this?
It has a smell.
- Uh, wait a second.
- How does it feel?
- Is it moist?
- Hold on.
- It had a smell.
- Does it smell?
If it smells,
that's good.
What the--it feels like
a tongue is licking me!
What are you talking about?
Whoa!
It's licking you,
isn't it? Isn't it?
- Wait, hold on.
- Doesn't it lick you?
- It licks!
- Stop it.
- See?
- Is it alive?
I couldn't tell
when it was my turn.
It definitely licked me.
It smelled fishy.
It might be seafood.
It was like a tail.
[Smelling each other's ears...]
You should clean out your ears.
[Passersby could mistake this
scene for something else...]
Let go.
Let go!
Let me go first.
I have something to tell you.
Why are you sniffing my ear?
Stay still.
Didn't it feel flat?
Isn't it flat?
Wasn't it like a tail?
What are you doing?
- I'm done.
- What was that?
- It smelled, didn't it?
- It did.
It's seafood.
- Of course it is.
- Definitely.
Can I put this against my ear?
Just be careful.
[Thinking...]
Hey, we have the same crab here,
so why are you looking over there?
It's the same crab!
I'll put it to your ear.
[Putting a live crab to his ear...]
It won't move, will it--Hey!
Hey, don't put its pincers to my face!
Stay still.
- That tickles. I'll do it.
- No, I'll do it.
Whoa!
Is it this?
Be more forceful.
[It was a pineapple]
Hey!
Hold on.
What is this?
Hold on. Hold on.
Is it this?
No but it didn't move.
I don't think this is it.
They didn't do it!
We're grocery shopping right now.
What?
What did you say?
This is ridiculous.
Why are you looking at us like that?
My eyes just look this way.
This is nonsense.
Why are you coming this way?
Why are you so thuggish?
Seriously that man...
What could it be?
Don't go far.
It's seafood.
That's what it is.
Like this.
It's like this. Do you sell
dry ones too?
- We don't sell it.
- You don't?
No, it's probably this.
It's not this.
It's this.
- It's not this.
- Yes it is.
It feels like this.
Really?
Come over here.
[Up to his tricks again]
Here you go.
Please give us two.
It's this.
Trust me.
This rice cake looks good.
How much are these rice cakes?
Stop spending money!
Just spending it left and right.
How much are these?
- W2000.
- Really?
If we have one, it'll be W500.
That should be it.
- All it needs is soy sauce.
- Thank you!
- Sesame oil.
- Soy sauce!
You need to dip it in
sesame oil and soy sauce.
- Sesame oil.
- Soy sauce!
You need to dip it in
sesame oil and soy sauce.
[This is what's so great about
shopping at traditional markets]
- Thank you!
- Only at traditional markets can we eat these!
Aren't these called 'sooro?'
Oh, it's 'sora?'
(conch)
- These are cockles.
- Cockles, yeah, that's what I meant.
Let me see.
- Oh, I think it's this one!
- Right?
Yeah, I was looking for these!
We'll take these.
Thank you!
We're taking out our groceries.
Okay.
Fish cake.
1, 2, 3!
See?
See? What did I tell you?
How can you confuse this with this?
This is 'uh-mook.' (fish cake)
And 'go-deung-uh.' (mackerel)
Why are you trying to take it?
You didn't buy it!
It's because I'm really hungry.
Let's see if they get it right.
This, this.
Cockles.
- 1, 2--
- We'll do it!
Okay! Sheesh, no need to get angry.
1, 2, 3!
- Pineapple!
- Pineapple.
[Correct answer: Pineapple]
You have to put it
up to your ear.
- Let's do this instead--
- It was this, I think.
She puts anything and
everything up to her ear!
- What is this like?
- I told you earlier!
Um, excuse me guys,
but you know we're being taped...
Don't push me!
Don't push you? Then don't act
like you deserve to be pushed!
Why are you guys
being like this?
You're going to get hit.
Why are you wasting our time--
So what if I get hit a few times?
[Now it's the red team's turn]
What is it?
Reveal it, please.
[It's a mango!]
This ought to be fun.
- Definitely.
- This will be fun!
Can I touch it?
- Don't feed it to them.
- Why? What?
Whoa!
- Stay still!
- What's the matter?
- What is this, seriously?
[The mysterious feel of a mango]
What is it?
Isn't it your hand?
- No, it's not.
- It's not your hand?
[Next, it's Joon Ha's turn]
Their reactions are...
They didn't seem scared by it,
so it must be something cute.
- It's not your hand?
- See? It feels like a hand, right?
- Okay, I'm done.
- What the heck was that?
Take a good guess.
I mean it.
Owww!
[Surprised]
Oh my gosh.
- What was that?
- He's overreacting.
He has such unlucky-looking ears!
Why are you judging my ears?
He has such hideous ears
I can't look at them!
- His ears are really--
- Is he done yet?
Still not done?
What the heck is this?
[Bam! Bam!]
- Are we done?
- Can we take these off?
- Can we?
- I don't know what it is.
[Sniffing each other's ears]
Make sure they don't see it!
Hide it well.
His ears smell the same.
Let's go.
[The red team heads to the markets first]
Now you have a weird smell
coming out of your ears.
- Isn't it this?
- Is it a banana?
Oh, nice!
[The red team has come
to the fruit section!]
[Here lies the correct
answer, the mango!]
- Put it against your ear.
- Banana?
Banana.
I'm sorry to have to do this...
It's a banana.
- It felt smooth.
- Yeah, like this.
Wait, check this out.
Other ear. It was the other ear.
Does it matter which ear?
- Oh, it's this.
- Right?
- Yeah, it's this.
- Let me try.
- It's this.
- Stay still.
- You have to put it against this ear.
- Seriously, does it matter which ear?
- This is it.
- Was it this smooth?
- Yeah, it was this smooth.
- It felt like this.
I told him not to put it against my skin.
- Isn't it a banana?
- Let me see.
Anyway, it's either a mango or a banana.
- The vendors are staring at us.
- I'm sorry, sir.
I think it was a mango.
I think it's closer to a mango...
I'm sorry, sir.
- Really?
- It's this.
- It's this, right?
- Yeah.
- Okay, mango it is!
- This, this!
It's definitely a mango!
We've got the answer!
We're quick.
Hey, the size is about
the same. Do you think--
- The shape seems similar.
- Did we really get it right?
- Whoa...
- They seem similar...
- They seem similar!
- Please, oh please...
1, 2, 3!
Three!
[Correct!]
We were right!
[Red team: Mission accomplished!]
I could tell it was this
at the very last moment...
Whoa, this...
We got this one right.
- We got this one right.
- We make a great team!
- Great!
- Awesome!
Now it's starting to kick in.
- Great!
- Awesome!
Now it's starting to kick in.
[Move Three Steps Forward]
[If you don't combine your strength,
you won't be able
to block the danger that is to come.]
One, two, three.
[Yellow Team Wins]
Do we go now?
You have to give us our theme.
[Move three steps forward]
If you can't combine your strength
you won't be able
to block the danger that is to come.]
What did you buy?
I bought steadily.
With exactly seven dollars left.
Ten fish breads were two dollars.
I bought two dollar's worth
and I had five dollars left.
I felt the hulled chestnuts were five dollars.
'Ma'am, how much are the hulled chestnuts?'
'Five dollars.'
Perfect match.
I think I'm going to match it all today.
- There's pumpkin in here too.
- There's pumpkin and red beans.
It's really good.
Wow, this tastes really good.
See, look at the color.
The chestnut is yellow and looks very tasty.
This is really good.
[Eating continuously]
I keep eating today.
[Blue Team- Completes the Baked Sweet Potato Mission,
Heads Towards Next Destination]
Is that a flower?
- Really?
- Oh my god.
It's true.
[Valley Water]
[An anxious hunch?]
- There's some weird stuff in the water.
- What do we do?
We're doomed...
What do we have to block that's flying over here?
- If I fall, you're going to get hurt?
- Yes.
It's very nice.
I feel like I've become an actual walker.
Choon Hyang!
Cross carefully, Choon Hyang.
Step where I step.
We're here.
Hey, what is this?
Take off the mic.
Why take off the mic,
are we drowning?
[Jokingly]
They say it's 170cm deep...
Then that leaves only 3cm of myself.
[Envy?]
You're left with only 3cm?
They said to take off the mic.
I think we're going to submerge under water.
Think that it's not cold!
[Training in the cool valley water]
Hurry up and come in Kwang Soo.
We can't go on filming because of you.
[Pyeong-gang Princess and the Fool Full Moon] Special Quiz Method
[Person from each team who will answer the question stands in front]
[They all volunteer]
I'm really good at quizzes.
Hello, I am 'Jung Quiz.'
I'm good at quizzes.
[Quarrel]
Rock, paper, scissors!
[Youngest Yoo Hyuk Wins]
Hey, you're the youngest and...
This is my sense of duty.
[Yellow Team 'Rock, Paper, Scissors?]
[Giraffe insists on playing 'Rock, Paper, Scissors]
[Yi Hyun Wins]
[Blue Team also settles with 'Rock, Paper, Scissors]
Go!
[Myung Ji Surprisingly Wins]
- How can she surprisingly win?
Hurry up and go in!
It's not even that cold,
stop being a crybaby.
[Glutton Monster Squirming Endlessly in the Water]
It becomes like this...
Like this...
You can wail and cry out loud.
Today's quiz...
is related to food.
Now the first question!
- It's a meat question. Meat.
- Oh, meat.
If it's about meat then, I had to go out...
- Can we change the topic about meat?
- Do whatever you want.
- I don't know much about meat.
- Just do it, since we chose meat!
- Okay, fine.
- Geesh...
Are you a valley hoodlum?
Why are you doing this?
Okay, meat question!
[Get 3 Questions Right and Win]
[Question Related to Meat]
What do you call the front and upper thighs
of the cow's hind legs?
Jae Suk!
Center Heel of Shank?
[Wrong]
How is that a shank of beef?
Yellow.
- Do you know?
- One, Two...
Rump?
I thought it was a rump.
Listen to the whole thing and then
answer it, Ji Ho!
How can you know that?
[You have an idea if you touch?]
- This side of the flesh, this area...
- Oh I... I remember, I remember!
- What is it?
Don't do it!
If you don't know, don't talk!
Blue team!
Shank of beef.
Yellow, yellow!
Brisket?
I thought it was going to be 'brisket'...
Jae Suk!
I don't think this is it. Beef from the inside ribs.
Blue team!
Thin flank?
Thin flank.
[Mommy...]
Itchy feet, itchy feet.
How is that 'Itchy feet'?
Mature age, mature age.
Jae Suk!
Pork Cheek Meat.
Jae Suk! Meat of the back neck.
[Older Brothers Getting Splashed Thanks to the Youngest]
- Hey, you!
- Neck meat.
Center heel of shank?
Really!
Neck meat!
Tongue fur?
[Only On One Side...]
- Why is only one side coming out?
[Okay, right on target]
[Then, the answer is?]
[Butt & Rump-
there is often less fat and rough meat]
Okay! The hint is...
the second consonant...
- 'D.'
- Jae Suk!
It's 'D', right?
- You sure you know what you're doing?
- Hurry up, hurry!
Sul... Sul...
[Out of time]
Sul...
Sul... Don?
Jae Suk!
Sul Doon. Sul Doon.
Sul Do. (Thick flank)
Sul Do.
That's too hard.
[Correct Answer]
[Finally, Yi Hyun Correct Answer]
- Come out.
- Come here.
Go in. You go in. Hey.
- I came out first.
Question's going out.
Which part is the thick skirt located
in which beef and pork have in common?
Thigh!
Yellow!
Front leg meat.
The thing above the tenderloin.
Red!
Stomach?
[Correct Answer]
He got it right! Got it right!
- The stomach, stomach.
- Stomach?
Because it's thick...
it's thick because it's chubby!
It's too difficult a question for Ji Ho.
Just two plus two is one!
Give us something like that!
One plus one is?
It's the next question.
A famous line from Drama, 'Jewel in the Palace',
which young Jang Geum says
- 'Because of the blank taste, it tastes like blank.'
- Answer!
- Red Team!
Yeon Shi (Ripe persimmon).
[Frustration]
Hong Shi (Ripe persimmon).
[Correct Answer]
[Yellow Team- Yi Hyun
Answers Two Questions]
- What's the correct answer?
- Hong Shi.
It's Hong Shi?
- Hey!
- Come here right now!
One more time!
[No mercy- Change players immediately]
Hey, go inside!
Hey, Yeon Shi and Hong Shi is the same thing!
- It's dried persimmon, just come in.
Pass with a total of three questions,
Yellow team answered two correctly]
Why say 'Yeon Shi', when it's 'Hong Shi?'
Ji Hyo!
Are you out of drinks?
Ji Hyo, it's okay.
You can't do that to me.
Hey, it's been a while.
Good boy, good boy.
Good boy, long time no see.
Good boy.
I have to film so get out.
Sayings Question.
It's a sayings question.
- Jae Suk's good at sayings...
- Ji Hyo, let's just lose!
If you have a good sense,
you get to eat 'this' at the Buddhist temple?
- Jae Suk!
- That's right!
Temple food.
Dried persimmon.
Is this a persimmon series?
Ji Hyo, don't say anything!
Rice offered to Buddha?
San Baek Sa.
Rice offered to Buddha
and San Baek Sa.
Ji Hyo, don't look back.
- It's a San baek Sa.
- Yes.
If you have a good sense,
you get to eat 'this' at the Buddhist temple.
'This'... goes well with pork.
- Red!
- Hurry up and say it!
- Salted Shrimp!
- I was going to say 'salted shrimp.'
-  [Correct Answer]
[Red Team Also Answers Two Questions]
- With Mexican hot peppers...
- Red!
Which mignon is it?
Filet Mignon.
Yellow! Yellow!
Jalapenos.
Jalapenos is right!
[Yellow Team Answers All Three Questions]
[You!]
You really got to win!
The two teams left have
to split second place.
- You're thankful to me now, right?
- Oh Ji Sup...
We misunderstood you.
[Rice Wrapped in Greens Meal]
[Nicely presented and abundant Snail
Rice Wrapped in Greens]
Hey this is snail soybean paste.
Gently place it on the green lettuce
The snail soybean paste looks good.
[Swallow in one shot]
Snail!
[The Red and Blue Teams who also passed
sample as well]
Hey you know this snail wrapped
rice in greens...
Eat a lot.
Can we eat some more rice?
Stop eating.
He's hungry that's why.
Why are you eating rice like that?
[This time chicken soup with rice]
Wow, we really ate all the meat.
[The effect of overeating slowly takes place]
Hey, you can't fall asleep.
[Falls asleep for real ths time]
I'm not sleeping.
[Deep Sleep]
Didn't you say you weren't going to sleep?
- Tell me the truth.
- I'll just sleep for five minutes.
Welcome, this round is going to be punishments.
[Yellow Team arrives at R11]
[Flying Fish punishment]
[One person answers the question,
while the other two take on the Flying Fish]
- It's a quiz so...
- Okay, I'll give you the quiz first...
[Kkuk, due to his shoulder and back, decides to answer the question]
[Yi Hyun and Kwang Soo ride the Flying Fish]
Aren't we going to wear life vests?
Both of you love yourselves very much...
I'll answer the question.
[As punishment- Without sampling,
they have to pass in order to go to the next round]
Running man...
Go all the way down
until your feet touch.
- If your legs don't touch, you'll get wet for sure.
- No.
- What happens to me?
- Are you that long?
Place your feet firmly down.
- Like that, okay.
[Feeling sorry]
I'll really get the answer right.
- Jong Guk, you really have to get it right.
- Yes, I will.
- I'll do well.
- You must.
The person who's suppose to answer the question,
could get it wrong?
[If the people riding the Flying Fish get the answer, it is counted.]
We're taking off!
- 37 x 98 x 26 is?
- What?
Thirty seven what?
Wait.
Thirty seven times ninety eight, what?
Thirty seven times!
Wait! 37 what?
[Flying Fish Takes off!]
[Flying Fish Flying Over Han River]
37 x 98...
7 x 8 = 56...
5 x 3 = 8?
What...
[Kwang Soo's hat...]
[Missing Hat]
[Mind is blank...]
30... 7! Multiplied by 98?
Multiply 27...37...
[Trying to figure out the question,
without calculating]
They're almost here. Now.
You said the last one was 27?
26?
37 x 98...
37 multiplied by...
[Yi Hyun tries her best to calculate]
Is it over?
Tell us the answer.
396?
It's wrong...jackpot...
[Go again.
- Wait]
598?
Next question,
22 x 73 x 42 is?
Wait... wait!
[Another take off!]
2 x 3= 6...
[Fly Again]
Oh no, if writing doesn't work,
how can we calculate mentally?
[Calculating in the midst of all this]
I apologize viewers...
I can't do this anymore...
Kim Jong Kook, you
need to get this right!
22 times 73 times 42...
[Blank]
I don't know.
[Buzzer]
Ahahaha...
He got it wrong again? Again?
Well, it's really--
[Then here they go again...]
You got it wrong again,
Jong Kook?!
Let's fight!
Wait, what did you say?
I don't know.
I really don't remember!
- Are you kidding me?
- I really can't remember!
I must've forgotten.
At the crispy rice restaurant
[Game board Jumanji: Complete
a word game in 30 seconds
beginning and ending with
'nooroongji' (crispy rice)]
[Is this a bomb?]
We're going to have to
choose words wisely.
A word that starts with 'noo?'
- No, a word that ends with 'noo.'
- Yeah, that's what I mean.
A word that ends with 'noo.'
Excuse me, everyone.
Please get out of the car now.
[In a daze...]
You guys have come here
to eat and sleep.
- We're eating again?
We're eating again?
- Seriously?
- They're already here.
That's it, I'm not bringing anything.
We're in trouble.
- We're eating again?
- What are we eating this time?
'Game board Jumanji...'
Word game that starts and
ends with 'nooroongji.'
We're eating again?
[Highly nutritious and delicious
nooroongji (crispy rice)!]
- Okay.
- So we start with 'nooroongji,' right?
I'm scared.
Ready... start!
Nooroongji!
Jirungi!
(worm)
Ireumpyo!
(name tag)
Pyo In Bong...
(name of a comedian)
Bongoori!
(peak)
Ri...sbon!
(Lisbon, capital of Portugal)
- Bon!
- Bon?
Hurry!
- Bon.
- I don't know!
Say 'bonshim.'
(real intention)
- Get it right!
- 'Bonshim.'
Bonshim!
(real intention)
'Shim Chung Yi!'
(name of a TV program)
Yibbal!
(tooth)
Bbal-re!
(laundry)
- Hurry!
- I don't have a word!
Hey! Turn that thing
the other way!
[Boom!]
Whoa!
Why couldn't you come
up with a word?
- That was so loud!
- You were wrong!
- What starts with 're?'
- Eliminated!
- Move over.
- Move.
- 'Remicon' (ready-mixed concrete).
- Lemon.
I just couldn't think of
one at that moment.
- Do you know how to play?
- Of course we do!
I played this game while eating
at the same time once.
And... games like this are meant
to be played in a leisurely way.
- Put that thing down.
- Hey, it's not going to kill us!
You shouldn't be so scared... like this.
Yeah, you should do it like this.
But that's why it's fun!
You have to be like this.
Start with 'aehobak' (green pumpkin).
Go!
Aehobak.
(green pumpkin)
Baksoo.
(applause)
Soobak.
(watermelon)
Bagaji.
(gourd)
Bagaji? That isn't
spelled with 'bak!'
Bak! Bak!
What? Just say something
that starts with 'bak.'
- A word that starts with 'bak.'
- Hold on!
Bak Nam Jung.
(Korean singer)
Jung Bal San.
(name of train station)
San Gi Seuk.
(foot of a mountain)
Seuk Gom Bal.
(bear's paw)
Bal... Bal Gil Jil.
(kick)
Jil Gyung Yi.
(plantain)
Yi Reum Pyo.
(name tag)
Pyo Joo Bak.
(gourd dipper)
- What word did we start with?
- 'Aehobak.'
[Boom!]
Aahhh!
What was that?
[And they were so confident...]
What was the last word we had?
It ended with 'bak.'
Then 'bak-e.' (charity)
We could've ended with that!
- That's right! 'Aehobak.'
- See?
Then why--
Darn...
- All right, your turn.
- Come on!
- Losing once is normal.
- Hey!
- Bring it on!
Cut it out, you guys.
- Hey!
Gogooma. (sweet potato)
Start!
Gogooma!
We need to end with 'go.'
Mazinga. (Mazinger - name
of an anime series)
Gazette.
T-trot... Try!
What word starts with 'yi?'
- Yi...
- Has to be a Korean word.
Yisa!
(move)
Sago!
(accident)
Oh!
[Started with 'go,' and
they've come back to 'go'!]
Hurry and say 'gogooma!'
Gochoo!
(pepper)
[Oh dear...]
- Say 'gogooma!'
- Gochoo!
- Gogooma!
- You're supposed to say gogooma!
[Fail...]
You were supposed
to say 'gogooma!'
I forgot we'd started with 'gogooma.'
I thought they were
going to win for sure.
Aaahhhh!
[The question's become much easier!
7 times 11 plus 59!]
[Utter exhaustion]
I'm scared... I'm scared.
[Calculating in his head?]
Can you repeat the question?
7 times 11...
77!
Plus 59...
I'm sure Jong Kook
will get it right.
What was the question?
Fifty...
Aaahhhh!
What did they say?
56?
Was it 77 plus 96?
- 77 plus...
- Three. Is that right? Three...
- Is 56 right?
- I think so.
This thing really makes you stupid...
Did you get it?
The correct answer is 136. Yeah.
13... 136.
[Finally... the correct answer!]
You're dead!
I can't do math. I need a pencil
and paper. I'm horrible at math.
Where did my hat go?
That--isn't that my hat?
Can I go in and get it?
Do you actually see it?
[Floating cap?]
- Is it not there?
- (No.)
No, my hat!
(sobs)
[My hat...]
That was fun.
Riding the banana boat was fun.
As long as that die doesn't land on 1,
you can go straight to the final destination.
If it lands on 1,
where do we go?
If it lands on 1...
then the banana boat.
It's okay. Get a hold of yourself!
Hey, it's okay.
As long as we don't get a 1.
The odds are in our favor!
- It's okay.
- Yeah, go ahead.
Throw it high!
[It's a two!]
It's a two!
If it landed on 1, I was going
to kick it into the water!
Get ready to go to your final destination.
[En route to the final destination]
Dashima. (kelp)
Start!
Dashima!
- Remember, we started with 'dashima.'
- Mazinga.
Gama!
(palanquin)
Mabu.
(horseman)
Buddumak.
(furnace)
- What word did we start with?
- Dashima.
- Buddumak. (furnace)
- Hehe.
Makgeolri!
(Korean rice wine)
- 'Ri?'
- Yeah, 'ri.'
Ribbon!
- Bondo. (highway)
- Bond!
- Wait!
Bond girl.
- Geollaejil. (mopping)
- Geollaejil.
Hey, Jae Suk!
Jil... jilso.
(nitrogen)
So-soda!
- Dashima!
[Success!]
You hate us now, don't you?
Hahaha!
Let's at least get this sucker.
Ow, that hurts!
This guy's good at acting wimpy.
All right, congrats to you guys.
[Blue team is headed
for the final destination]
The road to the final stop
is pretty narrow.
I wonder what we'll be doing
at the final destination?
Wonder what the final destination is?
It's the finish line!
I think we're pretty ahead.
They said the first team to get there
will receive an advantage.
Let's see what that is.
[Blue team vs. yellow team:
on to the final destination!]
At least we got a 3 and
were able to get out of there.
- That's true.
- Let's go!
Drive carefully.
[The rain pours down
harder and harder...]
[Which team will arrive first?]
[Final destination:
'G' Gymnasium]
[The yellow team is the first to arrive!]
Hey, we must be the first ones to arrive!
Huh?
What's this?
[The thing waiting for them
at the final destination is...]
[A gigantic game board!]
[And dominoes in the middle?]
- You see those yellow dominoes?
- Yes.
Line those dominoes up
along the path...
And if they cause all the dominoes in
the hamburger design to fall, you win.
- Whoa, what?
- We start now?
[It's a race! The advantage
is getting a head start!]
Hurry! Hurry!
Hurry, hurry, hurry!
Hey, what's this?
[The red team arrives too!]
[Make all the dominoes
on the board fall]
This isn't hard.
We can do it.
Sixteen.
I put those there.
Oh no!
Shoot.
- Why did you knock them all down?
- I didn't do it! They fell on their own!
How can they fall on their own?
Maybe they have feet of their own!
Wait, wait, wait!
Hey, wait! You have to
line them up straight.
- You're not lining them up straight.
- Ugh.
- Whatever. It's fine.
- You need to do it properly.
Space them out evenly.
Hurry, we don't have time to talk!
Can't we play the 'rip each other's
tags off' game instead?
- Stop talking and help me!
- But I like that game.
- Hurry and help me!
- Actually, I'm a mole.
What are you talking about?
Look at my back.
Don't believe me?
Ugh, seriously.
[After 20 minutes has elapsed...]
[The yellow team has almost finished
stacking their dominoes]
- Can someone distract the yellow team?
- They're almost done!
Oh no!
Yes!
[Big mistake for the yellow team!]
- Yes, yes!
- That's good for us!
Jong Kook!
- It's okay.
- What do you mean it's okay?
Yes, yes, yes!
Okay, we can do this!
- Hey, watch where you're stepping.
- Okay, okay.
What, are we doing it like this?
[In a zigzag fashion]
[Everyone's almost finished]
[30 minutes has lapsed]
We just have one more stack to go.
Place them carefully. Carefully!
We can win this!
Put it here.
Hurry, hurry.
Now all we have to do is knock them down.
That's a lot of curry.
Okay, we're done.
Let's knock them down!
- We're done!
[The red and blue teams have finished
stacking their curry dominoes!]
Hurry and push!
[Kick]
Push!
Push, push, push!
[The two teams start at
almost the same time!]
Good, good!
Go, go, go!
Nice!
Go, go!
That's it!
They're going! They're going!
Go, go, go!
Nice!
[Please don't stop and
reach the center!]
[Which team's dominoes
will arrive first?]
Go, go, go!
[Please...]
Yes, that's it!
That's it!
[Red team wins!]
[Red team is the winner!]
[Riiip]
- What was that?
- I ripped them off! I did it!
You're supposed to rip
them off when you win!
This is great! I didn't
think we'd win.
[Red team wins the prize]
I ripped off the name tags.
[The prize is a golden spoon]
- It's a golden spoon.
- Oh, a golden spoon!
- Yi Hyun, what did you think about today?
- I had a lot of fun.
- You mean that?
- Yes.
You're not acting, are you?
I'll just watch the show
from my home from now on.
[It must've been hard for her...]
I think we're the crazy ones
for always being on this show!
I'm glad to have come on this show,
which is very dear to me.
- And to have won.
- Ah, because you won?
- He really liked being here.
- He really means it.
He really liked it.
It was an honor to be
on this show and to win.
And this... I'm so happy
I got to tear them off.
[Rip]
- Thank you.
- Thanks.
Now that's how a real
idiot is supposed to act.
Um, I don't want to go that far...
You know, after this show ends,
I have to put on a suit and go home.
- Now that's really stupid!
- Hey, you should learn from him.
Subtitles by DramaFever
You've got me under
your spell right now.
[The devilish Gumiho
from Korean legend...]
You push your elbows
back, like this.
[It's Kim Soo Mi!]
[The five Gumiho sisters!]
1, 2, 3--
Kim Soo Mi! Kim Soo Mi!
She going to marry you!
[They're going to be a handful for
these guys of Running Man!]
Hey! You're dead!
[Kim Soo Mi shows us
how to rule over men!]
[But... she ends up falling
for Yoo Jae Suk instead?]