[Running Animal Kingdom]
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Rain drizzling down on an
amusement park.]
[A joyous place for animals and
children alike.]
- Look at all this rain.
- We're at the amusement park!
- I haven't been here in forever!
I sincerely welcome you to the amusement
park in the midst of this spring rain.
- What are we doing here?
- I'm cold!
- It's cold out here!
Since we're at the amusement park,
should we ride some rides?
[Even though it is cold out,
they can't skip out on the rides!]
[This is great!]
Bye!
- Is this ride scary?
- No, this isn't a scary one.
[Off to the 'Not-so-scary' ride.]
[Everyone's boarding the ride.]
- I used to ride this one all the time.
- You've been on this ride before?
- Of course, I have.
- I've never been on this ride before.
It's water!
There's water!
No!
[Off on their way down the rapids.]
[Excited like a group of little kids.]
[Water...]
[Most water-logged seat...]
[Combination of getting soaked,
and getting water slapped.]
Why is it just my seat that's
getting soaked like this?
[On the other hand,
Giraffe, Blank-Ji, Ro-Ro, and Kkuk...]
No!
[Getting sucked down the rapids...]
We've successfully climbed over our first hill.
- We'll be at the treasure chest soon!
- But this isn't the end.
[Two expeditionaries falling right
into sync with their story lines.]
What are you doing?
Bend down your heads!
[There are anacondas?]
- I thought we were sure as dead!
- They were bent on killing us!
Look!
A tribe!
Where?
Save us!
It's tribe members!
- Save us!
- The one who controls the time!
The one who controls the space!
- My butt is all soaking wet!
- I hate this!
I didn't bring any change of clothing!
- Who's that?
- Who is it?
[Down the stream...]
[A man and a woman standing by
to observe the Running Man members?]
[Could they be today's guests?]
- There's a man over there.
- Who is it?
- The guy...
- Why isn't he showing us his face?
Who is it?
Who's the guy?
- Who are you?
- The girl looks like Jessica.
Who's the guy?
Who are you?
What's that?
Who is that up there?
[The second group also discovers
the mysterious figures.]
Is that Eun Ji Won?
[Turn around!
Turn around!]
- What are you doing?
- We can kind of see your name tag.
Is he a dummy?
[Duh... the name tag!]
- Ji Won! We can see your name tag!
- Hello!
[Have we been caught?]
You can see my name tag?
- You can see my name tag?
- We can see your name tag!
- Hi!
[Eun Ji Won and Jessica.]
Jessica!
[Happily greeting one another.]
What are you doing on here?
Great to see you!
- It's been so long since I've seen Ji Won.
- Ji Won and Jessica are like family!
I thought I'd never get to see you
guesting on our show!
- Why would you say that?
- I know what you mean.
Today's race is...
Running Animal Kingdom.
[Running Animal Kingdom]
- Running Animal Kingdom?
- That sounds like a perfect fit.
[Running Man members' animal characters
that are the topic of internet conversations.]
Yoo Jae Suk is the grasshopper.
Ji Suk Jin is the impala,
Kim Jong Kook is the tiger.
Gary is the monkey, Ha Ha is the penguin,
Song Ji Hyo is the cat
and Lee Kwang Soo is the giraffe.
And as for our today's guests,
for the remainder of the day...
Eun Ji Won will be the panda,
as per his nickname.
- Panda?
- His nickname is the panda?
- What about Jessica?
- What is she?
She'll be the rabbit since she's so adorable.
[Is Jessica embarrassed?]
- You know that's not right!
- Do you not like that?
I think Ji Hyo would be better
suited as the rabbit.
How about... a poisonous snake?
- What did you say?
- How can you compare her to a snake?
[Elementary school level jokes that
just keep on going.]
- What do you mean, a poisonous snake?
- Something regal... like a cobra?
Every time you succeed
a mission today
you'll get the chance to earn something that
will become very useful at the final mission.
Let's move over to the mission location.
[Off to the safari for their first mission.]
Everyone, be careful!
The safari is about to start!
- I think this is going to be so much fun!
- Something could be lurking in here.
[What is the safari mission that's been
prepared for the Running Man members?]
- I have something for each one of you.
- Okay.
[Something inside the envelopes?]
Is there a mission inside the card?
- What does the 'elephant' mean?
- What is this?
[Giraffe's says, 'Giraffe'.]
[Everyone each receives a card with
an animal written on the inside.]
- A rhino.
- I have the rhino.
[Hm?]
- What is that?
- What did he get?
[A two-humped camel!]
[It's somehow fitting...]
- Why does it suit you so well?
- Suk Jin...
I got the white tiger.
What is the white tiger?
These are the animals that you will
all have to meet from this moment.
When you go see these animals,
you'll learn what your mission will be.
[Is it going to be like the panda mission
they had to do in Hong Kong?]
- You may get started.
- Should we go?
[Entering the safari.]
[What kind of missions are waiting
for them on the other side?]
[Even though the safari is usually done
while riding around in a car...]
[Running Man members will be doing
this mission on foot!]
[But, only white tiger Jong Kook
may go in a car.]
Why are you the only one
riding in a car?
- Sit down right here.
- What are you here, PD Myuk?
Good luck with the camel!
I have the flamingo.
[Gary's is the flamingo.]
[Come on... do you really think he was
given the mussel mission?]
What kind of a game do you think
he can play with mussels?
[A flamingo...]
- Look! Double-humped camel!
- Where?
[The double-humped camels
makes their appearance.]
[Hello?]
Why did I have to get
the double-humped camels?
[Imitating them?]
Giraffe!
It's the giraffe!
[Kwang Soo and Ji Won
discovers the giraffes.]
[Giraffe finally meets the real giraffes.]
Giraffes!
Giraffe!
[Running Man Giraffe meeting
the real giraffes.]
You look like them.
[Rhino]
[Even with their massive bodies,
they appear to be quite docile.]
I think there's something there.
It's a baby lion.
Why are you running?
[Baby lion, Ray,
born a mere 80 days ago!]
Look at her running towards it
as we back away from it.
What to do, what to do?
It's so cute!
- It's weird how much she likes it.
- Hello.
- Hi there!
Is it a baby lion?
Oh, I think I scared it. Sorry.
That's not a baby lion...
If you look at its eyes,
it's a full grown lion.
[Just staring at it while
keeping their distance from the lion.]
You poor thing.
Did I scare you? I'm so sorry.
[Saying their greetings while staying
far away from the animal.]
We have to go find the elephant.
It's staring at me.
Look at it!
Look at the way its claws
are standing out.
- Ji Hyo, we're leaving.
- Okay, go.
- I can't believe she's not scared.
- That's a full grown lion.
- Isn't that a full grown lion?
- That's a lion.
Hi.
[The only female member, Ji Hyo
moves right in to start petting.]
Hi.
Don't be nervous.
It's an honor to meet you.
I can't believe I'm touching
a lion right now.
Isn't that Eun Ji Won?
Ji Won!
- What are you going to see?
- The elephant.
The elephant is over this way.
- The mission is no joke!
- What's the mission?
Jae Suk... Jae Suk.
Your mission could be having to pluck
a hair from the elephant or something.
[The mission is to pull the hair
off the elephant?]
- Ji Won's getting started on his rants.
- Pull the hair off an elephant?
- What is she doing?
- That's Ji Hyo.
Ji Hyo isn't afraid of any animals.
The lions are even leashed up,
and they're just roaming around.
- Really?
- The giraffes are just walking around.
- It really is the nature out here.
- It's like the amazon.
Lions are very sensitive.
We just met a young lion.
It's not the amazon, but Africa.
- Really?
- There are no lions in the amazon.
Why wouldn't there be lions
in the amazon?
- Where are there lions in the amazon?
- Have you seen it for yourself?
- This is Africa.
- Isn't the amazon a jungle too?
- You're driving me nuts.
- Aren't there lions in the jungle?
If it was just one of them,
I can attempt to explain.
But with all three of them together,
I have to repeat myself over and over.
- Amazons and jungles are the same thing.
- Isn't it the same thing?
[Lions exist in the amazon vs.
lions do not exist in the amazons.]
- They can't survive in the amazon.
- Have you seen it for yourself?
You don't know, you don't know...
you don't know about the amazon...
You don't know...
you're an idiot...
He says lions don't exist in the amazon.
[Just then, the car carrying Kkuk
makes its entrance.]
Are you trying to valet that thing?
- It says 'valet' on it.
- Valley!
- Can't you read?
- Seriously...
- It says 'valley' on it.
- That's not what it says!
- The door's open!
- Huh?
- This is open!
- I know!
- Let us come with you!
- Where are you going?
Look!
It's going in the water!
- That's so cool.
- It's turning into a boat.
[Wow... going in the water
just like that?]
What is this?
Why are we going in the water?
This is amazing!
- I can't believe that!
- Look, it's just going in the water!
- Look at the way it's just going.
- I can't believe I'm seeing this.
It just turned into a boat.
- Wow... it turned into a boat.
- It's a boat now.
- Look at that thing.
- The car turned into a boat.
- Transformer!
- Jinx!
I said it too.
I'm serious.
- I swear, I said it too.
- The three of you think alike.
[His little brothers with like minds...]
To be the leader... of you three...
- Of us three?
- Say what?
What do you mean by that comment?
Seriously, you three...
It's a lion... it's a lion!
[At last... the white lions
are in front of his eyes!]
[Force]
[What?]
[What is that tiger doing here?]
The real scary thing is that someone
went in to install a camera in there.
Just who was it that went in there
to install that camera?
[While the lions were sleeping...]
Look up there next to the camera!
Look at that!
Hi! Guys!
Hi!
[Total disinterest]
You've now seen the lions.
[What is his mission?]
[If you can get all six of the lions to go
on top of the boulder, you succeed.]
What is this? What are you saying?
How can I get in there?
Do you see the boulder?
[Get all six of the lions
on top of that boulder?]
The lions really like that boulder.
You have to use whatever method
to get their attention...
and get a picture to prove that you did it
in order to succeed the mission.
Can I throw something?
Maybe throw some food up there?
Guys!
[As the tiger calls out to them...]
[Staring the tiger down?]
[What do you want?]
Guys!
[An audience of lions that
shows up out of nowhere.]
Lions!
Over here!
Go on up there.
That's right... the king has to go up.
If the king goes up, the rest will follow.
Look, the rest are following!
Get on up there.
Go on, get up there.
That's right, get up there.
If you go up, the rest will follow.
Go on up there.
It's staring up at the camera.
Get up there.
[Wondering if it should go up or not?]
Go up there.
That's right... head on up there.
Go up on the boulder.
The boulder!
There you go. There you go.
The king has to go up there.
Leader!
Lion king!
Simba!
Leader!
Go on up there!
Lion king!
No, you can't sit down.
Don't lay down!
You can't lay down!
Lion king, you can't lay down.
Stand up.
What is he doing?
Hey!
Hey, you!
What is he doing down there?
[Tiger trying to engage
the lion in a conversation.]
Hey, you brat!
[Zero interest]
What am I doing here?
Do you seen that
lone elephant down there?
That is the infamous elephant, Koshik.
I think I've seen that elephant on TV.
- That is the only known elephant to speak.
- So?
[The mission is to get Koshik to
say the word, 'like'.]
[Flabbergasted]
No matter...
that's still just an animal.
All your missions are similar?
Can't you see Jong Kook?
Yes, I do see him.
[On the other side of the glass,
the tiger is screaming at the lion.]
Koshik!
That's right!
I saw you on TV!
[Is he slowly making his approach since
Jae Suk seems to know him?]
Koshik!
Do you like flowers?
Koshik, do you like flowers?
Be quiet!
You be quiet!
I'm trying to do my mission!
[Missions forgotten, the Grasshopper and
the Tiger snarling at each other.]
Hey!
Don't lay down and get up!
Koshik!
Hang on, Koshik!
Do you like apples?
Koshik, do you like apples?
[Absolute silence]
Do you like apples?
Koshik, do you like apples?
Don't laugh.
I'm seriously trying to do the mission.
Koshik, do you like apples?
Keep it down!
Hey! You keep it down!
Can't you see I'm trying to do my mission?
There's no Koshik here!
Don't lie!
- Koshik, do you like?
- Simba!
Is this an experiment or something?
Is this an experiment?
Kiss!
[Jessica researching the rhinos.]
Koshik!
[Koshik having lost
his interest in Jae Suk.]
What am I doing here?
He's not even paying attention.
Koshik!
Ha Ha!
What are you doing?
What's he doing?
[Scaredy cat Ro-Ro on the other hand...]
My name is Haroro,
and I love all elephants.
[Must feed three different types
of snacks to an elephant.]
- Can it put it up here?
- Yes.
I don't think I can do this.
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry, Haji.
Haji... wait!
[The elephant just wants the snack.]
Wait... you're coming on too fast.
Seriously, I'm sorry!
I really don't think I can do this.
[Is he giving up on his mission?]
[Gary's mission with the flamingos is?]
Must take a picture of the flamingos as
seen in the picture. Where's the picture?
If you take a picture of them making
the heart shape, you succeed your mission.
So you want me to take a picture of
the flamingos in this stance?
Whether it's today, tomorrow,
or next year?
[As long as you get it done...]
Do they have to be in love to do this?
Seriously... how am I supposed
to do that?
[Will they get into this pose for him?]
Don't you guys play the cookie stick game
amongst yourselves as a couple?
Guys!
Okay... kiss time.
Starting now for the next minute...
it's kissing time.
[What's he saying?]
With your hearts open wide...
Everyone start loving on each other.
It's really big.
[Getting scared as the real giraffe
starts to approach him.]
No.
Come this way.
[Is he one of us?]
- What's with the tongue?
- It's way too close.
- The tongue...
- Giraffe!
[Shocked after seeing the length
of its tongue!]
Kwang Soo, is your tongue like that too?
[Similar]
Do you want to eat this?
[It seems as though it wants
to eat some of the food on the table.]
Do I just feed it like this?
No, that's just the camera.
Camera.
Do you want a close shot?
[A huge snort.]
This is the first time I've ever seen
a real live giraffe.
This is your first time?
[You're that human giraffe?]
[Kwang Soo the Giraffe's mission is a
united 'O-X' quiz with the giraffes.]
[Kwang Soo's answer and the
giraffe's answer must match to pass.]
[Will Kwang Soo be able to find
consensus with the real giraffes?]
- Here's your first question.
- Okay.
Lee Kwang Soo is handsome.
[Lee Kwang Soo is handsome?]
[What the heck?
Chooses, yes, without even hesitating?]
Am I done?
Choose something that the giraffe likes
to eat as your answer.
Both of these are their favorite foods.
Then I'll just offer the same stuff.
- That'll work.
- Right?
[If the giraffe chooses 'O', then he
succeeds the mission right away.]
There it is.
Ask the question.
Lee Kwang Soo is handsome.
[Heading straight to the 'O'?]
[Oh my...]
[Fascinating...
Does he understand the question?]
- Fail.
- You should've chosen 'X'.
- I'm pretty alluring though.
- Alluring doesn't mean handsome.
I'm pretty handsome...
That lion needs to keep it down.
Giraffes may be sensitive because of the lion.
[The chief lion letting out
a ferocious roar.]
Simba!
[The white lion reacting to the lion herd
making their appearance in the next area.]
What's wrong?
These guys are really angry.
- Koshik!
- Everyone, be quiet!
- Come here!
- Giraffes are sensitive animals.
- Come here, Koshik.
- You're being the loudest right now.
These guys are really angry.
[What's wrong with them?]
Simba!
[Finally heading towards the boulder...]
Koshik, do you like flowers?
Keep it down!
Koshik, do you like it?
[Koshik heading towards Jae Suk again.]
[Impersonating the zookeeper.]
I prepared something for you.
Koshik!
- What did you prepare? Tell me!
- I wasn't talking to you!
- What? What did you prepare?
- It's not for you! I wasn't talking to you.
Just what in the world is it?
Koshik? Do you like?
Do you like this?
Do you like? Do you like?
Koshik, do you like?
Koshik, do you like this?
Like?
Do you like?
Koshik, do you like?
[Reticent]
[Elephant show]
[What's he doing?]
Why are you looking at me like that?
This is just a mission.
Why are you staring at me like that?
Why are you looking at me like that
from behind the camera?
I'll be really honest with you.
I'm here to film the show.
To be honest,
this is the first time I'm seeing you.
To be honest, I know that you only talk
when you're in the mood to talk
and I know that it's not something that you
like to do just because you're told to do it.
But... do it for me just this once.
Let's be cool here.
Koshik...
Do you like?
Hey!
[Blank Ji is getting to know
the baby lion, Ray.]
- Ray...
- He's a little nervous.
So lions can get nervous too?
Ray...
- He's calmed down though.
- He seems much calmer.
Ray...
[Even giving him his bottle
in an attempt to get closer to him.]
You have to be cautious.
Don't scare him.
[Snuggling into Blank Ji's embrace.]
Hi, Ray.
[Blank Ji is carrying out her mission.]
[Attempting to carry out his mission
with his jumping skills.]
[Dissed by the double-humped camels?]
[What is he doing?]
[The two camels making
Big-nosed Brother sweat it out.]
[Not quite the illusion of being
on top of the camels...]
[Weak jumping skills...]
[Blank Ji attempting her mission.]
[If the baby lion, Ray runs over
to Blank Ji, she succeeds her mission.]
[Having come to much friendlier terms,
will he go straight to Blank Ji?]
[Oh!]
[Wow! Right into Blank Ji's embrace!]
[Blank Ji succeeds her mission!]
- Thank you.
- You've succeeded your mission.
['R' sticker as a proof of her success.]
Kwang Soo!
Is Kwang Soo ugly?
That's right, he's ugly.
What are you doing?
[Giraffe readily accepting it as if
it understands her question.]
He is ugly or handsome?
[Again, readily accepting
at the mention of ugly.]
- What are they doing?
- Hang on.
Look at them run.
- They really do run like me.
- They look just like you when you run.
[Immediately imitating them?]
[Possessed by the giraffes' spirit?]
You really...
you really do look like them.
Lee Kwang Soo is afraid of the tiger.
Afraid of the tiger?
Yes, I'm afraid of the tiger.
[Chooses the 'O' again.]
[Giraffe has to eat from his
left hand to win the mission.]
[Going to the opposite side
without hesitation.]
Please... please!
[Pulling the food back away from him,
and re-attempting the mission.]
[Please eat from the left.]
No, no!
[The right hand must appear to be tastier...]
He ate from the wrong hand!
Koshik... do you like?
How are you feeling?
You feeling okay?
Are you not feeling good?
So-so?
Tired?
Koshik, are you okay?
- What's okay?
- Are you done?
- No.
- Koshik can say, 'like'.
- Really?
- I think I saw it on TV.
Do you like?
[Barging in to intrude on
someone else's mission.]
He's not even muttering a sound.
Are you sure this one is Koshik?
Do you like?
[Oh!]
Like.
[Koshik spoke!]
- He said it!
- He did it!
- Eun Ji Won did it.
- Why did you do that?
I heard he only speaks once a year.
[How could silent Koshik...]
Koshik, do you like?
How did you do it?
Do you like?
Koshik, do you like?
Like.
[He spoke again!]
He speaks!
Koshik can speak!
This is...
Here, Koshik! Eat this!
Koshik!
Have some treats!
Koshik, do you like it even with the peel?
- Koshik, do you like it?
- Like.
[Like]
Hey... he really can speak.
[Succeeds his mission thanks to Ji Won
who came over out of boredom.]
Koshik finally opened his mouth.
Koshik!
Thanks, Koshik!
Koshik, do you like bananas?
No, I don't like it!
[The tiger speaks again...]
- I said, I don't like it!
- Hey, muscles!
- I hate it!
- You don't like it?
I hate it!
- Muscles, you don't like it?
- I said, I hate it!
- Muscles says he doesn't like it.
- What is he doing?
Muscles has to get all six of
them to go up on the boulder.
- Guys!
- All six of them.
[All of the white lions are enjoying
their own free time.]
Simba, you're killing me.
Simba, this is too hard.
[Not even acknowledging what
the tiger is saying.]
[Is he trying to speak in
the lion's language?]
This is what you call, rapport.
Take a good look, okay?
[Boasting after barely squeaking by
to pass his mission.]
Pay attention, Koshik.
[Is he trying to get Koshik to
say a different word?]
Lay down.
Lay down, Koshik.
Lay down!
[Oh?]
- Lay down!
- Lay down.
He said it!
[Great job!
He spoke again!]
I'm going to go insane here!
Koshik, you're so good!
Thanks so much, Koshik!
Tauros!
[Finally starting to call him
by the right name.]
- Get down!
- Tauros!
- Get up there!
[Starting to hinder the tiger as soon as
he completes his own mission.]
- Four of them are up there!
- Come down from there!
- Tauros!
- Come down!
- Get down!
- Tauros!
Tauros!
Tauros, get up there!
- Why don't you get up there too?
- These guys keeps looking up there!
[What did you say?]
What?
You suddenly can't talk?
[Tiger starting to get extremely annoyed.]
Don't you know how to talk?
Go away!
Get away from there!
[What are those two doing?]
Seriously... what temper.
[Goal is six. There are
currently four on the boulder.]
[Emergency weapon?
Pulling out the raw chicken.]
[Huh? Is it food?]
[Will he be able to throw it
up onto the boulder?]
[Um...]
Sorry guys!
[Is he trying to tease us?]
[Making another attempt.]
[Right under the boulder.]
[Uh... it's stepping down.]
[If anything, his bad throw is causing
them to step down.]
You should eat in a comfortable position.
Go on up there.
[What?
Five on the boulder now?]
Another one stepped up there!
Wait, I need two more.
[Interested?]
Look at them.
They're finally showing some interest.
[White lions showing some interest
with the food in his hand.]
You're the only one left.
You just need to step up there.
Just you.
You just have to step up there!
[Misses his throw again.]
You!
Get on up there!
[They're lions. Not even
paying attention to the tiger...]
Why aren't you going up there?
Go up there.
[A long distance to throw
on top of the boulder.]
I'm seriously about to lose my mind.
[Keeps missing his throws.]
Since you've had enough to eat,
I want you to listen to me.
Get up there.
[Is it getting up because of
what it heard?]
Get up there.
I want you to get up there.
[Four of them are staying up there...]
Get up there.
I just need you to get up there.
Where are you going?
Where are you going after all
you've eaten? Get up there!
[It's going up!]
[It went up!]
It went up.
Okay, hang on.
[Now if this one last lion will go up...]
Get up.
You're the only one left to go up.
[Continuing to talk to convince the
lion to get up on the boulder.]
You're the only one left.
We can end this battle if you go up.
Go up there.
There you go.
Hurry up and get up there.
There you go! Get up there!
Get up there!
There you go!
[Oh?]
Get up there!
Get your hind legs up there!
You have to get your hind
legs up there!
Your hind legs!
Jump up there!
What are you doing?
What's wrong with you?
Just get up there!
[Why does the heli-camera have to
come up right at this moment?]
Get down here, camera!
Camera, get down!
[This moment when only the hind legs
needs to get up on the boulder...]
Why is that camera moving right now?
[What is that?]
Get down!
Lower the camera!
Why did you bring that up?
That one is about to go up!
Go up!
Get up!
It's going up!
[It's going up?]
[The hind legs are finally...]
[How can this be!]
[All six of the white lions are
on top of the boulder!]
It's up there!
It went up!
There you go!
See?
They're all up there.
[The battle of will between the tiger
and the lions is finally over.]
Success.
That was way too hard.
I, Lee Kwang Soo am smarter
than Eun Ji Won.
Yes, or no.
[It needs to eat from
the 'O' hand to succeed.]
[The opposite again...]
[Making another attempt]
[Undeterred and going back to the 'X'.]
You're never going to get it.
Eat this one.
Kwang Soo, it ate the 'X'.
[Showing us their mutual
liking for each other?]
- Are you really...
- He's really become one of them.
- That's insane.
- He's not joking around.
He's become a real giraffe now.
I didn't know I'd go this far either!
I really didn't want to go that far!
[His affection with the giraffe
throwing everyone in for a loop.]
[Oh my...]
Even the giraffe is shocked!
[Giraffe kiss]
[Delicious]
- Your nickname was righteously given.
- Thank you.
Give me the next question.
[Correctly guess the three foods that
the rhinos really like.]
Here, this is delicious.
[Trying out the banana first.]
There you go.
[It really likes it!]
Sweet potato!
Sweet potato, banana, and carrots.
Wrong.
Guys!
Let's just get it over with, okay?
What's the problem?
Let's kiss!
It's okay.
I'll pretend I didn't see it.
I think I got it.
[Did he finally succeed in shooting
a heart pose?]
[Oh... in the middle?]
[Shape of a heart.]
Success?
Thanks, my friends!
I'm leaving!
Keep loving each other!
Love isn't easy.
Come here, come here!
[The giraffe must eat from
the 'O' hand to succeed...]
[Will it happen this time?]
[What got into him?
He's heading to the 'O'!]
Success!
[Is this what consensus is all about?]
You did good.
Good job.
Success.
[Earns the 'R' sticker as a sign
of having succeeded his mission.]
[What is Ji Won's mission?]
[If at least three giraffes stay in the
camera shot for five seconds to succeed.]
[Will he be able to succeed in his mission?]
You can't really see the shot.
[Giraffes slowly starting to
come into the shot.]
- There they are,
- Right now is your chance.
The Rose of Sharon is blooming...
you stay right there!
That's the perfect model pose!
[One giraffe standing motionless.]
- I think you can do it.
- You stay just like that.
Just stay right there.
Why is that one running around?
[You think it'd be that easy?]
We're going to start this game, okay?
'The rose of sharon is blooming.'
That one just won't stop
running around.
You failed.
- Right now. Right now is your chance.
- Do it right now.
The rose of sharon is blooming!
One, two, three, four...
Four of them.
[Huh?]
Hey! What are you doing?
Stop doing that.
[The human giraffe confusing
the other giraffes.]
Is he allowed to do this?
- Is he allowed to obstruct like this?
- This is obstruction?
- What were you doing then?
- I was just running because I was happy.
Seriously... I almost had it!
The sooner you succeed your mission,
the worse it is for me.
Why?
Because it took me so long for mine,
there will be too great of a difference.
Stop lying!
Are you just trying to get in my way?
- You don't have to go that far.
- You're always changing the story!
- I'm not changing the story.
- And what is that? It's too noisy!
It has to film us.
Now is the chance.
It's the perfect chance.
Everyone to the back.
I don't know.
What do you think?
- How did it go? Are you done?
- Ugh, it's him!
- Are you done?
- Why are there so many people around?
Why are there so many
Lee Kwang Soo's around?
Please keep it down.
You're ruining my mission!
If you're done, then just leave!
Guys!
What?
[Huh?]
Eat.
- Seriously...
- Eat this.
Get away!
What's wrong with his temper?
I said, get away from me.
[Another attempt]
Rose of sharon is blooming!
All three of them are the screen.
This is the chance!
[Huh?]
Hey... hey!
I seriously don't hit people like this.
I'm trying to help you right now.
Wait. Isn't it a success whether
he's in the shot or not?
[Including Kwang Soo?]
[His plan is to include the human giraffe,
Kwang Soo in the mission as well.]
- Then you're saying I'm one of them?
- You're just like these giraffes.
Even your coloring is similar.
I'll get you in there.
Why don't you get in the shot?
Come on, get in.
[The human giraffe is ultimately
included in the shot.]
- You stay right there.
- They're looking at me.
[Oh? It is staring at Kwang Soo.]
[Is this the human giraffe and
the real giraffe communication?]
[Attempt to succeed the challenge with
Kwang Soo as one of the giraffes.]
That one is staring at Kwang Soo
without even moving.
See that one?
The one staring at Kwang Soo?
The rose of sharon is blooming!
[Will he succeed?]
One, two, three, four, five...
succeed!
[Success]
[Ji Won's plan is a success!]
Kwang Soo!
I succeeded with you in there!
[Even human giraffe Kwang Soo
is fascinated...]
It's just staring at you.
I'm seriously!
You are totally staring at each other.
[The giraffe stepping closer to
be closer to Kwang Soo...]
[Gazes locked.]
Even though we're going
our separate ways right now...
I'm never going to forget you.
[This is really fascinating?]
That really is heartbreaking.
That really is sad.
Please...
[Eyes transfixed]
- This is a beautiful scene.
- Juliet...
- Its almost trying to communicate with you.
- Is this a love triangle?
Is this really a love triangle?
[Why is it suddenly being turned
into a love triangle?]
[Human giraffes and two real giraffe's
love triangle.]
[Kwang Soo's seduction.]
[That human giraffe Kwang Soo,
having communicated deeply with the giraffe.]
[But with the sudden appearance
of another giraffe...]
[A love triangle surrounding Kwang Soo
starts here and now...]
[That result...]
[means that the first love
didn't come true?]
[Don't go!]
No!
[Kwang Soo's seduction. The end.]
Anyways, thanks, Kwang Soo.
I succeeded the mission thanks to you.
I can't believe it's still
staring at Kwang Soo like that.
- It's still staring at me.
- I think even the giraffes are fascinated.
To see another creature that looks
so much like themselves.
[It seems as though his jumping skills
may have improved somewhat.]
[He's sitting!]
[Success!]
Thank you, guys!
He's already eaten several apples.
Apples, carrot, and bananas.
That's correct.
[Everyone succeeds their safari mission.]
[Second mission - Animal Kingdom.]
[Battle of knowledge.]
I'm in trouble.
Jessica says she's in trouble.
Okay, this quiz will be about the knowledge
that you already have yourselves.
- Ah...
- Ourselves?
The game will be played one on one and
the last one left remaining is the winner.
Rules will be explained to you in more detail
once you first each ask your questions.
So a question of our own knowledge?
Do I have to know the answer to it?
Isn't that just a given?
- Of course, you have to know.
- You have to know that to win.
What's the need to know the answer?
Can't you just ask the question?
[Just like mentioned,
this is a battle of their own smarts!]
I think I should ask something about
current events right now.
Jae Suk... that's not fair!
You're just trying to win by yourself.
Wow... it's hard to even come up with
a question when you don't know anything.
I can't ask anything about
my family, right?
[Of course not.]
Okay!
I'm done.
[The group completes coming up
with their own questions.]
- You nine animals yourselves...
- What do you mean, animals?
You're being too harsh with your words.
Then the nine of you...
First, one animal will step forward...
and ask their question.
[Privilege of first round's winner, Blank Ji-
Determine the order of questions asked.]
What is the name of this one special fruit
that lions, tigers and other carnivores likes?
- Ah! That one?
- The fruit that carnivores likes?
[Members standing in the back have to
write the answer down on a sketchbook.]
[And the person asking the question will
choose the person who won't know the answer.]
Kang Gary, come out here!
If the person you picked correctly answers,
then the questioner will be shot with water.
[But if the person you picked gets it wrong,
then that person is eliminated.]
Please don't do this!
[The last person left remaining
is the final winner of the game.]
[Big-nosed Brother and Gary
are the first two to be eliminated.]
This is bad.
My problem is really easy.
This is trouble.
My question is way too easy.
- Here we go.
- I'm really in trouble.
- What's the question?
- My question is way too easy.
- Give us an easy question then.
- I really am in trouble.
Okay...
- My brother, Ji Sung...
- What?
[Korea's eternal captain of soccer,
Park Ji sung is his brother?]
Don't you know who my
brother Ji Sung is?
- Are you referring to Park Ji Sung?
- Yes, he is.
I'm worried that you'll all know
the answer because it's about Ji Sung.
My brother, Ji Sung...
Which domestic neighborhood did he score
his first goal at the nationals competition in?
- What?
- His first goal.
- Neighborhood? You want the neighborhood?
- Yes.
Name the area.
- The arena where he scored his first goal.
- Wait...
When he was in the K leagues?
[He just said that it was
a nationals game...]
Kwang Soo doesn't know.
Kwang Soo doesn't know the answer.
- I don't think I know this.
- The stuff we say...
it could be a big hint to Jong Kook.
[Blank...]
The two ladies are spaced out right now.
You can't share your answers
with anyone.
[A difficult questions for the ladies.]
- Why is your answer so long, Ji Won?
- What?
No, I was just drawing something
next to it too.
The way I see it right now,
there are two candidates right now.
Who?
Lee Kwang Soo and Eun Ji Won.
[Two most likely candidates.]
Even though I'm sure the ladies don't know
this either, it's too unfair to them.
That's why you should attack them more!
What are you saying?
It's either Eun Ji Won or
Lee Kwang Soo.
[Thank goodness...]
You shouldn't be doing this, Jong Kook!
You should pick the giraffe.
[Everyone if trying to get
Jong Kook to choose the giraffe.]
- You should pick Ji Won!
- Lee Kwang Soo!
[Giraffe it is!]
- There you go!
- We're good!
- This is perfect.
- Kwang Soo is eliminated.
We did it.
[If the giraffe gets the answer right,
then the tiger will get soaked.]
[If the giraffe wrote down the wrong answer,
then he himself will get soaked!]
[Time to reveal the answer the chosen
giraffe had written down.]
[Suwon.]
- I think he's right.
- I think he got it right.
Please reveal your answer.
[Questioner, Jong Kook to
reveal the answer.]
What is it?
What happened?
- We're the only ones who know right now.
- What happened?
I felt a water drop!
I swore I felt something!
- What's going on here?
- Who won?
[If what giraffe wrote down is right,
it's the tiger. If not, it's the giraffe.]
- Kwang Soo!
- What's going on?
[Is Suwon the correct answer?]
Kwang Soo... Kwang Soo!
[Time to reveal the answer
the question Tiger wrote down.]
[Suwon]
[Miracle! Giraffe answers correctly!]
Park Ji Sung!
[Wow... Giraffe knew the answer!]
[Tiger is eliminated.]
- I can't believe Kwang Soo won.
- So this is how Kwang Soo survives?
I can't believe Lee Kwang Soo survived.
[Recharging the water cannon.]
- I'll go this time.
- Ji Won's question is hard.
- Ji Won't question is really hard.
- I didn't say what it is.
Ji Won is a little random,
but he said his IQ is like 200.
He knows the most random questions.
It's a question that more than 70% of
Seoul University students don't even know.
[A question 70% of the Seoul University
students don't know the answer to?]
I'm not a student of Seoul University!
You have to answer it within 30 seconds.
70% of Seoul University students
really don't know the answer to this?
- Yes, that is a fact.
- Then it's too hard. How would we know?
But I know it!
[The question being asked is up
to the person asking the question.]
- Good job! Ask whatever you want!
- You show them!
Here's the question!
Take a look at this picture...
and then solve the question.
Okay, here's the question.
Divide into three equal parts!
Divide it into three equal parts!
[Divide this into three parts?]
[Divide this shape into equal three parts.]
I'm not good at things like this.
- Okay!
- I know this. I've seen it on the internet.
I think I've seen this before.
[Is everyone pretending to know in
efforts to avoid Ji Won's suspicion?]
Everyone finished?
Is everyone done?
[30 seconds is over.]
I think at least one person
is going to get the correct answer.
You can't keep doing it, Kwang Soo.
- Lee Kwang Soo!
- I was doing something else.
Kwang Soo!
Kwang Soo, come up here!
[Giraffe is chosen for
the second time in a row.]
Lee Kwang Soo!
Why do I have to go again
when I was just up there?
This guy will do whatever
for the sake of our program.
This friend can do it.
[What kind of three parts did he
divide it into?]
Is it really me?
[If the Giraffe gets it right,
then it's the panda getting soaked!]
What?
You knew the question?
I really know.
I really know this answer.
This time, Eun Ji Won will
reveal the answer first.
Okay...
The correct answer is...
You just need to think very simply.
Here's the answer.
[A much simpler answer than expected.]
Seriously?
That was my answer too!
[What is the chosen Giraffe's answer?]
Lee Kwang Soo...
please reveal your answer.
[If the Giraffe gets it right, then
Panda will be the one to get soaked!]
[What?]
[What is that?]
[Wrong as expected!
Giraffe is eliminated!]
I got it right,
Ji Won, I got it right.
[The next one up is, Penguin Ha Ha.]
I'm going to go with a nonsense question.
Ask a question that's common sense
instead of a nonsensical question.
- Nonsense!
- Okay, give us your question.
The celebrity who's teeth always shows...
I've pretty much given you the answer.
- You have 30 seconds.
- You have to write down the name?
Who is it?
Gary just asked me who it is.
Okay, the final 10 seconds!
Ten, nine, eight, seven, six,
five, four, three, two, one!
Time's up!
[Celebrity who's teeth always shows.
What's the correct answer?]
It's someone we all know.
[Lee Bo Young.]
[Ha Ha now has to carefully choose someone
who's most likely to have the wrong answer.]
Be careful. Jae Suk
may just be pretending to know.
- You close?
- What?
- Are you two close?
- No.
You're serious, right?
You're not close?
- You're not close?
- We're close!
[Quickly changing his story.]
- When's the last time you saw the person?
- What did you say?
Why?
Just answer the question.
- It's been about... two weeks?
- Two weeks?
In that case... is that right?
You saw that person two weeks ago?
So it's been two weeks?
Then in that case...
What about you, Ji Won?
Are you two close?
Since I'm not sure about that.
- I... believe that we're close.
- You think you two are close?
- Yes, as a little brother.
- You're the little brother?
- Little?
Are you sure?
[Who did these two write down
as their answer?]
- What do you mean, little brother?
- Then what is it?
What did you say?
- What do you call the person?
- We have no titles between us.
- Then what is it?
- We're just friends.
- Really?
- We just go by our names.
- Yeah!
Okay then.
- What about you, Jessica?
- I like the person.
You like the person?
Do you call the person sister, or brother?
- Brother.
- Brother?
Brother?
- Brother.
- Are you sure it's brother?
- It's brother?
- It's brother.
[Jessica definitely seems
to have the wrong answer.]
Song Ji Hyo, you're next.
- You know this person?
- Yeah.
[Blank...]
We can tell that she's totally
spaced out.
- When did you see the person last?
-  I see the person on regular basis.
Often?
- What do you call the person?
- Senior.
Senior?
Is it a brother or sister?
- Not brother or sister, but senior.
- Oh, just senior?
[Does she know the answer?
Blank Ji is avoiding it well...]
I'm not sure about Ji Hyo.
- Jae Suk.
- What?
Since he always disregards me...
it upsets me!
Yoo Jae Suk!
[Yoo Jae Suk, get up here!]
Okay!
Let's see this!
Even if the answer isn't the same,
can't it be something in the category?
- Are you that confident?
- I think I'm right.
I'm sure.
I wonder if I should let him off the hook?
Since I can kill him whenever I want?
Go back, go back!
I'll let you live until next time!
- Seriously...
- At least say thanks.
Thank you!
I'll let you live!
- Seriously...
- This is a stab at my pride!
Jessica!
[Jessica is called out in his place!]
[Who is the person that she kept
referring to as 'brother'?]
Jessica, reveal your answer.
[Yoo Jae Suk]
[Oh no...]
Jessica!
You looked like you were shooting
a disaster movie.
I thought you were shooting a scene
from a disaster movie.
[Jessica is eliminated
along with her scream.]
How does your answer make
any sense?
I thought you said you saw
the person often?
Lee Bo Young!
It's your turn this time!
Get back to your spot!
It's my turn to ask the question.
You're finished!
- I let you off the hook once.
- Go back to your spot.
- Fine!
- Who asked you to let me live?
- I will make you shut that mouth of yours!
- Fine! Do it!
My mouth isn't easy to keep shut!
Let's go with the character idiom.
[A subject that all the animals are
weak at... character idiom.]
Really?
then write down your answer.
[Eliminated players can participate
out of boredom.]
- Can we go back if we get it right?
- Let us back in the game.
Here I go.
The three people standing back there...
any one of them is a good candidate
to get eliminated.
Excuse me...
What are you talking about?
- What did you say?
- My name is a character idiom.
How is it that those people
are the ones left remaining?
I can't believe they're
the ones left remaining!
[Remaining survivors that they
can hardly believe.]
- I can't believe this.
- This is what life is like!
This is what you call life!
Want to put our heads together?
[The three remaining people are
deciding to work together.]
- Put out heads together?
- Seriously?
- No problem! Put your heads together!
- Really?
- Sit down.
- Don't get upset!
[Doubt you'll get it right anyways...]
I'm not going to give you any breaks!
- Fine! Three against one!
- Let's do this!
We can do this!
Combine everything you've learned in
your life thus far and try to answer it!
[Seriously knocking down their pride!]
- He's really knocking down my pride!
- Try and see if you can get it!
- You know what to do, right?
- Give it your best shot!
Beat... Yoo Jae Suk!
[You've got the wrong game...]
- Beat... Yoo Jae Suk!
- Beat him!
- We can do this.
- Here we go!
This is a character idiom.
Then if one of us gets it wrong,
then all of us gets it wrong?
If we lose this, we have to live as fools
for the rest of our lives.
- This is no laughing matter.
- Okay.
It's a good thing we're not still alive.
[Actually more comfortable
where they're at.]
Okay...
With the meaning that one is working
earnestly to do their best...
what is the idiom that describes using
an ax to make a needle out of something?
What is the idiom that describes using
- Ax?
- Use of an ax...
Okay!
- Ax to make a needle out of something?
- We got this!
- We're good, we're good.
- How do you use an ax to make a needle?
What it means is...
The character idiom here is...
let's try to figure this out now.
- This is...
- Give us the question one more time.
I can tell you a hundred times over!
With the meaning that one is working
earnestly to do their best...
what is the idiom that describes using
an ax to make a needle out of something?
- What is the answer?
- If...
If you have the ax in hand but can't
make a needle, then it doesn't count!
Am I right?
- If you have the ax...
- If someone gave you the ax...
- But if you can't make the needle...
- Then this doesn't count!
It doesn't count!
What did you say?
There's a point to what they're saying.
You think they have a point?
- They really do have a point.
- We have a very valid point.
[So... you don't know the answer?]
Let's see how well you do!
- If you have the ax...
- That's right!
but if you can't make a needle,
then none of this counts!
Then this question doesn't count!
Since this may take a while,
I'll ask the disqualified ones one at a time.
[Interviewing the disqualified ones for the
answer since the others may take a while.]
- Jae Suk...
- Do you not know what character idiom is?
Why wouldn't I know that?
- I know it!
- I don't think you know what it means.
[First character idiom game he's ever
heard of at age 29...]
Did he not know what he
was saying?
- Making a needle?
- He has no clue.
Making a needle.
Look at them.
Look at those guys over there.
They're not even looking
at me right now.
[Avoiding meeting his gaze as
the given time is coming to a close.]
All I need to do is just reel one out!
[Even a casual throw is
a guarantee to bring one in!]
Hang on a second, let me see this.
[Using the boom mike as his
makeshift fishing rod.]
[Plenty of fish in the water!]
This is the fishing rod.
I don't even need any bait for this!
This is driving me crazy.
Okay... here we go!
Ha Ha, get out here!
[As predicted, he chooses Ha Ha!]
[Off the hook for now...]
Should I let you off the hook?
Thank you!
Okay.
You're really letting him off the hook?
Ha Ha, get out here.
Jae Suk!
Why are you being so evil?
Why do you keep picking on me?
[Grasshopper's image as seen
in the eyes of the Penguin.]
I let you off the hook last time.
I was wrong.
I don't care about getting soaked,
but my heart feels uneasy.
Thank you!
Why are you showing him
your weak side?
- Ha Ha, out.
- Why are you doing this?
Why are you doing this?
- Just do it like a man!
- You might even get it right.
- Just give it a try.
- You don't know until you try.
What you wrote down isn't so bad.
- Okay.
- Ji Won, get out here!
Ji Won, get out here!
[Ji Won is chosen.]
- What he wrote down is okay?
- He doesn't have a bad answer.
- I think he may even have it right.
- Ji Won, get out here.
You've... been left alive for too long.
- I'm not used to this either.
- Come here.
I can't believe that I'm still alive either.
[What did Ji Won write down
for his answer?]
[Is this right?]
Yes, I know.
Is it that bad?
Gary, is it that bad?
- Gary, what's wrong?
- Gary, is it that bad?
I think he really is stupid.
Are you all laughing because
you know the correct answer?
Why are you all laughing? Don't laugh.
You don't even know what character idiom is.
[The correct answer is...
Ma Bu Jak Chim.]
[If only Ji Won wrote down
the same answer...]
Please show us your answer.
Here.
[No Hak Ui Ryong.]
- I've seen that movie.
- I've seen it too.
I've seen that movie.
[Any four letters that he
could think of...]
What did you write down, Ji Won?
The movie you meant to write is,
'Do Hak Ui Ryong'.
- What did you write?
- Jung Shi Il Do.
What did you write?
[Yoo Jae Suk rocks.]
I let you off the hook once, okay?
Seriously...
Song Ji Hyo will ask another question.
Here's the question.
At an Italian restaurant...
the sauce that you dip the bread in
as an appetizer course...
You know this one, don't you?
That's seriously way too easy!
Ask a different question.
That one is way too easy.
He doesn't know.
Ha Ha doesn't know the answer!
- Ji Hyo!
- Ha Ha doesn't know the answer.
What is it that intensifies the flavor
if eaten in conjunction with the olive oil?
I'm writing it down now!
Hey, I already wrote down my answer.
I'm done.
[Writing down the answer
without any hesitation.]
This is really...
- Okay!
- I wrote down my answer.
I wrote it down. Why wouldn't I know this?
I know everything about food!
[Penguin Ha Ha,
appearing to be extremely confident.]
I'm a one-time carnivore!
How many letters is the answer?
- I know, but I can't say, can I?
- Just tell me how many letters.
Five letters.
What about you, Ha Ha?
Isn't it three to four letters?
[Who will Ji Hyo choose?]
Yoo Jae Suk.
[Evil Grasshopper is chosen.]
After I let you off the hook
with the last one...
You don't even have a sense
of loyalty!
- You dare call me out, Song Ji Hyo?
- Fine, Yoo Jae Suk, go back in!
- Ha Ha, get out here!
- Thank you!
When I let you off the hook
with Lee Bo Young!
[Three intertwined remaining survivors.]
I don't think he's the one, Ji Hyo.
[What did the Grasshopper write down
as his answer?]
[Spicy olive oil and pepper paste.]
[What?]
- What is that?
- What kind of a sauce is that?
I have no idea.
What in the world is olive oil
spicy pepper paste?
- What kind of sauce is it?
- Is it Italian or Korean cuisine?
[Cat's turn to reveal her answer first.]
[Balsamic vinaigrette]
Ha Ha, your answer.
I don't know if I got this right.
[If Ha Ha gets it right,
then Ji Hyo is eliminated!]
[Balsamic]
[Penguin wins!]
- What the heck?
- I got it right?
[Cat Blank Ji is eliminated!]
This is the answer?
You got it right?
I was laughing because I heard
someone say, 'balsamic'.
I was thinking what a weird name
balsamic was!
[This means that the Grasshopper and
the Penguin are moving up the finals!]
Unbelievable...
Why is it unbelievable?
Then come out here!
Let see how smart you are!
Come out here!
This is the last round.
- I can't believe it's Jae Suk and I.
- It's down to you and I!
[Grasshopper vs. Penguin]
You can do this!
I will confidently answer the question!
With confidence.
[Starting out with a battle of wills.]
- You're good at groveling.
- What did you say?
- I said, you're good at groveling.
You've come all this way with that
one single balsamic answer!
With that one answer, balsamic!
Balsamic!
- What? Ma bu, whatever?
- What did you say?
- You think not knowing that matters?
- Balsamic?
- Just go make needles with your ax!
You've just been lucky to get this far
with your lone answer of balsamic!
Why don't you just eat your
olive oil bean paste?
[To have lost to those two...]
Okay... the next question is...
nonsense!
Why is it nonsense again?
- It's my choice!
- Okay!
- Okay, call!
- This is the deciding question!
- This could be the deciding factor.
- Jae Suk is at a disadvantage.
Nonsense.
The final question.
Dear viewers...
This is like the 'Golden Bell challenge'.
You know what this means, right?
Anyone can rise up to the challenge!
Everyone that are watching this right now...
I will make Yoo Jae Suk fall!
With this nonsense question...
What do you call a sparrow in English?
[Sparrow in English?]
- I think I know this.
- Seoul University, answer this question!
I want everyone to try answer this!
What do you call a sparrow in English!
It's hard, isn't it?
Time is ticking!
Time is ticking away!
Time is ticking...
I think I know!
- Nine, eight, seven, six...
- Doesn't that sound right?
- I think you're right.
Show me.
[It looks like he may have it right!]
Seoul University!
Show yourselves!
[Getting excited all the same!]
- This is what I'm truly like!
- He got it right.
- I should've been a survivor.
- Back in the day when I was in school...
The quiz show came to our school,
and I didn't make the cut.
[The hurt I felt due to my lack of smarts,
I will make up for it today!]
This is the final question.
[A huge advantage
will be given to the winner!]
I should've been given this opportunity!
At the count of three, both of you
reveal your answers simultaneously.
It would be awesome if he gets it right.
[Did he guess the right answer?]
[What did Jae Suk write down
as his answer?]
[Correct answer -
'Jack'- due to the sound it makes!]
[What is Grasshopper's answer?]
[If he's right, it's Ha Ha.
If he's wrong, it's Jae Suk!]
[Jae Suk's answer: Jack.
He guessed it right!]
[Wow... Grasshopper gets it right!]
- Jack!
- I can't believe he got it right!
[The win was right in front of his eyes!]
That was way too easy!
- No!
- Jack!
Jack!
Second mission...
Animal Kingdom Quiz...
the winner is Yoo Jae Suk!
[Second mission, battle of knowledge:
Yoo Jae Suk's win!]
[Running Animal Kingdom-
Arriving at their final location.]
[An empty amusement park which
is like a scene out of a movie.]
This is something you see
out of a movie.
Coming to a totally empty amusement park.
What is that?
What's that?
Are they masks?
[Masks]
- What is this?
- Do you see your own masks?
- Our own masks...
- But...
How many years am I wearing this for?
- You look...
- How am I supposed to wear this?
[Ah... you sad beast with
the long neck...]
[I'm a giraffe!]
Try running.
Like this...
giraffes run slow like this.
[100% match to the real giraffes.]
[A loveable monkey, Kang Gary!]
I don't think Gary even
needs his mask.
[And the nation's beloved grasshopper.]
What does a panda do?
What pose are pandas usually in?
You really look like a panda with
your dark circles.
[Animal kingdom-
All nine animals makes their entrance!]
I'm getting a strange feeling.
[The final race -
Time to choose the king of all animals.]
Your final mission is...
not the name tag elimination...
but it's a mask elimination.
[The final race, Mask elimination.]
Kwang Soo is finished.
[Baffled]
But this is...
What is this?
As soon as someone grabs this,
it'll immediately...
The final race... starts now.
[Mask elimination as the
final race - Start!]
Is there a way I can sew this on?
I want to sew the mask onto my face.
Would it be too painful?
Mask elimination?
[A very feasible race for even
the weakest of animals.]
[And...]
[A special advantage given to the grasshopper
for having won the previous mission.]
Give me something
I can finish this game with.
Just give me a game ender.
[What is the game changer that
is given to him?]
[Oh!]
[A fierce and unpredictable battle
between the beasts starts now!]
I'm way too visible.
[A visible giraffe that can be seen
from a 100m away.]
[Blank Ji the cat, with an ax in her hand.]
- She's not easy to catch.
- What is...
- You stay away.
- I just grabbed your ears.
- Don't do that.
- You say you're going to catch me?
- Are you carrying a weapon?
- You can't carry an ax around.
I was going to give it to Jae Suk
for him to make needles with.
We have to work together.
We're all weak animals.
Fighting amongst ourselves is no use.
Penguin, panda, monkey and cat...
we're all prey.
- We have to get the predators first.
- Let's go.
Then let's go.
[Grasshopper watching
the whole scene from his hidden spot.]
- The Rabbit...
- What are you doing?
- What? I didn't do anything!
- Did you just attack?
- What? What did you do?
[Fighting within five seconds of
agreeing to work together.]
- Yoo Jae Suk is behind us!
- What?
Is he waiting to fire?
There he is!
There's the Grasshopper!
- There he is!
- Get that Grasshopper!
- Catch the Grasshopper!
[Grasshopper having become the prey
within mere moments!]
- Get that Grasshopper!
- Catch the Grasshopper!
I've got your ax right here!
Come make your needles!
I've got your ax!
[The Panda corrals him...
and the Cat blocks him...]
[And the Monkey attacks him!]
Why is that Grasshopper so fast?
[Grasshopper barely makes his escape.]
Why are they all attacking me?
They're attacking because they think
that I have something, don't they?
[Animals eyeing the Grasshopper first
for having been given an advantage.]
The way this is going...
I'm going to need like five lives.
We almost had the Grasshopper!
What are you guys doing?
Let's play together.
That's a very familiar voice.
[This voice is...]
Where is that voice coming from?
Where is he?
[The voice throwing the peaceful
animal kingdom into a sea of fear...]
Let's play together!
[Tiger makes his appearance on a scooter!]
- Guys...
- You can't be riding around in a scooter!
Here's a monkey!
I've got a monkey right here!
Panda is over there!
Pandas are delicious!
[Running Man animals recommending
one another as menu items.]
Don't you think you should be hunting
down the Grasshopper first?
Grasshopper has something that
none of us has.
Grasshopper has something.
We have to eliminate him first.
They're all probably fighting amongst
themselves, right?
That looks so good!
That looks so good.
Can I just eat one?
[The Rabbit is busy window shopping.]
[And...]
[Another herbivore's busy having his meal.]
You must've been hungry.
It's full of your favorite foods.
- I haven't eaten anything today.
- Right?
Is there any bread around?
I need something to eat too.
[Eat up...]
Is Grasshopper missing?
No, the Grasshopper is around
here somewhere.
What?
You startled me!
Grasshopper!
Ah!
He startled me!
[Runs away immediately!]
There goes the Grasshopper.
Wait!
[Tiger on the Grasshopper's tail!]
Was Song Ji Hyo in 'Home Alone'
or what?
[Panda Ji Won is blocking this door!]
- Jae Suk! I have to talk to you!
- What is it?
Stop running away.
I have to talk to you about something.
[Besieged!]
- I said, I have to talk to you.
- What is it?
- I have to talk to you, Jae Suk.
[Monkey's surprise attack!]
[Unbelievable! Succeeds in
eliminating Grasshopper's mask!]
[Grasshopper - Out!
Grasshopper - Out!]
I knew it...
[Is the Grasshopper ousted
just like this?]
They're all attacking me because
I was given something.
Since I don't know what's going to
happen, I'm going to go hide.
I'm going to get them all at the end.
They all think that I'm dead right now.
[Huh? They think that you're dead?]
[The special advantage he was given
earlier before the race started.]
What is 'Chance to exchange life'?
Aren't there stickers that you
gave out to all of us earlier?
All the members have traded in their
life for their masks.
That means...
Yes, you're the only one
who has two lives.
Then I have two lives to live on?
[This is the special advantage!
Grasshopper is given an additional life!]
[And thus...]
[Without the members finding out,
he re-dons his mask!]
[Will the resurrected Grasshopper...]
[be able to become the king
of all animals?]
[On the other hand, at the penguin theater...]
The owner of this animal kingdom is
none other than all of you!
- That's correct!
- Everyone pay attention!
[The Penguin is holding a meeting with all
the animals to overthrow the Tiger.]
- We can't live like this!
- We can't be on the run forever!
Everyone.. today is the day!
- The day has come!
- You're right!
- Will you fight with me?
- Yes!
As soon as we step out of here,
let's go capture the Tiger!
No more betraying amongst ourselves!
- No more betrayals!
- Peace amongst the animal kingdom!
Let's go!
What is that?
It's supposed to open the door.
Why is it so quiet?
Where are they and
what are they planning?
Where are they all hiding?
[Walking out hand in hand from
their distrust in each other.]
The Grasshopper died just like that?
I'm sure there's something,
don't you think?
[Tiger drops a surprise attack
on the Monkey!]
[Abandoning the Monkey to
make their escape!]
Let's not run away!
Monkey, Out.
[Monkey, Out!]
Run away!
Tiger is here!
I'll see you later.
[Fog settling in over
the chaotic animal kingdom...]
- Hey...
- Monkey sacrificed himself.
There's the Tiger.
- Tiger!
- Giraffe!
- What is he doing?
- The Tiger...
The Giraffe is aligning himself
with the Tiger.
- Tiger!
- Giraffe! Cross!
What is he doing?
[Traitor Giraffe aligning himself with
the Tiger as soon as he makes his getaway.]
- He really is too much.
- You really are...
You pathetic herbivores!
- You, Tiger!
- Come here, Rabbit.
Do you really trust the Giraffe?
[Resurrected Grasshopper is carefully
staying in hiding to not get caught.]
- We sent the Giraffe in.
- He's our spy.
By any chance... would you
be interested in accepting me?
- What is this?
- Would you accept me too?
[Oh my goodness...]
You've still got it, Tiger!
- Jong Kook...
- What?
I'd be so grateful if you left those two
and came over to us.
We will serve you with all that we have.
- Leave those two to us.
- Let me think about this a moment.
[What is going on out there?]
- What are you thinking?
- Those two are untrustworthy!
Everyone... all the animals...
now is our time.
We can get the Tiger together right now!
- Get your head on straight!
- I implore to my fellow animals!
[Just who will stick with whom?]
[Looking for loyalty amongst the
Traitors' Club members.]
[Giraffe blocking his ears out
of the agony.]
You're the only one we need.
You just need to come to us.
- Just you...
- I'm going over to the other side!
[Easy Brothers' coalition is broken!]
[Easy Brothers having become the prey
within moments.]
Get rid of them!
I have to hope that they fight
amongst themselves a lot.
[Easy Brothers making their escape
to inside the locker room.]
I will eliminate the traitors.
[Jong Kook, let's get rid of him.]
Yes!
[Protagonist Penguin is eliminated!]
You need to be eliminated!
Good job!
You did good.
[Penguin, Out!]
[Traitor Club's heart-wrenching friendship?]
The day is going to come for the
traitors one of these days.
Let's hide back here.
Let's stay here and hide.
[It seems as though there's some
sort of a plan in the works...]
[Go, go!]
[Ah... acting like Impala is ousted,
calling their bluff!]
- I eliminated him.
- Then you need to bring me his mask.
I need to bring his mask?
Wait, wait!
[As guessed!
Not even going in to help!]
- Where are you going?
- Not me!
- You can eliminate me!
[Impala, Out!]
- Where are you going?
- I just...
I will just enjoy my grass,
and live in peace.
Please don't pay any attention to me.
[Giraffe having decided
to go back to his forest.]
I just want to go back to
my peaceful life.
[Panda... springs an attack on the Tiger!]
I've been watching you!
I saw you making your moves
behind me!
My gloves!
My gloves slipped!
I saw you creeping up behind me!
- Do we have to keep...
- You scoundrel!
We should've been mating!
[What?]
[I'm sure you meant 'consensus',
not 'mating'...]
[Panda, Out!
Panda, Out!]
[Okay... everything is going well!]
Wait... but shouldn't we be thinking
about Jae Suk right about now?
I'm telling you,
there's something with Jae Suk.
I'm sure there's something.
There's something with Jae Suk.
I'm sure there's something we don't
know about Jae Suk right now.
Where are they?
Are they all together?
[Grasshopper checking out the situation
with the camera filming the scene.]
I can smell the Grasshopper somewhere!
Let's do something about that Giraffe.
- Don't get sucked in by those words.
- Should we eliminate the Giraffe?
[An uncertain element that they can't
trust if they leave him alive...]
[Giraffe hunting into the fog!]
Get the Giraffe!
Who's that?
Giraffe?
[Slowly closing in on him with
the aid of the fog!]
I know there's something
with the Grasshopper.
There's no way he'd be
that easily ousted.
[Giraffe having escaped the clutches
of the other animals.]
Jae Suk...
[Grasshopper is discovered!]
I'll lure them over here.
- What?
- I'll lure them over here.
- Let's end this quickly.
- Okay.
Giraffe!
Bring Jong Kook over here.
Giraffe?
You can see me?
I'm sorry!
I just want to live in peace.
I just want to live eating my shrubs.
[Luring them towards the tree.]
I'm positive there's something
with Jae Suk.
[The other animals suspecting
that something is going on.]
- Giraffe is working with the Grasshopper.
- You sense it too?
- There's something going on, right?
- I sense something.
He's hiding something.
[What are you doing, Giraffe?]
[Wait... then the Grasshopper is
going to take care of the Tiger...]
[Giraffe sets his target on the Cat!]
Why do you keep lurking around me?
[Giraffe attacks the Cat!]
Cat, out!
Cat, Out!
[Jessica Rabbit trying to get
revenge for the Cat.]
[Tiger joins in on the action!]
[Grasshopper sees his chance
from his hiding spot!]
[This is his chance!]
[Fails at his attempt
to eliminate the Tiger!]
Let go!
[Gives up on his attack.
Time to make his escape!]
[Tiger and the Rabbit having
survived the battle this time around.]
Jae Suk!
- Kwang Soo!
- Jae Suk!
What happened?
- What happened?
- The Tiger...
[What will become of these two?]
Let's escape, Kwang Soo.
Let's escape into the fog.
[Tiger and the Rabbit on full alert after
having seen the Grasshopper's resurrection.]
[Resurrected Grasshopper hiding
inside a shop.]
[Oh?]
[There's the Grasshopper!]
[Like a flash of lightening!]
[Both of his lives...
Lost without even a real fight!]
- I knew it.
- Giraffe...
Giraffe, I'm sorry.
- How can you get eliminated so easily?
- Grasshopper...
[And thus, the Grasshopper was not able to
become the king of the prairie.]
[The only animals left remaining are,
Tiger, Rabbit and the Giraffe.]
- You think you can take me on?
- You and I can easily take him.
[Giraffe attacks the Rabbit
without any hesitation.]
[Rabbit, Out!]
I'm sorry, Jessica.
[Giraffe is on a roll!
He now attacks the Tiger!]
[The ultimate battle!]
[Tiger vs. Giraffe-
Who will become the king of all animals?]
Tiger, don't give up!
Giraffes.... give me the strength!
[Strong energy that was passed between
them as they spent the day together...]
[Giraffes... please give me your strength!]
[Giraffe power at full blast!]
[King of all animals...
Will it be the Giraffe or the Tiger?]
[The Giraffe... to the Tiger!]
[The ultimate winner...
Giraffe is the king of all beasts!]
The king of all animals... is the Giraffe!
- Show it to us!
- One, two, three!
It's a gold crown.
[A golden crown!]
What are you doing?
What's wrong with you?
- Just take that.
- Why did you do that?
[Grasshopper having broken off
a part of the Giraffe's crown.]
This is my first time getting
anything like this! Why did you do that?
- This is real gold!
- I didn't think it'd fall off.
I should be wearing this on my head!
I wanted to go home like this!
You have to put it on the right way.
Put it on like this.
- Why did you do that?
- Kwang Soo...
Good job, Ji Won.
[King or not, it seems as though
everyone's ready to go home.]
You have to treat me like the king that I am!
- Let's go home.
- I'm a Grasshopper.
Grasshoppers don't live in the jungle.
- You and I live in different places.
- Where are you all going?
I'm the king!
- I'm turning the camera off.
- Why are you turning the camera off?
Subtitles by DramaFever
Wait!
Here's the slate!
One, two, three!
[The nation's daughter, Lee Bo Young.]
[And a man every woman wants for
their husband, Lee Sang Yoon.]
Are you ashamed of me?
[This isn't the 'daughter'
that we thought she was!]
[Coach Lee, even more fierce
than Coach Kkuk!]
[The handsome and the beautiful
gives Running Man a run for their money!]
Then we will now choose
the fateful couple.
That's awesome.
[The Best Couple Race]