[November of last year, monster pitcher,
Ryu Hyun Jin made his appearance on RM.]
[He was drafted into the major leagues
the day he made his appearance.]
[Drafted into the major leagues.]
[Joined the L.A. Dodgers with a
28 billion won contract.]
[Thus, he went onto
the major league stage.]
[2013 marked his first year
in the major leagues.]
[Korean Monster, Ryu Hyun Jin takes
the baseball world by storm.]
[And that man...
is returning to rule Running Man.]
[Complete the mission through
the choice given by Ryu Hyun Jin.]
[And... other formidable opponents?]
[The One Who Rules Running Man]
Subtitles by DramaFever
[The city of history, Boo-yeo.]
[The elegant 'L-outlet' that sits
amongst all that history.]
[And this is where...]
[Blank Ji is seen making her appearance
in a baseball uniform?]
Hey! Blank Ji Hyo!
You can't let others see
what you're signing.
[But that's how you're supposed to do it...]
She's supposed to sign like that.
[Like this?]
[Sign of interest just for the pitcher?]
- You're just outright about it now.
- What are you doing?
I'm just cheering her on!
[A strong wind up.]
[The right form...]
[Too much strength in the shoulders.]
[Anyways, she just started
a new popular pitching trend for others.]
- Why are you making us do this anyway?
- Is our guest a baseball player?
- Ryu Hyun Jin?
- Is it Ryu Hyun Jin?
[Could he have returned after a year?]
- If you shout out to the guest...
- What if Hyun Jin comes out?
- You think?
- Who do you think it is?
- Ryu Hyun Jin.
- Please come on out!
- Who is it?
- Hollywood!
- Hey! It's Hyun Jin!
[That's... L.A.?]
That's L.A.!
[One of the most famous cities
in America, Los Angeles.]
[Ryu Hyun Jin?]
[A familiar back...]
- He just pressed the bell with his left hand.
- It could just be another heavy person.
[Huh?]
- Did you come here from Korea?
- It's Ryu Hyun Jin!
[The real Ryu Hyun Jin.]
[L.A. Dodgers- Ryu Hyun Jin.]
[Korean Monster, Ryun Hyun Jin
made his debut in the major leagues.]
[14th place in his first debut year.]
[A major feat in baseball history
for a Korean athlete.]
[The monster pitcher making waves
right from the start in his first year.]
[Korean Monster]
[Ryu Hyun Jin with Running Man.]
[The familiar back that you saw was
VJ, Gwon Yeol.]
- That is Hyun Jin!
- It really is him!
Hyun Jin!
[Hyun Jin's spacious
L.A. home living room.]
You want to see my room?
You can't see my room.
- My golf clubs are in the way.
- There are so many.
[The house is full of athletic gear.]
This is my room.
[This is Ryu Hyun Jin's bedroom.]
My room is pretty empty.
- That's his room?
- I would've gone if you had told me.
- Why would you go?
- You're blocking the screen!
All I do is sleep in here.
This is my bathroom.
- Look at Hyun Jin.
- You've made it, Hyun Jin.
I'm sorry about the last time.
I should've been nicer to you.
I wish I could turn back time
so that I could treat you better.
The one who travels through time!
There are a lot of famous people
that live in this apartment building.
There are a couple of players on my team
that also live in this building.
[A few of his teammates are his neighbors.]
There are some basketball players here too.
Kobe Bryant lives here.
[L.A. Lakers basketball player,
Kobe Bryant is also his neighbor.]
- Kobe Bryant.
- Wow!
- He also lives in this building.
- I should be there right now!
[Superpower potion!]
The one who rules Running Man!
Then does this mean that I'm now
the ruler of Running Man?
And I can do...
whatever I want to do?
For this whole episode...
you have been given the power to determine
the fate of all the Running Man members.
Look at how happy he is with that.
I will now give you a mission that will help
determine all your fates.
- What's that?
- I'll be making several choices from now on.
[Different choices that Ryu Hyun Jin will be
making in several different situations.]
Running Man members in Korea must guess
which decision I would have made
and must go on with the mission based on
the correct guesses that you've made.
[Their course of action will change depending
on the decisions that Hyun Jin makes.]
Please do your best to complete
the mission that you are given.
Fighting.
Let's go!
Run!
Quickly! Kim Jong Kook!
I'm coming to get you!
- You two seem to be very close.
- No, it's not that.
It's just because he eliminated
my name tag the last time that he was on.
- I don't think he's afraid of me.
- He needs to do it again.
I don't think he's afraid.
Ryu Hyun Jin, the ruler of Running Man,
will be asking you some questions.
All the missions you'll be doing will be based
on the choices Ryu Hyun Jin will be giving you.
- So you'll have to choose one of the two.
- So it's a 50/50 chance?
Thus, if you answer the question correctly,
you'll be given an easy mission to do.
- I understand.
- Get it wrong, and you get a tough mission.
You have to discuss it with your teammates
to choose the right answer.
Okay, here comes your first question.
- A question from Ryu Hyun Jin himself.
- I'm really curious now.
[Huh? Hoola hoop?]
- He's not good at it either.
- He can't do it either. Fatso's not good.
Your skills are on par with
Kim Jong Kook's.
- Excuse me?
- Your skills are on par with Kim Jong Kook's.
No way.
I have to be better than
Jong Kook at this.
[Tiger Jong Kook doesn't seem to
put any fear into Hyun Jin?]
- He really is bad at that.
- I think I'm better than him.
Why don't you try it with this one?
- That's really hard.
- Doesn't that one hurt?
I'm going to be doing the hoola hoop
with this one now.
Depending on how many times or
how long I'll be able to spin this for
the fate of your mission will
hang on the balance of your guesses.
[How many spins will Ryu Hyun Jin be able to
get from the acupuncture hoola hoop?]
Can I wrap a towel around my waist first?
- Can I use a towel underneath?
- Doing that really hurts.
- Let me think about this.
- He can't really handle pain very well.
- Three, four, five... he's really good.
- How are you doing that?
- Why don't you keep going?
- It's because you're fat.
[Will Ryun Hyun Jin... be able
to last for more than 30 seconds?]
[30 minutes or more-
Can Do it vs. Can't do it.]
No, I don't think he can do it.
[A. Can do it.]
[B. Can't do it.]
He can do it.
I say that he can do it.
- Why do you think that?
- Hyun Jin is pretty limber.
- How would you know that?
- And he could've been faking us earlier.
I don't think he can do it.
That hoola hoop really hurts.
- I think he can do it.
- What do you think, Ji Hyo?
I...
What am I?
- Forget it. Pass.
- You're Blank Ji Hyo.
- You're just Blank Ji Hyo.
- You're so frustrating!
- Can do it or not?
- I don't think he can do it.
- Just leave her alone.
- Pass.
- I don't think he can do it.
- Can't do it.
- Ryun Hyun Jin can do anything.
- He can do it!
I think he can do it too.
It's three to three.
This hangs on your decision, Ji Hyo.
- Hey.
- She doesn't even know what's going on.
- She doesn't even know who she is right now.
- I don't think he can do it either.
- He can't do it.
- Okay, we'll go with 'Can't do it'.
On the count of three.
One, two, three.
B. He can't do it!
[B. He can't last for 30 seconds.]
Okay, someone take this.
[Given the 'B' mission.]
[Ryu Hyun Jin can't last 30 seconds
doing the hoola hoop.]
[If you chose that he'd fail,
then go to Geum River ferry.]
Geum River Ferry?
Just as a warning,
we won't be giving you any breaks.
You'll have to complete the mission
no matter how long it takes you.
- You have to keep going until you succeed.
- It must be a tough mission.
We could be doing this until tomorrow.
Let's all do this!
- Let's finish this and go home!
- Geum River ferry.
[B- Geum River ferry.]
March forward!
Geum river ferry.
[They can verify their answer only when
they arrive at their destination.]
[It would be more advantageous for
Running Man if they chose the correct answer.]
- I noticed that he lost a lot of weight.
- Yeah, he did.
- He's pretty stubborn too.
- You're right.
[He may be able to do it with
the determination of an athlete.]
But it's so nice for everyone to be going
together which we haven't done in a while.
- I like the group missions.
- I agree.
- There's a bee. Kang Gary, there's a bee.
- Be careful.
[A bee?]
Don't do it!
No, don't do it!
- Don't do it, Kwang Soo.
- Don't kill it.
- You can't kill it.
- Just leave it alone.
- You'll be punished if you do.
- Watch out for the camera.
[Worried about the camera.]
[Worry about the camera...
and worry about the bee...]
[A loud and chaotic Running Man car.]
This feels like a really
awkward family outing.
[Feels like a first awkward outing
for the Running Man family?]
It really feels like that.
[Beautiful fall scenery.]
- Wow! What's that?
- Look at that!
- Are we going to have to get on that?
- What's that forklift for?
- I'm getting a bad feeling about this.
- I see a forklift.
[Mini baseball field...]
[And a forklift?]
It's baseball.
But what is that forklift
doing here?
[Why is a chair attached to a forklift?]
- Did we get the right answer or not?
- I'm getting really nervous.
Did we get the right answer or not?
[Correct answer, then an easy mission.
Wrong answer, then a tough mission.]
[Running Man chose answer 'B'.
They can't change their decision.]
[The correct answer is?]
[Did Ryu Hyun Jin pull it off?
A- Can do it. B- Can't do it.]
- There he goes.
- He's doing good.
- Look he's doing a good job.
- Look at him go.
This really hurts.
[The power of the acupuncture hoola hoop
that makes the man scream out in pain.]
[Running Man members are slowly starting to
get more and more nervous about their fate.]
I think it's starting to fall off.
[Danger!]
[He endures the pain to keep spinning.]
[Almost to the 30 second mark!]
[Ryu Hyun Jin breaks through
the 30 second mark!]
[Running Man gets it wrong.]
He's nearing the minute mark.
[A whole minute and 14 seconds!]
I think this could help me lose
some weight.
This is nice.
As you can see,
I passed the 30 second mark.
[The answer is, A- He can do it.]
[Running Man gets the answer wrong.]
Hyun Jin's body is limber,
so he's good at things like that.
- What did you say earlier?
- I told you that he could do it.
- I want you to apologize, Jong Kook.
- You just wait until you get it wrong.
Okay, had you guys gotten
the correct answer...
you would've gotten a very
simple mission.
You would've been able to pass it
very easily. The reason being...
You would've had to receive a massage
for ten minutes without making any noise.
- That would've been so nice.
- You think it would've been a simple massage?
This is how the massage
would've been done.
What's the tough mission?
[Then what is the difficult mission
that awaits the Running Man members?]
Is the forklift going to give us
the massage?
Is it going to scratch our back
or something?
- What is that?
- I'm so nervous about it.
- Your mission is...
- What is it?
It's called, Running League.
We made a makeshift baseball diamond
as you can see to your right.
I think it would be better for us
to demonstrate it for you.
Let us show you.
[Running League demonstration time.]
- What is that?
- I can't do that.
- There's no way I can do that.
- How did you even think that up?
That's going to make me so dizzy.
- He just threw it.
- We have to throw the ball?
[Throws the ball to the catcher
on first base.]
[Catchers two and three have to catch
the ball while holding onto each other.]
[Then throw the ball to the fifth catcher
who has to catch it with a net.]
- They're good.
- Let's get it done in one try.
- We have to do it until we succeed.
The ball can't fall to the ground
when the hitter hits the ball.
The ball has to go up into the air
as a fly ball.
- Then Jae Suk can try doing that.
- Let me try hitting it.
Why don't we play rock-paper-scissors
instead of you just doing it yourself?
He just needs to hit it into the air?
[As long as someone can catch the ball
before the ball falls to the ground...]
[And pass it onto the first thrower again!]
- No way!
- He has to catch that ball?
[And lastly...]
- Stop it!
- This isn't even right.
- Are you guys playing with us?
[And if you can catch it like this...
then the mission is a success!]
- You expect us to do that?
- How did he do that so easily?
- Aren't you even dizzy?
- That would count as a success.
- Aren't you dizzy?
- He's a master at that.
Then does that mean... that the
person has to keep spinning around?
The person in the chair will keep spinning
until you succeed the mission.
- I really can't do that.
[Everyone's trying to avoid being
put into the forklift chair.]
- Ji Hyo's good at things like that.
- Yeah, Ji Hyo would be best.
- Ji Hyo's really good at things like that.
- Why are you making Ji Hyo do that?
- Song Ji Hyo!
- I'm not good at catching things.
What's Ryu Hyun Jin's number
on his back?
- 99.
- You have to succeed within 99 seconds.
[Must succeed within 99 seconds.]
You're such an awful person.
- Someone has to endure that spinning.
- Okay, I'll give it a try.
- Okay, Gary's good at things like that too.
- I'll give it a try.
I'll pass it onto someone
if I really can't endure it.
- Okay, then I'll take over.
- I'll hit the ball then.
You can change your positions once
you pass the 99 second mark.
- So here's your first attempt.
- Okay.
Let's try to get it done in one try.
- You have to do this right, Jae Suk.
- Don't even worry.
[Yoo Hyuk has the most important position
as being the first pitcher.]
This is a very important position.
- I have to get up there if you get it wrong.
- Don't even worry!
[Gary sat upon the spinning chair.]
Let's get this done in one try!
[Start spinning the chair.]
I'm scared!
Play ball!
- Catch it! Here!
- Okay!
[Slips from the very first step...]
- You have to throw it harder!
- Throw it lower.
Just stay where you are!
[Nice catch!]
[Time for these two to catch the ball.]
- Hey!
[Not even a chance.
Too short of a throw.]
You have to throw it high!
- Good! Hurry!
- Throw it high!
There you go!
What are you doing?
[He's doing well catching the ball...]
[Iron chest Tiger making the ball
bounce off of his chest.]
- Are you okay?
- I'm fine.
- This is hard.
- Try to do it right!
[Oh? Finally?]
[They caught the ball!]
[Time to throw it to the third person,
Big-nosed Brother.]
You got it!
[Wow!
Big-nosed Brother catches the ball!]
Throw it easy!
[Catcher Blank Ji- Nice catch!]
[Time for the hitter, Ha Ha
to hit a fly ball!]
[A ground ball.]
[Fail]
- I think we can do it.
- You have to hit it better!
- Seriously, what are you doing?
- You have to do better this time!
You have to throw it harder.
[Time for Coach Kkuk's nagging.]
The most important thing is for you
to do your own job right!
It's your fault that we're even doing this.
Otherwise, we'd be getting a massage!
- Am I wrong or right?
- You're right.
You wait until you get something wrong.
It's a relief that I haven't
gotten anything wrong.
It's a relief.
I was a bit nervous, but
I haven't done anything wrong.
It really is such a relief.
You think all we're going to do
is play baseball?
- Let's just wait and see.
- You can't play soccer either!
[Explodes!]
You can't play soccer either.
- Me?
- That's right.
- I think I'm better than you at soccer.
- Seriously.
- Wait until you do something wrong.
- You can't even play soccer either.
It's fun watching you guys
from over here.
This is your second attempt.
- You did good, Gary.
- Let's succeed this time!
- Okay, let's do this.
- Running Man, fighting!
- Fighting!
- Let's say it louder!
I can't hear any of you.
- Those two keeps ruining it for you.
- Stop angering Jong Kook!
Everyone get on the ground!
[Unhappy Running Man baseball team.]
- Let's stop that fighting, and do this fighting!
- Fighting!
[Blank Ji's fighting cry.]
Fighting!
Play ball!
Let's do this.
- Here I go!
- Good.
[Every mistake that is made...]
[Leaves the person open for
hostile attacks.]
- Why didn't you catch that?
- Throw it. Throw it right now.
Nice!
[Giraffe down?]
Hurry up and get up!
[Second catcher, Giraffe having lost
his strength in his legs.]
- Throw it right!
- Throw it high!
Good.
We got this one.
[Drops it again...]
[The duo has awful teamwork skills.]
- Wait a second.
- What are you guys doing!
Kwang Soo keeps trying to catch it
on his own instead of together.
[They fail the second attempt.]
Here, Jong Kook.
You can take this.
- But he's...
- Just go and take the net.
[The Iron Tiger is swapped out,
and is placed in the third position.]
Just go on to the third position.
Gary's suffering because of you.
We could all be resting
and getting a massage right now
but we're all running around like this
because of you right now.
We're all someone's precious
kids at home!
Look at how we're all suffering!
All this is happening because of you!
Let's do better from now on.
You almost got really angry, huh?
We can just do better from now on.
- We'll just do better from now on.
- You could've said that from the beginning.
- It's just that we're all suffering.
- That's a nicer way of putting it.
This is what I meant to say.
- Do a good job, Suk Jin. Okay?
- I'm much better than Jong Kook is.
- I'll be better than him.
- Please!
Get your heads on straight!
They told us that we'll be doing this until
we succeed no matter how long it takes.
[The mission will continue
until they succeed.]
- Team! Fighting!
- Fighting!
[Play ball!]
Pil-Chok-Cross!
[Again!]
- Can't you do it right!
- What are you doing?
[Even though the players have changed,
the outcome is still the same.]
- You got it!
- Get it!
Let's just get it once.
Kwang Soo keeps avoiding the ball
so he doesn't get hit.
[Oh?]
[They finally catch the ball,
and onto the third catcher!]
[There he goes again...]
- Seriously!
- He's like our black hole!
Seriously!
- You come over here.
- Seriously.
[Time to scold Kwang Soo?]
- Lee Kwang Soo!
- What are you doing?
Do you want to succeed or not?
- Are you even sane right now?
- I'm going to get it right from now on.
Is this your idea of teamwork?
Go tell Jong Kook right now.
Tell him exactly what I just said to you.
I got the message
loud and clear right now.
[Running Man baseball team is on the ball
when it comes to chastising others.]
- Jae Suk just told me...
- I just scolded him.
[Baseball team's youngest player getting
scolded by everyone in turn.]
- What are you doing?
- I've finally come to my senses.
- What are you trying to do here?
- I know what I have to do now.
Isn't Jong Kook the one who
made the mistake this time?
[No kidding.]
- Why are you scolding Kwang Soo?
- Jong Kook is the one who made the mistake.
- You tell him yourself!
- Relay my message to him.
- I told you what to say to him.
- You should've caught the ball.
The way I see it though,
you guys didn't throw the ball right.
- Listen to this guy.
- I'll do better.
I'm lonely over here!
- You're working really hard, Gary.
- I'm lonely.
- Let's do it right this time.
Let me say this as the captain of the team,
but this is really unacceptable.
- Who made you captain?
- Why are you the captain?
- Who made you?
- Who made you captain?
- I'm the captain!
- Listen to that Grasshopper.
Everyone get on the ground right now!
[Another attempt]
[Huh?]
[Gae-minator being lifted up into the air.]
I've become one with the machine.
The forklift and I are now one.
Even the color of your shirt
is the same as the forklift.
[Play ball!]
Nice!
Throw it!
[Yoo Hyuk's getting good at
catching now.]
[Oh?]
[The problem is the Iron Tiger,
the third catcher.]
[Misses again.]
- You need to throw it better!
- It was a good throw!
- Come on, Gary.
- Here I go!
You have to throw it now.
[Huh?]
[First catcher drops the ball.]
- Jae Suk!
- Yoo Jae Suk!
[But they still have plenty of time
left on the clock.]
[Second catchers, Easy Brothers are
now doing good at catching the ball.]
- There you go!
- Nice!
[Time to throw it to Blank Ji.]
[As predicted, nice catch!]
Concentrate!
[Time to hit a fly ball...]
[Hitter, Ha Ha...]
[He hits the ball!]
[Oh... Yoo Hyuk catches the ball!]
[Time for the last step!]
[Gary just needs to catch the ball from
his chair on the forklift!]
[Why did he throw the ball to her?]
What?
Why did you do that?
- What are you doing?
- What were you thinking!
Why didn't you throw it to me?
Get your head on straight!
[The teammates take turns scolding him.]
Your skills aren't the problem,
but it's your lack of memory.
[Finally got caught doing something wrong?
Iron Tiger doesn't hesitate to scold him.]
- You have awful memory skills.
- Let's just get him for this.
I think it's time for you to
get on the chair.
[Time for Yoo Hyuk to get on
the spinning chair?]
Getting dizzy is one thing,
but I'm too lonely up here.
Fighting!
- Let's succeed this time!
- Let's do this until we succeed!
- Fighting!
- This is no joke.
- You're too low.
Spin him faster!
Nice!
- Okay, I got it now.
- Throw it higher.
Do better!
We got it.
- There you go!
- You got it!
[All the way to Blank Ji
in the blink of an eye.]
[Ten seconds left on the clock.]
[Fails with Big-nosed Brother.]
Suk Jin!
- You want to get up there?
- Come up here!
- Suk Jin!
- I'm sorry.
[In the end...]
[Another position change?]
- You have to stay focused!
- I'm so dizzy.
- Stay focused!
- Play ball!
Suk Jin!
Fighting!
Throw it!
[He's just spinning around...]
Throw it now!
[An aimless throw to no one.]
You can't come down from there
until we succeed.
What are you doing?
- You have to focus!
- I'm so dizzy.
- I'm seriously so dizzy.
- What are you doing?
Okay.
Right now.
[Finally.]
[Second catcher duo does a good job
of catching the ball.]
[Even the Iron Tiger catches the ball
without a glitch.]
[And Blank Ji, who has never
failed at catching the ball.]
Here I go.
I'm so dizzy.
[He catches the ball!]
[Finally throwing the ball
to the first catcher, Gary!]
Look over here!
[Where am I?]
[Utter chaos.]
- Look over here, Suk Jin!
- Focus!
Open your eyes!
[Whatever!]
[So dizzy...]
[If he can only catch the ball...]
[No strength or motivation...]
You have to concentrate!
I'm sorry, but I'm way too dizzy.
[They're going to waste the whole day...
Running Man baseball team losing hope.]
[I'm so dizzy...]
[Continuing on with the mission...]
[Heading that you don't see on the
baseball field too often.]
Do I look like some
video game machine to you?
[Nonstop mistakes.]
[The elusive success.]
We have lighting prepared for when it
gets dark, so no need for you to worry.
- What are you saying right now?
- You think we're worried about lighting?
Why would you say that
to us right now?
It's all over for us!
We're never going to get to go home!
Let's go home!
Fighting!
[Meanwhile...]
[Korean Monster,
Ryu Hyun Jin arrives back in Korea.]
[The one who rules Running Man with
a happy smile on his face.]
This is your 14th attempt.
- Kwang Soo.
- Yes, Jae Suk?
What do you mean, you're going to
beat me if I make another mistake?
I'm doing the best that
I can right now.
What do you mean, get lost?
- Let's get it done this time.
- Let's really get it done this time!
Let's do this!
[The Easy Brothers know just
what to do now.]
[Even the Iron Tiger gets it right.]
[And Blank Ji always gets it right.]
[All the way to the hitter
in a blink of an eye.]
[Now time to throw it to the first pitcher.]
[Time for the final step.]
Just this once!
Now!
[Catch it!]
[Will this be it?]
[Will they succeed the mission?]
[So close... but fail.]
[There's still time!]
It's okay, we've still got time.
[Running Man baseball team has all
the moves down by now.]
[Even the black hole Tiger
knows what to do.]
[Blank Ji is a master at catching by now.]
[Back to Yoo Hyuk.]
This is it!
[This time!]
[Must time it right for
spinning Gary to catch it.]
[This time?]
[Will they do it?]
[He catches the ball!]
[Success]
[Running Man baseball team
succeeds in their 14th attempt.]
We can do it!
You did great, Gary.
[Thank you to Gary and the operator of
the forklift for all their hard work.]
Thank you!
[Time to check the next question.]
I'll pick the right one this time.
Look at him.
This is our L.A. baseball stadium
where we have our games.
[Ryu Hyun Jin's home stadium where he
racked up his impressive first season record.]
There are over 50 thousand fans that
come to the games to cheer us on.
It's such a fun and great place to be.
[The love and the cheer from the fans
gives him the energy to play on!]
This is the dugout where all the players
sit and wait for their turns.
- You see the dugout on TV during the games.
- That's where the coaches keep watch.
- He's called me from there a few times.
- Why would he call you?
- This is a phone you can use to call out.
- See? That's what he used to call me.
This is the phone you use to call out
to swap out the players.
This is the spot... where our team coach
always stands to watch the game.
And as for me...
This is where I sit during the games.
To the left of me is where Uribe
always sits.
This is exactly the spot where that
infamous incident occurred.
[This is the spot where the stern expression
was caught which started the news sensation.]
[What exactly happened then?]
I just went inside for a brief moment and
came back out during one of the games.
So Uribe asked me if I went inside
to take a little nap.
So I told him to stop kidding around and
playfully smacked him on the face...
and that was caught on camera.
I think this is how I was standing.
- I just hit him like that lightly.
- I wish I could hit him too.
- You want to hit Uribe in the face?
- Close enough friends where I can do that.
Why don't you start by hitting Jong Kook first
before you move on to hitting Uribe?
This is where I sit.
[This is the spot where Hyun Jin sits
when he's not in the game.]
So that's where he sits.
This is where I keep my towel.
And this is where I keep all my bats.
And this is how I go onto the field.
[Going onto the field with all that
energy when it's his turn.]
Where are we going right now?
[What is this place?]
This is where the players can warm up
before each game.
And the players who are on deck can use this
space to warm up before they go out.
Isn't it nice?
[Is he going to show us his pitch?]
Strike.
[Martin Kin, an employee who
acts as an interpreter for the Dodgers.]
Ball.
The fatso is so cute.
He's so cute even when he gets angry.
[But...]
[Why is he getting in
position to spin around?]
[What's he doing?]
[Spinning around with all his might.]
I'm getting really dizzy.
[Ten spins.]
[And pitching the ball?]
Ball!
Wow, I'm seriously so dizzy.
[Reduce it to only five spins?]
If you reduce it down to five spins,
I can pitch a strike.
- You can do it.
- Fighting.
[Only five spins this time.]
Set, go.
[Will he do it?]
Three.
Four.
Five.
[Oh?]
Strike!
Ryu Hyun Jin's challenge!
[Choose- Ryu Hyun Jin can pitch a strike
after spinning around seven times.]
[A- Strike]
[B- Ball]
- No, he can't.
- He can't do it.
[Another hot debate.]
He just got a strike after five spins.
- Strike.
- He'll get a strike.
- Who thinks he'll get a ball?
- Ball.
- It's a ball.
- He'll get a strike.
- I'm telling you that it'll be a strike.
- It'll be a ball.
- Let's go with a ball.
- I'm telling you, it's a strike.
- It'll be a strike!
- Hyun Jin can do it.
A person's body works like this.
- He won't be able to do it.
- Why does he make all the decisions?
- Then let's do this.
- Play rock-paper-scissors.
Let's play rock-paper-scissors and
go with what the winner chooses.
[Strike- Three people vs. Ball- Three people.]
Rock-paper-scissors.
Okay!
Paper. Okay!
[Giraffe wins three times in a row.]
[Gary wins.]
[It all comes down to Rock-paper-scissors
between Gary and Jong Kook.]
Rock-paper-scissors.
[B- Ball team wins.]
I'm telling you that
he's going to get a strike!
[Deciding to go with option B, Ball, after
a round of rock-paper-scissors.]
- On the count of three...
- It's going to be a strike!
One, two, three.
Ball!
- I know it's going to be a strike.
- Ball!
- This is seriously so frustrating.
- We're going to succeed this time.
[Ryu Hyun Jin can't throw a strike.]
[If you chose that he can't throw a strike,
then go to 'S' hanwoo barbeque place.]
[Oh... hanwoo beef barbeque place?]
- Hanwoo beef barbeque place.
- Let's go!
I doubt they'll let us eat that for free.
['S' restaurant in Boo-yeo.]
- It's a strike.
- No, it'll be a ball.
[Strike vs. Ball.
Still hotly debating one another.]
Let's check first.
[Time to check the answer.]
Okay, press it.
[Did they make the right
selection this time?]
Ryu Hyun Jin's challenge!
Okay, watch.
- Seven spins, right?
- I'm telling you that he'll do it.
[Ryun Hyun Jin can or cannot pitch a strike
after spinning around seven times.]
[They chose that he can't.]
I'm telling you that I'm dizzy
just from watching him do it.
[Will he do it?]
- See? He's stumbling.
- I know he can do it.
- He's stumbling.
- No, he's just finding his position.
- No, he can't do it.
- I'm telling you that he can!
- He's Ryu Hyun Jin!
- He just stumbled.
[Huh?]
[Ball- Running Man gets it right!]
This is what it's like.
[If there had been a hitter,
then the ball would've hit his face?]
You've got the right place.
You've come to the right place.
He told us we came to the right place.
- The person who got it right gets this ball.
- He's giving us his ball?
[A signed ball as a gift?]
So this is how you shoot that?
I've always been very curious about it.
[An immediate space travel?
Hyun Jin's signed ball from L.A.]
You'll receive a signed ball every time
you choose the correct answer.
How that ball will get utilized
will become a very important factor.
So you need to decide who's going to
keep the ball in safekeeping.
[Deciding for himself as to
who's going to hang onto the ball.]
It's not a bad decision to let
Suk Jin keep the ball.
- Yeah, it'll be easy to take it from him.
- That's right.
We can steal the ball later, right?
- Just give it to Suk Jin for now.
- Thanks.
Then we get the easy mission?
- It's an extremely easy mission.
- We're going to get to eat!
- If you had chosen the wrong answer...
- What is it?
You would've had to spin around
in the rice paddy
and find ten baseballs that are hidden
in the muddy fields.
See?
Aren't you glad you listened?
[Aren't you disappointed?]
I don't think we should have
too much faith in Ryu Hyun Jin.
- That's why you need to listen to us.
- Attention.
No thanks.
- I'm sorry, but what I said was wrong.
- You sure?
Wow... that would've been a nightmare.
We really made the right decision.
[The right and wrong answers-
A world of difference.]
- What's our mission?
- So your mission is...
You have to build a tower with all the
meat pieces that are on the grill pan.
- What?
- Build a meat tower?
[Build a tower with
the meat on the grill pan.]
[Like this.]
- That's doable.
- We can do that.
If the tower topples over...
we, the staff will enjoy the
fallen meat.
[We, the staff will enjoy the fallen meat.]
[The beautifully delicious hanwoo beef.]
[Dear God... please help us.]
Since the meat can't be cooked once it's
built in a tower, cook it before you do it.
But since it's the staff eating it if we fail,
let's not cook it as thoroughly.
- Why?
- Huh?
- Or we can burn it.
- Let's not cook it perfectly.
- It's better if it's undercooked though.
- You have to cook it so the meat stays firm.
If you cook it too long,
then it becomes too firm to work with.
[Coach Kook never stops with his banter
even in front of the grill pan.]
Why are you so full of nagging
over grilling meat?
[Wow...]
- This looks so good.
- You have to keep the juices in there.
- So that as you press down on it...
- It'll be easier to stack it up then.
- Leave it alone.
- Stop flipping it over.
- Stop flipping the meat!
- Don't you even know how to grill meat?
I like my meat really well done.
- Just leave it and you can do that later.
- I like my meat really well done.
[All the fighting over personal preference
on how they like their meat grilled.]
- This one, this one.
- No, it's my choice!
- No, it's this one!
- Be quiet!
[Everyone has an opinion of their own.]
[Ah...]
[I want to escape from all this chaos...]
This is why I don't go on
family vacations.
[Especially these two loud mouths.]
- Okay, I'm laying down the first piece.
- That's the one. Look at that.
[Ha Ha lays down the first meat block.]
- No, that's not the one.
- Lay this one down next.
[Blank Ji carefully lays down the next block.]
- We're going to succeed.
- Right in the middle.
There's no way for us to fail this one.
You have to lay it down carefully
so that it's stable.
- Hurry up.
- Stop cooking it.
We're going to be able to eat this
after we're done with this mission.
- Just lay it down for now.
- Okay!
- Look at it from above.
- Okay, I got this.
- It's over once you lay it down.
- Look at it from the top.
[Stable tower with their current four pieces.]
[Next is Kkuk with his rare preference.]
- It's leaning a bit to the side.
- No, it's okay.
I think it's leaning bit.
Look at it from the top.
[Carefully approaching in
a mermaid position.]
See?
It's leaning!
- See? It's leaning!
- No, it's perfect.
[Slightly less stable looking meat tower.]
- Okay, Kwang Soo.
- Kwang Soo.
[Kwang Soo taking his turn in sixth position
which has become quite crucial.]
[If he succeeds, there will only be
two more pieces left to go.]
[Please]
[Kwang Soo succeeds with his
sixth piece of meat.]
- You have to look from the top.
- This way more, Gary.
[It's time for hanwoo grilling party
as soon as Gary gets in his piece.]
Hurry!
You have to hurry, Gary!
[Hurry!]
[Hanwoo tower is in danger of destruction!]
[Will they be able to save it?]
[No! My meat!]
[Since they failed the mission,
the PD will confiscate the meat.]
[Chopstick madness.]
[In less than a blink of an eye,
all the meat gets stolen off the plate.]
[A completely bare plate.]
[You just wait...]
It's really good.
You've angered the staff members, so
they're giving you a different cut of meat.
- Can I get some cola?
- Not until you succeed.
It's going to be tougher than the last time.
These are shaped rounder.
[Rounder shaped meat pieces.]
Can we get a fresh grill pan?
[You think you're out to eat?]
- Let's do it. Give me that.
- Let's change the pan.
- Just give it to me, and let's cook it.
- No, let's change out the grill pan.
- What's wrong with you?
- This isn't good for you.
- No, it's fine!
- Change it. This isn't good for your health.
- Lets swap it out.
- What are you doing?
- No, you did the right thing.
- It takes two seconds to swap it out.
I'm sorry, Sir.
It's for the sake of his health.
[We're sorry for
making things difficult for you.]
What's the need to exchange it now?
- Okay, we got it now.
- This is much better.
- Wait until the grill gets hot.
- Just get the meat on there.
[Nonstop nagging about everything.]
- This is the first one.
- It's really good though.
- This is the second one?
- Let's do this quickly and eat. I'm hungry.
I think this is the easiest mission
we've ever gotten before.
[The meat is cooking nicely.]
Okay!
[Second attempt with the determination to
chow down on the meat when they're done.]
- We have to succeed this time.
- I think that's a good piece.
This one's good too.
Lay that one on top.
Lay it over.
- Get it right in the middle.
- I need better chopsticks.
[Getting serious about their meat selection.]
- That's a good piece.
- This should be good, right?
- Why are you laying it crooked?
- No, this is a good piece.
[Nonstop nagging.]
- No, this needs to be the last piece.
- That's crooked.
- No, do this piece.
- I think this will be better.
- Are you sure about this one?
- Do this one first.
It's exhausting for
all of us to go around together.
[So uncomfortable...]
[Jong Kook succeeds with his fifth piece.]
[Second to last turn, Kwang Soo.]
- You have to be very careful about it now.
- Let's please eat now.
- Let's eat.
- Don't move the table, and don't touch it.
- You have to be careful not to topple it.
- See? We should've done the other piece.
- You have to be more cautious.
- Move it over a bit.
[Six piece tower starting to
lose its balance.]
How many seconds does it
need to stay for?
[Must last for three seconds with all
seven pieces for it to count as a success.]
[The chopsticks are off the meat!]
[What will happen?]
[Oh! Kwang Soo succeeds!]
- You have to do it!
- get out of his way!
- We'll hold onto you.
- Come on, Gary!
Let's eat.
We've got you, so don't worry.
[Four people are holding Gary steady.]
Just worry about your balance.
[As long as he can do this,
then the mission is a success!]
- You can do this!
- No!
No, Gary!
That's not the spot!
[Desperation]
- No, that's not it!
- Come on!
[The last step towards
a hanwoo grilling party!]
[Gary... we're hungry...]
[What will happen?]
[Angry PD rushes in to
cover the meat with a plate.]
[Saves the meat from the attack
of all the chopsticks.]
That was unbelievable.
[The meat that he saved...
is for the staff members to enjoy.]
[Meat tower's third attempt.]
Bring it here.
[All the members are on edge after
having their meat taken away.]
[Annoyed members.]
It's not for us to eat right now.
Just put it down!
- Let's set it down.
- Should we change the grill again?
- No, we don't need to change it.
- Can I go first this time?
- Stop touching it.
Stop touching it and just leave it alone!
Seriously.
You're seriously stressing me out!
[Everyone's starting to get stressed out.]
Can I go first this time?
- Who cares who grills it?
- Come this way then.
- Let me go first.
- What are you talking about?
I don't think I can do this.
[Gary's cracking under the pressure
of being the last member to go.]
Okay, then we'll go this way.
I think we can do it this time.
[The meat is grilling to perfection...]
Okay, let's do this.
- Pick one for Gary.
- I'm not going to look.
[Clear out the mind...]
Okay.
This one?
This is the first piece?
Look at how serious we're all being.
Okay, that's good.
[Gary passes his turn without any burden.]
- No, that looks good.
- Go with that one.
[Kwang Soo is next.]
No, flip it around.
[I'm not looking.]
Save the thick pieces for later.
- Aren't all the meat pieces the same?
- No, lay that down flat.
[Through the second step in the midst
of all the nagging.]
- That looks good.
- I think we'll get it this time.
- Kim Jong Kook.
- Jong Kook's turn.
I think any one of them will work.
All the pieces look fine.
[Kkuk picks up a larger piece...]
- Just lay it on top.
- I think you'll be fine.
[Very stable looking.]
- That one looks flimsy enough.
Just seven pieces. We can do this.
- No, the other way.
- Flip it around.
Yes, there you go.
- See? That's good.
- No, that's perfect.
[Jae Suk completes his turn.]
This is a work of art.
[Even Big-nose Brother gets it done.]
[Their success is right in front
of their eyes!]
- We're almost there.
- We're going to get this done.
The last piece!
[Only... one person left to go.]
- If you don't get this...
- You're going to get beat.
You're going to get beat
if you don't do this.
We're going to beat you
on top of this grill.
[Will he get beat on top of the grill...]
[Or will they eat the meat on the grill?]
[Must last for three seconds for it to count!]
[Success]
Party!
You can now eat as much meat
as you'd like.
[Time for the hanwoo party to start!]
- This is great!
- This is a treat!
You're able to eat like this
because you made the right choice.
[This is only possible because they guessed
correctly on Hyun Jin's answer.]
- Thank you for a great meal!
- Thank you!
[Happiness level is way up!]
- Getting the answer right means happiness.
- We have to get the next one right too.
- Here's your next mission.
- Okay!
[Time to choose the next mission.]
Here you go.
[What's the next question from Ryu Hyun Jin?]
The next game isn't for me to do alone.
I have a very special guest here with me.
I'd like to introduce you to Yoo Suk Min
who has come to L.A. for a visit.
[Ta da!]
[He's here!
Yoo Suk Min!]
[Korea's top right-handed pitcher,
Yoo Suk Min.]
[The man infamous for
his razor sharp pitches.]
[A talented pitcher that the major leagues
are clamoring for.]
[First face-off between the top
left-handed and right-handed pitchers.]
Hello, my name is Yoo Suk Min,
and I'm a baseball player.
I will try to do my best.
Thank you.
You should come out on
our show once.
He needs to stop by on our show before
he goes onto the major league.
[Of course, he does.]
Hyun Jin had to go through us too.
- He and Gary look a lot alike.
- He does look a lot like Gary.
We're the face of this country.
[The three men who could pass for brothers.]
The next game will be
Ryu Hyun Jin vs. Yoo Suk Min.
Fighting.
[Yoo Suk Min vs. Ryu Hyun Jin.
The face-off between the two monsters.]
The first mission is... alkkaggi.
[Ryu Hyun Jin vs. Yoo Suk Min.
First challenge- Alkkaggi.]
Alkkaggi?
- I think Hyun Jin would be good at that.
- I think Hyun Jin is going to win.
Then should I start?
[Alkkaggi competition... start!]
I think Yoo Suk Min will be better.
[Ryu Hyun Jin counterattacks.]
For the first shot...
A straight shot.
I don't think you're good at anything
else besides baseball.
Get up really close... and lightly.
Maybe I shouldn't have done that.
[Hyun Jin takes a clean shot and
gets the white marble out of the board.]
[Current marble count- Four to four.]
Straight.
[Choose:
A- Ryu Hyun Jin wins; B- Yoo Suk Min wins.]
It's not going to be Hyun Jin.
- I pick Yoo Suk Min too.
- I choose Yoo Suk Min.
- I also pick Yoo Suk Min.
- I'm going to go with Ryu Hyun Jin.
[Gary and Jae Suk chooses Ryu Hyun Jin.]
I also choose Ryu Hyun Jin.
It's down to Ji Hyo again.
It's three to three.
[The fate is in Ji Hyo's hands once again.]
[Traitors Club is confident that their
choice B- Yoo Suk Min will be the winner.]
Going with our decision doesn't mean
that you're betraying Hyun Jin.
It's just about who's going to win.
Just because I choose this... it
doesn't mean I'm betraying Ryu Hyun Jin.
[Blank Ji also chooses 'B',
which means, Yoo Suk Min will win.]
Yoon Suk Min!
- One, two, three.
- Yoon Suk Min.
Since you chose Yoon Suk Min to win,
and that Ryu Hyun Jin would lose...
Here's your mission 'B'.
[Mission card 'B' is given to them.]
[B- Yoon Suk Min wins! Go to
the market for choosing Hyun Jin's loss]
[Mission 'B' location-
Off to the market!]
I don't know if it's going to be
a tough or an easy mission.
[A world of difference between choosing
the wrong or the right answer.]
[Did they make the correct
selection again this time?]
Here it is.
[Their third mission location-
The city market.]
[Happily greeting all the shoppers.]
Wow, it's a market.
[Everyone's excited by
the lively market atmosphere.]
- Wow, that rice cake looks good.
- I love rice cakes.
[Beautiful and delicious looking
rice cakes in all shapes and colors.]
I want some for dessert.
Look at the fish!
Look at the size of that fish!
[Full of large and fresh seafood.]
It's a chicken shop.
[A single table at their mission location?]
- Is this another easy mission?
- I feel like it's going to be an easy one.
How could a place like this
be for a hard mission?
- I think we got it.
- Check the answer.
[Checking to see if Yoon Suk Min won.]
I see Myuk PD here.
Which means, we failed at our guess.
[Left handed Ryu Hyun Jin
vs. Right handed Yoon Suk Min.]
[Alkkaggi competition!
Who came out the victor?]
We failed.
Straight shot.
[Straight shot fails!
Current score- Ryu-3: Yoon-4.]
[Cheering Yoon Suk Min on
with every fiber of their being.]
That's the perfect shot for you.
I totally set you up.
- Get it out of there!
- No, not that one.
Yoon Suk Min!
- Hit it, hit it!
- Yoon Suk Min!
Okay, there we go.
It's like we're watching
these two peel eggs.
He just has to throw it now.
I think he's going to win.
[Player Yoon is ahead by a point]
It can't fly off.
It flew off. It's off.
[Hyun Jin is excited about his mistake.]
[A crazy battle is unfolding.]
Can't he get one more try?
[Yoon Suk Min not giving up
his advantage.]
- That's right.
- He shouldn't give it up.
[That's right!]
[Ryu: 1, Yoon: 2]
Now, it's really starting.
One more time.
[What's Ryu Hyun Jin's next move?]
Okay!
[What's he so happy about?]
That's right. Attack!
But it's going to fly off.
[Will Player Yoon be able to win?]
[Or will Ryu Hyun Jin
get another chance?]
[Yoon Suk Min wins!]
- Yoon Suk Min!
I won.
It was such a short, but enjoyable time.
I'll work hard to take the remaining
time to get better results.
Since you answered the question correctly,
I will throw this ball to you.
- Okay!
- Give it to Ji Hyo.
Give it to her!
[Yoon Suk Min's signed ball]
But I left my signed ball over there.
I left it at the restaurant.
[When everyone lost their
minds over the meat...]
[Haroro claims the rare item.]
I'll have to tell my manager
to go and get it.
Hey Hyun Bin, at that meat place...
There's a signed ball.
You have to bring it back.
Okay everyone.
It's the right answer.
Congratulations.
- I think we get a gift.
- Something yummy?
Everyone, it's really a relief
you got the right answer.
- If you had been wrong...
- What would've happened?
- Remember the paper boats you made?
- Yes.
Your boats would've had
to pass through the Geum River.
- You really would've had to.
- Really?
But we've pulled out of those plans.
- That's ridiculous!
- We're not lying.
[However!]
[In reality, they prepared for it.]
We could've been in big trouble.
We should do it. Why not?
It's going to take 12 hours.
- It starts in the morning.
- You think it's possible?
Didn't you watch me cross it?
You crossed it barely
floating above water.
- You were drowning.
- This is crazy.
Since you were correct, here
is a simpler mission.
- One for each.
- Looks cute.
Please look over your
mission statements.
Your fourth mission is
a marketplace word game.
I think I know what this is.
We have to buy the items.
The first item,
we'll tell you what it is.
You'll have to buy another item that
starts with the last letter of the first item.
- Oh, so we have to buy it?
- Yes.
Then it goes on to the next person.
- Can't you write it out for us?
- We can't.
- Can we suggest items?
- You can't.
We will start right away.
Ready?
Okay, the first item.
Gan Jang (soy sauce).
- Jang Jo Rim (boiled beef).
- Jang Jo Rim!
- It doesn't matter.
- Don't bother brainstorming.
Jang. Jang. Jang.
Jang Uh (eel).
Jang Uh. Jang Uh. Jang Uh.
- Gan Jang is over there.
- Not gan jang. Jang Uh.
He's there.
Do you have Jang Gi (Korean chess)?
Or Jang Gap (gloves)?
Jang Gi. Or Jang Gab.
Do you? Oh Jang Gab.
Anything. That'll do.
How much are the gloves?
W1500?
That should be enough.
Thank you!
But the gloves...
- Jang Gap. Jang Sik.
- Jang Gi.
That's all.
Jang Mun (letter).
Are you kidding?
Okay, so it's Jang Gab (gloves).
- Gab, gab.
- What starts with Gab?
Gab. Gab. Gab.
[What starts with gap?]
- What are you thinking about Jae Suk?
- Uh Mook (fishcake).
From Gab Oh Jing Uh (octopus)?
What if she doesn't bring that?
I'm pretty sure there is no
Gab Oh Jing Uh.
Oh, wait a second.
[She spots the octopus!]
Sir, do you have Gab Oh Jing Uh?
- It's not in season.
- Oh really?
Gab. Gab. Gab.
Sir, do you have Gab Oh Jing Uh?
- Gab Oh Jing Uh?
- We don't.
Gab. Gab.
What starts with Gab?
- Gab.
- Gab?
Gab Oh Jing Uh!
But that won't do.
Gab Oh Jing Uh.
Gab.
I really wonder what she's
going to bring. Gab Oh Jing Uh?
[She seems to have bought something.]
What starts with Gab?
What are you doing?
There's no Gab Oh Jing Uh.
Then just buy regular
octopus and insist it's Gab.
How much is the cabbage?
She bought something!
Cabbage with a high Gab (price).
- Cabbage with a high Gab.
- This is tricky.
[Time's up.]
This is frustrating.
Time out.
Let's fight for this.
If we don't get this,
we can't win.
Come prepared with an argument.
[They dare to change the rules
in front of the producers.]
[Totally adamant.]
Let's be self-righteous.
Okay!
We have to be careful with our words.
Okay, let's resume.
Let's use our heads.
Reveal the item!
Ryu Hyun Jin.
How much is this?
Ma'am, how much is this?
What? This. How much
are the Go Chu (peppers)?
[Go Chu doesn't start with 'Jin'.]
Something very (Jin Jja) good.
A very (Jin Jja) tasty apple.
This is too much.
What do you mean?
You never said we couldn't.
A very (Jin Jja) good, new...
[Ha Ha returns]
[What's his item?]
A very (Jin jja) spicy pepper.
Very good.
This is how you do it.
Please give me a radish.
[It's supposed to start with Chu.]
Go ahead, go ahead.
Chu Uk's (memory's) radish.
Mu. Mu.
- A radish representing mother's touch.
- The past is coming back.
This radish means a lot to me.
Everyone has a memory about radishes.
Do you have to go by 'Mu' or 'Ooh'?
- Go by Mu.
- Just Mu?
Don't be worried Suk Jin.
Scarily (Mu Sub Gae) delicious kimchi!
- Scary! Scary!
- Chi?
Don't get nervous.
This is a hidden camera prank, right?
Surprisingly, only a minute
and forty seconds have gone by.
It's been a success so far.
- We can do it.
- I'm going to do this no matter what.
- That's right.
- At all costs.
- What is it?
- Chi Yak (toothpaste).
Very good.
That definitely passes.
What starts with Yak?
Is Suk Jin just standing out there?
- He's getting Yak Soo (mineral water).
- He doesn't have to be too ambitious.
Something a weak (Yak) man eats.
One minute and thirty seconds left.
- Where is he?
- What a weak (yak) man eats.
Or a slightly (Yak Gan) spicy pepper.
[Quiet]
He's here. Suk Jin.
[He was so nervous about this.]
[What does he bring eventually?]
Yak Gwa (flour cookies)!
[Doesn't try to be too creative.]
That's refreshing.
Don't you think?
Yak Gwa is totally refreshing.
We thought you'd do something
like what a weak (yak) man eats.
Thirty seconds left.
- Where's Ji Hyo?
- It's Gwa.
Where did she go?
Gwa Ja (cookies).
- Ja. Ja.
- Twenty seconds!
Just buy anything.
Boo Choo (chives).
What is this?
How much are the spring onions?
Ten seconds!
W500.
[No time! He has to go back!]
[How will the spring onions
start with Ja?]
Here (Ja)! Spring onions!
[What?]
That won't work.
Here, spring onions. Ja Pa.
Ja Pa. Look closely. Pa!
[Mission Fail]
What's wrong with Ja Pa?
A parent's thought of a child (Ja Sik)
as they grew this onion.
Seriously.
Ja, peppers.
Ja, radish. Ja, kimchi.
This is a good finale.
Ja, pa!
It's a good ending.
But you weren't as confident before.
H... here. Pa.
You should have really
committed to it.
If you had done better.
Since the producers have opened
their hearts, just bring whatever.
We'll reveal the item.
Ya Gu (baseball).
Gu Du (slipper).
Feeling as if you are floating
on a cloud (Gu Rum).
Gu Rum Bal (a strip of cloud).
Gu! This, this!
[Buying shoe polish might be faster.]
[What will Gary buy?]
Delicious (Gu Su Han) river snails!
Woo Rung?
No, it's Woo Rung Yi.
Has to start with Yi.
Nice job. Woo Rung Yi.
Yi. Yi. Yi.
How much is this?
- W8000 for all of it.
- Like this?
Here you go.
Yes, I'll take everything.
She's coming. She's fast.
Pretty (Yi Bbeun) baby radish.
- Nice!
- It's really pretty.
[Why couldn't I think of that?]
- It was W8000.
- Really?
- How could it be so pretty?
- Right? It's pretty.
Ji Hyo, the look on your
face was so pretty before.
Scarily (Mu Sub Gae) delicious kimchi.
Kimchi. Chi! Chi!
Chi, chi. Should we
go for the fish oil?
Number of people left is three.
Time left is two minutes and thirty seconds.
We've become so close
with the market lady.
She calls me her son.
Chi Yak (toothpaste)!
- Chi Yak!
- Nice!
- Suk Jin's so refreshing.
- Don't you think?
There's no wit, but it's refreshing.
Red peppers that make
weak (yak han) men get right up!
Now, it's Chu!
What is this?
If we don't do it,
we can't succeed.
- What do we do?
- It's fine. Chi Yak works.
[The game works without being creative.]
You could have just gotten Yak Gwa.
Why make it so complicated?
Next, next.
It's cold (Chu Wuh)! Cold.
That's how we got the cinnamon bark.
Gye Pi. Gye Pi.
Hurry up, go!
Ma'am. Ma'am.
Wow, Gye Pi is the best when it's cold.
[Continues to plead his case.]
Is it cold outside?
[The last one!]
[What's Jae Suk's answer?]
Through blood-inducing (pi nan) efforts
the farmer has grown...
onions!
[Finale: Through blood-inducing efforts
the farmer has grown onions!]
You could have just bought
Pi Mang (bell peppers).
[Anyway, it's acceptable.]
Now, we'll go over all the items.
Delicious (Gu Su) king snails (Woo Rung Yi).
Pretty (Yi Bbeun) baby
radishes (Chong Gak Mu).
Scarily (Mu Sub Gae) delicious kimchi.
Toothpaste (Chi Yak).
Red peppers (Go Chu) that make
weak (Yak Han) men get right up.
It's cold (Chu Wuh),
so you get Cinnamon Bark (Gye Pi)!
Through blood-inducing (pi nan) efforts
the farmer gives us onions!
[Mission accomplished!]
The last one was a clincher.
There's a phone call for you all.
Who is it?
Hello?
Yes, hello.
This is Ryu Hyun Jin.
Hyun Jin!
I'm at Incheon now.
- Hurry up. Hurry here.
- We have to rip your name tag off!
Let's face off Ryu Hyun Jin!
Since Jong Kook can't face me...
I let you off easy last time.
He just let you off.
Did you do the mission?
Of course. We did everything.
- Wasn't it hard?
- Totally hard!
- We love you Ryu!
- See you next time!
- Bye!
Okay now, it's the last
question for today.
Think carefully before you choose.
- Come over here to look.
- Let's look together.
Here you go.
I'm hungry.
- Hello.
[A Chinese restaurant in L.A.]
He must like Chinese food.
Jjajangmyun and Jjamppong.
Let's mix this.
[He's big enough to eat this much.]
Whenever I think of Chinese food,
I come to a Chinese restaurant to eat.
Should I eat jjamppong
or jjajangmyun?
What do you usually prefer?
Me?
Both.
[Ryu Hyun Jin's decision.]
I think it's jjajangmyun.
No it's gotta be jjamppong.
No, he needs jjajangmyun.
- He won't have the jjamppong first.
- First, he'll have jjajangmyun.
Then he'll have jjamppong
to get rid of the oiliness.
One, two, three.
- Jjajang.
-Jjamppong.
Do it over.
- One, two, three.
- Jjajang.
[And that is how they decide on jjajang.]
We'll start the mission
with you having chosen jjajang.
If you think Ryu Hyun Jin eats
Jjajang first, go to L outlet.
[L Outlet Mall.]
[There's a stage.]
[Someone's emerging.]
[They are finally here.]
[Welcome idol group, EXO.]
[A shocking and cool entrance.]
Okay, now your last mission will start.
EXO versus Running Man.
You'll take turns playing hide and seek.
You just got your question wrong.
[Ryu Hyun Jin's Choice:
Jjajangmyun versus Jjamppong]
[His choice...]
[After a bite of tang soo yook...]
I want jjamppong.
Since you got the question wrong,
you'll start by hiding.
EXO will start looking for you now.
- Running Man crew!
- EXO versus Running Man.
Running Man versus EXO.
Rotating hide and seek starts now!
[EXO has started looking.]
[EXO's preemptive strike.]
[Can Running Man overcome this?]
[EXO is now looking for you.]
- Hello?
- Where are you?
Are they gone?
Xiumin!
- Hurry and look for them!
- Hurry, hurry.
Is someone here? Hello.
What's wrong?
This is really hard.
They're really good at hiding.
[Scared to death.]
Where are you?
This isn't good.
- EXO fighting!
- Fighting!
Should we go this way?
Baek Hyun, I'm going this way.
You scared me.
- We're both looking.
- I'll look here. You look there.
[Kai looks through the storage
room in the back.]
Hey!
[He's been discovered!]
I can't do this alone!
- Where, where?
- The wild savage is this way.
Block him there.
Trap him, trap him.
Hello Jong Kook.
My name is Kai.
I know. Hey Kai.
Let's go. Let's go.
Hello, anyone there?
EXO gather there!
[EXO has brought in auxiliary troops.]
The rest of the team is now here.
Hey, you don't have to do this.
[Kai feels cornered instead.]
Wait, I think I've become a hostage.
- Everyone come here.
- He's too strong.
Go from the bottom.
[Jong Kook versus Four EXO members]
If there are a lot of people
here, it's not good for defense.
We should leave.
Hey guys, where are you going?
You can't leave us here!
He was too strong.
How are you getting out?
You can come as you please,
but you can't leave as you please.
[Mr. Capable is in danger.]
No. No.
[A bit of a feat for EXO to
catch Mr. Capable.]
[Suho got Mr. Capable's name tag!]
[How could this happen?]
Kim Jong Kook out.
Kim Jong Kook out?
[Running Man is in danger
without Mr. Capable.]
[Gary runs to hide in the clothing store.]
[Spotted!]
[EXO follows behind.]
Hello!
Hello, we're here.
[Past the storefront and
to the storage room.]
- He's not there.
- Oh hello!
[He hid well, but Gary
has been discovered!]
First, let me take your name tag.
[Exchanges greetings after
taking his name tag.]
Hello, I am EXO's Chen.
Chen, I'll make sure to
remember you.
[EXO's Chen claims Gary's name tag.]
How did he find this?
Gary out.
- Nice job.
- Good, good.
[Running Man team has lost
strong players too soon.]
But a place like this is too obvious.
One minute before rotating.
[EXO feels a sudden sense of urgency.]
[Now the seekers must hide.]
- Here.
- But this place is too open.
[EXO and Kai looking for a place to hide.]
There are doors on both sides.
When we hide, we can run...
We can escape either
this way or that way.
We will now rotate the search.
Look at these shoes.
Let's go.
Now, they feel confidence.
Nine, ten, eleven.
You may be a strong opponent...
But it's been fun.
[What is he saying?]
You know just by walking
and you can hear the ringing.
- Children.
- Hey kids!
- Hey kids. Here you are.
I'm calling you just in case.
[EXO's Chris seems to be nervous.
Looking for a new spot.]
What do I do?
Wait there Chris.
Chris!
I see you Chris!
He went in there.
[Chris seems a bit confused.]
[Goes into the closest clothing store.]
[Is someone else in here?]
Is he here?
I wonder where he is?
He's probably really scared right now.
[Kai is also in the store!]
This way...
[Chris doesn't hide. He runs!]
- Chris?
- Are they gone?
I'm happy. I'm sweating
so much right now.
Hey Chris is over there.
Come here!
- Where?
- Over here, over here, over here.
I got you Chris!
[Giraffe joins the feast.]
[Kwang Soo gets EXO Chris' name tag.]
Chris, you did well.
Chris, out.
Jae Suk, we're pretty good at this.
We need to get at least four
out to win.
I don't know how we can find them.
Where are you EXO?
Hey kids where are you?
Come out kids, we see you.
Where are the nice children?
I'm growling.
Children!
I'm growling now.
Hey. I have a feeling
someone's here.
- Was I feeling you?
- Yeah, it was me.
Do you think they're behind
the boxes?
Seriously.
Hey, bingo!
Nice to see you!
Let's start off by hugging.
I'm sorry. I love you.
I can't help it.
Oh my. We're sorry Baek Hyun.
Baek Hyun, out.
I'm in trouble.
[By any chance?]
[EXO's D.O. discovered.]
[He found a novel place to hide.]
Sorry about this D.O.
- Hello.
- We're sorry about this.
Thank you.
[So polite even after defeat.]
- You really scared us.
- I thought I could avoid being found.
D.O. out.
No way.
Who... who did all the ripping?
Did Jong Kook really get out?
Jong Kook. Jong Kook.
Is he really out?
But we're still getting
all these players out?
This is ridiculous.
I see the kids over there.
Come down, come down.
We got him!
Nice to see you.
Stay here Xiumin.
[Xiumin out!]
Seven people left.
[EXO: 7 players
Running Man: 5 players]
One minute until rotating.
In a bit, it will be EXO's turn to look.
EXO's right here.
- There he is.
- EXO's over here!
- Hello!
- We're here.
Come here. We're right here.
There's not much time left.
[Tao runs toward the elevator.]
[Jae Suk's in the elevator now.]
[Not much time until rotation.
What will happen next?]
[Next week. D-day!]
- It's time to spit it out.
- Wait!
- Over there!
- He's going back!
[Korean Monster]
[The World Series starts now!]
[Running Man takes to the mound.
With Suzy!]
Subtitles by DramaFever