[Running Man - Battle of the money.]
[There will be no mercy!]
[The bottom line is to get the
cash envelope!]
[Neither tears or blood will
get you any sympathy!]
[Welcome to the battle of the money!]
[I'm a guest!]
[SBS Broadcasting Center]
Subtitles by DramaFever
Hello to all the viewers out there.
I'm your host for the day, Kim Hwan.
With the arrival of the long awaited 2013,
we now start our opening ceremony for 2013.
[Running Man opening ceremony?]
[Picket... entrance?]
Wow... the wind...
It's so windy out here.
[Cutting through the icy wind
to enter the lobby.]
- Hello.
- It's so nice to see you.
- Thank you.
- Hello.
I'm glad to see everyone with
a smile on your faces.
[Happy to see Kim Hwan here as
Running Man's official announcer.]
What's going on here today?
I see that you've all walked in with
your new year's resolutions for 2013.
[To slap Jong Kook on the face
more than twice this year.]
To hear Jong Kook plead for his life
more than twice this year...
and to eliminate Jong Kook's name tag
more than three times this year.
[Every one of his resolution involves
besting his Tiger brother.]
Shall I read you mine?
To hold Jong Kook down with my strength
and rip his name tag off with my left hand.
Ten times... to do this at least ten times.
I wrote down, Unification of the nation.
[To put out a popular song.]
And... to announce my retirement.
Since I need to reaffirm my character...
And your last one is SBS' Grand Prize?
That is my humble dream.
[From the Excellence award to
Grand Prize award?]
[Hoping for an entertainment award
more than a music award?]
Then what about you, Impala?
I wrote down that I want to be the victor
more than five times this year.
And... I would like to bring back
the gold prizes for the races.
Bring back the gold prize!
Bring it back!
We're in the middle of
our opening ceremony right now.
And now, we will bring out the special guests
who'll honor us for our opening ceremony.
Please welcome them with a
round of applause.
[Entering the lobby with
picketing signs of their own.]
It's Shin Yang!
[Park Shin Yang and Uhm Ji Won]
[A man synonymous with the word,
romance, whom everyone loves.]
[Amazing acting ability,
with a face to match - Park Shin Yang.]
[Overflowing with attraction, an
actress symbolic of purity, Uhm Ji Won.]
[Welcome, Park Shin Yang and Uhm Ji Won.]
Ah... it's Shin Yang!
Please give them a round of applause.
Hi, Ji Won!
[The two guests catching the members
of Running Man in a total surprise.]
- Hello.
How is it that you're on our show?
- I'm a huge fan of yours!
- Let's see what Shin Yang's resolutions are.
- Wow, you have a great handwriting.
- Did you write that yourself?
[To shoot a great movie.]
Can you say it in your screen voice?
[In the voice that was used in 'The Promise'
which had become a topic of conversation.]
[This is the scene!]
[In the same tone as that time...]
And to make a good movie...
[Exactly in the same tone
which was used back then.]
To ski better... and to love more.
[A man who does everything
with a flare of elegance.]
[If nothing else, at least for today,
that image will surely come to a ruin!]
[A new image of Park Shin Yang that
can't be seen anywhere else!]
[Next up is Thumbelina Ji Won's
new year's resolutions.]
For the advertisements to succeed,
and for the marriage to succeed.
- It sounds like you'll be successful.
- Thank you.
[An innocent image that she
once portrayed...]
[A revealing of her real image
coming to you soon!]
Next, we have a new year's greeting
from the General Manager.
[Could it really be the General Manager?]
Really? The General Manager?
- Really?
- Please welcome him with a round of applause.
- The General Manager is coming?
- Is he really?
- He really is coming!
- Oh my!
[The real General Manager
makes his appearance!]
- General Manager...
- Oh my... hello!
We're all dressed in sweat suits...
My name is Park Jung Hoon,
the program General Manager for SBS.
I've been to the award show a few times,
but coming on the program like this...
I feel a little bashful to be here.
Hello, I'm 2012's super model, Jung Ha Eun.
[A noticeably different welcome?]
Two and a half years have gone by
since Running Man first started airing.
You've all worked very hard for those years
running to bring laughter to our viewers.
I hope that you get the inspiration to
bring even bigger laughter in the new year.
Thank you.
Why don't you announce the teams
for today's race for us?
- General Manager will announce the teams.
- Team announcement?
He came to the opening ceremony to
announce today's teams.
I will announce today's teams.
The first team...
It's full of members that I like.
Song Ji Hyo... Ji Suk Jin and Yoo Jae Suk.
Me too?
Then does that mean you don't like us?
The second team...
Uhm Ji Won...
and Kim Jong Kook,
whom I respect very much.
Respect?
Lee Kwang Soo,
whom I love very much.
I'm full of respect and love for you!
I wish you nothing but
the best in the new year!
And lastly, our guest, Park Shin Yang...
Ha Ha and Gary will make up
our final team.
- This is great!
- But this is...
These guys lack too much to be
on the same team with Shin Yang.
- How can you say such a thing?
- They lack too much to be with Shin Yang.
I'm the one who's really close
to Shin Yang!
What do you mean, you two are close?
- Let's see about this in 10 years!
- What a joke!
In gratefulness for all your hard work thus far
and for your continued efforts in the future
- A bonus?
- Yes, the General Manager...
- Really?
- Yes, he's giving out a special bonus.
[Special Bonus!]
- Wow, that looks thick.
- Thank you very much.
[Closing out the opening ceremony
with warm hearts and greeting.]
- Really? 50,000 won bills?
- Can you just tell us the color of the bills?
It's real money in here.
What is this?
[Target General Manager's bonus cash!]
[Real battle of the money targeting
the bonus cash!]
[Each team is given
1,000,000 won in bonus cash!]
[But the team that comes in last at missions
will have to forfeit some of their cash!]
[Which team will protect their bonus to
the end to laugh their way to the bank?]
Finally, the money is within my grasp.
Anyway, everyone be aware to protect
your cash bonus to the end, okay?
Our two guests who took the time out
of their busy schedule to be here...
be sure to take good care of them.
I'm going to win the money,
and give it all to her.
- Really?
- Of course.
Without even asking me about it first?
Since they took the time to come on the show,
of course she should get the money.
- Seriously?
- Of course!
Geun Young was way too young for you!
When I told people that I was coming
on the show, I was told that I needed
to do whatever I could to get
Kim Jong Kook on my team.
There you two go pairing off now.
And I was told to do whatever I could
to stay away from Kwang Soo.
- What does that mean?
- I was told not to get close to him.
You can think of them as two opposites
ends of the extreme.
How about you, Shin Yang?
Have you been told who to team up with?
To be perfectly honest... these two weren't
amongst the recommendations.
Shin Yang... I won the race last week!
I don't betray anyone,
and I'm a very valuable member too!
Seriously, that's so disappointing to hear!
I won the most races last year!
[When?]
Manager Gae, take good care of him.
Yes, I will take very good care of him.
Manager Gae, take very good care of him.
And over here,
we have the Lady and her servants.
[Team Lady and servants?]
Lady and her servants.
As for us...
Our team is a family who's been together
for a very long time.
I think this is the first time
the three of you are on the same team.
[Bonus target race - Start!]
[Stepping out into the icy cold winds.]
- It's so cold.
- It's really cold out.
- Who has the money right now?
- It's in Kwang Soo's bag.
- You have the money?
- I do feel a little nervous about it...
I was told Kwang Soo can't be trusted
with such things.
- Give it to me.
- I'm really not like that!
[Ji Won takes the bonus to
keep it close to her.]
- This team up really sucks.
- That's what I'd like to say!
- I don't like our team.
- Seriously, Song Ji Hyo...
- You can call us babies.
- What did you say?
- Babies?
Please say, 'Come on baby, let's go.'
- There's something I'm really curious about.
- Yes?
Why is your name Gary?
My nickname when I was
in middle school was Gae (Dog).
- Shin Yang!
- Yeah?
Why do you keep calling out his name?
[Off to their first mission location!]
But why is it... that I was told not to
choose you and Gary to be on my team?
I think they must be mistaken.
[Seems to like the little brothers
that he's been teamed up with?]
Keep it down when I'm talking.
[Scolds the navigation.]
[Quietly ordering the navigation around.]
- No more sounds, right?
- 'In a little bit...'
[The gags are slowly getting started.]
I heard what you said to
Shin Yang earlier.
Yes. I decided that I wanted to become an
actress after I saw him in 'The Promise'.
[Her decision was made after seeing
Shin Yang's movie, 'The Promise'.]
- The movies that you were in...
- What have you seen?
I've seen every single one of them.
Just name it, and I've seen it.
- 'The Promise'...
- That was the beginning. 'The letter'...
Even though you wore the cap in the movie
because you played an ill patient...
But Gary is wearing his cap today
in honor of your role in that movie.
With a touch of Hye Min's feel to it...
'Why can't you say it?'
'That this is my man!
Why can't you say it?'
I'm asking you, why can't you say it?
Don't you love me?
When I'm your man!
[Even after the passing of all these years,
the scene is still clear in their minds.]
From now on, you can call us
Baby one, and Baby two.
- Let's go, babies.
- Gary...
Gary, let's go.
Ha Ha, let's go.
[Bonus target race -
Their first mission location is?]
- What are we going to do at a gas station?
- We've never been to a gas station before.
What are we going to do there?
What if we have to go through the
automatic car wash in there?
Jong Kook is like Running Man's
own fortune teller.
- I'm a fortune teller too.
- I know.
[Ji Won plays a shaman in her new movie.]
Then I'll see if I can guess.
At the gas station...
[I can see it... the vision...]
[I can see the mission...]
What is it?
What kind of a game will we be playing?
First, everyone will be gathered around.
After we're all gathered around...
[That kind of a prediction is something
anyone can guess...]
At the gas station...
there will be water involved.
[Water?]
We're going to be playing with water?
At the gas station?
[In... this harsh winter?]
Since there's a self-car wash
at the gas station...
I think we're going to be
playing around with that.
Self-car wash...
You seem to be pretty tired,
why don't you just get some rest?
Who's going to play around with
water in this cold weather?
I know. Not in this cold weather.
Today's the coldest we've had yet.
[A shaman?
Could Ji Won's predictions be right?]
Let's go and check to see if our
Shaman's predictions are right.
[Red Team arrives at the gas station.]
[What could be the mission that
awaits them at the gas station?]
- See? I was right!
- Where?
[Just as Ji Won predicted...
playing with the water?]
- There's someone from 'The Matrix'.
- Who is that man?
Dong Hwan!
[You... you're...]
[Are you from 'The Matrix'?]
What's with him?
- Go-Trix, please step forward.
- Go-Trix?
The name of this game is,
'Gas station Matrix'.
So what does that mean?
I will show it to you,
so please step to your left for now.
I wonder what it'll be about. Maybe
we'll have to put some water in there.
In that water container.
I'm getting an uneasy feeling about this.
What are they doing?
Ah... on our back? Like this?
[What is that?]
- What is that?
- What is he doing?
I think it's about gathering much water
as you can in the bowl.
- How are we supposed to do that?
- No way!
[Just like the scene in the movie.]
[The key point to this mission is
the flexibility of their backs!]
[The water has to reach the red line level
for it to be considered a success.]
I can't bend backwards like that.
That's too funny.
- Shin Yang's face... is starting to harden.
- What is this?
[The smile on my face really isn't a smile.]
He came on the show because he didn't
realize what he was getting himself into.
This is just way too funny.
[This is what variety shows are
all about...]
All of you are happy about receiving
your bonus cash today, right?
The team that comes in last
in this game has
to pay for other teams fuel fees
with the bonus cash that they received.
[Rule: Loser team to pay for
other teams car fuel fees.]
[No wonder the fuel in the car
was so low...]
The time you will be given
is 40 seconds.
[Must fill past the red line with water
to succeed the mission.]
It doesn't matter if you just
lie down on the ground either.
[Aggressive Ji Won.]
Do you think we can catch a lot of water
if we lie down on the ground?
You guys should be doing that.
How can you make Ji Won do it?
[The two inconsiderate men leaving Ji Won
to be proactive all on her own.]
- She's lying down on the ground by herself!
- We're still thinking up a plan.
- Ji Won, why don't you lie down?
- Come on, hurry up!
[Lying back down with a bright smile
on her face.]
And behind us, Shin Yang is
waiting for his ski lift.
[Where did he find the goggles?]
[I'm not going to go down that easily!]
[Red Team - Start!]
Stay still! Just stay still!
[Giraffe and the Tiger dumping
all the water on Ji Won.]
[What will be the result of their plan?]
Ji Won is...
[Ji Won's face getting completely soaked.]
- Help me get up!
- Hang on!
[In order not to waste even a
single drop of water...]
[A perfect matrix position.]
[Oh no! All the hard-earned water...]
What are you guys doing?
Help me get up!
[There's no time!
Gathering up the water in his mouth...]
We got it!
[Such precious water...]
[Oh no... you spilled so much of it!]
[Time over!]
[Fail...]
- How did I spill all that?
- You should've helped her up, Jong Kook.
[Ji Won's hard efforts going to waste...]
I'm completely soaked!
I'm soaked!
- Okay, challenge.
- Challenge!
We came up with a plan of our own.
[What is the plan that they
came up with?]
[A human stretcher?]
[Just what are they planning
by doing this?]
- Okay, let's do it!
- We're ready.
[Blue Team - Start!]
[Shots of water being shot out
once again!]
- Why is the water...
- Why is the water being sprayed?
Why is the water being sprayed?
Go Dong Hwan!
- You!
- Are you really going to be like this?
That's not right!
Let's go dump what we have.
[Thought they were just getting soaked...
but gathered up a nice bit of water!]
- Shoot the water!
- Go-Trix!
[Should I make it harder?]
[Their protesting is no match
for the forceful stream of water.]
[Impossible to even approach.]
- Hey! Go Dong Hwan!
- Go Dong Hwan!
[A fervent outcry directed at
Agent Go-Trix.]
[Time over!]
- Why are you giving us the water like that?
- Why are you giving it to us like that?
What are you doing?
[Their plan fails due to water being shot
at the differently than they had predicted.]
Do you even know how
heavy Ji Hyo is?
Don't be like that.
- His goggles...
- Why are you wearing the goggles?
[The goggles finally make their appearance.]
[Perfectly armed.]
[Team babies' turn at the challenge.]
[Raincoat brothers with a matching
cringe on their faces.]
More! Give us more water!
That's not enough water!
[Did he come to earth from out of space
from lack of water at his home planet?]
[Armed with his goggles...
Shin Yang doesn't hesitate.]
[Give me my water!]
[Ah... there's the disadvantage of
not being able to see very well...]
[A new plan, Human pedestal.]
[Armed with the goggles...
Shin Yang gathers the water and dumps it.]
[Is their plan working?]
[But the water stream has
a mind of its own...]
Give us the water the right way!
What are you doing?
You scoundrel!
[The ever gentle Park Shin Yang
explodes during his first mission!]
Give us some water!
What are you doing?
What is this? A water spray?
[As if they've been waiting for it,
getting right up in front of the water.]
[I'll give you as much as you want...]
- I can't see... I can't see!
- Over here!
[His vision is blocked
because of his goggles...]
[Time over!]
[Fail]
He can't even see in front of him
because of his goggles.
[Blue Team's challenge]
[Their plan is to form
a single line this time?]
Set... go!
[Taking turns to move
quickly through the line!]
Where do you think you're
shooting that thing?
[Definitely an unpredictable
water stream.]
Hey! Watch where you shoot
that thing!
[Is he gargling?]
You've got 10 seconds left!
[10 seconds to go!]
[Give me my water...]
[Their last spurt of attempt.]
[Just concentrating on their bucket
without even being able to open their eyes.]
Stop!
[Time over]
[Almost to the line... did they succeed?]
[Ah... just shy of the line!]
[Will Blank Ji fill the rest?]
What the heck!
[All that water in the end!]
[Blue Team succeeds!]
[Crap...]
- How did you do that?
- I couldn't see, so I just did what I could.
- How did you catch so much water?
- I can't believe this!
- How did you catch all that water?
[Running Man's Ace
showing off her true skills.]
[Blue Team passes as first place winners.
Free gas for their car!]
It's okay.
We just need to come in second.
- We just can't come in last.
- As long as we're not last, we're okay.
- Fighting!
[Red Team's challenge.]
Set... go!
[What could it be this time?]
[His position ensuring that
he'll get soaked to the bone.]
[If anything, he's only getting in the
way of his own teammates.]
[Gathering more water in his mouth
than in the bowl itself.]
[Giraffe is too stubborn to think about
changing the position he's taken.]
[On top of it all,
he's spilled everything he's got.]
[Ji Won working hard to pick up Giraffe's
slack to gather as much water as she can.]
[It seems he's gathered quite a bit,
but he spills quite a bit too.]
[Time over!]
Are you a water beetle or something?
[Ah... too bad...]
[Unbelievably disappointing... fail.]
Did you see Kwang Soo?
He only filled it up once.
I know! He only got in the way,
and didn't even help out!
You have to go and dump the
water immediately!
Being on the same team with
you is awful!
Come on, Ji Won... we just started!
- We just started.
- My manager told me to stay away from you.
- Team Baby, fighting!
- Fighting!
Be better about giving us
water this time.
Set... go!
[Shin Yang showing no hesitation.]
Is he not able to get up?
[Every drop is precious.]
[Green Team filling up
the water pitcher drop by drop.]
You've got 10 seconds left!
[10 seconds left to go!]
[The last burst of attempt.]
[Ever so carefully...]
[Pouring it in carefully.]
[Will it go over the line?]
[Success.]
If you had been a little quicker,
we could've won!
[Blaming the Giraffe.]
I never should've even met you.
With the Team Baby coming in second,
the Red Team will pay for everyone's gas.
[Red Team to pay for everyone's gas.]
- How much is it?
- What?
- How much?
- What do you mean? I'm filling it up.
- Since the gas is expensive, just a little...
- No, I have to fill it up!
- You can stop pumping now.
- What are you talking about?
- You can stop the pump.
- Fill it up, please.
Stop the pump.
[Blue Team wanting to fill up vs.
Red Team wanting the pump to stop.]
[The gas is currently scraping
the bottom of the fuel tank.]
Excuse me... I'm going to fill it up.
We'll take 150,000 won worth of gas.
- How about just 50,000 won worth?
- No, we have to fill it up.
50,000 would get you plenty
to drive around for the day.
Why are you being wasteful?
Why!? Why are you being wasteful?
I can't understand this!
Why are you being wasteful? Why?
50,000 will be plenty for the day,
so why are you being so wasteful?
Just put 50,000 won worth!
- There's the next game to consider!
- If anything, 50,000 is still too much!
Be quiet!
Just sit there and wait!
[Shin Yang is the one who beeped.]
[Immediately becomes docile.]
[You're the best!]
Okay then,
I'll just put in 60,000 won worth.
- I'll just put in 50,000 won worth.
- No, put in just 50,000 won worth.
[Blue Team's 60,000 won vs.
Red Team's 50,000 won.]
- Why are they being wasteful?
- Can you talk some sense into them?
50,000 won is a lot of money.
You can get to Busan with 50,000 won!
[When are you ever going to gas up?]
Ugh... seriously!
Come on... let's just settle on 50,000 won.
You can get to Busan on 50,000 won!
I'm not settling.
Just fill up 60,000 won worth.
[Finally settles on 60,000 won.]
- We'll see how you do at the next game.
- 60,000 won isn't even a lot of gas!
We should be filling it up!
- Seriously, you people...
- Fill it up, please!
As requested, we'll fill up your tank.
- Wait!
- Fill it up!
[Red Team rushing over in a hurry.]
- Wait... hang on a minute.
- Suk Jin!
[Red Team is now starting to
deal with the Green Team.]
We don't need to be frivolous here.
With 50,000 won worth of gas, we
can drive around all day for our games.
Why do we have to be so wasteful?
- There's no need to do that.
- Why don't' you make the call, Shin Yang?
[Green Team leaving their decision
making up to Shin Yang.]
Please fill it up with diesel gas.
[Fill up the car with diesel gas?]
Shin Yang, even with 50,000 won worth,
you can get all the way down to Busan.
We're going to leave all our
decision making up to Shin Yang.
Why don't you discuss it with Shin Yang?
You can discuss it with him though, right?
You can't trust him on a
deal like this.
What are you talking about,
Monk Gae?
Okay, okay...
we'll just take 60,000 won worth.
- Thank you, Shin Yang.
- Okay, 60,000 won.
- Yes, 60,000 won worth of gas!
- The fancy kind, please!
[Red Team pays out
120,000 won in gas costs.]
We're supposed to go to
the health club in Shilwaldong.
- That's something Jong Kook would like.
- You're right, it is.
- Have a great day!
- Bye, and thank you!
Okay, let's get on our way.
Our next location...
Ji Won, please read it out loud.
Go to the health club in Shilwaldong,
and find the Running Man landmark.
- A health club?
- Yes.
- The health club in Shilwaldong.
- A health club...
It's the same thing as
going home for Jong Kook.
You didn't swallow too much water
back there, did you?
You were on your back too much and
you had so much water dumped on you.
Did you not see me
lying down on my back?
Even though you did,
you weren't of much help to us.
- Yeah! You should've moved quicker!
- If you had done better, we could've...
Of course, don't you think?
[Ji Won and Kkuk joining together
to scold Giraffe.]
When it was just us two doing it,
we almost had it to the line, didn't we?
We could've won for sure if you'd just
made at least two trips to the pitcher.
We could've been in first place.
You just looked like a water beetle.
- I promise to do better at the next game.
- We're in the last place because of you.
- Just watch... I'll do it this time around.
- What? You're going to win this game for us?
- You guys are siding against me, aren't you?
- No, it's not like that.
[Are we detecting a love line?]
We're just banding together
because we're on the same team.
- Team work... it's called team work.
- No, this is more like a love line.
- It's team work.
- You're not denying that it isn't either.
- The way you guys are banding together...
- It's not that. But this is about winning.
Your goggles were a nice touch.
You were very prepared today, Shin Yang.
Yes, I always keep them in my car.
I can see how competitive you are now.
Our... that's...
[Sharing his emergency stash of
chocolates with his little brothers.]
This will give us more energy.
Shin Yang...
[Is this... the love line that had
hoped for in the new year?]
What are you guys doing?
My wish this year was to...
make five love lines this year.
You're my first for the year.
Can we not do that?
Are we a love triangle then?
[Arrives at the second mission location.]
[Shinwaldong's fitness center.]
Kim Jong Kook... he's going to love this.
This might as well be Jong Kook's home.
[Huh? A microphone on the
weight machines?]
- Look at this... this is karaoke.
- Look at the microphones.
Ah, that karaoke room?
Try this. Can you even do this?
- I hate games like these.
- Games likes these aren't good for us.
What do you mean, 'wow'?
Kim Jong Kook's on that every single day!
- This game is meant for Kim Jong Kook.
- What kind of a game is this?
If you can get over 90 points by singing into
the mikes attached on the machines...
Isn't this my house?
This is my house.
- Stop being so happy.
- I feel like I'm home.
Lunch rides on the winning of this game...
[The loser team from this game will have
to pay for everyone's lunch bill.]
- We have to pick really good dishes.
- Are there any good mushroom dishes?
How about the sea urchin soup?
That sounds god, the sea urchin.
- How about the sea urchin soup?
- We should definitely have sea urchin soup.
- Shin Yang, what are you going to eat?
- I'm going to have the sea urchin soup.
[Fitting right in.]
- Do you like sea urchin soup?
- Do you even know what that is?
Yes, I eat this soup every day.
[Sly as a fox, Shin Yang.]
Sea urchin soup is baby's
favorite thing!
- What are you going to eat, Ji Won?
- I'm going to have the sea urchin soup.
[Sea urchin soup seems to be
the most popular item on the menu...]
- The staff will be joining in on the meal.
- What?
[On top of that, there will be an added
100 staff members joining their lunch!]
- What did you say?
- We have to pay for all theirs too?
The loser team has to pay for everything?
I told you earlier that you'd have to
pay for the lunch bill.
Okay! It's not going to
be us anyway.
[As long as they don't come in last...]
- As long as we're not last, right?
- Fine, we can do this!
It's not going to be us!
[Staff members lining up to
put in their lunch order.]
[Staff members ordering what they want
without any care to what the dish costs.]
Get whatever you want!
Order whatever you'd like to order.
[With the confidence that he
won't be the one to come in last...]
I'm feeling uneasy about this.
[If we lose this...
my entire bonus goes out the window.]
Thank you for the meal!
[Whomever comes in last is about to
lose all their money in one shot.]
[Blue Team's challenge.]
- We're going to sing, 'In the bus'.
- This is the best song for this.
Let's not waste our energy
and wait for the song to start.
[Blue Team confident of their
singing skills.]
There's the beat.
[Dancing spirit starting to seep out.]
[Trying to lure Shin Yang into
join in on his dancing?]
[Shin Yang joining in on their dancing.]
[Baby Team falling in sync
with their dancing.]
[Not strong enough?]
[Big-nosed Brother singing
through his stomach.]
[Breathing becoming impossible.]
[Ji Hyo is the only one
not missing a beat.]
[What are you doing?]
Suk Jin really isn't doing a thing.
[46 points.]
Suk Jin, what are you doing?
Seriously!
Suk Jin contributed six of those points.
Our team got here first.
[The food they ordered!]
The food's already here?
[Being welcomed with a
round of applause.]
Enjoy! Enjoy your lunch!
Everyone, enjoy your lunch!
Look at Gwan Yeol...
He looks happier than
he did at his own wedding.
[Can't hear you.]
[A feast fit for a king.]
- We've got the total for the lunch bill.
- How much is it?
The total amount for all of you,
and the staff members is...
The total amount is...
930,000 won.
[A total of 930,000 won!]
[The loser team is about to
go bankrupt...]
[All we have to do is eat...]
Maybe we need to thinking of something else.
I don't think we have enough money.
[Full of worries.]
- The Green Team will now take the challenge!
- Challenge!
Fighting!
[Their song of choice is 'Let's get away'.]
I'm not completely down yet!
[Whatever...
They're solely focused on their food.]
[Singing upside down!]
[His blood is flowing more and more...]
[Not even budging.]
[Exhaustion hits.]
[Showing off his extreme flexibility.]
[Even his voice is loud and clear.]
[Ro-Ro changing his machine.]
He's not pulling it taut enough!
[Perfect size for me.]
- This is simple.
- It's because you're so short!
[Screaming at the top of his lungs.]
[This one is on the verge of
his deathbed.]
[End of the song.]
Can you pull this up?
Please pull this up.
[Too bad... but a fail, nonetheless.]
[Shin Yang having shown off
how flexible he could be.]
Can you stretch down completely
this way?
Why are you asking me to do
such weird things?
- I was just asking.
- You really surprised me with that.
- Can you show us?
- I doubt I can do it.
- Just in case, can you show us?
- He says he can't do it.
Why do you keep asking him to do it
when he says he can't do it!
- Shin Yang says he can't do it!
- I'm trying to weed him out!
- Why aren't you working harder?
- You saw him pull up the weight!
He was just about to do it!
Then why don't you give it a try?
No thanks to you,
we all have to do it now!
This is a good thing!
We can see what his downfalls are!
What about the two losing teams
give the winning team 10,000 each?
- Should we do it?
- Don't do it. He used to do gymnastics.
- What?
- He used to do gymnastics!
Shin Yang used to be in gymnastics?
Why didn't you tell us that earlier?
- Why didn't you tell us!
- Does he have to tell you everything?
In that case...
[With 10,000 on the line, each team
chooses one person to do the splits.]
We have no one else on our team
other than Ji Hyo.
- Both of us are too stiff.
- Let's do this quickly.
- I think someone may need to hold her.
- Should we hold your hands?
[A desperate cry to win 10,000.]
[Giving it her best shot while
screaming out 10,000 won.]
This was our best shot.
Ji Hyo, you did good.
You're more flexible than I thought.
- You have to hold on to me.
- 10,000 won is hanging on this.
[Amazing flexibility!]
- What in the world was that?
- Why did you keep quiet about that?
Her hand was shaking so bad
while she was doing that.
[This is all... power of 10,000 won?]
- Pull your pants down... pull them down.
- Why?
You have to pull your pants down
so that you can get down really low.
You have to pull your pants
down, Shin Yang.
You know hip-hop style, don't you?
- You have to pull them down this much.
- Why are you following them and doing that?
[Doing everything that he's
ordered to do.]
[10,000 won is riding on this bet...]
Look at Gwan Yeol eating while
he watches the show we're putting on.
Park Shin Yang, fighting!
He touching the ground!
He's down all the way and touching!
[Wow! He really is touching the ground!]
Shin Yang, wait... are you okay?
Are you okay?
You really are something else.
[Green Team wins 20,000 won!]
What the heck is this?
It's all Suk Jin's fault.
Pay up first.
- We'll give it to you later.
- We'll give it to you in a little bit.
- Give it to us now.
- Hey!
We want to get paid while
the cameras are rolling.
- Later! Let's do it later!
- No, give it to us now.
- Just do it later!
- Come on, give it to us now.
- Give me my money. My money!
- Hey!
[Screams erupting without even
realizing it herself.]
[Was my scream too loud?]
- You did good! Okay, it's back on.
- Here's your money!
- Where's Red Team's money?
- Ji Won went to get it.
I have to give them the money? Now?
10,000 won! 10,000 won!
I'm coming!
- Give it to me! Give it to me!
- Be quiet!
Here!
[A lady with a boisterous scream.]
Remember when you had to beg your mom
to buy you something when you were little?
I felt like that's what I was seeing.
There's a sassy attractiveness
about that.
Are you giving out
any extra points for dancing?
If there are extra points for that...
we'll sing 'Run to you'.
We can dance a little.
I can't dance.
Let's see Ji Won's dance moves!
- Here it comes.
- Ji Won, you look cute.
[Huh? The song's starting even before
they can get into position?]
[Aren't you going to sing?]
You have to sing too!
[Chaotic dancing]
[They're going to sing together?]
[Is Giraffe going for his new year's
resolution in this situation?]
My foot!
[As a final move,
snapping the band in his face?]
[Giraffe and the Tiger's chaotic duet.]
[Once again... step!]
[Whenever the opportunity arises,
his betrayal DNA comes to life.]
[The Tiger's counterattack.]
[The Giraffe and the Tiger tossing
and turning in their scuffle.]
[Somehow remembering to dance
in the midst of their situation.]
[The song finally comes to an end...]
[To make matters worse, they
receive the worst score thus far.]
- 36 points.
- Sorry.
We're going to sing the song...
that made so many women's hearts flutter
from 'Lovers in Paris' a few years ago.
[The song, 'Is it okay to love you?']
We're going to sing,
'Is it okay to love you'.
That's too high for me.
Yes. He would like for you to
come down a couple octaves.
Park Shin Yang's 'Glass Box'...
No, not that...
Park Shin Yang's
'Is it okay to love you'.
'Is it okay to love you'
by Park Shin Yang.
[In truth, he's about
to start singing his own song.]
Shin Yang just realized that
there's 90,000 won on the line here.
- So that's why he's singing his own song.
- Come on, baby!
[Yes... that's the song!]
[The scene that made so many
women's hearts flutter.]
[The sweet and melodious,
'Is it okay to love you'.]
[The song has a different feel to it
depending on who's singing it.]
[Singing the song again for
the first time in 10 years.]
[The same gentle voice...]
- I'm just going to soak it in.
- Keep it down a bit.
I love listening to Shin Yang
singing it!
[Everyone just sitting back
to listen to the song.]
[Is it the children's turn?]
[The sweet song taking on a
different tone...]
[Is the record skipping?]
[The whole family breaking down
in laughter from the dissonance.]
[Just as touching as it was back then...]
[Singing just as sweetly today...]
Let's take a little break.
[The highlight was rapper Gary's remix?]
Park Shin Yang!
Shin Yang was awesome!
Park Shin Yang's 'Is it okay to love you'
sung by Park Shin Yang himself. 50 points.
We're going to take another try.
[Red Team's challenge.]
[Shaking like a leaf.]
[On the other hand,
these two are singing with ease.]
[Already at his limits?]
[The weights starting to go down
inch by inch.]
[Shouting it out loud.]
[The nose getting further and
further away.]
[Come on down.]
[Save a giraffe!]
[Comfortable?]
Wow... look at Jong Kook.
Move... move.
[Taking the equipment away from him?]
[Ji Won singing consistently
without missing a beat.]
[Did he finally find his resting spot?]
[Now that he feels like he can breathe,
he's even adding ad-libs?]
[Giraffe showing some serious talent
at being the backup singer.]
[Even adding an upside down dancing.]
[Red Team succeeds with
over 90 points!]
We won!
[Passes the mission in first place.]
[Big trouble.]
[An unbelievable amount of money is about to
be spent by one of the two remaining teams.]
[Each team to sing once more, and
whomever has the higher score wins!]
I think the most important thing is
to sing as close to the mike as possible.
I think you're right.
[The song they chose is, 'Tiger butterfly'.]
[The weights are just too much...]
[Blank Ji struggling in her position.]
[What...]
[Big-nosed Brother's voice
not heard even once during the song...]
- Suk Jin, what are you doing?
- Suk Jin...
[Still scores 72 points!]
[Time for Green Team's final attempt!]
The food's here!
- Thanks for lunch!
- Thank you I'm going to enjoy it!
That looks really good.
Suk Jin... are we done?
Fighting... fighting!
[Shin Yang channeling his discontent?]
My leg was bothering me.
- You're a little jokester.
- You are! You're a little jokester.
Fighting... fighting.
[The loser in this round has to
pay for the entire lunch bill!]
[Extreme nervousness.]
[Singing with all his might.]
[Each separately singing earnestly
with their own workout equipment.]
[They have to beat Blue Team's 72 points
for them to escape last place standing.]
[Blue Team wins with 72 points!]
[Green Team chosen to pay for
the lunch bill.]
The food doesn't look very appetizing to me.
[Crap!]
- It's 980,000.
- What? That's more than what we thought.
[A total of 986,000 won including
extra items added to the order.]
- Thanks, Dong Hoon.
- I had no idea you'd treat like this.
- Thanks for lunch!
- Thank you. I really enjoyed it.
[Including after meal dessert,
all of their bonus cash is now spent!]
I just want to go home.
[Green Team feeling empty after spending
all their bonus cash at lunch.]
[All they've got left is the 20,000 won
they earned with Shin Yang's splits.]
The money we earned with your splits...
Had I known, I would've asked for
more money for doing the splits.
No kidding.
Just to earn 20,000 won...
I ripped my legs apart.
[But had he not done that,
they'd be penniless right now.]
[Red Team: 840,000 won; Green Team: 20,000
won and the Blue Team: 990,000 won.]
[Bonus Race - Final location.
SBS' Headquarters in Mokdong.]
- This is where I won...
- We know! Stop bringing that up!
- It's been two years now, stop it.
- This is where I shoved him off...
This muscle man...
I shoved him aside and won.
Please take a mission card from
the table in front of you.
[You'll only survive if you find the chair
with the General Manager's logo on it...]
[and sit on the chair!]
[If you can't find the chair within
the allotted time, you're eliminated!]
[The team with the survivor
is the ultimate victor!]
There are six of those chairs
within this building right now.
[Must be seated in the chair with the logo
when the time's up to remain alive.]
The chairs that you must sit on
have the GM's sticker stuck to the back.
You must make sure to check that
the sticker is on the back of the chair.
And only those six people sitting in the chair
will survive to go on to the next round.
[In other words,
it's a musical chair game of sorts.]
Wouldn't that put the teams with a lady
in their group at a disadvantage?
I'm sorry to tell you this...
But even with the last game,
it's your girl partner who won it for you.
[A combination of competitiveness
and her fierce temper.]
- If you joke too carelessly...
- I know that too.
And Shin Yang is no joke either.
He asked me if I wanted a piece of chocolate,
and when I said yes, he gave me stones.
[Gives him chunks of stone
instead of chocolate!]
I don't know what's gotten into him,
and why keeps acting like that.
See how you feel when you have
only 20,000 won left in your pocket.
I'm not the one who took
all that money away from you.
[Protect your seat! First round,
30 minutes, six chairs!]
- This is going to get interesting.
- Let's go!
- Let's go this way.
- Suk Jin, I'm going to go that way.
[Running Man members feeling anxious
right from the get go!]
I'm going to go up to the 18th floor,
and work my way down from there.
[No room for their personal
VJ's to get in...]
Those of us who's VJ can't make it in here
just won't be shown on TV!
There's nothing we can do.
It's cut and dry!
[In the end,
the elevator gets on its way!]
Where's Gwan Yeol? Gwan Yeol!
There you are!
I'm going to get off on the sixth floor.
- Not a single one of our Team's VJ is here.
- But you can use the CCTV.
You're going to be seen on the CCTV.
You're where?
[Red Team's Ji Won searching
through the sixth floor!]
[Of all these countless chairs,
where are the ones marked with the logo?]
[Ji Won already discovers one?]
I got the wrong one. This isn't it.
[Go Dong Wan.]
[PD Myuk.]
This isn't it. This is the PD's.
[Not with the GM's logo,
therefore, it's a fake!]
Just so that others will find this too.
It was false alarm.
[Shin Yang searched through 18th floor.]
[When are they going to get the time
to search through all these chairs?]
[16th floor - Variety show Department.
Running Man's office.]
[There's something on back of the chair!]
[Did the Giraffe discover one already?]
- Jong Kook!
- This one says PD Myuk...
[It's PD Myuk's sticker is stuck
to the back of the chair...]
[The chair that Kwang Soo found...]
It says Go Dong Wan on it.
[The chair that Kwang Soo found has
Go Dong Wan's sticker on it.]
Who are all these people?
Why aren't there a single picture of us
when this is the Running Man office?
[What is he looking for all of a sudden?]
[Finding a picture of himself in the calendar
and leaving it on his page...]
[Blank Ji walking into the radio studio.]
Go Dong Wan...
Seriously, Go Dong Wan...
Found it... I found it.
[Finally discovers a chair marked
with General Manager's logo!]
[Hiding the chair in fear of
someone else finding it.]
[That makes it look even more suspicious...]
[Yoo-ruce Willis searching
through the 13th floor.]
[He discovers another chair marked
with the correct logo on the back!]
[Blue Team's Ji Hyo and Jae Suk
are both off to a good start!]
[Since there's still a lot of time left,
hiding away the chair he's already found.]
[Only those found sitting in the chairs when
the timer goes off will go on to second round]
I can't believe how easily I found it.
I must be lucky... this is my lucky day.
I need to pretend I didn't find it,
and walk around like I'm still looking.
I can't believe my good fortune!
Ji Hyo!
Did you find one?
[Definitely our Ace... having come up all
the way up to the 13th floor with the chair.]
- So that's what it looks like.
- Ji Hyo, get up for a second.
- Do I look stupid to you?
- No, no...
- Kwang Soo...
- I just wanted to take a look.
[Slowly walking away...]
Jong Kook, are you just going to leave?
Hey... instead of fighting with her,
I'd rather just go look for another one.
- Hurry up and come.
- Why are you just leaving?
Come on. Look for another one.
[If he goes in there, he's going
to find my chair that I hid away!]
- Where are these chairs?
- Jae Suk, Ji Hyo found one.
[Jae Suk engaging them in a conversation
to stop them from entering the room.]
- Have you not found one yet?
- No.
- I can't find one anywhere.
- Which floor were you just on?
- Ji Hyo is on this floor.
- Then I should head down more.
That could've been bad.
[Returning to the auditorium to check
that his chair is still safely hidden away.]
It's still there.
It's still back there.
I keep circling around here as if I'm
protecting a safe or something.
[Too nervous to leave the chair,
but can't really stay either...]
[Will that chair remain in
Jae Suk's possession to the end?]
[On the other hand, Shin Yang of the
Green Team investigates 16th floor.]
I'm starting to feel a little anxious.
[So many chairs around,
but the General Manager logo...]
[Green Team's Shin Yang discovers
a chair with the right logo on the back!]
[Everyone's on the same page.
Anyone who finds one, hides it.]
[And Shin Yang goes the extra step...]
[Even makes a fake sign!]
[Park Shin Yang.]
Don't come into this room. Over.
[On the other hand, Big-nosed Brother
works hard searching through sixth floor.]
It's been awhile... it's really
been awhile since I've seen you.
Long time no see.
[A chair with PD Myuk's sticker
on the back.]
It says PD Myuk. I thought I found it...
[Oh? Did he discover a real
one this time?]
[Blue Team's Big-nosed Brother also
finds a General Manager marked chair!]
Its all over if someone else
comes in here.
I need to find a spot where
I can stay hidden.
[Since he has no confidence to win a fight,
he opts to take the chair and go into hiding.]
[Moving to the furthest corner of
the editing room on the sixth floor.]
[Using every ounce of energy he has
to hide the chair that he's found.]
[If only the time will just pass
in this state...]
[Come on time... pass by quickly!]
[Hyena Ha Ha having secretly
watched the whole scene unfold.]
Come in. This is Big-nose.
Did you find one?
I haven't found one yet.
You told me that you did.
It's because there's someone
lurking around me right now.
[Without hesitation as soon as
Big-nosed Brother steps away!]
[Big trouble!]
[Hyena Ha Ha steals the chair!]
- I found the chair!
- I know!
Since it's already come to this,
go and find yourself another chair.
Isn't this the rules of the game
around here?
[Of course you'll get caught after being
so obvious about hiding it...]
You were so obvious hovering
around here nonstop.
[Green Team's Ha Ha takes
over the chair!]
[Time is slowly ticking away.]
[Gary searching around on the
seventh floor.]
[Starting his search in the
corner closet room first.]
Found it... I found it.
[Wow! Gary discovers a chair with
the marker!]
Okay, I'm just going to stay in here.
[Seems as though he's planning on
sticking it out with the door locked.]
[With this, every member of the
Green Team now has a chair in possession.]
Just in case, I'm going to lock the door.
[Who's that?]
[Gary opens the door!]
- No, I haven't found one.
- Yes, you did!
- Then why are you sitting down?
- I'm just taking a break from searching.
- You did find one!
- No, I didn't.
I haven't found one.
What are you doing?
- You did find one!
- What... I don't know what to do!
[Ji Won finally shows off her skills!]
Wait!
[With not much time left on the clock,
if he loses the chair, he'll be in trouble!]
- I told you, I don't have one!
- You're sitting on one!
I'm being attacked!
I'm being attacked my Uhm Ji Won!
[Each asking for help from their
team member.]
Eighth floor! Come to eighth floor!
Jong Kook!
- Jong Kook!
- Where do you think you're headed?
[Red Team aggressively starts
their attack!]
Wait!
[Ha Ha and Shin Yang not coming to his rescue
since they're already seated in their chairs.]
Hey! Hey!
I can't give you this chair!
Hey! I only have 20,000 won left!
I have nothing else to give!
You can't be doing this to me!
Give it back!
Hurry up and get out of here!
I think Kwang Soo is taking the chair
and running away from me. Isn't he?
That traitor, Giraffe.
[He'd do that and then some...]
You took the chair and ran, didn't you!
Ji Won...
- We have to find another chair.
- You take it. I was going to give it to you.
[Gary doesn't give up on the chair
and barges in after it!]
Let's sit together!
If this is what it comes down to,
let's sit together!
Let's die together then!
I can't just let it go!
I have nothing else left!
My underwear is about to fall off!
Fine! Take it all off!
I'm not doing a woman any favors today!
Ji Won, hurry!
Get the chair out of here!
Get on the elevator!
It's all over.
[Gary screaming to the end.]
If you don't want to lose your last
20,000 won, just stay quiet.
[Impala back on the search after having
his chair stolen by the Hyena.]
There's not much time left...
[Totally lucky! Big-nosed Brother
discovers another chair!]
Oh my God! This is a miracle.
I think I have a knack for finding things.
[If he can keep the chair for the next four
minutes, he'll go on to the next round.]
[Ah... what cruel fate...]
You found one?
[Anyone could see that he's found one
and is sitting on it to keep it.]
- Kwang Soo, I'm glad you're here.
- Hi, Jong Kook.
[Two members of the Red Team
are here!]
[Now having the chair taken away from
him is just a matter of time?]
- It's not that...
- Don't feel upset by this, okay?
- Don't get upset by it.
- Okay, okay...
[Big-nosed Brother about to
make a proposal.]
Let's put the chair in the middle and
we'll all make a run for it, okay?
Stop trying to stall time.
[Tiger and the Giraffe moving right
into their take-over mode.]
[As predicted, a simple task to carry out.]
[Attempting to separate
Suk Jin from the chair.]
Okay, okay...
I'll be cool and just give it to you.
- I'm serious.
- No, you're already cool enough.
[What a cool position to be still
attached to the chair.]
Okay, fine...
- Let me at least hear you say thanks.
- Thanks. Thanks so much.
Let me hear you say thanks.
Seriously... how many times has it been?
[Big-nosed Brother heading off
to find himself another chair.]
I'm going to intertwine my leg
through this chair.
[Tiger stakes his claim on the chair.]
I wonder if I'm too spread eagle?
I'm sorry...
I have no choice at the moment if
I don't want to have it taken away.
[There are two minutes
remaining on the clock.]
[It's almost time!
Time to find the chair to sit on...]
[Suk Jin having found his way all the way
here after having two chairs taken away.]
- Suk Jin...
- What's going on?
- Did you find a chair?
- I heard you had it taken away twice?
- I did have it taken away twice.
- What are you going to do?
Jong Kook... is on the eighth floor.
You don't think we could take him?
- Let's give it a try.
- I know that you're desperate...
- I have to try to survive.
- But...
Then I'll just have to find yours
to sit on it myself.
[Determined to find a chair even
if its own team member's chair?]
It's in there, isn't it? It is!
[As the first round is about to end,
Suk Jin doesn't care who the opponent is!]
- You had it hidden back here?
- Come on, this is...
How can you take your own team's chair?
[One minute left remaining.]
There's only a minute left remaining.
You're getting the weird glint in your eye!
Seriously...
Get off that chair!
- Seriously... what are you doing?
- Let me live, okay?
What are you doing?
Ji Hyo!
- Jae Suk, what's going on?
- Suk Jin has a weird glint in his eye.
Suk Jin...
He's got a scary glint in his eye!
[Suk Jin starting to get violent.]
Suk Jin, you can't be like this!
[One minute left remaining.
One minute left remaining.]
[Someone is headed his way!]
[Giraffe attacks Ha Ha
as soon as he sees him!]
No way in hell!
- There's no way in hell!
- Jong Kook! I'm on the seventh floor!
Seventh floor! Jong Kook!
Get off the chair! Let me sit in it!
[Blue Team - Internal struggles!]
- Suk Jin, seriously...
- Get down!
Jong Kook, where are you?
Jong Kook! Jong Kook!
[He came! The Tiger!]
[Came rolling in his chair to
save Kwang Soo!]
No way in hell! Hey! You thieves!
[But you stole the chair yourself...]
[Succeeds in separating Ha Ha
away from the chair!]
- There's no way! No way!
- Kwang Soo! Come on!
This is my chair!
[A total chaos! The time is over!]
[Time over - End of the first round.]
- End of the first round.
- It's over!
Yes! Kwang Soo is sitting in the chair!
[A very dramatic end to
the first round.]
[Shin Yang passes the first round
in comfort on the 16th floor.]
[Ji Hyo on the 13th floor and
Ji Won on the seventh floor also passes!]
The sticker on the chair!
Oh, there it is...
Dong Hoon, we're really sorry.
I didn't want to have to do that.
- I understand, Jong Kook.
- I'm sorry for having done that.
I stole that chair myself.
- Who did you steal it from?
- Suk Jin.
Do you know who I stole mine from?
Suk Jin.
Really?
- What the heck is this, Suk Jin?
- You could've stepped down from the chair.
- I miraculously found two of the six chairs.
- Why couldn't you have protected it?
It's unbelievable...
[In any case, three out of nine are out!]
[Six remaining survivors!
On to the second round!]
[Second round rules: 20 minutes on the clock!
And only three chairs to be found.]
[Only 50% chance of surviving
past the second round!]
[The location of the chairs are three of the
locations where the chairs were last at!]
Ah... the last place we were at?
- Jong Kook, then we...
- Shh...
There...
[Seventh floor where we
were just at...]
Shin Yang, you're not on our team...
[Was just trying to get some information...]
- I can understand that you're lonely...
- Sorry.
[The only remaining survivor
on the Green Team.]
[Second round starts now.]
[Everyone headed to the place
where they were at last!]
[Tiger and the Giraffe headed to the
seventh floor where they were just at!]
Jong Kook! Wait!
- There will at least be one chair there...
- Okay, go after Jae Suk!
Go after him! I want you to go after him!
No way... I can't handle him on my own.
Jong Kook! I can't handle him alone!
Just for there for now!
Kwang Soo!
Go after Jae Suk and radio me!
[Only one chair left in the spot
where they left the chairs!]
Go find Jae Suk and radio me
and tell me where he's at!
[Shin Yang arrives on the 16th floor where
he left the chair from the first round.]
[There it is! Shin Yang also finds a chair!]
I need to check and see what
the situation is like first.
If I see anyone that I want to
help out... then I'll help save them.
[What you doing?]
[Having decided to hide the chair for now
so that he doesn't have it taken away.]
Excuse me.
Is it okay for me to keep this in here?
[A staff member revealing
a hideout for the chair.]
Thank you.
[Even draping the chair with
his own clothes!]
Thank you so much.
You're a life saver!
[A perfect disguise.]
[Ji Won also heads to the back of the
seventh floor where she was last.]
It's not here.
[No longer in the spot!]
[Starting the search all over again
floor by floor!]
[It's got to be hard to have to start
the search over from the beginning...]
I have to start over!
[Huh? Isn't this 13th floor where
Jae Suk had his chair?]
Maybe not these chairs
since they can't be moved?
What's that chair over there?
[The chair that Jae Suk had sat on
during the first round!]
[Red Team's Ji Won
stakes her claim on the chair!]
Hide... go and hide somewhere.
Either hide behind the curtain...
Is there room back there?
[Ji Won hides behind the
stage curtains just like Jae Suk had.]
[She goes the extra step...]
[Carries it into the waiting room!]
[Extremely thorough Uhm Ji Won.]
[Green Team's Shin Yang is
heading her way!]
Go away! Don't come here... go!
[Coolly going away after a big laughter.]
He's really nice.
If he pushed his way in, I would've lost.
He really is gentle.
[Walking around with ease since he has
the chair he's hid away on the 16th floor.]
[Giraffe following Jae Suk around and
bothering him since the start of the round.]
Why don't we... why don't
we go to the ninth floor for now?
[Jae Suk finally arrives on the 13th floor.]
[Going around in circles to lose Kwang Soo.]
Jae Suk!
Why are you going around in circles?
You're making me dizzy.
[Blue Team's Ji Hyo also making her way over
not having found any of the chairs.]
[If the chair that Ji Hyo had
also disappeared...]
Then there's a high probability that the chair
Jae Suk had sat on is one of the chairs.
Where? Here?
- Why would it be here?
- I'm following Jae Suk around.
- Jae Suk wasn't here a little bit ago.
- No, I wasn't.
[Pesky Kwang Soo... now's the time!]
[Punishing Kwang Soo
and getting their retribution!]
All I've done is follow you around.
No! Not my shoes!
Jae Suk, don't take off my shoes!
Jae Suk! Let me keep some dignity!
[Just in case he still decides to follow,
he even takes the socks away from him!]
Jae Suk, come on... Jae Suk!
[Leaving the rest to Ji Hyo and
rushing off to where he was the last time.]
Don't take my clothes off!
Wait... what's wrong with you!
You're driving me nuts!
[It used to be up here... but it's gone?]
[Then could it be back here?]
Ji Won...
[Discovers Ji Won hiding in the corner!]
- Ji Won, listen... calm down.
- No!
[Scream!]
Yoo Jae Suk's here!
No, I'm the one who discovered you.
- I discovered Yoo Jae Suk...
- You're not the one who discovered me.
- Ji Hyo, Ji Hyo, Ji Hyo...
- Come where I was last at!
Hurry up and get here!
Okay, Jae Suk. Where are you?
What does she mean?
The place where we were last?
I have to get to my chair
and sit on it right now though...
There's no time!
I have to hurry!
[There's no time!
An extremely urgent situation!]
- Ji Hyo, hurry!
- I've got Yoo Jae Suk!
[What! Giraffe is the first to arrive here?]
[With revenge nailed deep
within his heart.]
- Ji Hyo!
- You stripped off my feet!
You took away my shoes and took my socks off!
Ji Hyo, hurry! Ji Hyo!
Ji Hyo!
[At a quick glance, it may come across
looking like a steamy love scene.]
[Blue Team's rescuer, Ace Ji Hyo arrives!]
Come help me! Or run away!
Ji Won, run!
[Ji Hyo needs to rush over and take
the chair away from Ji Won!]
Ji Hyo, hurry!
[One minute left remaining.
One minute left remaining.]
Kwang Soo... I've got to go.
Why would you take off my clothes?
Don't step on my foot!
Outbreak of total chaos.
[There's no time!
Just who will end up with the chair?]
Ji Won, I'm sorry!
No! I'm a guest!
Ji Won...
I'm going to kick you where it hurts!
- Ji Won!
- My foot is where it's going to hurt you!
[End of second round.
Ji Hyo takes the seat!]
[End of the 2nd round: Red Team's Jong Kook;
Green Team's Shin Yang; Blue Team's Ji Hyo.]
- It's over...
- Where are my socks and shoes?
Where's my jacket?
[Rather than worrying about winning,
maybe take care of the Giraffe first...]
Ji Hyo, you have to stay alive.
- Ji Hyo, you have to stay alive.
- Who else is still alive?
I'm sure Jong Kook's still alive.
[Ace Ji Hyo having survived with
her fierce competitive streak.]
Why is Ji Hyo so strong?
I really didn't use any strength
in case you'd get hurt.
That was you not using any strength?
Seriously...
Stop trying to act like you're nice!
- I'm sorry, Ji Won.
- I've got you all figured out.
[Anyways, one survivor per team!
Time to go into the last round!]
Kwang Soo!
Jae Suk and Kwang Soo...
and Ji Won.
- Shin Yang is still alive!
- I knew it would end up like this.
- Ji Hyo's still alive?
- Yeah, Ji Hyo's still alive.
- I'm sorry.
- I think Jong Kook is going to win this.
Ji Won, seriously... I think
she's the fiercest guest we've had.
- My mental state right now...
- Why? Did she hurt you?
No, not hurt.
But she really caught me by surprise.
'I'm a guest... I'm a guest!'
['I'm a guest... I'm a guest!']
'If you keep this up, I'm
going to kick you where it hurts!'
'My foot is right by that area right now!'
'It's right in front of my foot!
I'm going to kick it! I'm kicking it!'
[Boisterous lady quieting down
now that she's in jail.]
[Now the final third round.]
[Out of the three chairs that were on
the 16th, 13th and the seventh floor...]
[Now there's only one single chair
left remaining!]
[Round three! Only 10 minutes on the clock!
Take over the last remaining chair!]
This is like Russian Roulette.
[We will now start our third
and final round.]
Go!
[Where they head now could be the
deciding factor on who wins the race!]
[Jong Kook and Ji Hyo rushed
to head in the same direction!]
[The 13th floor?]
[The last General Manager chair is here!]
[Red Team's Jong Kook's
gut instinct pays off!]
This is nerve wrecking.
[Ace Ji Hyo is
unfortunately one step too late.]
It really was on this floor.
This is unbelievable.
My gut instincts... it really is...
[What is he doing?]
[Mr. Capable molds his body to the chair!]
- Earlier... Uhm Ji Won said something...
- What?
'I'm going to kick you where it hurts.'
How can you say such a thing? Hey...
[Right here, a few minutes ago...]
[Switching his direction from fear
of getting hurt.]
[Shin Yang heads down after having
checked that it's not on the 16th floor.]
[There it is...]
- Why don't you have a seat...
- Was this your chair?
- This one?
- Yes, Shin Yang...
- Why don't you have a seat?
- Is it okay to sit like that?
Is it okay... to have your legs
intertwined through the chair like that?
- Excuse me?
- Huh?
Since there's still a lot of time left,
why don't we talk about it first?
- Let's talk about this...
- I'm checking to see how I can pull you out.
Why are you trying to do that?
- I can beat you with one move.
- What?
- I can do it in one shot.
- Me?
- How are you going to do that?
- I can do it within five seconds.
[Take Mr. Capable down within
five seconds?]
You're going to pull me off this chair?
No. I'm saying I'm going to
sit on it with you.
[I will share the seat with you!]
Me too! Me too!
Me too! Include me!
[Taking it from you may be too difficult...]
Jong Kook is trying to win by
dragging the time right now.
No, Shin Yang. If you've seen me
on the show, you'd know...
You won't be able to do it. Shin Yang...
Shin Yang! Let's talk this out.
Shin Yang!
[The last three survivors vying
for the final victory.]
[If he doesn't abdicate his seat within
10 seconds, the attack will commence!]
One... two... three...
[Just how to respond to the comment...
so unsure of what to do...]
Six...
[Time left on the clock...
One minute and 13 seconds.]
Ten!
[No more warning!]
[Mr. Capable in extreme danger!]
Shin Yang!
No, Shin Yang! Shin Yang!
Shin Yang! No!
I want to win!
It's been too long since I've won!
[Park Shin Yang shows the strength
that he's kept hidden!]
[Ji Hyo resorts to tickling his foot!]
I'm okay! I'm okay...
I don't feel anything.
[Extreme skills? Enduring
the tickling through a mantra?]
This isn't going to work.
Sorry about this!
- Sorry! I'm going in!
- Hurry up and sit down!
I'm going in!
[Shin Yang shoving his way in!]
[Two people in the chair!
How will it turn out?]
[Who will be the final victor to sit in
the chair to keep their bonus cash?]
[Time over!]
[How will this be judged?]
[An extremely difficult situation to judge.]
You're not sitting properly.
- I protected the chair to the end.
- No, his butt is sitting on it.
[Carefully inspecting to see if his butt
is touching the bottom of the seat.]
- His butt is not on the chair.
- We'd have to get up to see.
We're going to discuss this
before we rule the judging.
[Final ruling to be announced in a bit.]
[Judging aside, they'd need to get up...]
- I need some help...
- Wait... that really tickles.
[With both of them so stuck on the chair,
separating them is proving difficult.]
[Barely manages to get
Shin Yang separated.]
My body right now...
please don't touch me.
[Impossible to help Mr. Capable
in his state.]
- You want me to lift this up?
- I'm too embarrassed right now!
[First real photo opportunity of 2013.]
[Just what will the final judgment be?]
- I'm really curious.
- Here they come.
I think it's going to be Jong Kook.
- Look at Jong Kook struggling.
- I can't walk without the support.
[Everyone arriving looking worse
for wear.]
They decision hasn't been made yet.
Decision will be made from the footage.
- Really?
The results from having
watched the footage...
This is a first in the history
of Running Man.
It's a mutual win by the Red Team
and the Green Team.
What? We both won?
This is the first time we've
had this situation.
[Both sitting on the chair!
A definite win for both teams!]
[A first in history of Running Man!
Two teams share a win!]
With it being a mutual win...
Decide who will go first to see whether
your bonus will be doubled or tripled...
- Why don't you go first?
- They're not going to win much.
At most, they'll win 60,000 won.
How much did you guys have left?
We have a lot left.
We have 840,000 won left.
[Red Team's current leftover is
840,000 won.]
- Come over here...
- They can win up to 252,000,000 won.
[Green Team is given the chance to
maximize their money first.]
You just need to open up the flap.
Shin Yang?
One, two, three!
[Depending on the ball they pick,
their amount could change drastically!]
Congratulations on your 20,000 won.
[What? Multiplied by one?]
[Green Team- 20,000 won x 1= 20,000 won.]
- Multiplied by...
- It's the money he earned from the splits?
At least you got something, right?
[It's the Red Team's chance to
increase their bonus cash amount!]
Pull it up.
[She picks one!]
[Red Team's 840,000 won... will they...]
I wonder if there's a times zero?
The number...
that the Red Team picked is...
Please... please!
[Out of the three options,
which one did they get?]
This is disappointing.
- Is it one?
- Three.
[840,000 won x 3=252,000,000 won.]
[Blue Team succeeds in tripling
their bonus cash!]
- Wow! Seriously!
- Wow...
It's for real.
- And for us... 20,000 won.
- I can't believe this.
- It's still something.
- Shin Yang earned that money.
[The 20,000 won he earned by doing
the splits during the karaoke mission.]
He's giving snack money to the kids.
How much?
How much did you guys get?
- 252,000,000 won.
Shall we go for 500,000,000 won...
[The splits?]
[The prize money was donated to the
Indonesia Relief Fund by the Blue Team.]
Subtitles by DramaFever
[The heat from last year's summer...]
[2012 Running Man Olympics' victory
went to the ambitious Idol team.]
[And today...]
[This is the day they've been waiting for.
Running Man's desire for revenge.]
[But their opponents have
only gotten stronger!]
[Idol Team has been
upgraded in their skill level!]
[The real competition starts now!
Running Man 2013 Winter Olympics!]
[Everyone on the attack!
Everyone on their defense!]
[The return of the terrifying
Bell Race!]
[A scorching hot race
in the middle of winter!]
Come here!
[Next Week,
2013 Running Man Winter Olympics!]