[You are a suspect.]
[If you seek freedom,
then you must escape.]
[But... there can only be one person who
can take possession of the key to freedom.]
I don't think this is going to work.
Subtitles by DramaFever
['P' Green Building in Song-Do.]
[What is this place?]
[And the man being dragged into this place...]
What is this?
[Totally confused about the situation.
Locked behind bars as soon as he arrives.]
- Suspect, Yoo Jae Suk.
- What?
- What do you mean, a suspect?
Crime- Excessive dancing.
[Crime- Excessive dancing.
Crime of dancing whenever the music plays.]
- Crime of excessive dancing?
- Suspect Yoo Jae Suk.
You are guilty of dancing excessively
whenever the music starts playing.
You are suspected of dancing too
excessively at your advanced age.
Thus, you are being detained under
the suspicion of dancing too excessively.
I only dance because you guys keep
playing the music for me.
It's not like I dance when I shouldn't be.
How can this be a crime?
This is absolutely ridiculous.
Let me out of here.
I haven't committed any crimes.
- You're the ones who keep playing music.
- What is this?
- How can you call what I do a crime?
- Isn't this for criminals?
They told me that I committed the
crime of dancing too excessively.
- They're right about your crime.
- How can that be a crime?
- You really need to stop with the dancing.
- Listen to you.
[What is the crime Big-nose is guilty of?]
[Crime of being needy-
Crime of being too high maintenance.]
- What crime am I guilty of?
- You have to pay for your crimes.
- Don't say something so ridiculous.
- You really need to pay for your crimes.
You and your dancing...
Hey, Someone else is coming.
[The third criminal is now
about to enter the room.]
What he is guilty of?
[Crime of addiction to coaching.
Needing to coach everyone on everything.]
You try to teach baseball to a baseball player
and soccer to a soccer player.
[Coach Kkuk teaching baseball to Ryu Hyun Jin
and Soccer to Park Ji Sung.]
Your crime is fitting.
[This scenario looks a little too natural...]
- What's Gary's crime?
- Is it the crime of being too ugly?
[What crime is Mr. Gary guilty of?]
[Nine degrees of love crime-
Wanting to love despite his looks.]
- Why are we being locked up in jail?
- What crime are you guilty of?
[Crime of being a smart ass-
Causing chaos with his smart assed mouth.]
Ha Ha, your crime is always letting your
smart ass mouth run off
and causing all sorts of chaos
to the rest of your members.
- Yeah, he really needs to pay for that.
- That is a very fitting crime for you.
Fine, then I'll take it down a notch.
- I'll be better.
- This guy here says he's in charge in here.
- I'll pledge my allegiance to you then.
- Pledge!
- Seriously.
- Do it! Lift up your hand and do it!
- I'm not doing it!
- Salute me!
What is this?
- Are we going to be locked up with a woman?
- Why is she in here with us?
Suspect, Song Ji Hyo.
Crime of beauty.
- There's no such thing as a crime of beauty!
- That's a bunch of crock!
That certainly is a crime
since she has already stolen my heart.
I think Lee Kwang Soo will be guilty
of plenty of crimes.
Let go!
I haven't committed any crimes.
- You just wait until you hear your crimes.
- Suspect, Lee Kwang Soo.
- Suspect Lee Kwang Soo.
- Yes?
Crime of excessive
overreaction to a situation.
[Crime of excessive
overreaction to a situation.]
Lee Kwang Soo, you are guilty of excessively
overreacting to any and all situations.
Also: crime of betrayal, crime of misfortune,
crime of being cowardly...
He's guilty of many different crimes.
Under the false disguise of being
the Prince of Asia...
we've received intel that you've tried
to flee at every chance that you get.
Thus, you are being detained
as a suspect.
He needs to be forbidden
from leaving the country.
- Why can't I leave the country?
- He really is guilty of those crimes.
- That's pretty fitting of his crimes.
- I'm your new cellmate. Take good care of me.
Okay.
Why have you put us behind
bars like this?
What have we done so wrong
to deserve this?
You are all being detained in here
under suspicion
of the previously mentioned
individual crimes.
And we've just received word that more
suspects have arrived.
There are others?
- Kwang Soo.
- Yes?
- Train the newbies right.
- I understand.
- I'll make sure to train them right.
- Come here.
Yes, Jae Suk.
What do you mean, crush them?
Who am I supposed to crush?
- Let's put some fear into them.
- Okay, let's scare them a little.
Let's see who they are.
[Just who could be the other suspects?]
I feel bad for these newbies.
[What?
Everyone's up on their feet?]
[Detective...]
[Suspect, Park Hee Soon.]
[Actor, Park Hee Soon- Enthralls the audience
with his charismatic performance.]
Isn't he a detective?
[He is today's eighth suspect.]
- Don't you normally play a detective?
- Are you a detective, or a suspect?
- Park Hee Soon.
- He still looks so cool.
Your crime is being too charismatic.
Why are you acting like that when
you're here like the rest of us?
You're under arrest too then?
Even though you do still look very cool,
you're still here for being a suspect.
What is it?
Is someone else here?
- What is it?
- Is someone else here?
Who is it?
[Just then...]
[Another suspect?]
[He's finally here!
Gong Yoo!]
[Real live thrilling action!
Transformed into a tough manly man!]
[A real lady killer!]
- Is that Gong Yoo?
- Are you serious?
- Wow!
- It's really Gong Yoo!
Gong Yoo!
He really is a friend of mine!
- What are you talking about?
- Get away from him.
[Smart ass Ha Ha being denied of his claims
of being friends with Gong Yoo.]
- I'm being serious.
- How is he a real friend of yours?
I'm telling you, he is my friend.
- Being close in age doesn't make you friends.
- Stop acting like you know him.
- Get away from him.
- I'm serious! Tell them, Gong Yoo!
[Begging Gong Yoo to admit
that they're friends.]
Suspect Gong Yoo.
[Suspect Gong Yoo-
What crime is he guilty of?]
- Crime of arson?
- What? Crime of arson?
For setting the hearts of women
ages 10 to 50 on fire.
That is the crime
you are guilty of committing.
Every single one of us has set
at least one woman's heart on fire.
- I'm sorry.
- No, what would you be sorry for?
- Let's take a look here.
- Sure.
I've set quite a few fires myself
back in my day.
Yes, he really did set some fires.
[On fire? Seriously?]
On fire?
You?
He lit up some fire pits in neighboring towns
so that the elderly wouldn't get cold.
That's the fire we meant.
He's an actor,
and he was born in '79.
- He was born in the same year as Ha Ha?
- Maybe you two really are friends.
- I'm serious.
- Crime of arson.
Being born in the same year
doesn't mean anything.
You were just born the same year, don't go
around telling people that you're friends.
Remember when you told us that
you're friends with Lee Jung Jae?
And you looked so awkward
sitting next to him.
- What are you talking about?
- You're so right!
- I saw that too.
- He doesn't know what he's saying.
- Remember when we all went out to eat?
- What are you talking about?
When he said, 'Good to see you, Jae Suk',
you bent 90 degrees and bowed to him.
[Same greeting but in a different pose.]
- We saw you bowing to him.
- You bowed in middle of dinner.
What are you guys talking about?
Jung Jae and I are really close.
What do you mean, you two are close?
You two aren't the least bit close.
- Gong Yoo and I used to be very close.
- Stop being so absurd.
- He and I used to get drinks together.
- Then why don't we ask him?
Ask him.
Were you two really close?
- I don't really remember.
- Wait!
- How dare you try to fool us?
- You really have grown, Gong Yoo.
I've always been bigger than you.
[What a sense of humor.]
[A difference of 15cm...
A huge difference in their height.]
[Seeing the jokes flowing back and forth,
they really must be friends.]
You keep him away, Jong Kook.
You keep him away.
To the new suspects who
have just joined us...
We have prepared outfits befitting of your
new status in the dressing room.
- Please change into your new outfits.
- You two are dressed way too nicely.
You two are dressed too nicely.
And make sure to act like
the newcomers that you are.
Know the order of seniority in here.
- Let's let them change first.
- They need to change their clothes first.
[A matching uniform that even these two
actors can't escape wearing.]
- Do we really just change right here?
- Yes.
All nine of you are in here at the moment
because you're guilty of your own crimes.
All of you, who are suspected of
being guilty of your own crimes...
we will now give you one last chance to
rid yourself of your accusations.
- The crimes that you are accused of...
- He's getting into his theatrical mode.
You will be able to escape being framed
for your accusations.
In order to win your freedom,
you will have to pass several missions first.
[Must pass several missions for a chance
to escape their accusations.]
In order to pass your missions...
you're going to need to
escape from here first.
Put your heads together to come up
with a way to escape.
The secret to your escape is
within this room.
- A secret?
- I bet it's a number. Let's find it.
[Find the secret code to the lock!]
- Seven!
- Number seven is circled.
[There are so many numbers everywhere...]
Could it be 8191?
- Let's all think about this.
- We need to put our heads together.
I don't think this is something that's
going to be all that simple.
- Everyone come and put your heads together.
- Everyone gather around.
[Come put your heads together.
The answer is near.]
Come and let's put our heads together.
We'll figure out the answer.
- Okay, that's good.
- What are you doing, Hee Soon?
[Even Hee Soon steps forward to put
his head together with the group.]
- What could it be?
- What is it?
What could it be?
What's the answer?
[Just... where... is the secret code?]
We're going to have to figure this out.
[Their escape route to the outside world
is proving to be difficult to open.]
- There are seven blankets in here.
- Which movie are you currently working on?
- 'The Suspect'.
- The Suspect?
Then could the number be on a person?
On one of the suspects?
[Could the hint be on a person?]
- You think it's on our clothes?
- How could it be on our clothes?
[The suspects are starting to
check out each other's clothing.]
It can't be under our name tags, right?
[Wait...]
[Now that I think about it...]
Don't you think it's weird that only the two
of them were asked to change in here?
[Now that he's saying that...]
- Take a look at their clothes.
- Look by the neck and other areas.
[Is that why Gong Yoo and Hee Soon were
asked to change in the room?]
Can you take your clothes off
for a minute?
- No, we're serious.
- I have a feeling it's on your clothes.
I think the number is on their clothes.
The number is right here!
- On the back of this tab!
- On Gong Yoo's jacket!
[A two digit number behind the tab!]
- I think it's these two numbers.
- This is it.
- Don't you think this is it?
- You really know your stuff.
- See? This is it.
- Try 0628.
- I knew there was something.
- The lock opened up!
[Wow! The lock opened!]
[The secret code was 06-28.
Indicated on the clothes of the suspects.]
Come on, cheer with us!
[However... they were all still clues
as to what lies ahead of them.]
[The truth of a bloody battle that
awaited them right in this building.]
[They're all still suspects- Can only
move when instructed by the guards.]
I've only seen this on TV.
We will tell you about your
rules for the day.
- Today's rules?
- Okay.
Your race for the day is...
The Suspect Target Race.
[The Suspect Target Race.]
[With the passing of each mission...]
[They can earn themselves
a suspect target ballot.]
[Can vote to target the suspect they want to
oust as many times as ballots they have.]
[Rule- Can only eliminate the name tag of
the suspect whose name has been drawn.]
[Only one person can remain to
earn their freedom at the end.]
[Unable to resist the temptation,
Yoo Hyuk plays a prank on Kwang Soo.]
You guys always write down my name
whenever we do something like this.
- You have us, so no need to worry.
- Seriously, don't do it.
What is this?
Why do they want us to vote?
[Name tag elimination and voting...
Just what fate awaits them?]
What happens if we get a lot of votes?
I'm not sure what's going on.
Since the three of us are a team...
We're not going to write down each other's
names just because we get a ballot, are we?
- Why are you even saying that?
- I know that this is unnecessary to say...
The fact that you even brought that up means
you're going to write down one of our names.
No, I'm not.
[What? You're not?
'Gong Yoo.']
[You're not going to?
'Yoo Jae Suk.']
[Suspect Target Race-
Arriving at their first mission location.]
[Order message received.]
This is an explosive message.
This message will self-destruct if you
don't read it within 15 seconds.
[Suspects- we want to see your action
on the water.]
[Dump your opposing team members into
the water in a one-on-one match.]
[The team that dumps all members of
an opposing team gets two ballots.]
[Team that comes in at second place
gets one ballot.]
- [Last place doesn't get any ballots.]
- Second place team gets two ballots.
- We have to make sure to get two ballots.
- The message already self-destructed.
First team to arrive goes to final round.
[First team to change and arrive on scene
moves on to the final round.]
First team to arrive has the advantage.
Let's hurry up and go, Suk Jin.
First team to arrive goes to
the final round.
[First team to arrive by the 'R' flag
automatically goes to the final round.]
- Hurry up, Suk Jin!
- Hurry up and take off your pants!
Hurry, Hee Soon!
[Gong Yoo is waiting for his pants
from his coordinator.]
Hurry up and take off your pants!
There's no time!
Suk Jin!
- Ji Suk Jin!
- Coming!
You want us to grab this?
The Blue Team will go on to
the final round.
[Blue Team will move on to the final round.]
Awesome.
- You're very quick.
- To the final round!
[And one very slow person...]
Gong Yoo!
This is all your fault!
The Blue Team got moved up
to the final round!
I told you to just take your pants off
right where you were standing!
Seriously, Gong Yoo.
We could've been moved up to the final round
had you been a little quicker.
I was trying to be quick when I
went into the dressing room
but there weren't any cameras in there.
Did you expect them to be filming you when
you're stripping naked to change your clothes?
- Well, I just thought...
- He's so naive!
[Sweet and naive Gong Yoo.]
This will be a one-on-one match,
and it'll be an all-kill.
If Gary beats his opponent, then he'll keep
on playing until he's defeated.
[First round-
Green Team vs. Red Team.]
Once you're on the bar, you
can't come down until you're defeated.
Ready.
[First players up-
Green Team's Suk Jin vs. Red Team's Jae Suk.]
- Show him, Suk Jin!
- Show him what?
[Jae Suk easily lifted himself up on
the bar like a roasted chicken.]
[Slowly inching himself over above
Big-nose's head.]
What are you doing, Suk Jin?
I'm playing the game!
Grab Jae Suk!
[You want me to grab Jae Suk?]
[Oh?]
[Oh My God!]
No!
[A major catastrophe.]
[Everyone bursts out in a fit of laughter.]
Put my pants back on!
- Put my pants back on!
- I don't know what to do!
[The pants are in Big-nose's hands.]
[Kwang Soo's trying to put
a towel around him?]
[Second huge catastrophe.]
[It could've been big trouble...]
[Fell in the water himself while
attempting to protect Jae Suk's modesty.]
What is going on here?
[No other choice but to
come down from the bar.]
You almost pulled down my underwear!
- What are you doing?
- Yoo Jae Suk is out.
What do you mean, I'm out?
I had my pants taken off!
[Crime of corrupting the public is added
to his other crime of excessive dancing.]
What were you thinking?
- I was just trying to help.
- Tie your pants on tight around your waist.
- Make sure you watch your pants.
- Look at Gong Yoo tightening up his pants.
[Gong Yoo is quietly tightening up the
string around his waistline.]
[Hee Soon is suddenly quiet, and seems
busy doing something with his hands.]
- Seriously...
- We won that round.
- We won, we won!
- Their humiliation is our win.
Their humiliation is our win.
I'm really curious to see if Gong Yoo
can beat Ji Hyo or not.
[Will Gong Yoo, the gentleman,
be able to beat Blank Ji?]
Wait, I'm not so sure about this.
Is it really okay for me to beat her?
- Of course, show us your skills.
- Of course.
Why are you saying something so weak?
You can't look at Ji Hyo
like any other woman.
[His opponent is our Ace,
who's better at games more than most men...]
Grab him.
- What do I do here?
- Just dunk her, Gong Yoo!
Drop her in the water!
[Gong Yoo makes his way forward for now...]
- I'm so sorry, so sorry.
- What do you have to be sorry about?
[Gentleman Gong Yoo gently wrapping
his legs around Blank Ji.]
- Drop her in the water!
- You have no other choice!
[Blank Ji is starting to lose
strength in her arms.]
[Blank Ji takes a dive.]
You're doing great!
[Next up is Gary,
the last player on the Green Team.]
[If Gary falls in the water,
then the Red Team wins this round.]
Gary.
[A sudden change?]
[Wow! Binds Gary within moments!]
[Brings himself up and over
Random Mr. Capable in the blink of an eye!]
[A simultaneous dive- His plan succeeds!]
Gong Yoo!
[An astounding play that showed off
his mannerism and strength all at once!]
You're no joke, Gong Yoo!
Great job!
Red Team wins.
[Red Team wins.]
[Off to the final round-
Blue Team vs. Red Team.]
- Do you want to go first?
- Do you really need to do all that?
[Coach Kkuk preparing for his play.]
[First players up-
Blue Team's Hee Soon vs. Red Team's Jae Suk.]
[Game start]
[First player up for the Blue Team is,
Charismatic Hee Soon.]
[Something about him is giving off
the 'Big-nose' vibe...]
[Charismatic Hee Soon's flustered footwork.]
[Look at this guy.]
[Where are you going?]
You're disqualified if you
get off the bar.
- Go forward a bit.
- I can't.
I can't.
- You'll be more comfortable if you go up.
- Wrap your legs up around it.
[Hanging will make it easier to last longer.]
Lift up your legs.
Is it that you can't wrap your
legs around it?
What are you doing?
Are you okay?
[Self-submersion after a shouting cry.]
What are you doing?
[Charismatic Hee Soon's
weak physical strength.]
Wow, this is really slippery.
[Blue Team's second player- Ha Ha.]
This is really slippery.
This is bad.
You can wipe it down with the towel.
[The game is momentarily paused
due to the slippery bar.]
What are you doing, Hee Soon?
Are you trying to tickle the bar
or something?
- What are you doing with that towel?
- Don't you even know how to do it?
[An actor who belies his image
with his bumbling actions.]
- He's really adorable.
- Come on, Hee Soon.
Just stop it!
Stop it.
Hee Soon just told us to do it quietly.
As if he's shooing everyone away.
[Red Team's Jae Suk vs. Blue Team's Ha Ha.
Time to start their game.]
Jong Kook's going to have to
do all the work.
[A dropkick?]
[A high kick with all the rage
that's been building up for years.]
[An excited crowd of onlookers.]
One more time.
Wrap your legs around him.
[There they go!]
[Ultimately caught...]
[Let's both you and I die together!]
[Ha Ha and Jae Suk fall in simultaneously.]
[Yoo Hyuk eliminated
two of his opponents.]
Here, grab onto my hand.
Why aren't you saving me first?
Okay, the remaining players are,
Kim Jong Kook, Lee Kwang Soo, and Gong Yoo.
I had no idea that Hee Soon
would be this bad.
Hee Soon, are you okay?
Are you okay?
[Just go.]
Why can't you even say anything?
[Dropping to the base of the bar
without a word.]
How can I step on him?
Come here, Ha Ha.
- Let's do it together.
- Hee Soon, he says he can't step on you.
- I can't step on you, Hee Soon.
- Let me do this at least!
Let me do this at least!
[Hee Soon's voice can finally be heard.]
He wants to be able to do
that at least.
[Weak older brother wants to be able
to help his teammates in some way.]
- He wants to be able to do that at least.
- Hee Soon, you're so cool.
[Red Team's Kwang Soo getting ready
to climb up on the bar.]
[His plan is to get up on the bar
by kicking himself off.]
Okay, push me off.
One, two, three.
[What the...]
[Kwang Soo lost
after all that commotion...]
- What is he doing?
- Kwang Soo is disqualified.
What are you doing?
[Kkuk is now able to compete against Gong Yoo
without having done anything.]
- Gong Yoo.
- Jong Kook has the advantage.
Oh my goodness.
[Crawling across the bar?]
[Tiger is at an advantageous position.]
[Darn...]
You're going to get flipped around
if you keep that up, Jong Kook.
[Tiger in danger!]
[The time is now!]
[A flustered Tiger!]
[Gong Yoo's onslaught.]
[It's on!
Tiger vs. Gong Yoo!]
We have to win!
No, Jong Kook!
[The two men are still hanging on
with their impressive strength!]
Attack Jong Kook's legs.
You can do it, Gong Yoo!
[Gong Yoo, gritting down on his teeth.]
Jong Kook lost his advantage
when he got flipped around on the bar.
No, Jong Kook!
You're our last hope!
Hee Soon was never our hope!
[Just who will win this battle?]
Jong Kook is about to fall off!
[Mr. Capable is in danger!]
[But he's still able to withstand this attack
with tremendous amount of strength!]
[Mr. Capable sticks his head in
between Gong Yoo's legs!]
[Supports himself with his head...]
[And tries to unwrap Gong Yoo's legs
from around the bar!]
[And one last arm...]
[Mr. Capable ultimately wins!]
[The onlookers are left speechless.]
[No different than an iron wall of strength-
His name is, Coach Kkuk.]
We lost because of you!
[If Kwang Soo had depleted Mr. Capable
of even the smallest bit of energy...]
Wow, Kim Jong Kook.
The members of the Red Team each get one
ballot for having come in at second place.
Remember what we talked about earlier.
No writing each other's names down.
- Of course.
- That's a given, Jae Suk.
- We have to write down the strongest person.
- Of course.
We don't know what's going to happen,
but that's what we should do.
For example, there's no need whatsoever to
write down Hee Soon's name.
Hee Soon?
Don't even bother writing down his name.
I don't know.
[Voting for their most
formidable opponent, Jong Kook.]
[Kwang Soo too?]
[Gong Yoo]
[This naive man doesn't even know
what just happened.]
Let's go.
[He'll realize what it's like to feel betrayed
once he sees this episode being aired.]
Each member of the Blue Team gets two
ballots for coming in at first place.
- Two ballots each?
- Well...
Kwang Soo really is someone whom we
should eliminate as soon as possible...
Let's all each write down
Kwang Soo's name first.
[Rid themselves of the traitor?
Each to write down Kwang Soo's name.]
[Then how about their other
remaining ballot?]
[Pondering over their vote.]
[Huh?]
- What's that?
- Who's over there?
I can see the red coat.
[Gong Yoo caught eavesdropping.]
[Women's dressing room.]
[Flustered and almost walked into
the women's dressing room by mistake.]
Why are you acting so flustered?
Look at you trying to eavesdrop.
Sorry I have to say this,
but don't try anything.
- I'm seriously trying to tell you.
- What?
- Don't write me down.
- Who, me?
You need to hide better, Kwang Soo.
[This is what you call being inconspicuous?]
[Write down Jong Kook's name.]
- Lee Kwang Soo, we're writing you down.
- I'm writing it down now, Lee Kwang Soo.
[The two biggest figures of betrayal
on RM- Haroro and Giraffe.]
I swear that I didn't
write your name down, Jong Kook.
Stop lying to me.
[Jong Kook gives both
of his votes to the Giraffe.]
I wrote down Gong Yoo's name.
- Hey, Gong Yoo's standing right behind you.
- What did you say?
[What?]
[Weakling Hee Soon is targeting both
Kwang Soo and Jae Suk with one vote each.]
[Traitor Haroro votes for Kwang Soo...]
[And Jong Kook!]
- What is it?
- Ha Ha just sent me a text.
[We need to pick one person
to target...]
[As guessed, he's up to no good...]
I'll start a group chatting room,
and I'll leave Jong Kook out of it.
[Starting to plot their plan of betrayal!]
[Kwang Soo: I've started a group chat
without 'you-know-who'.]
[Jae Suk: Okay.
K.S.: Let's talk comfortably without him.]
[Ha Ha: Sounds good.]
[Lee Kwang Soo: Today's the day, everyone.
Ha Ha: Who did you write down, Hee Soon?]
- Is that sent to me privately?
- Wait a minute.
What are you doing?
I just got a private text.
- You can't say that out loud.
- Who are you texting right now?
- I was just texting someone.
- See? This is the text I just received.
[These scoundrels!]
[Fine... you want to see how far
we can take this?]
[Kim Jong Kook: Kwang Soo... Don't
even think about trying anything funny.]
[Kim Jong Kook: I know what you're doing.]
He says he knows what you're doing.
[Kwang Soo: What, Jong Kook?
What are you talking about?]
[Kim Jong Kook: You better shut down
that group chat right now.]
He totally caught you.
[I don't know anything.]
What else could I say when Jong Kook is
talking about finishing you off?
I have no more reasons to help you
if you keep acting like this.
[What fate awaits for the Giraffe?]
[Eul-wang-li Beach.]
[Razor sharp winds seem to be
especially fiercely today...]
- It's another explosive message.
- It self-destructs after 15 seconds, right?
This time...
[We're going to test your ability
to escape.]
[Even though you may be accustomed
to your prison...]
[there are quite a few things you need
to know about your escape routes.]
But only two of those rooms are
programmed as escape routes.
So you need to escape
as soon as the door opens
and open up the lock to the bun steamer
that you will see outside.
There's only one keep that will
unlock the padlock to the bun steamer.
- But the key is...
- Oh no! The message exploded already.
What about the key?
Wow, that wind is no joke.
What's this?
- Where's the key?
- Wow, it's cold.
[Everyone walks through the cold wind
to walk into the container room.]
- Don't you want to eat that steamed bun?
- I really want that steamed bun.
- I'm hungry.
Wow, it's cold.
I'm hungry!
[The nine suspects are locked up
in the container room together.]
Only one of those keys you see on the
table unlocks the bun steamer.
Okay, we understand.
If you pick the wrong key, then
you have to go back into the container.
Okay, we understand.
What if Kim Jong Kook is the only one who
goes in and out of this place?
- What are you talking about?
- It's always just Kim Jong Kook.
[Loud and chaotic container room.]
For example, if Kim Jong Kook comes out
and picks the correct key...
then every member of the Blue Team
passes this mission.
[Whomever opens up the lock
frees up rest of their teammates.]
[Coaching addict starts strategizing
without a moment of hesitation.]
[Everyone gathers with their own
teammates to strategize.]
We will now start the first round.
[First round- Start!]
[An immediate dance scene.]
[Escape plans are far out of their minds-
These suspects are only feeling the rhythm.]
[The mood is getting heated up!]
[A hot club scene in the container!]
[Everyone dancing with each other
in this club scene.]
There it is!
[Gong Yoo's sly pranks.]
[No signs of the escape door opening.]
[No sign of them even
wanting to escape...]
[So fun!]
- This is it!
- I hear it!
[One of the doors are about to open!]
[A quick escape out the door!]
[Just who will it be?]
[Huh?]
[Big-nose Brother's body was first
to crawl out the door...]
[But Hee Soon slides over him
to escape first!]
[Blue Team's Hee Soon makes his escape!]
[So close...]
- Yes, Hee Soon!
- He's so fast!
You were just saving up
your strength earlier, weren't you?
[Of course!]
- What happened, Suk Jin?
- Someone pulled me back.
Make sure to pick the right one.
You have to think very careful about this
because you only have one chance.
The moment you touch one of the keys,
that's the key that you have to choose.
- Hee Soon!
- Fighting!
- Hee Soon, you have to do this at least!
- No!
- One, two, three. Make your choice.
- The one to the left!
No, Hee Soon.
Pick whichever one you want.
Go with your gut feeling.
[He's made his decision.]
[If the lock opens up,
then rest of the Blue Team can escape.]
- Please!
- Hee Soon made his choice.
[Hm?]
[It won't open...]
- It's not it.
- It didn't open!
- Okay, we're good.
- Come on, Hee Soon.
We're set.
Then are you taking that key out,
or are you mixing that back in?
- We're taking that key out.
- Okay!
[The key that was just chosen
is to be taken out of the mix.]
Wow, he's so fast.
[Everyone is shocked at the speed
of Hee Soon's movement.]
Are you all ready?
[Ready]
[A sexy song for this selection.]
[Gong Yoo's solo dance?]
[No, that's better.
Please don't be good at dancing too.]
[Park Hee Soon's solo performance?
Park Hee Soon- Come Back Boy.]
Park Hee Soon, Come Back Boy.
No, don't do that, Hee Soon.
[Weakling Hee Soon-
His dance brakes are malfunctioning.]
No, no... not yet.
Here we go!
[Let's go.]
[The heat of their dancing is making them
forget about the icy winds.]
[Prudent Gong Yoo is discreetly searching
for an escape route even in this situation.]
[The music ends.]
[Already escaping through the opened door.]
[Park Hee Soon again!]
[He really is quick...]
Let me do this at least!
[He may not have the strength,
but he has the speed?]
He doesn't have 'soon'
in his name for nothing.
Park Hee-Speedy.
[With his quick feet, his new name is,
Park Hee-Speedy.]
[As soon as a door opens up...]
[He appears out of nowhere
to shoot through the opening.]
[The key that Park Hee-Speedy
chose this time...]
[Will it open the lock on the
bun steamer?]
[Fail]
It didn't work!
Come on back!
[He did have the speed...]
- Why can't he pick the right one?
- Luck isn't on his side.
Is everyone ready?
Are you all ready!
[Everyone's is excited to hear
a familiar Turbo song.]
- Here it comes!
- Get in the middle!
[Here he comes, Mr. Turbo man.]
Kim Jong Kook!
[Dance addict suspect always
wanting to take the center stage.]
What are you doing?
[Ha Ha's spastic dance.]
That's good.
[Oh... not bad?]
[Haroro's got the feel for it now.
On the spot dance choreography.]
[His spastic dance is pretty entertaining.]
Hey, this is fun!
[Just then...]
[The siren is activated!]
[Where's the open escape route?]
[There it is!]
[This time, it's Gong Yoo!]
[Excited Red Team.]
[Seven keys left remaining.]
- Gong Yoo!
- You have to choose carefully!
Okay, that's the one.
[Chooses a key.]
It's not going to be that easy.
Please let this one be it.
Please!
[Will the padlock open?]
I got it!
- Seriously!
- It opened!
[It opened!]
- Seriously!
- It opened!
- Seriously?
- It opened?
[Wow... it really opened!]
- Kwang Soo!
- It opened!
- Kwang Soo, let's get out of here.
[The entire Red Team escapes!]
[How can this be...]
We did it!
I feel a little disappointed because
I did want to dance a bit more.
I can't believe that opened.
- Which one is that?
- It's the pizza flavor.
[The winners get cold weather's best snack-
A nice and warm steamed bun!]
[I vow to escape out of here...]
[Give me just one bite!]
[Their own slice of heaven.]
Just give me one bite!
[Just one bite...]
[Oh? Gentleman Gong Yoo heads
toward the container?]
[Huh?]
[You are one cruel man...]
You're so annoying!
Ugh, it's so cold.
- Okay... is everyone ready?
- Yes!
I just had a steamed bun,
and it's really delicious!
[If you want one of these,
you must escape out of there!]
Mr. Park Hee-Speedy,
let me hear you scream!
Yeah!
[At least the music is upbeat!
Dancing to the rhythm of DOC!]
[Is that the jiang-shi dance?]
(Jiang-shi=Chinese vampires that hops.)
[It's a dance scene on the
outside as well.]
[It's the siren!]
[Where's the door?]
[Here it is!]
[An escaped Tiger!]
- The Green Team never once made it out.
- What are you Green Team members doing?
I was trying to get out,
but he's just way too strong!
We're no match for his strength.
[Will this key work?]
- I have a good feeling about this.
- I have a bad feeling about this.
- Just use your strength!
- One, two, three!
[This man has opened up a lock with the use
of his strength alone before...]
How is that even possible?
I think it's going to turn.
That's the feeling I'm getting.
[Will it open?]
[The icy winds are making his eyes tear up.]
It opened!
[It opened!]
[The entire Blue Team escapes!]
Can you give us just one
steamed bun?
[Can't hear you!]
- You don't eat things like that, Jong Kook.
- This is okay.
- Which flavor is that one?
- I'm not sure.
Just take a small bite.
How can a girl take such a huge bite?
There's nothing better than
a steamed bun in the winter.
- It's literally melting the chill off of me.
- Isn't it good?
The Red Team gets two voting ballots.
And the Blue Team gets one voting ballot.
And the Green Team doesn't get any
voting ballots this time either.
[Time to vote.]
Even though we don't know what it is,
just write it down for now.
[Even though they don't what it is yet,
just write down Kim Jong Kook's name?]
I'm not sure if writing this is a good thing.
[And the last remaining vote...]
[Jae Suk?]
[Gong Yoo?]
[Kwang Soo...]
- Please show it to the camera.
- Okay.
[Figures...]
- You didn't write me down, right?
- Of course not.
- Really?
- I really didn't write you down.
It really wasn't you.
[Kkuk's only target is Lee Kwang Soo?]
Let me borrow your back.
[Kim Jong Kook- This is his way of
thanking him for lending him his back?]
[Park Hee-Speedy chooses...]
[Chooses Kwang Soo again!]
I'm just not sure...
Is this how it always...
I feel like this is the blockbuster
of all variety shows.
I never knew this show was so big
with this many staff members.
[On to the next location!]
[Driving time without a doubt means
it's time to text.]
[Kwang Soo: I trust you, Ha Ha.
Ha Ha: You can trust me.]
[Kwang Soo: Thanks to all of you
for all your hard work.]
[Ha Ha: Traitors!
Kwang Soo: Today is the day, Ha Ha.]
What are you chatting about now?
What are you planning?
I'm not planning anything.
- I'm just chatting with the Blue Team a bit.
- Really?
[A secret chat amongst the
Traitors Club.]
'We only have one goal'?
[Kwang Soo: Today is the day.
Ha Ha: Traitors!
Ha Ha.
Why am I the only one not
getting any texts?
[No answer, only silence.]
But he's not...
very trustworthy, is he?
[That's true...]
Ha Ha is like an expert when it comes to
scheming up these plans.
[Suk Jin: Traitors' Club, fighting!
Jae Suk: Kang Soo...]
[Kwang Soo: Yes, Jae Suk?]
[Kang Soo? Jae Suk is unable to resist
teasing Kwang Soo again.]
I'm in the middle of an
important conversation.
If you're going to be saying things like this,
then I'd like for you to leave this chat.
- What am I doing?
- What is with 'Cho Kang Soo, Oh Kang Soo'?
I'm in the midst of an important meeting.
[Cho Kang Soo...]
[Gong Yoo: Will we be
able to do this tomorrow too?]
[Jae Suk: No,
but I'm sure we can do something.]
[Kim Jong Kook: This won't do...]
[Park Hee Soon: I feel like death, and
I'm confused. They want more tomorrow?]
[Arriving at the next mission location.]
['D' Museum in Incheon.]
- Did we get it?
- We've got a message.
[How about some rest time since you've all
been working so hard to earn your ballots?]
[You can share the snack your opposing team
holds in their hand while hoola hooping.]
[If the snack falls or breaks, it won't count,
so you must be careful not to do either.]
- I'm really bad at hoola hoops.
- I'm bad at it too.
- What is it that you're good at?
- I've got nothing.
People are going to think that I'm
an airhead who can't even do anything.
[The first team to finish the snack will
receive three voting ballots.]
[Second placed team gets two ballots,
and the last team gets one ballot each.]
The team that finishes the snack gets
three ballots and the last team gets one.
Three ballots is a huge deal.
The first team to arrive can choose
which team they'll compete against.
We can choose who to compete against
if we're the first team to arrive.
- Where do we have to go?
- Let's go. Let's try to win this time.
We have to eat a snack?
[Red Team is the first team to arrive.]
- What is this?
- While doing the hoola hoop...
I didn't really understand earlier.
You can't drop the hoola hoop,
and the first team to finish eating wins.
[Does he even understand the mission?]
- Wow, you're good.
- I can even walk while doing it.
[Gong Yoo- An expert in hoola hoops?]
Jong Kook's really bad with
the hoola hoop.
[Everyone starts to practice their hoola hoop
skills as soon as they arrive.]
- This isn't really working.
- Why don't you give it a try, Hee Soon?
- This is hard.
- Why can't I do this?
You can't do it either?
[Ah...]
He really can't do anything.
- How are you so good at that?
- Kang Gary's good at it.
[So envious...]
However, you're going to be spinning
the hoola hoop with your arm.
[Awful hoola hoopers are overjoyed.]
That's so much better!
[If it's spinning with the arm, then
there's a better chance of winning!]
- Do you see the numbers in front of you?
- Yes.
You must choose one of them.
[Numbers one through four.
What kind of a snack will they find inside?]
What kind of a snack is inside?
I bet it's something difficult.
- It can't be anything that'll break.
- Number one.
Let's go with number two, Jae Suk.
Number two?
Okay, number two!
[Number two- Celery!]
- This won't break very easily.
- That's not going to break easily.
So the faster we spin, the better for us?
If you want your team to win...
[Mr. Capable spinning
the hoop at a warp speed.]
[You can't spin it that fast...]
You guys really are too much.
Okay, you can't let your arm
get too tired.
- I actually want Hee Soon to do it.
- I wish Hee Soon would spin for us.
[Red Team only wants Hee Soon.]
[Mr. Capable is already battle ready.]
You know what I think?
I think Jae Suk should go first.
No, that's okay.
- I feel like I'd get beat up.
- I know.
Stop being afraid
and let's just do this.
[Red Team's challenge.]
[Jong Kook starting off slowly?]
[Giraffe training session
with the celery stick?]
It hurts!
[Who knew that being hit
with a celery stick could hurt?]
[Even the tears are starting to well up?]
No, I think we're doing fine.
[Trainer and Giraffe's battle
over the celery stick.]
- He keeps hitting me with the celery stick.
- I won't do that anymore.
My whole face smells like parsley now.
- I mean, celery.
- Okay, I heard you.
[At least know what you're
being beaten up with...]
- Kim Jong Kook, you're being warned.
- Okay, I got it.
[With Jong Kook's warning,
the Blue Team switches our their player.]
You have to give it a try too.
Here, you do it.
What's so difficult about doing this?
Go on and do it.
It's Hee Soon's show.
It's time for Hee Soon's show.
[It's once again time for,
Park Hee Soon's show.]
Practice and give it a try.
[There he goes again...]
[People watching are even more
nervous for him...]
This is Park Hee Soon's show.
[Okay, he's got the feel for it now.]
You have to spin your wrist.
There you go.
- He's making me nervous.
- Okay, ready!
[Red Team's second attempt.]
[But he's still not giving up.]
- You just need to spin it.
- Hee Soon's never played this before.
[Murderous hoola hoop.]
[After all those nerve-wracking spins,
at last...]
[Still not giving up- Another attempt.]
There you go.
[Oh... finally seems to have
gotten the hang of it.]
This isn't easy to eat.
[Trying to chase the celery with his tongue.]
[The key to success is to control the
distance between the hoop and the celery!]
[Oh! He gets it in his mouth!]
[A fierce tooth brushing
with the celery stick!]
[Hee Soon's spins are slowly starting to
become bigger and bigger.]
This is really dangerous.
[Total concentration.]
[He may have it...]
[Or maybe not...]
[Erupting in annoyance.]
Whatever, this is exhausting me too.
Take your turn, Gong Yoo!
Get in there!
[Calm]
[Hee Soon seems to be slowly losing
the strength in his arm as well.]
[Only 30 seconds left on the clock!]
[Ugh, this is exhausting.]
[Ouch...]
He stopped spinning.
It hasn't been a minute, right?
[Gong Yoo asking for a referee time.]
[But it's still time out- Red Team fails.]
Okay, the Blue Team.
Okay Hee Soon.
Let's go with number four.
[Number Four]
[Chewy candy stick]
- Isn't that chewy candy stick?
- Chewy candy sticks are good.
[A nostalgic snack that
they haven't seen in a long time.]
It's something that Jong Kook can't eat!
That's not an easy thing to bite off.
[That won't be easy to eat since
it'll be so hard to bite off...]
[I will get my revenge for earlier.]
- Rock, paper, scissors to see who'll go?
- Why don't you go first, Hee Soon?
[Respecting the elder to go first only
at times like this?]
This could be something
that you're good at, Hee Soon.
[Blue Team's challenge.]
This could be the thing that
you're good at.
[Hmm...]
[All over his face as if he's applying
makeup with a brush.]
I'm not even looking right now.
[A little bit... just a little bit more...]
[Seems to be annoyed.
Going for the bite with gusto.]
I'm seriously not looking.
I have no idea what's going on.
[Oh!]
[Blue Team's Park Hee Soon succeeds!]
[It's now Kkuk's turn.]
[The Giraffe immediately gets worked up
at the sight of the Tiger.]
[Extreme desire for revenge.]
What's wrong with him?
[Come and get it!]
[Slowly inching backwards.]
[Tiger-phobia.
Following his instinct to inch away.]
Why are you backing away?
He has to do this right.
I've stopped the time for now.
Okay, start again.
[Oh... so that's how you're
going to play?]
[Whatever! Let's just
attack the Giraffe's front paw!]
Don't you think that this is
just too much?
[Impossible for the Tiger to succeed
as long as the Giraffe is the one spinning.]
[Green Team's turn.]
- Three ballots for the team in first place?
- Three ballots?
- Three ballots to the winning team.
- We need to win this one.
We haven't come in at first place
in anything at all today.
We haven't had a single ballot all day.
[Let's see here...]
We're at an advantage right now
from having the most number of ballots.
We have to pick one person to target.
[Gong Yoo, having heard
the Blue Team's meeting earlier.]
- We all have to write down Kwang Soo.
- Let's all give one vote to Kwang Soo.
How about Jae Suk and Gong Yoo?
[If the Blue Team is
trying to eliminate me...]
[Then it'll be dangerous for
the Blue Team to come in at first place...]
[In that case...]
[It may actually be better for
the Green Team to come in at first place...]
- Look at what a gentleman he is.
- Look at how nice he is being to Ji Hyo.
[He's spinning it VERY slowly.]
[Hurry up and eat it, Ji Hyo.]
[She truly is our Ace!
Eating it from the side, which is easier!]
[Ace Blank Ji immediately succeeds!]
[Time for the Big-nosed Brother!]
Gong Yoo is being too nice.
Green Team needs to come in
at first place.
[Even the Big-nosed Brother
easily succeeds.]
[Now only Gary needs to succeed for
the Green Team to come in at first place.]
Hey, what you're doing could
be a good plan.
The reason being, it could be better for the
Green Team to win rather than the Blue Team.
What you don't know is that the Green Team
would probably write down your name.
- You need to think carefully.
- How much of that is left?
[Perhaps thinking that it's too easy,
Gong Yoo suddenly speeds up his spinning.]
[Mr. Gary also succeeds!]
[Green Team comes in at first place,
and wins themselves three ballots each!]
[Only Hee Soon is left in order
for the Blue Team to succeed!]
This won't be good, right?
I really can't be doing this.
[His face seems to have aged
since earlier this morning...]
[Even Gong Yoo seems to be
pretty exhausted.]
40 seconds left.
One bite!
[Smacking himself in the head with
the hoola hoop.]
- 15 seconds left on the clock.
- 15 seconds is plenty of time.
Watch it carefully...
[Gong Yoo's spin have slowed down considerably
from being too exhausted with the spinning.]
[Park Hee Soon succeeds!]
[Blue Team comes in at second place
and wins themselves two ballots!]
[Time to cast their final votes.]
- We have to vote for the strongest player.
- We each have to vote for Jong Kook.
We have to get rid of
the traitors quickly as well.
- Let's vote for Kwang Soo too.
- Okay.
[It's soon time for the individual battle!
Off to vote in secrecy.]
[Thinking even more carefully since
they were given three voting ballots.]
I have a feeling that you and I
will get our share of the votes.
I don't think there's any need for
you and I to vote for each other.
I don't think any of the members on
the Green Team have gotten any votes yet.
We need to spread out the votes a bit, or
one person could have too much of an edge.
[Aha... have to spread out the votes?]
[Just what will these ballots determine?]
[The voting that went on all day long...
The secret behind it will soon be revealed.]
This is going to be our last mission location.
What is all that voting going to do?
Guys, should we all be honest and
tell each other who we just voted for?
- I just voted for Ha Ha.
- I voted for Hee Soon.
I voted for Gary.
So we all spread out our votes?
They're all people whom I didn't even suspect.
I don't think Ji Hyo's received any votes.
Yes, it's very possible that
Ji Hyo didn't get any votes.
I have a feeling that Suk Jin
voted for her.
I know that I always say this to our guests
before we go into this battle...
But when we go into the name tag elimination,
you can't let it get personal or disappointed.
[Don't feel disappointed no matter what.]
Is it an individual race now?
Yes, it is an individual race now.
[Arriving back at the same location where
they were locked up this morning.]
We will now start the individual race.
You must all find a hiding place
and await the order announcement.
- What is it now?
- So it's an individual race?
I'm nervous.
I really feel like
this is finally Running Man.
What is this?
There are a ton of boxes in here.
I can just hide in one of these.
[What is Hee Soon doing with
that refrigerator?]
[Are you trying to get in there?]
[Children and immature adults should not
imitate what he's doing.]
My reflection is going to
show off of the window.
I will now...
announce your final mission.
Your final mission.
Suspect Target Race.
Eliminate the target's name tag.
Every time you completed a mission
you all got to cast your vote for
one of your fellow suspects.
The order of person targeted will be
determined by the number of votes received.
Ah, the person with the
most votes?
Oust your target in the order that they're
determined by the number of votes received.
Is there any other way around it?
You can't eliminate each other's name tag
except for the person being targeted.
You can only eliminate the name tag of
the person that is being targeted.
Really?
If the target survives and remains alive
without having their name tag eliminated...
then the target must find the hidden
whistle and blow on it.
A hidden whistle?
- What happens when we blow it?
- When you blow on the whistle...
Then the new target will become
the next person on the list.
And the current target will
become the last person on the target list.
So we're going to have to find the whistle
if we don't want to be eliminated?
I just need to find the whistle.
I can't even blow the whistle
unless I'm the current target?
Then we will now start the
target name tag elimination race.
The first target is...
- I doubt I'm the first target.
- Your first target is...
- I will announce your first target.
- I bet everything I have that it's Jong Kook.
- Kim Jong Kook.
- Your first target is...
With a total of...
11 votes...
I'm sure of who this is going to be.
That sure is a lot of votes.
- Kim Jong Kook.
- I'm either the first or the second.
- Your first target...
- First or the second.
With a total of 11 votes...
[Who's the first target
with a total of 11 votes?]
Is Lee Kwang Soo.
Your first target is Lee Kwang Soo.
[First target with a total of 11 votes-
Traitorous Giraffe.]
They're all way too much.
They really are too much.
Come back here and hide.
Lee Kwang Soo.
[First target is Kwang Soo!
It's not Jong Kook!]
It's Kwang Soo?
Is Lee Kwang Soo.
Lee Kwang Soo.
- Is Lee Kwang Soo.
- They're so mean.
Eliminate your target's name tag before
he finds and blows on the blue whistle.
Eliminate his name tag before
Lee Kwang Soo finds and blows the whistle.
Everyone must really dislike Kwang Soo.
[The Giraffe is hiding inside this box.]
What the heck?
How could I have 11 votes?
I thought that I saw the whistle.
You may now start.
[First target race is about to start.]
Two.
One.
Start!
[First target chase- Start.]
[Catch your first target, Kwang Soo!]
- Kwang Soo!
- That's unbelievable.
- Lee Kwang Soo, where are you?
- Kwang Soo!
- Wow, unbelievable. I'm so shocked.
- Where's Kwang Soo?
- I really thought it would be Jong Kook.
- Me too.
- I think Kwang Soo's downstairs.
- Lee Kwang Soo.
- Hey, where's Kwang Soo?
- Lee Kwang Soo, don't you dare move!
Wow, this place is so small that
there's not even a place for him to hide.
I feel so bad for Kwang Soo.
The poor thing.
We promised each other that we'd
both last until the very end.
I'm pretty sure that I'm next.
I need to find it.
I just need to survive once.
I need to survive once.
Come on, Jong Kook.
Why is it me?
Come in here.
Come in.
[I'm sure there are those of you
who've already discovered where it is...]
[But the blue whistle that Kwang Soo needs
to blow is right in front of his eyes.]
[The truth that Giraffe is
certainly unaware of...]
[Ji Hyo?]
[I'm going to go crazy...]
[Kwang Soo's right there.]
[Kwang Soo is right here.]
Lee Kwang Soo!
[Ji Hyo discovers first target, Kwang Soo.]
Jong Kook!
Kwang Soo's right here!
[Giraffe takes Ji Hyo as his hostage
out of sheer desperation.]
In here!
He's in here!
[Ah... the whistle is right here.]
[Giraffe is on the verge of exploding
from having felt betrayed.]
It really wasn't me.
I really didn't vote for you.
- Jae Suk, how could you do this to me?
- Kwang Soo...
- It really wasn't me.
- We've been together all day!
[We were teamed up together all day!]
- We can't write each other's name down.
- Of course not.
[They've agreed not to write
each other's names down.]
[I trusted what you guys told me...]
We can't write each other's names down just
because we win ourselves a ballot, okay?
[I cared for you and even did everything
I could to help you because we were a team.]
[We promised each other that the three
of us would stay together to the end...]
- We were together all day today!
- Let Ji Hyo go.
- It wasn't me, Kwang Soo.
- Don't come any closer!
- We were shocked ourselves.
- Kwang Soo.
- There's nothing that can be done about this.
- How can you do this to me?
- What? 11 votes?
- I was shocked too.
- Hey, it wasn't me. I didn't do it.
- You had 11 votes?
[At the very least, everyone had to have
voted for Kwang Soo at least once.]
If it's 11 votes, it means that all of you
must've voted for me at least once!
[Monday boyfriend, Gary, steps in
to rescue Ji Hyo.]
Kwang Soo.
[Everyone comes to join in on
this tragic scene one by one.]
- Jae Suk, no!
- Come on, Kwang Soo.
I'm going to get my revenge!
I'm going to wreak havoc next week!
- You've all been warned!
- I'm sorry.
[First target, Lee Kwang Soo- Out!]
[In a traitor's term... He was bulldozed.]
You need to be a better person
all year around.
I was shocked too
when I heard the announcement.
- I didn't write your name down.
- At least three of you wrote my down twice.
I'm going to watch this episode when it airs
to see which one of you wrote me down.
- Jae Suk!
- I can't believe he got 11 votes.
[Only Kwang Soo's blue whistle remains
by its lonesome...]
Let's see who's laughing next week!
What?
I'm back in here?
The cameras aren't even finished
being setup yet.
[Sorry, we didn't think you'd be
back in here so quickly.]
- I thought it would be Jong Kook.
- We all wanted to get rid of the traitor.
- I thought it would be Jong Kook too.
- Then I guess Jong Kook is up next.
[Then the next target surely is...]
- He knows himself.
- Jong Kook didn't show up on purpose.
Let's go find Jong Kook.
Let's split up into two groups,
so we can work from up and downstairs.
Lee Kwang Soo, out.
Your next target is...
with a total of 10 votes...
- With a total of 10 votes.
- 10 votes? That's only one vote difference.
[Exactly one vote difference from
Kwang Soo's total votes.]
[Second target with a total of 10 votes.]
Your next target is Kim Jong Kook.
[Target race's second target-
Kim Jong Kook with ten votes.]
Before Kim Jong Kook finds
his purple whistle...
you must eliminate his name tag.
If we don't get him now, then we're all dead.
If we don't get him now,
then Kim Jong Kook will surely win.
I wonder if he's inside.
[Big-nose and Ro-Ro are searching
the outside parameters.]
- Would you go on your own if it was you?
- Is he hanging off the ledge somewhere?
He's not hanging off the ledge
somewhere, is he?
That's what I was thinking.
I wouldn't put it past him.
[Jong Kook is desperately searching
everywhere for his purple whistle.]
Where's my whistle?
My whistle.
[Will he be able to find his whistle
to remain alive to the very end?]
[The purple whistle!]
[It wouldn't even do Jae Suk any good
to blow on that whistle now.]
I can just leave it here, right?
[Leaving it so that it can't be found.]
[Leaving it alone and buried
so that it can't be found.]
[So detailed about he how leaves it...]
[Jong Kook...
I never touched your whistle.]
Hey there.
What have I done that's so wrong?
- Look, I was shocked about it myself.
- 11 votes?
I can't tell you how shocked I was
when I heard that announcement myself.
- Getting 11 votes means...
- I will do whatever I can to free you.
How?
You know of a way?
Don't worry.
Just wait... just wait a bit longer.
- I'll get you out of there.
- The cameras aren't even setup in here yet.
- It's totally bare in here.
- Okay.
- Don't worry about it.
- What do you mean, don't worry?
No one's even in here to film me, Jae Suk.
Jae Suk.
I'm ruined.
I'm totally ruined.
[Jong Kook is still searching
for his purple whistle.]
Even with the building so small...
it's not so easy to find him.
I'm positive that he's outside.
But he doesn't even have
his coat on.
- Is he not there?
- I don't see him.
Jong Kook.
[Okay... I need to get out of here
if I want to survive...]
[This sound means that the second target,
Kim Jong Kook has been discovered!]
- He's right here!
- Here!
Kim Jong Kook is here!
Where?
Where did he go?
[Second target Jong Kook escapes
to inside of the building.]
[Discovered as soon as he steps inside.]
[A dead end of all places!]
[Surrounded from all sides...
and the Ace jumps to grab him!]
[Hee Soon jumping in on the mix to
join in out of his excitement.]
Let me be the one to eliminate you.
[Second target, Kim Jong Kook- Out!]
Hee Soon.
[You said not to be disappointed by this...]
[So this is what it feels like.]
Kim Jong Kook, out.
[I'm in trouble if I'm the next target!]
I'm sure it won't be me.
It won't be me.
- I don't think it'll be me either.
- Your next target is...
Your next target is... Gary.
Me?
Gary.
[Third target- Gary.]
- It's me?
- Before Gary finds the yellow whistle...
You must eliminate his name tag.
It's in here, Gary!
It's right in front of the jail cell!
Your next target is, Gary.
[Third target- Random Mr. Capable.
Capture Gary!]
- It's Gary!
- Where is he?
Before Gary finds the yellow whistle,
you must eliminate his name tag.
[Gary must find his yellow whistle
for him to remain alive.]
- Did he go up the stairs?
- Gary!
Where did Gary go?
[Fleeing all the way to the top floor.]
Is this the end of the hallway?
Wait!
[I've got you!]
Is this the end of the hallway?
Wait!
[We're about to meet face to face!]
What do I do now?
[Gong Yoo makes a beeline for Gary!]
[Gary is like a rat caught in
a mousetrap.]
- Hurry!
- Why is it me?
- This makes no sense!
- You're the next target.
[Random Mr. Capable landed himself
in third place with five votes.]
- I worked so hard to stay alive!
- Sorry, Gary.
[Third target, Gary- out!]
How did you get so many votes?
[With the total of being second strongest,
many seemed to have feared Gary.]
Gary, out.
[Could the next target be... me?]
[I can't fit in here...]
I wonder who's next after Kang Gary?
[Who could the fourth target be?]
This is really exciting.
It's a very exciting race today.
I can't believe how good it feels
not to be the target.
Your next target is...
- Your next target is...
- Ha Ha.
Your next target is...
[Who could be the fourth target?]
Yoo Jae Suk.
[Fourth target is Yoo Jae Suk,
with a total of four votes.]
[Everyone alike panics whenever
they're announced to be the next target.]
Before Yoo Jae Suk finds a black whistle,
you must eliminate his name tag.
[Target- Yoo Jae Suk.]
[Serves him right!]
- Wow! Let's go get him!
- It's Jae Suk!
- That's hilarious.
Before Yoo Jae Suk finds a black whistle,
you must eliminate his name tag.
[Oh! He's right in front of me!]
Next target is Yoo Jae Suk.
[Being chased after by Ji Hyo
as soon as the race gets started.]
Before Yoo Jae Suk finds a black whistle,
you must eliminate his name tag.
[Ji Hyo having discovered both Kwang Soo
and Jae Suk today on her own!]
I have a bad feeling that I might be next,
so I'm too nervous to even eliminate anyone.
Let me think who we've had so far.
Kwang Soo, Kim Jong Kook, Gary, Yoo Jae Suk.
Which means that the next target
will either be me or Ha Ha.
[Jae Suk's voice can be heard
from nearby!]
[His black whistle is right here!]
[To get caught in this room of all places!]
[Fourth target, Yoo Jae Suk- Out!]
Which floor was the whistle on?
[What do you mean, which floor...]
[It's right here.]
So this is what it feels like
to eliminate someone's name tag?
That felt really good.
The truth is...
I gave Jae Suk one of my votes.
Where did Gong Yoo spring out of?
There's not even any place to run to.
Wait, a minute though.
How did I end up with so many votes?
[Who were the four people
that voted for me?]
[Who are you grumbling about injustice
in front of right now?]
- What? You didn't vote for me?
- But wait a minute...
How did I end up with so many votes
when everyone denied voting for me?
People just must not like you.
[Not because he's a strong opponent,
but because they don't like him?]
It's possible for people to not like you
because you've won so may races.
- That's not the factor in this right now.
- But how was I the third target?
- How did you end up with 11 votes?
- It's because you're a formidable opponent.
My 11 votes should end up in
the Guinness Book of World Records.
- There are a lot of others to vote for.
- Why didn't any of you vote for Gong Yoo?
I saw your purple whistle.
That's what I thought.
Why did you take it?
- You saw it?
- Yeah.
- You should've just left it alone.
- I didn't steal it, and I did leave it alone.
- Are you sure?
- I didn't even touch it.
All I did was close the lid to
where the whistle was.
- I can understand how you could do that.
- Why did you do that?
Your next target is...
- I bet it's Ha Ha.
- Your next target is...
[Suk Jin, Hee Soon, Gong Yoo, Ha Ha, Ji Hyo-
Who could be the next target?]
I have a feeling that it's me.
Your next target is...
[Who could be the fifth target?]
Gong Yoo.
And...
- Gong Yoo, and...
- He should've been a target sooner.
- Ha Ha.
- They're both targets?
[Fifth targets are Gong Yoo and Ha Ha.]
Before Gong Yoo and Ha Ha find
the red whistle...
you must eliminate the name tags
off of your targets.
Look at everyone down there.
[Red whistle...
I have to find it no matter what!]
[Ji Hyo, who's discovered everyone today...
starts her search for the new targets.]
I have to find the red whistle first
in order to get them.
[Who should I find first to
make it easier for myself?]
[Oh?]
[Discovers Gong Yoo!]
[Discovers fifth target Gong Yoo!]
Why isn't anyone around?
Hee Soon!
Gong Yoo!
Gong Yoo's right there!
[Hee Soon runs to help her.]
Where is everyone?
Hee Soon!
Fourth floor!
[Gong Yoo makes a break for it
to get away from Ji Hyo's chase!]
[Fifth target, Gong Yoo-
Everyone's new focused target!]
[How is he going to get himself
out of this danger?]
I see someone going down.
[Hee Soon is continuing his chase
after Gong Yoo.]
[Everyone's watching...]
[Try your best and hide...]
[Hee Soon is approaching the emergency
stairway that Gong Yoo is hiding in.]
[Wait, that sound means?]
Hey, someone blew the whistle.
[This is the unmistakable sound of
a whistle being blown.]
Who blew the whistle?
Did he blow the whistle?
[That means...]
[Ha Ha, having been on the run...]
[Sees the red whistle on the ground!]
[Discovers the whistle by total luck!]
[Blowing this whistle puts Ha Ha and Gong Yoo
at the end of the target line!]
[The whistle blow to sound
their freedom.]
Ha Ha and Gong Yoo are saved.
[Whistle is successfully blown-
Gong Yoo and Ha Ha to the end of the line.]
Ha Ha and Gong Yoo are now moved to
the back of the target line.
I found it!
Gong Yoo!
You owe me!
Ha Ha will move to the very back of the line
for having been the one to find the whistle.
And Gong Yoo is now second to last
in the target line.
That was nice.
Park Hee Soon!
It's me, Gong Yoo!
[Now desperate Hee Soon quickly
escapes as far away as he can.]
[Come in.]
I will announce your next target.
[Which out of the three is the next target?]
Your next target is...
It's probably me.
- Ji Suk Jin, Park Hee Soon...
- It's not me?
- Ugh, it's the both of us.
- Both are your new targets.
[Suk Jin and Hee Soon both
are the new targets.]
Suk Jin and Hee Soon both
are the new targets.
Before Suk Jin and Hee Soon
find the green whistle...
you must eliminate both of
their name tags.
Before Suk Jin and Hee Soon
find the green whistle
you must eliminate both of
their name tags.
[Will they be able to create a miracle
just like Ha Ha did?]
More than anything else,
I'd think it would really hurt your hands.
Are you okay?
- Congratulations, Gong Yoo.
- Congratulations.
You could win the race.
Ha Ha blowing the whistle
was a huge help.
[Having survived thanks to
his friend, Ha Ha.]
If Gong Yoo were to get ousted,
he needed to have been ousted now.
- I know.
- It'll be difficult to oust him now.
I'm starting to feel the greed
to win now.
[Now's about the time for anyone to get
greedy about winning.]
The desire to win now...
[So envious...]
You can't get out this way, right?
I found the whistle.
[The whistle that Suk Jin and
Hee Soon needs!]
[In that case...]
[Should I hide to attack them
right here?]
Hee Soon. Hee Soon will be
good at something like this.
Even though he may not be good at
things that require strength...
I bet he'd be good at hiding since
he's such a quiet person.
[Oh? Why is this door left open?]
No way.
Hee Soon.
It's all over now.
He's not here.
I think he's found himself a good place.
No one knows of this place right now.
[Hee Soon is behind that
door right now!]
This space feels like...
It feels like an action sequence from a movie
that I just shot needs to happen here.
Even the lighting is a bit
darker in here.
I eliminate about 10 to 15 bad guys
in a scene that looks like this place.
[Just leaves after
chattering on the whole time.]
In an underground chamber.
Where could he be?
[He's leaving...]
So only one person needs to blow the
whistle for both of us to survive?
[You're searching for it, right, Suk Jin?]
[You're searching for it, right, Hee Soon?]
- I searched the basement, and no one's there.
- This is driving me crazy.
- Ji Hyo!
- Hee Soon's good at things like this.
- He's good at hiding
- Yeah, he's a very quiet person.
He's a very quiet person.
Oh, and where do you want to meet?
- For what?
- You owe me a night out.
First... since we're the two last targets...
- Let's see what happens at the end.
- Okay, fine.
- Anyways, don't forget what I did.
- What you did was huge.
I was shocked when I heard
the whistle blow.
- It was like a scene right out of a movie.
- It's all over now.
- You have to come back on the show, okay?
- Okay.
[Ha Ha's good at getting people
on the show...]
- I think we need to strategize.
- Ji Hyo's really good at finding people.
Actually, this is no time for me to be
going around searching for Park Hee Soon.
I need to find a hiding place for myself.
This is no time to be searching for someone.
This is no time for me to be doing this now
when I don't even know where my whistle is.
[Must find her own hiding place whether
or not Suk Jin and Hee Soon are found.]
[Huh?]
[Blank?]
Okay, I got him!
[Gong Yoo starts chasing
after his target, Hee Soon.]
He totally took me by surprise just now.
- Ha Ha!
- Yeah, I know.
[Surrounded on both sides.]
We're all pretty much
in the same boat right now.
- Where's Song Ji Hyo?
- She's downstairs right now.
I want Ji Hyo to eliminate me.
- Okay, fine then.
- That's better for us.
- I think she already went into hiding though.
- I'll tell you where Ji Hyo is.
- No, we'll find her ourselves.
- Really?
I'm sorry.
We have no other choice, Gong Yoo.
- I know.
- In this situation...
You should've moved faster.
You did good, Hee Soon.
[Immediately says 'Good work' like
the cool guy that he is.]
[A man who's quick to give up,
Park Hee-Speedy.]
[Park Hee Soon- Out.]
[Seventh target Suk Jin, and
eighth target Ji Hyo are also ousted.]
The next target is... Gong Yoo.
Gong Yoo is the next target.
I think today's the day.
Before Gong Yoo finds the red whistle,
you must eliminate your target's name tag.
[If Gong Yoo finds the red whistle, then
he moves behind Ha Ha in the target line!]
[The victory is pretty much guaranteed
as long as I can find the red whistle!]
[Gong Yoo is feeling the pressure.]
[Running around swiftly to search
every corner of the building.]
Ugh, this is exhausting.
Where's the whistle?
There he is.
I see him right there.
I'm sure he's feeling quite nervous by now.
Aren't you?
Okay, I can see what he's doing.
He's in too nervous of a state
find the whistle right now.
[Having figured out Gong Yoo's location...
Ha Ha heads inside the building.]
[Where's the whistle?]
[Ha Ha is now right in front of
where Gong Yoo is standing!]
[Ha Ha springs his attack on Gong Yoo!]
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Gong Yoo.
I'm sorry!
[One of these two will become the victor!]
[A battle for victory between
these two good friends!]
Gong Yoo!
I really am sorry!
But this won't affect our friendship!
[Gong Yoo- Out!]
I'm sorry, my friend.
After three years... I finally...
[Ha Ha's sole victory!]
Hey.
I needed to look cool on Running Man since
I played such a cool character in the movie.
This is what a variety show is like.
Hey, this is so far from anything that
I imagined this show was going to be like.
A UFC champion came on our show
and had to play gong-gi in our past episode.
[This was only just a game...
Hope this won't affect your friendship...]
Get in there, Gong Yoo!
I'm sorry, my friend!
You idiots!
The victor of this week is me!
Fighting!
- Ha Ha actually won?
- This gold card is mine!
[Haroro wins a gold 'R' marked card!]
[The rage felt by these eight suspects
who weren't able to escape their injustice...]
So anyone can win on Running Man now?
I'll go see 'The Suspect' when it hits
the theater since I'm free now.
- You're going to rot away in there.
- No!
Ha Ha's Running Man!
[Ha Ha's sole victory celebration.]
Bye!
[Are you that happy?]
Hee Soon... are you okay?
- Yes, I was fine with the show.
- People's opinion of you will change.
- After watching this episode.
- Well, this is a variety show after all.
- I was just trying to be funny.
- You were just trying to be funny, right?
You were just trying to be entertaining.
And you even wore that hat
of all hats.
[Even his hat says 'AC'.]
(Equivalent to saying, 'Ugh'.)
You even earned yourself a new nickname
on our show today.
Park Hee-Speedy.
- Park Hee-Speedy.
- Gong Yoo.
You should come back on our show sometime
since you lost your winning today.
I'm already preparing myself
for the next time I'll be on.
Subtitles by DramaFever
[End of the year special-
Brightening up the year of 2013.]
[All the big names are here
on Running Man.]
[Who is the ultimate man who makes the hearts
of women between the ages of 10-50 flutter?]
I love you.
[First condition for being the top male-
Must be strong.]
[Second- Ability to understand
what women are saying.]
[Third- An unknown quality that
keeps you intrigued.]
[Order of popularity between all these men.]
[Must put your pride on the line to survive!]
Let's keep it moving!
[Next week's Running Man-
Man of popularity race.]