(Early summer in 2016, Ganghwa Island)
(What race will they have in the summer breeze?)
(The member who arrives first is...)
(Jae Seok.)
- Aren't you hungry?
-  What?
- Before the race,
-  It smells good.
you'll enjoy the food first.
Gosh, what is this?
(A sumptuous feast for the Running Man members)
Wow, you've prepared so much food!
Goodness.
(There are various types of seafood, meat and vegetables.)
It's amazing.
(They're all in one table.)
(Sizzling)
Gosh, these look great!
(This is quite a feast.)
This is unbelievable.
We've prepared...
- white and blue plates.
-  Okay.
Please choose one plate and help yourself to the food.
Let me see.
I'm wearing a blue cap today.
(Jae Seok chooses a blue plate.)
My goodness.
(What should I eat first?)
Goodness, the food looks great.
(The food looks very delicious.)
Wow.
This is my favourite.
(Jae Seok is happy.)
(He puts food on his plate while excitingly making noises.)
This is amazing.
This is eel.
(Charcoal-grilled eel and beef)
This is beef.
(It's hard to resist.)
May I have some eel?
Thank you.
(His plate is full of food.)
Gosh, I'm so happy.
(He's very content.)
It looks so tasty, doesn't it?
This is so nice.
(Why are they treating us so well today?)
(A plate full of food)
- Can I eat now?
-  Before you start eating,
- please look over there.
-  Where?
(Please look over there.)
Please don't do this.
What is Dangerous Meal?
(Dangerous Meal?)
(What is this?)
Why is this dangerous?
I just picked whatever I wanted, so why is this dangerous?
I was about to happily enjoy my breakfast.
Don't do this to me.
- Please take that "R" off.
-  You guys are so weird.
What is this?
I will get you if something weird comes out when I take this off.
(A menu?)
Today, you'll have a Dangerous Meal race.
Please enjoy the food...
and get the ingredients used for the food you chose.
(They must get the ingredients for the food.)
(How can I get all the ingredients for the food I eat?)
Goodness.
Seriously.
This is ridiculous.
Why do I have to gather the ingredients? Why?
(He must get various fish, vegetables and crabs.)
Why are you doing this?
(He's in despair.)
I shouldn't have chosen this rockfish.
(I should have taken less food.)
(Jong Kook arrives.)
Hello.
Good morning.
I'm sure he'll choose only chicken or beef.
Please take as much food as you'd like to eat.
- Choose one plate there.
-  Okay.
(Among the two dishes...)
Well...
(He chooses the white one.)
Can I take as much as I want?
(The plates represent the teams.)
You've prepared steak, right?
I have no doubt he'll choose it.
Gosh, what should I put on my plate?
What are you talking about? We all know what you'll choose.
Yukhoe.
See?
I told you he'll choose beef and chicken.
(He takes a large amount of yukhoe without hesitation.)
This is sashimi.
(He loves raw food.)
Chicken porridge is my favourite.
He chose chicken porridge.
He's grilling meat.
(He finds charcoal-grilled meat.)
I want some eel.
He's not on my team, so I hope he takes a lot of food.
(Jong Kook adds eel and meat to his plate.)
I'm done. Let me eat now.
(He also takes a lot of food.)
Wow, this is nice.
I'm so excited.
You chose a blue plate.
The best choice I've made today is this blue plate.
(They squabble over nothing as soon as they meet.)
I guessed what you'd choose,
- and you did exactly as I guessed.
-  No way.
Please enjoy.
You'll have to get the ingredients of the food.
(You have to get the ingredients of the food you brought.)
(What did you say?)
(I knew there would be something.)
You brought chicken and beef.
So you have to get all of that.
(He must get various fish, meat and vegetables.)
Okay? This is good.
The chickens will teach you a lesson.
(You need to be taught a lesson.)
I never thought...
they'd ask us to get the ingredients.
(The mission is beyond his imagination.)
This is unbelievable.
- It is something I never expected.
-  I decided to just enjoy the food.
(Following Jong Kook,)
(the other members also arrive.)
What is that?
Such a sumptuous feast means...
today's mission is a hard one.
(Ji Hyo chooses a white plate.)
This is a great breakfast.
She chose the white plate. Poor Ji Hyo.
(Ji Hyo must get the ingredients of the food she and Jong Kook chose.)
I love these lettuce wraps.
(Ji Hyo also takes a lot of food.)
There's a lot here. I don't know what to choose.
Gosh, Ji Hyo, don't take too much.
Why is she choosing so many different types of food?
Listen to this.
This boiling sound is so nice.
This is curled mallow soup.
Ji Hyo is doing great!
(Jae Seok and Jong Kook show different reactions.)
You brought all kinds of food.
- You have to get the ingredients.
-  You need to.
Gosh.
We have to go gather strawberries because of you.
(She even brought fruits and eggs.)
- Really?
-  Yes.
Gary's here.
(Gary chooses a blue plate.)
This is an unusual opening.
He chose a blue plate.
(Knowing nothing yet, Gary also takes various dishes.)
This is the best treatment ever.
We're in trouble.
We'll have to borrow a fishing boat.
Hello.
I like coloured ones.
- No way! Not Seok Jin!
-  This is exciting.
You know he's really lazy. Gosh.
(But he diligently adds food on his plate.)
- The eel's tail is good.
-  Strawberry cakes...
Let me have a fried egg.
- Yes!
-  Gosh!
(They have to get all kinds of ingredients.)
I'll choose this white one.
Plates must be white.
Will you weigh the food I take?
Why do you give me such a nice meal? It makes me worry.
I'm worried.
He's choosing similar dishes.
- Long time no see!
-  Hello.
Are we on the same team?
We have to get the ingredients of the food we eat.
What?
- We have to get the ingredients.
-  Eat first.
Sorry?
Gary,
we have to get the ingredients for everything we eat.
They said we have to get all the ingredients.
(Gary also chose a lot of food.)
(Haha mainly chose beef.)
(Seok Jin's choice includes fish, vegetables, beef and egg.)
- Hello.
-  Kwang Soo is here.
Hello.
I hope Kwang Soo chooses a blue plate.
Pick the white one.
He should pick the blue one.
My goodness.
Thank you.
- Gosh, we're done for.
-  Good choice!
- Wow!
-  Great choice!
(Kwang Soo is on the Blue Team.)
This is the most frustrating thing of the day.
He's of no help.
I like tomatoes.
(Kwang Soo takes a lot of food.)
I love cucumber kimchi.
This is a great meal.
(The Blue Team now has to get strawberries.)
There's honey here, too.
(He even adds honey.)
This is how I enjoy strawberries.
Great. You should visit a bee farm.
(The Blue Team has to go to a bee farm.)
- Go to a bee farm and get honey.
-  I will get him.
I think...
Why did you put honey on your plate?
- Sorry?
-  Kwang Soo, enjoy the food.
You have to get the ingredients of the food you eat.
(He tells Kwang Soo the rule.)
Do what?
You have to go get the ingredients.
- I have to get these ingredients?
-  Yes. All of them.
You have to get all the ingredients of the dishes you chose.
- You have to catch eel.
-  Kwang Soo, there's no choice.
Since you're the only one who chose honey, get it yourself.
- Gosh.
-  Your team is perfect.
We're thinking about how to push the responsibility to each other.
Is this our team?
- This is our team.
-  Isn't it obvious?
Why am I getting punished from the beginning?
- Hey! You can't say that.
-  What's with this team?
You're the one who brings us bad luck.
- So we are all unlucky people.
-  Hey!
Gary completes the team by bringing his share of bad luck.
(Gary is not an exception.)
We are very unlucky. Our team is complete now.
By the way, there is an empty seat. Someone must be coming.
- You're right.
-  Right?
- Look!
-  What is it?
(At that moment, someone appears and surprises everyone.)
(A man with a unique aura appears.)
(It's Yeo Jin Goo, the actor of every girl's dream.)
(He grew from a cute, child actor to a handsome, young actor.)
(He proved his talent the last time he was on Running Man.)
- Hello.
-  Hello.
Hello.
It's Yeo Jin Goo!
- Really?
-  Jin Goo.
Jin Goo, whose mother is the same age as me?
- Yes. Right.
-  Jin Goo's mother...
- is my age.
-  Jin Goo's mother.
- Can I take whatever I want?
-  Yes. Take whatever you want.
Everything will be fine, right?
It feels strange.
Will I have a harder time the more I eat?
It's okay. Eat.
Stop it.
I'm done.
- You can take it upstairs.
-  Okay.
Jin Goo!
- Jin Goo!
-  Hello.
- I remember the last time.
- Jin Goo.
-  Jin Goo,
did you put honey on your food?
Where was the honey? I didn't see it.
He got crabs, too.
Jin Goo, we have to go get all those ingredients.
We have to get the ingredients of the dishes you picked.
You have to get all the ingredients used to cook those dishes.
It makes you lose your appetite, doesn't it?
Jin Goo has to butcher a cow.
- He has to catch eel.
-  Also crabs.
- He has to catch crabs.
-  There is so much.
- I will explain the rule.
-  Gosh.
The team that completes the Dangerous Meal first...
through various missions will be the winner.
The team that loses will get...
a truly dangerous meal as a penalty.
(What is this truly dangerous meal?)
I will tell you what that means.
It contains food that is good for your body but uncomfortable to eat.
It includes one of the seven stinkiest food, stinky tofu,
which is a Chinese beloved health food.
It also includes pickled herring, which is five times stinkier,
Sophora root tea, fermented skate and many more.
(We will take charge of your sense of smell.)
(They are terrified.)
- I once got stinky tofu on my hand.
-  I am sorry, but...
The smell lasted for two weeks.
Pickled herring smells five times worse?
Here's your first mission.
It is called the "Ingredient Gathering War".
You have to get all the ingredients within the time limit.
At every spot, you will have an opportunity to obtain a card.
The winner of the first mission will be given an advantage...
that can be used for the final mission.
(The Ingredient Gathering War begins.)
(Each team has a list of ingredients they must gather.)
(The two teams head to different areas.)
- We have to get the card.
-  Right.
- Jin Goo.
-  Yes.
What's good about being an adult?
What do you want to do the most?
Since I have a driver's license...
If you were to go on a trip,
which girl group member would you take with you?
Who's your type? I don't care about the looks.
- Do you want me to guess?
-  Sure.
I think I know who it is.
- It's her. That's right.
-  Jun Hyo Seong?
What do you think about a girl like Hyo Seong?
She's beautiful.
- Right?
-  You were so quiet all along!
He reacted.
- I've never seem him so excited.
-  I know.
I have her number.
Do you really have her number?
Call her.
(His heart pounds.)
- Maybe she won't pick up.
-  Hello?
(His heart starts racing.)
- Hyo Seong.
-  Oh, dear!
- We're shooting Running Man.
-  Is that right?
- Yes.
-  Hyo Seong!
This week's celebrity guest...
chose you as his ideal type.
- Talk to him and guess who he is.
-  Go ahead.
Listen to his voice.
Here. Talk to her.
Hello.
(He has a great voice.)
- Hello. Who are you?
-  My goodness.
- They're getting acquainted.
-  I am...
- Yeo Jin Goo.
-  Oh, dear!
Hello.
Hyo Seong, what do you think about Jin Goo?
- He's every girl's dream.
-  Oh, gosh!
(He's every girl's ideal man.)
Talk to her, Jin Goo.
I'm excited, too.
Ask her to have dinner with you one day.
- Let's eat dinner sometime.
-  Okay.
(Let's have dinner.)
(He's a real man.)
"Let's eat dinner sometime."
It sounds very nice when you say it.
(His low voice is irresistible.)
I'm fascinated.
- Okay, Hyo Seong.
-  Hey.
Jin Goo told me to tell you this.
"You're my girl."
(You're my girl.)
- Thank you, Hyo Seong.
-  Thank you.
Thank you.
- Why am I getting hot?
-  Tell us if there's someone else.
We will instantly call that person.
Now, I know what kind of style he likes.
- Do you?
-  Yes. I know.
(Gary and Ji Hyo come to fish because they ate fish.)
This is the match of the century.
- The match of the century.
-  A match of the century.
(This is where Ji Hyo and Gary will have the match of the century.)
It's lovely.
Gosh, listen to the seagulls.
The sound of the seagulls makes me realise that I'm near the sea.
(Welcome. It's been a long time, hasn't it?)
It's the ocean!
Please give me fish!
(Will Ji Hyo and Gary be able to catch fish?)
Bye.
(They're ready to go out.)
- Don't you think it's too empty?
-  Goodbye.
Bye, seagulls.
- Seagulls!
-  Seagulls.
Seagulls!
(It sounds like a name of a mixed drink.)
What kind of big fish can you catch here?
Trout and grey mullet.
How big are they? This big?
We sometimes catch big ones which are a few metres long.
- A few metres?
-  A metre?
One metre long.
Today is that day.
(Today is the perfect day to catch a big fish.)
(It's the match of the century! Who will catch the big fish first?)
- I feel it. Is this the spot?
-  Yes.
I got the feeling.
He's putting on the bait.
- Please put one here, too.
-  You can do it here.
(He's terrified.)
(They're in shock.)
(Is that really a worm?)
That looks more like a centipede.
No way.
(What is that monster?)
- That's a centipede.
-  Where did you get this?
- This worm grows in this area.
-  Really?
(They must endure this after eating a few pieces of fish.)
That looks like a centipede. I hate it.
(They put the worm on the rod and start fishing.)
- Let it go while throwing it.
-  Do I let go while throwing it?
(Throwing)
Where did it go?
(It sinks.)
(Let's wait.)
Nice!
(Gary throws the rod, too.)
(They look the same.)
(There's a silence.)
Fishing is like fighting with time.
It went in well, right?
(There is no sign of biting.)
(Suddenly)
I feel like I caught something.
Look at that. Doesn't it look like it's moving?
I think it's moving.
It's moving!
Sir! Captain! I think I caught something!
Look! I caught something!
I caught something, Ji Hyo!
- Did you?
-  Look!
I think it's a big one!
- Ji Hyo, look!
-  It looks like a big one!
My goodness!
(Will I lose like this?)
(Let's see.)
What?
(There is nothing.)
Your worm is gone.
Captain. Sir.
Captain, what happened?
(I don't know.)
It's here.
(It looks like there's really something this time.)
It's biting! Ji Hyo, it's biting!
You caught it! You caught it!
It's nothing...
- There's nothing.
-  Just leave it be.
It's here! Ji Hyo, it's here!
Ji Hyo! This is crazy!
It's moving! The tail is moving!
Hey! Ji Hyo!
I think it's a shark!
(A shark?)
(The shark just ate the worm and disappeared.)
Captain, what is wrong?
Captain, what's wrong with me?
(Is Gary fishing for fish or for luck?)
What type of crab do we need to catch?
I'm not good at catching crabs.
Don't they bite?
Of course.
Do you really think they won't?
Man, I'm worried.
It must be here.
The map says we've arrived.
- There is a mudflat on our left.
-  What is it?
- Here.
-  There are a lot of holes.
This area is completely covered in mud.
(The endless mudflat makes them sigh.)
My goodness.
(There are many large tools waiting for them.)
- I haven't been here for some time.
-  It's been so long.
- The other members have it easier.
-  It's a mudflat.
- Isn't that a crab hole?
-  I think so.
(Welcome to the mudflat.)
- Greetings, everyone.
-  Okay.
- You can grab...
-  By the way, who are you?
I'm a sub-producer, Park So Hyun.
- Really?
-  You must be the new sub-producer.
Let's introduce ourselves first.
My goodness.
They must hire based on looks these days.
What are you saying?
- What are you talking about?
-  You don't know for sure.
- She's really pretty.
-  It was so sudden.
You could've just said that she's beautiful.
But you went like this. What was that?
- She's pretty. Greetings.
-  My goodness.
This is a mudflat where you can grab your crabs.
- All right.
-  Was that a rhyme?
"You can grab your crabs"?
Here at a mudflat, we can catch crabs
- What are you doing?
-  Are you serious?
You might get buried in a mudflat if you keep doing that.
Watch your tongue, Seok Jin.
(Embarrassed)
You have five minutes in total.
Freely choose a tool from the table.
- We can freely choose.
-  If you catch a total of 20 crabs,
you will be granted a chance to draw a card.
Wait. But why do we need fat?
Is this to lure the crabs?
- Or a snack?
-  I can't tell you.
- You must figure out its purpose.
-  Crabs must eat this.
They might smell the fat.
Can crabs smell?
Can they?
(Slapping)
I'm sorry. I didn't mean to.
Seok Jin. You know how bad I can be if I really want to.
- You know him.
-  Seok Jin,
I'll put this in your nose and take it out of your mouth.
(I'll put it in your nose and pull it out of your mouth.)
(The time limit is 5 minutes.)
- We don't have to go far.
-  We don't need to go far.
- Look. Come here.
-  There are no crabs.
- Here. Get ready. Come, Seok Jin.
-  Okay.
- Ready.
-  Dig it.
(Jae Seok finds a suitable spot.)
Are there any?
Why aren't there any?
(Screaming)
Oh, gosh.
(What's wrong?)
It's an anaconda.
- That's gross.
-  They must be nearby.
Deep in there. Here.
They must be in here.
- Step back. Go back.
-  Dig here.
(It's their second attempt.)
- Look. Here's a crab.
-  Where?
(Slipping)
- Why are you pushing me down?
-  Hey, look.
- Where?
-  Here. Right here.
- It must be underneath.
-  Get ready to grab it.
(Will it be a crab this time?)
(Screaming)
(They are in panic for the second time.)
- It's irritating.
-  What is that?
- That's really gross.
-  There is a snake underneath.
It's not even moving.
- Gross.
-  That was horrible.
- There must be some crabs.
-  Worms are everywhere.
- Let's change the spot.
-  Hurry.
There are so many worms.
Why are there so many worms?
Let's try here.
You're a professional crab hunter. You decide without any hesitation.
- Do you mean it?
-  Crab hunter.
- I just realised that...
-  Do you hunt crabs?
I'm the only one digging.
It's because you always go ahead us.
- Like this.
-  Everyone has their own role.
All right. We're crab hunters.
- Dig here.
-  Step back. It's dangerous.
I'll dig deep at once.
- Here we go.
-  Come on.
(Will they catch crabs this time?)
(We don't want to dig up nothing any more.)
- Yes!
-  Okay!
(We got you!)
- It's really big.
-  What is that?
- Hey, Kwang Soo.
-  Great.
- Yes.
-  It's really big.
- Wow.
-  What is that?
- Hey, Kwang Soo.
-  Jae Seok is really good.
- Did you see that?
-  You're really good.
- It gave me the chills.
-  It's a crab.
You're a real crab hunter.
- Did you catch it?
-  I really got the chills.
- Amazing.
-  Look. It's dancing.
- That's big enough to serve five.
-  Seriously,
- it's a king crab.
-  It's like we're at a crab buffet.
- Where is the next spot?
-  It's as big as a lobster.
Okay, give me the way. Let's go.
This hole is big.
- This is the spot.
-  Dig in.
- Kwang Soo. Come.
-  This hole is big.
- Hey, look.
-  Get ready.
- How many minutes do we have?
-  It's here!
- Where?
-  It's right here.
- It's big.
-  Yes. It's big.
(The crab hunter has done it again.)
- It's here.
-  Where is it?
- It's right here.
-  Hurry. Catch it.
- Here.
-  I got it.
It's not moving.
- Here's another.
-  Where?
(Come grab a crab.)
- It's solid.
-  Kwang Soo.
Seok Jin. Don't just stand there and help him.
Okay.
That's why we get penalised all the time.
There's always a reason.
- I found one.
-  Where?
- I got it.
-  Good job.
You need to catch some, too, Seok Jin.
I have sharp eyes, just like an eagle.
(They make a really nice team for crab hunting.)
We only needed Kwang Soo and me to come here.
Is it over?
Were we able to catch 20?
All right. Let's count them.
Put all the crabs that you caught...
in the plastic box in front of you.
We can cook a crab dish with these.
- Look at this. One.
-  One.
- I don't think there are 20.
-  It tried to bite me.
- They're so small.
-  Two.
They can be hiding.
- It must be really small.
-  Three.
- Four.
-  Four.
Six.
How did you catch a crab like this?
- 14.
-  Here's another.
- 15.
-  15.
- 16.
-  That's right.
- 17.
-  17.
(They are focusing really hard.)
Gosh.
- No way.
-  That big one.
Wait.
I think three of them...
Why aren't you touching the big ones?
- I'm scared.
-  Because it's scary.
Put it on top of this.
(They use the fat to pick it up.)
- Oh, my.
-  It's scary, isn't it?
We only picked up small ones.
It's so big and clearly visible, but no one's grabbing it.
We have many things in common, such as this.
- I'm scared.
-  We all are.
- It bites.
-  Be careful.
- Careful.
-  Move. Let's do it like this.
- I'll do it.
-  It has big claws.
It's big enough to serve many.
So we only need one more crab. Don't we?
(They just counted the 19th crab.)
- Look. What is this?
-  There's one more.
- Where is it?
-  There. Right there.
- It's really there.
-  It's amazing.
It's really amazing. We need to film it closely.
It's amazingly small.
(It's an extremely small, micro crab.)
- This may...
-  What is it?
- Can you see it?
-  This?
It's a crab. Can you see it?
- Is it a biological crab?
-  It is.
This is the one, right?
- It's a crab.
-  It fell down.
It really is a crab. It's a crab. That's amazing.
(They successfully catch 20 crabs.)
I should give them this fat so they can eat it.
Do they eat this? Do they eat fat?
(Actually, that fat is...)
(to lure crabs into a trap.)
- Really? No way.
-  Amazing.
- Wait. Do you really mean it?
-  Yes.
- Shall we give it a try?
-  I'm curious.
- No way.
-  I've never heard such thing.
But it takes around a day.
- Nonsense.
-  What are you doing?
Do you want to fight me in the mudflat?
Are you teasing us?
(I just told you the truth.)
(Fat Trap: If you bury a bowl and put fat in, it'll lure crabs.)
- You succeeded, so...
-  Okay.
I'll give you the chance to draw a card.
I'm not so confident about this.
- I don't think we should.
-  Can you choose one for us?
- I'll draw one, then.
-  Yes. Please draw one for us.
We're all unlucky.
(Producer Park So Hyun will draw.)
- No, not that one.
-  I don't think that's the one.
You shouldn't participate in the draw.
- She's new.
-  I can see the wrong ones.
Please draw any, Producer Park.
Okay. Good.
This is Producer Park's choice.
All three of us are unlucky.
We didn't participate at all.
Let's see what her choice is.
How old are you again?
- She's not good.
-  We mustn't ask her again.
- No, this is invalid.
-  It's invalid.
- Because you drew this card.
-  We were supposed to draw.
We must draw our card.
Why are you meddling in our own problems?
- Wait. This must be invalid.
-  No way.
- Producer Park, we decided that...
-  This isn't right.
we will draw the card.
- Put this card back in the deck.
-  Okay. We'll draw again.
Which card will you choose? What's your guess?
- I'd choose this one.
-  This? Let's remove this one.
Shall we pick a card each?
- Let's do rock-paper-scissors.
-  Rock-paper-scissors, Kwang Soo.
- The winner's card.
-  We'll go with the winner's card.
- Let's go.
-  Rock, paper, scissors.
- Rock, paper, scissors.
(Seok Jin wins.)
(What is Seok Jin's card?)
I'm sorry, guys.
- No way.
-  I'm sorry.
(It's the No Chance Card.)
(Seok Jin is always unlucky.)
My goodness.
- Maybe they're all No Chance Cards.
-  No. Open them.
- No way.
-  No way.
(What are the other cards?)
(It's a Location Card.)
(Oh my goodness.)
We're really unlucky.
How can this be?
Why is it? It's a mystery.
We need to hire someone to find out why.
(Blue Team fails to acquire a card.)
- How can this happen?
-  It doesn't make any sense.
- We're just unlucky.
-  How does this happen?
We should've gotten a card.
We failed to pick a card twice in a row.
Where should we head next?
- Where else do we need to go?
-  The strawberry farm is nearby.
- Let's go.
-  Let's go pick them.
- It's 6, 1, 1.
-  It's 1, 1.
- Yes?
-  Hello.
Blue Team, your next destination is...
the bee farm.
- Really?
-  Don't we have a choice?
White Team...
won their game...
and used the Location Card. So you must go to the bee farm.
I caught it again. Isn't this too easy? Goodness.
Oh, dear.
Goodness.
You can do it. There you go.
- Let's go.
-  Hyo Seong is watching.
Good job.
- We're done!
-  It's done!
- You've passed.
-  Aren't we amazing?
- Can I see it?
-  Yes.
(White Team picks a card.)
- It's a Location Card.
-  All right.
You can pick the other team's next location...
and disrupt their plans.
- Should we go with the bee farm?
-  Should we?
- Okay.
-  We pick the bee farm.
- Sure.
-  All right!
- That's great!
-  Awesome!
- This is great!
-  Let's go!
Just feed us stinky tofu!
(You scoundrels!)
They won the game.
Our team is cursed!
- We need Hwang Jung Min here.
-  My goodness.
We need a shaman here.
We really need a shaman here.
This is where "The Wailing" is really taking place.
This is insane.
- I can't believe this.
-  I wanted to avoid the bee farm.
What if we get stung by a bee?
I didn't even think about that.
I'm more upset at that team...
because we're right by the strawberry farm.
- It's near here.
-  Is it?
- This is the farthest from here.
-  Really?
Why did you have to dip the strawberries in honey?
Oh, gosh.
(Strawberries and honey are delicious.)
- That was for dessert.
-  Why would you?
Who dips strawberries in honey?
You're a troublemaker.
I didn't even see the honey.
Am I a troublemaker for dipping strawberries in honey?
My gosh.
Are you saying you're not?
Isn't that causing trouble?
We have to hurry up...
or we'll have to eat stinky tofu.
We have sea sickness...
(They can't go fishing due to sea sickness.)
And we can't go on rides because we'll throw up.
We're afraid of heights...
and scared that the crabs will bite.
I'm also scared of the dark.
Oh, gosh. Why was I born like this?
My goodness.
(They approach the bee farm.)
- It's the bee farm.
-  We're really here.
How are we supposed to do that?
I've never done this before.
Must we do this?
It's because you dipped strawberries in honey!
The staff members didn't do anything wrong,
and they look like they're in a warfare.
(The staff members brace themselves.)
(They're fully equipped.)
(You may enter, but you won't be able to get out easily.)
- I see bees already.
-  There are a lot of them.
What are we supposed to do?
We'll get stung as soon as we open the door.
We'll get stung as soon as we get out.
We're going to get stung by the bees.
There are bees out here.
We can't get off.
How's this different from going into lava?
I can clearly see the bees outside. How am I supposed to get off?
- There are bees outside!
-  They're everywhere.
They want us to get stung.
Give us the clothes.
They're not aggressive so you can get off.
How do you know how they are?
Are you friends with them?
This is driving me nuts.
Hey, Kwang Soo.
- This is your fault.
-  We'll stay in the car...
- and you can go.
-  Bring us the clothes.
Bring us the honey.
Hurry up.
- How?
-  You...
What do you mean?
You're a devil!
How could you say that?
There are bees everywhere.
- We're in trouble.
-  Look at those bees.
- Where are the clothes?
-  Look at the bees.
- We have to cover up first.
-  Hurry up.
- Hold on. Don't bees...
-  Don't they like yellow?
- like this colour?
-  It's the colour of honey.
Why do you get green, but we get yellow?
This is the colour of forsythias.
It looks sweet.
- Come on, Kwang Soo.
-  Kwang Soo, you brat.
(Kwang Soo, you rascal.)
We have to change quickly.
Isn't this too small?
Is it supposed to stick to your body?
My nose is pressed down. What about you?
(He can't breathe.)
- Why is this so tight?
-  It's because you have a big nose.
It doesn't cover my ankles.
- And...
-  My ankles might get stung.
(Kwang Soo is exposed.)
(He gets his ankles taped.)
Let's go together.
We're such cowards.
You're fully equipped.
Are you wearing boots?
They look like boots.
- It's necessary.
-  I have a trauma.
I've been stung by a hornet twice.
What do you not have a trauma about?
(Jae Seok is full of traumas.)
You have a bunch of traumas.
Why did you dip it in honey?
- He has traumas about everything.
-  Kwang Soo.
Why did you dip it in honey?
Let's get started quickly.
The other team...
- is ahead of us.
-  Let's pick the Location Card...
- and make them suffer.
-  Exactly.
Let's send them to the most difficult one.
Let's get going.
(The bees work hard...)
(and make honey.)
Look at this, Jae Seok.
- My gosh.
-  Be quiet.
- Wow.
-  Oh my goodness.
There are about 30,000 to 50,000 bees in each box.
You have to create fumes first.
This is mugwort.
You create smoke.
(Smoke is created by burning mugwort.)
- I can smell it.
-  Let's close it.
(Bees don't like the smell of mugwort.)
- Hold the brush.
-  I smell it.
- All right.
-  Is this it?
Hold onto it.
Let me calm them down.
Stop taking all the easy jobs.
- Should I open the lid?
-  Sure.
Is this it?
(Yelling)
Why? What's wrong?
- Hold on. There are so many.
-  There are too many of them.
- What should we do?
-  What do we do now?
- Should I open it?
-  Before you open it,
do this first.
(They open it slightly.)
That's insane.
Spray it!
Hey, slow down.
Slow down.
- Oh, gosh.
-  I'm sorry, bees.
- Slow down.
-  Sorry.
Watch this.
Listen to the sound.
- Are they mad?
-  Wow.
- What do you do now?
-  Is this a lot of honey?
What comes next?
You have to shake them off.
- Do you?
-  Please.
That's good.
Kwang Soo.
Would two of these fill up a container?
(Jae Seok gives it a go.)
- Do it here.
-  It's not easy.
(He has to be brave and shake the bees off.)
(Will Jae Seok be able to do it?)
There are so many of them.
(He shakes it.)
(All of the bees fly off.)
Don't do that!
- Stop doing that!
-  Hurry up!
- Don't shake it so fast!
Brush them off!
Hurry! Brush them off!
- Who told you to do that?
-  Hurry!
I think they're attacking me, Kwang Soo.
Sorry, bees.
- Oh, dear.
-  It's all good.
(These cowards are frightened.)
(They finish the first one.)
- I'm sorry, bees.
-  I'm sorry.
You punk, you shouldn't have had the honey.
- I only had a little.
-  Next.
(Kwang Soo gives it a go to make up for it.)
Oh my goodness.
- Look at this.
-  There are hundreds of them.
They look upset and aggravated.
Hurry up.
- Do I shake it now?
-  Go for it.
(Shaking)
They're aggravated.
- The smoke!
-  They're angry.
We need the smoke!
- Just shake it off!
-  It's not there.
- Hurry up!
-  We need the smoke.
- I said, hurry up!
-  The smoke!
Spray it.
Put it back in.
- I'm sorry.
-  I'm sorry for ruining your house.
They're going nuts.
- That almost got me.
-  We won't forget this.
I can't move an inch.
Hey, Jong Kook!
(White Team is on their way to catch chickens.)
Jin Goo, you picked the right team.
You got to speak to your ideal girl and you'll win as well.
Do you like cute women? How's Son Na Eun?
- I actually really like Apink.
-  Do you really?
- I really like their songs.
-  I see.
- There are a lot of them.
-  Who's your favourite in the group?
Which type of woman do you like from Apink?
- Who do you think is nice?
-  Who is it?
I...
(It's okay, you can tell us.)
like Ha Young.
(Is it Ha Young?)
- It's Oh Ha Young, right?
-  Yes.
- She's the youngest in the group.
-  That's right.
Let me make a call again.
- It's all right.
-  Let me just ask her.
- Go ahead.
-  No, it's okay.
I find it funny how you were trying to act like you don't know her.
I know, right?
You probably know everything about her. Look at this guy.
- He does.
-  Hello?
Hey, Bo Mi.
- Hey, Haha.
-  Are you busy?
We're shooting Running Man right now.
- Hi, Bo Mi!
-  Are you?
- It's about Ha Young.
-  Okay.
What type of men does she like?
(His heart is pounding.)
- Ha Young?
-  Yes.
(Ha Young?)
She likes men like Lee Min Ki...
Does she like Jin Goo, by any chance?
(What about Jin Goo?)
- Yeo Jin Goo?
-  Yes.
Ha Young is downstairs. Should I get her?
- Okay!
-  Yes!
- Hold on.
-  Okay.
This is perfect.
- My goodness.
-  Hello.
Hello, Ha Young.
- Hello.
-  Hello.
- Who's this?
-  Talk to her.
- Come on.
-  My name is Yeo Jin Goo.
You're lying! Aren't you Kwang Soo?
(Are you Kwang Soo?)
Ha Young.
It is Jin Goo.
It is Jin Goo. Don't regret it later.
- Ha Young.
-  I don't think so.
Let's not drag this on. We'll do this only once.
We're going to play a game of telepathy.
(Jin Goo and Ha Young will play a game.)
- Sure.
-  Is it jjamppong or jajangmyeon?
You'll pick one after I count down.
All right, the two of you. This is a game of telepathy.
Do you prefer jjamppong or jajangmyeon?
In one, two, three!
(Is it jjamppong or jajangmyeon?)
(He signals her to choose jajangmyeon.)
In one, two, three!
- Jajangmyeon.
-  Jajangmyeon.
(They chose the same one.)
It's meant to be!
Look at this. I'm getting goosebumps!
(Jin Goo's heart is racing.)
- Right?
-  I'm getting goosebumps.
Before you go, he wants to say something.
- That's right.
-  Go for jajangmyeon.
- Let's have jajangmyeon later.
-  Excellent.
- Perfect.
-  This is great.
Are you really Jin Goo?
- It is.
-  It is me.
Any time. I know a good restaurant.
- Oh, wow.
-  Thank you.
That's great.
If you say, "Mr Chu",
Jin Goo will say, "Chu".
You can sing a line,
and he'll say "Chu". Then we hang up.
- Mr Chu
-  Chu
- Chu on my lips
(Mr Chu, chu on my lips.)
(How's this possible?)
(Ha Young makes him smile.)
We'll call you another time.
- Yes.
-  Bye.
This is perfect.
(I'll see you at the jajangmyeon restaurant.)
This is great.
- I should let Hyo Seong know now.
-  My gosh.
(I forgot about Hyo Seong.)
- You guys should just be friends.
-  You're mean.
- I feel bad for her.
-  You could be...
- good friends with her.
-  That's right.
- Hyo Seong.
-  Yes.
It's about Jin Goo, but don't get offended.
Do you know of Ha Young from Apink?
- Apink?
-  Yes, she's the youngest member.
He's already moved on to her.
Did he change his mind?
"Did he change his mind?"
But you two can be good friends.
You'll be like a family. Let's keep it that way.
(Let's root for each other.)
How did this happen out of nowhere?
(I need to hear an explanation.)
She's disappointed.
- You're disappointed, right?
-  She is.
Jin Goo wants to say sorry. Hold on.
Say something, Jin Goo.
All right. Hyo Seong, you have to treat me next time.
(You still need to buy me dinner.)
You're quite funny, aren't you?
(You're a funny kid.)
(Why should I treat you?)
That was funny. Good one.
- That's enough.
-  Leave it at that.
- That was funny.
-  "You're quite funny."
She made me laugh.
(They finally arrive at the chicken farm.)
Let's go.
Jin Goo's never caught a chicken before.
It probably hurts when they peck you.
Doesn't it hurt when they peck at you?
This is a farm where you can obtain chickens.
- You must catch them yourselves.
-  Right.
Under the heading "Wanted",
there are specific chickens that you must catch.
- You must bring them back.
-  They're marked.
- Look at the nose.
-  There's a heart.
- That's a plus sign.
-  There's the plus sign...
- and this one's just white.
-  It's a white string.
All right, I get it.
There are 60 chickens inside the fences.
You have three minutes.
- Three minutes?
-  Aren't we using bare hands?
How are we supposed to catch them?
(This one's huge.)
Those are huge. Look at the black one.
- Get set, go!
-  Hold on.
Look first. We have to search for them first.
Look. It's not this one.
- Gosh, look at this one.
-  It's not that one.
- What's this?
-  I think that's it.
- I think it's this one.
-  This one?
Try catching it.
- Which one?
-  It's a triangle.
- Isn't that it?
-  Look at its claws.
- What now?
-  I can't see the marks.
I'm going nuts.
Hey, don't do that. I'm scared.
(He's startled.)
Come this way.
They hide so well amongst themselves.
(Swift)
(Aren't they fast enough to be ostriches?)
(Come on, chickens.)
(He spots one!)
I found Kkomi.
Did you find it?
(It's similar to the picture.)
- It's Kkomi.
-  That's it.
Run. Catch it!
(It's fast.)
It's so fast.
(It takes a sharp turn.)
- Haha, it's this one.
-  Where?
Wait, I'll corner it.
- Oh, gosh.
-  Goodness.
(You're such rookies.)
Hey, hey.
(Jin Goo corners it.)
- Block that side.
-  I got it.
I got this side. Catch it. You got it.
(They succeed!)
You got it! Go.
You got it.
(It's caught.)
- Let me see the mark.
-  It's Kkomi.
You're correct!
(They are a match.)
- You have one minute left.
-  What do we do?
- Isn't this it?
-  Where?
Is it a heart?
- It has a heart.
-  It's that one!
(It runs for its life.)
Catch it for me. It's that one!
- Catch it.
-  It's that one, right?
- It's that one.
-  Is it the right one?
- It's this one.
-  This one.
It's this one.
(He catches it in one try.)
You're amazing, Jong Kook.
(Jong Kook is so talented.)
Take the wing.
Is this right? It is.
(They have 15 seconds left. This is their last chance.)
- It's correct, right?
-  Yes, you got it!
(They are a match.)
That wasn't easy.
- We're awesome.
-  Good job.
- How did you do that?
-  How did you catch it?
I can't believe I've been working with him for six years.
I respect him so much.
Jin Goo, you caught one in the beginning.
He's in a great mood, so why don't we do an acrostic poem?
Your word is "Chicken", Jin Goo.
In 1, 2, 3. "Chick".
"Chick".
("Chick")
Shut your mouth?
(Shut your mouth.)
- Stop it.
-  Shut your mouth.
- All of you, shut your mouth.
-  That's funny.
You've completed the mission, so you'll pick a card.
- We're too strong.
-  Pick...
- a card.
-  They'll never pass this mission.
- All right.
-  There you go.
That one's good.
As long as it's not a No Chance Card, it's fine.
- Please.
-  Open it.
(What did he choose?)
(Is he astonished?)
- Please.
-  Open it.
- It's a Free Card.
-  It's a Free Card.
- Do we win an ingredient?
-  Yes.
Okay!
That's perfect. He picked a good one.
- We'll take crabs.
-  Let's cross that out.
We are not going to catch crabs.
(White Team has eel, crab and chicken.)
I'm getting sleepy.
Do you make ramyeon on the boat?
(They make 3 bags of ramyeon with shrimp.)
(It's seafood ramyeon.)
Oh, yes.
- Oh my goodness.
-  Look at the shrimps.
(Ramyeon on the boat has a strong fragrance of the sea.)
Thank you for the food.
(Slurping)
This is no joke.
It's delicious.
(You have to try this.)
(He peeks at the fishing rods while they eat.)
Is there more?
- Where?
-  That one's moving.
(Did it move?)
Is it mine?
(Ji Hyo is quick to get up.)
Sir, it feels loose.
No, it can't be.
I caught something, Gary!
(Something's on the hook!)
Gary! Gary!
- Gary!
-  No!
- This can't be!
-  I caught a fish!
(Shrieking)
- Captain, I'm scared!
-  Be careful! Watch the ramyeon!
- Captain, Captain!
-  Don't drop it in the ramyeon!
I'm so scared.
What do I do?
(It's a big catch.)
(Will I ever beat Ji Hyo?)
You said this side was better.
Why did she catch it over there?
(Sighing)
I lost again.
You're good to go. You're always lucky.
(Ji Hyo goes ashore first.)
- I'm leaving.
-  See you, Ji Hyo.
- Bye.
-  What are you doing next week?
- Next week?
-  I'll face you again next week.
Okay, Ji Hyo?
(Waving)
I'll see you next week!
Gary, cheer up!
(He's no rival to the lucky Ji Hyo.)
Why can I never beat her?
(He cannot fall behind. He must hurry.)
(He gives it a big swing.)
(He casts 5 fishing rods into the water.)
If I can't catch anything like this, it means I'm cursed.
(Let's wait and see.)
(I wish luck is on my side.)
(He watches like a hawk.)
(At that moment!)
(It moves.)
I got it. I'm certain.
It's coming along!
It's biting! Please don't swim away!
This one's strong! It's strong!
(What has Gary caught?)
(It's a big catch.)
(He catches a bigger fish than what he ate earlier.)
(A squid catches a fish.)
I caught it right away.
(Both teams manage to catch fish.)
We're done with that part.
(Blue Team is still collecting honey.)
Are we removing the by-products?
- Yes.
-  You have to make a path...
- for the honey to flow.
-  You have to skim off the layer.
This knife is hot.
- Is this edible?
-  Yes it is.
This is beeswax.
Is this beeswax?
- The honey is dripping.
-  Look at the honey.
- Look.
-  It's full.
It melts when you put the hot knife to it.
This is amazing.
Ouch! It's inside my body.
- Really?
-  Where?
- It's inside of me.
-  You're joking.
- I'm not.
-  Where?
Where?
- It's not inside.
-  It's stuck to your head.
You coward.
I swear it hit me with its wings.
It hit you like this?
What a joke. Please understand him.
I apologise.
- It's really in there!
-  Is it?
(Has it gone through the suit?)
(The bee is inside.)
It's inside, Jae Seok!
- Is it? Where?
-  You didn't believe me.
- How did it make it in there?
-  I might get stung.
(The bee breaks through the protective layer.)
(They need a countermeasure in place.)
(What? What's this?)
(Seok Jin sprays him.)
- No, Jae Seok! Don't do that.
-  Where is it?
- Hurry.
-  Don't move.
Hey, hey. Why would you open this completely?
Do it quickly! Come on!
- I'm almost done.
-  The bees are...
flying around me.
- There was no bee.
-  What are you doing? No, there was.
- There's a bee.
-  Do it quickly!
(He's in a hurry.)
- Gosh.
-  You just laughed, didn't you?
- There really was one.
-  How did it get in there?
- Look at this.
-  I don't understand.
How did it get in there?
I don't know either.
Then let me spin this.
Spin it. Jae Seok.
That's too fast.
Slow down.
- It's coming.
-  It is.
It's coming out.
This must be very sweet.
- It's amazing.
-  This is real honey.
This is real, isn't it?
Kwang Soo, let's visit the strawberry farm after this.
Sounds good.
Let's take some of the honey and dip strawberries in it.
Wow, that's a lot.
(Blue Team obtains honey.)
- Now's the time to get a card.
-  Okay.
Why don't you pick one?
- What if we fail again?
-  No way.
(Will they be unlucky again?)
Take one card for yourself.
- Remove one card.
-  Okay.
I removed one card for you.
I should think before I pick. I was so thoughtless before.
- Right.
-  Yes.
For your information, the card I removed is a Location Card.
(It's a Location Card.)
We need to get it right this time.
There are two chance cards out of the three.
- What's important is...
-  We should pick a chance card.
Let's do this.
If you are not confident, just give up.
If you are confident, stay here.
I'm out.
- Really?
-  Yes.
- Show me your card.
-  Show it to us.
One, two...
(Which card does he have?)
- It's a Free Card.
-  My goodness.
(We're so unlucky.)
This is not good.
(He's totally unlucky.)
This is crazy. I should've had the No Chance Card.
There's one Steal Card and one No Chance Card.
- We can steal something with it.
-  This is unbelievable.
Please! We must pick the Steal Card.
- Forget about being funny.
-  How about rock-paper-scissors?
Let's pick the loser's card.
- Let's pick the loser's card.
-  Rock-paper-scissors!
Jae Seok lost.
- Do you want to switch?
-  Okay.
(They decide to exchange.)
(What will be the result?)
We're done for if we don't get the Steal Card.
(Will their unlucky fortune continue?)
(Or will they be able to catch up with the Steal Card?)
(Steal Card)
(This is a jackpot!)
- Great.
-  We made it.
It's good that we exchanged our cards.
If we didn't, we'd be doomed.
- We're destined to get this card.
-  We should always exchange cards.
We must switch our cards.
- It was a good choice.
-  We can change our fate!
We should exchange our cards at the last minute.
- Let's not catch eels.
-  White Team will go there.
(Blue Team takes White Team's eels.)
(Blue Team obtains honey and takes eels from White Team.)
The strawberries are very fresh. We can eat them now.
- Wow, there are cows.
-  Right.
(White Team obtains milk.)
Can I pick this from the root, Ma'am?
These grow a lot in summer, right?
This game is called "Vegetable Halli Galli".
(Both teams meet at the vegetable farm.)
- Okay!
-  What are you doing?
You did great.
You're so good at this.
Since White Team won,
we'll give you a chance to pick a card.
(What card did White Team pick?)
(The "Ingredient Gathering War" is over.)
I can drink the tea.
You should eat the stinky tofu.
- Wow, this is honey.
-  Great.
Please put them on the table.
You've put all the ingredients on the table.
- Please look at the board.
-  Okay.
White Team brought...
fish, chicken, crab, milk and vegetables.
- Okay.
-  Blue Team brought...
crab, fish, honey, eels,
- strawberries and vegetables
-  Right. We have one more than them.
- We haven't opened our card yet.
-  Oh, the card?
It can be the No Chance Card.
- It shouldn't be the Steal Card.
-  Then we'll be fine.
- Please pick the No Chance Card.
-  Please.
- Open it now.
-  No Chance Card!
- No Chance Card!
-  Don't let it be the Steal Card.
- I think they have the Steal Card.
-  Goodness.
In 1, 2, 3!
(What...)
(card...)
(will it be?)
(It has to be Steal Card.)
(It's Steal Card!)
Ji Hyo is a lucky girl!
- Is it the Steal Card?
-  Yes.
- It's unbelievable.
-  My goodness.
- It's amazing.
-  Goodness.
- I didn't know I'd pick that card.
-  That's amazing.
Can you believe this?
Can you?
- Let's steal eels.
-  What about honey?
- We caught eels.
-  Let's take eels.
- Give them eels.
-  Okay. Take eels.
- This is...
-  Hey, take our eels.
To the White Team who won,
- we'll give...
-  What?
- an advantage...
-  Is there something else?
- for the final round.
-  That's not necessary.
- Good! We got an advantage.
-  This is great.
- What is this?
-  What's that?
(White Team has an advantage.)
(What will it be?)
This is for you.
(Revival Card)
- Wow.
-  Revival Card?
- I don't know what this is for.
-  Is it okay to show this to them?
- Gosh.
-  Can we revive with this?
There's no one to revive on that team.
- It's our team that needs the card.
-  They don't need it.
Many of us need to revive.
They don't need the card at all!
- They won't die.
-  We can die.
- This is ridiculous.
-  That card is to revive the dead.
- They're not dead yet.
-  Look at Gary.
- I'm lost for words.
-  What is this?
I am really angry.
I can see how angry he is.
I am really mad.
Since you had a long day acquiring the ingredients,
we've invited special guests...
to cheer you up.
Really?
- Really?
-  Where are they?
- There they are.
-  Wow!
This is unbelievable!
(Am I dreaming now?)
- Wow!
-  Welcome!
(The atmosphere is freshened.)
(It's TWICE who topped various music charts with "CHEER UP".)
- Wow, It's TWICE.
-  This is great.
- Good to see you.
-  Hello.
- Hello.
-  Welcome to Running Man.
- It's so nice to see you.
-  Hello.
- Hello.
-  Isn't it cold?
- Wow.
-  Hello.
In 1, 2, 3. One in a million. Hello, we're TWICE!
Wow.
("CHEER UP" captivated everyone's ears.)
(They've made all the guys fall for them.)
(The 9 members each have different charms.)
Wow, here you are!
You're very cute and pretty!
- They're cute.
-  I'm not tired any more.
We can sing TWICE's songs as much as we want and enjoy.
- Right.
-  But Jin Goo can't.
-  That's sad.
- Why can't he enjoy them?
-  It'd be hard for him.
- I see.
-  He talked about Ha Young.
- This isn't easy for him.
-  He said he talked to her.
My goodness.
- Ha Young thanked me.
-  Right.
- Ha Young is attractive.
-  He's cute.
- We'll make teams.
-  Okay.
To be fair,
those who choose the same colour will form a team.
Pick one, Jeongyeon.
He knows each member's name.
She picked a white spoon.
- Good choice.
-  Great.
It's Tzuyu's turn.
(Tzuyu also picks a white spoon.)
- Great!
-  Good.
- Nice.
-  You did a good job.
- Done!
-  Let's go play the game.
This will be fun.
Sana is in our team.
(TWICE members are split between the teams.)
Let me announce the final mission.
(What will this big group do?)
- "Dangerous Recipes".
-  "Dangerous Recipes"?
- He's a dangerous director.
-  He loves dangerous missions.
Why is everything so dangerous?
Today's final mission is "Dangerous Recipes".
Blue Team with nine members...
should complete recipes for Western dishes.
And White Team with eight members...
will complete recipes for Korean dishes.
Please discuss with your members and hide the ingredients...
that the other team needs under your name tags.
When we give the start signal, you'll play Name Tag Elimination...
and take the ingredients which are under others' name tags.
Then, complete the recipe first with the ingredients you get.
The team to finish first wins.
We have three butter and milk ingredients.
They should be put on those who can defend themselves well.
- Jin Goo...
-  Salmon.
I'll hide broccoli.
Momo, come here.
Hide this under the tag.
Gosh.
(Bumping)
You focused all your attention on TWICE, didn't you?
Don't embarrass us in front of TWICE!
Please don't do this.
- This is your problem.
-  You can't come this close!
You shot me from a distance at the bee farm!
This is a serious problem.
A member from each team...
will have Pepper Bombs under their name tags.
If anyone eliminates the Pepper Bomb name tag,
the team he or she is on will lose immediately.
- Really?
-  Immediately?
(Pepper Bomb is very dangerous!)
Wow, this is unexpected.
They can't use the Revival Card, can they?
- Pepper Bomb! Pepper Bomb!
-  Pepper Bomb! Pepper Bomb!
-  Then...
we should be careful with ripping.
Today's highlight is...
- It's the Pepper Bomb.
-  Yes, it's the Pepper Bomb.
- In 1, 2, 3. Let's go!
-  We can do it!
(Which team will get the penalty?)
Let's go for it.
- We can do it.
-  Okay. Let's Go!
- We must win this time.
-  We should.
- We should find the lunchbox first.
-  Right.
- Let's find the blue one.
-  Right, the blue one.
We're looking for a lunchbox. Tell me if you find one.
(They look for Pepper Bomb hints.)
What should I do? Do I just look around?
Take a close look like this.
(The hint informs of the other team's Pepper Bomb.)
You'll find it somewhere.
Do they usually hide things behind water purifiers?
We must win.
(Dahyun searches thoroughly.)
What is behind this?
Where is the lunchbox?
(Where are you, lunchbox?)
Excuse me.
Even though I might fail to eliminate name tags,
- I want to find a lunchbox.
-  Me, too.
(TWICE politely keeps searching for a lunchbox.)
Nothing is there. I've already checked.
I'm sure something is near here.
No, no.
- I think it could be here.
-  It can't be here.
No, it's not in a big place like this.
It's not here.
Is the lunchbox here?
(She starts talking to the cameraman.)
- Is it here?
-  It's not here.
- Is it not here?
-  It's not in...
- a big space like this.
-  It's here, isn't it?
- Is it really not here?
-  It should be somewhere small.
I think it's here.
My intuition tells me it's here.
I'm just going to rip a name tag first.
- Already?
-  Yes.
What if you get Pepper Bomb?
(What if he picks Pepper Bomb?)
The chances are too low.
(There is a 1 out of 9 chance of getting it.)
I still won't do it...
because I am unlucky.
First of all, we have to collect many recipes.
(Gary thinks they must rush.)
That's one way.
It'd be helpful if we knew their gender.
Someone's coming.
It's Ji Hyo.
- Should we rip her name tag?
-  Let's rip it.
- Where are you going?
-  This building.
So one of you is not the Pepper Bomb for sure.
Who knows?
At least one of you isn't.
Why? You must be the Pepper Bomb.
That's why you're filled with confidence.
- You are the Pepper Bomb.
-  No.
It's positive that one of you isn't.
Okay. Try ripping us then.
Kwang Soo, you can rip it.
I can't do it because of our past relationship.
What are you talking about?
- We had a past, you know?
-  What are you talking about?
If I do it and fail, you will blame it on me.
- No!
-  So is that it?
So you are the Pepper Bomb.
Should we begin by ripping name tags?
I don't think neither of them has the Pepper Bomb.
- I know.
-  Anyway...
(At that moment,)
(Jong Kook and Tzuyu come to rescue them.)
- I think it's Kwang Soo.
-  First...
Anyway...
- I don't think it's him.
-  He's here, he's here.
- Jong Kook is here.
-  Oh, dear.
-  I think it's Kwang Soo.
- What should we do?
-  Let's run.
Then we should've run immediately!
- We should've done that!
-  So run faster!
What's wrong?
Jong Kook, Kwang Soo is the Pepper Bomb.
Do you think it's Kwang Soo?
(I will sprinkle pepper on you.)
He's coming! He's running!
Hurry up!
(It's like a conditioned reflex.)
- Why are you...
-  Why are we running away?
- Jong Kook is coming.
-  What is it for?
Why are we running away?
- Jong Kook must be the bomb.
-  But we are four.
- It's the four of us.
-  He must be it.
- We're four people. Let's not run.
-  He might be the Pepper Bomb.
- I'm certain that he's not.
-  Really?
(What is Jong Kook's identity?)
Actually, this is yours.
(30 minutes ago at White Team's strategy meeting)
(It's the card that could instantly change everything.)
(White Team made Jong Kook the Pepper Bomb.)
- He might be the Pepper Bomb.
-  I'm certain that he's not.
They can't rip our name tags for sure.
- It's because...
-  That's not it.
It could be Tzuyu.
Maybe it's Tzuyu and Jong Kook is just guarding her.
Right. That's possible.
But if she's the Pepper Bomb, they don't need to be together.
Maybe they're trying to fake it.
They made it really easy to rip Jong Kook's name tag.
It could be Tzuyu.
(While Jong Kook and Tzuyu distract them,)
Let's go find some hints.
(Jin Goo and Dahyun look for hints.)
(They search carefully.)
- I think they hid it around here.
-  Right?
- I think so.
-  I have that feeling.
- Why?
-  It's here.
I found it.
- I found it.
-  Did you find it?
(They finally found it.)
(Blue Team's Pepper Bomb is a man.)
- It's a man?
-  It's a man.
(Who are the men on the Blue Team?)
We have to let everyone know.
There is Jae Seok, Kwang Soo,
- Gary and Seok Jin.
-  Seok Jin.
- It's one of those four.
-  It's one of them.
So we have to hurry up and tell everybody.
(TWICE is not the Pepper Bomb.)
Let's hurry up and tell the others that the Pepper Bomb is a man.
It should be around here, but it's not.
Why isn't it here?
Isn't this it?
(He finds the lunchbox!)
I got it.
(He found it!)
- What is it?
-  "Blue Team's Pepper Bomb..."
I knew it.
Blue Team's Pepper Bomb is a Running Man member.
- Then it could be Kwang Soo.
-  Kwang Soo.
- He was approaching us fiercely.
-  Should we destroy this?
It wouldn't be here, would it?
(Chaeyoung and Sana try to find a lunchbox, too.)
- It's not in here, right?
-  I don't think it's there.
Where should we go?
(At that moment, Jin Goo and Dahyun appear.)
(Oh my gosh!)
What? Why?
(The first battle breaks out.)
Don't do this to us!
(Sana is driven into a corner.)
Don't do this to me! Where are you going, Chaeyoung?
- Chaeyoung, don't go.
-  I am sorry, Sana.
(Sorry, Sana.)
What's wrong?
Chaeyoung, be careful.
(Chaeyoung barely got away.)
- Jin Goo is here.
-  I'm scared.
- He ran as soon as he saw me.
-  Jin Goo is here.
Are you going to touch me?
Kwang Soo is coming.
(They rip her name tag.)
- Let's go.
-  Let's go.
- Let's go!
-  Chaeyoung!
(You're late!)
Did they rip your name tag?
I got ripped.
Chaeyoung abandoned me.
I ripped It. I ripped it!
I'm sorry, Sana.
I am sorry.
Sana is out.
- They're so quick.
-  It's all right, Sana.
(Sana was the cabbage.)
Sana is out.
(Oh my gosh!)
Why?
- Sana, you were cabbage, right?
-  There was only one cabbage.
There was only one cabbage. Kimchijjigae.
Watch out for chilli, garlic and pork.
Cabbage.
We got just one.
- We got Sana.
-  Chilli, garlic and pork.
(White Team gets cabbage.)
Okay. Let's get more.
They're here.
Yes. That's it!
Don't run.
- What are you?
-  I am the Pepper Bomb.
- I know.
-  I really am the Pepper Bomb.
- I know that.
-  I'm really the Pepper Bomb.
- I'm the Pepper Bomb.
-  Give it to me. I'm sorry.
I'm serious.
Don't do it. Don't.
I am the Pepper Bomb.
(She lies down on the floor to guard her name tag.)
- Okay.
-  Look at the girls.
(Getting up)
These girls are unbelievable.
- Gosh.
-  They are unbelievable.
There.
(They must rip TWICE's name tags.)
Run.
- Tzuyu, rip their name tags.
-  We have to rip them.
- Tzuyu, hurry up.
-  Tzuyu!
No!
- Tzuyu.
-  Rip it.
Catch her.
- Tzuyu.
-  Let's get it over with.
(She appeals to him by acting cute.)
Oh, gosh!
- Please grab her.
-  No!
No!
(It's a mess.)
- We have to rip her name tag.
-  Hold on.
Please hold me.
- Oh, gosh.
-  It's okay.
(Jin Goo comes to help.)
(What?)
(These girls used to be...)
(very elegant.)
(They are brawling fiercely.)
(They are so persistent.)
(They are tough.)
(I'm not used to seeing them like this.)
Move.
- I will do it.
-  Rip it.
(Momo is cleaning the floor with her body.)
(They scare me.)
- Rip it!
-  I am sorry.
No. No.
(While Jin Goo hesitates, someone else rips her name tag.)
(Tzuyu ripped it!)
I got it!
(He's shocked.)
I got Nayeon's.
(Momo is out.)
- I got Nayeon's, too.
-  Her tag got ripped.
- Look at her hair.
-  Are you okay?
- I will take this.
-  No.
(It's stuck on her hair!)
It's still on me, right?
- It didn't end yet.
-  I am sorry.
Aren't I still okay?
Momo is out.
(They get green onions.)
Oh, dear.
(They can complete jeyukbokkeum and dwenjangjjigae as well.)
- White Team got green onions.
-  This is ridiculous.
Green onions.
We got two ingredients.
(White Team is winning!)
Did I die?
Am I still alive? Yes!
I'm alive, right?
(Thanks to the name tag on her hair, she's still safe.)
It doesn't hurt at all.
Isn't it okay to move around like this?
(What?)
We need milk and...
- bacon.
-  We need bacon for carbonara.
(Blue Team needs to work harder!)
Oh my gosh.
Don't do this to me.
- I am not the only one.
-  Don't do this to me.
I think Jin Goo is the Pepper Bomb.
I am the Pepper Bomb.
I'm the Pepper Bomb, too.
(Everyone claims to be the Pepper Bomb!)
I am the Pepper Bomb.
I'm the Pepper Bomb.
(Let's see.)
It's here.
(They already know that the Pepper Bomb is a man.)
Blue Team's Pepper Bomb is a Running Man member.
(Then Chaeyoung is not the Pepper Bomb!)
Come here, Chaeyoung.
It's dangerous.
(White Team traps them.)
(Their target is Chaeyoung.)
No.
(Jae Seok tries his best to guard Chaeyoung.)
- No.
-  Get out.
- Rip her name tag.
-  I am the Pepper Bomb.
- No.
-  Let go.
- I am the Pepper Bomb.
-  Run, Chaeyoung!
(Chaeyoung is in danger!)
(Tzuyu tries to make a bold attack.)
Run, Chaeyoung.
(Did she suddenly change her target?)
- No!
-  No!
It's not him!
- No!
-  No!
It's not him!
(Jae Seok was the Pepper Bomb of Blue Team!)
(Jae Seok is out and the race is over.)
It's over.
He's the Pepper Bomb.
(How did this happen?)
What happened?
- What happened?
-  How did this happen?
(Jae Seok feels sorry.)
Tzuyu.
(She didn't know Jae Seok was the Pepper Bomb.)
- But...
-  It's better that Jae Seok gets it.
(1 hour ago during Blue Team's strategy meeting)
- Me?
-  They might...
- expect it's you. That's why.
-  They might expect it.
- I'll be the Pepper Bomb then.
-  You do it.
Jae Seok is out.
- What?
-  What?
- Jae Seok is out?
-  Jae Seok?
- Out?
-  Is Jae Seok out?
So did we win?
Did they really lose?
(Screaming)
(Blue Team is so excited after hearing their unexpected victory.)
This is amazing!
(This is the power of the Pepper Bomb!)
Who ripped his name tag?
- Yes. We won!
-  It's a miracle.
- We won!
-  What is this?
- Did we lose? Just like that?
-  Look.
I told her to rip Chaeyoung but she ripped Jae Seok.
- But no one...
-  I thought it was Kwang Soo.
Jong Kook. Kwang Soo is the Pepper Bomb. It's Kwang Soo.
Kwang Soo is the Pepper Bomb.
Blue Team's Pepper Bomb...
(As they found hints, they all guessed the Pepper Bomb...)
(to be Kwang Soo.)
(It's surely Kwang Soo.)
Should we destroy this?
- But this happened because...
-  Tzuyu can run really fast.
Tzuyu is a really good runner.
But it can't be helped.
Let's go.
(Blue Team is the winner of Dangerous Recipe.)
- That's all right.
-  It's okay.
Kwang Soo! We made it!
We did it, Kwang Soo.
- We won.
-  Who ripped your name tag?
Who ripped it? Who?
Was it Tzuyu?
(White Team has lost. Blue Team has won.)
(The truly dangerous penalty will be revealed.)
Prepare some dishes for the White Team.
- How will they eat that?
-  Blue Team members, come here.
- Amazing. This is today's penalty.
-  Dangerous Meal.
I'm so glad that I don't have to eat this.
As soon as they open that, they will not want to eat it.
In 1, 2, 3.
(What a smell!)
- What is that smell?
-  What are those?
- What is this?
-  I'll explain.
(6 different dishes that taste strong but are good for your body)
- What is that smell?
-  What are those?
- What is this?
-  I'll explain.
There's tofu inside.
I can see it, too.
They even prepared separate dishes for us.
- Is that the stinky tofu?
-  No, it's not.
- Aren't they eggs? Duck eggs.
-  They are duck eggs.
- They are fermented.
-  Why would you ferment duck eggs?
(I can't take this smell.)
- Fermented skate. Sophora root tea.
-  Sophora root tea.
I'll drink Sophora root tea.
- We also have spicy hairtail.
-  Where's the stinky tofu?
(It's so spicy it will burn your mouth.)
- It must be really sour.
-  Do I need to eat those?
- They are delicious dishes.
-  Can I start eating first?
- Yes.
-  Okay. Get ready.
In 1, 2, 3.
- Should I eat now?
-  Yes.
- I like fermented skate.
-  In 1, 2, 3.
(Ji Hyo, who likes fermented skate, eats first.)
Wow, this one's strong.
It seems strong.
- Should I eat now?
-  Yes.
(Jong Kook drinks the tea at once.)
- Wow, this one's strong.
-  It is.
Gosh.
(Jin Goo tries the stinky tofu.)
- It's tasty.
-  How does it taste?
(This stinky tofu really stinks.)
(The members of TWICE try sophora root tea and spicy hairtail.)
How does it taste? Is it okay?
(The smell of fermented skate catches her off-guard.)
- Is it ham?
-  Ouch, my nose.
- What's the problem? Does it hurt?
-  My nose...
- My nose hurts.
-  Are you okay, Ji Hyo?
- Look at Ji Hyo.
-  Oh, my nose. Gosh.
- What happened?
-  What is this? It looks delicious.
My gosh, the smell. No, Jong Kook. No.
- No.
-  Come to think of it, I'm eating...
- It's really delicious.
-  This is...
- The taste is strong.
-  It's really strong.
Jin Goo, thank you for joining us despite your busy schedule.
And thank you to all the members of TWICE for joining us. Thank you all.
(We'd like to thank Yeo Jin Goo and TWICE for joining us.)
(Ahn Sung Ki)
(Cho Jin Woong)
(Kwon Yul, Han Ye Ri)
(They only have 8 hours.)
(They've become fugitives due to a moment's choice.)
(Run away from the chaser and grab 7,000 dollars.)
(Run away as fast as you can or chase them by any means.)
(It's a race between the hunters and fugitives.)
They got them all.
(The Hunt)