(Battle for the Centre)
(If you want to attract attention, centre is your position.)
How does it feel to sit on the throne?
Don't covet for the centre seat.
Get lost, all of you!
- My goodness.
-  She can't reach.
- You are good at this.
-  One, two, one, two.
You only care about yourself, don't you?
(Only the centre takes it all. Survive this cruel game today.)
I should receive a camera, at least.
- One!
-  I hope it turns off.
(Battle for the Centre: The One Who Holds the Throne)
(It is unusually gloomy today.)
(Today, these seven seats hold the fate of many.)
(R Hotel in Hwaseong)
Hello.
Good day.
(Kwang Soo arrives first, and he sees something strange.)
What are you doing?
What are these?
(What are these?)
(There is a cameraman for every seat.)
(Startled)
That's the throne.
- Take a seat anywhere you want.
-  Pardon?
Sit anywhere you want.
(The centre)
Then I'll sit...
(I'll sit in the centre, of course.)
This is the seat that I want to sit on.
Shouldn't I?
Would I attract too much attention?
- Hello, Gary.
-  Hello. Why are you sitting there?
You can sit anywhere you want.
- Can I sit anywhere I want?
-  Yes.
That's the worst position.
- You'll see how things turn out.
-  Can I change seats?
- That's the worst position.
-  Can I change now?
I can, right?
You must sit there. You can't change seats now.
No, I was not certain and haven't made up my mind yet.
(How will this change the fate of Kwang Soo?)
- The weather's great today.
-  Hello. You're here.
(The throne is empty.)
- Are the seats all separated?
-  You can sit anywhere you want.
I'm a side-seeker too.
(He's an extreme side-seeker.)
What's going on here?
You can take a seat anywhere you want today.
I'm 100 percent certain that he will sit in the centre.
Today's your day, Seok Jin.
- What do you mean?
-  The throne is empty.
Can I sit on the throne?
- Don't worry about us.
-  We left the seat for you.
- I know you're a centre-seeker.
-  We left the seat empty for you.
I didn't know that I can actually sit here.
(Completely satisfied)
It's so great when everybody knows my preference and cares about it.
- It's so cold today. So cold.
-  Hey, Ji Hyo.
Take a sit anywhere you want.
Can I sit anywhere I want?
(Ji Hyo sits on the third row.)
Here's our Mr Centre-seeker.
- What is this?
-  Hello, Centre-seeker.
Why is Seok Jin sitting in the centre?
What's the matter? I'm sitting here because I want to.
- That's why you are sitting there?
-  Of course.
- You sit anywhere you want today.
-  I can't believe you sat there.
You know that I'm a centre-seeker.
- Jong Kook may try to take over.
-  It's so free today.
- There he is.
-  He's here.
- Hello.
-  There he is.
(I'm here to sit in the centre.)
There he is. I'll pretend to be in a bad mood today.
What is this? Why are you sitting on a throne like a prince today?
- You sit anywhere you want.
-  You can sit anywhere.
- Really?
-  He's a centre-seeker. Seriously.
Really? He...
His centre-loving is at a level of obsession. We should be considerate.
- So should we let him sit there?
-  Yes, of course.
You're almost a doctor, Jae Seok.
Seok Jin sitting on the throne doesn't seem right.
You'll only see him at the centre very briefly.
That's right. That makes sense.
(Enjoy while you can.)
I'll try really hard today.
We talked about a side-seeker, Gary, and a centre-seeker, Jae Seok.
- Yes.
-  Yes.
(Last week...)
Je Hoon is the guest for today, but you're sitting in the centre.
- You love the centre seat so much.
-  I sat here unconsciously.
Is the centre seat that important? Je Hoon, sit here.
I must be out of my mind.
- I'm sitting in the centre.
-  No, you don't have to.
(Jae Seok sat in the centre as well.)
- He's a centre-seeker.
-  Are you mad?
- What did you say?
-  You're a centre-seeker.
- A centre-seeker?
-  I know I am a side-seeker.
(We identified side-seekers and centre-seekers.)
We were inspired by the idea,
and we counted how many times each member stood in the centre...
- and made up a list.
-  Really?
- I wonder what the outcome is.
-  I never stood in the centre.
Because Seok Jin is sitting in the centre today,
- you'll be the host for now.
-  Okay.
- No way.
-  I've been waiting for this.
- What is this?
-  I've been waiting for this chance.
Don't make this show too old-fashioned.
Old-fashioned.
All right.
Keep your mouth closed, Jong Kook.
Jae Seok, you'd better keep quiet, too. Don't interrupt in the middle.
Seok Jin runs the show like in the late 90's.
Hold it properly. Gosh.
- Loot at that.
-  Gosh.
(The weather isn't helping.)
Gosh. What are you doing?
- The wind is too strong.
-  What are you doing?
- I'll hold it like this.
-  Yes. Grab tightly.
- Is that correct?
-  Gary stood in the centre often.
Are you running this show or having a conversation?
Hey. Hold it.
(The board must dislike Seok Jin.)
- Hey!
-  Wait. I'll hold it like this.
- What are you doing?
-  He's doing well.
- Sit Jae Seok. Sit.
-  Okay.
I actually stood in the centre so many times.
- You're right.
-  Really?
Don't walk, but run. Welcome to Running Man.
(For the last 6 years, 298 episodes of Running Man was aired.)
(Who stood in the centre the most for the last six years?)
- That's close.
-  That's a lot.
Yu Jae Seok stood in the centre for 109 times.
- Wow, 109 times.
-  That's right, 109 times.
Followed by Kim Jong Kook, who stood in the centre for 38 times.
Gary stood in the centre for 19 times.
- Gary was in the centre 19 times?
-  It must be by coincidences.
Gary stood in the centre for many times than I expected.
- Is the fourth row the last row?
-  Yes.
- That's where side-seekers stand.
-  That's the outskirts.
Haha stood on the side for 144 times.
- Kwang Soo stood for 161 times.
-  Kwang Soo had to.
- Yes, he had to.
-  He's too tall.
- It's because he's too tall.
-  Yes. He had no choice.
- Kwang Soo had too.
-  I see.
- There are flowers.
-  You only see them now?
- That's a flower carpet.
-  What is that?
(A flower carpet is laid down all of a sudden.)
- That's a flower carpet. Literally.
-  I have high hopes for the guests.
Why is the carpet laid down toward Seok Jin?
There are supporters to help you...
- with your fight for the centre.
-  Really?
Please go on, Seok Jin. Introduce us the guests today.
So Seok Jin is responsible for the ratings for this episode...
- even if the ratings drop?
-  Of course. You can count on me.
She once said that,
- "Give the centre position..."
-  No.
- "to Seok Jin."
-  This is so boring.
She's a beloved actress with her fresh and lively charms.
Here is the actress, Cho Bo Ah.
(Seok Jin's supporter is Cho Bo Ah.)
- Really?
-  Cho Bo Ah?
- Wow. Cho Bo Ah!
-  Oh, my.
- Really?
-  Cho Bo Ah?
(She looks so lively and charming even from far.)
We have a great guest today.
(Cho Bo Ah)
Say hello.
I want to marry him.
(She makes men's heart flutter with her beauty and performance.)
(A big umbrella and a flower carpet is for the centre supporter.)
- An umbrella and a flower carpet?
-  That's so great.
- Nice to see you, Cho Bo Ah.
-  Goodness.
- Oh, my.
-  She's so pretty.
- Thank you, Seok Jin.
-  You're welcome.
Go away, Jae Seok. Go away.
- Cho Bo Ah.
-  Hello.
She's Cho Bo Ah.
(Bo Ah will assist Seok Jin today to make him sit in the centre.)
Is she here to support Seok Jin today?
- Ji Hyo, come here.
-  Of course.
Why is she getting a penalty from the beginning?
This is not a penalty.
We should change the host!
- Resign, Seok Jin.
-  Just sit down.
- Sit down.
-  Resign. Resign.
- Resign.
-  Why didn't you sit in the centre?
Sit down. Hurry up.
- All right, Kim Jong Kook.
-  Is it my turn?
If Kim Jong Kook is the centre of TURBO,
she is the centre of all the trot scene.
He is commentating on his own. We can't hear him.
She attracts all men with her charms and cuteness.
- A singer, Hong Jin Young!
-  It's Hong Jin Young.
It's Jin Young.
- Oh, it's Jin Young.
-  It's Hong Jin Young.
- Come this way.
-  Come here.
It's so nice to see her.
(An umbrella and a plain carpet for the second row supporter.)
(Hong Jin Young)
Why didn't they prepare you the flower carpet?
Nice to see you.
- She's Jong Kook's girl.
-  Yes, there's definitely something.
Probably the only potential couple.
- There's something.
-  Jong Kook is happy.
Sit everyone. Please sit.
Can't you make a big fancy introduction for Jin Young?
- That was so simple.
-  How can I make it more fancy?
- That was too short and simple.
-  How can I make it better?
- It's not fun at all.
-  How should I do it then?
- Everything is being blown around.
-  My gosh.
(The flower carpet is being blown away.)
(What a mess.)
Oh my goodness.
This must be a sign. This must be.
(This must be a sign. This must be.)
(It's a sign telling Seok Jin to resign.)
It's all because of the host.
- What's going on?
-  It's because of the host.
- What a mess.
-  The host is to be blamed.
You should change the person sitting in the centre.
It's time to introduce the supporter for Yu Jae Seok.
- My supporter?
-  It's Jae Seok's partner.
Who is it?
She looks tough on the outside, but soft on the inside.
Her unexpected charm makes many people become her fan.
The name of the university she attended means the centre too.
Actress, Yoo In Young.
- Wow.
-  In Young?
Long time no see, In Young. She was my partner last time.
She was your partner last time.
- In Young.
-  She joined us once before.
In Young.
(It's so great to see her again.)
- She's my partner.
-  She's my old partner.
Show us your face.
(Yoo In Young)
(She looks cold but has an opposite character.)
Gosh, you ruined it.
(Actress Yoo In Young is brave.)
- I can see In Young's so angry.
-  She is.
(Acclamation)
- She was on Femme Fatale Special.
-  Hello.
- It's been a while.
-  Long time no see.
- Here you are.
-  Please take a seat.
- Wow. He'll be with us too.
-  What is that?
Hey, the third row is acupressure mat.
- Who is it?
-  He is the one in the centre.
He says he will make sure Ji Hyo gets the centre today.
- The centre of Block B, Zico!
-  Zico!
- Zico!
-  Zico?
- Really? Wow.
-  Oh, my.
- Zico, take your shoes off!
-  Zico!
You should take your shoes off.
- That's it!
-  Good.
Zico is here!
- Zico!
-  Look at him! He's so cool.
(He remains cool even when his feet hurt a lot.)
- Hey, Zico!
-  Hello, I'm Seok Jin.
Hello, Zico!
- Hello.
-  He's here.
- Please take a seat.
-  I'd love to meet the next guest.
Kwang Soo. Get ready to welcome the next guest. You'll like her.
- Her favourite animal is giraffe.
-  Isn't she Uhm Hyeon Gyeong?
So she's here to help Kwang Soo who looks like a giraffe.
- An actress, Uhm Hyeon Gyeong!
-  Uhm Hyeon Gyeong!
- It's Uhm Hyeon Gyeong!
-  It's been a while.
Gosh, wait.
(I'm here to help Kwang Soo get the centre.)
(Uhm Hyeon Gyeong)
(Hyeon Gyeong, a giraffe maniac, is a talented entertainer.)
- Hyeon Gyeong is so pretty.
-  Uhm Hyeon Gyeong!
- I met Hyeon Gyeong on "Xman".
-  That's a long ago.
Hyeon Gyeong! Come here.
- Why are you here, Hyeon Gyeong?
-  Look who's here.
- What's this?
-  Your hair got stuck.
- What's going on here?
-  Take this.
- What is that now?
-  Look! That's ice.
- Is that really ice?
-  It's ice.
Who's next?
To make Haha get the spotlight, she visits us today.
She's 177cm tall, and her body has a perfect proportion.
- She transformed from a model...
-  It's Stephanie Lee!
(At a loss for words)
- Hey.
-  Wasn't I right?
I was going to say that...
- although I have a hoarse throat.
-  Stephanie Lee!
(Haha's supporter is a model, Stephanie Lee.)
- The way she walks is different.
-  Look at her umbrella!
- Stephanie Lee...
-  My goodness.
(Stephanie Lee)
(Stephanie works both as a model and an actress. What a nice body!)
(She played a career woman role in "Yong Pal".)
- This is great.
-  She has to walk on ice.
- That's real ice right there.
-  Stephanie...
- You have big feet.
-  Just walk fast.
I'm sorry. Gosh, I can't believe this.
- Goodness. What's this?
-  Just walk. It's okay.
- Stephanie...
-  This is too rude!
Goodness! Everything is messed up today.
- It's because Seok Jin is hosting.
-  It's a total mess.
Everything is out of order.
It's a chaos!
Look at this mess. It's because Seok Jin is hosting this show!
- Poor Stephanie.
-  She's trembling.
It's time for our next guest.
- She is really something!
-  Who is it?
She visits us to help the side-seeker, Gary,
and make him a centre-seeker.
- It's Kyung Su Jin!
-  She is...
-  Kyung Su Jin!
Stop there!
- Oh, Su Jin is here.
-  Gosh, there she is!
- She's Gary's favourite actress.
-  It's Su Jin!
- Su Jin!
-  Welcome!
- Gary really likes you.
-  My goodness.
(Although she has a small body, she is very charismatic and cute.)
(She also appeared on Running Man as Gary's partner.)
What happened to your umbrella?
(That's because you are a side-seeker.)
Kwang Soo, you have to hold her hand. Hold her hand.
- Su Jin, I'm so sorry.
-  We are sorry!
- Goodness.
-  Oh, my.
- Are you okay?
-  It's your fault, Gary.
- Watch out.
-  Gary really likes Su Jin.
- Hello.
-  What is this? Come on.
- Isn't this too much?
-  Gary told me that...
It's Gary's fault for sitting on the fourth row.
- Seok Jin, please keep going.
-  Okay.
- Why is there so much to do today?
-  You going so slow.
All right. She's Cho Bo Ah. Please give it up for her.
Please give her a big hand again.
She arrived here a while ago.
- Are you interviewing her?
-  I'll start the interviews, then.
Bo Ah, please introduce yourself.
Hello, I'm Cho Bo Ah.
What do you... Are you an actress?
(Are you an actress?)
- Gosh.
-  What are you doing?
- That's ridiculous.
-  Please study before you come here.
You should learn how to host a show.
I'm currently acting in the drama, "Monster".
- You are in the drama, "Monster".
-  Yes.
Do you guys speak the same language?
I think it'll take two hours just to start the show.
- Is it your first time here?
-  Yes.
- How does it feel?
-  Is it your first time hosting?
Gosh, I've been doing it for 20 years.
- Tell us how you'll play today.
-  My goodness.
- That's so weird.
-  Isn't this the way we do it?
No, we no longer ask such questions.
- Why do you ask that?
-  Just tell us.
- Please go ahead.
-  I came here...
- to help Seok Jin keep the centre.
-  Okay.
Oh gosh.
- But I'm not sure if I can.
-  What?
- Of course, she's not sure.
-  Don't worry.
I'll be in the centre the whole day.
Then, next!
(Then, next!)
- She barely said anything!
-  Was that it?
- You should ask more questions!
-  You're a bad host!
Please get up. The host is here.
- Get up.
-  Why would you make her get up?
I'm older than you. Just get up.
- So In Young...
-  What are you doing?
- You're Jae Seok's partner.
-  Yes.
- How do you feel about it?
-  He's always been at the centre.
So If I do my best...
- He can get to the centre position.
-  Yes.
That won't happen today. Today is the day...
- Jae Seok gets a side position.
-  Cut it out!
- Cut it out!
- Okay. That was it.
-  Goodness.
- Are you kidding me?
-  Get up, now.
- How can he do that?
-  Hey, get up.
- We need Jae Seok back!
-  He didn't even call my name.
He said, "Hey, get up".
- She's Jong Kook's partner.
-  You're a partner of Jong Kook.
- Do you like him?
-  Well...
She called Jong Kook late at night when she was drunk.
- But he didn't answer the call.
-  Really?
What are you talking about, Haha? I didn't call him.
- I didn't call him.
-  She didn't.
She wanted to get Jong Kook's phone number...
- Gosh, I didn't call him.
-  No. She didn't.
- Okay, what should I do now?
-  Right, well...
- Yes.
-  Did you gain weight?
(What a novel question for an interview!)
- How can you ask her that?
-  I just...
- What are you doing?
-  Are you trying to mess with her?
- Are you out of your mind?
-  Do you think I gained weight?
- Yes, a little bit.
-  But you look good.
- You look fine.
-  Okay. Please sit down, then.
- Have a seat.
-  Was that it?
- Zico, Zico.
-  Zico!
- Hello. Hello.
-  Hey, Zico.
Two of the best three Co's are here.
My nickname is Wang Co, and you're Zico.
Do you think you'll get the centre today?
- To be honest,
-  Yes.
I'm not really obsessed with being in the centre.
(One less competitor!)
But for Ji Hyo, I'll do my best...
- to move to the front.
-  I'll count on you.
I saw Zico dancing before on TV. He's a great dancer.
- What is that out of the blue?
-  Should he dance all of a sudden?
- That's so unexpected.
-  Play the music.
You know I danced like this.
(Haha seems to know Zico's dance.)
- Can you chant like this for me?
-  Okay.
- How?
-  Like this.
(I say "Ho", then you say "Ho".)
That's it.
(That's exciting.)
(I'm the centre of Block B!)
(Haha follows Zico's lead.)
There it is. Do it like this.
Yes, that was it.
- Okay, he's Zico!
-  Just do the way you always do.
Finally...
- What are you doing?
-  Zico's interview is done.
- Why is Zico's turn over?
-  It's over.
- It ended so suddenly.
-  It ended in the middle of dancing.
It's over.
- Hyeon Gyeong, Nice to meet you.
-  Hello.
- I'm a big fan of yours.
-  Really?
I do like you a lot.
You're so cute on the show that you do with Jae Seok.
It's not the time for a confession.
- You're all flushed. What was that?
-  Is he out of his mind?
You know Hyeon Gyeong...
became a good entertainer thanks to SBS.
- That's so right.
-  Were you on "Xman"?
- Yes.
-  On "Xman",
she was become famous for being too nervous.
- That's right.
-  Really?
It's been 10 years, and she changed a lot.
Hey, we're in the middle of an interview.
- Sorry?
-  I'm still interviewing her now.
- He's way better than you.
-  So what happened next?
At that time, she wasn't a good dancer.
Right. She never danced before.
- But she's so good at it now.
-  How do you feel to be here?
- I am very happy.
-  I see.
Do you always answer this short?
- Do you?
-  Please interview her sincerely.
Please ask her something she can come up with a long answer.
It's so chaotic here today.
Are you a fan of Kwang Soo? Do you like him?
She didn't say she's my fan. Why do you ask her such question?
- She collects toy giraffes.
-  Really? Why?
- Why?
-  She has many toy giraffes at home.
- Kwang Soo also collects it.
-  Really?
- Do you have a lot of them?
-  His nickname is giraffe.
- People think I like Kwang Soo.
-  That's right.
So you don't like him. Do you want to...
- change your partner to me?
-  No.
- What was that?
-  I can't believe this.
- Your partner, Bo Ah, is there!
-  Are you out of your mind?
- That was so wrong.
-  Call the police!
So today, show us your charms one by one.
That's it for Hyeon Gyeong.
- That's it?
-  Really?
- What's with that face?
-  It's such an old style.
- Have a seat.
-  Sure.
I want to yell this to the entire world.
This host sucks!
- Goodness.
-  All right, next.
- Su Jin's shoulders look cold.
-  I'm freezing.
- She's a broad-shouldered gangster.
-  It's been a while.
Would this be enough?
This should be good for now.
Su Jin, this is for the other side.
This should be good.
She's a broad-shouldered gangster.
She is.
- She's really strong.
-  She definitely is.
Last time you were on the show,
- you ripped out all our name tags.
-  Yes.
Gary mentioned...
that he's a side-seeker.
- He is.
-  So...
I think they partnered me up with him on purpose.
- We won when she was my partner.
-  That's right.
Gary changes depending on how the women treat him.
Is that right?
- Oh, gosh.
-  I'll do my best.
All right.
- Gary, you...
-  Stop asking questions!
- She said she's cold!
-  I'm cold!
Okay, we'll find out your charms with time.
(Let's explore your charms when it's warmer.)
(He's abrupt.)
- Have a seat.
-  What's he doing?
My goodness.
I'll work harder from now on.
- This is great.
-  I've learned again.
- Nice to meet you.
-  Hello.
Your name is...
- Is it Stephanie?
-  It's Stephanie Lee!
- It's Stephanie Lee!
-  I'm sorry. I'm bad with names.
- It's Stephanie Lee.
-  You're the one who introduced her.
It's Stephanie Lee.
You introduced her.
- You were in a commercial, right?
-  Can you show us what you did?
Can you show us again?
(Her perfect English pronunciation made her well-known.)
From Neutrogena.
(From Neutrogena)
(She sounds like a foreigner.)
Who do you like the most on Running Man?
To be honest, I wanted to be Kwang Soo's partner,
but I got Haha.
- So I didn't wear heels today.
-  Who's that?
She has no heels.
She should have worn heels to help me out.
Really? Like this?
(That would have been funnier.)
"Neutrogena".
(It's funny enough.)
Okay, Stephanie. We'll find out your charms with time.
- How's the time?
-  My goodness.
We have a lot of time.
What do we do next?
The theme is Battle for the Centre: The One Who Holds the Throne.
Through each mission, the winner will take the centre...
and will enjoy extravagance and great treatment.
But those who are ousted from the centre...
will receive punishments accordingly.
Depending on your ranks in each mission, you will be awarded points.
According to the results, all but the person in the centre...
will stand in front of the blue screen in a blue outfit...
- and will disappear.
-  Oh, my goodness.
We'll award your first points by where you are sitting.
(Seok Jin's Team earns the most, 4 points.)
(Battle for the Centre)
What do we do now?
- The first game for today...
-  All right.
is called, "Only I Belong on TV".
Before we play the actual game, we'll do a warm-up.
- This is an old school game.
-  We used to play this a lot.
- You blow out the candles.
-  This is old school.
You have to flip the skirt.
The winner gets a whistle so you can decide when people go.
The warm-up will be played by...
the guests who are here today to move their partners to the centre.
- They'll play for us?
-  The guests will go.
Seok Jin, can you lead the game?
- He doesn't know what to do.
-  Let's get into the game right now.
- Slow down.
-  We have to talk.
When do we get to hear the guests talking?
- We have a lot to cover.
-  But Jin Young...
For all the times I've been on this show, I've never been this quiet.
- She's never like this.
-  This is the first time I spoke.
We want to hear their voices.
Seok Jin, use me as your reporter.
He could be the assistant.
- I'll be your assistant reporter.
-  That's right.
- This doesn't look good.
-  No, I'll be your assistant.
Let's hear from Jae Seok on site.
- Just say that.
-  Okay.
- Reporter Yu Jae Seok.
-  Yes.
- Please lead this segment.
-  All right.
- Jae Seok is on site.
-  On behalf of Seok Jin,
This is what we've come to.
I'm your assistant.
You passed it down.
- That's what it is.
-  Let's make it that.
Su Jin, you met Gary again...
- after one year.
-  Exactly.
- We won.
-  You won last time.
Earlier, she was putting on her heels and asked,
"We are ripping name tags today, right?"
(She's determined to rip name tags once again.)
I'm being honest.
- She's no joke. She's very strong.
-  Seriously.
- Your face became smaller.
-  Gary...
- spoke a lot about her too.
-  Really?
He mentioned her while he was getting dressed for today.
- He wanted to be on Su Jin's team.
-  Yes.
(He wanted Su Jin to be on his team.)
He said he'd get her number no matter what.
(He is determined to get her number.)
Goodness.
Hey, stop it.
- Keep quiet. Let him be.
-  I know, right?
Can I ask you one thing?
Su Jin, do you have a boyfriend right now?
(Is she seeing anybody?)
- No.
-  That's good!
Gary isn't seeing anybody either.
- That's good.
-  Gary's lucky.
- Gary.
-  If I had one, I'll wrap it up.
Our next team is a romantic couple that we've been looking forward to.
It's been so long after Yoon Eun Hye.
- Seriously.
-  Yes, right?
Why are you doing this to me?
Jin Young's trademark is her cuteness.
- There are a few she usually does.
-  That's right.
- Can you do it to Jong Kook?
-  He'll fall for it.
- To me?
-  He'll get uneasy.
That's right.
I'm feeling great.
Jong Kook, you.
How's this?
Thumbs up for you
(Thumbs up for you!)
(Snapping)
(Goosebumps)
It'll pop up in his head before he goes to bed.
- That's excellent.
-  He'll remember it.
-  Jin Young is so good.
I think everyone's having a great time except me.
(He's the only one not happy.)
- They're full of laughter.
-  You're right.
- I'm having a good time.
-  This is great.
(I have a bad vibe.)
- Seriously...
-  Hold on a bit longer.
Hold on a little bit. It'll change after this game.
This must be a poisonous grail. Watch out.
It makes your face gloomy.
You don't look too well.
Guys, don't try to be the centre.
For me, to say this bluntly,
I'm still wondering about this.
- Aren't you surprised?
-  I don't know why you are a team.
Why were you two put together?
Bo Ah, weren't you hoping to be on Jae Seok's team?
I didn't make any guesses on who my teammate was going to be.
- But the partner I wanted...
-  Be quiet.
- was Jong Kook.
-  Me?
Why are you happy?
(Are you smiling?)
Are you?
- I could be happy about it.
-  Gosh, I can't do this.
- That's good to hear.
-  You.
-  Fine.
- Turn your body towards me.
-  All right.
- I'm your partner today.
-  I know that.
This is great.
Then, let's start with an acrostic poem with Seok Jin's name.
- Should we?
-  This is a must.
- You'll go next with Bo Ah's name.
-  Okay.
- Let's go for it. "Jee".
-  "Jee".
Jee Seok Jin.
Okay, "Jee Seok Jin". "Seok".
I'm disappointed.
"I'm disappointed." Okay, "Jin".
I really want to change my partner.
(I really want to change my partner.)
She's being serious.
This is real.
- She's telling the truth.
-  It's the truth.
- It's the truth.
-  It is for sure.
- This is for real.
-  She really doesn't want it.
- Let's go with Bo Ah's name.
-  Why would I do this?
- Let's go with her name.
-  I'm not in the best mood.
- Okay, "Cho".
-  Get rid of it.
- I had some expectations...
-  My goodness.
to be the centre.
- "I had some expectations..."
-  Okay, "Bo".
Like you see it here, I'm a mess.
- That sounds good.
-  "Ah".
Oh, I hate to be in the centre.
(His poem touches everybody's hearts.)
As for Hyeon Gyeong,
- she was on "X Man" in 2004.
-  She was so cute.
She never spoke much, so I nicknamed her Nervous Girl.
- But she's changed completely.
-  Even when she danced,
she was so nervous but that made her popular.
But she learned to dance from her friend...
and now she's a dancing machine.
- Am I right?
-  Yes, I'm good at dancing.
Can you do a body wave?
- She's so confident.
-  I'm not even joking.
If you have music ready, she can show you.
- Show us.
-  I want to see it.
This is the "X Man" version.
What do I do?
(What's this?)
- I'll go again.
-  Hey!
(Hey!)
Stop lying.
- What were you saying?
-  Hold on.
- She didn't prepare anything.
-  She's so cute.
- I thought she was actually good.
-  She's good.
I can't watch her.
- There you go.
-  What is this about?
She can do hip-hop dances too. She really is.
Is she being serious?
She is.
Isn't she trying to be funny?
No, she's doing this for real. She's serious.
- You are bold.
-  She learned all this.
She doesn't dance to the music. It's just whatever she learned.
Do you want to see her do it? She'll dance the same to hip-hop.
(They play a hip-hop music.)
See? The same applies here.
(She's rigid.)
- See?
-  She always starts like this?
It's the same for every type of music.
She's not affected at all.
(She's rusted.)
Hyeon Gyeong, do the body wave.
- Make her stop.
-  There you go.
Look at her. That's great.
That's excellent.
- You have your own style.
-  Right?
She always does the body wave.
She's the boldest dancer.
- She's one of the best in Korea.
-  She's so bold.
We didn't really see Zico dance.
- That wasn't enough earlier.
-  Okey Dokey
- My dance?
-  His movements are different.
You'll be shocked when you see him move.
- Zico!
-  Victory...
(It's Zico's turn.)
Something like this?
Go with the groove.
(Grooving)
There you go.
(He's in rhythm with the beat.)
How do you do it?
(Cheering)
This is spontaneous.
Watch this.
(Zico's dance is full of hip-hop.)
This is it.
(Let's copy Zico.)
You're good.
- Wow.
-  Do you have to make that face?
(They're good but they don't look good together.)
Wow, look at Stephanie.
You're too tall.
She's too tall. She's this big.
- Hey. Wait a minute.
-  He has to look up.
She's so tall that he has to look up.
You look very pathetic.
Your neck almost got paralysed.
It felt like I was a child dancing with my mummy.
It looked like a grade school talent show.
(It was like "Oh My Baby" in Running Man.)
He has to punch like this.
- All right. That's so funny.
-  The dance was sexy.
I am Reporter Yu Jae Seok.
- Thank you!
-  All right.
- I am a little bit pressured.
-  Okay.
- Now, the whistle...
-  Yes.
(He ruined the mood.)
- Whistle...
-  What about the whistle?
- You can win it on this game.
-  Okay.
- Your partner will wear a skirt.
-  Yes.
The team that blows out the most number of candles wins the whistle.
Obviously.
We have to first change into those outfits.
- Yes.
-  Come on!
- Me?
-  Let's do this.
We will start with the fourth row.
Gary, you are on the fourth row, right?
- Yes.
-  Haha and Gary are.
- Su Jin will start first.
-  Me?
- You only get one chance.
-  Let's go!
- Su Jin has quick movements...
-  That's right.
- and is very competitive.
-  She is very competitive.
You are pressuring me. Stop it.
- Relax. Don't get pressured.
-  Okay.
- Okay.
-  It's her first time to do it.
- Here we go.
-  Let's go!
Go, Su Jin! Fly!
(I'm counting on you!)
(She always had a fighting spirit.)
- I got it.
-  Go!
- Su Jin. Su Jin.
Kwang Soo is there. Su Jin, don't do this to me.
Su Jin! Please!
(The female warrior, Kyung Su Jin, is back!)
- Let's go!
-  Okay.
Go, Su Jin! Fly!
(Running)
(She generates a powerful wind.)
(She gave her everything.)
- She fell.
-  She did her best.
- Bravo.
-  She's good.
You're good.
- She's really good.
-  You are really good.
- She blew out a lot.
-  That's considered a lot.
- That was really great.
-  This is it.
- This is it.
-  Good job!
- Good job.
-  Impressive. She's good.
- She's really good.
-  She's good.
- That's really good.
-  Good job.
She did really well.
Next is Stephanie. She is tall.
- Yes.
-  She has an advantage.
- She has an advantage.
-  Right.
- How many can you blow out?
-  Maybe you grabbed it too high.
I will blow out all of them.
(She has a big ambition.)
- She's ambitious.
-  She will blow them all out.
All right. Let's go!
Make it as wide as you can.
Here she comes.
(She bows powerfully.)
(It's a wind blast!)
Here she comes.
(She ran lightly and flapped the skirt from high above.)
- Some revived.
-  It was so close.
Some revived.
- Some revived.
-  It was so close.
-  The last part is important.
- She blew out 33 candles!
-  Yes!
You did well.
Su Jin blew out 31 candles, and Stephanie blew out 33 candles.
Next is Hyeon Gyeong. All right, let's go.
She says she's not competitive, and she's a bad athlete too.
- You should make...
-  But she might do well today.
But she used to be known for being nervous all the time,
and she's being reborn as an entertainer.
- I am really bad at sports.
-  Get ready. Go!
(Please do well!)
- Let's go.
-  Go Hyeon Gyeong!
(She screams shortly.)
(Jumping)
(She collapses right away.)
She tripped, didn't she?
- She tripped, right?
-  Are you okay?
- She's good.
-  She's a good entertainer.
- Let's go!
-  She started like an athlete.
(She started like an athlete and landed like an entertainer.)
She tripped, didn't she? She tripped, right?
She tripped, didn't she?
- She tripped, right?
-  Are you okay?
- She's good.
-  You're good.
She's a good entertainer, isn't she?
- She's an entertainer.
-  She's a treasure.
- She tripped.
-  What's her score? 10 candles.
- 10 candles?
-  That's bad.
- All right.
-  Shouldn't Jong Kook...
cheer her up by raising his thumb?
No, it's okay.
- Please do it for me.
-  It's a good idea.
- Do it for her.
So how do I do it?
- Thumbs...
-  Thumbs up for you
- You have to bounce at the end.
-  Jong Kook,
you have to make sure to bounce your bottoms.
- Hurry up.
-  Hurry up and do it.
Thumbs up for you
(Thumbs up for you!)
(Her cuteness makes Jong Kook dance.)
- You're really liking it.
-  Jin Young.
- He never does that.
-  Here we go.
- Go! – Fly. Fly.
(Jin Young departs!)
Thumbs up for you
(Come on, Jin Young!)
(Did Jong Kook's cheer help?)
- Go! – Fly. Fly.
What?
(What was that?)
- What is she doing?
-  What is she doing?
(She falls on her back.)
(She just lied down on her back.)
Is she drunk? Is she?
- Go!
-  Fly. Fly.
(There are many parties during spring, but drink moderately.)
- What is she doing?
-  Is she drunk? Is she?
(I regret raising my thumbs up.)
- What did you just do?
-  This is too bad.
- You are out.
-  You lose!
- She's terrible at playing sports.
-  You are out.
- You should act instead.
-  I can't play sports.
You would've blown out some candles if you just fell.
Next is In Young!
- That's it.
-  What is he doing?
- What are you doing?
-  Wait.
I wanted her to relax. Do the shadow boxing.
Come on, In Young. That's right.
(She's doing it.)
She avoided the punches.
- She went like this.
-  No way.
She avoided the punch.
Good job, In Young. 1, 2. 1, 2.
- I can't believe it.
-  Good job.
- Let's do this, In Young.
-  Let's go, In Young.
- Don't hesitate, In Young.
-  Go!
Open it widely. That's it.
Go. Go.
(She drops from high above.)
(It was a powerful one.)
Open it widely. That's it.
(She dominated the air and fell aggressively.)
All right.
Okay!
(What is In Young's record?)
- But she did really well.
-  Only about five...
- It was good though.
-  If you hold it...
- Let me count. 1, 2, 3, 4...
-  too widely, it's not powerful.
- Good job, In Young.
-  You should hit strongly.
- In Young blew out 19 candles.
-  But she was good.
Right now, Stephanie is leading the game.
- Zico!
-  He has a strong chance to win.
He's the only male participant.
- Actually, Zico is...
-  I think he will do well.
Zico, how many candles do you think you can blow out?
About 35 to 40.
Really? Actually that's just enough.
- That's not too many.
-  He has to do it.
- Here we go. Go!
-  Go, Zico!
Zico!
(Hip-hop trained him to be brutal. Zico's power is revealed now.)
- Let's go!
-  Go!
Zico!
(He flops down.)
- Zico.
-  Hold on...
Zico!
(He just fell on his nose!)
- Zico.
-  Hey.
- Zico...
-  He fell on his nose!
- Is your nose all right?
-  He fell on his nose.
Are you okay, Zico?
(He gathered all the energy within the skirt and ended in misery.)
- Is your nose okay?
-  He fell on his nose.
- Are you okay, Zico?
-  Are you all right?
- Bo Ah is up next.
-  Are you okay?
Now it's most likely that Stephanie is going to win.
We don't know how Bo Ah will do.
(Stephanie who blew out 33 candles is most likely to win as of now.)
- She's going to do well.
-  She's good.
So 33 is the record.
- Bo Ah is going to try it.
-  Go, Bo Ah!
She's the competitive type.
- Go!
-  Go.
Wait. But Bo Ah.
(Flapping)
(The wind was strong.)
(The majority of the candles are blown out.)
- Yes. I knew she'd do well.
-  She's good.
Seok Jin can't be the winner again!
- No way.
-  Really?
No way.
(What is Bo Ah's record?)
- 34?
-  34.
(Bo Ah blew out 34 candles!)
Oh dear.
(She beats Stephanie by 1 candle.)
- 34?
-  By 1 candle?
It's okay. It was fun.
- I should've just sat and flapped.
-  But it doesn't feel too nice.
- This can't happen.
-  Seok Jin gets to keep the centre.
(Seok Jin maintains the centre position.)
This is the real game to determine the first centre.
You will dance to an exciting song,
- and when the winners of...
-  They will blow the whistle.
the pre-game blow the whistle, you will run to the TV frame.
The camera is on a timer.
You'll succeed if you are included in the picture.
According to the game result, you'll be given points.
And that will determine what you eat for lunch.
(The game result determines their lunch menu!)
- I want to eat something good.
-  I'm hungry.
You always eat something delicious.
- But I want to have it today.
-  Then we need to win.
(The centre table is like a feast.)
So we begin when Seok Jin blows the whistle, right?
You know the rules, right?
- Yes.
-  Dance to the music.
And when I blow the whistle, jump in front of the frame.
- If both are in the picture...
-  You pass?
Tall ones have the advantage.
- That's true.
-  Music, cue!
(Music starts.)
(Waving)
(There's strange tension!)
(They show perfect harmony.)
(They have to stay alert even while dancing.)
- Don't stay here.
-  Move.
- Move.
-  It's dangerous.
(Seok Jin teases them.)
(Everyone is looking at Seok Jin.)
Come on, Su Jin.
I can't do it.
(He blew it!)
(They all jump.)
(The centre is mine!)
- Move!
-  Jump!
In 1, 2, 3.
- In 1, 2, 3.
-  In 1, 2, 3.
(Everyone is trying so hard to be at the centre.)
- All right.
-  Let's check it.
- I think we did okay.
-  We might be there.
Don't all go to the front.
You'll definitely be on the picture.
- You held onto me.
-  I had to.
I need to be the centre again.
- You have to do it to know.
-  It's not something...
We are at a disadvantage.
(The picture is revealed.)
- We are there!
-  Look.
Haha did it.
- We are not there at all.
-  We can never do it.
It's really tough.
- You're not there.
-  Look at Stephanie.
(Kwang Soo couple and Haha couple succeeded.)
Stephanie are you into reggae?
- She's like Bob Marley.
-  Stephanie looks like Bob Marley.
- What is that?
-  You got blocked by him.
- Look at Hyeon Gyeong's hair.
-  She's Bob Marley.
- Look at Bo Ah's hair.
-  Look at Hyeon Gyeong.
- We're in the picture!
-  There you are.
Haha's couple and Kwang Soo's couple passed.
(The two candidate couples are decided.)
Well done.
- Yes.
-  We don't have to do it the same.
It would be better to find a good spot.
- Let's go find the good spot.
-  In Young, let's move forward.
- Do you just keep jumping?
-  In Young is tall.
- In Young will get it.
-  Su Jin is tying her shoes again.
- She's determined.
-  She's ready to beat us all.
We will do it until we have the two losing teams.
We will do it until three teams pass.
Give us the music!
(I want to be on television)
(Then it would be very nice)
Zico sure is different.
- I want to be on television
-  I want to be on television
- Let's dance together.
-  Don't cheat.
- What's wrong with you?
-  Why would you do this?
(Shall we get it started?)
Wait.
(He blows the whistle.)
Start jumping.
(They all gather in the centre.)
In 1, 2, 3.
- In 1, 2, 3.
-  In 1, 2, 3.
-  Jump.
(Get out of my way.)
(They commit fouls to get in the picture!)
(Team Jong Kook jumps when the others are coming down.)
(The game is over.)
Who kept grabbing my shoulders?
- In Young is great.
-  Maybe we got it.
In Young, you have to be in the picture.
- Good job, In Young.
-  What did you do?
- I'm in it!
-  I'm in it too!
- We are in it, In Young.
-  Are we in it?
We are in it!
(Team Jae Seok, Team Gary and Team Ji Hyo succeed.)
We passed!
- His hat's off.
-  You passed.
- We are there.
-  He's wearing a hat.
- Look at Gary.
-  Please put a hat on my head.
(Even Gary must've been pressured.)
- Who is he?
-  Gary looks so funny.
- Gary looks so funny.
-  Gary hasn't changed at all.
- The picture looks nice.
-  I am sorry.
- In Young, good job.
-  I am sorry, Bo Ah.
(It seems like Gary's time travels backwards.)
- Gary looks so funny.
-  What's up with his hair?
- I look ridiculous.
-  All right.
So now, Team Jong Kook and Team Seok Jin will take the fourth row.
Does that mean we can't eat something good?
Let's just eat what we get.
(The middle rank play-off begins!)
- Good job. Come on.
-  Let's go!
In 1, 2, 3, 4.
(They are nervous.)
In 1, 2, 3.
(The centre is mine!)
- I wonder what happened.
-  I just jumped.
In Young and I passed!
- That's it!
-  Team Gary is in the third row.
All right.
(The three teams are the centre candidates.)
(Team Gary and Team Ji Hyo are in the third row.)
(Team Jong Kook and Team Seok Jin are in the fourth row.)
- It became smaller.
-  The TV is smaller now.
Only the dirtiest players are here.
- This is really tricky.
-  All the dirty players are here.
- Gosh.
-  This is going to be tough.
- Now the centre will be decided.
-  Yes!
- Are you ready?
-  You look very happy.
And let me remind you...
that your meal quality depends on your rank.
- Okay.
-  I haven't heard that word in ages.
- You know that, right?
-  Yes. We know.
Music, please.
Did you practise it?
(They do a couple dance and livens up the vibe!)
(What do we do?)
(You can count on me!)
(They start the sparring dance.)
Keep going!
(Trying hard)
(I will do my best so that you can become the centre!)
Change the role.
Okay.
(Next is Haha and Stephanie!)
(Punching)
(Gosh!)
(It's the upgraded version of Team Jae Seok's dance.)
(Let's do it energetically!)
Let's go.
(The time is now!)
- This way.
-  How do we do it?
Okay. You have to get in the picture.
- Stephanie, come to the front.
-  It's not easy.
- You have to jump!
-  Come here, In Young.
- Push him.
-  In 1, 2, 3.
(Kwang Soo is using his height to push Jae Seok down.)
(They play all kinds of tricks!)
(I am going to be in the picture!)
(Game over)
- It's over.
-  Gosh! I couldn't jump!
- Gosh.
-  We did it this time.
You just have to stand.
- We did it this time.
-  Did we do it this time?
Did we make it this time?
(Who will be getting...)
(the centre table?)
- Who is it?
-  It's Kwang Soo.
-  It's Team Kwang Soo.
- Yes!
-  Gosh.
- It's the worst.
-  Jae Seok blocked me.
Yes!
(Kwang Soo becomes the new centre!)
- It's the worst.
-  Jae Seok blocked me.
(They are disappointed.)
You could've made it hadn't I blocked your face.
Kwang Soo got it.
Kwang Soo became the centre.
I am excited!
- Congratulations.
-  Well done.
(The first row goes to Team Kwang Soo.)
(The second row goes to Team Haha and Team Jae Seok.)
Bo Ah, wait for me.
(What kind of a meal will they get?)
- Bye.
-  What is that?
(Elegant Korean table d'hote is laid out for the first position.)
(Home style dishes are prepared for the second row.)
(As you go further down, the quality of food goes down!)
(The fourth row only gets rice balls and water?)
- This is us.
-  What is this?
- What's this?
-  This is too much.
- Don't we deserve more than that?
-  The second row is nice.
- It's quite nice.
-  Su Jin.
I saw this a while ago.
- We deserve more than this.
-  I really love this.
- I love it.
-  The second row deserves more.
- What do we get?
-  The centre ones are lucky.
- Come on.
-  Are you guys hungry?
- I really love this.
-  Really?
By the way, what are you doing?
I was asking if you are hungry.
- Right. You're the host now.
-  You can't sit down just yet.
- Jong Kook, don't sit.
-  There's too much difference.
- Why?
-  You can't sit down yet.
Don't we deserve some pickled vegetables at least?
- It's a rice ball.
-  Fourth row!
- There's just too little food.
-  It's okay.
- Zico. What did they get?
-  You got more than me.
- Gary and Su Jin got the same.
-  We need some condiments.
- Haha.
-  Can we get soy sauce?
It's just steamed white rice.
- We deserve some ham.
-  Gosh...
- Give us some dried laver then.
-  Give us some more food.
- I'm afraid I can't help you.
-  The rice is too hard.
- Wait. I'll go get some food.
-  It's seasoned?
It's really seasoned?
- It's cold.
-  You can start eating.
- The rice is cold.
-  We only have rice.
- Give us something.
-  I'm sure there's something inside.
- It should be at least seasoned.
-  We have nothing.
Are you gangsters?
- You can't just take our food.
-  Anchovies and...
How can you take everything?
- How can you do this?
-  Why did we play the game then?
- We need some condiments.
-  What do you want, In Young?
(We could do this!)
(Team Seok Jin goes too.)
What's happening here?
- Wait. Chef!
-  We won't take the good ones.
Wait. The chef is coming. What on earth is happening?
- Please let me get some meat.
-  Let me get some pancakes.
If you take everything, what will we eat?
- It's like a buffet.
-  Then what's the point?
I will flip the table so that no one can eat it!
- It's like a buffet.
-  Why is this a buffet?
- It is a buffet.
-  Hyeon Gyeong! Where is she?
- Hyeon Gyeong!
-  Why did you take that?
Why did you bring the egg rice?
We have more delicious things there!
- I'll take some japchae too.
-  No!
(They looks like a group of starved hyenas.)
- How can you eat all of this?
-  What's going on?
- Why would you take that?
-  What are you doing, Hyeon Gyeong?
- You should follow the rule.
-  I have conscience.
- So I don't take the good ones.
-  Chef! Chef!
Get lost, all of you!
(Get lost, all of you!)
- Gosh! Go away!
-  Get some meat.
- Get that one.
-  Stop it!
I told you to stop!
(I told you to stop!)
- You are so mean.
-  Stop it!
- Go away!
-  This is the end.
- Why are you trying to eat this?
-  My egg!
(He keeps shouting, but he can't stop them.)
- Don't take our food!
-  The egg is ours.
- Hyeon Gyeong! Why are you there?
-  It's really delicious.
Why are you sitting there when we have a table?
- It's really delicious.
-  Wait.
- It's margarine rice.
-  Ji Hyo took a lot of food.
-  Look at it.
- That doesn't look appetising.
-  What happened here?
That looks really delicious.
- It's really good.
-  Hey!
It's been a long time since I ate like this.
Gosh...
I only took a little bit.
- I didn't get any of that.
-  Do you want some of this?
- We have the meat, it's okay.
-  Let's eat meat.
- Let's eat meat.
-  The seaweed is really good.
It looks delicious. Is that Korean beef?
- Is he grilling meat now?
-  Yes. He's grilling the meat.
- Everyone, the meat is grilled.
-  Hey, come on.
- I'll just take a little.
-  You can't take this.
You can't take the meat.
You can eat other things, but you can't take the meat.
- Hey, come on Zico.
-  Please cut it for us.
- I will cut it.
-  Wait. You can't take the meat.
- You are the host!
-  We worked so hard for this.
Please take your seats.
What are you doing? Are you stray cats?
What are you doing?
- Could you cut the meat for us?
-  I haven't even had rice yet.
- Wait.
I will...
- Isn't that hot?
-  Now, we need scissors.
All we need are scissors.
- Where's meat?
-  Give it to me.
Where is that big chunk of meat?
Hey!
What is it?
Jin Young took it.
Why did you take it?
It's hot.
- Here's some meat.
-  Really?
Thank you.
(Su Jin and Gary also get meat.)
- My goodness.
-  I'll cut it for you.
Thanks to Jin Young, I get a lot to eat.
- This is so great.
-  Isn't it?
All I have on my rice is the meat's blood!
(There's just blood on his rice.)
Where is all the meat?
(He lost them all.)
I think...
Jin Young eats the most.
- She eats really a lot.
-  Gosh, don't use your hand!
Isn't it hot? Hey!
Is she an animal?
Hey!
Jin Young is amazing.
- She's good.
-  Gosh.
(Disappointed)
- This is unbelievable.
-  Where's your rice?
What? Where's my rice?
Gosh, give me my rice.
I need rice at least!
I'll check your tables!
Where is it?
Hyeon Gyeong, how could you not protect my rice?
What?
Do you care only about yourself?
(She's selfish.)
Hey! Where has my rice gone?
I was grilling the meat for you!
(Intimidated)
- Where is my rice?
-  That's funny.
There's one more privilege for the centre.
Okay. I definitely need it.
- What is that?
-  From this moment,
we'll pull out the cameras for the second, third and fourth rows.
Okay!
- No way.
-  Thank you!
(Will they pull out our cameras?)
Gosh, we need at least one for the second row.
- Leave some cameras...
-  That's nonsense.
(All the cameras except the centre one are withdrawn.)
Except the centre camera...
- Really?
-  What are you doing?
Wait. You're here for Running Man. Come here and let them shoot you.
Eat here.
Just shoot me. Zoom in on me.
- Good, Bo Ah.
-  We'll shoot only the centre.
No way.
Gosh, why are you all here?
- What is this?
-  What's going on?
Just shoot me only!
- Good.
-  Hey!
Get out!
Get out. Hey!
Why are you all here?
All right. Did you enjoy your meals?
- Yes!
-  Yes!
- Then, it's time to move on.
-  What's next?
I'll count from 1 to 3. Please shout "Kwang Soo's Running Man" together.
"Kwang Soo's..."
- Stupid!
-  Gosh.
(What will be the next mission?)
Please line up there.
- Okay.
-  Okay.
- There.
-  Where?
There.
What is this?
- Please line up here.
-  What are we going to do here?
There are three colours of buoys in the pool.
- Everyone...
-  So we sit on there.
I think that's the centre one.
(This centre mission doesn't seem easy.)
(Kwang Soo is the main host for now.)
This mission is "Conquer the Main Camera".
Goodness.
(You're a bad host.)
What's wrong with you?
- You're so bad.
-  Okay.
This mission is "Main Camera"...
What did you say?
Come on!
(He needs to be more awake!)
He has been conquered already.
Start it!
It's "Conquer"...
- "The Main Camera"!
-  "The Main Camera"!
("Conquer the Main Camera")
- The monitor has seven sections.
-  Okay.
- That's the main one.
-  Then,
one camera will shoot...
- I got it.
-  one of the buoys.
We need to get on that buoy, right?
But there are many buoys with the same colour.
- So we don't know which one.
-  Right.
- We should find the right one.
-  You're right.
This won't be easy.
There are many buoys with the same colour.
So if you win,
you'll be shown in the biggest section of the monitor.
Okay.
The lower your rank, the smaller your section will be.
(If their ranks are lower, they'll get smaller sections of the screen.)
(It means, if they don't win,)
(they'll gradually disappear from the screen.)
(The last mission to get the centre position starts.)
- Only one team can win.
-  Okay.
We can do it!
Let's find which one will be the main one.
- We can do it.
-  In Young, this is it!
- In Young, this one.
-  The screen...
The screen will show...
- In Young!
-  Yes.
Zico, go for it!
- We can do it.
-  Get ready.
- Let's go for it.
-  In Young, this will be faster.
(The new couple will get the biggest part.)
You may start when I blow my whistle.
(The first round of "Conquer the Main Camera" will start soon.)
(Red buoy is their target.)
It's the middle one!
(Even the ladies dive in.)
(But which red buoy is it?)
Which one is it?
Go, Su Jin!
(They must find the right buoy faster than others to win.)
Which one is it? Is this the one?
Red one!
Isn't this the right one?
(They all go for the red buoy.)
Hyeon Gyeong! You got it!
(Hyeon Gyeong gets there first.)
(Is this the right buoy?)
(Bingo!)
Wow.
Drag her down!
Push her!
What's going on?
(Chaotic)
(Hyeon Gyeong succeeds to climb on the buoy.)
(Now, it's Kwang Soo's turn.)
Hurry up.
Take them down!
(Hyeon Gyeong falls off.)
(To conquer the centre, they should conquer the buoy first.)
What is this mess?
- Jin Young.
-  Goodness.
(While everyone is struggling near the buoy,)
(Zico pulls Ji Hyo up.)
(If they do the heart gesture, they can win the first round.)
Zico!
(Success!)
(Ji Hyo and Zico win the first round.)
(They get the centre section.)
You should've stopped her.
Ji Hyo and Zico won this round.
In Young, what were you doing?
In Young, I was right in front.
- We were so close too.
-  Kwang Soo!
How could they succeed?
I have to give this to them?
(He loses the whistle.)
Right now?
No way. I hardly did anything.
(Was my position a temporary one?)
From now on,
Ji Hyo and Zico will be shown at the main section of the screen.
(Ji Hyo and Zico gets the centre section.)
(Although it was short, it was nice to be at the centre.)
This round will decide which team comes in second.
- All right. We should go this way.
-  This way.
Yes, you should dive into the water first.
Start!
(They blow the whistle.)
(Diving)
(This time, it's the yellow buoy.)
(Stephanie uses a blue buoy as her transportation.)
(She slips.)
(She can't control her body.)
Which one is it?
Get moving.
(All of them move towards the yellow buoys.)
- I got it.
-  Where is it?
Which one is that?
- It's here!
-  Gosh, wait.
(Jong Kook gets the right one.)
Jin Young, come here!
- Don't pull me down.
-  Jin Young.
(Kwang Soo pinches Jae Seok.)
(While Kwang Soo distracts Jae Seok, Jong Kook and Seok Jin climb on it.)
(I won't lose.)
(Kwang Soo bites Jong Kook.)
- Jin Young!
-  Stop!
That hurts!
- Don't bite me!
-  Grab on!
- Good job!
-  Stop biting me!
(He bites into the meat.)
(How low are you willing to go to win?)
(We can go as low as possible.)
(This is war.)
(It's good that we won the first round.)
(We can't never let anyone else get the second row.)
(You got mail!)
(What a lucky girl she is.)
(Haha, come over here!)
(I'm on my way.)
Stop him!
(We must stop him.)
- Don't let him!
-  Stop him! Stop him!
(Stephanie, I'll be there soon.)
(Haha slips.)
(Too short to reach)
(How can you be that short?)
(Come on! It's not too late!)
Stop him! Not Haha!
It would've been cool if he succeeded.
(Su Jin grabs Jae Seok down, using her weight.)
Who are you?
(Haha, hold my hand.)
- Who's on my back?
-  Su Jin, do it now!
(Haha loses Stephanie's grasp.)
No way!
(Instead of helping her, he makes her fall off.)
- That is...
-  Who's on my back?
Who are you?
Don't push me down.
This is driving me crazy!
- Go!
-  Let me go!
Don't push me down! This is driving me crazy!
She's climbing!
- They're climbing up!
-  This is tiring.
They all are up there.
- Jong Kook.
-  What's that?
(Jong Kook's one blow drops so many people from the buoy.)
What was that?
Look at her!
(Bo Ah never falls from the buoy no matter how steep it becomes.)
- Hurry up, Seok Jin!
-  Bo Ah!
Bo Ah, I'll be there soon.
(Now, Su Jin changes her target to Kwang Soo.)
(She is one scary woman.)
(Let me go up.)
- Bo Ah, wait for me!
-  Stop him!
Don't let him go up!
(Bo Ah still hangs on the buoy.)
(Bo Ah, wait a little longer.)
(The centre couple enjoy seeing them struggle.)
Come back down!
(Struggling)
- Seok Jin!
-  Hold on, okay?
- Hold on to it.
-  Seok Jin!
What are you doing, Kwang Soo? Where are you going?
Kwang Soo!
You'll fall apart.
This doesn't count.
(They're having their own competition.)
Wait for me, Bo Ah!
(I'll be back, Bo Ah. Wait for me.)
(Suddenly, Jae Seok reaches for the buoy.)
Jae Seok is making his way up!
(Stop Jae Seok!)
(Hopping)
(He makes a surprise attack.)
We did it. We both did it.
We did it!
(Jae Seok and In Young takes the win.)
(Look how unfortunate I am.)
(I didn't come back in time.)
(Team Jae Seok gets the second row.)
Let's go right away.
There's another chance for the second place.
- There's one more for second place.
-  All right.
Watch out for Su Jin.
Watch out.
Watch out for Su Jin. This is a word of caution.
- You held onto my back, right?
-  Yes.
I'm sorry, Bo Ah.
- You had to be fast.
-  I was so close.
Let's go again. In one.
(The third round starts.)
(Everybody goes for the yellow again.)
(Splashing)
(She swims like she's in the Taeneung Training Center.)
(Hyeon Gyeong moves from one buoy to another.)
It's this one!
- It's this one.
-  Hurry!
- Kwang Soo.
-  It's this one!
- It's this one!
-  Look at Kwang Soo.
- Kwang Soo's got it.
-  It's this one.
- No, no.
-  Is that it?
- Go, go!
-  Stop pulling me down.
Stop it.
Don't give up!
(I'm here.)
In 1, 2, 3.
(Hold on to my hand.)
(He lifts her up.)
(He's like a fisherman.)
In 1, 2, 3. Hurry.
(They make a heart.)
(Jong Kook and Jin Young take the win.)
(Jong Kook is incredible.)
(They clench the second row.)
I want to go with Jong Kook too.
- Bo Ah, I'm bleeding.
-  I want to go with Jong Kook.
Let's keep going.
(Here's a missing pair of pants.)
- I found this.
-  Has anybody lost their shorts?
(Has anybody lost their shorts?)
Anybody's shorts?
(Are those mine?)
- Who's is it?
-  Where did your pants go?
Give it to him.
Why is he always taking his pants off?
(Team Ji Hyo is in the centre while Jae Seok and Jong Kook are second.)
Hey, Bo Ah. Watch which buoy it is.
It's going to be two buoys. They're different colours.
(The targets are one blue buoy and a yellow one.)
- Get that one.
-  Check the blue one.
Come here!
(Thanks to Hyeon Gyeong, Kwang Soo and she takes an easy win.)
Let's go, Bo Ah.
(There's only one space left in the third row.)
Bo Ah, you are here.
We both made it.
(After a fierce competition,)
(the three teams make hearts at about the same time.)
You came in first.
(Seok Jin and Bo Ah are the winners.)
Bo Ah. Yes!
(The rest of the teams are in the fourth row.)
Hold on. Some of you...
- They've changed, right?
-  Yes, a bit.
Some of you look more beautiful without any make-up.
Hyeon Gyeong looks prettier without make-up.
Su Jin as well.
In Young too.
- Stephanie's the same.
-  Jin Young too.
Zico too.
- It's everybody.
-  Zico too?
- Zico has no make-up on.
-  You look better like that.
You look better like that.
- Look at Bo Ah.
-  She looks good.
- You look better without make-up.
-  That's right.
(In a little while, some of these people...)
(will disappear from the screen without a trace.)
(Who will be the last one standing?)
This must be the chance to turn things around.
- What's all this?
-  We are in the centre.
- Come here.
-  Is this the third row?
-  Does it matter if it's 3rd or 4th?
- It does matter.
-  This is the second row.
We're in the second row.
Are we in the second row?
Do you have to go now?
- Pardon?
-  She has to go first.
- What? Really?
-  She was supposed...
to fly for her next event which would have been enough time.
But the weather hasn't been good, so her flight got cancelled.
We're sorry to let her go, but she has to take the train.
She has to get going now.
- I'm sorry, Jong Kook.
-  That's all right.
Good job, Jin Young.
Great job!
Good job, everybody.
- Thumbs up
-  Thumbs up.
- See you later, Jin Young.
-  Good work.
- Bye.
-  Good work!
Jong Kook, you get the camera to yourself.
That's good.
(Who's that?)
The guy at the other end looks like my neighbour.
- My goodness.
-  I'm a celebrity.
A few teams didn't gain a win in the last game.
This is your chance to flip the table.
- It's called, "Camera On/Off".
-  "Camera On/Off".
- What is it?
-  It's "On/Off".
You can bet points you've earned...
and gain bonus points.
- There are cameras on both sides.
-  They're here.
If you disconnect one of the cords,
the screen will either stay on or turn off.
We have to unplug one of them.
- I'm really bad at this.
-  It's up to luck.
Yes, if the screen doesn't go off you get twice the points you bet,
but if it goes off, you lose all the points you bet.
You have to be wise about this.
You can only bet from the points you've earned.
Like I said before, the penalty has to do with the blue screen...
It's chroma key.
Are you really going to do this?
- What's all this?
-  It's a penalty.
- Is this paint?
-  This is too much.
(Who will fall to humiliation?)
Look. Haha and Stephanie will bet everything they have.
- Would they?
-  Of course.
- Gary and Su Jin...
-  They'll bet everything too.
- I'm betting everything.
-  You need 10 points at least.
We bet five points.
This is all-in.
- They're betting five points.
-  We'll bet everything too.
- How many do you have?
-  We have four points.
- Then, we'll start with Haha.
-  Okay!
- Let's do this.
-  Let's watch them first.
Should we watch them first?
- We'll go.
-  It's either 1 or 2.
- In 1, 2, 3.
-  In 1, 2, 3.
Make up your mind!
(Stephanie chooses number one.)
(On or off)
Make up your mind!
(How will the monitor respond?)
(Oh, no!)
(It turned off!)
- We are good now.
-  Yes.
(They bet everything.)
(He's stunned.)
- It's done now.
-  We got this.
- We are good.
-  There's a good chance.
This is for real.
- I'm glad we got rid of them.
-  They get the last place.
Gary and Su Jin, you're fourth row. How many points are you betting?
- We'll bet all 4 points.
-  They are betting 4 points.
- This is your last chance.
-  It'll be double or nothing.
In one...
Two...
(Su Jin succeeds.)
They did it.
That's amazing.
They have eight points now.
- We'll bet everything.
-  I hope they don't take it.
- It's all or nothing?
-  That's it.
- I hope the screen goes off.
-  We need another loser.
- Go for it!
-  In 1, 2, 3.
(She unplugs number two.)
(It's all or nothing.)
(What is the result?)
(The monitor stays on.)
(Seok Jin and Bo Ah earn bonus points.)
(I'm doomed.)
That's 14 points.
- My goodness.
-  You have to bet all you have.
We'll bet 7 points and leave 1 point.
- It's okay.
-  You never know.
- Okay, Kwang Soo.
-  I hope it goes off this time.
- In 1, 2, 3.
-  Turn off.
(They choose number one.)
(The monitor stays on.)
- Oh, my goodness.
-  Why did so many stay on?
It's 15 points.
- Wow.
-  They get the first place.
(Who knew Kwang Soo will get lucky this time?)
How many went off?
(They climb up to the first place.)
We'll bet eight points.
We'll bet eight.
Make us laugh.
You're only betting eight? You won't come in last.
In Young says she's really bad at this. Same goes for me.
I never pick the right one.
- I recommend number two.
-  In Young, don't listen to him.
- I say two.
-  Just pick whichever you want.
- Have you made up your mind?
-  Please!
- Please.
-  In Young, trust your instincts.
- Just go with your instincts.
-  Trust your instincts.
- Hey, think again.
-  In one...
- Did you think it over?
-  Turn off. Please.
- Let's go. In 1, 2, 3.
-  Please don't go off.
(The screen is out.)
(The monitor goes off.)
(They're always unlucky.)
- Way to go.
-  They were in the first place.
- Oh, gosh.
-  I only need two points.
Come on, In Young.
- I bet five points.
-  I'll beat you again.
Okay, I'll bet 5 points and leave 2 behind.
Are you ready?
- Yes.
-  We'll start.
- I hope he doesn't get it.
-  In 1, 2, 3.
- Turn off.
-  Go!
(He chooses number one. What is the result?)
(The monitor stays on.)
(Exclaiming)
It was always number two for me from the moment I walked in here.
This is why I hate him.
What are you complaining about?
- Kwang Soo's team is first place.
-  Yes.
Seok Jin's team is second place, right?
- You have to bet everything.
-  Please.
What happens if we bet everything and then lose it all?
Then they won't be last place any more.
Either way, bet everything.
This kid is really not that bold.
Bet it all
- It's all or nothing.
-  They're tempting you.
(Don't get swayed.)
- Really?
-  Bet it all
- Bet it all.
-  It's all or nothing.
- Ji Hyo is good at these things.
-  But...
- Zico, you got dragged into this.
-  I take risks.
- That's right.
-  It suits you.
- It's all or nothing.
-  I can do this, right?
- All right.
-  I'm confident.
- Believe in yourself.
-  I won't regret after.
- Let's do this.
-  Let's go.
- Would things turn around?
-  Let's watch the monitor.
- In 3, 2, 1.
-  In 3, 2, 1.
(They choose number 2.)
(Please let them fail.)
(The monitor stays on.)
(Ji Hyo and Zico succeed this mission.)
- We did it. We have 16 points!
-  Yes!
- We are first place.
-  Seriously, Ji Hyo?
- This is perfect.
-  You two are incredible.
Look at you two.
Why is Haha's team on our screen?
- I'm not on my screen either.
-  Kwang Soo is on our screen.
- This is irritating.
-  Hold on.
There's a twist at the end!
(I think there was something suspicious.)
Am I wrong? There's nothing?
Come on.
- You got me.
-  There's no twist to this.
- I thought...
-  What are you trying to do?
- You sounded so hopeful.
-  My heart was racing.
- You were so nonchalant.
-  That's right.
(We will make twists from now on.)
(Ji Hyo and Zico are the ultimate centre couple.)
This is making me nervous.
- Stephanie and Haha are last place.
-  We are second row.
- Thank goodness we're second.
-  My goodness.
Centre, centre
- Are you second?
-  How did we end up last?
- I'm third row.
-  Please stand behind the box.
All couples except the centre couple...
- will open the boxes. Open them.
-  Open them.
Gosh, what's this?
(These blue outfits will make them blend in.)
It's just the top.
You want us to put this on our faces?
Isn't this too much?
(Paint for colouring their faces)
- This is your punishment.
-  But...
I like these pants. They're comfortable.
Can I have them?
They're good, right?
(Gary does Zico's dance in his comfortable pants.)
- I should wear these to Itaewon.
-  In Young.
You don't have to put these on.
(Either way, these won't make you look pretty.)
This is nice. This looks so nice.
- It looks nice on you.
-  It does.
- They look really nice.
-  Why is it always you and me?
- I'm so mad.
-  It just had to be these.
I want to see this again.
- There's a show in Las Vegas.
-  Go away.
- They're called Blue Man Group.
- I'm being serious.
-  Do we do this too?
They're called Blue Man Group.
- Girls should get painted.
-  I can do it.
- Are you painting his entire face?
-  You're supposed to.
- Can you do it?
-  He disappeared.
- He's more handsome this way.
-  Can I try it?
(She wants to give it a try.)
Do you think I'm a merchandise?
Do it for her too. Do it for Stephanie.
No, draw something pretty. Draw a heart.
I'm so relieved we didn't come in last.
- What just happened?
-  I didn't know it was this bad.
(Shocking)
- Are you okay?
-  He doesn't look okay.
- They're going to disappear now.
-  All right.
- They're gone.
-  Wow.
Haha and I are here for sure.
- I only see your eyes.
-  We'll keep going.
- Squids!
-  They're squids!
(The change the background into squids.)
(Where are you, Gary?)
We'll end off today with my partner's song.
Let's play Block B's new song.
Okay, everybody. Great work!
Block B!
(The chroma key changes the scene into a night club.)
(You can't see them but they are dancing.)
We disappeared!
Where are you? I can't see.
(Stephanie is shrugging her shoulders.)
- What are you guys doing?
-  People can't even see you.
(It's a world where only those in the centre stand out.)
- I'm a toy
-  We can only see Zico.
(Survival of the centres)
(Thank you to all the guests who made all of us laugh.)
(7 years, 71 months, 2142 days, 300 episodes)
(7 vs 300)
(This is the biggest mission ever.)
(Running Men warriors are not afraid of anything.)
(They're not afraid of being humiliated.)
(300 warriors challenge them.)
(And)
(Don't be deceived.)
(The members took the bait.)
(300th Episode Special: 7 vs 300)