(Machines are an apparatus that move using power.)
(Human and machine)
(Human hands created machines.)
The tendency to depend on machines is getting severe.
More people are getting addicted to smart phones.
The number of jobs disappearing will surpass the number of jobs created.
(Machines are now replacing humans.)
(Messi competes against a robot goalkeeper.)
(And finally, machines are about to surpass humans.)
It's tough for humans to beat artificial intelligence.
- Watson, who is Jude?
-  Yes.
(Computer beats humans on a quiz show.)
Do you think robots will take over the world?
Don't worry. Even if I evolve into a terminator,
I will keep you warm and safe in my evil zoo.
(The unavoidable competition will be held today.)
(Human versus Machine)
(Hyeri, the ultimate weapon)
(Song Min Ho and Nam Tae Hyun of WINNER)
(Running Man versus Machine, a match where no one backs down)
How can we beat that?
(Will the heartless artificial intelligence win?)
(Or will the human's instinct counter-attack them?)
It's the final war that Running Man has declared against machines.
(The final war begins now.)
(Dogok-dong, Gangnam-gu, Seoul)
Jae Seok and Seok Jin's...
one-on-one preliminary match will begin now.
What?
A preliminary match for what?
- What is it?
-  Starting now,
without a GPS...
(Can they not use a GPS?)
- I have no sense of direction.
-  I find my way very well.
I have no sense of direction, whatsoever.
He has no sense of direction.
- In the past,
-  I'm terrible.
he was known for two things.
No sense of direction and troublemaking.
(He was known for having no sense of direction and for making trouble.)
I am serious.
He was well-known for that.
Okay.
You will only use a map and the provided address...
- to go and pick up the guests.
-  Is that right?
- Here's the address.
-  That's an old map.
- In the old times...
-  22-19 Cheongdam-dong,
- This...
-  Gangnam-gu, Seoul.
You can't use any digital devices.
You're banned from using a GPS or a cell phone.
This is crazy.
This is too tricky.
Without using any digital devices, GPS or cell phones...
I can't make it to a grocery store without a GPS.
I know Seoul better than him.
I don't know the roads well.
I really don't know my way around.
It's impossible for me to win.
You can go now.
Why is Kwang Soo my partner?
It's a game I just can't win.
(The mission is to find the guests without using a GPS.)
(The GPS was first introduced in England during the 1920s.)
(In 1997, the GPS with a 2D map was released in Korea.)
It is a device that gives you detailed information of the roads...
so that you can find your way easily on trips.
Go straight until you receive the next direction.
(It has location detection ability.)
(It guides you through the fastest route.)
(They are freed from machines.)
(They must find the guests using only maps.)
(Seok Jin and Jae Seok head to Cheongdam-dong at the same time.)
(The pick up location is 22-19 Cheongdam-dong.)
I've thought of this before.
I've thought about what would happen if there were no GPS.
I can't even find the exit.
I have to go towards Yangjae Station, right?
(He first heads towards Yangjae Station.)
It's 22-19.
(All he has is a map.)
All right.
But 22-19 is...
I've never...
read a map before.
Where is 22-19?
(Even Jae Seok is struggling.)
Let's see...
Gosh, I want to...
I want to press this part.
After pressing it,
can't I zoom in?
It's so frustrating.
(Haha and Ji Hyo leave Ttukseom Resort at the same time.)
All right. I will...
go to a real estate agency as soon as I get there.
They are all old, so a real estate agency...
or a police station is the place to go.
Where do you go when you get lost as a child?
You go to a police station.
(In old times, people went to the police station when lost.)
I will go to a police station.
(She will go to a police station.)
I don't know where the police station is.
(It will be a tough journey.)
Where is the police station?
397.
(I didn't know how precious a GPS was.)
I found it.
(Did he find it?)
It's here.
I should go this way.
I'll make a P-turn here and come back.
There's a gas station over here.
(There's a gas station nearby.)
Instead of going into the gas station,
I'll turn right.
(Kwang Soo's destination is also Hapjeong-dong.)
What should I do?
I don't think I should get off this road.
(He is moving in the complete opposite direction.)
It's Dongjak Bridge.
(He found a path to Dongjak Bridge.)
Should I get off here?
I missed it. What should I do? I missed it.
I missed it.
I think this is the way to Namyangju.
What should I do? Should I cross Hannam Bridge?
(He's getting further away from Hapjeong-dong.)
I think I should cross Hannam Bridge.
That's the road to Hannam-dong. I need to go...
I missed it!
Whatever. I'm going to drive all the way to Busan today.
There's a police officer.
(Officer, please help me.)
Hello, Sir.
Do you know the way to Hannam-dong?
- Hannam-dong?
-  Yes.
It's right across this bridge.
- That's Hannam-dong?
-  Yes.
- Exactly where are you going?
-  Hannam-dong...
It's Hapjeong-dong.
(Guest pick up location: Hapjeong-dong, Mapo-gu)
I'm sorry. I meant Hapjeong-dong not Hannam-dong.
- In Mapo-gu?
-  Yes.
Then why did you come this way?
Is this the wrong way?
From here,
you need to go in the opposite direction for Hapjeong-dong.
- You can't turn around here.
-  I see.
So this is the fastest way.
I should cross Dongjak Bridge then. Thank you.
- Thank you, Sir.
-  You look handsome.
Thank you, Sir. Salute!
(Police officers are always there for us.)
(He finally finds the right direction and sets off.)
(It's so difficult to be independent from machines.)
(Who is the guest that they will meet today?)
(With lively bobbed hair,)
(she's a woman whose bright smile is beautiful.)
(They are both cute and chic.)
(These two men are full of charm.)
(The drivers are on their way to pick up the guests.)
I think I know roughly where this is.
It's near Cheongdam Nursery School.
I found where it is.
(He found the location of his destination.)
I found it!
From now on, I should walk on foot.
I think it's somewhere near here.
I think I should take a look around here.
22-19.
It's around here.
(It is frustrating since they can't use their phones.)
(Laughing)
Isn't this it?
The zip code is 06062.
This is 1-11.
Then it's not this place.
Excuse me, what is the address of this place?
It's 22-20.
Did you say 20? Then 19 is the next one.
(19 is next door.)
This must be it.
It's here. Wait.
It's 20. This is it!
I found it.
(Seok Jin arrived at 22-19.)
I think it's nearby.
Wait, is this it?
(Jae Seok also arrived at 22-19.)
There are many...
(Who arrived first, Jae Seok or Seok Jin?)
Yes!
(Inside the building, a charming woman is waiting for them.)
(She resembles the beauty of spring.)
Oh, my.
Hello.
Are you today's guest?
(A charming woman is getting her hair done.)
(Who will it be, Jae Seok or Seok Jin?)
It's Hyeri.
Hello.
Are you the guest today?
Are you not?
- What are you doing here?
-  What?
(It's the rising actress, Hyeri.)
(From Hyeri of Girl's Day,)
(she has transformed into an actress.)
My mouth is paralysed from the cold.
(Thanks to Hyeri, everyone in Korea is reminiscing the 80s.)
(Hyeri captivated the viewers' hearts.)
Are you not?
- What are you doing here?
-  What?
They told me to find a place with the address 22-19.
So I was looking for this place.
- Really?
-  Yes.
- Wow.
-  Am I right? Yes!
- Hyeri.
-  Hyeri.
- It's nice to see you.
-  Goodness.
Thank you.
- You look very cute in person.
-  Oh, gosh.
Thank you.
What should we...
It's Jae Seok.
(Jae Seok is calling Seok Jin.)
Hello, Jae Seok.
- Are you there yet?
-  Did you find it?
I'm at the intersection in Dosan-daero.
- You're at the intersection?
-  Yes.
Wait a minute.
- Let's take a photo.
-  Sure.
(It's my victory.)
He's at Dosan intersection.
- He's a fool.
-  A fool.
He must be a fool. He was so confident.
All right.
(A smile of triumph.)
(Laughing)
(What's he doing?)
(Hello, Seok Jin.)
(Jae Seok walks out from the bathroom where he was hiding.)
Oh, my.
How embarrassing.
This is embarrassing.
(I'm so embarrassed.)
You're great at acting.
(His compliment sounds menacing.)
You're a great actress.
(How did this happen?)
Hi, Hyeri!
Goodness.
Hello. Hyeri.
It's been a long time.
- Are you healthy and well?
-  Yes.
- Really?
Oh, my.
Do I need to take a photo with Hyeri?
- Really?
-  Oh my goodness.
- Come here.
-  Okay.
(Even without a GPS, I can find my way to Hyeri.)
- Finish getting your hair done.
-  All right.
- See you later.
-  Where are you going?
I need to wait for Seok Jin.
Get your hair done. I'll go hide.
Hyeri, pretend that I didn't arrive yet.
- All right.
-  I'll be hiding here.
This is funny. It's so fun.
You're great at acting.
My goodness.
How could you just hang up on me?
How could you... You're better than him.
You looked innocent.
- Really.
-  So...
Hyeri, Seok Jin and I are on the same team.
- Yu.
-  Hye.
- Jee.
-  Cross!
- Let's get going. Let's go.
-  Yu Hye Jee.
- Let's go, Hyeri.
-  All right.
(How are Gary and Kwang Soo doing on their race without a GPS?)
Is this the right way?
Is this it?
I think it is.
This must be a coincidence.
(He found it by chance.)
(He gets out of the car to check the address.)
(Is it YG Entertainment?)
Hello.
Is the address here 397-5?
- Yes.
-  Is it?
(He found the destination without a GPS.)
Then who could the guest be?
(Where is the guest?)
(He looks confused.)
(Wriggling)
Hold on.
(Wait a minute.)
(He's acting awkwardly.)
It's Song Min Ho.
- Hello.
-  Are you today's guest?
Yes, I am.
(Song Min Ho is the charismatic rapper of WINNER.)
- You look handsome.
-  Thank you.
I need to take a photo with you.
(He first takes a photo to complete the mission.)
(Two rappers take a photo together.)
(But it looks like a star and an ugly man.)
(Haha and Ji Hyo have arrived near Cheongdam-dong.)
It's strange. I can't find it when I need it.
Wait, I think it'll be here.
(He is looking for a real estate agency.)
There are many real estate agencies here.
(There are many over here.)
I've already succeeded.
(I'm going to win.)
I found it! I found the police station!
Oh, yes! Oh, yes!
(Guest pick up location: 5-9 Cheongdam-dong, Gangnam-gu)
Hello, Sir.
Do you know where 5-9 Cheongdam-dong is?
- We are over here.
-  I see.
So 5-9 is over here. Cheongdam intersection is over here.
- I need to turn left here.
-  You need to go this way.
- I need to go this way.
-  I see.
Thank you.
(Haha versus Ji Hyo)
(Who will arrive first?)
I found it, I found it!
Is the guest in the salon here?
(Haha arrives at the front door of the building.)
(Ji Hyo arrives at the parking lot in the basement.)
Hello.
What is the address of this building?
- It's 5-9.
-  Is it 5-9?
It is the salon. I was smart to come here.
(Running)
(Oh, my.)
(Goodness, it's Ji Hyo.)
(Haha and Ji Hyo arrive at the same time.)
(They need to find the guest first.)
Oh, my.
Where is the guest?
Who is it?
(He kidnaps the guest.)
Why are you doing this?
Come here.
- Hello.
-  I need to take a photo with you.
-  I need to take a photo.
(He takes a photo immediately.)
(It's Tae Hyun.)
(It's Nam Tae Hyun of WINNER who has a sweet voice.)
(He is skilled in not only dancing and singing, but acting as well.)
That was close.
(A one-second difference separated the winner from the loser.)
- It's hectic from the first meet.
-  I know.
So you're the guest.
- I didn't know. They don't tell us.
-  Really?
- Oh, my.
-  Let's go.
(They complete their mission by picking up the guest.)
(Mok-dong SBS Broadcasting Centre in Yangcheon-gu, Seoul)
Is it that difficult?
You only need to visit a real estate agency.
(Gary, Kwang Soo and Min Ho arrive.)
- It's Kwang Soo and Gary.
-  It's Gary.
- Oh, it's Min Ho.
-  Oh, really.
- It's been a long time.
-  Today's guests are so handsome.
We have such handsome guests today.
We'd better keep a low profile today.
- She's coming.
-  Who's the other guest?
- Oh, my.
-  Hello.
-  It's Hyeri.
- It's Hyeri!
-  It's Deok Seon!
- It's Deok Seon.
-  Deok Seon.
- Deok Seon.
-  Hello.
- Oh, my.
-  It's Deok Seon.
- "The winner is Song Min Ho."
-  It's Min Ho and Tae Hyun.
- Hello.
-  Welcome.
- I can't believe this.
-  It's Deok Seon.
It's Deok Seon!
- Hyeri is here.
-  I can't believe this.
- It's unbelievable.
-  Hyeri's sister...
is a huge fan of yours.
But I like Hyeri more.
(He likes Hyeri more.)
Her sister is beautiful as well.
- Really?
-  She's so beautiful.
It's very nice to meet you.
It's very nice to meet you, too.
He's standing right next to Ji Hyo.
- I know.
-  I'm your fan.
- Tae Hyun loves you.
-  I'm your fan, too.
- By the way, I don't see Jong Kook.
-  Where is he?
- Hurray!
-  Hurray!
- Is he not coming today?
-  That's why...
- it's been unusually...
-  It'll be so nice.
- Really?
-  cheerful today.
- The staff look happy, too.
-  They do.
It's so peaceful.
We're finally free.
He's attending an awards ceremony abroad.
- I see.
-  Oh, okay.
If he's attending an awards ceremony,
I'd like to wish him good luck.
It'd be perfect if Jae Seok wasn't here.
(Haha wishes Jae Seok was also gone.)
It'd be so nice.
That'll never happen.
(Frozen)
You were not allowed to use your phones or GPS, right?
- No, we weren't.
-  We didn't use them.
The reason for this mission is because recently,
the match between Lee Se Dol and AlphaGo received a lot of attention.
Today's theme is "Human versus Machine".
Oh, "Human versus Machine".
- Are we fighting against them?
-  You'll fight against machines...
until there's only one survivor left.
The final winner...
will be given a prize...
while the others will be penalised.
By accomplishing intermediate missions,
- you'll win R Coins...
-  Really?
which you can use in the final mission.
For the intermediate missions,
- we'll hand out maps.
-  Okay.
- "Robot Arms"?
-  "Robot Arms".
- Is it the number of coins?
-  They're all in Ilsan.
- There's something at SBS, too.
-  We should start here.
We'd better start here.
You should finish all the races by 5pm...
- and arrive at the destination.
-  I see.
Okay, let's go!
- Let's go.
-  Let's go.
(The war between humans and machines begins.)
(What kind of cutting-edge robots will be waiting for them?)
What should we choose?
Robot Arms, 30 versus 30,
Rap Battle...
- Should we try Robot Arms?
-  Sure.
What do you think?
(They choose Robot Arms.)
We have to go to Deogeun-dong, Deokyang-gu, Goyang-Si.
(They have to get there without a GPS.)
(Pondering)
- Gyeongui Line...
-  Don't you know how to read maps?
I have no idea.
Deok Seon, please.
(She has the same character as her role does.)
Deok Seon has no idea.
Tae Hyun, do you know how to read maps?
Then again...
(Isn't this how you read it?)
I don't think you'd know.
(Tae Hyun is of no help, either.)
Let me see.
(Will we get there in time?)
I know we should take the Jayu-ro.
- We can't use the GPS?
-  No.
That's crazy. Gosh.
Should we follow them?
Should we follow Jae Seok?
Should we? It'll be too hard otherwise.
I'm sure Jae Seok will be able to find his way.
Jae Seok is good with directions.
I'll follow him.
Follow him.
I bet Gary will have a hard time.
Gary's very bad with directions.
Min Ho will look even more handsome around them.
He will shine among them.
- He definitely will.
-  You're right.
I wish I was in his place.
(Anyone can look handsome around them.)
I wish I was with Gary and Haha.
Hurry.
(To the left is a squid.)
(Behind is a mushroom.)
Where should we go?
Why don't we go to Rap Battle?
Do you want to go to Rap Battle?
(They decide to go to Rap Battle.)
Rap Battle.
Min Ho will have an advantage.
We just have to win against the machines.
- They can't be good rappers.
-  That makes sense.
- I can easily beat them.
-  Of course.
- Gosh, that confidence.
-  He's so confident.
(Min Ho is confident.)
I'm sure Min Ho has already come up with at least 100 rhymes.
I have 120 rhymes ready.
Great.
I have 125 of them.
Wow, that's swag.
Can we hear three of them?
Jo, yo, ho
(Jo, yo, ho)
(Haha used to be a part of Z-Kiri.)
- Is that the three?
-  Exactly.
"Jo, yo, ho".
(The hip hop brothers are ready to battle against the machines.)
(Team Jae Seok has already arrived at the destination.)
- It must be here.
-  It's here.
- Nice.
-  Yes.
(Excited)
Let's get off.
(Is that Seok Jin?)
Follow them.
It's better to come second than get lost.
You're right. Let's follow them.
We shouldn't lose them.
Where is it? It's here!
It's here. Let's get off!
- Get off.
-  Seok Jin, get off!
(They rush out of the car.)
Let's get off.
What is this?
- We came first!
-  We came first!
(What?)
(What is this?)
(The two teams are greeted by...)
(a robotic arm.)
Why is there a balloon?
(There's a balloon.)
- What is this?
-  This mission...
will require you to compete with a robotic arm.
(This industrial robotic arm was made in the 70s.)
(They're used in electronic production processes.)
(They can move 30cm in less than half a second.)
(German ping-pong player Timo Boll has competed against it.)
In this mission,
you will have to pop as many balloons as possible.
(Whoever pops 30 balloons the fastest wins.)
Popping balloons?
The robot will pop balloons on the screen...
while you will pop the real balloons.
Whoever pops 30 balloons first will win.
You got here first, so you can go first.
- I'll go first.
-  Okay.
I'll go first.
A battle between a human and a machine.
The human representative is...
Jee Seok Jin, the weakling.
Seok Jin will play first.
(Seok Jin will represent the humans.)
Humans can win.
- You're right.
-  Seok Jin.
- Look at that.
-  It's so fast.
(It's so fast.)
It's so fast.
- Look at that.
-  What is it doing?
- What's that?
-  It's dancing.
- It's dancing.
-  Is it dancing?
It's only warming up, but it's so fast.
- It's incredible.
-  Don't I look like a machine, too?
- It's really fast.
-  It's amazing.
This game will be no problem for the machine.
Look at what Seok Jin is doing.
- Get ready.
-  Gosh.
I'm losing my confidence.
(Seok Jin versus Robotic arm)
- It has started.
-  Something's coming up.
I can definitely win.
Okay.
(Popping)
I'll alternate between two hands.
- Left hand.
-  Oh, my.
This doesn't seem too hard.
With two hands...
He's in trouble.
(A bunch of balloons come up.)
He's in trouble. He has no chance.
Look.
- Look at that.
-  How will he beat that?
(Struggling)
He has no chance.
(Popping)
Look at the robot.
How can it do that?
How is it possible?
Look at that.
(How will he beat that?)
(I can't give up.)
(Seok Jin spurts.)
(I might be weak,)
(but I can't lose to a robot.)
(The robotic arm is done with the mission.)
(Despite his spurt,)
(Seok Jin lost by three balloons.)
- That was close.
-  That was really close.
(Disappointed)
(Seok Jin did a better job than expected.)
- That was close.
-  It's possible.
The thing is,
I hit the balloons with my knuckles because I'm used to that method.
- But these were on my fingers.
-  Why are you used to it?
(Jae Seok humiliates him.)
Why are you used to hitting things with your knuckles?
He's famous for his punches in Suyu-dong.
(His punches are famous in Suyu-dong.)
I'd love to experience them.
They're famous for being weak.
Please give me a punch.
- He's famous.
-  People love my punches.
His punches make people laugh.
Because they're so weak.
(Only humans can laugh after losing.)
Next, it's Hyeri's turn.
(The next human representative is Hyeri.)
- I can do it!
-  You can do it!
You can do it!
(They enthusiastically cheer for her.)
Ready.
Bring it on!
(The match between Hyeri and the robotic arm...)
(starts.)
You should read the pattern.
She's fast.
Hyeri, you're faster than the robot.
Good job.
(Hyeri is ahead so far.)
(The balloons will start swarming out soon.)
They'll swarm out.
Take it easy.
(I won't miss anything.)
(Hyeri has strong arms from years of dancing.)
(I'll show you what I can do.)
- Hyeri, you're doing great.
-  Jump!
- You're doing a great job.
(She's as fast as the robotic arm.)
- They're neck-and-neck.
-  No one knows what will happen.
(No one can predict who will win.)
(The robotic arm finished first again.)
(A swift and accurate movement)
That was close.
(Still, Hyeri did an amazing job.)
- Only three balloons were left.
-  She was fast.
My goodness.
(Is it even possible to beat the robotic arm?)
The weather is nice today.
(Team Gary is headed for Rap Battle.)
- Should I turn left?
-  Yes.
- Machines have no emotions.
-  Exactly.
But we have a rapper who is full of emotions.
(Gary, the hip hop poet)
- Stop it. You're flattering me.
-  I'm a huge fan.
I loved your rap.
Back in 1996...
(Arrogant)
I used to...
You know what?
Gary almost became a member of H.O.T.
- Really?
-  Stop it!
- Come on.
-  If he didn't do hip hop,
- That's embarrassing.
-  he could've replaced Kangta.
- Really?
-  Yes.
No, I couldn't.
Yes, you could've.
It's a bit too late to say now.
I did audition though.
You denied their offer afterwards.
(If Gary didn't deny the offer after passing the audition,)
(people would've seen this kind of H.O.T. debut in 1996.)
That's so interesting.
Isn't this the world's first rap battle against a machine?
How is it possible?
(What will these three rappers show us in the battle?)
(The three rappers have arrived for the battle.)
(Gary, one of the most famous rappers in Korea)
(Haha, a renowned rapper from the group Z-Kiri)
(Min Ho, a talented and rising new rapper of WINNER)
(Who will compete against them?)
Is this where the battle will take place?
Rap battle.
Don't we need more people for a rap battle?
- Rap battle.
-  What is this?
Where is the rapper?
Where is the microphone?
Welcome to the rap battle.
Before we begin,
you must show us your rap skills.
Don't you know how good we are?
What's up?
Roll your brows up
We have showed up
Everyone, put your hands up
(This is Z-Kiri style rapping.)
(He is ashamed of what he has done.)
I guess that was enough.
They only asked us to do this so we can see Min Ho rap.
(It's Min Ho's turn.)
Show us your rhyme.
Ayo, rap battle
This is hip hop
I want to eat some gimbap
(He wants some gimbap.)
Everyone, come here and hop
Yes.
This is hip hop, you know?
It's MINO in the building
The winner is Min Ho.
All right. It's time to begin the rap battle.
- Was that it?
-  You are making me feel awkward.
Delete my rapping scene, okay?
Don't make me repeat. Do as I say.
- Just remove the part.
-  Use Haha's part.
Get rid of it.
Here comes your opponent.
All right. Please come in.
What is that?
Rhyme box?
Rhyme box.
So that is the rhyme box.
(Who is going to have a rap battle against these three rappers?)
(It looks cool...)
(and has a colourful fashion style.)
- Wow.
-  What is that?
(Here comes the rapping robot.)
- Rapping robot?
-  Rapping robot?
Where is it from?
- Isn't that a plastic wrap?
-  Goodness!
(Plastic "wrap"?)
- So it's "Wrap"?
-  Is this what you're talking about?
So this was a "Wrap" battle?
So are we competing on how fast we unwrap things...
or how fast we wrap boxes?
(It was developed and sold in the 80s.)
(It's a robot that automatically wraps large factory objects.)
(It can travel 80m per minute.)
(Its radius of rotation is 800mm.)
(It works 200 times per charge.)
- So it's "Wrap"?
-  Is this what you're talking about?
Are we going to wrap the boxes?
(Why did we rap just a minute ago?)
We were shouting, "This is hip hop!"
You will compete against this automatic wrapping machine...
on how fast you can wrap objects.
You must wrap the bottom area 20 times as fast as you can.
(Whoever wraps it 20 times first wins.)
Please begin as soon as I blow the whistle.
- Let's go.
-  We can do it.
Ready.
(Will this robot, which was made for wrapping, win?)
(Or will Haha, a rapper from Z-Kiri, win?)
- Go.
-  Let's go.
Let's go.
(The machine moves.)
- All right. Let's go.
-  One.
Be careful.
Two.
(They are wrapping at similar speeds.)
(Haha is faster.)
- I'm dizzy.
-  Four.
It's only your fourth round.
- Five.
-  Fifth round.
(Haha's already on his fifth.)
- Six.
-  Haha, you'd better go lower.
(It's the sixth rotation.)
- Seven.
-  Seven.
(It's the seventh rotation.)
(He is getting noticeably slower.)
- Let's go.
-  Go. Yes.
Z-Kiri.
- Z-Kiri, show us your skills.
-  Z-Kiri!
(Haha falls down.)
- Oh, no.
-  You are on your ninth round.
Try to catch a rhythm.
- He is on his 10th.
-  10.
(The robot is on its 13th turn and Haha is on his 10th.)
- Come on.
-  Go, go, go!
Keep your rhythm.
Yes, keep the rhythm.
(Haha falls after his 11th turn.)
11. Haha.
- Come on, Haha!
-  You don't have time to rest!
(The robot is on its 13th turn with constant speed.)
- Z-Kiri.
-  You have bad stamina.
This is so tiring.
(He falls again.)
(I can't do this any more.)
(Haha gives up after his 13th turn.)
Haha has failed.
Well done.
You have done well.
- Well done.
-  This is so hard.
This... This is so hard.
It's because you have to keep your back bent.
This is so hard. Try it.
Try it. You'll die.
(Is it too tough for humans to beat a machine?)
Song Ji Hyo.
Yes.
- I will give it a try.
-  Stretch your arms out.
All right. Ready, set...
You can do it, Ji Hyo.
(Popping)
She's accurate.
(The second balloon is popped right away.)
You are doing well.
Good job.
(Here comes the swarm of balloons.)
There you go.
(The balloons bounce off.)
- Come on, Ji Hyo.
-  Goodness.
(Ji Hyo misses many balloons.)
- She is doing well.
-  Good job.
- She is catching up.
-  She might win.
- You're doing well.
-  Come on.
- Come on.
-  Behind you!
(They are at a similar pace.)
- Behind you.
-  Come on, Ji Hyo.
(She is punching like Mayweather.)
(Can she defeat the robotic arm?)
Come on, Ji Hyo.
(There is only 1 left.)
(The robotic arm beats Ji Hyo by 1 balloon.)
That was so close.
- You lost.
-  Just one more.
You were one balloon short.
That was so close.
You were one balloon slower.
- It was 0.3 second faster.
-  Robots are not humans.
- Ji Hyo is a human.
-  That was so close.
That was close.
That was so close.
I thought you'd actually make it.
That's too bad.
(The robotic arm is victorious once again.)
- I will give it a try.
-  Okay.
- Come on!
-  Let's go.
- You can do it.
-  Go, Jae Seok.
You have good posture.
Get ready...
(Can Jae Seok beat the robotic arm this time?)
(The match begins.)
(Who will be victorious? A skilled man or a precise machine?)
(What was that?)
(A balloon came out from the back.)
(The balloon came out from the back.)
(It continuously comes out from behind.)
(What is the truth behind these mysterious balloons?)
(It was you.)
(Kwang Soo is more cruel than the robotic arm.)
(You can have as many balloons as you want, Jae Seok.)
(A human's enemy is another human.)
(The robotic arm is victorious.)
What was that?
Why were there so many balloons?
(It was just your imagination.)
No, there were 30 balloons.
There were too many balloons.
Only 30 balloons came out.
(The balloons seemed to be never-ending.)
(More balloons come out.)
(Kwang Soo is the master of trickery.)
What are you doing?
Come here.
What are you doing here?
(Screaming)
No, wait! It really hurts!
Hold on! Wait!
No! Wait!
Why isn't anyone helping me?
I will do it!
- Come out.
-  I will go out.
(Kwang Soo is taught a lesson.)
Are you serious?
How can you do this?
I won't do it any more.
It's too late.
- How dare he?
-  He thought you'd win without it.
All right. No more foul plays from now on.
(No more foul plays)
I promise. There will be no more.
All right. Who's next?
Tae Hyun is next.
(Tae Hyun versus the robotic arm)
Ready, set...
(Start)
He has a decent chance.
(He is slender.)
I wanted to be an athlete.
Many people gave me offers.
- Really?
-  What kind of sports?
Baseball, football,
- He's multi-talented.
-  MMA, aikido, taekwondo and more.
(Tae Hyun, the talented athlete.)
- He can do it.
-  The balloons are in the front.
There you go. He's fast.
They will come out fast.
Nice.
He is quick.
(He is faster than the robotic arm.)
(How will he handle the swarm of balloons?)
What's wrong with his face?
- Look at him.
-  Tae Hyun, control your face!
(He can't control his facial expressions any more.)
There goes Tae Hyun.
Control your face!
He's actually doing well. He might make it.
(Will he...)
(succeed?)
(I'll show you the potential of humans.)
(A skilled athletic man versus a precise machine)
(Extraordinary)
- You are almost there.
-  Come on.
(Nam Tae Hyun wins.)
- Wow.
-  Amazing.
(Nam Tae Hyun is victorious.)
You are amazing.
(Tae Hyun did the impossible.)
He was really quick.
- Tae Hyun.
-  Yes?
Everything was good except for your face.
He was fighting like a middle school girl.
(It's how a typical middle school girl fights.)
"Go away!"
Gosh...
Tae Hyun is the only one who succeeded.
I'm jealous.
- Thank you.
-  Gosh...
(Tae Hyun has six coins, and he's currently the front-runner.)
- Are you ready, Min Ho?
-  I am ready.
- I will show you what wrapping is.
-  Let's go!
- He's the wrapping genius.
-  Check it out!
- Don't use up all your strength.
-  Ready.
(Wrapping robot versus Min Ho)
Let's go!
You are much faster.
- Yes, that's it. That's good.
-  Wrapping, wrapping!
- I will never fall down.
-  He's fast.
- Wrapping.
-  You're doing well.
(Min Ho went around twice while the robot went around once.)
(Will Song Min Ho win?)
I am tired.
You can't be tired yet!
I'm tired. Wait.
- You went around three times now.
-  No, no.
- I am so dizzy.
-  Hey! Hey!
- Keep going.
-  I am so dizzy.
(Struggling)
I am too dizzy.
- You can do it.
-  This is too tough.
(We never imagined him to be that weak.)
- You can do it.
-  Min Ho, one more round!
- The robot is too strong.
-  That's it.
That's good, that's good.
(The wrapping robot gets ahead of Min Ho.)
Let's go. You have to go now.
(The machine doesn't get tired.)
(Screaming)
You can do it. You can do it.
(He got worn out after going around five times.)
- I can't do it.
-  You have to do it.
(Laughing)
- This is no joke!
-  He's so weak!
- This is too tiring!
-  Go! Go, Min Ho!
I have weak endurance!
Get up, you punk!
- I have weak endurance!
-  Get up!
Get up!
(It's just that I am scared.)
Come on!
It's the 20th round.
(The machine went around 20 times.)
- It's over.
-  It's over.
(The machine wins.)
It's crazy, isn't it?
(How can they beat this monster?)
This is the worst situation I had imagined.
(He's the last man standing.)
We can't possibly beat it.
(We can never beat machines.)
It doesn't make sense.
(Humans get tired,)
(but the machines never rest.)
(It makes a thundering noise, and its accuracy gives us the chills.)
(It's the moment humans feel weak.)
It doesn't make sense.
(Can humans never beat the machines?)
Now, I will show you how I wrap!
- Ready.
-  Go, Gary!
(Wrapping robot versus Gary)
Show us how you wrap!
- You are too fast.
-  I need to get a head start.
You have to do it fast in the beginning.
- Great. That's it.
-  The robot catches up soon.
Your speed is perfect.
That's good.
- It's a stamina fight.
-  Lower your body more.
You have to go even lower.
Yes. Just keep walking.
(But the machine is not stirred by it.)
A little bit more.
- Is this a penalty?
-  A little bit lower.
Lower your body more. I will push you.
- My bottom hurts!
-  I know, I know.
(Time passes.)
- You have to go lower.
-  10.
15.
This is the 15th round.
Hey.
Just run three more rounds.
- Go. Come on.
-  Go, Gary!
- Just three rounds.
-  That's great!
You have to win, Gary!
(Humans get tired more easily than machines.)
(But humans encourage each other.)
- You went around 17 times.
-  How many left?
Three rounds.
(And they become stronger.)
You have three more rounds to go.
Gather the last bits of your strength!
(Here I go!)
Take your time. You have to do it right.
(Whenever he takes a step,)
(his colleagues cheer him up.)
- It's the last round.
-  Lower your body more.
(There is a magical power about doing things together.)
(But machines will never understand it.)
This is 19. It's the last round, Gary.
- It's the last round.
-  It's the last. Do it well.
It's the last round.
Lower your body more.
- I'm done!
-  That's it!
(Gary finishes the last round.)
(Gary arrives first and wins.)
You won.
- It really hurts, doesn't it?
-  Good job.
(The human wrappers check on Gary first.)
The game is over.
You successfully completed the mission.
Each of you gets two coins.
Gosh, that was tiring.
- Wait. Where do we go next?
-  Where is "Path"?
Path is...
- Should we go with Path?
-  Yes.
- Wait, Hyeri. It's...
-  Sarihyeon-dong.
I will look for it.
- Okay. You look for it then.
-  Okay.
(Groaning)
(Does she have cavities?)
Should I take a look?
(Jae Seok wants to check the map.)
Thank you, Hyeri. I will check the map.
They don't even have the address.
They're trying to follow us.
- They don't know about the map.
-  They don't.
Where did the map go? I put it here.
Ji Hyo said she put it here.
- Is this a different car?
-  This is the right car.
Where did it go? Where did the map go?
(10 minutes before they moved the car)
Where did they put it?
(Tae Hyun stole the map from Team Seok Jin's car.)
(He knows how to keep another team in check.)
- Should we go there?
-  Yes.
- I think they will be kind.
-  Okay. Let's check.
They are going to ask.
Should we go steal their map?
- Let's go get their map.
-  Let's steal their map.
Did they take the map?
- Make a U-turn and...
-  I will go get their map.
(They are planning to steal Team Jae Seok's map.)
- They're out.
-  They're out.
- What's wrong?
Okay.
They don't even bother to get out of the car.
(What's going on?)
(Kwang Soo appears.)
Tae Hyun, do you have that?
Wait.
(We don't feel like talking right now.)
(Give me back my map!)
It's right here.
(Giggling)
They sensed it.
Sense what?
- That you are trying to steal?
-  They sensed it.
- Get in first.
-  Let's get going.
We missed the timing.
- We should've moved faster.
-  Why don't we have a map?
It's 764 Janghang-dong.
(Will they be able to find the place with the address?)
What's this place?
It was so tough to find this place.
How can people find this place?
It's a studio.
(What is the truth behind the hint, Path?)
- I'm curious.
-  Who owns this place?
(Gary's surprised.)
What's this?
- Are we the first to come here?
-  What's this?
There's a blindfold. What's this?
- It's a maze.
-  It's a maze?
We have to find the path!
This time, you will compete with a machine...
to escape a maze.
(It's a maze escaping match!)
All right.
Please bring out the opponent.
(Which robot will be playing this time?)
(What? Where is it coming from?)
(The door opens.)
(Is it coming out from there?)
(It's a robot vacuum.)
(In 2001, a Swedish vacuum company invented it.)
(Using the cameras on all sides, it checks where to clean.)
(It can clean the areas underneath sofas and beds, too.)
(Its auto-escape function enables it to escape from obstacles.)
(Its maximum speed is 35cm per second.)
(It's very cute.)
It hurts my pride.
It does hurt my pride.
The robot vacuum will try to escape the maze.
If you escape the maze faster than the robot, you will win.
But you will have to keep your eyes covered.
Okay.
Let's do that.
(Smirking)
(Don't you think you are underestimating us?)
- We could memorise the path.
-  We could.
(They are very confident.)
(They check every corner of the maze.)
(It would be too easy if they could memorise the path.)
Don't you think it's too complicated?
- Wait.
-  Gosh...
(They can't memorise it.)
(Robot vacuum will do a simulation of its performance.)
Come over here, cute.
(The cute robot vacuum starts.)
What can it do?
(It moves forward with composure.)
(It senses a wall...)
(and makes a left turn right away.)
It's good.
- It finds its way around well.
-  I can't believe it.
It's good.
- Is someone controlling it?
-  I know.
- How can it follow the path?
-  How can it avoid the dead ends?
We can't be easy on it.
It's fascinating.
We can memorise the path, right?
- Sure.
-  I memorised it.
- This is easy.
-  Right.
But I memorised the entire path.
I memorised the entire path. Is that okay?
Then we will start from the other side.
(No way.)
You are smart, aren't you?
I didn't think of that.
(His plan is ruined.)
I didn't think of that either.
(No wonder it was so easy to remember.)
My head hurts all of a sudden.
(Robot vacuum versus Gary)
- Ready.
-  Go, Gary!
- Go, Gary!
-  Good luck!
(Start)
Okay.
- It must be scary though.
-  It must be.
(The human has to use his senses to move forward.)
This is really tough!
Gosh! Where am I?
(To make it fair, both of them can rely on only one sense.)
(They are moving at a similar speed.)
I can't go as fast as I thought.
(Gary is on the bottom, and the robot is on the top.)
(The robot vacuum makes a smooth turn around a corner.)
(Gary is using his arms as his antennas.)
Hey! Wait!
- Is it tough, Gary?
-  This is...
(Gary loses his confidence.)
This is crazy. This is no joke.
(Gary struggles.)
This is crazy.
(He doesn't know the path.)
If I get lost once, that will be it for me. Wait.
(He sounds pitiful.)
Should I go forward?
(He's moving towards a dead end.)
Gosh... This is crazy.
What's this?
Wait.
(It's funny.)
It has to be a straight path.
Hey!
I am in trouble! Haha!
Min Ho! I am in great trouble!
(Bye, Gary!)
(The game is over.)
- Just walk towards the exit.
-  It's over.
We lost again.
- The time is up.
-  It's really tough.
Where am I?
If I get lost once, that will be the end.
It's really tough. It's tougher than you think.
(Next human player is Min Ho.)
- Ready.
-  Wait!
Wait!
Ready.
(Min Ho crawls fast.)
(He hits a wall.)
(The human player is fast this time.)
Yes. This is it.
(He's not afraid to hit walls.)
This way.
What is it?
(The robot vacuum is moving stably at a constant speed.)
Gosh, this is...
(He hits all the walls.)
Okay! I have a good feeling!
Go, Min Ho!
Come here.
(Team Jae Seok enters the mission place, too.)
(Hyeri guides him with her voice.)
(Floundering)
(The human is on the left, and the robot is on the right.)
You're doing great.
- Great!
-  I'm feeling good about this!
You can do this.
(He's better than me.)
Where is this?
Wait.
(The left side is a short cut, and the right side is a trap.)
(Will he go to the right?)
(He chooses to go to the left!)
I think I found the path!
(His confidence shoots up.)
He's amazing.
- Is he a genius?
-  Was I right?
You were right.
I am just following my gut feeling.
- He's really good.
-  He's very precise.
I can hear your voices.
Okay. I know the way out from here.
Wow. A young man is different.
(He hits a wall.)
That's it.
(Youth is painful.)
(The robot is playing the game mechanically.)
Min Ho! Move back a little!
- Okay.
-  You have to move back a little!
We can hear him from here.
(He desperately tries to win.)
- You can come here.
-  I'm so exhausted!
(The robot exit is on the bottom, and the human exit is on the top.)
(They are both near the finishing line!)
(It's Song Min Ho versus...)
(cute robot vacuum.)
(Which of them will be...)
(the final...)
(winner?)
That's crazy.
(They're both so close.)
- No way!
-  Wow!
(Song Min Ho wins!)
Bravo.
Success! I did it!
The robot did bad!
How did you get out?
That was crazy.
- How did you do that?
-  He knew the path.
- I just followed my feeling.
-  That doesn't work though.
Did you memorise the path?
I remembered the path around the middle.
Is that right?
We have to give it a try, too.
(It's Hyeri's turn now.)
I can't see anything. I have no idea.
- Gosh...
-  Gosh...
No way! She succeeded!
(Hyeri succeeds!)
- We'll do it.
-  You should speed up a little.
Why am I out of breath?
Why is he so slow?
- Hurry up!
-  I did it!
(Time's over)
(Currently, Min Ho has the most number of coins.)
(Finally)
What's this?
I hate getting plunged.
Are we getting plunged again?
I am scared.
It's really scary.
- It's horrifying.
-  I am really scared.
(The grand stadium for the last match.)
Jong Kook, who is currently in China,
also competed against machines...
while you were doing the same here.
He competed against three machines we use all the time.
How do you think it turned out?
- Please make a guess and vote.
-  I think he won by 2 to 1.
I think it's either this or that.
And...
I think it's either 2 to 1 or 1 to 1.
- We have to guess it right to win.
-  Yes.
What's the result?
The first match was juicer versus Jong Kook.
The first machine you will fight against is...
- a juicer.
-  Okay.
The one who produces a cup of juice first will win.
You have to fill the cup until the line.
- Okay.
-  Ready.
(Who will be the winner?)
(It's a juicing match.)
Start.
(The match starts.)
(Grunting)
(Grunts versus machine noises)
(It's a time of ordeal for oranges.)
(It's a competition between Jong Kook's momentary power...)
(and the juicer's consistent power.)
It's getting all over my hands.
(Squeezing)
(Juicing)
(It's nearing the end.)
Okay! I am done!
(What is the result?)
Stop.
I'm done, right?
I knew it. You machine...
A machine can't beat a human.
(Does he believe in humanism?)
Jong Kook won.
(Three people are out.)
- Jong Kook won?
-  Jong Kook won.
- How can you beat a juicer?
-  He's mad.
- Does it make sense?
-  He could do it.
How could he beat a juicer?
He had to juice oranges.
- That doesn't make sense.
-  He's not a human.
How can you beat a juicer?
Don't you think he needs a drug test?
Are you sure he's not a machine?
- No way.
-  And then?
The second match was AI Alkkagi versus Jong Kook.
I'm sure the machine won.
(Did Jong Kook win this match, too?)
- The game...
-  Jong Kook won.
(Some are thrilled, and some are devastated.)
- How did he do that?
-  We did it!
- We guessed it right!
-  What happened?
Everyone's gone.
Yes! This is amazing.
- This is unbelievable.
-  I hope he won all three.
- I made a wrong guess.
-  I hope he won all the matches.
- Right.
-  Tae Hyun will be the only winner.
- The last match was blender...
-  It's a blender this time.
- versus Jong Kook.
-  That's impossible.
(Blender versus Jong Kook)
(So many...)
(coins...)
(depend on this!)
The blender won.
(The machine won the last match.)
- I did it!
-  Gosh...
- Song Min Ho wins!
-  Yes!
He guessed well.
- I should've followed Min Ho.
-  That's unbelievable!
- You should've followed me.
-  Then that's four.
(Gary and Min Ho get 4 coins each.)
- Min Ho has 18 coins now!
-  He already has a lot.
Min Ho is unbelievable.
(Min Ho is winning with 18 coins.)
- That was crazy.
-  I think I have seven coins.
- He hit the jackpot.
-  I have nine.
- You will play the final game.
-  I am really bad at it.
It's called AI Kungkungtta.
- AI?
-  You'll play the word chain game.
- How can we beat a computer?
-  How can we win?
(Word chain game with a computer)
(How can we beat a computer?)
On your right, there are...
lanes from 1 to 9.
But you have different options.
You can change directions, or if you get a difficult word,
you can attack another person.
You can also get help from a news anchor.
- There are many option cards.
-  I'll just attack.
- Me, too.
-  Me, too.
That'll help us eliminate someone.
I need that.
(The members have obtained different kinds of chances.)
(They each stand on a lane.)
Running Man declared the final war against machines.
This is the final match, Kungkungtta.
Artificial Intelligence Kungkungtta!
(AI Kungkungtta)
- Hello.
-  I will win!
When I discussed with the crew,
they thought Jae Seok had the best chance of winning.
That's not true. I will eliminate either Kwang Soo or Seok Jin...
before I get eliminated.
- Why would you do that?
-  Which chance did you choose?
I will get eliminated anyway even if you don't do that.
On the other hand, they chose Kwang Soo as the best loser.
- Me?
-  Yes.
I'm a bookworm.
You're not holding anything in your hands.
I have a dictionary.
- A dictionary?
-  Yes.
I have two dictionary chances.
- Do you have two?
-  Yes.
Now, let me introduce your opponent.
It's an artificial intelligence programme.
Let's meet the opponent.
(Their last opponent is revealed.)
(Emerging)
(What is it now?)
Let's meet the opponent.
(It looks mysterious.)
(This is the final opponent.)
(Marvelling)
- That's a laptop.
-  Its name is...
J-bot. It's four years old.
It was born on August 18,
- 2013.
-  Is that right?
- It's the same age as my son.
-  I see.
Based on the standard dictionary,
this artificial intelligence programme...
- can play word games.
-  We can't beat it.
I'm getting nervous.
- I'm nervous.
-  If you fail to put in a word,
you'll be eliminated.
If you win, you'll move onto the next stage.
Until we have a final survivor,
the match between humans and the artificial intelligence...
will continue.
I'm getting nervous.
Will someone beat artificial intelligence?
They'll compete against artificial intelligence in a word game.
The final game, AI Kungkungtta,
begins now.
(Ai Kungkungtta begins now.)
- What's that sound?
-  You silly thing.
The match starts now.
Jae Seok, write your word.
I'm getting nervous.
You shouldn't start with a word that will end the game.
It's your first word. Make a careful choice.
Pick something difficult.
All right.
He's taking his time.
(It's not easy to pick a word.)
- He wrote "Summer".
-  "Summer".
(He enters the first word.)
- "Summer".
-  That's hard.
-  It wrote "Remuneration".
- Is that a word?
-  With the word "Remuneration",
J-bot counter attacked.
- "Remuneration"?
-  What does that mean?
Is that even a word?
Is there such a word?
I'm nervous!
"Remuneration".
What does that mean?
- I've never heard of it.
-  It's my first time hearing it.
It's similar in meaning to "Wage".
- I never heard it.
-  It's Min Ho's turn now.
- Choose your word.
-  Can we use the dictionary?
You have 30 seconds.
- Brass...
-  Brass, bronze...
I'm not sure.
- "Brass-copper".
-  What's that?
-  I know it.
Enter it if you're sure.
I think it's a word.
I've never heard it before.
Okay.
- It says, "Please enter a noun."
-  You made a mistake.
- He failed one time.
-  Was he confused?
If you make another mistake...
(He passed with "Brass".)
(What a relief.)
J-bot entered "Verb".
It's Gary's turn.
What will he write?
"Selfishness".
- "Personalism"?
-  "Personalism"?
- J-bot counter attacked...
-  Is that a real word?
with "Personalism".
Is there such a word?
- A word that starts with Deok?
-  "Deok Seon".
I thought of that, too.
How about "Nerd".
He has to come up with a word...
- that starts with "Deok".
-  This has nothing...
- to do with my will.
-  This one's hard.
Haha seems nervous.
- "Deok".
-  It's hard.
You have 30 seconds.
Write "Deok Seon".
- Write "Deok Seon".
-  I can't think of anything else.
Deok is hard.
Won't "Nerd" work?
(He's unsure.)
- Should I try?
-  I think it'll count.
- I think it will.
-  You can try.
- "That word does not exist."
-  Goodness.
(J-bot is strict.)
- It's not a word.
-  That word does not exist.
All right.
- It's artificial intelligence.
-  You have to do well.
- It's your last chance.
-  J-bot knows what it's doing.
You can use your chance if you want...
- or just give up.
-  "Nerd" was hilarious.
- How could he write that?
-  You have 30 seconds.
Oh, right.
All right.
"Deoksugung" worked.
"Deoksugung".
- It worked.
-  You were running out of time.
-  J-bot entered "Distress".
- "Distress".
-  It managed this time, too.
- The word is "Distress".
-  What does it mean?
- "Distress".
-  Is it "Tae"?
Write "Legend".
"Legend"?
Write "King".
Write "Tae Jin Ah".
- Hyeri entered "Sun".
-  "Sun".
- "Ear".
-  J-bot entered "Ear".
It's Tae Hyun's turn. If you're not sure...
- Can I write anything?
-  what the word means,
- click on the word...
-  He's so serious.
- and read its meaning.
-  He's focused.
Keep that in mind.
- "Ghost".
-  "Singyeongi"?
- "Singyeongi"?
-  What's that?
What does that mean?
It wrote "Singyeongi".
- Is that a word?
-  That's right.
"Singyeongi".
"Singyeongi"...
is a name of a plant.
It must be similar to "Jilgyeongi".
It's Ji Hyo's turn.
You have 30 seconds.
- What?
-  Will that work?
- I'm sure it will.
-  "Tooth".
- Does that work?
- "Basin"?
-  By writing "Basin",
- What's that?
-  J-bot counter attacked.
It wrote so many difficult words.
It's Kwang Soo's turn now.
Write "Meal".
- "Meal".
-  "Palm".
(It's Kwang Soo's turn.)
- "Jacob".
-  Hey.
J-bot entered "Product set"...
to counter attack.
Seok Jin.
(How will Seok Jin fight back?)
"Union".
(Seok Jin got a hint from J-bot.)
Seok Jin wrote "Union".
Next is "Legitimacy".
What does that mean?
- It returned back to him.
-  J-bot counter attacked.
Seok Jin, it's your turn again.
Go ahead.
I can't think of a word.
- You're running out of time.
-  You have no time.
- All right.
-  Go ahead.
You have 10 seconds left.
In 10, 9,
eight,
- Where's the cursor?
-  seven,
-  six, five,
- Just write anything.
-  four,
(Seok Jin forgot to move the cursor.)
(Will he fail?)
- Just write anything.
-  Four,
three...
- "Red".
-  Okay.
(Red)
- It's your turn.
-  "Saxophone"?
- "Phone"?
-  It counter attacked.
- It has to start with "Phone".
-  I once lost because of "Phone".
- "Phone"?
-  Is there anything?
He's in trouble.
Kwang Soo, you shouldn't write a compound word.
- "Phone case".
-  Will it work?
-  "Phone case".
- It's a compound word.
-  Try it.
- Try it.
-  Go ahead.
It's a crisis.
Dictionary chance!
(Kwang Soo wants to use a chance.)
Dictionary chance.
You can search the dictionary, starting now.
Will it be enough time?
- How much time does he have?
-  He has one minute.
I don't think there's any word.
- Find a word in the dictionary.
-  There's nothing.
- I can't believe this.
-  Is there a time limit?
He has one minute.
- He is looking now.
-  I don't think there's one.
(Kwang Soo is fighting against artificial intelligence.)
(He's been flipping through the dictionary for 20 seconds.)
- Time is running out.
-  It has to start with "Phone".
There's no "Phone"!
(There's nothing.)
There's no word that starts with "Phone"!
Gosh.
I have two dictionary chances, but they're of no use!
- Wait!
-  There's nothing.
Give me another dictionary! It doesn't have the word.
- That can't be.
-  It's true.
That's the only dictionary we have.
I'm sorry.
Is there no word that starts with "Phone"?
- Is that true?
-  Kwang Soo, you're doomed.
Wait.
"Phone".
- You have 30 seconds left.
-  What should I do?
"Phone".
- "Phone"...
-  Is there really nothing?
(Kwang Soo is unlucky as always.)
Why do you all look away?
(Don't look away from me.)
(They avoid eye contact.)
- Hey.
-  "Phone".
- Isn't there any word?
-  You have 10 seconds left.
- In 10,
-  Oh, no.
- nine,
-  You'll be eliminated.
eight, seven,
six, five,
- Just write anything.
-  four, three,
- "Phones".
-  two,
- one.
-  It's over.
You're eliminated.
(It was expected.)
Kwang Soo is eliminated.
No, Kwang Soo.
- Wow.
-  Oh my goodness.
Kwang Soo.
My goodness.
- It's too early.
-  Kwang Soo.
Wait.
Please stand in the middle.
No, wait!
- Kwang Soo.
-  He didn't use his second chance.
I have one chance left.
Please look at me.
- Bring your arms together.
-  It's also the dictionary chance.
Kwang Soo.
Out.
(The floor opened.)
(He falls.)
- Kwang Soo has been...
-  That's scary.
eliminated.
(It was scary.)
Is it scary?
- Goodness.
-  It was fast.
It's so scary.
Kwang Soo, are you okay?
He's been eliminated.
Jae Seok!
You fall longer than you think.
It looks quite high.
I fell for at least four seconds.
- That's scary.
-  We can fall on our bottoms.
Gosh, we survived.
I'm scared.
(Kwang Soo is eliminated.)
Kwang Soo is the first to be eliminated.
(Kwang Soo is sitting here.)
- Now...
-  Do I look stupid?
- I'm so upset.
-  This is exactly what...
- the staff had expected.
-  "Phone" is hard.
There is no word for that.
You could have written "Font".
- There was that.
-  That could have worked.
- "Font"?
-  The second round...
will begin.
(The second round begins.)
Ji Hyo will start the round.
Please enter a word.
- Me?
-  Yes.
You can write any word...
that does not end the game immediately.
You're lucky to be the first.
Write anything.
Will this work?
Maybe.
- It won't count.
-  It will.
- Ji Hyo wrote "We".
-  It knows "Linen"?
It knows "Linen"?
- You're in trouble.
-  J-bot wrote "Linen".
- Ji Hyo, I'm disappointed in you.
-  J-bot...
- Jae Seok.
-  Tae Hyun!
- It wasn't intentional.
-  Tae Hyun.
Tae Hyun!
(Come here!)
- It wasn't intentional.
-  What should I do?
- Ji Hyo.
-  It's unbelievable.
The difficulty suddenly became higher.
- It's the computer's fault.
-  There's no word for "Nen".
- "Nen"?
-  The difficulty...
- went up.
-  "Linen" is...
a textile made from the fibres of flax plants.
- This is hard.
-  This word is included...
- in the standard dictionary.
-  Ji Hyo, you're horrible.
- Jae Seok.
-  Think of anything.
You can use your chances.
You have to think of a word that starts with "Nen".
(Rummaging)
I'll use my chance!
- I can't think of a word for "Nen".
-  "Nen"...
You can use your chance cards.
It's "Nen".
(Which chance will he use?)
(Everything depends on this chance.)
I'll choose change of direction.
- He chose change of direction.
-  I'll choose change of direction.
(He changed the direction.)
- He chose change of direction.
-  Don't do that!
- Ji Hyo is up next.
-  Don't do that.
Go at each other.
- That's great.
-  What word begins with "Nen"?
- Ji Hyo, please enter a word.
-  It's coming back to me.
(How does it feel?)
Why did you choose change of direction?
I barely survived just a while ago.
It's a change of direction.
I'm sorry. I choose to skip my turn.
- She chooses to skip her turn.
-  Is it me?
(I shouldn't be excited.)
- We will skip her turn.
-  Is it me?
- Then...
Seok Jin will...
- have to...
-  Seok Jin, come here.
- continue.
-  Come here.
Because she has skipped her turn.
- I just had my turn.
-  Goodness, Ji Hyo.
That side hardly had their turns.
- Someone will leave soon.
-  Please enter a word.
- How many times...
-  10.
- Why is it already 10?
-  9.
I just got here.
The people before you used up the time.
- It just became my turn.
-  Ten,
nine, eight,
- seven,
-  What is it?
- six,
-  Chance.
I'd like to look in the dictionary.
He chose to look in the dictionary.
- You will have one minute.
-  Go find it, quick.
- Look in the dictionary.
-  I'll bet everything on him losing.
- It's "Nen".
-  Why did you...
- Wait.
-  It was "We" to "Linen" and now...
- Where is it?
-  It must start with "Nen".
- "Linen" is a difficult word.
-  Where is it?
- I've never heard of it.
-  It's "Nen".
You have enough time.
You have 40 seconds remaining.
You have 40 seconds left.
(Is there nothing?)
- There's nothing.
-  Seok Jin.
You have 30 seconds remaining.
(Laughing)
(There's no way out.)
- That chance is of no use.
-  Seok Jin.
- Look for "En".
-  Hey, you.
- Try "En".
-  You have 30 seconds left.
What in the world?
(What is this?)
I just began.
You have 20 seconds left.
- Please wait.
-  "Nen".
I'm going to write down anything.
How do I do this? The cursor.
- Where's the cursor?
-  Please click enter.
- Enter.
-  Click enter.
What is that?
There are 10 seconds remaining. In 10,
- nine,
-  Hold on.
eight, seven,
- "Nancy Lang".
-  six,
five, four,
Seok Jin, you're out.
- Seok Jin is out.
-  This is really...
- Please stand on the spot.
-  This is really unfair.
This is really...
So the second person to be out...
is Jee Seok Jin!
(The second round)
(Seok Jin is out.)
(Falling)
(Seok Jin falls down.)
(I won't forget you, "Linen".)
(His efforts were in vain.)
- There was no way out of "Nen".
-  Seok Jin.
I did so well.
- Three chances were used.
-  Change of direction and skip turn.
- Then it was the "Nen" from linen.
-  That line is really difficult.
- There's no word for that.
-  "Nen" was difficult.
This is really annoying.
This is really difficult.
You should remember this.
The words that the computer comes up with...
- is totally unexpected.
-  It's completely different.
- The machine is skilled.
-  It's at an advanced difficulty.
It's the end for us if that robot gets angry.
- Next is the fourth match.
-  It's going to be fast.
We will begin.
I'll do my best.
(Ji Hyo was eliminated in the third round and the fourth round begins.)
The order is very important.
Tae Hyun, please enter the first word.
- "Camera".
-  Now you remember, right?
- Right after I was dropped.
-  He wrote "Camera".
- That's difficult.
-  J-bot enters "Scrofula".
The word must begin with "Yeok".
Please remember that you can apply initial sound law.
You can begin with "Yeok".
This is difficult.
There are many words to choose.
Hyeri wrote down her word.
- "Yeok".
-  "Gwol"?
"Mountain strength".
J-bot countered "Mountain strength" with "Sanggwol".
- What about "Gwoljang"?
-  It's "Gwol".
(He escaped from crisis.)
It's "Gwol".
- Oh, my.
-  "Rally".
- Even Haha is doing well.
-  Contrary to our expectations,
Haha keeps surviving.
J-bot entered "Corporate rights". It's now "Gwon".
"Mr Gwon".
- I know a "Mr Gwon".
-  He wrote "Power".
- In response to "Power",
-  Wow.
("Seychelles")
- J-bot...
-  Min Ho.
- Min Ho!
-  entered "Seychelles".
Now it's Min Ho's turn. He is in a tough spot.
"Shall we dance"?
I think it'll work.
- That's a sentence.
-  It's incorrect.
- Use a chance.
-  "Chelles".
- Chance.
-  Chance.
Everything depends on this.
Min Ho will use his chance.
I'll use the attacking chance.
He chooses to attack someone else.
- Min Ho.
-  Who will it be?
Please shout out their name.
(The person designated by Min Ho has a risk of being eliminated.)
(Will it be Jae Seok?)
(Will it be Gary?)
Tae Hyun.
- "Chelles" is passed on...
-  Oh, my.
- to Tae Hyun.
-  Thank you.
- To Tae Hyun.
-  Thank you, Min Ho.
"Seychelles"? I've never heard of it.
- It's an island.
-  Isn't it a nation of archipelagos?
- That isn't a word we usually use.
-  "Chelles".
- Really.
-  Yes, it is the name of a country.
The Republic of Seychelles.
I'd like to use an announcer chance.
Tae Hyun chose to use the announcer chance.
- You don't know, either. Do you?
-  "Chelles".
- He's typing something.
-  Is he allowed to do that?
- This is better than a dictionary.
-  It is.
It's better than a dictionary.
I want that one.
(He's blaming his elimination on the dictionary.)
There must be no words that begins with "Chelles".
He's shaking his head.
- "Self-service car wash".
-  It really is an AI.
- Ten, nine, eight,
-  Eight,
- seven, six,
-  seven, six,
- five, four, three,
-  He gave up.
- two, one.
-  two, one.
- Time is up.
-  It's over.
- You're out.
-  I'm sorry.
Tae Hyun is out.
- "Chelles" is hard for me, too.
-  You can still write it.
You can try.
- It worked!
-  Can we try again?
(What just happened?)
- "Shelley".
-  It worked.
- "Chelles" is hard for me, too.
-  You can still write it.
You can try.
(Tae Hyun manages to survive.)
- It worked!
-  "Shelley".
- It worked.
-  "Shelley" worked.
(Tae Hyun succeeded with "Shelley".)
(It is a plot-twist that occurred in a matter of seconds.)
(Luck is another ability bestowed upon only humans.)
- It worked.
-  "Shelley" passes.
- I can't believe this.
-  Now,
- "Shelley" passes.
-  What is "Shelley"?
What is "Shelley"?
"Shelley" is the name of a British poet.
- "Shelley" is a British poet.
-  Is she a poet?
She's one of the greatest Romantic poets.
- What's the next letter?
-  "Shelley" is a word.
It's "Hoong".
Since Tae Hyun needs to go two times,
- That's too difficult.
-  it's his turn again.
- It's "Hoong".
-  You must have angered it.
That's a useless chance!
(Tae Hyun uses the announcer chance again.)
Just use the time.
He used the same chance.
(Will he be able to save Tae Hyun?)
- There's a word.
-  "Public relations".
"Hoonggeo".
- Pardon?
-  "Hoonggeo".
- What is that?
-  Please type in "Hoonggeo".
(Tae Hyun survives.)
- "Hoonggeo" works.
-  What does it mean?
"Hoonggeo" means...
the death of a king.
Next up is Hyeri.
"Seong Deok Seon".
Use the time to think.
- "Seong Dong Il".
-  "Holy water".
- Okay.
-  What?
- It's "Royal secret inspector".
-  "Royal secret inspector".
A word that begins with "Ddo".
(It's another name for royal secret inspector.)
- "Tortilla"?
-  "Tortilla"?
"Ddoddo burger".
- Wait.
-  Is there such a thing?
- "Ddoddo burger"?
-  It ends if you press enter.
- Press enter if you're confident.
-  Shouldn't you press enter?
I'll begin the countdown. Ten,
nine, eight,
- He has many chances.
-  seven, six, five,
- Attacking chance.
-  He will use the attacking chance.
- To whom will you use the chance?
-  Attacking chance.
(Everyone is nervous.)
(Who will Haha choose?)
Please shout...
(He points numerous times.)
Please shout out their name. Who is it?
Tae Hyun.
I heard him! It's Tae Hyun.
People are getting eliminated in order.
(Why is it me again?)
- Tae Hyun is out of chances.
-  A word that begins with "Ddo".
- You're out without chances.
-  What word can there be?
- Haha used his designation chance.
-  You're out without it.
It's now Tae Hyun's turn.
- Skipping is...
-  That is wrong.
(Please show us another miracle.)
- Skipping is...
-  That is wrong.
- You were incorrect once.
-  Try "Insane".
(He did it.)
- "Peer".
-  There's that word.
(Tae Hyun knows how to change the game.)
- Tae Hyun...
-  He's like a weed.
- You're amazing.
-  is very skilled.
You're today's winner.
It pops out immediately.
I don't think we can win against that.
(J-bot continues with difficult words.)
(Jae Seok is out.)
Oh, my.
- Isn't "Stony slopes" too much?
-  It is.
(It means a slope with a lot of stones.)
(Haha is out.)
Type in anything.
(Gary is out.)
Oh my goodness.
(Tae Hyun perseveres like a weed.)
Tae Hyun, come over here.
Oh my gosh!
(Tae Hyun is out.)
- J-bot has its critical blows.
-  Really.
He is out.
It has difficult words up its sleeves.
Now, we are left with Hyeri and Min Ho.
It's a match between the top two.
- Hyeri, write anything.
-  Go, Min Ho!
(It's a match between Hyeri, Min Ho and J-bot.)
It's the final match!
The final battle against AI draws near.
It's the final round of...
AI Kungkungtta.
(The finals to decide Running Man representative)
The final winner will be decided soon.
(Only one person can compete against J-bot on behalf of humans.)
All right. The final round begins now.
(The eighth round of AI Kungkungtta begins.)
Hyeri is the first.
(Question)
J-bot writes "Nicely".
Please write the next word.
It will be the other person's turn after writing a word.
- "Law department". Incorrect.
-  That's wrong.
10, 9. "Parents of students".
He wrote "Law" and J-bot wrote "Parents of students".
All right. "Brothers". "Extinction".
"Seats".
J-bot wrote "Asbestos".
Write "Haha's mum".
You don't have any more chances!
"Yoong"...
It's "Yoong" from "Asbestos".
- She's writing "Loan".
-  That will work.
She wrote "Loan".
The next word is "Magnetism".
Hyeri is really serious about this.
"Stairs". Next is "Gloss".
There are only two people on the stage, but a whole page is filled.
Min Ho wrote "Law department" before. What will he write?
(Laws)
He wrote "Laws" this time.
Next is "Sapling". What will be next?
I will count to 10 as soon as his turn begins.
(Incorrect.)
Her first attempt was incorrect.
10... "Adept". She wrote "Adept".
Now it's "Reconstruction".
This is really tricky.
"Reconstruction"?
He doesn't have much time to think.
- You have 10 seconds.
-  I don't know if there are any.
We will start counting down. Ten, nine,
eight, seven,
six, five,
- four, three,
-  Write something!
2... "Jeupsik"? That is not a word.
We'll start counting down. Ten, nine,
eight, seven,
- six, five,
-  There is a word.
- four...
-  "Juice squeezer" sounds right.
Again, we'll count down. 10, 9...
(Will he win this time?)
- Four, three, two, one.
-  "Juice squeezer" sounds right.
"Jeupjuh" is not a word.
Min Ho. Out.
"Juice squeezer" would've worked.
- What did you say?
-  There was "Juice squeezer".
Min Ho. Out.
(Min Ho is out.)
Hyeri.
(Mixed emotions)
There was "Juice squeezer".
Min Ho is out.
Hyeri wins.
Congratulations.
(She is the winner of AI Kungkungtta.)
- Hyeri, I'm so proud of you.
-  I can't believe she won.
But everything so far was to choose one person...
who will compete against J-bot,
one-on-one.
Who will be the ultimate winner?
Hyeri, the last one standing,
will compete against J-bot.
(J-bot is 4 years old.)
Let's find out...
who the ultimate winner will be.
The match starts now.
(The final battle begins.)
- All right.
-  You can do it.
(Does J-bot have a weakness?)
The next word is...
(During the practice game...)
"Cheater".
(Seok Jin won J-bot with the word "Cheater".)
- What is that?
-  Congratulations, you made it.
- What is wrong with it?
-  Did it resign?
- Have I won?
-  Yes.
Did he defeat the machine?
Oh my gosh. I didn't realise.
Is there no word connecting "Cheater"?
(She used to act in a world without machines.)
(Now, she challenges J-bot by herself.)
"Master" is the first word.
All right. Would Hyeri be able to achieve victory...
in the battle against J-bot?
"President" was the first word, and "Funeral" is the second.
(They do not want...)
(Hyeri to be defeated.)
"President" was the first word, and "Funeral" is the second.
She wrote "Doctor", and J-bot wrote "Huntsman".
(Huntsman?)
- Really?
-  Oh my.
(Oh, my.)
All right. J-bot writes "Huntsman".
- That happened last time.
-  Hyeri's next.
Is someone eavesdropping?
Now, Hyeri must continue.
- Hyeri, try "Kkundon".
-  Maybe that'll work.
This is a difficult word.
"Kkundon" turned out to be incorrect.
- Isn't there a word?
-  This is too close.
- This is too bad.
-  J-bot is mean.
All right. Ten, nine,
- eight, seven,
-  Try any word.
- six, five,
-  Write some random word.
- four, three,
-  Try "Kkunsa".
- two, one.
-  Is that a word?
Stop. Hyeri. Out.
(AI J-bot is victorious.)
- That was so close.
-  All right.
Are you ready?
Hyeri. Out.
(In the final round, Hyeri loses.)
(Crying)
That was the end of the AI Kungkungtta.
So Seok Jin is pretty much the winner.
J-bot is the winner of the final round.
(J-bot is the final winner.)
So this is the end.
Although we lost in this battle...
against J-bot,
we do have a winner among us.
Congratulations, Hyeri.
(Hyeri is the winner of the day.)
I will give the winner her prize.
- Thank you!
-  What is it?
- I envy you.
The prize is...
a set of electromagnetic shielding equipment.
- What?
-  Is that it?
It will protect you from electromagnetic radiation.
- Hold on a second.
-  Please defeat all the radiation.
- What are these?
-  Thank you.
- It's a full set.
-  Look at her facial expression!
- There are even long Johns.
-  Goodness.
(She'll be fully protected.)
- What are those?
-  They're long Johns.
Hyeri is the winner!
(Congratulations, Hyeri. Thank you, Min Ho and Tae Hyun.)
(Next week...)
(at 6:10pm,)
(there will be a Running Man Spring Special.)
I'd like to dine with you.
It's Seo Joon.
(I'm Sorry,)
It's Actress Lee Yo Won.
(I Love You.)
- Really?
-  He's Kyuhyun.
(Next week at 6:10pm, I'm Sorry, I Love You.)