(Game of Emperor's Throne)
(In the beginning of the R Empire, there were 10 princes.)
(Princes Jae Seok, Jong Kook and Kwang Soo)
(Princes Ji Hyo, Haha, Seok Jin and Gary)
(Princes Lee Joon Gi, Kang Ha Neul and Hong Jong Hyun)
(The day of the proclamation for the emperor's heir)
I just wanted to let you know in advance...
that I'm willing to give everyone a spot when I take the throne.
(What did you say?)
You're so uneducated and vulgar.
(Princess Jong Kook and her brothers, Haha and Jong Hyun)
- Where did that come from?
-  How dare you look me in the eyes?
What just happened?
(Princess Jae Seok and her brothers, Ha Neul and Ji Hyo)
- I'm Princess Kwang Soo's brother.
-  You're my brother?
- You're his brother?
-  Yes.
(Princess Kwang Soo and her brother, Gary)
(The Rebellion of the Princes)
I'm sure we will be take the throne.
You know, considering all things including the looks.
Do you want to start a fight?
- Do you want to start a fight?
-  Try me.
- Let's see what happens.
-  You little...
Did you even finish studying the Chunjamoon?
- Have you?
-  Chunjamoon?
Whatever you say.
I know you got in here through some special admission.
- My goodness.
-  It's funny you say that.
There's bad blood running in your family.
Princess Kwang Soo has the superior genes.
- What did you say?
-  Our family is the most superior.
- Why would you say that?
-  She doesn't look superior at all.
Aren't you a totem pole? Shouldn't you be standing outside?
(There are suspicions on Princess Kwang Soo's origins.)
- Did you call me a totem pole?
-  Yes, I did.
(There is so much drama.)
I'd like to make things clear.
Once the emperor has spoken, it's final.
- It is final.
-  Whatever.
- It's going to be me.
-  Goodness.
Don't you work at the tavern?
Don't get me started.
(Do you want some of this?)
- How dare you?
-  Can I get a pint of mead?
Don't make me angry.
Do you have what it takes to take the throne?
I'm just her brother.
- What was that?
-  Who is that?
Here comes Your Majesty!
- What's going on?
-  Who is that?
- Honey!
-  It's the emperor!
-  Hey, Honey.
(He enters with a glowing appearance.)
- Honey.
-  It's the emperor!
- Honey!
-  Honey!
(Emperor Lee Joon Gi)
Honey!
- Our Highness is so sexy.
-  Honey.
- That's my husband.
-  Oh, Honey.
Don't you think that's getting old?
- What does that make me?
-  That's not funny any more.
Quiet down.
I've said this many times. There is no order in the palace.
Fire all of them, Honey.
That's not how you talk to the emperor!
- He called him Honey.
-  He's my husband, after all.
- He should be kicked out.
-  I said, quiet down!
Quiet down!
His Majesty has spoken!
Yes, sorry.
What's wrong with you all?
I say Joon Gi, you say Emperor.
- Joon Gi.
-  Emperor.
I say Joon Gi, you say awesome.
- Joon Gi.
-  Awesome.
Make some noise.
(They'll do anything he says.)
- That's much better.
-  The emperor speaks English.
- Is he drunk?
-  Is he a DJ?
He has adopted the Western civilisation.
I've been traveling there.
Anyway, there's a reason...
why I summoned you all.
I will pick the heir to the throne.
- It's about time, Your Majesty.
-  Yes.
I've heard the news...
that the princes are fighting over the throne.
I shall send my sons to the future...
and make them compete for it.
What did he say?
Are you ready?
(The bloody battle between the 10 princes begins.)
(They shall fight for the throne in future times.)
(Only one will survive to take the throne.)
(Who will become the last survivor?)
- Understood, Your Majesty.
-  Understood, Your Majesty.
I will choose the new emperor...
on the day the Moon and the Sun overlap.
(The heir will be chosen then.)
Take this.
(You will meet again on the day they overlap.)
(The scroll is passed down to the princes in the future.)
Oh my.
(Future princes, follow the emperor's commands.)
What is this?
(He throws it back.)
(Take it back.)
(He plays around.)
What is this? Is this the scroll from the past?
(The Emperor of the R Empire commands you.)
I will choose the new emperor...
on the day the Moon and the Sun overlap.
I can't count the times I've travelled to the past.
"To the princes who were born with the destiny of the empire,"
"the Game of Emperor's Throne is about to begin."
"Game of Emperor's Throne"?
(Game of Emperor's Throne)
(Three more princes are invited to the Game of Emperor's Throne.)
I feel like they're going to throw something at us.
(They seem to be handsome.)
(Yes, this is how princes should look like.)
(They have travelled time from the R Empire...)
(and have brought their handsomeness with them.)
Look out.
(He grabs it.)
(Nice catch)
(He's already into it.)
It's time.
It looks like it's from them.
I think so too.
Are you ready?
- Yes, we are.
-  Yes, I am.
"To the princes who were born with the destiny of the empire,"
"the Game of Emperor's Throne is about to begin."
"You shall pass through where the sun and the moon overlap."
"In order to do so, you must win over the hearts of the people."
(The scroll explains the rules of the game.)
(It's a clue pointing where they must go.)
(They must interact with the citizens.)
I think something big is about to happen.
I must be from the past.
Come on, it's the 21st century.
What is this story about princes and the empire?
Does this even make sense?
I don't understand a single word. What is this talking about?
- So we're working individually?
-  Yes.
I shouldn't have shared this with you two.
I was wrong.
I thought this was a team game.
I'll be going now.
Where are you going?
Do you want to see my kick?
- Don't make me do that.
-  I was going to the restroom.
We thought that it wouldn't be a fair game...
since you're against a very experienced group of people.
So we will provide you with items for the game.
The two of you appearing on the show for the third time will get this.
- This doesn't feel right.
-  I have a weird feeling.
It's a voucher that allows me to participate in this show again.
(That's funny!)
You're so greedy.
(Prince Ha Neul is hungry for TV appearance.)
Look at that colour.
Is this possible?
It must be blood.
Don't look.
I don't want you to get a head start.
(He takes a quick glimpse.)
(What item did Prince Joon Gi get?)
I hope these two will shine today.
As for me, I'll just strive to do my best.
He's not going to go easy on us.
- It's begun.
-  So it begins.
Okay, let's go.
- Good luck.
-  You too.
- Wish me luck.
-  Hey, hey.
You'll be seeing my kick today.
(Everyone's an enemy in battle.)
(Jong Hyun is running away.)
Let me give you some tips.
How do I get to the ground floor?
- Hey, Jong Hyun.
-  I found it.
Calm down, Jong Hyun.
Hey, it's right over here.
Ha Neul, sorry to bother you but I left something back there.
- Can you go get it?
-  I'll get it after this all ends.
(Joon Gi, your trick is so obvious.)
(Win the support of the people to compete for the throne.)
I will approach the first person I see.
"I am a prince..."
"of R Empire."
"As one of my people,"
"do you know my name?"
- "I am a prince of R Empire."
-  Gosh. You surprised me.
- "Do you know my name?"
-  "Do you know my name?"
- I don't know who you are.
-  You are Grasshopper.
- What?
-  You are Grasshopper. Aren't you?
Your name must be Shorty, then.
You must be on your way.
- Hey.
-  They are my people.
- What are you talking about?
-  Go away.
Look at your clothes.
You tried to look fancy? It's just horrible.
I must find a person who seems good at playing games.
Ji Hyo.
Long time no see, Jong Hyun.
Hello. "I'm a prince of R Empire."
(I'm happy to see this lady, not you.)
Hey. She is mine.
Who is this? Hi, Jong Hyun.
Hello.
"I am a prince of R Empire. Do you know my name?"
- That... What was it?
-  It's Jong Hyun.
Let's see.
Let's find out...
who are my people.
Hello.
(He's greeting his fans.)
Thank you.
"I am a prince of R Empire."
"As one of my people, do you know my name?"
- I do.
-  What is it then?
- It's Lee Joon Gi.
-  You're correct.
Now, you can join me. Will you come with me?
(Screaming)
All right.
- It's "Two Bodies, One Heart".
-  I'll give you the words.
Choose between action and melo. One, two, three.
- Melo.
-  Action.
That's okay.
What was the dialogue? R... R...
I'm R... "I'm a prince of R Empire."
- "As one of my people..."
-  Ask if they know your name.
Gosh. Do I really have to say this?
Okay. I'll choose him.
(Grabbing)
"I am a prince of R Empire."
"As one of my people,"
"do you know my name?"
No, I don't.
- Kim...
-  What?
No, it doesn't start with "Kim". It doesn't.
"Do you know my name?"
- What?
-  I don't know. Sorry.
- Why not?
-  Sorry. Bye.
- Please tell me you know my name.
-  I'm sorry.
Please.
"I am a prince of R Empire."
"My people, do you know my name?"
- It's Lee Kwang Soo.
-  That's right.
Thank you so much.
- It's "Two Bodies, One Heart".
-  Okay.
Summer or winter. One, two, three.
- Summer.
-  Summer.
(Prince Kwang Soo passes "Two Bodies, One Heart".)
Okay.
Should I go with her?
Okay. Let's go.
"I am a prince of R Empire."
"As one of my people, do you know my name?"
It's Kang Ha Neul.
That's right. Let's play "Two Bodies, One Heart".
It's "Two Bodies, One Heart" now.
Mulnaengmyun or bibimnaengmyun. One, two, three.
- Mulnaengmyun.
-  Mulnaengmyun.
(Shouting)
I must go with him, right? All right. Please come with me.
"I am a prince of R Empire."
"As one of my people, do you know my name?"
- It's Hong Jong Hyun.
-  That's correct.
Please tell me the next game. We must be really quick.
- Hurry. We must be quick.
-  Oh, no. We must hurry.
Choose between mountain and sea. One, two, three.
- Sea.
-  Sea.
Can you spare a few minutes?
- Just a moment.
-  Yes, I can.
All right. Let's go. Quickly.
(Screaming)
She is really enthusiastic.
"I am a prince of R Empire."
"As one of my people, do you know my name?"
- It's Lee Joon Gi.
-  Correct.
Now, you can join me. Will you come with me?
- Yes. Of course.
-  So your answer is yes?
Can I get a hug?
Of course.
Okay. Get ready.
Let's begin.
Choose between Coke or Sprite. One, two, three.
- Coke.
-  Coke.
(Prince Joon Gi passes "Two Bodies, One Heart".)
She is a smart one.
(She is a smart one.)
(They need two balls in their crown to pass Sun's Gate and Moon's Gate.)
Bounce the ball high in the air. Bounce it hard.
(Bouncing)
Isn't it in? Give me a moment.
Why isn't the ball in? Let's try again.
Is the ball in? Okay.
Is it in?
I passed the mission, right?
- We passed it. We passed.
-  Yes.
You bounced them really well.
(Now, they need to cast a spell to open Sun's Gate and Moon's Gate.)
- This time...
-  Let's put the ball in at once.
- Bounce the ball like this.
-  Hello, Jae Seok.
- Hello, Kwang Soo.
-  Hello.
- Hello.
-  Let's finish this in two throws.
What are you doing here?
(Kwang Soo blocks the ball.)
- That's a foul.
-  Is he playing a game?
Is this a mission?
- Kwang Soo is so annoying.
-  Is this a mission?
- How can you do that?
-  I didn't know.
All right. Two throws left.
(The ball goes in.)
Just one more.
(They succeed once again.)
Yes. That's it.
- Are they finished?
-  This is it. Come.
- What's going on?
-  It's Kang Ha Neul.
Let's go back. It's you, Ha Neul.
- Hello, Ha Neul.
-  What? Are you leaving already?
How have you been?
- Hello. How are you?
-  Hi. Good to see you.
- Jong Hyun. How have you been?
-  Hello, Haha.
- Get ready. Hurry.
-  You must aim the crown...
and bounce the ball once like that.
We don't have any balls left. We must try one more time.
(Prince Ji Hyo fails the mission.)
(Prince Kwang Soo gives it a try.)
(The ball goes in.)
I got it.
(They are amazing.)
Open sesame!
(Prince Jong Kook is the first to pass the gate.)
(They have to cast a spell to open the gate.)
Open sesame!
(Prince Jae Seok is the second to pass the gate.)
(Open sesame!)
(Come to think of it, this is quite embarrassing.)
Why isn't the gate opening? Should I just go through?
(Prince Kwang Soo is the third to passes the gate.)
Shall we begin now?
(Prince Ha Neul begins the mission.)
Catch it well.
(The ball goes in.)
(He's quite good.)
(He shouts in joy...)
(over his success.)
Thank you so much.
- You will travel back in time.
-  Okay.
(Now, he has to cast the spell.)
(Laughing)
Open sesame!
(He shouts shyly.)
(Prince Ha Neul passes the gate fourth.)
(Prince Jong Hyun begins his mission.)
It was too low. Bounce the ball just a bit higher.
I failed.
- Can I try one more time?
-  Jong Hyun, come out.
That handsome brat...
- Let's go.
-  Let's go.
(Another handsome brat, Joon Gi begins the game.)
(Bouncing)
(Come on, Prince!)
No. This is not right.
You must find another person to proceed.
It's okay.
(Don't worry.)
Open sesame.
(Prince Haha is the fifth to pass the gate.)
Open up sesame.
Wrong spell?
Open sesame for me.
Why? What's wrong?
(It is said that he eventually passed quite a moment later.)
(Prince Jong Hyun gives it another try.)
I can't see the ball. Bounce it a bit higher.
(Meanwhile, Prince Joon Gi is busy having a good time with his fan.)
(Is the ball in or out?)
(It's in.)
All right. The last one.
(He needs only one more ball to pass.)
(Prince Jong Hyun passes the mission.)
- Thank you, Se Jun.
-  Thank you.
Open sesame!
(Open sesame!)
(Prince Jong Hyun is the seventh to pass the gate.)
(Prince Gary is on his mission.)
The ball got in.
(No!)
No!
- It's in.
-  No. I must go in before him.
Thank you. Open sesame.
Can I go in now?
(Prince Gary passes the gate as the eighth.)
(Only Prince Joon Gi and Prince Ji Hyo are left.)
Nice.
(Is Prince Joon Gi about to cheat?)
(He just pretends.)
It's in.
(Prince Ji Hyo passes her mission.)
The ball finally got in.
(Oh, no.)
Open sesame!
(Prince Ji Hyo is the second last.)
(Only Prince Joon Gi is left here, alone.)
Okay.
(Prince Joon Gi finally passes his mission.)
Good job.
- You are really amazing.
-  Thank you.
You're worthy to become my vassal.
My man. Oh my.
Thank you. See you in next life.
Open sesame!
(He might annoy the emperor if he comes too late.)
(It seems he doesn't care about it.)
(The ones how passed the Sun's gate,)
(are you ready to fight?)
(The secret of your birth...)
(will be unveiled here, today.)
All the babies are holding a toy hammer.
Aren't these pictures of us when we were babies?
- That's right.
-  When we were babies?
Is that boy with two toy hammers you, Jae Seok?
- Your family must have been rich.
-  No.
No way.
- Those clothes look expensive.
-  They do.
- Look at those clothes.
-  They look new.
Those clothes look modern.
Who is this? The one with black top...
- Is this Ji Hyo?
-  Yes. That's me.
- She looks exotic.
-  You looked really handsome.
- Who is this naked boy?
-  Who is it?
Isn't it Joon Gi?
- It's Joon Gi.
-  Joon Gi. Is it you?
- He is.
-  Is that Joon Gi?
That's how he looks when he's naked.
Who is that boy next to Jong Kook?
- He's handsome.
-  Isn't that Ha Neul?
- It must be Ha Neul.
-  Yes, it's me.
- It's Ha Neul.
-  He's so handsome.
- Ha Neul was a handsome boy.
-  He was fashionable.
- Is that Jong Hyun?
-  Yes, it's me.
(He looks like a son of a rich family.)
Who's that in the picture from the Korean War era?
- It's even crumpled.
-  Who's that?
- Is it Seok Jin?
-  It was hard to find the picture.
- It was you.
-  Is it from Joseon Dynasty?
I saw that picture in a history book.
You look cuter than I thought.
It cost about 6 yang.
Welcome, Princes.
Now, a full-fledged war of the emperor's throne will begin.
So toy hammers, the symbol of the R Empire, will be bestowed upon you.
But the 9th and the 10th princes who came later than the others...
should find the toy hammers on their own.
They should find on their own.
There should be some disadvantage like that.
(Joon Gi and Ji Hyo will be our prey then.)
- Okay.
-  Is this something to applaud?
Of course.
- Your misery is our happiness.
-  There were lots of people looking.
But seven princes among you...
are very used to a variety of games,
whereas the three of you are less accustomed.
Right, I admit to that.
So I will grant them a special chance.
What will you give them?
- Why do you give them such a thing?
-  Please don't.
- They're all good.
-  Jong Hyun is really good.
Jong Hyun is so good at games.
He is the fastest one I've ever seen.
Yes, he is.
- He really is fast.
-  Right, he's so quick.
Don't you think Seok Jin needs some chances too?
Yes, along with them.
I think it's not fair.
- I should get one.
-  Give him some money or something.
Money? Why money?
Please do not neglect him.
The emperor's orders have arrived.
The first round will start.
Those who obtain two hearts from the back of the others' heads...
with the hammer will win.
Four winners will face the door of victory...
whereas the rest will go to the door of defeat.
Ji Hyo and Joon Gi should find the hammers on their own.
- They should find the hammers.
-  They should?
According to the result of this game, the fate will be...
different between the 4 winners and the 6 losers.
- Really?
-  They will play different games.
I can already guess who the six losers will be.
- Right.
-  This will be...
a fight in the mud among the six.
As you said, the losing team will play a game in the mud.
Literally?
The one who ranks last in the losing team...
will be dethroned on the site.
(Will that person be dethroned even before the show ends?)
- Then is that the end for him?
-  Dethroned?
- It's the end.
-  Then can he just go home?
- He'll be the dethroned prince.
-  Does he go home?
- It's the end of him.
Seok Jin is interested in this.
Can that person go home then?
He won't be able to participate in the final mission.
Will he still be on camera?
The winner...
among the four will receive an advantage that will help him...
in the final game.
We should target Ji Hyo first.
We should send people home.
(The Rebellion of the Hammer)
(They get prepared on separate sites.)
(Seok Jin practises.)
Oh, it works well.
(Kwang Soo practises defending his head.)
I can just avoid getting hit over here.
(The heart falls off.)
I have to be careful of my back.
(He is totally into today's theme.)
Let's go. But wait.
It's not time to put on airs but it's time to find a hammer.
If Kwang Soo finds the hammer first, he might hide it.
(The 10 princes are all ready.)
(The Rebellion of the Hammer begins.)
(Let's get started.)
(Would you like a taste of my hammer?)
Let's go.
I'm getting slightly nervous.
I want to be the emperor.
I have to guard my head well.
Going out there empty-handed with a hammer...
is almost like suicide.
(Joon Gi and Ji Hyo need to focus on finding their hammers.)
I don't think they hid them nearby.
(Here comes my prey.)
Do I have to run like this...
without knowing where to go?
Oh my.
(There is no use running without a hammer.)
- You're not attacking me already.
-  Of course not.
- I need to promote my drama.
-  Sure.
Let's get Joon Gi.
(Let's get Joon Gi together.)
(All right.)
(Not knowing anything, Joon Gi is busy looking for the hammer.)
(Prince Joon Gi, wait right there.)
Where is he going?
I'm scared.
(Prince Joon Gi sneaks out casually.)
(We lost him.)
Wait a moment.
- Go first.
-  Let's go together.
You need to protect your head too.
Don't come near me.
(Distrust has now become a habit.)
What's that? There is a box.
Isn't that a box?
(Ji Hyo has found a hammer.)
I found it.
(She has obtained a hammer.)
- Who's that?
-  It's Jong Hyun.
I see. Haha is over there too.
(Ji Hyo hides the hammer from them.)
- Ji Hyo doesn't have...
-  What, she has already found one.
Without this hammer, my life is in danger.
(Seok Jin meets Kwang Soo.)
What's behind the house?
I don't know if there is a road.
Seok Jin, why don't we hold our hammers upside down?
(Okay. I'll trust you.)
Let's give one heart to each other.
(Seok Jin tries to negotiate.)
Then we just need one heart each.
(That sounds tempting.)
- I'll go first.
-  You shouldn't go first.
- Then how?
-  At the same time.
Let's give one each.
In 1, 2, 3.
Hey.
(It looks like the Rebellion of the Fools.)
I knew you would do that.
I feel dizzy.
(They are fools who don't know anything but betrayal.)
(How's Joon Gi doing?)
Gosh, I can't find one.
(He searches around...)
(in vain.)
This must not be the right place.
Where is it?
(He's damaging his own dignity.)
I thought it was a hammer.
Joon Gi is still searching.
Shall we go to him?
- We should get him first.
-  Let's go.
- Let's go.
-  Le's go.
He didn't find a hammer yet. Let's go quickly.
Watch out for your backs.
(Haha sneaks behind Gary and surprises him.)
Watch out.
I'll just smash. I won't look out.
(Haha swings his hammer.)
(You are so annoying.)
Oh my gosh.
Oh, I got it!
He really got it.
(Gary takes one of the hearts.)
I got it.
- Come on.
-  I got one.
Really?
So why did you fool around?
Gosh, I'm sorry, Haha.
- You don't have to be sorry.
-  The fight has begun, Gary.
(Prince Gary obtains 1 heart.)
(Realising the power of the hammer, everyone gets nervous.)
The hearts detach easily.
(They intimidate each other.)
(Someone hits Seok Jin from behind.)
(One of his hearts is taken.)
What? You can't do that.
Of course, I can.
I should have watched out for my back.
- What happened to Haha?
-  He lost one heart.
(Sneaking)
(This is what happened to Haha.)
(It's like this.)
(Boing)
What was that?
Who was that?
It's Kwang Soo, right?
(Prince Kwang Soo also obtains a heart.)
(Now, the hammer battle has officially begun.)
(They attack each other.)
(Haha joins the battle with another heart.)
My hammer burst.
Wait, mine burst.
- Mine's damaged.
-  I know.
Jae Seok's hammer burst!
It's damaged.
You should've been careful with it.
(They all attack him.)
- I got it!
-  Oh no.
What...
I said mine burst.
(It's dangerous here. I'd better get moving.)
(He runs away while defending his head.)
(That looks ridiculous.)
(I won't let you take mine.)
(Seok Jin, Haha, Ji Hyo and Jae Seok have one heart each.)
(Joon Gi still hasn't found a hammer.)
It's so hard to find.
(Where on earth is it?)
(I found it!)
Yes!
(Finally, he finds a hammer.)
Now, the time has come.
No one will get out alive.
(With the help of the hammer, he's more into his character.)
(You guys better be prepared.))
(Shall I begin my hunt?)
(Kissing)
They are doomed.
(He swings his hammer.)
(He pretends to be Thor.)
No one will get out alive.
(Princes, watch out for your backs.)
Joon Gi, do you have a hammer?
No, I don't.
- You have one behind your back.
-  No, I don't.
- Just let me see the hammer.
-  Ha Neul.
- Joon Gi.
Please just show me if you have one.
Let me see your hand.
- Okay?
-  You saw it, right?
- I'll hate you if you attack me.
-  Me too.
I won't attack you.
(They make an alliance.)
I'm very scared.
(Jae Seok comes back with a new hammer.)
- Gosh, you're scary.
-  Did you get a new hammer?
(Kwang Soo, you jerk.)
You...
How could you gather everyone...
when I had a flat hammer?
- I'm sorry.
-  How could a human being do that?
How could you?
- Jae Seok, let's get Kwang Soo.
-  Let's go.
- Let's go.
-  Ha Neul.
I'll help you.
- Ha Neul, why will you help him?
-  We promised.
- Think again.
-  Ha Neul.
- Why would you help him?
-  Don't listen to Jae Seok.
- Kwang Soo, let's end here.
-  Don't listen.
- Otherwise, you may be out.
-  Think again.
Ha Neul, don't listen.
(I'm in such a dilemma.)
- I never...
-  You should choose carefully.
I never...
- Why are you stepping back?
-  I'm not...
- going to attack you.
-  Okay, okay.
- Aren't you strong, Gary?
-  I'm weak.
- Why?
-  He's very fast.
He was very strong in the swimming pool.
(Jong Kook suddenly attacks him.)
(It's suddenly a chaos.)
Goodness, it doesn't fall off easily.
It doesn't fall off.
That was a great attack.
(Haha hits his head.)
(Haha's attack fails.)
Why didn't it fall off?
(At that moment,)
(Haha gets hit.)
(Haha is out.)
What happened? I'm out.
I didn't think someone would come from behind me.
Pointless fights aren't necessary.
- Why don't we...
-  Let's eliminate Kwang Soo.
- Let's eliminate Kwang Soo.
-  There are two hearts.
One of the hearts fell off already.
We need to eliminate him.
- He needs to be eliminated.
-  Let's go.
(Everyone hits Kwang Soo.)
I took one of his off.
- Taking this off is... Okay!
-  Hey.
(Ha Neul approaches her slowly and hits her hard.)
Yes!
(I'm sorry, Ji Hyo.)
That's it!
Ji Hyo is out.
(Ji Hyo is out.)
Ji Hyo.
I'll keep my eye on you.
I won't go easy on you today.
Ji Hyo is very upset.
(She walks off angrily.)
(Hitting)
- The hearts are gone.
-  What are you doing?
Why are you eliminating me twice?
(She's already sad to be eliminated.)
(The men start to hit each other.)
What was that?
I think I'm eliminated.
(Seok Jin's counter-attack)
- I did it.
-  Seok Jin eliminated me.
(Mud, here I come.)
(Haha, Ji Hyo, Jae Seok are out.)
Shouldn't one of the guest members be eliminated?
Let's eliminate one of the guests.
- Each of them has two hearts.
-  Really?
(We can't leave them like this.)
Where's the prison?
Where do people go when they're eliminated?
Kwang Soo.
- How many hearts do you have?
-  I'm already out.
I'm already out.
(Kwang Soo approaches Prince Jong Hyun's back.)
He's out.
(Now is the time!)
(Kwang Soo hits him.)
(He takes off Jong Hyun's hearts.)
(Kwang Soo's plan was successful.)
You told me you were eliminated. You fooled me.
- You said you were out.
-  I did it.
I have two hearts.
(The winning team is determined as he takes the first place.)
(They find out Kwang Soo took the first place.)
Where do I go next?
(They start attacking each other again.)
(They hit one another.)
(Hitting)
Goodness.
(Joon Gi obtains Seok Jin's headband by default.)
What's that? I dropped it.
- It doesn't matter.
-  Does it mean I'm eliminated?
- I am, aren't I?
-  You were supposed to guard this.
It's a little sly, but this is what it takes to win.
- Come here now.
-  You are here.
People who are going into the mud were already decided.
That's right.
(He's in high spirits as a winner.)
I'm sorry.
- What did you say?
-  I'm not in the same boat as you.
- I'm a winner.
-  You're already?
I won because I took off two hearts.
I'm of a different class now.
I think one of them is already finished here.
(His anger rises.)
Ha Neul, you'll be the main character next.
Let's play a fair fight.
(He gets startled.)
It's Jong Hyun.
(I won't let you attack me.)
(He gets hit.)
(How about this kind of attack?)
(Gary places second and joins the winning team.)
I'm sorry, Joon Gi.
I was just lying down.
(Is this the kind of fun on variety shows?)
Did you lose one heart?
- Let's finish the game.
-  Okay.
- Joon Gi. Joon Gi.
-  No.
(It's Jong Hyun versus Ha Neul and Jong Kook versus Joon Gi.)
(Only two of them will join the winning team.)
- Did he stop playing?
-  It's Gary.
(Ha Neul tries to fool Jong Hyun.)
(However, he fails.)
(You tried to fool me?)
All right, stop it.
(Jong Hyun places third and joins the winning team.)
Oh my goodness.
(Who will win between Jong Kook and Joon Gi?)
Jong Kook, please calm down.
Wait a minute.
(Only one of them can join the winning team.)
(Neither of them can give up.)
(Joon Gi hits him.)
(His hearts are taken off.)
Wait, are you okay?
(It's impossible to fight with strength, so he approaches shyly.)
- I did it.
-  Did you take them off?
(Prince Joon Gi is the last to join the winning team.)
Okay.
He's coming. Is he on the losing team?
What's wrong with your clothes?
I was in a fight with a wild animal.
Did you fight with Jong Kook?
I'm an actor, but this show almost became my posthumous work.
That's nonsense.
- Is Jong Kook coming here?
-  Jong Kook is coming.
- He's one of the winners.
-  Are you a winner or a loser?
I'm going into the mud.
(Seok Jin, Jae Seok, Ji Hyo, Haha, Ha Neul and Jong Kook lost.)
(The winning team celebrates.)
He's going into the mud.
(However, the losing team will be punished.)
Jong Kook, why did you have to join our team?
- He shouldn't be on our team.
-  It wasn't my choice.
- We're all old and weak.
-  Exactly.
(All of them sigh at the same time.)
Princes of the winning team, please move on.
Two princes and two patients, please enter.
- Open sesame!
-  Open sesame!
(They shout the spell to Sun's Gate.)
- Open sesame!
-  Open sesame!
(They shout the spell to Moon's Gate.)
Why do you sound so down?
I don't want to go in there because of him.
Come on, let's go.
- Goodness.
-  Let's go.
(What kind of competition awaits them behind this door?)
(Next is the second round of the Rebellion of the Princes.)
(The winning team arrives after passing through Sun's Gate.)
- Hello. Wow.
-  Hello.
- The water is clean here.
-  The air smells fresh.
It looks cool.
It's for the winning team.
(It's a swimming pool for the winning team.)
(What awaits the losing team behind Moon's Gate?)
- Goodness, we have to climb up.
-  It looks better.
Is that it?
- Is that it?
-  Goodness.
(It's a mud stage for the losing team.)
(A loud noise)
Here's an order from the emperor.
Princes must receive the order.
Are you going to plot treason again?
No, I won't.
Please read it.
The second round of the Rebellion of the Princes.
- "The Princes' Bows".
-  Bows?
Grab the arrows in the water and shoot it to knock out the opponent.
The prince to knock out all the toys with others' names attached wins.
The winner will obtain the imperial secret weapon.
Haven't you done archery before?
- No.
-  No.
- I can't shoot arrows at all.
-  I'm sure you did in the drama.
No, I've never done it.
(Is this playing darts, then?)
You did it in the recent drama.
- Come on.
-  I didn't.
I won't have a chance against them.
The prince whose toy remains until the end wins.
Aim the toys with other people's names.
You can only shoot the arrow on the buoy.
- This looks fun.
-  Why must we cheer for them?
- Gosh.
-  We're only watching the game.
Goodness.
- We don't have to cheer.
-  No, you don't.
It's that jingle.
(This stop is Imperial Station. The exit is on your left.)
- What is it?
-  I've never heard of it before.
(This stop is Imperial Station. The exit is on your left.)
When do we start?
(It's a Korean traditional music show.)
(The music stops.)
("The Princes' Bows" starts.)
(He runs hurriedly.)
Here it is.
(Kwang Soo is the quickest.)
(The bow bounces off.)
(Move out the way.)
(I must hurry up to survive.)
- This is too hard.
-  There's only one.
(The arrow is stuck.)
He's in a hurry.
- Goodness.
-  Why doesn't it work?
(I've shot arrows before.)
(He shoots his own toy.)
- Wait.
-  That was yours.
He shot his own toy.
Jong Hyun is good.
(Here I go.)
(He shoots Joon Gi.)
Joon Gi's toy got knocked down.
Let's go again.
(Here I go.)
Block him.
Why are you so bad at shooting, Gary?
The arrow doesn't fit my bow.
(Kwang Soo is annoyed.)
Bring the sword.
(Bring the sword.)
It's okay.
- Jong Hyun is good.
-  Jong Hyun is shooting well.
(He's doing it for real this time.)
Please hit the target.
(His arrow hits the target.)
He hit Gary. Jong Hyun is good at archery.
(One of Jong Hyun, Joon Gi and Gary's toys are knocked down.)
(It's my turn now.)
(Screaming)
How will they know which one they shot?
It hit Jong Hyun's.
(Kwang Soo shoots his own.)
(One of Kwang Soo's toys is shot.)
- I'm sorry.
-  It was Kwang Soo.
(Watch this!)
Bring the sword.
(He hits Kwang Soo's toy.)
Why is Jong Hyun so good?
Kwang Soo is out if someone shoots his toy.
(Kwang Soo has only one toy left.)
Stop shooting at mine!
- He missed it.
-  Stop shooting at mine!
- Let me shoot one more time.
-  Okay.
(He shoots at Gary's toy.)
- I'll kill him.
-  Why are there so many?
- Joon Gi...
-  Gosh!
(Gary hits his own toy.)
(What's wrong with me today?)
- Gary is totally out.
-  Okay!
- It's called self-destruction.
-  Gary is out!
(Prince Gary is out.)
(Joon Gi lies down to shoot.)
(He lies down and shoots an arrow.)
Look at him. He makes it.
Joon Gi cares about his looks too much.
Are you doing equestrian martial arts?
(Joon Gi has become Cupid.)
(Ladies, would you gladly accept my arrows?)
I'm the prince of the R Empire.
(He aims to capture the ladies' hearts.)
My goodness.
(This is how you should do in Running Man.)
(The arrow touches Joon Gi's toy.)
It's falling back.
(The arrow slightly touches the toy...)
(and the toy falls down.)
- Yes!
-  He made it.
Wait.
Joon Gi needs to make it just one more time.
(Here are the remaining toys.)
(His bowstring is broken.)
(Prince Kwang Soo even breaks his bowstring.)
- Let's go for it.
-  Go!
He's so good.
Kwang Soo, it serves you right.
(Prince Kwang Soo is out.)
I will win this round!
(If he hits the toy first, he wins.)
(It's either Joon Gi or Jong Hyun.)
Jong Hyun.
I envy him. He's a handsome and talented archer.
Without Gary and Kwang Soo, it looks great.
I feel like I'm watching a drama.
(This is such a great scene to look at.)
(It's more than beautiful that they're together.)
It's good to see them together.
(Now, it's time to shoot my arrow.)
(He hits his own toy.)
(Here is another self-destruction.)
(No way!)
- Gosh.
-  Okay!
(Jong Hyun wins The Princes' Bows.)
Wait. I will make an incantation.
(He's about to open his card.)
(Prince Joon Gi received a special card.)
- What is it?
-  Is it the time travelling chant?
Fix my hammer first.
The time has come.
- Why is he so phony?
-  "The time has come"?
The sun and the moon!
Set time free!
It's no different to the time travelling chant.
(I look better.)
There he goes again.
He re-winded time.
(He winds time backwards.)
(Will Jong Hyun, the talented archer, win?)
(Or will Joon Gi be able to make a different result?)
I'll put an end to this now.
(Jong Hyun hits his own toy.)
That was dangerous.
(Joon Gi hits Jong Hyun's.)
(Everyone's so focused.)
Move to the left.
(Jong Hyun hits both toys.)
(It's very fierce.)
How is Jong Hyun so good?
It's like the Olympics.
(Who...)
(will become the final winner?)
(Jong Hyun shoots the arrow.)
(He hits Joon Gi's toy.)
(Prince Jong Hyun wins The Princes' Bows.)
Wow, Jong Hyun.
(What a bowman!)
Wow, he's an excellent archer.
Let's go to the mud pit.
(Jong Hyun wins and obtains a chance card.)
(Jong Hyun earns a chance card.)
(Now, it's the losing team's Consolation Game.)
It's time for the "Consolation Game".
"Those who lost really disappointed me."
"If you lose in this round, you'll never be able to hold the throne."
(We must avoid dethronement.)
(They'll fight in a mud pit to avoid dethronement.)
Ha Neul, don't forget to make us laugh even if you lose.
(Ha Neul's pressured.)
Start when I say so.
Are you guys planning something?
Stop planning things out.
- We weren't.
-  They were just talking.
(Those left in the mud 30 seconds after the music starts will lose.)
(I will make you lose your mind with my modern dance.)
That's a nice collaboration.
- You must compete!
-  Or you'll lose.
Go fight!
- You should do your best.
-  Go for it!
(They're watching for a good chance.)
What if all of them win this round?
30 seconds is too short.
What are they doing?
Only one person gets to lose. Think wisely.
Everyone...
Let's go.
(They start the fight.)
Please move.
(Everyone, go down to the mud pit.)
Wait, push him.
- 10 seconds!
-  Please.
Haha, you can do it.
- I can make it.
-  Don't push me.
- You can't do it.
-  Do not push me!
- Hold him.
-  Wait.
- Look at them.
-  Wait!
- Wait!
-  20 seconds left!
Wait! Wait!
(Two members fall into the mud.)
(They're Prince Seok Jin and Prince Haha.)
Hey!
(Haha grabs Ha Neul tightly.)
(Prince Ha Neul, we need to cling onto you.)
We must push him down.
(Let me go up.)
(I want to avoid dethronement desperately.)
(Seok Jin falls into the mud.)
(The first round is over.)
We made it.
Am I out?
Let's get ready.
The four princes have survived.
I made it!
- This is so funny.
-  Ha Neul.
Ha Neul!
- Ha Neul, are you all right?
-  I survived!
How could this happen?
Why is it Seok Jin again?
Why did they target us?
You'll have the last round.
Now, this is the real fight.
- Gosh.
-  It will be so fun.
- This will be a fun fight.
-  This is real.
- If you lose...
-  Right.
(Who will win this round?)
I never expected this round.
- Right.
-  This is the main part.
(It won't be easy, Prince Haha.)
(That's for me to say.)
(We fear nothing when we fight together.)
(The last round between Seok Jin and Haha begins.)
I can't bear to watch them.
You must go up.
(They both fall down.)
(Thanks to the mud, we'll at least have great skin.)
- No!
-  20 seconds left!
(What a fierce fight it is.)
(Who will be the one to leave?)
- Go up.
-  You should go up.
Ten!
(Seok Jin falls.)
(Haha trips him and gets the chance to win.)
(But Seok Jin pulls him down.)
Go up!
(Seok Jin grabs Haha's shirt.)
(They have less than 10 seconds.)
(Prince Seok Jin gets a chance this time.)
(He tries to jump,)
(but fails.)
(How can a man that bad at jumping?)
He failed to climb up.
Who will become the loser?
This is a really funny fight.
(The first round is over.)
I failed to jump.
Go for it! Do it again!
This is so funny.
Everyone,
you will start on the platform.
The one who falls first loses.
That will be the rules.
- Okay.
-  That's a good idea.
You can do it!
(Are you there, Seok Jin?)
(Yes, I'm here and you're there.)
(When this round is over, one of them will no longer be a prince.)
- Push him hard.
-  Push him.
- Okay.
-  You made it!
(Go down!)
(Haha uses force on Seok Jin.)
- Okay.
-  Good job.
(Are they playing ssireum now?)
- This is so fun!
-  It is.
- This is really funny.
-  Goodness.
(Seok Jin is struggling.)
- What are they doing?
-  Are they wrestling?
(He even uses his facial muscles.)
This is like the Olympics.
Go for it!
You can do it.
- Great. That's it.
-  You can do it.
(Their match impresses us the way Park Sang Young did.)
(I can do it. I can dethrone him.)
I don't know why this is so moving.
Why are you so heavy?
This is a close game.
- You're so tenacious.
-  I'm so tired.
They're exhausted.
- They're both winners today.
-  You guys look great!
You're really strong.
- You were tenacious.
-  This is so touching.
Goodness.
- He's moving.
-  You're very strong!
(Let's play fair and square.)
(Haha grabs a forbidden area.)
Haha, you can't do that.
It hurts! Seriously!
What is he doing?
(Their dirty fight commences.)
Haha, push him with your legs!
(Prince Seok Jin falls into the mud.)
- You must go up to the platform.
-  He won.
(The round is over and Prince Haha wins.)
The ending was funny.
He's the true winner today.
You're irritating him even more.
You also did a good job.
Since Prince Seok Jin...
failed to win the round, he's dethroned.
Be quiet!
(Prince Seok Jin is dethroned.)
(The final round awaits the princes.)
(This is the final place.)
Prince Seok Jin.
What do you mean? He's no longer a prince.
Actually, dethroned princes usually...
enjoy the rest of their lives.
Aren't they sent into exile?
Since Seok Jin is dethroned, let him fill the time.
Hey.
What's he got to do anyway?
Dethroned prince has a different task.
- I see.
-  He must have another role.
You shouldn't have revealed that.
Maybe it's something important.
- Well...
-  Here comes the scroll.
Stop throwing things at us.
(He has no manners.)
- How could you miss that?
-  Throw it nicely.
(Let's give it another try.)
Catch it. Show us what you've got.
(He is serious.)
- Gosh.
-  What should we do?
Joon Gi.
(You are an utter disgrace.)
He failed.
- But it's hard to catch.
-  Stop acting foolish.
Maybe he wants more attention.
Let's just start.
Joon Gi, show us what you've got.
(He gives it another try and succeeds.)
(Joon Gi, what a nice catch.)
But you know what? They'll air the part you failed.
You mean they'll air the part I failed?
(Please edit the film nicely for me.)
Who will sit on the throne?
The final race to determine the one to take the throne will start.
- The final race.
-  It's the last race.
(So this is the final race.)
To take the throne, you need to offer two name tags of others.
- It's going to be hard.
-  Two name tags?
You can rip the name tag in person,
but there's another secret method only passed on to the princes.
What would that be?
Find the emperor's cushion that will appear randomly.
Sit on it and chant the spell with a name and hold for three minutes.
Then, you'll obtain the person's name tag.
(If you manage to stay seated for three minutes, you'll gain the tag.)
You want us to stay on it for three minutes?
If someone uses a cushion once, you cannot reuse the same cushion.
Remember. You must stay on the moon while you hold out.
(This isn't going to be easy.)
We should prevent others from getting two name tags.
Let's say I'm on the cushion.
What happens if someone kicks me and I fall off from it?
The cushion is going to be on the moon which is a little bigger.
If you go off the moon, it'll no longer be effective.
- I can rip it off by hand, right?
-  Of course.
Oh, you mean that's also possible.
It's going to be a busy day.
(I'm sure we'll be running everywhere.)
Can we rip off the name tag of the person who's on the cushion?
Yes, you can rip it off even if the person is on the cushion.
(The answer is yes.)
Does that mean I have to defend my name tag for three minutes?
If three minutes pass, you can eliminate the person you called.
Can we move the cushion from its place,
instead of sitting on it?
There'll be a moon on the floor which is bigger than the cushion.
Three minutes must pass while the cushion is on the moon.
You mean we can eliminate the person even if he's on it?
You'll be eliminated if your name tag is ripped off,
- and if you're off the zone.
-  We've gone over this a minute ago.
Can we take off the name tag of the person who is on the cushion?
We repeated this three times already.
How many cushions are there?
He said, it will appear one at a time, randomly.
- One by one...
-  You should read this again.
- One by one, Ji Hyo.
-  Will you please read this again?
You'll be able to find out when it is broadcast.
How many times do we have to repeat the same thing?
Pass the Gate of Total Eclipse,
and you'll be led to the final race.
But before that, we have something for Prince Jong Hyun.
- Yes, he has an advantage.
-  What is it?
- He won a mission.
-  Yes, he did.
- He must have an advantage.
-  Really?
That may give him power to summon the cushion.
(What could this advantage be?)
- What can it be?
-  Jong Hyun does have an advantage.
Jong Hyun, I hope for your victory.
Take the throne.
Get ready.
We'll start the final round.
- Let's go inside.
-  What about me?
- You can't enter. I'll explain.
-  So I'm not allowed to enter?
(Nine princes, come through the Gate of Total Eclipse.)
(But only one will take the throne.)
(Who will be the prince to sit on the throne?)
(The final match will be held in this building.)
I'm going to win.
It's all mine. I'm going to have it all.
All I need is two name tags, right?
First, I'll team up with Jong Kook and Kwang Soo.
And eliminate everyone we meet on the way to find the cushion.
I think I'll be eliminated soon.
I have a bad feeling about this. I'm going to be eliminated soon.
If Jong Hyun's advantage is reversing the effect,
I'm sure he'll try to attack me.
I should use this to save myself rather than to eliminate someone.
(What would be the chance card that Jong Hyun has?)
(Nine princes, prepare yourselves for the final match.)
Microphone testing.
Gosh, it scared me.
The game is about to start.
It's Seok Jin.
So that must be his role.
I'm the voice from the sky.
The race will start in a minute.
(Laughing)
(His tone is so awkward.)
I can tell he is a first-timer.
I hope no one else but us is listening to this.
I hope no one else is listening. This is so embarrassing.
I apologise.
(I apologise on behalf of him.)
What's he doing? There are people working here.
(Seok Jin is being frivolous.)
(Laughing)
So is he like the spirit of mountain?
The final round is about to start.
Prepare yourselves, nine princes.
Who would be the one to take the throne?
Five,
four,
three,
two,
one.
The game starts now.
Can I go now?
(It's time for the final match.)
Let's go find them.
Hiding is not always a good thing,
because someone else can get two name tags first.
The best strategy is to find the cushion.
Someone's coming.
(Running)
(Who are you?)
I think someone's there.
Who is that?
(Running)
(Let's charge forward.)
- Joon Gi, it's you.
-  Jae Seok.
- Can you give me some advice?
-  What kind of advice?
Just run. That's all.
I see. Jae Seok, will you help me?
- I know you're good.
-  Me?
- Well, later...
-  Yes.
Well... We need to look into each other first.
- Someone's coming.
-  Really? Where?
- There she comes.
-  It's Ji Hyo.
- It's useless if Jong Kook appears.
-  That's what I mean.
We need to find the cushion before he shows up.
- I think that's what's important.
-  Yes, that's important.
- Joon Gi, you need to think hard.
-  We need to eliminate him first.
I've no intention of attacking you. I'm here for some advice.
- Then, let's go find the cushion.
-  Let's find it.
- Let's go find the cushion.
-  Okay.
- Are we allies now?
-  What I mean is...
Ji Hyo, who's that over there?
Jong Hyun, we are trying to find the cushion to eliminate Jong Kook.
- Really?
-  Yes.
That's a good idea.
- Hello.
-  Ha Neul,
- go find the cushion first.
-  All right.
Let's find the cushion and eliminate Jong Kook first.
You mean we should eliminate Jong Kook?
Jong Kook is over there.
(Jong Kook alarm is issued.)
Ji Hyo, hurry.
Hurry up, Ji Hyo.
(Roar)
Jae Seok,
it's fine.
- Ji Hyo, hurry.
-  We should hurry.
(It's an emergency. Evacuate.)
- Shall we go for it now?
-  Shall we?
- We should eliminate them.
-  You are very intuitive.
(Let's go and hide.)
- It's Jong Kook.
-  Jong Kook teamed up with Haha.
- Really?
-  Yes.
- This is a dead end.
-  This way, Ji Hyo.
I already know your strategies.
(It won't be easy for you.)
I have an important information.
What is it?
The cushion has appeared.
(The cushion has appeared.)
The cushion is on the ground floor of the main building.
(Ground floor of the main building?)
- On the ground floor?
-  Let's move. Hurry.
He said it's on the ground floor of the main building.
It's on the ground floor of the main building.
- Where is that?
-  Let me repeat.
The cushion is at the main building, on the ground floor.
Ground floor of the main building? Hold on. This is the annexe.
I thought this was the annex. Is this the main building?
(Ground floor of the main building)
(The cushion is waiting for you.)
(Princes, hurry up!)
- Let's cooperate until we find it.
-  Okay.
Be careful.
(Joon Gi arrives first.)
(Running)
(What?)
(Kwang Soo arrives second.)
- Did you just get here?
-  Kwang Soo, I just heard...
(Where will it be?)
(It's here.)
that the cushion appeared.
(Whoever is faster will get the cushion.)
(Kwang Soo sits on the cushion first.)
(Now, Kwang Soo has the power to eliminate one of the princes.)
(What should I do now?)
Hurry. We'll guard you. Name someone who's not here.
- Whom should I eliminate?
-  Hurry up.
- Choose someone who isn't here.
-  I'm here.
- Jae Seok.
-  Call Jae Seok. Hurry.
Hong Jong Hyun, Hong Jong Hyun.
- Hurry.
-  Jong Hyun is here.
Jong Hyun is here.
(The princes are gathering around the cushion.)
We'll help you.
(What am I supposed to do?)
Hey, call out someone who's not here.
What is he doing on the floor?
(Jae Seok and Ha Neul are observing the situation closely.)
Everybody's here.
(Kwang Soo can't make up his mind.)
(Will he eliminate the strongest member, Jong Kook?)
(Or will he eliminate Jong Hyun with a chance card?)
(Who will Kwang Soo choose to eliminate?)
The third prince Gary will...
(Oh my.)
be dethroned from his position.
He won't be able to become the emperor!
Why me?
Why is it me?
You're the only one who's not here.
(That was a great move, Prince Kwang Soo!)
Everyone is near me except you.
Why is it me? He must be out of his mind.
- We have to block him.
-  We should block him.
Let's block him.
(The members plan to intercept Gary.)
But why is it me?
You were the only one that wasn't here.
I was up there!
(Gary must get Kwang Soo off of the cushion.)
Block him for me.
Get closer.
(We'll show you what defence is.)
Why is it me?
- Everyone else was here.
-  Why me?
Everyone was here except you.
(Now is the time.)
(Don't you dare.)
Gary.
(Joon Gi makes a sudden attack.)
At least give me a try.
I'm sorry, Gary. We have no choice.
(He moves quickly.)
(They're playing tight defence.)
Look at him.
(These will be your last moments, Gary.)
How much time is left?
Take him out.
(Gary has 1 minute and 30 seconds left.)
(Goodness)
(Gary loses his balance and gets encircled.)
- Let's hold him like this.
-  No!
(I just need to hang on a bit longer.)
(Thanks to Kwang Soo's attack, will Gary be out?)
Goodness, no.
(Gary grabs onto Haha's tag.)
No, no!
No, you can't!
(I'll save you, Haha.)
Hurry.
- Cover him.
-  Hey, hey.
(Is that Haha's name tag in Kwang Soo's hands?)
No, you can't!
(Kwang Soo betrays Haha.)
Kwang Soo!
Cover my tag. Hey, Kwang Soo!
- Okay!
-  Kwang Soo ripped mine.
Kwang Soo ripped mine.
- Get Kwang Soo out.
-  I just have to hold out.
- No!
-  We have to get Kwang Soo out.
- Get Kwang Soo out.
-  Kwang Soo.
- He ripped mine.
-  He'll have two name tags.
We have to get him out or else, he'll have two name tags.
(In that case, let's get him out.)
Wait, I'll go out! I'll go out! I'm out!
(Kwang Soo quickly gives in.)
I'm out! I'm out!
- Wait.
-  Get him!
- Wait! Hold on!
-  Joon Gi, hurry and rip his tag!
(I've come to get Kwang Soo.)
Rip it, quickly.
I'm out!
(Kwang Soo, this is the price you pay for betraying.)
- Get him then.
-  Gary ripped the tag!
Guys! I got off the cushion a long time ago!
(Ripping)
(Jae Seok makes a quick attack.)
(Joon Gi is out.)
I'm sorry, Joon Gi.
I couldn't help it.
- Jae Seok!
-  I'm sorry, Joon Gi.
(Haha and Joon Gi are out.)
(Jae Seok and Kwang Soo have two tags.)
(What will the members do with Kwang Soo?)
- What do we do?
-  Don't trust him.
Let's rip Kwang Soo first.
I don't have the desire to attack any more. I only have one tag.
- I'm on your side, Jong Kook.
-  We have to eliminate him.
I'm so angry. I can't believe you, Kwang Soo.
(His betraying instincts can't be ignored.)
I gave my all to help him.
I feel sorry to Joon Gi.
(Jae Seok starts to feel guilty.)
Whatever.
I can't trust Jae Seok.
He suggested joining hands before.
Can the top host of Korea act like this?
Gosh, I'll complain about this on the show's website.
(I'm going to tell on you, Jae Seok.)
Get up now.
Get up, Kwang Soo.
Do you really have to get me, Jong Hyun?
Jong Kook, I was on your side from the beginning.
Why'd you rip Haha?
Gary ripped most of Haha's tag.
Goodness, you got blinded by your greed to win again.
They tried so hard to protect you.
(Gary barely ran away.)
(Let me catch my breath.)
(Oh my gosh.)
(He's nervous. It shows that he's a rookie.)
(Ha Neul is over there.)
(Shall I go for a hunt?)
(Attacking)
(Ha Neul quickly positions himself for an attack.)
Ha Neul.
It's nothing, Gary. That wasn't anything.
(You've improved, Ha Neul.)
(Ha Neul's attention is elsewhere.)
(I will show you the true skill of name tag ripping.)
(Ripping)
(Ha Neul is out.)
This is how you play the game, Ha Neul.
I'm sorry.
This is how you rip name tags.
(Hello, there.)
(Jong Kook makes a surprise attack.)
No! What is this?
Gary.
(You should practise a bit more, Gary.)
Hey, Gary. So this name tag game...
This is how you play Name Tag Elimination.
I'm so mad. I'm embarrassed. Go away!
Go away! I'm embarrassed.
This is my most embarrassing moment ever.
(This is my most embarrassing moment in Running Man's history.)
(Ha Neul and Gary are out. Jong Kook has two name tags.)
Here they come.
(What are the people in jail doing?)
- Is Jong Hyun our last hope?
-  Oh my goodness.
Why did I win the mud fight?
Don't join hands with anyone, Haha.
I really trusted Kwang Soo this time.
You'll get betrayed.
- Honestly...
-  Kwang Soo is out.
Kwang Soo is out.
(Serves him right.)
(Kwang Soo was cornered by Jong Hyun and Ji Hyo.)
I got it.
I got it. Kwang Soo is out.
(Why did you betray if you were going to get out like this?)
(Trudging)
You dirty fool!
(It's an angry water slap.)
- Dirty fool!
-  I'm sorry.
I have nothing to say. I apologise.
- You're horrible.
-  I'm sorry.
I should've shown you a better side of me. I'm sorry.
But really, how could you do that?
It's not that, Haha. Listen to me.
Gary ripped most of it.
I got away though.
I didn't know that.
- How can you not know?
-  You showed your back too easily.
And it's not even that.
It's the fact that I was helping you.
I don't want to be like this, but I can't help it.
I don't want to do this either.
But I can't control myself any more.
I'm upset, too. I don't know why I'm like this.
I drank a lot because of this.
There's nothing I can do any more. I'm done for.
- I can't change.
-  He says he's done for.
I really can't change.
Okay. If it's that serious, I'll understand.
- I really can't.
-  He can't change.
He can't go back.
- We have to understand him.
-  He can't change no matter what.
- Some things can't be changed.
-  I'm done for. I can't change.
Stop it now. I understand.
My cheeks hurt.
My niece has big expectations.
She said that she hopes...
I'll stay alive until the very end.
It's going to be on his SNS.
Joon Gi practising ripping name tags.
(Joon Gi practises diligently. Ripping name tags is hard.)
I'm really going to practise.
(I'll get revenge.)
(I'm sorry, my niece.)
(What's going on at the site of The Rebellion of the Princes?)
(They all ripped one name tag except for Ji Hyo.)
A mysterious cushion has appeared.
The cushion is on the second floor of the main building.
(The 2nd cushion is on the 2nd floor of the main building.)
(Jae Seok is the first to enter the cushion zone.)
(At this rate, the prince sniping chance will go to Jae Seok.)
(Who will be Jae Seok's target?)
Prince Jong Kook will never...
be able to become the emperor.
He won't become the emperor.
(Jae Seok snipes Jong Kook.)
Where is it? It's not over there.
They said the second floor but there's nothing here.
This doesn't make sense.
I win if I just hold out for three minutes.
The emperor's cushion has been operated.
Someone on the second floor...
has called out Prince Jong Kook's name.
Where is it? Let's go.
Please.
(Please let's hold out for 3 minutes.)
My goodness.
(Who is this?)
Get out when I say it nicely.
Has it not been three minutes yet?
- You're mistaken. It's not you.
-  Get out.
- Just get out now.
-  Jong Kook.
Get out when I say it with words.
- Jong Kook, you're mistaken.
-  Get off.
- It's not you.
-  I said, get off.
- Jong Kook.
-  All right.
- Come on now.
-  It's not you.
- Get out.
-  It's a misunderstanding.
Get off when I say it nicely!
- You're mistaken.
-  Get off when I say it nicely!
Get out!
- Get out!
-  Jong Kook.
They called my name.
I just heard it!
(I'm sorry, Jong Kook.)
I'm sorry. Please let me go.
- What are you sorry about?
-  I'm so sorry.
(Be quiet and get out.)
Jong Kook, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Can't you be generous...
and ignore it just this once?
- If I get another chance,
-  Why did you do that to me?
- I'll never call your name again.
-  You shouldn't have done it.
A mysterious cushion appeared.
- The cushion is on...
-  Where is it?
the ground floor of the annex building.
(The person who obtains the cushion...)
(will take the emperor's throne.)
(Which prince will hold the cushion that will determine their destiny?)
(Prince Jong Hyun sits on the cushion first.)
(Who is his target?)
Prince Jong Kook may not take...
the emperor's throne.
Also,
(Also)
I'll use my chance card.
(It's time to use his secret chance card.)
Play the music.
(Prince Jong Hyun won "The Princes' Bows".)
There must be something like teleportation.
(He was given a chance card.)
Jong Hyun has an advantage.
(Music card)
I'll use my chance card.
(Play the music.)
Everyone, freeze. Someone used a chance card.
What's going on?
(What's the music card about?)
Prince Jong Hyun's last chance is the music card.
When the music card is used,
nine princes except Prince Jong Hyun...
must freeze immediately for two minutes.
(Music card makes the other princes freeze.)
(If we don't stop him, Jong Hyun will take the emperor's throne.)
We don't know how long it'll last.
This is such an advantage.
(If we don't stop him, Jong Hyun will take the emperor's throne.)
Prince Jong Hyun used his chance card.
To follow the prince's order for everyone to sing and dance,
DJ Seok Jin will play some music.
Enjoy it.
This is great. Here we go.
(People are forced to dance for two minutes.)
Goodness.
I'm not in the mood to dance right now.
Must we do this?
Do we get to know whom he called?
Whose name did he call?
- He said Prince Jong Kook.
-  What? Me?
That was great.
This is fun.
We don't know how it'll turn out.
Come on. Let's go.
(They must stop Prince Jong Hyun before three minutes are up.)
Jong Hyun has the most advantage.
I should have eliminated him.
I hope Jong Hyun wins.
(All he has to do is last a little longer.)
(They must take him off of the cushion before the time is up.)
- Can we move when the music stops?
-  Yes.
(The music stopped.)
Has it stopped?
(Has it stopped?)
(Jong Hyun, you've been waiting long.)
(He shudders.)
Move out, Jong Hyun.
Move out.
(Frightened)
What's going on?
(Jong Kook's anger...)
(is about to explode.)
Hey.
Goodness.
(Prince Jong Kook tries to take revenge on Prince Jae Seok.)
(What do I do?)
Give me a chance.
Come here now.
(If any of them take a name tag, they can become an emperor.)
(They start to move.)
Why doesn't it come off?
(Now, everyone has a chance to become an emperor.)
(Who will it be, Prince Jae Seok or Prince Jong Kook?)
(Is it Prince Jong Hyun or Prince Ji Hyo?)
(Who will take the emperor's throne?)
(A name tag tears.)
(The Rebellion of the Princes ends.)
Everyone, come this way.
Goodness.
Here comes the emperor.
(May the emperor live forever.)
(The royal face of the emperor is revealed.)
- Is he the emperor?
-  Is he really the emperor?
(His appearance seems awkward.)
- Is that him?
-  No way.
(He trips immediately.)
He's a eunuch.
- I know you're a eunuch.
-  I'm playing two roles.
(He's a hybrid eunuch.)
Are you envious of me?
Now, I'll turn over the throne.
(Now, I'll turn over the throne.)
(Who's taking the emperor's throne?)
- How many times have you won?
-  I'm sorry.
- You're so tactless.
-  That's not true.
You're so tactless.
(The one to take the emperor's throne is...)
(During the decisive match 10 minutes ago)
(A name tag gets torn.)
I did it. I did it.
(Jong Kook eliminated Prince Jae Seok.)
Why didn't it come off easily?
Why is Jong Kook so good at tearing?
(Prince Jong Kook takes the emperor's throne.)
I'll turn over...
- the emperor's throne to you.
-  Thank you.
My gosh.
(Emperor Kim Jong Kook)
(Prince Jong Kook puts on the royal robe.)
Did you bring it yourself?
Is this your actual outfit?
- Really?
-  Yes.
That's mine.
Joon Gi was very ambitious today.
- Joon Gi worked hard.
-  He was very ambitious.
I want to be on the show again.
I'll practise all night.
(I'll come back for a revenge match.)
I feel very awkward and left out.
I'm sorry.
- Why am I standing alone in this?
-  Go back up.
- Go and sit over there.
-  I want to end the show with you.
- Sit down.
-  How many times have you won?
- I feel lonely.
-  I'm tired of it.
- I'm tired of his winning.
-  I feel lonely.
- Good job.
-  How many times did you win?
- You can be the emperor forever.
-  Goodness.
The first episode of "Moon Lovers: Scarlet Heart Ryeo"...
is going to air tomorrow.
Don't miss it, and I hope you'll like it.
- That's great.
-  Thank you.
(We thank Joon Gi, Ha Neul and Jong Hyun for being on the show.)
(Complete Running Map)
This is a problem.
(A guide in entertainment, Cha Seung Won is here.)
(Find the last piece and complete the map.)
(Find R Mon hidden in various places.)
- The last one is...
-  There's another one.
- We have two hints.
-  I don't think that's it.
Hey, I kicked it.
- I've never seen it before.
-  He looks so sexy.
He's someone who loves variety shows.
(And)
I can't believe it.
Just follow the order.
What's going on?
Why would I go to prison?
How could this happen on the train?
I'm not a criminal.
If I succeed, can I escape?
You're not Hyo Lyn today.
Why did you do that to me?
(Train to Prison is coming soon.)