Hey, guys.
In six hours, you shall meet me...
and receive a deadly punishment.
(It's time for the deadly punishment.)
(The sun has set, and it's time to receive the penalty.)
("You won't be in your right mind.")
("All you will want to do is escape.")
(It's famous in Incheon for its frightening angle.)
(It's the roughest pirate ship in the world.)
(It's a pirate ship on Wolmido Island.)
(And...)
(a man waits for them.)
(Who is he, sitting in front of a pirate ship?)
(David McInnis)
Hello.
(It's David, the man who warned them about their upcoming penalty.)
It's David McInnis.
(Should we greet him or fear him?)
Hey.
(They greet each other with swag.)
Oh my goodness.
Why is David here?
(Why is David here?)
This is your last chance.
David will ask each of you a question.
You must reply with either a "Yes" or a "No".
Your answer will determine...
whether or not you will ride the pirate ship.
- It's nice to meet you. - Nice to meet you.
- I'm your fan. - You're my fan? I'm your fan.
- Thank you, Bro. - Thank you.
You should call me "Big Brother".
- Big Bro. - Good.
(David begins to ask the final questions.)
Okay, I'm going to give you one question.
Yes.
You're going to have three seconds to answer that.
- Got it, three seconds. - Okay.
You might not like this question,
but if you're a thrill seeker, you might like it.
But if not,
you won't.
So, are you ready to face your punishment?
You don't like?
Yes or no?
- Three. Two. - Is that his question?
(Seok Jin has no idea what the question was.)
(What is his decision?)
- No. - I think that's wrong.
- That's tough. - He just answered.
- All right. Seok Jin. - Yes.
(Seok Jin said no.)
(Will he be able to avoid the penalty?)
(He's...)
(safe.)
Yes.
(Seok Jin will not ride the pirate ship.)
- Yes! - Does he not have to ride it?
- He avoided the penalty. - Thank you.
- Did he get it right? - Did you choose...
- between yes and no? - I just guessed.
I might be the only one riding the ship.
- I just guessed. - No way.
You don't want to say you will ride a pirate ship,
but you can't say you won't...
because you don't have a choice.
So you're going to be honest with me.
He said a long sentence, but the only word I understood was "choice".
Would you rather die...
or live...
and ride a pirate ship?
- Live, live. - Live, live.
Okay. So now, it's your choice. Yes or no?
Oh, my.
(I have a master's degree.)
Do you choose not to ride the pirate ship?
I'm going mad.
Please.
(What will Haha say?)
Yes.
Do you want to ride the ship or not?
Haha.
(Will Haha be able to avoid the penalty?)
(I really don't want to ride the pirate ship.)
- You'll ride the ship. - Oh, no!
(Haha will ride the pirate ship.)
(Oh my goodness.)
Really?
(That's too bad.)
- Haha couldn't avoid the penalty. - He has to ride the ship.
Now, regardless of your will,
you will eventually choose to ride the pirate ship.
No.
You may eventually have to ride the pirate ship.
What do you say? Yes or no?
(Ji Won's answer is no.)
No.
What's the result?
(She avoids the penalty.)
Yes.
(It's a series of successes.)
(All three of them avoid the penalty.)
They got lucky.
Is that it?
Yes.
- Kwang Soo will ride the ship. - I knew he would.
That was great.
(That was perfect.)
(You'll be riding the pirate ship.)
- Why? - What are you doing?
- Why? - Put your hat back on.
(Three people have to ride the pirate ship.)
Put your seatbelts on and hold on tight.
I really hate this. Gosh.
- Can you move over a bit? - Can you lower the safety bar?
It's tight on me.
I'm not really good at this.
Please, don't do this. Stop.
- Producer! Please stop this! - It looks scary.
Look at Gary.
- Gary looks so handsome. - Producer!
- Look at Gary. - No.
(He shuts his eyes tight.)
My stomach feels funny.
The ship goes really high up.
(The pirate ship of Wolmido Island swings up high in an instant.)
(That's why it's called the "crazy pirate ship".)
Oh my goodness.
Help me.
Goodness. Keep your eyes closed. Don't open your eyes.
Don't open your eyes. Why is this ride so long?
I really hate this.
(They experience the horrifying feeling of falling.)
I'm falling. I'm falling.
(They both feel fear and rage.)
Gosh. I'm sorry.
Please. Please.
(Why did I get it wrong?)
(One decision can change everything.)
(There are chairs...)
(by a pool.)
Look, chairs are set up.
- What are they for? - They are flying chairs.
What are these for?
It's outside.
(Welcome to the splash pool.)
- What are we doing? - All right.
The game for today is "Find the No Man".
"Find the No Man?"
- Do we have to say no? - How do we play this game?
We will tell you more about today's game in just a second.
We have three special guests for today.
- Do we have three guests? - I think so.
- Who are they? - It won't be fun if I tell you.
- Okay. - They can be inside.
To find out who the guests are,
we prepared a game called, "Dangerous No."
- Please take your seat at the back. - It's a mind game.
- Please take a seat. - All right.
- Okay. - The producer is dangerous.
He prepared a series of dangerous games.
Okay. I'll sit here.
Does it matter where we sit?
We might not have to go in the water.
- What is that? - I don't want to get in the pool.
- I got this. - Seok Jin.
- Yes? - Don't you think the viewers...
will think it's rude of you to be wearing sunglasses?
- I have to. It's bright out here. - I see.
(He's in his 50s so he needs his sunglasses.)
He has to.
- I'm sorry, everyone. - That's funny.
I want sunglasses, too.
I apologise to all the viewers.
(It's because I'm getting old.)
- You will be asking questions. - Okay.
The guest will answer your questions.
- I see. - The answer will be a yes or a no.
You won't be penalised if the guest answers yes.
- What? - If he says no...
- That's tough. - Who gets to say no?
- Will the guest say no? - Yes.
If you find out who the guest is,
the guest will be thrown into the pool.
- Really? - Okay.
- We must find out who the guest is. - Let's do this, everyone.
- Don't ask simple questions. - All right.
- Ask questions that will help us. - Okay. Let's go.
- Don't ask obvious questions. - Okay.
Don't ask questions like, "Are you human?"
- We must do well. - We should.
All right. Shall we begin?
Okay. Please come out.
If the guest answers no, we'll be thrown into the water.
- Hello. - Nice to meet you.
(They don't have a clue.)
Hi, all.
- I think it's a guy. - Is it male or female?
- In my opinion, the guest... - It's a guy.
hasn't been on that many variety shows.
He's very cautious.
- Let's ask his occupation and age. - Let's do that.
- I will ask him a question. - Okay.
(This one question will determine their fate.)
Are you...
(First question)
an actor?
(Is the man behind the curtain an actor?)
Yes.
(They don't have to go in the water.)
- This is crazy. - Okay.
Are you...
(Second question)
in your 30s?
(Second question: Are you in your 30s?)
Yes!
- Yes. - He's in his 30s!
- He's an actor in his 30s. - An actor in his 30s.
He's an actor in his 30s.
Ask him if he's handsome.
Ask him if he has a hit song.
I don't want to ask him if he thinks he is handsome.
Listening to his voice makes me think that he's not.
- What? - But still...
- What's the logic in that? - I know.
- I know it. - What is that?
- I am certain about it. - I have no expectations.
- His voice is hinting that... - Let's ask about his work.
- Ask him. - Ask him about his famous work.
Have you starred in a movie that sold over 10 million tickets?
That's a good one.
- Is he a well-known actor? - All right.
Have you ever starred in a movie...
that sold over 10 million tickets?
(Third question: Have you ever starred in a movie...)
(that sold over 10 million tickets?)
No.
- No? - Oh, dear.
(Falling)
(Have a taste of "No".)
(Jae Seok shows us how it's done.)
(You instantly become ugly.)
This is really tough.
- He's not a top actor then. - This is ridiculous.
- It's terrifying. - Jae Seok.
- It's freezing! - Jae Seok.
- The water is unbelievably cold. - Are you okay?
- It's unbelievably cold. - This is absurd.
- Gosh, it's cold. - I can't do it! Wait!
- Is it that bad? - It's cold!
This is ice water.
Hey!
Come and put some water on your chest.
- You have to get ready. - Hold on.
It's crazy.
(Everyone's shocked by the power of "No".)
- Where's my towel? - Is it really cold?
What's this? Kwang Soo!
What?
(Ji Hyo is terrified.)
What did you just do?
- You should experience it. - Ji Hyo, you should just go home.
You're being so difficult.
- No! - Just go home.
You are extremely moody today.
- Gosh... - Jae Seok.
Ask him about his character, Kwang Soo.
Ask him if he normally plays a cool role or a funny role.
- That's a very subjective question. - Listen.
- Ask him if he plays the bad guy. - Ask him if he plays the villain.
Or ask him if he usually plays a funny character.
(They give Kwang Soo suggestions on what to ask.)
You're just trying to get me in the water!
No, I'm not.
- What kind of a question is that? - Don't worry.
We need to know so that we can guess who it is.
Why don't you ask if he's been on Running Man before?
- Yes. Ask him that. - Okay.
- Have you... - It will narrow the list down.
been on Running Man before?
(Fourth question)
(Have we met before?)
No.
- See? - Never?
(It's his first time to be on Running Man.)
(Why have you never appeared on Running Man?)
(Are you Cho Sae Ho?)
(Falling)
I told you.
You should've asked if he's been on other variety shows.
(Kwang Soo is shocked by the cold water.)
It's very cold.
Kwang Soo, you shouldn't have asked that question.
It's just like ice water.
Maybe we should put some water on our bodies.
Put some on your chest then.
- Should I? - Get your body used to it.
(Something feels strange.)
- What's wrong? - Hey.
- I didn't do anything. - What are you doing?
- I didn't do anything. - Be careful.
If you push me, that's the end of our friendship.
Hey!
You little...
(Jae Seok doesn't hesitate to end their friendship.)
It's cold! It's cold!
- It's too cold. - It's not that bad.
(Seok Jin is destined to be tortured for life.)
It's more difficult because he's never been on Running Man.
That's why I said he's new to variety shows.
- He doesn't do variety shows. - How about this one?
"Have you ever wanted to appear on Running Man?"
- What's that? - No. No.
He'll say yes.
- Don't ask questions like that. - Do you think he will say...
- he wanted to be on another show? - Don't ask that.
- This is hard. - Ji Hyo.
- Let's ask him if he's married. - Okay.
- Let's ask him that. - Yes, ask him if he's married.
I don't think he's married.
Most people in their 30s aren't married.
Then ask him if he's single.
Are you single?
(Fifth question)
- Yes. - He's not married.
- Seok Jin. - What should we ask him next?
How can I guess who he is without knowing his last name?
Let's ask him what his last name is.
- Yes. Let's ask him that. - We do need to know that.
- I'll ask him. - Narrow it down.
Is your last name...
(It's Seok Jin's time to ask.)
Is your last name Kim, Lee or Park?
(Will Seok Jin get lucky this time?)
- Yes. - Oh, my.
- We should just pick one. - Just take a guess.
He's never been on Running Man. His last name is Kim, Lee or Park.
- Shouldn't we discuss it first? - Let's ask him this question.
"Did you recently shoot a TV series?"
No, let's ask him about his upcoming gig.
- He must have one. - I'm sure he came...
- to promote it. - Right.
- That's possible. - Let's ask him.
- Ask him. - Go on.
Should I ask him if he came here to promote his work?
- I will ask him... - He came to promote his movie.
Ask him if his movie is going to be released soon.
- Excuse me. - Yes.
By any chance, is your movie going to be released soon?
(Last question)
Yes.
(Yes!)
- We were right. - I think I can guess.
You know a lot about upcoming movies, right?
- Which ones are coming out? - What are the upcoming movies?
That's...
(Well...)
- He doesn't know. - The one with Captain America.
(Captain America is most likely in America.)
Not that one.
- Gosh. - Is that all you know?
That's an American movie.
There are too many movies coming out.
I know. There are too many.
Let's think about this.
He's an actor in his 30s with the last name of Kim, Lee or Park.
Park? So it's one of those three.
- Is he Park Hae Il? - He was on "Radio Star".
- Is it Lee Je Hoon? - Is he Park Hae Il?
- Is it Je Hoon? - Is he Hae Il?
- It must be Je Hoon! - Je Hoon!
- He has a movie coming out. - Is he in his 30s?
- Yes, he is. - He is...
The producer looks frustrated.
- It's Je Hoon! - It must be Je Hoon!
- It's Je Hoon. - It's Je Hoon and Go A Ra.
- He never appeared on Running Man. - Are you sure about this?
Is he the one that starred in "Signal"?
Is he older than you?
- He's older than me. - It's Je Hoon from "Signal".
I think I saw the poster.
- I am his biggest fan. - His movie's coming out soon.
The other guest must be A Ra then.
- Look. He's not laughing. - Is that right?
(They give a bitter smile.)
- It's Je Hoon! - It must be him!
- It's him! - Let's go with Je Hoon.
- It's Je Hoon. - Let's go with him.
Look at them. They look upset.
- In 1, 2, 3. - I think we guessed it right.
If it's Je Hoon, automatically the female guest is A Ra.
I will ask if she's A Ra for the first question.
- Okay. Great. - That will do.
- That's great. - Let's go.
- She'll be thrown in immediately. - Let's hurry up.
- All right. I have the answer. - What is it?
It's Lee Je Hoon.
(I might be wrong.)
I'm dead.
- He just said that he's dead. - Did we get it?
- Did you hear what he said? - Is it really him?
Let's see if you got it right.
(Did the Running Man members guess right?)
Please come on out, Je Hoon.
(It's Lee Je Hoon.)
- We did it! - Yes!
- We got it! - We did it!
- We guessed it right. - I know!
- We got it correct. - Oh, dear.
- Poor him. - That wasn't that hard.
I feel bad for you.
- Je Hoon! - Hello!
- Hello! - It's nice to meet you.
- It's really him. - Oh, dear.
(The actor in his 30s is Lee Je Hoon.)
(In the TV series "Signal", he played the role of Park Hae Young!)
(Not only is he handsome, but his acting was also superb.)
- Welcome! - Hello.
- Oh, dear. - Hi.
- It's really him. - Gosh...
- Lieutenant. - Je Hoon.
(I should've had my poker face on.)
You said you've never been on Running Man.
So I thought it could be you.
- I shouldn't have said anything. - Look at his nose.
- Why did you say it? - Will Je Hoon go in the water?
I didn't know it was Je Hoon.
(Haha approaches Je Hoon.)
You can keep talking.
- I will take your mic. - He needs to take a dip.
Shouldn't we talk to him first before he goes in?
Look at his body. You can tell he works out.
- Goodness. - Look at that.
Je Hoon.
You need to get ready.
(He gets a cold water massage.)
- It's cold. - It's cold, isn't it?
(It's time for you to go in the water.)
It's his first time on Running Man.
(Je Hoon will dive in now.)
I'm a big fan of his.
Please say hello to our viewers.
Hello, everyone.
- I'm in "Phantom Detective". - That's right!
I am actor Lee Je Hoon. Hello.
(He greets the viewers,)
(and takes a dive.)
(We won't cut him slack just because he's handsome.)
(We hope he will enjoy the cool, refreshing water.)
He looks good.
(Look at his body!)
(He has broad shoulders.)
Take a picture!
(They are amazed.)
- Get him on camera. - He's got a great body.
Hurry.
(His face glows even more with water.)
That is crazy.
Look at his abs.
Don't give him a towel.
- Don't let him dry off. - Just leave the towels there.
He looks great.
- You look good. - Don't give him a towel.
He is handsome.
- Look at his body. - Look at his muscles.
It's great.
Look at his muscles.
(We love you, Lieutenant Park.)
He's so handsome.
(Even Seok Jin's heart skips a beat.)
He has a great body.
- Oh, dear. - Look at how...
- his muscles are so cut. - It's impressive.
Can you do this once?
- Do this. - I think you can handle it.
(He's muscular.)
(They can't help but clap and cheer for him.)
- All right. - Did you see his abs?
- Please take a seat. - Okay.
Is our next guest Go A Ra?
- A Ra is here, isn't she? - Here we go.
Just get it right.
I think you had a tough time guessing the first guess.
We will allow you to use the Guest Card from now on.
You can ask Je Hoon to ask the questions for you.
Okay. That sounds great!
If the guest says no when Je Hoon asks the question,
- all of you will fall in. - Okay.
Do you understand?
- What? - You're really handsome.
Let's begin.
Please say hello.
- Hello. - It's Go A Ra!
(They guessed right.)
- It's A Ra. - Should we go for it?
- It's her! - Should I say her name?
- They could've changed the voice. - We need to wait for our turns.
- I'm sure it's a woman. - Is that so?
(Laughing)
- It's a woman. - A Ra,
are you...
female?
(First question)
- No. - Oh my gosh!
(It's not Go A Ra.)
Did we guess wrong?
- What? - Oh, no.
Is it a man?
(Splashing)
- Is it not Go A Ra? - It's a guy.
It's a guy?
Wow, he looks like a squid!
It's so cold!
- He looks tasty. - It's seriously cold!
Is it not Go A Ra?
That voice belongs to a guy?
- It's a guy, then. - It is.
- It's a guy? - What should I ask?
Shall we use the Guest Card?
- Should I use it? - Do it.
- I'll use the Guest Card. - He can make us dive if he wants.
Je Hoon, this is a question of your conscience.
- Please help us. - Give us a hint.
- This person is funny. - Funny?
Are you a comedian, by any chance?
- No way! - That's not it!
- What are you doing? - Oh, come on.
- Je Hoon... - Well...
No!
(They all dive into the water.)
(Giggling)
(Screaming)
(They can feel the chilling water in their bones.)
- It's so cold! - It's cold!
(He's deeply satisfied.)
- It's cold! - My back is burning!
Gosh, my back!
It's cold.
(They are in dire need of sunlight to warm them.)
(Screaming)
(Je Hoon plays along.)
Gosh, it's so cold!
It's burning.
- My back is burning. - Goodness!
My back is burning so much!
All right, Je Hoon.
That was a good first impression, Je Hoon.
- Let's do this. - Okay, Je Hoon.
Hey, your hair turned into spaghetti.
- It's spaghetti. - I'm getting hungry.
(Slurping)
- It's spaghetti. - Spaghetti?
Is the restaurant open today?
(His hair resembles the entrance of a Chinese restaurant.)
- Are you open? - Is this a Chinese restaurant?
You should create a new nickname for him.
You made me the squid.
Make sure you add subtitles.
You have to turn his hair into spaghetti.
(The newly released menu is called squid spaghetti.)
We can handle it, but the cameraman in the water is cold.
- It's really cold. - It's part of his job.
- Are you serious? - You're too harsh.
(Seok Jin is brutal.)
Come on, Seok Jin.
That's not nice.
- It's part of his job. - Watch what you say.
They'd rather work than stay home and do nothing.
- Come on. - They look best when they work.
- Come on. - "They look best"?
All right, it's my turn now.
Are you in your 40s?
(Are you in your 40s?)
- No. - Oh, dear.
Only we got to ask a question.
(Exclaiming)
He's not in his 40s. He might be in his 20s.
- Are you cold? - My back hit the floor.
It's part of your job.
(It's part of his job.)
Would you rather stay home...
- Or work here? - or burn your back?
(Everyone should work.)
- You look best when you work. - Exactly.
It's part of your job.
- That's why you are a comedian. - The cameramen are laughing hard.
- Aren't you happy? - What a man.
- It's... It's part of my job. - Right.
He's so positive now.
- Burning your back is part of it. - Right, I should enjoy my job.
- Exactly. - Right?
- Who was in the movie? - Can you remember?
(Who's starring in the same movie alongside Je Hoon?)
- Kim Sung Kyun? - Hold on.
- Try it. - Go for it.
- Is it Kim Sung Kyun? - It's him.
Is it him?
- I think it is. - Was he in the trailer?
It might be him.
Look at his face. We're right.
It's not him.
It is Kim Sung Kyun, no?
- It must be him. - It is Sung Kyun.
- It is him. - Kim Sung Kyun!
It has to be him.
Je Hoon will reveal the answer.
What if it's not him?
(Je Hoon will reveal the answer.)
Sung Kyun, you're caught. Come out.
(Je Hoon calls Sung Kyun out.)
(They got it right again.)
- We're so good. - This is our day.
- That's great. - What did I say?
We wouldn't have guessed it without Ji Hyo.
Hello!
Do you like pizza?
(He has played diverse roles...)
Let's go!
(and he's proven himself to be a scene-stealer.)
Nice to meet you Nice to meet you
I love him.
- I watched all of it. - You are looking good.
You do look much better.
You don't have a mic on you, right? Let's take it off.
- Really? - He wore a nice suit though.
He wore a nice suit, but he has to take it off.
Sung Kyun looks so much nicer now.
This is really something.
- It's your first time, right? - Don't worry, you won't fly.
Please say hi.
My name is Kim Sung Kyun and I'll be acting the role of Kang Sung Il.
- Bye, bye. - See you.
(Nice to meet you.)
(This is his first and last greeting.)
He's in.
(Giggling)
- Lie down. - Lie here. It's cold.
(You must dry yourself.)
- Isn't it warm here? - You must be cold.
That's funny.
- It's A Ra's turn next. - A Ra!
- It's A Ra. - It must be A Ra.
It has to be.
(They have no doubt it's her.)
Shall we still give it a go?
Let's hear your voice. Hello.
- Hello. - A Ra!
- A Ra. - Hello, A Ra.
- Go A Ra! - Show us your beautiful face.
Is your last name "Go"?
(Is her last name Go?)
Yes...
(It has to be Go A Ra.)
- It has to be her. - What should I ask?
Are you an actress? Actually, have you been on Running Man?
(Has she been on Running Man?)
Yes.
- We know who it is. - We do.
You are the beautiful woman that we know, right?
No.
(Bye, Jae Seok!)
What was that about?
My goodness, that was funny.
- She's so modest. - Hey!
- You shouldn't have asked. - Hey, hold on!
Hold on!
This is really no joke!
- Hey, then... - It's her opinion.
You can't ask an actor if he thinks he's handsome.
Oh, dear.
(She got on his nerve.)
I'll get it right. She angered me, so I'll just guess it right.
Right, dump her in the water.
- Gosh! - Save me, Jae Seok!
(Screaming)
- What was that about? - What's she saying?
- What's she saying? - I don't want to get soaked!
Then why did you infuriate me?
- I love you, Jae Seok! - Come on!
- We have to throw her in the water. - Of course!
- Let's dump her in! - Let's go.
Would Jae Seok really...
let an actress get soaked?
- Of course. - He's changed a lot.
But we came this far, so we can't play dumb.
- That doesn't make any sense. - Viewers won't like that.
Viewers won't like that.
You better not say Ko Chang Seok.
Don't say something else.
If I say "Go Wa Ra", it's wrong, right?
- Don't do it! - Don't do it!
Fine, you guys sound very angry.
- Why would he do this? - It's obviously Go A Ra.
What is it?
Is there anyone who'd take my place?
Just be quiet.
(Rejected)
We don't have such a thing.
What do you think?
(We don't show mercy to an actress.)
Come here!
- Jae Seok. - Seriously.
A Ra is making me mad.
- Don't be easy on her! - Just say her name!
- We are already soaked. - It's so cold.
Say her name and she'll fall in the water.
Jae Seok, don't drench an actress.
- What? - Don't let an actress get wet.
(Jong Kook is a gentleman.)
(What a man.)
(Let's protect women.)
What a man.
Don't make me laugh, you punk.
(You must be kidding.)
You are seriously funny! You really are!
I'll take care of it! I will!
Hey, this is not the time.
- I'm getting mad. - Hey!
- Stop trying to look good. - And what did you say?
- Quit it. - I'm so mad.
- Gosh, that's funny. - I'm going to call her name!
- Go for it. - I can't take this any more!
- The answer is... - Go for it.
(He is about to say the answer.)
Just say it!
(Annoyed)
I was about to say it!
You're really enraging me!
- Be quiet. - A Ra.
A Ra must be getting mad, too.
- Count for me. - In 1, 2, 3.
(He will really talk this time!)
(A Ra, are you ready for this?)
(Her heart is racing.)
(Will Jae Seok dump the actress into the water?)
- In 1, 2, 3. - In 1, 2, 3.
Gu Ha Ra.
- Gu Ha Ra. - Come on!
(She's happy,)
(but they're not.)
(Pandemonium follows.)
- Gosh! - My goodness!
- Darn it! - Thank you!
It's so cold!
(Save yourselves!)
(He lies down in the sun again.)
(He proves himself a gentleman once again.)
I couldn't!
So our last guest is Go A Ra!
(Go A Ra has a multitude of charms.)
(She looks innocent but played many unique roles.)
That's what he said.
- This is really nice. - It is.
We have A Ra, Sung Kyun and Je Hoon with us.
- It's really nice. - Let me explain today's mission.
It's called Find the No Man. There's only one answer.
And you should find the No Man.
- No Man? - Yes.
The No Man is among you and you'll have to find out who it is.
If you find the No Man in three tries, Yes Men win.
But if you don't, the No Man wins.
Those who lose will get the mud bomb penalty.
Mud bomb?
I'll explain how you can guess the No Man.
We'll give you a question before you start each mission.
Then five members will become a team.
If there are only Yes Men in a team, the team's answer will be "Yes".
But the team with the No Man will automatically answer "No".
You will have to pay the price if your answer is wrong.
(No Man's team will always answer "No".)
If you win each game, you'll earn a Member Swapping Card.
You can either maintain the members or change three of them.
(You have the choice.)
So we have to find the No Man.
So we'll decide the No Man.
- Can you see the tent behind you? - Yes.
When you enter it, you'll see many phones on a table.
Choose one of the phones.
Once you remove the battery,
you'll find either a "Yes" or a "No" sticker.
No one will know who it is.
If you choose the one with the "No" sticker,
you are the No Man.
(The one who chooses "No" will be the No Man.)
(Kwang Soo goes first.)
Do I choose whatever I want?
(Nervous)
(He removes the battery.)
(I am "blank" Man.)
(The members each choose a phone.)
(They all have ambiguous looks on their faces.)
(Everyone chose a phone.)
- Did you all check? - Yes!
Then, I'll announce the first question.
- Okay. - Here goes the first question.
(Here comes the first question.)
"Will you wear humiliating t-shirts?"
(Will you wear humiliating t-shirts?)
(Humiliating t-shirts?)
- Gosh! - My goodness.
- I hate it! - That's really humiliating!
(Behold!)
- That's unbelievable. - Gosh.
Oh, dear!
- Gosh. - It says "I'm younger than Haha".
(He's at a loss for words.)
Look at Jong Kook's.
That's when they shot air at my face.
I remember what is on Ji Hyo's shirt.
Look at her's.
Gosh, Song Ji Hyo. Goodness.
You are too mean to us.
- Gosh. - Haha's photo is...
when he threw the ball in the opening ceremony of a baseball game.
Were you in pain or something?
(I want to be like Gary.)
Gary, yours isn't that bad.
But Haha's makes me mad.
- Look at A Ra's. - Gosh.
- A Ra. - What's that?
Kwang Soo's isn't humiliating at all.
That's how he looks every day.
- What do you mean? - That's your everyday look.
What's that on Je Hoon's t-shirt? "Come on"?
We couldn't find any humiliating photos of Je Hoon.
Let's make one today!
(Let's make one today!)
- So you all saw your t-shirts. - Yes.
- That's not that humiliating. - Then,
five of you will have to wear the t-shirts.
- We must have the No Man with us. - Right.
- We need the No Man in our team. - No Man's team has the advantage.
We should be on No Man's team.
- Now, we'll form teams. - Gosh.
The three guests will be divided into two teams first.
Then, they'll choose the members they want...
until each team has five members.
Okay.
- Rock-paper-scissors. - Rock-paper-scissors.
(Je Hoon won.)
- Go ahead. - Haha.
(Je Hoon picks Haha.)
- I'll pick Gary. - Just choose him.
- You chose Gary. - We need to choose the No Man.
Whom will you choose next?
- Good. - He chose Ji Hyo.
- I'll choose Kwang Soo. - Me?
(Je Hoon picks Kwang Soo.)
That's right. Kwang Soo could be the No Man.
- I'll choose Seok Jin. - Yes.
- Good. - You made a right choice.
- Good. - I feel good.
I pick Jong Kook.
(Sung Kyun picks Jong Kook.)
Great.
I think one of you may be the No Man.
- Kwang Soo or... - We're safe!
We never know.
(They are finished.)
- Are we done? - Will you wear the t-shirts?
- Yes. - No.
The team whose members will wear...
the humiliating t-shirts is...
(Which team will it be?)
(Je Hoon's team)
- We need to wear them. - Gosh.
- We should've... - It means the No Man is here.
- Who is the No Man? - Who is it?
- Please go get changed. - None of us is the No Man?
- The No Man isn't with us. - Who's the No Man?
- It's not me. - Gosh!
(The No Man is in Team Sung Kyun.)
- We'll move onto the next mission. - Okay.
- Before we get going, - Okay.
- Question. - we'll announce the next question.
Is it...
(The questions can change the outcomes.)
(What will their second question be?)
"You don't want to eat delicacies, do you?"
- No. - No.
- We can't eat them? - They cannot eat them.
- They made the question tricky. - Yes, it's us!
- Yes! - We can have delicacies, then.
We can eat!
- So... - We can't eat if we're together.
This is your second question.
So the Yes Team will have a frugal meal.
And the No Team will have delicacies.
If you win this mission,
- the Member Swapping Card is yours. - I see.
If the No Team wins,
you don't have to change members...
- and just enjoy the delicacies. - Of course, we will.
- Or you can change members... - Can we change just one member?
and receive a hint about who the No Man is. It's your choice.
- We don't have to change members. - We should...
But we should find out who the No Man is.
- We should eat first. - No way.
(When everyone says "Yes", Jae Seok says "No".)
What we need right now is food!
- Eating always comes first! - We can eat first.
What's so important about finding the No Man?
- We should eat first. - We're here to find the No Man.
- Gosh. - What's our ultimate goal today?
- It's finding the No Man. - No, it's eating!
- We're doing this to eat! - Gosh.
- That's ridiculous! - Let's go, then!
(Then we must win this mission.)
(Both teams are moving to their next destination.)
(How will both teams end up?)
So the No Man is among us.
- It feels weird. - It does.
- It's not me. - It's not me either.
We'll find out soon.
(Who among these 5 is the No Man?)
- Je Hoon. - Are you usually competitive?
When you play games, do you tend to be well-mannered?
- Please tell us. - I am well-mannered,
but I believe in playing fair to win.
Do you mean that...
you check to see if someone's cheating?
If you watch the Premier League games, each team has its style.
And our team tends to cheat a lot to win.
Like Diego Costa of Chelsea?
Right. That's right.
(Do you want me to play like Diego Costa?)
As Diego Costa of Chelsea used violence on an opponent player,
he received penalty for his wrongdoing.
He even pushed the player down...
when the opponent tried to stand up.
- Like Diego Costa of Chelsea? - Right.
If Haha, Kwang Soo and I are in the same team,
- it's a given. - You should cheat as well.
It's weird if we don't cheat.
A Ra also joined us a few times...
and she's not a fair player.
- Gosh. - What are you talking about?
- I'm lost for words. - She's definitely not.
- When you... - I saw you cheating.
- My goodness. - I know you cheated a lot.
- Right. - A Ra is a pretty dirty player.
- We must win today. - Okay.
We should use any means to win.
- We don't have to be gentle. - He's right.
You can swear and even hit them when the camera isn't rolling.
You'd better be prepared to cheat in order to win today.
Let me explain the rules.
You should clear the "Road Mission Shows" and come...
- to the restaurant first to win. - Okay.
The first mission is...
- jegichagi. - It's jegichagi.
You should bring three passers-by...
and play a relay jegichagi.
- This is our first game. - Okay, let's go!
Do you know how to play jegichagi?
Is anyone good at jegichagi?
Good. Come here.
(Jong Kook casts the first player.)
- Are you good at jegichagi? - Jegichagi.
He said he's a good football player.
Come out.
- Come with us. - It's okay.
This is the order that we should go by.
All right. Let's go for it.
- Get ready. - In 1, 2 and 3.
- We can do it! - We can do it!
(The winning team can take the advantageous position.)
Play it slowly.
(Mission starts.)
All right!
(Gary tosses the jegi to Sung Kyun.)
Good. Toss it higher.
(Pass!)
- Good! Go! - Gosh, what happened?
(Ji Hyo is the last player.)
Gosh, what happened?
(They succeed in first try.)
We did it!
(Yes Team succeeds the first game in 3 minutes.)
(Stunned)
We did it!
(Thank you so much.)
Let me go first. Do I pass this to him?
- That's it. - Wait!
(A Ra misses the jegi.)
- A Ra, you can do it, right? - Yes.
- Can you do this? - Why don't you go last?
- Don't you want the delicacies? - Look at this.
Do like this.
(Haha gives A Ra a tip.)
Toss it at this point.
- That's right. - All right! Let's go!
Start.
(They attempt again.)
(If I do as Haha taught me, we can make it!)
(Tossing)
- A Ra! - Mark my words!
- Look at him! - A Ra, please.
Toss it like this.
- Do not throw it. - Try it.
One, two... Kick this.
(Kick it.)
(She misses.)
(This is so frustrating.)
- Okay. That's enough. - Try it again.
- Will you please kick it like this? - Why can't you do it?
Don't kick it away.
- Wait. - Try again.
You almost got it.
- Let's change the order. - Okay. You'll be the last.
Let me go first.
- Okay. I'll go last. - Let's begin.
- Hold on. - Okay. Go.
(They can't delay it any longer.)
(They must succeed in order to get the Member Swapping Card.)
(Mission starts.)
- There you go. - Good.
- There you go. - Good job.
- That's it. - Keep it up.
Kick it with your right foot.
(He saves the jegi from falling.)
I got this.
- There you go. - Nice.
I'll get it.
- Good job. - We're doing great.
(A Ra has to kick it once to complete the mission.)
(Will they succeed?)
(Success)
- You did it. - Good job.
(Yes Team completes the mission.)
We did it.
- We need to swap members. - Hey.
- We should thank the No Man. - Thank you.
The person is doing a great job.
No Man is trying really hard.
No Man must be hungry, too.
- I see. - No Man must be hungry, too.
You know, everyone needs their own goal.
Look. There's an elderly woman.
- Where? - Excuse me.
- Excuse me, Ma'am. - Excuse me.
- Hello. - Can you spare five minutes for us?
- Do you have time? - We will draw a picture.
You just have to guess what we are drawing.
- You just have to make a guess. - In 30 seconds.
Thank you.
Thank you, Ma'am.
Ma'am, do you know who we all are?
- Do you know him? - Hello.
- Hello. - I know you!
- You're Kim Jong Kook. - You're right.
- I see you on TV all the time. - Thank you.
Do you know who he is?
I don't remember.
(Embarrassed)
- He plays the role of a villain. - Goodness.
- Is he a singer? - Maybe this will jog your memory.
- "Goodness. Hello." - "Hello."
- "Nice to see you." - "Nice to see you."
- I remember now. - Okay.
How about him?
(Does she know who Gary is?)
(It's me, Gary.)
It's Dary. Dary.
He's not Dary.
(Dary must sound more familiar to her.)
She just called you "Dary".
Dary.
- I'm really good at this. - Okay.
- You can count on me. - Okay.
(Mission starts.)
(Fork crane)
- How do I draw that? - Oh, my.
Wouldn't this be too difficult for her?
Look closely, Ma'am.
This might be a bit difficult.
(She has 30 seconds to get the right answer.)
- This is difficult. - Don't forget...
to draw the crane.
(What is this thing used for?)
- Hold it tightly. - Okay.
- You need to hold on to it. - Is it a bowl?
Hold on. Let me do this.
Just follow my lead.
Jong Kook is good at drawing.
- He is. - This is difficult.
It looks okay.
Wow.
(It's getting better with Jong Kook's lead.)
- Please give us the answer. - One.
Please, tell us your answer.
Ma'am, take a closer look.
Do you know what this is?
- Five, four. - Don't feel pressured.
- Four. - Feel free to guess anything.
- Three, two. - Is it a fork crane?
(Is it a fork crane?)
Is it a fork crane?
(She got it right.)
- That's right. - That's great, Ma'am.
Ma'am, you're the best.
(No Team completed their mission.)
Thank you so much.
(How is Yes Team doing in their second mission?)
(Owl)
- Okay, we can do this. - All right. In 1, 2, 3.
- Here we go. - Loosen your grip.
- Loosen your grip. - Not that way.
Loosen your grip.
- What are we doing? - You're doing it wrong.
- Gosh. - Stay still.
It doesn't look right.
- I don't think this looks right. - This is not it.
No, it's not.
- Loosen your grip. - This isn't right.
- Why don't we finish here? - Loosen your grip.
Why won't you loosen your grip?
- I can't finish here. - Move it over here.
- Move it over this side. - Just skip this.
- What are you doing? - What are you drawing?
(It's a fat owl.)
Who's in charge?
This is horrible.
(I was trying to draw an owl,)
(but what is this creature?)
- What is that? - Hold on.
What is this?
This looks weird.
Can you tell what this is?
- Here it is. - Did I draw this?
You did.
(Can he figure out what this drawing is supposed to be?)
- Is this our final drawing? - What's your guess?
It's a chick.
- Wait. - No.
- Hold on. - You spoke too soon.
You have to answer when we count to three.
Take your time and look at the drawing again.
I understand why you said chick.
- Wait. - That looks scary.
- What is your guess? - One.
- Two. - King Kong.
- King Kong. - It's not King Kong.
(They fail their mission.)
- What's the answer? - It's...
- an owl. - Sorry.
- We're sorry. - We apologise.
(He is shocked.)
- Let's ask them for help. - Please help us.
Excuse me.
- Please come here. - Maybe they'll get it.
(She starts running.)
- Please come here. - Bring them over.
Hello. We need some help for Running Man.
Could you guess what we're drawing?
- It's simple. - Well...
- Come on. - It's too difficult.
- Hello. - Are you good at drawing?
Please begin.
(We want all the viewers to take a guess, too.)
Okay.
- Good. - That's good.
That's good. Let's stop here.
- I'm sure she can do it. - Okay!
Please turn around.
It's small, so you should come closer.
- It is a bit small, isn't it? - It's tiny.
One, two, three.
(Will Yes Team be able to complete this mission?)
It's an anchovy.
(Anchovy)
(Correct)
- You're right. - It's an anchovy.
- Wow. - We did it.
Well done.
You completed all the Road Missions.
This is the address of the restaurant.
- We need to get there quickly. - Hurry.
- Okay. - Hurry. Hurry.
- Okay. - Go. Go.
- Let's go. - Come on.
(They need to get there before the other team does.)
We have to either swap members or find the No Man.
Let's think about finding the No Man after we eat.
- You're right. - I don't think we'll find him.
We have to find the No Man.
Is No Man really that important?
Is finding the No Man still important?
How should we swap members?
Let's decide whom we should swap first.
- Jong Kook, Sung Kyun. - Yes.
- I think Jong Kook is the No Man. - I think so, too.
Jae Seok could be the No Man, too.
If it's either Sung Kyun or Jong Kook,
we should leave them and us three should swap teams.
If Sung Kyun or Jong Kook is the No Man, we have a 50 percent chance.
It's pretty high.
- We should go that way. - Okay. Let's send...
- three people to the other team. - All right.
- That's it. - Okay.
Okay. That's it.
- This isn't goodbye forever. - It's temporary.
If the No Man joins the other team, will he be the one eating?
- Yes, that's right. - Of course.
(Will the No Man be able to hide his identity?)
- It's a big feast. - Did we get here first?
- Wow. - We came first.
Yes.
(Yes Team won.)
- We won. - That was hard.
It's a big feast.
- Look at the food. - What is that?
- What is that? - It's rice with soy sauce.
It's barley rice.
- Are they hiding here? - That looks so cruel.
Let's choose first.
Let's choose who we will swap.
- They will be leaving. - Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
- We don't have another choice. - Okay.
You can only put out rock or paper.
(Haha signals everyone except Kwang Soo.)
It's rock or paper?
I meant, paper or scissors.
What are you doing?
- Why are you doing this to me? - What did I do?
- That wasn't fair. - Those punks.
- What are you doing? - That wasn't very fair.
Okay. Let's do it.
All right. Let's go.
(Kwang Soo signals rock, and Haha signals paper.)
(Whom will they listen to?)
- Rock-paper-scissors! - Rock-paper-scissors!
(Kwang Soo will be swapped.)
Yes.
Did anybody see my signal? Did you just ignore me?
(He wanted them to put out rock, but they just ignored him.)
I can't believe you didn't put out rock.
All right. You are leaving.
- You're leaving. - Okay.
How should we choose the next person?
Je Hoon, do you have any ideas?
- All right. - Wait. How will we choose?
- The loser has to leave. - Okay.
- Okay. The loser will leave. - Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
Rock-paper-scissors.
(He signals rock to trick Seok Jin.)
- Rock-paper-scissors! - Rock-paper-scissors!
(Seok Jin will be swapped, too.)
(Okay.)
(You tricked me again.)
Did you guys plan this?
Why are you looking at me?
Let's only put out rock or scissors.
- Only rock or scissors. - Scissors?
- Yes. - Okay.
- Rock-paper-scissors! - Rock-paper-scissors!
(What is this?)
You cheater.
(Hurrah)
He's a cheater.
- Je Hoon just cheated. - Why? What happened?
He told me to put out scissors.
- He got you. - Haha,
he tricked me, too.
(We did it.)
This is great.
This side is much better.
- We're not sending No Man. - We're not.
- That's right. - That was great.
(Je Hoon signaled scissors to Haha, first.)
(He puts on a poker face.)
Only rock or scissors.
(Then he signaled scissors to A Ra.)
(After that, he put out rock and played them.)
He's the best among all the actors I've met.
No Man can be on your side.
We're full of surprises today.
I can't believe that Je Hoon did this.
People like you cause dramas like "Signal" to happen in real life.
(Je Hoon played a traitor today.)
I'm sorry.
They're here already.
(No Team finally arrives.)
- You're late. - You are.
(You're one step late.)
- It's nice to see you all. - What delayed you?
We already know who we want to swap.
- Really? - Yes.
- Let's play black and white. - Okay.
- Are we choosing three people? - Yes.
- Black and white. - White.
Who's left?
- Those 3 are leaving. - Those 3 are staying.
We are leaving.
If the three of us swap teams...
and we get to eat, it means that it's between...
- the two of them. - That's right.
- We'll know for sure. - It'll be one of them.
- It'll narrow it down. - We'll have a 50 percent chance.
All right. Let's move.
These three will join your team.
- Are you joining us? - Yes.
(They swap team members.)
- Who is the No Man? - All right. Look.
- Is the No Man on our team? - It's the two of them, isn't it?
We have the two candidates on our team.
If your team gets the meal,
either Jong Kook or Sung Kyun is the No Man.
- We're close to figuring it out. - That's amazing.
- It's 1 of those 2. - I'll give you the second question.
All of you must answer yes to the question...
"You don't want the feast, do you?"
The team that doesn't get the meal will be penalised.
Okay. Let's find out.
(Is Jong Kook or Sung Kyun the No Man?)
(Or is it someone else?)
- The No Man is on that team. - Oh, my!
- Do we get to eat? - It's one of those two.
(Jong Kook's team will have the feast.)
All right. Who's the No Man?
- Who is it? - It's not me.
It's 1 of you 2.
- Do we get to eat? - I knew it.
- Do we get to eat? - I knew this would happen.
(They seem depressed.)
That's too bad.
It's either Sung Kyun or Jong Kook.
- Sung Kyun. - Let's eat.
Whatever.
(Anyway, it's a feast!)
- We did it! - It's a feast!
- Je Hoon guesses so well. - He's so good.
Who is it between the two?
They're the two people that we predicted.
Je Hoon is sharp.
Je Hoon is thriving today.
It's Je Hoon's day today.
Je Hoon is amazing.
- Can we eat now? - It's a feast!
- Thank you for the food. - It has all the delicacies.
Enjoy.
(They are happy that they can say no.)
I like something chewy.
Eat the meat, too. Eat a lot.
It's delicious.
The beef is...
authentic Korean beef.
It's really nice.
Try the raw beef, too.
- It's delicious. - I'm jealous.
They look so pitiful.
(The Yes Team looks so sad.)
Look at this beauty.
(Different situations under the same roof.)
- But isn't this too much? - What is?
Isn't that life?
- Gosh. Think in our shoes. - Seok Jin.
- What would you do? - I am really sorry,
but Je Hoon's the special guest. Why are you sitting in the middle?
Why is that so important?
- Why are you obsessed... - The guest should be there.
- about being in the centre? - I just sat here unintentionally.
- What's the big deal? You sit here. - He always wants attention.
- What's the big deal? - That's great.
- Now, it's balanced. - Now, it's perfect.
- How about Sung Kyun then? - How about him?
Sung Kyun is meant to stay there.
- And why is that? - His head looks small from there.
- I must be crazy. - Why?
- I sat in the middle. - Don't say that!
(How could I?)
- You are mad. - Gosh...
- He didn't even know. - I must be mad.
- He's an attention-seeker. - Gosh, I didn't know.
- What? - You seek attention.
- I am an attention-seeker? - You want to be in the centre.
- I want to be in the centre? - He's a centre-seeker.
Gosh...
I'm a side-seeker.
(He's a side-seeker.)
So I am the centre-seeker.
It's my first time being accused of such a thing.
(Now, he is determined to find the No Man!)
Let's go.
- Let's go. - Let's go!
- Let's try it. - We have to win.
I love it. It's going as we planned, Je Hoon.
We picked the two of you as the No Man suspects.
- We thought it'd be one of you. - Right.
- We guessed it right. - It's the first time...
we narrowed the list to two candidates.
(There's a 50 percent chance.)
Then should I pretend not to know anything to make it extra fun?
- To make it more fun? - I have no idea who it is!
If we are too quiet, do the producer talk to you through walkie-talkie...
- and tell you to talk more? - By any chance,
- Can you reenact that scene? - The scene with the walkie-talkie?
- Please. - Right.
(He attempts to communicate.)
Detective.
Yes, I am listening. Did you catch the suspect?
(Reenactment of the breathtaking scene.)
I caught the suspect.
Can you hear me?
(He reenacts a scene from "Signal".)
(They are lucky to witness Je Hoon's acting up-close.)
Do you hear my voice?
(Do you hear my voice?)
Call him.
Detective Lee Jae Han.
(They get the chills.)
Detective!
Open the window. They're watching.
Detective Yu!
- He's talking to Detective Lee. - We're watching "Signal"!
- I am Park Hae Young. - Lieutenant Park.
Are you listening to me?
- Yes, Detective. Where are you? - They are so different.
- Lieutenant Park. - I want to hear it, too!
I guess it's different there now.
It must be better now, right?
(He bets on his name...)
I caught the suspect.
(to catch the No Man.)
- First of all... - I loved that drama.
- I am going crazy right now. - We still love it.
It's a basketball court.
Oh my gosh.
- We have to use our strength. - I'm so weak.
- It's all about your strength. - I think we have to dangle.
- Gosh... - No way.
This...
- This doesn't... - This doesn't make sense.
You want us to do this?
We can't even dangle.
- Isn't this too unfair for us? - What is it?
- What's wrong? - We have to dangle...
- and make the opponent fall. - It's that game!
(Same mission, different reactions)
- It's unfair for us. - Gosh...
- How can this be? - Let's do this!
- It's unfair for us. - Why?
It's not like we planned it. It just happened this way.
Only one person can play, right?
Seok Jin, I am sorry, but you're not the one we are afraid of.
Why are you acting confidently?
- It's just that we are a team. - Gosh...
- We're a team. - You drive us crazy.
When will I be this confident?
You're unbelievable.
Before we play the game, I'll reveal the last question.
(The last question is revealed.)
What will it be?
(What will it be?)
"Will you carry your opponent?"
(Will you carry your opponent?)
- To where? - Our answer is no, right?
Right.
- We don't want to do it. - After this game, you will...
move to the last venue.
And it's about 1km away from here.
- We have to walk 1km? - We have to carry them?
- We will piggyback them? - And walk 1km?
The team with No Man will be...
- exempted. - We won't have to carry them.
- The Yes Team... - We have to win.
will carry the No Team and walk 1km.
But how will you find the No Man without switching members?
- That's true. - We won't find him then.
We won't find him and we will be carried.
- I won't switch. - How can we walk 1km?
Whenever the feet of the person on your back touch the ground,
a mole will be drawn on your face.
Yes. Great.
- We will win for sure. - We will get at least 10 moles.
- How can we do this? - They will turn into leopards.
How could you add more ugliness to the already ugly face?
What will I do?
- We have to win and get carried. - Let's talk...
- after we win. - Let's talk after we win.
One of you is the No Man.
- They are in one team. - So who is it?
- Only two are left. - Honestly, we really don't know.
- I am sorry, but... - We'll know if we separate them.
But it's really not me.
We're leaning towards him.
- Isn't it too unfair for us? - It's too unfair.
- It's very unfair. - Are you trying to kill us all?
- It's... - It doesn't make sense.
This mission is one-on-one hanging leg wrestling.
- Hanging leg wrestling? - How does it work?
Each team will determine the match order.
Then each team member will come out and choose a box each.
They will wear what they get from the box around their feet.
And then they'll leg wrestle while hanging.
- Let's begin. - Let's do it!
We have to win this.
Song Ji Hyo!
Seok Jin.
Please announce it.
Go A Ra.
- Lee Je Hoon. - That's good!
All right!
You each get to choose one.
- I got green onions. - That's a nice one.
That's nice.
What's that?
What's this?
(Ji Hyo picks inflated rubber gloves.)
I got green onions.
But I have to be able to hang up there.
(Gravity is his biggest enemy.)
(Seok Jin versus Ji Hyo)
We don't know what will happen.
- Here we go. - Okay.
(It's the match of the century.)
Ready.
(Seok Jin's green onion versus Ji Hyo's rubber gloves)
Start.
That's it, that's it.
(Ji Hyo climbs up Seok Jin.)
(Ji Hyo attacks Seok Jin first.)
(She hits Seok Jin's face.)
(Let me borrow your face for a while, Seok Jin.)
- Oh, no. - Oh, dear.
What should he do?
- Drop his glasses! - She's amazing.
- She's great. - Grab him.
- Hey... - Grab Seok Jin's fingers.
Attack his fingers, Ji Hyo.
(But the game is not over yet.)
(I can't give up like this.)
(Will Seok Jin begin his counterattack?)
(Fails)
(Flapping)
(He falls.)
(Ji Hyo wins.)
Ji Hyo. Ji Hyo. Ji Hyo, you are...
You are really impressive.
Gosh, I am so upset!
- I'm so upset. - I'm sorry, Seok Jin.
(I'm sorry, but I was being easy on you.)
(Je Hoon and A Ra choose their boxes.)
- Is it a flower? - What is it?
It's a flower!
- It's a flower. - Give it to me.
You could tickle his face.
I got...
It's a feather. That would be even more ticklish.
- That's... - Please bring your items.
(Je Hoon and A Ra get ready.)
(Their appearances...)
(brighten up the mood of the game.)
Isn't this the last round?
- All right. - This is the last round.
(But behind this beautiful match is a dreadful penalty.)
Ready.
Set.
(It will be a tough match.)
Start.
- Are you all right? - A Ra.
They are too close.
(Are you okay, A Ra?)
- You have to do it. - A Ra, you must win.
- Tickle him. - Wrap him.
- Wrap him. - You have to win.
(They hesitate to battle and exchange eye contact instead.)
Je Hoon, you can't win like that.
- Come on! - You can even kick him.
- Je Hoon, I am sorry. - A Ra, wrap his waist.
(I'm sorry, Je Hoon.)
(She kicks Je Hoon lightly.)
(She just touches him lightly.)
(This is strange. This game is supposed to be...)
(a merciless war.)
No. You are amazing.
- Wrap your legs around him. - Grab him.
I am sorry, Je Hoon.
- That's it, A Ra. - I don't know where to attack.
You have to wrap your legs around his waist to win.
(She falls.)
Yes! I knew it!
(What happened? Did Je Hoon do something?)
He's perfect. He's handsome and strong.
- It's tough to stay hanging. - It's tough for a girl.
(Currently, No Team is winning by 1 point.)
(Sung Kyun versus Jae Seok)
Ready.
Get set, go!
- He's getting right into it. - Look at him go.
(Jae Seok surprises Sung Kyun.)
Raise them higher!
(He rests his legs on Sung Kyun's bar.)
- It didn't work. - I don't think this is right.
(It didn't work.)
- It didn't work. - What am I doing?
- Hold on. - This is unpredictable.
Sung Kyun, you might win.
- Jae Seok, bite him. - Raise them the other way.
- Where? - Go the other way.
Lift yourself with your arms.
(Biting)
Did you bite him?
- He bit him. - He bit his foot.
(Nobody thought it would be an easy match,)
(but they didn't think it would be this extreme.)
Good job. Way to go.
Poke his bottom.
(Jong Kook tells Sung Kyun to poke Jae Seok's bottom.)
(He pokes Jae Seok's bottom.)
(Sung Kyun attacks back.)
Look at him.
(Shaking)
(Let's send him to the other side of the world!)
(Please do not try this at home.)
- Isn't that too deep? - Goodness.
- That's too much. - Gosh.
Isn't that too deep?
(Jae Seok succumbs to it and drops.)
What was that about?
- That wasn't expected. - Hey.
- What was that about? - That was a good match.
- Hey, Sung Kyun. - We won.
How could you do this?
Jae Seok, that was close to a colonoscopy.
His hand disappeared completely.
- Hey. - Did you see what he did?
Come on, Sung Kyun.
Did you find any polyps in there?
- Ji Hyo. - There weren't any.
- That's good to hear. - Did you get a colonoscopy?
- Jae Seok. - Congratulations.
He really poked me hard.
Sung Kyun is enthusiastic, but he doesn't understand comedy.
- Is that right? - He didn't have to poke that deep.
- It was this much. - I thought he was an anaconda.
- Even his arm... - Hold on.
- He's a cobra. - This is a first.
Ji Hyo, I'm leaving it at that because I'm on television.
- Oh, gosh. - This is part of the act.
(Was he always this competitive?)
One of you is the No Man.
Who is it? Tell us who the No Man is.
It's not me.
- We are leaning towards him. - We are.
- It's not me. - We never know.
(Was he trying so hard because he's the No Man?)
Is this allowed?
- You can't do anything about it. - You should have worn a diaper.
Why would I wear a diaper? He went too far.
I'm sorry. I apologise.
- So the final score is 3 to 1. - That's right.
- We can do a match worth 2 points. - Let's do it for 10 points.
Hold on. You were the only one who lost on your team.
- Why are you showing off? - So?
- Don't boss us around. - I'm on this side.
- This is my team. - I am at a loss for words.
We can give you up to 100 points, but you need to bet on something.
- Did you say 100 points? - Yes.
You need to give up something.
- Doesn't that hurt your pride? - We don't have to do this.
I won't do it!
Don't do it, then! Forget it.
There's no reason for us to do this.
I do want to win,
so let's do a match worth 400 points.
I won't play dirty any more.
If I lose, I'll admit my failure.
If we lose, we'll give you 2.5 trillion points.
(We're willing to put 2.5 trillion points on the line.)
You're getting on my nerves.
- You're getting on my nerves. - You can take 2.5 trillion points.
If we lose, we'll even give you a piggy back ride home.
All right.
I'll go.
(Jae Seok will compete in this crucial match.)
- Give him a gastroscopy this time. - It's worth 10 trillion points.
(We meet again.)
- In 1, 2, 3. - Yes!
(Jong Kook versus Jae Seok)
Ready, go!
Give him a face massage.
- Use your feet. - You've done this before.
Lucky you, Jae Seok.
(You've come again, my dear customer.)
- Hey. - This is humiliating.
Gosh.
(Struggling)
Your feet stink.
(Jong Kook's feet stink.)
(Don't my feet smell nice?)
You're so cute.
- Go, Jae Seok! - Go, Jae Seok!
He's good at giving a meridian massage.
(Jong Kook starts rubbing Jae Seok's face again.)
This isn't right.
(Dropping)
That's our win.
(You're welcome to challenge me again.)
- We wanted to give you more points. - Couldn't you do better?
It was right on the table.
(That was fun.)
Gosh.
So the final score is 2,500,000,000,405 to 1.
(The No Team takes the win.)
- 2.5 trillion to... - It's 2,500,000,000,405 to 1.
What did you say?
(The score went from 3 to 1 to 2.5 trillion to 1.)
- That's a big difference. - It is.
This is how you become penniless.
(This is why you shouldn't gamble.)
- You need to run away. - Life turns itself around...
- in a split second. - You shouldn't invest everything.
(This game taught them a life lesson.)
- The No Team is the winner. - I'm exhausted.
- Yes. - Great.
- Oh, gosh. - Yes Men, think about this.
- What? - Let's rip their name tags.
What if we rip Sung Kyun's...
- and find out that he's the No Man. - Then, we have to take the penalty.
- Exactly. - Why would we risk that chance?
Then, give us Jong Kook.
- What if it's not him? - What if he's the No Man?
- What do you mean? - What do you want us to do?
- Who'll give him a piggy back ride? - To be honest,
I'd rather not separate from him.
- I want to be on his side. - Did we just play...
that game to narrow down the No Man?
- She's upset. - This is too...
She's upset.
- This is unfair. - Go over to them.
- We need a different game. - Complain for us.
We have to separate the No Man candidates.
- A win won't do. - That's right, A Ra.
- At this stage, - She's upset.
don't we need to talk this over in a quiet space?
It's fine if we have to give them a piggy back ride.
- But we'll get mud-bombed. - We have to find the No Man.
- You guys are impossible! - We'll get mud-bombed.
- Can't you tell? - Then, let's not do the piggy back.
Let's just take the mud bomb.
- Seriously? - You take it on your own!
Do you think that's fair?
- This is not a joke! - This isn't fair.
- I have a bad back. - We should have done this before.
- It's better to take the mud bomb. - Listen.
- He has a disc problem. - Don't put yourself through this.
- I can't do this. - We'll be giving piggy back rides,
- but we'll all be mud-bombed. - One thing is for certain.
- You're wrong. - Why should we be punished?
We won so why should we be punished?
You know what the best scenario is? If we do neither...
- of the punishments. - Exactly.
- Why would we... - We can just choose.
- It's a 50 percent chance. - That's right.
Hold on. Sir, what are you doing in this group?
- What's your role in the group? - I'm a member of this team.
(I'm a member of this team.)
- I guess you didn't know. - Sir.
So, No Man Team.
- Are you switching members? - No.
(The No Team is not switching their members.)
Give us one person.
- Who? - I'm a Yes Man,
but I'm going to avoid the piggy back ride.
Can't we find the No Man in the next match?
(Sung Kyun or Jong Kook)
(Which one of them is the No Man?)
(Find the No Man.)
(Jong Kook is the strongest candidate.)
- Am I heavy? - It's okay.
- I'll hold you close. - Oh, dear.
(If the feet of the person on the back touches the ground,)
(they get to draw a dot.)
(His feet touches the ground.)
My feet touched the ground.
(Kwang Soo's legs are too long.)
Wait, you only took five steps.
- No! - You took five steps.
(He draws five dots.)
- We're almost there. - It's here, right?
Hold on. In 1, 2, 3.
(Here we go.)
We're here.
(A Ra brings Je Hoon across the finish line.)
You did well.
(I did it.)
(Jae Seok takes Sung Kyun for a piggy back ride.)
(He looks like a son carrying his father.)
I passed.
(All five of them cleared the mission.)
This is the day.
(They'll make their final choice.)
This is the final moment.
- There's 10 of you, right? - Yes.
If the majority doesn't guess the right No Man,
- Yes Men will be punished. - everyone except the No Man...
will be mud-bombed.
But if the majority guesses the right No Man,
then only the No Man will be mud-bombed.
The No Man won't write their own name then, right?
- That's right. - Yes.
(Sung Kyun and Jong Kook are the likely candidates.)
- Right, Sung Kyun? - Yes.
Are you going to write your name?
I'm going to write Jong Kook's name.
(Blinking)
(Staring)
It's you, Sung Kyun.
(Sung Kyun is surprised while Jong Kook remains calm.)
- They'll pick each other. - He's acting.
Shouldn't we ask them to say a few words?
Let's hear their closing arguments.
- Let me make my closing argument. - Good.
If I was the No Man,
I would have said it wasn't me.
But since I'm not the No Man, I'm saying I'm not.
- I follow what you are saying. - Can I have a pen?
I understand what you are saying but your face...
- says otherwise. - I'm not convinced with that face.
I'll bet...
- my... - Don't bet on your family.
- We got in enough trouble for that. - Have you?
That's how certain I am.
You humiliated me and invaded my private space.
It's your turn.
- Me? - Yes.
I'm sure you already know, but it's not me.
- Why isn't it you? - Because it's not me.
Goodness.
- It's not me. - Okay, that's enough.
I'll bet on my right arm,
that humiliated Jae Seok and his bottom, that it isn't me.
(Even after hearing the closing arguments,)
(it's still difficult to predict the No Man's identity.)
- Make the right choice. - We made up our mind.
Have you made up your mind?
Then, we'll have each of you go in the booth...
and cast your vote. Flash your paper to the camera.
(If they make the wrong choice, they'll be mud-bombed.)
(Who's the No Man between these two?)
(Kwang Soo is the first to vote. Who will he choose?)
(He chooses Jong Kook.)
Whenever he takes on these roles,
he says things like, "It's not me."
- Because it's not me. - Gosh.
- It's not me. - That's enough.
He always gets these roles.
So I'll pick him.
(Je Hoon also chooses Jong Kook.)
I had a hunch from the beginning.
I had a feeling it was Sung Kyun near the end.
In the closing arguments,
I was convinced that Sung Kyun is the No Man.
So I chose Sung Kyun.
(A Ra chooses Sung Kyun.)
(Jong Kook and Sung Kyun each earned 2 votes so far.)
(Sung Kyun stares at A Ra.)
- Why are you looking at me? - You didn't pick me, did you?
- Sorry? - I'm not the No Man.
I am warning you. I am not the No Man.
I'm really not.
I hope you didn't make the wrong choice.
- He's so sincere. - Why didn't you say that before?
I told you that I wasn't the No Man.
- What? - I made up my mind.
Sung Kyun, you're amazing.
(He laughs in disbelief.)
- Sung Kyun is... - Gosh.
- Who is the No Man then? - Goodness.
(They both deny that they're the No Man.)
- We'll see. - Gosh.
- I am so confused now. - He's driving me crazy.
(They still don't have a clue.)
I knew it was Sung Kyun from the beginning.
They really confused me towards the end.
(The remaining members cast their votes.)
(Sung Kyun and Jong Kook also cast their votes.)
(The voting is complete.)
- I'll announce the results now. - Please.
(I really don't want to be mud-bombed.)
Sung Kyun got six votes.
(Sung Kyun received 6 votes.)
(Yelling)
And Jong Kook got four votes.
- Really? - Goodness!
(Sung Kyung received more than half of the votes.)
I told you so many times that I am not the No Man!
Are you really not the No Man?
(I can't believe this.)
- Gosh. - All right!
He's still pretending he's not the No Man.
- I'm really not. - If Sung Kyun is the No Man...
- Is it Jong Kook? - It's Jong Kook.
If Sung Kyun is the No Man, he will receive the penalty alone.
- Did you vote for Jong Kook? - If Sung Kyun is not the No Man,
everyone except Jong Kook will receive the penalty.
(Who will be the ones to get mud-bombed?)
(It's time to find out who the No Man is.)
- We're all going to get mud-bombed. - No way.
- One. - I am sorry, Sung Kyun!
Please!
(I'm so sorry.)
Two.
(Please...)
Three!
(Who will get the mud bomb?)
(Wow!)
(That's unbelievable.)
(The mud pours endlessly.)
(Everyone except Jong Kook receives the penalty.)
(The No Man is Jong Kook!)
(I told you that it wasn't me.)
It's pouring down.
(Where have all the pretty and handsome people gone?)
- Gosh. - I can't believe this.
- You fools! - How could you not notice?
(They're all filthy.)
- Towards the end... - No.
- I changed my mind at the end. - Why did you stammer?
- Why didn't you listen to me? - You weren't convincing.
- You should've been more clear. - This is ridiculous.
- You guys... - Why weren't you more clear?
Jong Kook said...
It was hard for me to keep a straight face.
Towards the end, Jong Kook...
looked at Sung Kyun in disbelief. That's when I fell for it.
Me too. That's why I chose Sung Kyun.
Sung Kyun, you're amazing.
(I can't believe you, Jong Kook.)
(Jong Kook was able to deceive everyone.)
The No Man is Jong Kook.
(Jong Kook is the No Man.)
It was really hard for me to deceive all of you.
- It was a hard role to play. - I can't believe this.
- It wasn't easy. - I thought it was him.
I was going to write Jong Kook's name.
You guys kept convincing me that it wasn't him.
- I was fooled at the last minute. - Me too.
I voted for Sung Kyun because his closing argument was weak.
It was my first time to appear on Running Man.
This is payback.
(This is payback.)
(He's angry.)
- Jong Kook is really angry. - You're in trouble now.
- He's really mad. - Are you okay?
If I deserved this, I'd have nothing to say.
Why did you do that?
- I can't understand him. - Why did you do this to me?
I've had my fair share of being on variety shows,
but I don't get why Kwang Soo just did what he did.
Look at me. What is this?
What is this?
(You shouldn't have done that, Kwang Soo.)
What was that for?
It was fun though.
I'm getting angry.
(Thank You, A Ra, Je Hoon and Sung Kyun for joining us.)
(The Battle for the Centre has begun.)
(7 guests join the show to support the members.)
What happened?
(In Young, Stephanie, Jin Young, Hyeon Gyeong, Zico, Su Jin, Bo Ah)
Standby.
Don't even think about being in the centre.
What are you doing?
Are you going to appear on television by yourself?
(The one who sits at the centre shall gain everything.)
Do you want to be the king?
(It's a fierce competition.)
- Ouch, that hurt. - I need to be in the spotlight.
(They fight for screen time.)
It'd be a good idea to change it.
(Who will win the Battle for the Centre?)
(Next Week's Special is Battle for the Centre.)