(On a fine day in autumn,)
(five items have been delivered to Running Man.)
(What would the items be?)
What's all this?
Coward, kid,
reggae, cooking...
and wit.
It all seems relevant to me, right?
Did you have to use that picture? Goodness.
(He's very muscular.)
The five items in front of you...
are the most popular search words about each of you.
Unlucky, grasshopper, cardboard,
James Bond and skinny jeans.
You mean these are the most popular search words about me?
Are we starting a mission already?
"Hot Race".
"For your individual mission, please make the most popular video."
"A three-minute video you made...
will be opened to the public on the Internet."
"Members will be ranked according to the number of views of each video."
"The results will have a major impact on the next race."
You mean I need to make a three-minute video?
Please choose a keyword that you'd like.
Well, I think...
it's most likely that Jae Seok will win this mission.
Let's be realistic.
What am I supposed to do?
Goodness.
I think I have nothing to do with this one.
It's my face. That one's out.
There's no reason for me to choose that one.
I'm sure if I choose that one,
it'll make me do something like bungee jump...
Goodness. What's this? Soo Ae?
I'll need to cast her first if I am to choose that word.
- That's too much. - But we found that in the big data.
Did her name really come up in the big data?
Oh, well. Goodness.
I'll choose this one since I don't know what to expect.
- You mean the big nose? - Yes, I choose the big nose.
Since people call me dazed Ji Hyo,
I'll choose dazed Ji Hyo.
I'll choose 1 between these 2.
I'll choose this since it's been a while.
Should I shoot the members with this water gun?
(Members selected their keywords.)
We'll give you a mission regarding Trainer Kook.
Please make "Kook's 3-minute Workout" video.
Korea's favourite weakling will also feature in your show.
Who would this Korea's favourite weakling be?
Will Yoon Seok be on the show?
(If it's Korea's favourite weakling, will he be Yoon Seok?)
(Groaning)
(Shaking)
Is this 30kg?
(Who is this frail figure waiting for Jong Kook?)
Cinderella's nose?
"Find the Cinderella who only left behind the trace of a nose."
"The mould of Cinderella's nose and 'nose brothers' are given as hints."
So this must be similar to finding Cinderella's crystal shoe.
I need to find a nose instead of a crystal shoe, right?
- Is this the nose? - Yes.
(Who are you?)
Cinderella has such a high nose bridge.
Am I supposed to find whose nose this is?
Who are you? Whose nose is this?
I'm coming for you. Wait for me.
(Cinderella, I'm coming to find your nose.)
"Finding Ms Right."
"Go find a female celebrity who said Kwang Soo is her ideal type."
"Go on a date with her."
"It's a success if it turns out that Kwang Soo is really the ideal type."
Am I going on a date?
"Make a one-minute theme song for Running Man."
"But in the song, each member's voice...
must be included more than once."
(Laughing)
(Is this really my mission?)
"Compete with Crush who won the Space Out Contest."
"And find out who is the best at spacing out in Korea."
This is the mission for...
- James Bond. - What is it?
(What would Jae Seok's mission be?)
(Return of James Bond, Scene-stealer)
What? You mean I'm Scene-stealer?
Now, you've become Scene-stealer.
(Are you talking about something like a prominent supporting role?)
"You can steal 10 percent of others' views."
You mean I can steal their views?
I can steal the views from that specific member?
Really?
"But once they finish their mission, your identity will be revealed."
"If they eliminate you, you'll lose 50 percent..."
This is ridiculous!
You'll lose 50 percent of your views.
By all ways and means...
Ways and means are not the issue. There must be members...
who already noticed the Scene-stealer mission.
I'll give you a GPS.
You'll find out where they are.
What should I tell them about my mission?
(I should never get caught.)
(And from now on...)
What's this?
"Beware of Scene-stealer."
Scene-stealer?
Then there must be something.
Will someone show up when we film the video?
Let's start. So I need to make a three-minute video, right?
(Which member will have the highest views?)
Oh, dear. My goodness.
Have you heard of the Space Out Contest?
I don't know. Aren't you dazed Ji Hyo, by the way?
(Yes, I am.)
There's a contest called, the Space Out Contest.
There's a person...
who won first place...
and I need to compete against him.
Look at him.
Look at him. How can I possibly win against him?
There's a person I'd like to meet personally.
Can I make this an excuse for meeting the person?
- So this mission will be an excuse? - Yes, that's what I'll do.
The person I really hope to meet is...
There's a greater possibility that it won't happen.
Jeon Do Yeon.
(Jeon Do Yeon)
I wish I could meet her.
It'd be amazing if I ever get to meet her.
I'm sure my video would have the highest views.
What should I do when I go on a date?
(It's an unexpected date.)
I'm a person who loves to surprise a woman.
You should've let me know in advance to prepare for an event.
(I should've at least bought some candles.)
Who said I'm her ideal type?
(He searches celebrities who said he is their ideal type.)
Here's the title of an article.
"Beauties Like Kwang Soo."
(Lee Sun Bin and Kang Seung Hyun, Beauties Like Kwang Soo.)
Actress Moon Geun Young.
"Members of WJSN also picked Kwang Soo as their ideal man."
Even Kang Seung Hyun said, I'm her ideal type.
Seung Hyun picked me.
U Ie,
She wouldn't like me now.
(U Ie and Lee Sang Yun are in love.)
I get upset when they take advantage of me like this.
If you search, "Kwang Soo is my ideal type",
you get 23 pages of articles.
Song Ji Eun, a member of Secret,
"I think Kwang Soo is amazing."
It says, "Lately, I like Kwang Soo."
But this article was written in 2014.
It's been quite a while.
Did Jeong Eun Ji say that I'm her ideal type?
(Jung Eun Ji Picked Kwang Soo as Her Ideal Type. Why on Earth?)
(Kwang Soo is calling Jung Eun Ji.)
- Hello? - Eun Ji.
Why did you call me all of a sudden?
I'm filming Running Man right now.
- Okay. - I've been searching some articles.
- Yes.
I found that you picked me as your ideal type.
Why on earth did I do that?
(Why on earth did I do that?)
You can't do this to me right now.
I need to find a person who picked me as her ideal type.
You once picked me as your ideal type.
Well, yes.
What was the reason?
- When was it? - Why did I say that?
- Do you remember when? - No, I don't.
Then get lost.
(Kwang Soo is acting like bad guy.)
- Eun Ji. - That was annoying.
I'm sorry.
I need to find a person who thinks I'm her type of man.
- Okay. Good luck. - Thank you. I'll call you later.
- All right. Bye. - Bye.
Okay. She's off the list now.
(Eun Ji is off the list.)
(Kwang Soo calls the next person on the list right away.)
I haven't called her for a long time.
- Hello? - Hi, Geun Young.
(He's talking to the actress, Moon Geun Young.)
- Who is it? - Geun Young.
- Yes? - Hello.
Hello.
Well, it is embarrassing to say this myself,
but do you remember saying that I'm your ideal type of man?
No, I didn't mean it that way.
One's ideal type always changes, doesn't it?
You means I'm not your type any more?
I'm sorry, Geun Young.
(I'm not your type of man any more?)
I'm so sorry to bother you.
- That's okay. - Okay.
I'm just going to date anyone.
What do you mean?
I told you that I'm recording Running Man right now.
Are you?
What do you mean you want to date anyone?
I want more dating experience.
(Well...)
- Okay. Geun Young. - Yes?
Are you drunk?
- What are you talking about? - I'm really flustered right now.
- Are you? Okay. I see. - Yes.
- All right. I will call you later. - Okay. Bye.
(He quickly hangs up.)
Okay. Geun Young seems a bit drunk right now.
She says that someone's type changes over time.
("One's ideal type changes.")
She made her point.
(Who is the next candidate?)
- Hello? - Hello?
- Seung Hyun. - Yes?
Well...
(He's talking to the model, Kang Seung Hyun.)
You... Well, Seung Hyun.
Why did you call me?
What do you mean, "Why did you call me?"
I found out that you appointed me as your ideal type of man before.
No. I didn't mean it that way.
It came up during a small talk and we were talking about petty things.
It might be petty, but it could be important.
Where did you read the article? That is...
I searched for it myself.
That's not important. This is the important bit.
You appointed me as your ideal type, didn't you?
- I did. - I'll give you a chance to date me.
- You're giving me a chance? - Why are you laughing out loud?
I'm actually nervous. Okay.
- Such an honour this is. - Hey, Seung Hyun.
Where are you right now?
I'm walking my dog in front of my house.
- Oh, are you? - Yes.
- I'll see you there then. - Okay.
(Kwang Soo will go on a date with Seung Hyun.)
I haven't dated anyone for quite a long time.
(Will she still consider Kwang Soo as her ideal type?)
It's a lovely day for a date.
I could really get into it.
This must be the place.
Hey, Seung Hyun.
(Laughing)
(They are embarrassed to see each other.)
Hey, Seung Hyun.
(She's Korea's famous supermodel, Kang Seung Hyun.)
Long time no see.
Did you put on makeup?
Yes, I did.
It's a date. I haven't been on a date for ages.
- What? Yes, we have a mission. - What's the mission?
What's wrong?
(Barking)
- What's the matter? - I don't know. He's acting strange.
(Stay away from Seung Hyun!)
Oh, my.
It's Haha.
- Yes, Haha. - Hey, Kwang Soo.
What's your mission? Do you have to find your first love?
No, I need to find someone who likes me...
and said that I'm her type.
- I need to cook. I'm on my way. - I see.
Are you on your way to see who appointed you as her type, too?
No way. I'm married with a kid.
(He's married.)
I'm sorry.
(Don't worry. I met my woman a long time ago.)
- Anyway, have fun. - Okay, Haha.
- I'll call you later. - Sure.
I need to search the Internet.
(Haha has to cook "Haha's Dish" with food only from convenience store.)
I've found them already.
"120 convenience store dishes".
What is "Mark's Dish"?
"For your information, the reason why..."
"it's called Mark's Dish is because Mark's fan invented the menu."
It's really popular right now.
(Okay, Mark. I choose you!)
We need to...
cook a proper dish, but we also need to add...
something more stimulating to it.
(It must be hot, no matter what.)
We're at JYP Entertainment agency.
We need Mark for "Mark's Dish".
Let's go. Just push ahead.
Mark?
Mark? I knew I could count on you.
You're all set.
- Hello. - Hi, Mark.
(Mark from Got7)
Yes. We're all set.
To be honest, I was a bit worried.
Mark, here's your microphone.
(Why is Haha holding Mark's microphone?)
I'll set it for you.
It's all being recorded, right?
Stay focused. Don't miss anything. Not even the shortest moment.
Come on, I'll do it for you.
(Mark,)
(I need your help.)
Come on, I'll do it for you.
(Ta-da)
Why? What's wrong?
(Is Mark's sexy body the stimulant of the show?)
No. I'll do it for you.
- There you go, Mark. - I can do it myself.
No, don't put it that way.
(Haha lifts up Mark's shirt.)
(Come on, Mark. I really want to win this game.)
- What are you doing? - I'm sorry.
How should we do this? Where are your group members?
- They are off on their holidays. - How about you?
- I couldn't go home. - Why not?
My home is in Los Angeles. It's too far.
All the other members went home for Chuseok,
- and you're staying here? - Yes.
(How are you, Mum?)
(You must be having a hard time. I know what you are going through.)
- Are you okay? - Yes, I am. Please stop.
(Haha successfully lifts Mark's shirt for the second time.)
(We have to work on this anyway, so let's do our best and win together.)
All right. I'll be honest with you.
I thought it wouldn't be really fun if we just cook.
That's why I was showing some skin.
- Is that your idea? - Yes.
So...
(Why didn't you tell me earlier?)
(I'll do my best to secure the first place.)
Yes. That's the spirit.
What about Mark and I go to sauna and eat half-naked?
- We can just cook half-naked. - Really?
Can you do that for me? He's really cool.
He's so open-minded.
They are already set out.
What should we do with these?
Well, Park Jin Young is here.
(Park Jin Young?)
- Is Park Jin Young here? - Yes.
(Park Jin Young? You mean JYP?)
- Is Jin Young here? - Yes.
(Of course, not.)
That was a good one. Nice to see you.
- Hello. Nice to meet you. - Come this way.
We have Junior JYP, too.
We're going to cook "Haha's Dish".
- Are you a good cook? - Me?
- I'm good at cutting things. - Really?
- Yes, I am. - Really?
All right. First,
take off your top.
(Take off your top.)
(Do you want us to take off our clothes?)
- We're back. - Okay.
Awesome! You look great.
This is just amazing.
You need to take off your shirt, too.
Okay, I will. Really.
(Do you really want me to take off my shirt, too?)
(Seriously?)
You look nice.
Show people how determined you are.
Now, we are a team.
I'm just doing it because you want me to,
but this won't affect the outcome at all.
(Their indecent cooking show begins now.)
Let's cook curry udon first.
Wow. We have a lot of desserts.
I will boil this because we need a bit of curry sauce for those.
- Got it. - Okay.
(Mix some instance curry sauce with water and boil.)
Please open up the udon.
When you serve those, don't serve them like any other.
- Do you mean this? - Show off your body when you serve.
(Haha's trying to show off his physical beauty.)
(We need you to watch this.)
That's great.
Amazing.
("Click Bait")
That's great.
(Thank you in advance for your views.)
We have a great teamwork.
(Add the instant udon sauce and an egg...)
(and boil them together with the curry sauce.)
This will taste great. I'm sure of it.
(Throw the sauce over the cooked noodles.)
(That looks quite nice.)
You're a good cook.
- We're making it just like pizza. - Yes, that's right.
Based on the idea,
I'll put some cheese on it.
Rip crab sticks in smaller pieces. Wash your hands before this.
Then I will throw in some salad, which are really healthy...
and mix them together.
(Rip crab meats in smaller pieces and mix with salad.)
This looks quite delicious.
(Put the mixed salad on a slice of puffed rice.)
To finish off with a bit of flavour,
put some sliced dried laver on it.
- It's delicious. - One dish is ready.
Put it over there nicely.
Put it on that large dish.
That's it. You're doing great.
(They know what to do to get more nunber of views.)
That's it. You're doing great. Show your physical beauty.
(Haha is definitely getting more views on his video with them.)
Show it more. Great.
(This is really embarrassing.)
Thank you. Thank you so much.
Where are you, Jae Seok?
What are you up to, Seok Jin?
I need to ask you something.
What is it?
Didn't you go to school with Jeon Do Yeon?
Yes, that's right.
Can you call her that casually?
Of course.
This is the reason why I called you.
I want to meet with her with my mission as an excuse.
We used to be close.
Used to? That's past tense.
Do you have her number?
I used to know, but now I don't.
The last time I saw her was at a car wash.
When was that?
That was in 1997.
(I saw Do Yeon in 1997.)
(Reply 1997)
I'm hanging up.
- What? - You're no help at all.
- What are you talking about? - That was 20 years ago.
Do you know how glad she was when we met back then?
That was 20 years ago at a car wash.
- Yes, it was. - Are you kidding me?
You're useless.
(Seok Jin will have to come up with a different plan.)
(How is Ji Hyo preparing for the Space Out Contest?)
(She arrived at Crush's studio.)
Oh, my.
Hello.
Is this your studio?
(He's dazed already.)
(He's the hottest musician at the moment. It's Crush.)
(He is the winner of the Space Out Contest.)
The weather is perfect to space out.
- Take this first. - Okay.
- Read it out loud. - I accept your challenge.
"Crush, I challenge you."
"Let's see who's the best at spacing out."
This is nuts.
(I accept your challenge, dazed Ji Hyo.)
This is nonsense.
What is this trophy? Is this it?
(She found the trophy he received for winning the Space Out Contest.)
2016 Han River Space Out Contest.
May 21.
He won this.
This is who he is.
Look at this.
Look at this trophy.
You're putting me up against someone like this?
This is so funny.
I watched some episodes of Running Man.
I think you could be a match for me.
I'm not like that.
Am I the only one who thinks that?
You got me all wrong.
Anyway, let's head out. The weather's nice out.
Let's take a walk outside.
(Will she be able to get the most views and win?)
How do we get more views?
(Gary gathers everyone he knows to help him out.)
I'm sorry, Se Yun.
This is Panda.
(Professional musicians team up to create a minute-long theme song.)
This is my long-time friend from elementary school.
Nice to meet you.
They've worked with many Korean artists.
Wait a minute.
I have to put other members' voices in there.
- The members of Running Man? - They all have to go in the song.
(They're having conversations with music terminology.)
- That's a good idea. - It could work.
Maybe I'll get them to sing along and record it all together.
(He's calling Ji Hyo to record her voice.)
She's probably spacing out right now.
She could already be doing it.
(He has another phone ready for recording.)
Hey.
- Ji Hyo? - Hi.
- Where are you? - I'm with Crush.
- You are? - Yes.
Where did you say you were going? Hannam-dong?
No, we're going to Jamwon, near Banpo-dong.
- Oh, Han River? - Yes.
Are you here right now?
I thought I might meet you there.
Sure, come over.
Hey, Gary.
- Hey, Crush. - Long time no see.
- How have you been? - Good, thanks.
Be good to Ji Hyo, Crush.
Of course, she's really pretty.
Don't seduce her.
See you there, Crush.
- Okay. - Goodbye.
- I'll hang up now. - Okay.
I could even get Crush's voice in there.
(He's going over the conversation.)
Ji Hyo sounds so happy.
(She does sound really excited.)
She does. Is that because of Crush?
- I'm with Crush. - You are?
She laughs when she says his name.
Are you jealous?
Are you kidding me?
(Is this what jealousy feels like?)
Did you write the lyrics yet?
- Be quiet. - Okay.
I have to go there quickly.
I kidnapped Crush from his studio.
He's very confused right now.
(Running Man's Space Out Contest is about to begin.)
He needs to be looked after.
We even have a judge today.
(The founder of the Space Out Contest and judge, Woops Yang)
We will now begin Running Man's Space Out Contest.
(It's Ji Hyo against Crush.)
(The person to keep the steadiest heart rate will become the winner.)
What I do is...
I sing the lyrics of my songs in my head.
So I can't fall asleep, right?
I have to stay calm and space out, right?
(It won't be as easy as you think, Ji Hyo.)
(Space Out Contest starts now.)
(They're spacing out.)
(The video is not paused.)
(This video is also not paused.)
(How can they be this calm?)
(Running Man is very strange today.)
(We should call the show Sitting Man.)
(What's this?)
(These are embarrassing pictures of them.)
(He's completely ignoring it.)
(They're trying to make their heart rates go higher.)
(She looks peaceful so far.)
(He glances at the picture.)
(This looks dangerous.)
(What do they have this time?)
(These are even more embarrassing pictures.)
(You won't hold it in this time.)
(She can't hold it in.)
(This won't be easy for you, either.)
(He's about to burst into laughter.)
(Somebody help me.)
(They're measuring their heart rates after the interruption.)
(The results are taken right back to the judge.)
(Gary shows up.)
Are you doing it right now?
You don't stand a chance against Crush.
Are you not allowed to speak?
You can't talk?
I need them to talk.
(What is it? Come here.)
I need to make a theme song.
Just shout, "Run".
(This is ridiculous.)
Don't laugh, Ji Hyo.
(This guy is in another world.)
I haven't seen Crush since last year and he's not even saying hi to me.
(He's keeping his glance forward.)
Just give me a shout.
(Gary tries to record Ji Hyo's voice.)
Say that again?
(She barely makes a sound.)
I just need you to say one word!
(It's not like I don't want to.)
(She blows into the microphone.)
(It doesn't look like he will be getting anything good out of her.)
You said all I needed was her voice.
This is what your voice sounds like.
(It's the sound she made when she blew into the microphone.)
Do you hear that? I can't use this. Just say run.
Run.
That's it.
Hey, Crush.
Say what you want to say.
Go away.
(It was short but strong.)
Do you think I can record a song with this?
Go away.
(I must not laugh.)
At least I got what I came for.
Thank you, everyone.
Don't stay in the sun for too long. Good luck.
(Bye, Gary.)
This is hard.
(Ji Hyo goes back to spacing out.)
I feel drained already.
I need the voices of Kwang Soo, Jong Kook and Seok Jin.
I only got one syllable out of them and I'm already tired.
(Kwang Soo receives a call while he's on a date.)
It's Gary.
- Hello, Gary? - Hey, Kwang Soo.
- What's up? - Can you say run?
- Run? - Yes.
Give me a shout.
Run!
Run.
(The sound of Seok Jin's run sucks the energy out of you.)
What?
(Seok Jin has more to offer.)
- Was that good? - Goodness.
Shall we record "Left ear, right ear, Seok Jin is out"?
(He gets an idea from Seok Jin.)
Please listen to the song with headphones on.
Left ear, right ear
(Did he just create a new theme song?)
(They start to make a song with voice recordings.)
Shall we start with something like that?
- Play it. - Did you make...
a sample already?
(He adds a beat to the members' voice recordings.)
(It sounds so good.)
(What's wrong with the sound?)
It sounds like...
a video game.
(It's a sound you often heard at the arcade.)
(The sound makes you want to insert coins.)
(The hottest one-minute theme song is coming soon.)
What's your ideal type of men?
Lee Kwang Soo.
Why is that?
I like...
(I like...)
(Tell me why I'm your ideal type.)
I like people who are big.
You might as well like Seo Jang Hoon.
Isn't that what you mean?
We have to go on a date. What kind of date do you usually like?
Since I have a dog,
I enjoy walking the dog together and chatting.
I enjoy having conversations like this.
It's a Hollywood-style date.
A date while walking the dog.
(I know what that feels like.)
(He attracts her by going on a Hollywood-style date with her.)
(He prepares a romantic date.)
(The dog barks aggressively.)
I have an incoming call.
(The reality is that the dog barks randomly.)
Ji Hyo is calling.
Hello, Ji Hyo.
- Where are you? - Right now, I am...
What kind of tone is that?
Hello, Jae Seok.
Jae Seok.
For today's date, so many people...
- Hello. - are helping me out.
- Ji Hyo. - Yes?
- I'm on a date now. I'll call back. - Long time no see.
He said he's looking for people whose ideal type of men is him.
Seung Hyun said I'm her ideal type.
- Is that why you met him now? - Yes.
- We'll go on a date. - I know this is just a mission.
- However, Kwang Soo, - Yes.
pardon me for saying this, but what a dirty trick.
A dirty trick?
- It is. - We're just starting our date.
- What's wrong with you? - I'm not sure when she said it,
but he came to her to ask if she likes him.
I don't remember, but I was shocked that he knew about it.
- What do you mean? - Don't you remember, Seung Hyun?
- No. - You should be more aware.
Don't say that to a world-class model.
I looked it up and found out I actually said it.
When did you say it?
It's been a few years ago at least.
- Kwang Soo, what is that? - Come on.
Come on, Jae Seok.
(He backs away from Kwang Soo.)
Gosh, that's such a dirty little trick.
- I'm still your ideal type. - Right.
- She says it's still the case. - Right.
Why did you say that back then?
At that time,
Jang Ki Ha asked me if I enjoyed being on Running Man.
Leave it, I'll do it for her.
Are you okay?
(He's good at interrupting. What's going on here?)
(Is Jae Seok Scene-stealer I should be cautious of?)
- You should show your face. - He asked if I enjoyed the show...
- and which member is my ideal type. - I see.
Was it among Running Man members?
See? This is what was missing.
- Was it among Running Man members? - Seung Hyun's answer...
wasn't her ideal type in the entertainment industry.
- Was it me out of six people? - This was missing.
Seung Hyun.
Who's your ideal type in the entertainment industry?
Kwang Soo.
- Really? - Be quiet.
You lost your chance.
Things seem quite uncomfortable between you two.
What would you have done if I weren't here?
(If you weren't here, we would be enjoying our date.)
I definitely have a potential.
- Have you eaten? - No.
Let's go eat.
What are you doing right now?
- Are you trying to ruin my date? - Let's go eat.
You haven't eaten, right?
There's a cafe nearby.
Shall we go there?
(He's very suspicious.)
Two iced coffee, please.
(Their Hollywood-style date starts at a cafe.)
I enjoy things like this for a date...
instead of doing something special.
I like doing things that are ordinary.
Since with your last girlfriend,
you haven't been on a cafe date in a while, have you?
- It's been a while. - Right?
(The three are slowly getting to know each other.)
(Don't worry about me.)
He's definitely Scene-stealer. He's always in my sight.
- Jae Seok, look over there instead. - I didn't do anything.
- Go and play with the dog. - He's always around us.
Gosh.
- I'll leave after I get my drink. - She keeps looking at you.
I'll leave after I get my drink.
(He's a professional interrupter.)
Let's not ask about each other's past.
It's because he wants a casual relationship.
What do you want?
- Do you want my name tag? Take it. - No.
I would have done that already.
- Goodness. - Are you on some kind of mission?
No, I'm not.
I'm leaving after I get my drink.
I feel like a third wheel at Kwang Soo and Jae Seok's date.
- I'm not sure how to act. - Okay.
Sit on this seat, Seung Hyun.
Sit on this seat.
- That's what it feels like. - You're so sensitive.
All right, let me get my toast.
Isn't it ready yet? Here it is.
(What is he really up to?)
How do I take it?
(What does he mean by that?)
- If you bring up the past... - Are we...
on a date or not?
Sir.
- Stop moving around. - Pardon me.
I really have to leave for my mission now.
I was very happy and grateful...
- that you came to see me. - Me, too.
It wasn't about having fun. I took it seriously.
- I took it seriously and... - Continue your conversation.
Kwang Soo, can you put your foot here?
(He asks for Kwang Soo's foot.)
Is he mentally sick?
Why are you asking for my foot when I'm on a date?
I need to make a tracing of everyone's feet.
- You can do it for me, right? - Sure.
Come on, please let me do it.
- It can be embarrassing. - Gosh.
I just need your foot.
Is it so difficult to put your foot on this?
- Come on. - Gosh.
I also need to get tracings of other members' feet.
Wait a minute.
- Is this what I think it is? - What?
Is this your mission?
I have to get tracings of six members' feet...
to identify as Scene-stealer.
I have to put this up on a bulletin board at the end.
- Just let me do it. - We're competing after all.
Just let me do it.
- Will you leave after this? - Yes.
Gosh, why is this happening?
(She sees Kwang Soo's foot on their first date.)
Here you go.
Sign your name right here.
(You might as well sign your name.)
- Gosh. - The toast is ready.
(Didn't Jae Seok say he'll leave when the food is served?)
That looks delicious.
That looks amazing.
It looks very delicious.
(He runs away quickly with a shoe in his hand.)
What's going on?
He ran away.
What?
(My shoe)
- He ran away. - Gosh.
He's a thief.
He's a thief. Catch him.
He's a real thief.
(A real scene-stealer appears.)
Catch him.
He's a real thief.
(It's a real thief.)
(Jae Seok runs without looking back.)
(Did he follow me all day just to get my shoe?)
(Suddenly, he's left without his shoe.)
Goodness.
That was amazing.
When did he steal the shoe?
I'm definitely the third wheel on their date.
(It's a date between two strange men.)
This isn't a date.
I feel like he dumped me on our first date.
Gosh.
That was close.
(Why did Jae Seok steal Kwang Soo's shoe?)
He has such large feet.
I have to decide between the two.
How about this?
"James Bond mission is finding as many members as possible..."
"and steal a shoe from them no matter what."
Stealer of shoes.
(He's assigned as a stealer of shoes.)
(Who knew they meant shoes?)
It's delicious.
(What does Scene-stealer gain when he steals a shoe?)
Gosh, Jae Seok.
Gosh.
(They say your shoes can be easily stolen in Seoul.)
What is this?
What just happened?
What's this?
Urgent news.
"You lost a shoe to Scene-stealer and 10 percent of your views."
"When the mission's over, you get a hint to recover your views."
(If you lose a shoe, Scene-stealer takes 10 percent of the views.)
He's Scene-stealer.
Do I get a chance to recover it?
When the mission is over.
(He still has the other shoe.)
I need to meet other people.
I'm sorry, Seung Hyun.
I'm not someone without manners.
You didn't find your shoe?
He stole it and ran away.
That was his mission. What do I do?
(It may be rude to continue their date like this.)
What's your shoe size?
(By the way, what's your shoe size?)
Do you have money?
I need money to buy shoes.
Do you know anyone whose ideal type is me?
I'm sorry.
I think our date is a flop.
I'm sorry, Seung Hyun, but I'm going to eat.
(He eats a lot at the end of their horrible date.)
You must fill your stomach for the next date.
(What is on Seung Hyun's mind?)
(Is Kwang Soo still her ideal type?)
(They'll use lie detector to find out what's on her mind.)
(Kwang Soo will ask her three questions.)
You can start now.
(If she says yes to all and it's true, Kwang Soo is her ideal type.)
I am willing...
to have another date...
- with Kwang Soo again. - Yes.
(Her answer is yes.)
I couldn't show you my real charms today.
(Let's see if she answered truth.)
I really...
(This sound means she lied.)
(But she looks fine.)
(Didn't she get the electric shock?)
I don't feel anything.
- Earlier, it worked. - It says you're lying.
(The detector says Seung Hyun is telling a lie.)
(Then, we'll regard it as the truth.)
Since she didn't feel anything.
You heard the sound.
Isn't she pretending?
- No, I'm not. - I don't think that's possible.
I found it hard to pretend.
(He tested the detector 30 minutes ago.)
- Are you the most handsome member? - Yes.
(He said yes.)
I'm serious. Who do you think is more handsome than me?
Seriously...
(He's shocked.)
You all heard the alarming sound...
as if a disaster occurred, right?
Next question, please.
(Did she really tell the truth or did she fake it?)
If you have to go to a desert island...
with one of Running Man members, will you choose Kwang Soo?
Yes.
(She's willing to go to a desert island with him.)
I'm sure she said the truth, since she said this earlier.
(He seems confident.)
(Let's see.)
(What?)
(Does it really not hurt?)
Her hand is trembling.
I really don't feel anything. Why are you so doubtful?
If I seriously ask you out...
Your question is so...
Will you say yes?
(He asks if she will go out with him.)
Yes.
This is the most important question.
(Is Kwang Soo really her ideal type or nothing more than a weirdo?)
What if it says... Gosh, it hurts.
Gosh, it hurts.
(What is that?)
(That was a pure lie.)
Are you playing with me?
I tried to help you.
I endured the pain twice.
(Now I am trying to hold back my anger.)
You don't have to say that.
Am I not your ideal type? Was I your ideal type in the past?
You used to be.
(I wish I could go back in time.)
(I thought Kwang Soo was my ideal type in the past.)
(It turned out that Kwang Soo is no longer Seung Hyun's ideal type.)
Haha is in Cheongdam-dong now.
Jong Kook is in Apgujeong-dong. He must be working out again.
Everyone, this is the gym I go to.
(He arrives at the gym to start working out.)
Who is it?
(He doesn't look familiar.)
(Who are you?)
Goodness.
(Who will be Jong Kook's partner today and exercise together?)
It's nice to see you!
(He is...)
(Sleepy of Untouchable.)
(He's a charismatic hip-hop singer with 8 years of experience.)
(He's Korea's famous weakling.)
Let's do it later.
I can't do this.
(This weakling joins Running Man!)
People think you're very weak.
Let's show them that you're not weak.
- Show them how strong you are. - I'm trying to bulk up these days.
(I'm actually working on it.)
(You must be joking.)
- Are you? - I gained 10kg.
Are you serious? Why are you still so skinny?
Why are you still so skinny?
(He daringly exposes his belly.)
What was that?
I want to be muscular. Next year,
I want to get married... No. I want to perform without a shirt on.
(What did you say?)
- That didn't come out right. - Get married?
I want to perform like that.
Right. When rappers perform without a shirt on,
it is so cool. You must try it, too.
I hope so.
Then, let's analyse your body composition first.
(This is essential to find appropriate exercise for him.)
It's coming out.
(Let's see how healthy Jong Kook is.)
I have 42.1kg of skeletal muscles.
I weigh 79.2kg and have 6.3kg of body fat.
You have about 6kg of fat?
- Right. - Then, do your muscles weigh 73kg?
(Do your muscles weigh 73kg?)
(He's not a crustacean.)
- I also have bones. - Oh, bones.
Of course, the rest aren't muscles.
(It's Sleepy's turn.)
Okay.
It's coming out.
You have 14.8kg of muscles...
and 16.6kg of body fat.
(His body fat weighs 16.6kg.)
How can you have this much fat? You look so skinny.
- I'm thin but obese. - Really?
People call me E.T.
(He's an E.T-like hip-hop singer.)
You have 10kg of fat more than me.
Your body fat weighs 10kg heavier than mine.
- I really want to work out. - Let's begin with the basics.
Let's do push-ups first.
- Relax your shoulders. - I'm good at this.
This is for warming up.
Do as many times as you can.
Wait, get up.
You must straighten your body.
You should straighten your body. Keep the posture.
Ready, go!
(Ready, go!)
- One. - It's too painful.
- It's too painful. - Already?
Where do you feel painful?
- Where? - My back.
Does your back hurt?
This is a chest exercise. Why does your back hurt?
Do it again. Go!
Good.
Two more. Go!
Great. Keep it up!
That's it. You did well.
(A deep sigh)
You already look tired. Lie down, then.
(He's totally exhausted.)
- Can I take a break? - You can't.
Start!
(It's time for bench press.)
Go!
It's a piece of cake.
(It's a piece of cake.)
(His arms are shaking.)
- Gosh. - One more.
(He's on vibration mode.)
(He screams.)
(He finishes his chest workout.)
Get up.
Get up at once.
(It's time for back exercises.)
Two!
- It's too heavy. - Good.
- Is it heavy? - Yes.
- Please lower the weight. - Lower the weight?
(His back exercise is over.)
That's it. Push it! Good.
- Two more to go. - I think it's too heavy for me.
No, it's not. Even women can bear this weight.
(I miss my mum.)
- Isn't it too harsh? - No.
You must enjoy it. It's so fun.
- It's so fun. - It is fun.
Picture how you'd look after working out.
- My name will be on top search. - That's right.
- I can't do it any more. - You must.
- Gosh. - Jong Kook, I really can't.
- Three more to go. - I'm serious.
One, two...
and three. Good job.
(He moans in pain.)
I helped a lot of celebrities with their work out.
I recently helped Park Bo Gum.
- He's a superstar. - I taught him how to work out.
I just taught you the way Bo Gum works out.
- Really? - Yes.
(He seems to come to his senses again.)
I taught Bo Gum the same exercises.
You're doing exactly what he did.
- Can I become Park Bo Gum, then? - Of course.
(I wish I can be like Park Bo Gum.)
Bo Gum works out the same way.
- Park Bo Gum! - Good.
- Park Bo Gum. - Park Bo Gum.
- Good. - I can't do it.
No way. Keep it up.
Great! Just one more set.
Let's do it for the last time. In 1, 2, 3.
Park Bo Gum!
Park Bo Gum.
(Running Man's Space Out Contest)
What is that?
(Scene-stealer Jae Seok arrives at Han River.)
What is Ji Hyo doing?
(He wants only one thing.)
Crush!
I see why you won the competition before.
(Jae Seok tries to distract Crush.)
My goodness.
He doesn't even move his eyes.
He's amazing.
(Where are my shoes?)
(Why is he here?)
(She stares at Jae Seok.)
(He's intimidated.)
Why do you move your body?
If you move your body, you'll lose the contest.
(Go away.)
If you speak, you'll lose.
(He tries to annoy Ji Hyo, saying she'll lose if she moves.)
Crush won the contest before.
What is that? What is he doing?
What is that for?
(It's a good chance for Jae Seok since they should stay calm.)
It's amazing.
What's her heart rate?
(He moves Ji Hyo's shoes.)
Did you say it's 14?
(This is very thrilling.)
How can you...
My goodness.
Crush doesn't even smile.
(He has nothing on his mind.)
(Ji Hyo is writing to Jae Seok to leave her alone and go.)
Okay.
(The longer he stays here, the more they'll find him suspicious.)
(Finally, he jumps into action.)
Goodbye, Crush.
(Ji Hyo looks back!)
(But she can't see the shoe from here.)
(Her shoe is gone.)
(Scene-stealer Jae Seok gets away with this.)
That was really easy.
It was a piece of cake this time.
(She is dazed.)
She doesn't even realise her shoe is gone.
I got it very easily.
Who comes next?
Jong Kook is near here,
but he is not easy to deal with.
Then I should call Min Hyo Rin's agent.
(The first one Seok Jin picked for Cinderella's nose is Min Hyo Rin?)
- Hello. - Hello. Mr Ko.
I'm Ji Seok Jin from Running Man.
Oh, hi. How are you?
I didn't make an appointment but I'd like to meet Hyo Rin now.
She is in Japan for shooting for a magazine.
- Is she in Japan? - Yes.
Oh, I see. Okay, then.
I'll try Gaeko then.
The number you have dialled is in roaming area...
- He is overseas now. - You'll be charged after the beep.
Next is Zico.
(You were my pick from start, Zico.)
- The number you have dialled... - It's not going through.
I'll meet somebody after all.
(Starting is important, but he's having a trouble from the start.)
Who was that? There was a celebrity van.
Why don't you check it out?
Shall I stop the van and check it out?
Would you get closer to the left side of the van?
Roll down the window please.
(He's looking for Cinderella's nose in the street.)
This is embarrassing.
Excuse me. Go a bit closer.
Hello, I'm Ji Seok Jin.
Is this a celebrity van?
- Whose van is it? - Who's in there?
I'm shooting Running Man. Whose van is it?
(I met you on Seongsu Bridge but who are you?)
It's Park Si Yeon's.
I'd like to meet Park Si Yeon! Is she in there?
Let me pull off the van.
Great. Thank you.
So we happened to meet Park Si Yeon like this.
I got a chance to meet Park Si Yeon in the street.
(He is so excited to see her.)
I can't believe I can meet her.
Is it really Park Si Yeon?
Hello.
Is this Park Si Yeon's van?
(She looks so surprised.)
- Oh, hello. - Hello.
Hello, Si Yeon. I'm sorry to stop you.
- I'm surprised. - Me too.
I was on the way to a salon.
You were.
- Sorry I suddenly stopped you. - That's okay. I'm nervous.
I'm nervous too, and I'm sorry for being rude.
I need to find someone who has a nose that matches this one.
May I check your nose?
- I'm sorry. - Okay.
- Let's check. - What if it matches?
It's like Cinderella's glass slippers,
but now we're looking for Cinderella who has a matching nose.
I'll put this on your nose and see if it fits you.
(He just bumped into Si Yeon.)
(Can she be Cinderella he was looking for?)
I think it fits you. Wait.
No, the shape of the lips is different.
(This is embarrassing.)
Sorry to make you have all the trouble.
- I apologise. - No problem.
- I'll invite you as a guest. - Okay. That sounds good.
- I really appreciate it. - Okay. Goodbye.
- Bye. - Thank you.
I really appreciate it.
I'm so grateful to Si Yeon.
I think we can see a lot of celebrities at salons.
Let's go to salons. Is it okay?
And our goal today is to catch all the celebrity vans.
Catch all the vans and let's go to salons.
I believe we can bump into the person with this nose.
Is this a celebrity van?
Who is it? Lim Ji Yeon?
- Hello, Seok Jin. - Hi.
Good to see you here.
My mission is to find the person that has this nose.
- May I try it on your nose? - Really?
- It's too big. - I think it's big.
It's big, isn't it? There is room inside.
- Don't press it too hard. - I didn't mean to.
It hurts.
I'm sorry.
- Thank you for the interview. - No problem.
- Goodbye. Thank you. - Thank you.
There are many celebrities in this neighbourhood.
The number looks like that of a rental car.
And the windows are tinted.
- Hello. - Would you like to get out?
Give me the nose.
Whose nose do you think it is?
- This one? - Wait.
- Is it yours? - No, it's not.
(Kim So Hee tries on the nose.)
No. This is too big for you.
Wait. Excuse me.
(He goes for the van behind.)
Seung Yeon of Kara?
May I go with you?
I'll get to meet Han Seung Yeon.
(He goes to a salon where Seung Yeon is.)
Seung Yeon. Where is she? Seung Yeon.
- Don't record this. - Please help me.
- It's okay. You're pretty enough. - It's been a while.
- This is incredible. - Let's see if it matches.
- Put it on your nose. - There is something in here.
No, it's clean.
(Seung Yeon is the fourth candidate.)
No, you're not the one. The lips are...
located very low.
- I think this belongs... - To a man?
Yes, I think so.
(Is this a nose of a man?)
I think Seok Jin is too excited now.
I think I need to let him calm down a little bit.
There he is.
(What kind of strategy should I use for Seok Jin?)
Who is it?
(He's still trying hard to check the vans.)
(Jae Seok is running.)
Who's in there?
- Excuse me? - April.
- April. It's a new girl group. - Yes.
Are they all in?
(While Seok Jin is distracted by the girl group,)
(Jae Seok is planning the operation.)
Please hold Seok Jin.
Why are you here?
- What were you doing? - What about you?
I'm looking for a matching nose. It's nonsense.
I'm looking for the person whose nose is matching with this one.
What is this?
The person... What are you doing?
(They hold him tight.)
What are you doing, Jae Seok?
(What do you think I'm doing?)
(I need your shoe.)
Hey, wait up.
(What a brat.)
What's wrong with him?
(Laughing)
(What a robber you are.)
(Jae Seok is fast.)
- Jae Seok. - Go, go. Just go.
(He slams the door.)
- Hey. - You can go.
How could you? Are you crazy?
Jae Seok. He must be crazy.
(Bye, Seok Jin.)
You can just leave.
Is he out of his mind?
Gosh.
(Why did you steal my shoe?)
I don't know what to say.
I'm at a loss for words.
He must be Scene-stealer.
He is Scene-stealer.
"He gets 10 percent of your final viewership."
(If he steals a shoe, he'll get 10 percent of the viewership.)
After the mission, you have a chance to get it back.
Let's go, anyway.
I need to borrow some slippers in the salon.
I can't walk around without a shoe.
(I'll take revenge on you for sure.)
(What's the main dish of Haha and Mark?)
What else do we have to do?
Now,
let's make the main dish of our own.
(What's the main dish of their own?)
Let's combine my recipe your recipe together.
Instead of the sausage, let's add a hamburger steak.
- A hamburger steak? - Yes, an instant hamburger steak.
Let's put it instead of sausage.
I think it must be delicious.
(Cook tteokbokki and instant spaghetti and mix them.)
(Pour some mozzarella cheese.)
(Put a hamburger steak on it and top it with more cheese.)
(Lastly, microwave it and it's done.)
This looks so good.
We're really making a dish with foods from convenience stores.
(To make a dessert, put bananas around a cream puff.)
(Drizzle melted chocolate and top it with green tea ice cream.)
(It looks great. Please order in now.)
You need just two ingredients for this.
All you need is chocolate chip cookies and banana milk.
Eat it in five seconds after you pour the milk.
- Nice. - Time's up.
I think we have a great teamwork.
- We're fast. - Let's cheer.
(They try to show their muscles to raise the viewership.)
(Please click a lot on Haha's broadcast.)
I hope the result will be good.
(Here is a full course meal made with instant foods.)
(An appetiser topped with crab meat, curry udon...)
(and the main dish of their own.)
(They created dishes on a whole new level with instant foods.)
Here is someone who can help you.
(Is there someone who will help Haha's cooking show?)
Oh, it's Chan Sung.
(Here is Chan Sung of 2PM.)
- Chan Sung. - Hello.
- Hello. - What is all this?
You came here. Congratulations on your comeback.
(He showed up on Haha's show before a music show.)
I saw him in the restroom.
I was wondering why he was here.
This is my agency.
Oh, this is your agency.
- I'm sorry. Now... - Okay.
- Guys. - What's all this? They look weird.
What are you guys doing?
- Take this off. - Take it off.
(Haha tries to reveal Chan Sung's muscles, too.)
We should take it off here.
Since when did Running Man become like this?
What are you doing?
- Roll it up. - Why are you doing this to me?
It's for the viewership.
- No, it's okay. - Come on.
(Breaking news! Chan Sung shows his muscles on Haha's show.)
- Please do it like this. - Please don't.
- You have great muscles. - I'm puzzled.
- Great. - I give up.
The hot guy in 2PM...
(At that moment, Seok Jin enters the room.)
(What is Seok Jin doing here?)
- Hello. - Hello.
(What brings Seok Jin to Haha's cooking show set?)
Gosh, Jae Seok is such a rascal.
How do I find the person with this nose?
How far do I have to go?
It's impossible to find the person.
How do I find the person with this nose?
Goodness.
I need a hint. It's so unfair compared to other members.
Give me a hint such as the location of this person.
Tell me which neighbourhood I should go.
Otherwise, I can't do it.
How do I find the person? Think about it.
Where would I find them with just a copy of their nose?
Considering your mission is more difficult compared to others',
we'll give you a small hint.
Give me a big hint instead.
What's the hint?
The person with this nose is an idol member...
who works for either SM, YG or JYP Entertainment.
(It's an idol group member at 1 of the 3 agencies.)
- It's one of the idol members? - Yes.
Big nose idol.
(He searches "Big nose idol" online.)
Big nose...
There's information on big nose idol.
(Which idol member did he find?)
He's a big nose idol member.
Look at this.
(Chan Sung of 2PM is the top suspect.)
It's Chan Sung of 2PM. He works for JYP Entertainment.
Let's go.
- Seok Jin. - I'm exhausted.
- I don't want to talk any more. - Don't do it.
Come here, Chan Sung.
Don't go near him.
Come here.
Looking for the person has been exhausting. Come here.
- Leave now, Chan Sung. - It's you, isn't it?
- Right? It's you. - Hurry up and leave.
Wait a minute.
(Where are you going?)
- Seok Jin, I have to go. - Wait a minute.
Wait, let me take a look.
- Really? - Isn't it his nose? Look.
The nostrils look different from his.
It's definitely his nose.
(It was neither Park Si Yeon, Han Seung Yeon nor Lim Ji Yeon.)
(Is Chan Sung the person with the nose he's been looking for?)
(It fits perfectly.)
(What? It fits perfectly.)
I can't breathe.
Seok Jin, you completed the mission successfully.
(The big nose is Chan Sung's.)
Really?
(He finally succeeds in finding Cinderella's nose.)
I had no idea that it was you.
(Seok Jin finds another big-nosed person in Seoul.)
I wondered how you would find me.
- This is incredible. - I was really curious.
We have another mission for you.
Both of you completed your mission, so we give it to you simultaneously.
- At the same time? - Here's your mission.
Scene-stealer is James Bond.
(James Bond?)
Eliminate James Bond who stole your number of views and your shoe.
(Eliminate James Bond who stole your views and your shoe.)
(What's this?)
This looks amazing.
It looks so delicious. Wait a minute.
He's a thief.
(He ran away with Kwang Soo's shoe without a reason.)
(He stole Ji Hyo's shoe.)
That was so easy.
What are you doing?
What's wrong with him?
(He stole Seok Jin's shoe in the middle of the street.)
Hey.
Jae Seok, have you lost your mind?
(James Bond's intention was to steal their views.)
(James Bond is back.)
What does it mean?
I'm about to lose my mind right now.
Should we eliminate him by taking off his name tag?
- How do we know where he is? - You'll get a GPS.
- This will determine the winner. - Do we have to look for him?
I'm tired of looking for people.
(The person who takes off Jae Seok's name tag gets all his views.)
This is the end of Running Man Space Out Contest.
Jae Seok took one of my shoes.
Why did he take one of my shoes?
I was happy to be a part of...
the Space Out Contest between Ji Hyo and Crush.
Based on the overall performance,
Crush is the winner of the Space Out Contest.
He's a strong opponent.
You're a strong opponent. Congratulations.
- Thank you. - Congratulations.
(The story of the Space Out Contest will be told on Ji Hyo TV.)
What's this?
The person who eliminates him takes all the views...
he obtained from other members.
(The person to eliminate Jae Seok will take all of his views.)
He stole my shoe.
Gosh.
(She's wearing two different shoes because of Scene-stealer.)
I need to change my shoes.
I can't run or walk in these.
Shall I give you a piggyback?
May I borrow one of your feet?
I'll follow your walking speed.
(Ji Hyo and Crush go to find Scene-stealer.)
(Haha, Seok Jin and Ji Hyo start the chase.)
(Kwang Soo walks carefully in two different shoes.)
Can I enter the salon looking like this?
(He goes to meet her wearing two different shoes.)
This is the place.
(Where's the woman that chose me?)
I'm looking for a salon.
(Who is the second woman to express her love for Kwang Soo?)
Hello, it's nice to meet you.
Hello.
(Kwang Soo's second love is Song Ji Eun.)
By the way,
it's embarrassing to say it myself,
but I heard you said I'm your ideal type.
(He asks such a direct question during their first meeting.)
Have you ever said that?
You've been my ideal type of men for seven years.
(She's liked me for seven long years.)
I was very surprised to hear from you.
It feels like meeting...
- a special celebrity in my heart. - Gosh.
I feel nervous.
I've never been in such a situation before.
It feels like meeting a special celebrity in my heart.
(They both feel very nervous.)
May I...
speak casually with you?
Of course, go ahead.
Is there anything you wanted to do on a date?
I haven't been on many ordinary dates.
I want to get my nails done...
with my boyfriend...
and have a conversation. I like to do small things.
I've never done that before with someone on a date.
- I haven't, either. - Really?
(Shall we get our nails done?)
That's why.
(For their date, they get a nail treatment together.)
I've never done this before,
- so I don't know. - I'll set it up for you.
I'll explain it to you.
What do men usually get?
Some get character designs that match their girlfriends'.
- That sounds cute. - I see.
(He checks her reaction.)
May I get a character design?
(He'd do anything she thinks is cute.)
Which design shall I get? Can you choose one for me?
- Let's get each other's initials. - Let's do that.
(He's startled by how quickly they're getting close.)
How are my hands?
They're quite dirty.
(They're quite dirty.)
How could you say that when...
A lot of people are interrupting my date today.
Your hands are much cleaner than I expected.
How dirty did you expect them to be?
(His hygiene level is much higher than she expected.)
What type of men do you dislike?
I'm asking because I want to be the best I can be to you.
I don't like men who pry too much.
- Someone who's nosy? - Right.
Did I misunderstand?
I think I heard you saying that you're the obsessive type on TV.
I heard you were the obsessive type.
Me?
Who said such a lie?
I'm not like that at all.
I've never been obsessed with anyone.
Where's Kwang Soo? He has ulterior motives right now.
- Hello, Ji Hyo. - Hello.
- Hello. - Hello.
- Hello. - Congratulations, you won recently.
You don't have the luxury to relax and get a nail treatment.
- You don't have time right now. - What's going on?
What's wrong?
You're missing a shoe, Kwang Soo.
He had mismatched shoes ever since I met him.
You're missing a shoe.
Kwang Soo.
How can you be relaxed and get a nail treatment right now?
I'm on a date.
Is it finished?
Thank you.
(Her initials are engraved on his nail.)
I've never done it before.
- That looks so cute. - That's so cute.
(He smiles.)
Do you like it, Kwang Soo?
It's my first time doing this.
Do you like it?
(Now that they have a keepsake,)
(it's time to find out how each other feels.)
Is your ideal type of men Kwang Soo?
(Do your feelings for me remain the same since seven years ago?)
Yes.
(Kwang Soo, do you feel my love?)
(What are Ji Eun's feelings for Kwang Soo?)
(Her feelings for him haven't changed.)
This is so boring.
(Ji Hyo suddenly asks Ji Eun a question.)
While observing Kwang Soo today,
were you disappointed in him at all?
No.
Wow, she was being honest.
(She's in love with him.)
Would you like to meet him in private after recording the show?
(Would you like to meet him in private after recording the show?)
Yes.
(Will their love continue off-air?)
Ji Eun, you're an idol member.
(Kwang Soo's heart flutters.)
(It's time to check Kwang Soo's feelings.)
(Is Kwang Soo's love for Ji Eun true?)
This is amazing.
- Let's see. - I'm feeling confident.
- If you're lying, I'm going home. - I'm confident.
- I'm really confident, Ji Eun. - I'll actually go home.
Would you like to meet her again privately?
(It's the same question.)
Yes.
(My heart is pounding.)
(This is the truth, Ji Eun.)
(She smacks him.)
(Aren't you forgetting something?)
We're shooting a show here.
(Ji Hyo is worried about them making the headlines of the news.)
- What show? - Get to work.
Why are you hitting on her?
What are you talking about?
What's going on?
(Was that really the truth?)
Kwang Soo.
Would you date me if I asked you out?
I'm sorry, what?
What? I have to say yes?
- Yes, to show the machine works. - Okay, then.
- Will you date me? - Yes.
(Let's see if Kwang Soo was serious about his previous answer.)
(Oh, gosh.)
(Machines do not lie.)
(This means he was serious about Ji Eun.)
Are you okay?
The machine works.
- It works, Kwang Soo. - It's a weird feeling.
(Exclusive news! Kwang Soo was serious about Ji Eun.)
(Kwang Soo is Ji Eun's kind of guy.)
(Did Kwang Soo find the other half of his life?)
(Meanwhile, in Gary's studio)
It has to sound like a runaway.
(Musician Hee Geon is busy writing lyrics.)
(The recording begins.)
(He's charismatic.)
(He looks cool all of a sudden.)
(He's trying his hardest as if he's releasing a new album.)
I'll go again.
Let me do go again.
(He's trying his hardest as if he's releasing a new album.)
This is a party for the winners
The night is victorious
(We might hit the top views.)
There's no right or wrong
Watch your back and know who you are
Run
(He finishes recording in the blink of an eye.)
(Gary is infatuated with his music.)
- Are we done? - Not yet.
- There's more? - We have to take the video now.
(Mikey of Turbo came to help but is exhausted now.)
It's a workout for everyone.
It's easy to follow even for beginners.
This is what people need.
(What's he doing?)
Are you warming up?
Where did you learn that?
My trainer taught me.
- That? - Yes.
- He told you to do that? - Yes.
(It caught on to other people.)
I've never seen anything like that.
Like this.
(It's addictive.)
We start off with a squat.
One squat.
One.
Go down, straighten your legs and do a push-up.
- Okay? - Okay.
(Kook's Workout consists of squats and push-ups.)
Come back up and jump. Easy, right?
Do it in one motion. One.
There you go. Push up.
Stand up and jump.
Hold still. One, two.
(I want my mum.)
Release.
- Hold them up. - They're so heavy.
Let's do one more. One, two, three.
This is easy.
A push-up. Then come up bending your legs.
(Kook's Workout consists of crawling and push-ups.)
- I can do it. - Now, jump.
(What will become of Kook's Workout?)
- Let go. - Wait, this feels awkward.
This is weird.
You have to stretch it out after a workout.
- Hey. - What is this?
Sleepy.
(He's Deep Sleepy.)
Hey.
- He's sleeping. - Hey.
(Tell my family that Kook's Workout was fun.)
Hey, wake up.
- Wake up. - I'm good.
You have to tell the viewers how great the workout was.
- Where am I? - Get up.
You have to encourage the viewers.
There are beginners like you out there.
If you do the workout,
(If you do the workout,)
you'll feel energetic.
(That's hilarious.)
Exercising is great for your body.
Do you think you'll get a nice body from this workout?
I got it already.
See? It worked.
I'm here now.
(Someone came to see Trainer Kook.)
If I go to see Jong Kook,
he'll know I'm up to something.
(How can I take his shoe off?)
What should I do?
I'm being chased.
I don't have the luxury to spend time with other members.
Things might go south.
(Jae Seok)
(Ji Hyo is right behind him.)
I need to catch the thief.
(Ji Hyo starts chasing Scene-stealer Jae Seok.)
- I'll go in first. - Okay.
Can you take us to Hyundai Senior High School?
(Ji Hyo)
(Haha)
I have to take the cab. I'm going to chase him, too.
(Haha is also chasing Jae Seok.)
Is the actual mission starting now?
Does the prize only go to the one person that catches him?
(Only one person can steal Jae Seok's views.)
(Everyone moves towards Jae Seok.)
Gosh.
I might get caught here.
One, two, three.
- Let's go! - Let's go!
- Let's go! - Why are they underground?
- Hey, Sleepy. - Hello.
What are you doing here?
I have to stop by everywhere.
- Why? - Let's get Jae Seok to try.
- I have to go. - Go where?
- Work out with us. - What?
- Let's start exercising. - I don't have the time.
Why are you here?
I have to do my mission as Scene-stealer.
- What's that? - I have to be in your videos.
That's fine. You can work out with us.
No, I'm really tired.
We have to work out for the video. What are you supposed to do?
I'm not sure. I'm really tired.
I've been running around everywhere.
(The members are after me. I can't stay here for long.)
It said we should watch out for Scene-stealer.
(It said we should watch out for Scene-stealer.)
- Why? - That's what it said.
Oh, I know.
That's because I'm taking video time from you.
- Hence the name, Scene-stealer. - I see.
Are you supposed to do something?
Not really.
I'm supposed to take 10 percent of your time on the video.
- I'll be mine. - 10 percent?
(Is Jong Kook getting suspicious?)
If he takes Jong Kook's shoe, it might get difficult for us.
(The game depends on Jae Seok.)
He must be around here somewhere.
(The three-minute videos will be released after the show.)
(Members will be ranked according to the number of views of the videos.)
(The videos will be open for 24 hours after the show.)
(The fate of Running Man lies in your hands. Click now!)
(The chase to catch Scene-stealer begins.)
Jae Seok is Scene-stealer.
(The identity of Scene-stealer has been revealed.)
- He started to move. - He's at Han River.
Where's Jae Seok?
I'm going to try my hardest.
(We have to catch Scene-stealer.)
(Get back the viewership he stole.)
Let's find Jae Seok.
I'll go after him, too.
(They chase.)
(He runs.)
Did you find him?
(The result of this chase...)
(will decide the fate of next week's race.)
(How will this chase end?)
(The fate of 7 Running Man members lies in your hands.)
(Look up Running Man on Internet portals now.)