Ji Sung heads from the right-back.
(January 10, 2016, Shanghai Hongkou Stadium)
He receives the ball. Haha is quick to receive.
It's a perfect opportunity.
Seok Jin is in shadow play.
Seok Jin is in the centre.
- Seok Jin attempts a header. - Seok Jin!
(Jumping)
(Heading)
(And an amazing story...)
(unravels.)
(Running Man in Shanghai)
(Running Man)
(Mission Impossible in Shanghai)
(Transcending time and space,)
(running through Shanghai's past, present and future)
I can't trust anyone.
It's becoming more difficult.
(Running Man in Shanghai starts now.)
(Flying)
(Seven drones are flying across the winter sky.)
(What is going on?)
- You need my approval for this. - This isn't good news for you.
- What? - Look at that!
(The object attached under the drone is a football.)
There are seven of them.
- It looks really cool. - It's amazing.
- It's heading this way. - Come over here.
(Those drones are headed straight...)
(to the seven members of Running Man.)
- Come on over here. - It's a football.
- The drones are coming closer. - It's coming to us.
- It's coming nearer. - Be careful.
Come over to me.
(The drones fly precisely towards their target members.)
- Oh, my. - Over here!
- Come over here! - I can't reach it yet.
It's here.
(The footballs...)
(drop down.)
Yes, over here.
Now!
I've got the football.
(Who, for what reason, sent the footballs?)
The drones delivered the footballs.
Oh, my.
- What is that? - What is it?
- It looks like a present. - Maybe it's an invitation.
(And...)
(this isn't all?)
Come over here.
(It doesn't look like a football this time.)
- It looks so high-tech. - With these, you can...
The drones makes deliveries.
(Dropping)
And off it goes.
It's so high-tech these days.
It's a message.
(It is a message box.)
(Who sent the message box?)
Someone recorded the message.
Turn up the volume.
(It's Park Ji Sung.)
Hey, Ji Sung!
Hello, I am Park Ji Sung.
(Return of the Captain)
(Korea's one and only, all-time Captain, Ji Sung)
("Ji Sung is perfect in any role he is assigned to." Alex Ferguson)
(Asia's star football player that played 154 games in Premier League)
(After retiring, he performs as an ambassador of Manchester United.)
(The recent big news was...)
(that he has become the captain of his family with his baby girl.)
(Running Man's all-time hero and beloved friend, Park Ji Sung)
(What is the message...)
(that Ji Sung sent?)
Hello, I am Park Ji Sung.
I am headed to Shanghai as I have been invited to FC Smile Cup.
I hope to see all of you.
He's become so gentle now.
I hope to see all of you in China...
when you arrive.
I'll be waiting for you.
(Captain Park's invitation that will lead Running Man to Shanghai)
Are we going to Shanghai?
Oh, is that so?
I'm going to score a goal this time.
We're having...
- another charity football match. - We should do it.
I'm going to score a goal this time.
You even missed the penalty kick the other time.
(Jae Seok never scored a goal once in three of the previous games.)
(Jae Seok struggles on the field.)
(He falls over all by himself and gets knocked over too.)
(His passes never seem to get through clean.)
(Six years of total disaster on the field)
- My mission to touch the ball... - But...
do you know you are terrible at football?
(Burst of anger)
Excuse me,
but let aside your pride.
I'd rather have you call me a terrible singer.
- No, you're a superb singer. - Nothing's wrong with your singing.
Just make fun of my singing instead.
You're a great singer but a poor football player.
- He is really bad at football. - Please, I beg you.
That's nonsense.
Please be aware of your footballs and we'll head to Shanghai.
- All right! - We're off to Shanghai!
Let's go!
(Running Man in Shanghai, the mission begins.)
(Incheon International Airport)
(Haha arrives with his football.)
Here I come, Shanghai.
Here I come, Ji Sung.
(Startled)
(Have a safe trip!)
Here I come, Ji Sung.
Congratulations, Ji Sung,
on your newborn baby girl.
But did you have to ignore my text?
(Following Haha,)
(Jong Kook arrives.)
Is this the right way?
(My precious)
(Jae Seok looks a little tense.)
(Ji Hyo is excited and ready.)
See you later.
(Nervous Jae Seok and excited Ji Hyo are ready.)
It will be different this time.
I've been practising.
(Will Seok Jin be able to even touch the football this time?)
I think I'd better sign this football before scoring a goal.
I will score a goal with this.
(Looking all too eager)
I can't even handle it though.
(Lacking the skills)
I'm all set.
I've been thinking of football all this past year.
I even played football in my dreams.
I'll show you all I have.
I will not...
let you down.
(Full of passion)
I'll make sure to score one goal.
Goodbye, everyone.
(Shanghai)
(Running Man arrives in Shanghai.)
(Shanghai is China's largest city situated at the mouth of Yangtze.)
(It is the heart of China's culture and business.)
(Where China's past, present and future co-exist.)
(And...)
(where the game will be held, Hongkou Stadium)
(Today,)
(on this field,)
(we will...)
(write history.)
(Seven o'clock in the morning, the day of the match)
(Someone opens the door.)
(Creeping in)
(Tip-toeing in)
(The production crew are sneaking into the members' rooms.)
(Room 716, Jong Kook's room)
(Room 617, Gary's room)
(Room 610, Seok Jin's room)
(Room 816, Kwang Soo's room)
(Room 616, Ji Hyo's room)
(Room 817, Jae Seok's room)
(Sound asleep)
(The phone rings.)
Gosh.
(Startled)
(The phone rings.)
(Jumping upright)
(I can't be bothered to get that.)
(He goes all the way to the living room to answer the call.)
(Hello)
What?
(He's surprised.)
(How did these people get in here?)
Hello?
(Why is someone calling them in the morning?)
- Good morning. - Right.
I'm Park Ji Sung.
What?
I called to inform you about today's mission.
Please find the football in another member's room...
and come to the garden.
You can complete your mission by scoring a goal in the goalpost...
that's in the garden.
You should head out as soon as possible.
But you are not allowed to take your own ball out of your room.
Please begin.
(Their morning mission begins.)
I'm sorry. I didn't understand a thing you said.
What on earth is going on?
(Sighing)
(What is going on?)
They're making me exercise...
(She's mad that they woke her up.)
so early in the morning.
(They're making me exercise so early in the morning.)
(Ji Hyo climbs out of the bed.)
(The phone rings in Seok Jin's room.)
(They have to quickly hide their balls.)
Where should I hide this?
Jong Kook is in the room next to mine.
What should I do?
Where should I hide this?
(Where should I hide this?)
(They have to hide their balls well.)
(And find others' balls as quickly as possible.)
No, that's too easy.
(A lot of the members...)
(are hiding their balls on the window ledge behind the curtains.)
(Haha, Kwang Soo and Ji Hyo are done hiding their balls.)
(We will now begin today's morning mission.)
(Mumbling)
(Gary just got up.)
Goodness.
(He looks for a place to hide his ball.)
There's nowhere to hide my ball.
(He's found a spot.)
(This is unexpected.)
(He's hiding it in the bathroom ceiling.)
(He's quite proud of himself.)
(Jae Seok's room, Kwang Soo's room)
(I am here to take your ball.)
- Good morning. - Are you...
- serious? - Where did you hide it?
You've got to be kidding me.
(He just asked Jae Seok where he hid it.)
- Come on, you... - I don't have much time.
- Are you serious? - Jae Seok.
Hey.
(Jae Seok is going for Kwang Soo's ball.)
(Jae Seok runs into Kwang Soo's empty room.)
(They went all the way to Shanghai for this.)
Ouch.
There's nowhere to hide it over here.
(He found it.)
(Jae Seok rushes to the garden with Kwang Soo's ball.)
Where on earth did he hide it?
When did you guys get here?
No, you can't!
(Gary runs towards Seok Jin to take his ball.)
No!
(Seok Jin hasn't even hidden his ball yet.)
- Just let me be. - Stay still.
- Just go to my room and take mine. - Stop.
- Which room are you in? - 616.
- What? - 616.
616.
(Jae Seok is already passing through the lobby.)
(Running)
I'm the first one here.
Should I do it from over here?
(He has to score a goal with someone else's ball.)
(Will Kwang Soo be eliminated if I score this goal?)
Come on.
(He fails.)
(He has to pick up the ball.)
(Jae Seok's second attempt)
(Will he score this time?)
(Bouncing off)
Oh, no.
Come on.
It's nowhere to be found.
(He's determined to score.)
(Jae Seok shoots.)
Goal.
(Jae Seok scores.)
(Kwang Soo is in the seventh place.)
Seriously...
Kwang Soo barged into my room first.
Last night, we had a good long conversation on...
how we should do our best today.
How dare he..
(Kwang Soo is still in Jae Seok's room.)
No way.
He must be crazy.
This isn't "Mission Impossible".
Was this really necessary?
Hey.
Hey, Gary.
- There's no one else here? - Seok Jin...
- You have to score from here. - What?
(He has to score a goal.)
(Haha arrives at the garden with Jong Kook's ball.)
Yes!
(Gary scores. Seok Jin is in the sixth place.)
(Haha shoots and he scores with Jong Kook's ball.)
Yes!
(Kim Jong Kook is in the fifth place.)
- There he is. - He's already here.
- He's here. - Over there.
Where?
(Kwang Soo arrives first.)
Whose ball is...
(Kwang Soo kicks Jae Seok's ball.)
Goal.
(Surprisingly, Kwang Soo scored in one try.)
(Kwang Soo scores with Jae Seok's football.)
(Jae Seok is in the fourth place.)
- He scored. - Just kick it?
Just kick it from here?
(Jong Kook scores with Haha's ball.)
(Panting)
Here he comes.
- You found it first? - What?
- Whose ball is that? - He really...
- doesn't hold back. - Whose ball is that?
(Kicking)
(It wasn't...)
(even close to the goalpost.)
Great job.
(Is he doing this on purpose?)
He's really bad.
I think he just exhausted his energy for today.
He must be exhausted.
Ji Hyo's here.
It's over if she scores first.
Hurry up.
(The only balls that are left are Ji Hyo's and Seok Jin's.)
It's over if you score first.
(Ji Hyo shoots first.)
(But she fails.)
Get out of my way.
How did that not go in?
(How on earth did he miss that?)
- You have to run. - Run.
(It must be hard to miss like that.)
(Meanwhile, Ji Hyo misses again.)
- It's in. - He scored.
(Seok Jin finally scores a goal.)
(No one scored with Gary's football.)
- You must be exhausted. - Hey.
(The later the goal was scored, the higher the rank of the ball owner.)
- Thank you for getting up so early. - Okay.
Check what's underneath the cloth.
(Check what's underneath the cloth.)
- There are a bunch of balls. - What is it?
Gary, please take the gym ball.
- What? - That must be the best one.
And Ji Hyo, who's in second place...
I should have blocked him.
Haha, who's in third place,
- gets the football. - I think I got a nice one.
Next...
The rugby ball is the worst.
Isn't that the worst one?
Please take the rugby ball.
- This is too... - That's for Jae Seok. Jong Kook,
- Seok Jin and Kwang Soo. - I'm...
- almost last. - What is this?
We'll tell you what to do...
with your balls later.
Please keep them with you for now.
I wonder what it's for.
(Their busy morning in Shanghai comes to an end.)
- You're right. - We're here.
- We've been here before. - I told you so.
- You're right. - This is where we played...
- football with Evra. - That's right. Evra.
Evra was awesome.
(This is where today's match will be held.)
(In 2013, they held the Dream Cup here.)
(The players gave their all even in the pouring rain.)
(We still remember the excitement and passion...)
(of that day.)
It's been such a long time.
- Evra was here. - I remember.
- Wow. - This was where it was held.
- I did a tiki-taka over there. - Right.
- Hey. - That wasn't a tiki-taka.
- It was a tiki-taka. - Yes.
That wasn't a...
- Stop lying. - Jae Seok ran like...
this when running.
- Good luck today. - Good luck.
Kwang Soo did a header here.
That's right.
With this facial expression...
That's the face all...
- football players make. - Like a toad.
That's right. A toad. What is this?
(Why is the music playing?)
- What's going on? - What's happening?
(They're running into the stadium.)
- They're cheerleaders. - The cheerleaders.
What's going on?
(Demonstrating kung fu all of a sudden)
Is this kung fu?
Wow.
He has a mask on.
(His moves are smooth.)
Right.
(Spreading)
- Wow. - Wow.
(They mixed traditional Chinese dancing with unique costumes.)
(They are amazed by the performance.)
(They hurdle together to make...)
What?
They're linked by their sleeves.
It's a football!
(And...)
- Wow. - It's a football!
(one performer jumps into the circle.)
(Who is the man behind...)
(the amazing finale of their performance?)
(The hero appears.)
(Korea's legendary football player, Park Ji Sung)
(In his numerous appearances in the past,)
(he'd always wanted to make a calm entrance.)
(But today, his entrance was dynamic.)
- Hey. - It's nice to see you.
(Embarrassed)
- What are you doing? - He's embarrassed.
Aren't you embarrassed?
(We haven't seen this side of Ji Sung before.)
You've changed a lot, Ji Sung.
Your entrances used to involve smoke before.
Right?
- It's been such a long time. - Wow.
(Welcome, Captain.)
- Welcome. - It's been such a long time.
How have you been? Are you still in England?
I landed this morning...
- from England. - Is that right?
How old is your baby?
She's now 50 days old.
- How fascinating! - She's just a newborn.
At that age, the baby is unbelievably lovely.
- But for the parents, - It's tough.
- it's a tough time. - You don't get to sleep.
- He looks gaunt. - Yes.
Now that you have a baby,
your mind-set must have been changed.
- Yes. - How did it change?
Right now, I'm thinking if it's okay for me to have fun here.
- He's anxious. - I understand.
- You're anxious. - So even Ji Sung thinks like that.
Oh, gosh.
- What's that? - Here.
(Running Man prepared a gift for Captain Park.)
- It's... - You're used to it now.
- There are name tags. - There's one for everyone.
(There's a t-shirt for his wife too.)
They're matching shirts!
Congratulations!
(And there's one for Captain Park junior.)
- How adorable!. - It's so cute.
- It's so cute. - So cute.
- How cute! - Really.
- Her name is Yeon Woo. - Her name is Yeon Woo.
- This is it. - Wow.
It's a matching outfit for the family.
- Like this. - So lovely.
You should take a picture and send it to us.
(We will raise Yeon Woo well!)
We played football together many times before.
- So... - So I have invited...
two other football players to join us.
- Really? - Really?
Who are they?
Look!
(They are...)
Hello.
Hello!
I know him!
(It's Ji So Yun and Jong Tae Se.)
(Jong Tae Se was the best striker of North Korea.)
(Currently, he's a big-time football player in Japan.)
(He's Gary's doppelganger, and he's funny too.)
That's it! Shoot!
(She's a world-class football player from Korea.)
(She led Korea to rank number 3 in Female U-20 World Cup.)
(She signed with Chelsea FC and was picked as the Player of 2015.)
- Ji So Yun! - That was an amazing kick.
(They are the two world-class football players.)
Hello.
Hello!
She's "Ji Messi".
- Hello. - Aren't we from the same family?
It's such an honour to meet you.
She's the pride of the Ji family.
We have Ji So Yun and...
Jong Tae Se here.
I'm so honoured.
I never knew her voice would be so lovely.
- I didn't know she was that girl. - I know.
Do you watch Running Man?
Yes, I watch it often.
- We are honoured. - We really are.
We see you on TV often.
But you invited me too late.
Apologise to her!
- We are sorry. - We thought you were abroad.
It's been such a long time since Tae Se was last here.
- Yes. - I know.
How long have you been married?
- About two years. - I see.
How's your marriage?
It's the best.
A lot of people say marriage is like digging your own grave.
(This is the guy who said it.)
I know.
Why are you looking at me?
- Hello. - Hey.
But I want people to know that being married makes you happy.
Is that right?
- How about you, Ji Sung? - Of course I am happy too.
(Of course I am happy too.)
- Hey! - That was a perfect answer.
- It didn't sound sincere. - You were getting ready to say it.
You didn't sound so sincere.
- You meant it, right? - Yes.
(I am very happy.)
Today's race is called Running Man Champions League.
You'll be divided into Team Ji Sung, Team Tae Se and Team So Yun.
- Three teams? - Really?
- Really? - Let's do a tiki-taka.
So...
the balls you got as soon as you got up...
- No way. - Now, the three team leaders...
will knock down the ball that belongs to the person they want.
- Really? - Yes!
- Now... - So Gary has a good chance.
You can each take two members.
You can pick whichever ball you want.
- Kwang Soo's is a baseball. - Why did I get a baseball?
If your team members score a goal...
or if they assist the goal,
- then you will get points. - If you help attack...
They are both strikers.
- I know. - They are both strikers.
- Right. - You need a winger!
- Ji Sung will go first. - Come on.
- Ji Sung! - Ji Sung!
- I won't say anything. - It's world-class.
- I think he will hit it. - Cheers!
I think he will hit it.
- I think he will hit it. - Let's go, Ji Sung!
- Just hit one. - That's it.
- All right! - It has to be Jong Kook and me.
(Who will be Captain Park's first choice?)
(It hits Jae Seok's ball.)
(He hit Jae Seok's rugby ball.)
Nice shot!
He's even good at throwing his shoe.
He's good at this too.
That was nice.
- It's not easy. - So Yun is next.
- Go, So Yun! - The risk is...
- Just go easy and hit mine. - too big.
You need someone to assist you.
- I think she can hit it. - Gary's ball is the biggest.
- Gary plays football well. - What if I hit Seok Jin's?
(What if I hit Seok Jin's?)
What if?
Don't think about the worst case scenario.
So Yun!
Did you say what if you hit mine?
The risk is too high.
(Which one will she choose?)
Please!
(She chooses Gary.)
(With a powerful shoot, she hits Gary's ball.)
That was amazing.
Gary!
Yes! Yes!
- Next up is Tae Se. - Tae Se!
Because I played with you last time, I know who plays well.
- Right! - Right!
- He knows. - Then it's...
- I will only target one ball. - Jong Kook.
- It must be Jong Kook. - I knew it.
Maybe he will accidentally hit Seok Jin's?
(She's worried for him.)
That would be the worst.
(That would be the worst.)
The worst?
- The worst. - How could you say that?
It will be the worst.
I mean marriage is the worst. I mean we're in the same situation.
Marriage is the worst.
It's very near.
Yes!
(Tae Se chooses Jong Kook.)
(They precisely hit the ball they target!)
- That's okay? - Okay.
(Tae Se and Jong Kook make the most powerful team.)
- Go! go! - Which one should I go for?
- Seok Jin's. - Kwang Soo's.
- When it comes to football... - Kwang Soo's.
- Awesome. - Yes.
- I don't know yet. - You're going for Seok Jin?
I'm a fellow married man.
Right. You're right.
You can't get him. You can't get Seok Jin.
(Will Tae Se really choose Seok Jin?)
(He chooses Kwang Soo.)
He didn't choose Seok Jin.
- Yes! - He didn't choose Seok Jin.
(Winning is more important to Tae Se.)
We are all set.
(Tae Se chooses Jong Kook and Kwang Soo.)
All right.
- You know it. - We're in trouble.
Ji Sung, come on.
I'm trying to hit the ball.
(He kicks the football.)
(He precisely hits Haha's ball.)
- I chose you. - Yes!
- Gosh... - You're my partner.
(Ji Sung chooses Jae Seok and Haha.)
- Who's left now? - Ji Hyo and Seok Jin.
- Ji Hyo. - Ji Hyo.
- Pick me! - I will make you a couple.
She's going to make them a couple.
(Will Ji Hyo and Gary become a couple again?)
Go!
Okay!
(She precisely hits Ji Hyo's ball.)
You did it!
(So Yun chooses Gary and Ji Hyo.)
- All right. - I waited for you.
Jong Tae Se!
- Jong Tae Se! - Jong Tae Se!
- Let's go now. - Jong Tae Se!
- Let's go now. - You almost got hit.
(The teams are formed.)
(They go to the locker room to change into uniforms.)
It's the same place.
(They came here for the 2013 Dream Cup, so they're used to the place.)
- This is the place. - This is the place.
- The massage place... - It's here.
(Someone's inside?)
(It is...)
(Song Joong Ki, Running Man's family.)
I almost died.
Joong Ki!
Hey, Joong Ki.
(They are always happy to see Joong Ki.)
Oh, dear!
(Joong Ki is here.)
Joong Ki!
You're here!
Hello!
It's been such a long time, Joong Ki.
- Joong Ki. - I missed you.
Happy New Year.
(I missed you, my family.)
(They are happier to see him in Shanghai.)
(Family is the best!)
I got this, Seok Jin.
7012.
- Hey! - That's sweet.
- What's wrong with you? - Don't do this.
(Seven Running Man members together forever)
It's too cheesy!
- Gosh. - Gosh.
Goodness.
We might get injured while warming up.
This is good for you. It's red ginseng extract.
(Drinking the ginseng extract to get over the nervousness)
- Red ginseng! - Red ginseng!
(Will we be able to score a goal today?)
(As time passes, they get nervous.)
Let's go.
- I've been waiting for this time. - It has begun.
I've been waiting for this time.
(It's time to go meet their teammates in the next room.)
- Hello. - Hello.
(Hello)
(Welcome)
Why are you here?
(Kim Dong Jin, Lee Chung Sung, and Lee Dong Gook are here.)
Please help us a lot.
Wow.
(Look who's here!)
Dong Gook.
You're on the other show that's aired at the same time as this.
Is it okay for you to be on this show?
You're here for the charity football event.
Yes, you are right.
(Your babies are doing well, right?)
I was afraid it would be a problem.
He's Patrick Kluivert from the Netherlands.
And he's Gianluca Zambrotta from Italy.
Il Woo's here as well, and...
Joong Ki, too.
- Joong Ki. - Yes.
He's like our member.
He's one of us.
We are very honoured to play with amazing players.
Thank you.
He's famous too.
He's Lee Chung Sung.
(He's the director of Korean All Star team.)
(Choi Kang Hee, the renowned football director in Korea)
- Hello, Sir! - Hello, Sir!
- Seok Jin is here. - Sir!
- Hello, Sir! - Happy New Year, Sir!
We wish you good health.
(They all bow to the director.)
- Don't overdo it. - Attacking is the only way to go.
Jae Seok and Kwang Soo...
play football with their mouths.
(Jae Seok and Kwang Soo play football with their mouths.)
So you will be divided into three teams.
Team Ji Sung, Team So Yun and Team Tae Se.
But you shouldn't pass the ball...
only to your teammates. Don't be like that.
(All three teams should do their best to win.)
Coach Kim will call your names.
Get ready.
Team Ji Sung will have...
Park Ji Sung, Yu Jae Seok, Haha, Han Kook Young, Lee Dong Gook,
Song Joong Ki, Kim Dong Jin, Zambrotta and Kim Se Joon.
- That's amazing. - That's a great lineup.
That's amazing.
Team So Yun will have...
Ji So Yun, Song Ji Hyo, Kluivert, Lee Chung Sung, Jang Hyun Soo,
Gary, Jung Il Woo, Kim Jae Sung and Kim Byung Ji.
(They are very confident.)
Team Tae Se will have...
Jong Tae Se, Kim Jong Kook, Lee Kwang Soo, Jee Seok Jin,
Lee Chun Soo, Han Sang In, Kim Tae Ryoong,
Park Chan Yong and Park Hyung In.
- That's great. - We have Chun Soo.
- Get together with your teams. - Okay.
- Plan your strategies for a minute. - Okay.
Let's take a picture together.
Here I go.
(Team Tae Se wants to have the MVP from their team.)
Let's get together.
(Team Ji Sung takes a group picture.)
Okay.
(They're ready to take a picture.)
Here we go.
(Team Ji Sung wants to score three points each.)
Are you all ready?
- Yes. - Let's do a cheer.
(It's time to go and play football.)
- Let's go! - Let's go!
(Good luck, everyone!)
(Let's win this game!)
(It's time...)
(for the big match.)
(Running Man Champions League in Hongkou Stadium)
Hi, this is your sports caster Bae Sung Jae.
The 2016 Running Man Champions League...
is being held in Hongkou Stadium in Shanghai.
Park Moon Sung commentator is here.
- Hi. - Hello.
The 2016 Asian Smile Cup in China...
is the first half of the Running Man Champions League.
There is a final mission for the second half.
Korean players are entering the stadium.
- Dong Gook and Chung Sung are here. - Yes.
Patrick Kluivert from the Netherlands and...
Gianluca Zambrotta from Italy are here too.
Ji So Yun, Jong Tae Se and...
Running Man members are here too.
They seem uneasy.
I believe they are very nervous.
(Please smile, Running Man members.)
There are a lot of fans in the stadium.
Today's game will be Chinese All Stars...
versus Korean All Stars.
Korean All Stars are divided into Team Ji Sung, Team So Yun...
- and Team Tae Se. - Yes.
When a player scores,
assists or blocks a goal,
- the team will get points. - I see.
The points they earn will be used...
- in the final mission. - I see.
Their director is Choi Kang Hee,
and Kim Tae Young is their coach.
(Bumping)
(What was that?)
I think Jong Kook is very nervous.
Ji Sung looks very excited.
Ji Sung and Byung Ji are on the field together.
Yes.
- They look excited. - Yes.
(Jong Kook and Kwang Soo got chosen as substitutes.)
- Yes, Sir! - Do well.
You'll be up soon.
(I'm so nervous.)
(Get ready.)
It's important to win against the Chinese team.
But how each member of these three teams,
Team Ji Sung, Team So Yun and Team Tae Se,
do a good job and earn points will also be looked forward to.
(Team Ji Sung, Team So Yun and Team Tae Se)
The Chinese team is on the right wearing green uniform.
- It started. - The Korean team is on the left...
- wearing white uniform. - I'm so nervous.
What shall I do?
Players sitting on the bench...
- look more like spectators. - Yes.
- They are here to watch the game. - Yes.
The ball is snatched in the middle and then passed.
Han Kook Young is dribbling the ball.
Kluivert stops the ball.
Ji Sung!
Ji Sung, my friend!
- He's cheering. - Yes.
Why is he screaming now?
Ji Sung runs to the right side.
He passes it to Dong Gook,
- but gets intercepted. - Looking after the baby...
- must have had an effect. - Yes.
Ji Sung is just getting warmed up.
He didn't have time to practise.
He seemed to have lost weight.
He just flew from London. He must be jet lagged.
- Yes. - He must be tired.
Ji Sung's wife seemed to have...
gained weight after having a baby,
but Ji Sung lost a lot of weight.
- That's funny. - They're running.
They are going in.
(There's an open space.)
They need defence.
He passes it.
They need to block it.
- That was a good pass. - It's going across.
- He gets it out. - All the Chinese players are...
former or current national football players.
- Yes. - Some players seem to be...
- moving a bit slow. - Yes.
The ball is in the middle.
The ball gets passed and he shoots!
(The Chinese team shoots.)
It's their first shoot.
He's the former midfielder of...
the Chinese national football team.
(Will it...)
(go in?)
He shoots the ball! It's the first shoot.
Kim Byung Ji blocks the ball.
(Kim Byung Ji blocks a goal.)
He's a great Chinese midfielder.
He blocked a goal.
- He blocked a goal. - Yes!
He caught it.
- Look at him. - He's so good.
The game just started.
I think we have a chance today.
- Don't we? - What?
- Yes. - The Running Man teams need to...
score points for the second half.
- Ji Sung passes the ball. - Great.
Chun Soo shoots!
It didn't go in.
They both played in the 2002 World Cup.
Right. Both of them still...
- play very well. - Yes.
Chun Soo retired not too long ago,
- didn't he? - Ji Sung's uniform seems too big.
- He lost weight. - The ball gets passed.
Kook Young receives the ball.
And he passes it.
He goes to the other side.
(Over here!)
He passes it to Ji Sung.
Ji Sung falls down.
Was he this weak?
(What just happened?)
I don't think he has been eating too well...
- in England. - Ji Sung actually scored...
- on the same spot in 2002. - Right.
- That's too bad. - It was close.
(Ji Sung runs fast.)
I hope Ji Sung does better.
The players fight for the ball.
That was good defence by Ji Sung.
He's good at defence.
That's great.
He turns around.
That was good.
You shouldn't make him angry.
He's really something.
(Ji Sung intercepts and runs with the ball.)
Jae Sung receives the ball.
Ji Sung runs to the right.
He's using his left foot.
He shoots with his left foot.
When he was playing for Manchester United in the past,
he once scored a goal beautifully at the end of the game.
This is the same spot.
That's right.
That reminded me of the time...
when Ji Sung played for Manchester United.
It was similar. It happened in the same zone.
Let's see if he'll do it again.
He runs to the side.
He shoots with his left foot.
The ball veers left.
(Will it...)
(go in?)
(The ball veers left...)
(and doesn't go in.)
- Too bad. - It didn't go in.
It's okay.
He's good.
He's still good.
(He still plays well.)
Ji Sung moves faster now than...
- the beginning. - Yes.
It's Zambrotta.
He looks at Ji Sung and passes the ball to him.
He passes the ball...
but the pass was too short.
- Wait. - What?
(What?)
(Patrick Kluivert, the legendary Dutch football player)
Kluivert received the ball!
It went in the wrong direction.
But that was...
a great play between the two world-class players.
Zambrotta and Kluivert made a great move.
That was wonderful.
I agree.
You're my hero!
(You're my hero!)
Don't lie. You don't even know who Kluivert is.
Come on.
- Hey, Kwang Soo. - Look over there.
Right.
That's a tiny gap.
No one would be able to tell that they're retired.
- They're good. - You never even knew them before.
(You never even knew them before.)
(Everyone pretends to know much about football.)
Come on. Stop lying.
(I wish I knew him in person.)
When I was a student,
I couldn't afford fan jerseys.
But I managed to buy...
- Kluivert's jersey. - I see.
That was the only one I bought.
Tae Se likes him a lot.
(Kluivert is Tae Se's favourite player.)
How can they know if it will be an offside?
Exactly.
Can we get rid of offside?
That's no fun.
I am talking...
about that boxed lines.
It feels great to go through an offside.
(Jong Kook talks as if he's a great player.)
Go, go!
- Ji So Yun. - She passes the ball.
Jong Kook's in the field.
He's running.
So Yun passes.
Jong Kook gets a chance.
He faces the goalkeeper.
He can't lose this chance.
(Will he score?)
The ball should have been theirs.
Why don't you go in and play yourself?
Ji Sung receives the ball.
We see him dribbling the ball in the centre.
- It's great. - That's a good pass.
Chun Soo receives the ball.
He shoots with the right foot.
The ball drops.
(Will he score a goal?)
Kluivert shoots!
(Will he be able to score a goal?)
The ball drops. He shoots with the right foot.
Kluivert!
(Kluivert scores a goal.)
He makes the first goal.
He is an exceptional striker.
It was a difficult pass to receive.
Yes, he scored the goal.
Kluivert made a goal.
With Chung Sung's assist, it seems that Team So Yun...
will receive two points.
Team So Yun leads with two points.
Well done!
(Kluivert scores with Chung Sung's assist, earning two points.)
Ji Sung should have scored a goal.
Go team!
Running Man members look cold. They are covering their legs.
Is that so?
(Il Woo substitutes Chung Sung.)
Il Woo is brought on as a substitute.
(Tae Se and Chan Yong enter.)
Tae Se and Chan Yong came in to substitute.
Tae Se is currently a player.
- That's true. - Let's expect him to play well.
You're my...
(Coach tells members to warm up.)
Good luck.
(Kwang Soo and Jong Kook are waiting to enter the field.)
Kwang Soo and Jong Kook will be the next substitutes.
Kwang Soo is quite tall.
He's 190cm.
He'd do well as a post player.
That's right.
Chun Soo starts to attack.
Chun Soo passes the ball.
(They are waiting for a chance.)
Kluivert receives the pass. Ji Sung!
Ji Sung makes a shoot.
He misses the perfect opportunity.
It's a pity.
This is the same place when he scored a goal...
in 2002 against Japan.
(Pull down your pants.)
He wears his pants pulled up too high.
It just looks like that because his legs are so long.
His underclothes are showing.
Substitute Ji Sung.
Excuse me?
(Kwang Soo substitutes Ji Sung?)
(Will I be able to replace Ji Sung?)
Ji Sung comes to the bench.
As Ji Sung walks off the field,
he hands the captain's armband to Kwang Soo.
- That armband is special. - That's true.
(Go, Captain Kwang Soo!)
Many Chinese fans have come to see Kwang Soo play today.
So Yun substitutes Chun Soo.
- He looks exhausted. - You're right.
You did well Ji Sung.
- You did well. - Well done.
You did well.
Everyone on the bench,
including the Running Man members,
greets Ji Sung.
Last time at the Indonesia match,
Kwang Soo actually missed...
many opportunities.
Over here Kwang Soo!
(A huge failure in Jakarta)
(To redeem that day,)
(he went into special training.)
- I thought he was Crouch. - Crouch?
He looks like Crouch.
He'll sit right back on the bench if he keeps on walking.
He might be as tall as Crouch.
Yes, the English football player Crouch.
I think you might be right.
That's true, either Crouch or the Korean player Kim Shin Wook.
Tae Se passes the football.
- It is a great opportunity. - Kwang Soo is ready.
- The ball is near Kwang Soo. - He just needs to kick it.
He just needs to make a run for it.
Kwang Soo!
(Crouch can take leaps and score.)
This is what we expect from him.
A little jump for Crouch...
overwhelms others.
- Kwang Soo is similar. - That's true.
His legs are just as long. The Korean Crouch,
Kwang Soo! Tae Se passes the ball.
- It's a great opportunity. - Kwang Soo is waiting.
He just need to make a run for it.
Kwang Soo! He runs towards the football.
(Will it be possible?)
(For Kwang Soo to score?)
What is that?
(A free hug)
The ball is in the air.
His height is no asset to him.
He runs more like a defender than a striker.
(He is my replacement, right?)
He had the perfect chance.
He just needed make a little jump.
But he falls down.
(He makes the day.)
He lacked the power.
It looks like he's a trained slider.
He is running to nowhere.
- Tae Se gets the football. - Kwang Soo! The long-legged guy.
He dribbles the ball.
He is trapping the ball.
He attempts at something but loses the ball.
He clearly knows what trapping is but didn't practise enough.
The crowd looks quite amused.
His role is done.
He attempts to tackle.
It is good to see how eager he is at this game.
Is he crying?
I can't bear to watch this.
- I feel sorry for him. - I can't watch this.
We usually say moving without...
- the football is important. - That's right.
Today the football rolls by itself.
It's a great opportunity.
Tae Se keeps passing to Kwang Soo.
Kluivert makes a great pass.
Run faster!
- From the right back side. - No, you have to kick it forward.
The opponent isn't keen.
He lets him pass. Kwang Soo...
makes a ground pass.
He just needed a little more energy.
The female fans are disappointed.
The opponent gave a great chance.
His arms look so weak.
He isn't marked by anyone.
Everyone's just watching him.
No one is marking him.
That's right.
He dribbles the football fast.
He passes the football which is smoothly received...
but is caught by the goalkeeper.
You did great!
(We need Jong Kook's skills dearly.)
All eyes are on Jong Kook.
If the opponent let him pass, he would have scored a goal.
It's quite a pity.
He dribbles the football!
The football is passed to Jong Kook.
He can make this.
- He needs to push. - He is tackling the opponent.
(He has been preparing for this moment for a long time.)
(This is the perfect opportunity to show off his muscle power.)
(Show us your skills!)
(Show us!)
Jong Kook!
He can make this.
(Will he make it?)
(The opponent pushes him aside.)
(Look at Jong Kook getting pushed aside.)
It's not all about strength.
You need to have the skills too.
It must be an honour.
To receive a pass from Kluivert.
- It must be an honour. - Yes, it must be.
The opponent easily...
blocked him.
He lost in the tussle for the ball yet again.
Balance is the key.
He's as weak as a paper tiger.
A paper tiger?
- He's a real entertainer today. - A paper tiger!
(Will he be able to redeem himself?)
So Yun!
She is supporting from behind.
But the members aren't ready.
She gets the ball.
Great play.
Jae Sung is doing well.
He's in a great position.
Il Woo!
(Il Woo follows the football.)
He looks handsome even from this afar.
(Handsome)
Il Woo is still handsome when he's panting.
This isn't an easy game.
The opponents are all members of the national team.
Considering that they are playing against such a team,
they are doing great.
Il Woo is doing great.
(He kicks the ball and runs for it.)
- He must be an experienced player. - I think you're right. So Yun!
She passes the football but is blocked.
Il Woo's attempt to pressure the goalkeeper and defence...
from the front side is a great move.
- He has been running for so long. - He is very willing.
You're right. Though he may lack the skills,
his willpower is the best.
- That's a great move. - He makes a pass.
Kluivert makes a pass. Tae Se!
That's how you tussle.
Kwang Soo runs to support.
They're doing great.
- Kwang Soo is catching up! - He just needs to make a pass.
Tae Se makes a shoot.
He didn't trust Kwang Soo.
- He couldn't trust him. - Right.
Kwang Soo...
Kwang Soo is on Tae Se's team...
but he didn't earn Tae Se's trust.
It would have been a right move to pass to Kwang Soo,
but he couldn't trust him.
I would love to watch Kwang Soo make a header.
Me too!
He even practised earlier on.
Just before, Kluivert and Tae Se...
- played very well. - Right.
It's a pity that it ended like this.
The first half is over.
Be careful!
We didn't score any more points.
The Korean All Stars lead with a point.
We witnessed Kluivert's superb goal.
Yes, and also Byung Ji's good defence.
They are leading the game.
Kwang Soo and Jong Kook gave their all.
They did push to their limits.
(No points for Team Ji Sung and Team Tae Se)
(Everyone enters the locker room.)
Kwang Soo, is that all you have?
Gary.
You did well, Kwang Soo.
You did well.
So Yun, you did well.
(The MVP of the first half)
- She fought alone in the midfield. - Yes, that's true.
Nobody was in the centre.
(iKON's special stage)
In the first half, there was one assist...
from Chung Sung.
And one goal from Kluivert.
(Each earned a point for the team.)
There was one good defence by Byung Ji.
Well done.
(Team So Yun, alone, earns three points.)
Earlier on Coach, you said...
Jae Seok will join. Which position do you have in mind for him?
He's eager to score a goal.
So he'll play as a striker with Tae Se.
(Striker)
Me?
I can't possibly do that, Coach.
If you find it difficult to score,
you can substitute Crouch.
No, I'm ready now!
(Crouch is ready to score.)
(We'll lead the second half.)
(How will they play?)
Let's go score some goals!
(It's time to finish the match.)
All right.
(Let's just keep up this momentum.)
- One, two, three. - We can do this.
- All right. - Yes.
(The second half starts.)
They switched out the players for the second half.
I wonder if...
Haha and Jae Seok will get to play as promised.
Right. There may have been some changes.
- There he is. - He's out on the field.
Jae Seok looks just like Kim Bo Kyung without his glasses on.
- Last time, he was on the field. - Right.
- They took a picture together. - Yes.
- No one could tell them apart. - That's right.
With his glasses off, Jae Seok will join the second half.
Will he be able to do well in the second half?
But, still...
Joong Ki, don't push yourself too hard.
He's going to play for five minutes?
(Joong Ki has a knee injury.)
- You shouldn't play. - Joong Ki...
- has a knee injury. - I see.
Song Joong Ki used to play with the Running Man members.
(Jae Seok is nervous.)
Does Jae Seok know what he's doing?
Jae Seok will play as a striker with Tae Se.
- He's going to have a tough time. - Right.
How will he play?
Jae Seok looks so thin.
(Jae Seok is very thin.)
Why did he tuck his shirt in?
Untuck your shirt!
He's like an old lady.
He's like an old lady, right?
He's like an old lady in an aerobics class.
(Is he really the striker?)
With his headband on...
(The reason he has a headband on...)
He's about to shoot...
Shoot.
(Jae Seok missed a penalty kick in the 2013 Dream Cup.)
(In the 2014 Dream Cup, he made another terrible mistake.)
Jae Seok is very passionate.
(Jae Seok hasn't scored a single goal.)
(But today is going to be different.)
(Jae Seok charges towards the ball.)
(Jae Seok is putting pressure on his opponent's defence.)
(He became much more agile through the years of ripping off name tags.)
(What just happened?)
- The defence doesn't falter easily. - Right.
Jae Seok is still excited.
(The ball is faster than him.)
He looks like Kim Bo Kyung,
but I think he's still warming up.
He's wasting his energy by...
- making meaningless moves. - Right.
(Jae Seok spots an opening.)
(Jae Seok tries to steal the ball.)
(Jae Seok fails.)
- He's got to do better than that. - Right.
What are you doing, Jae Seok?
(What are you doing, Jae Seok?)
Please pull your shirt out of the shorts.
Your shirt!
(It's not going as planned.)
(The coach said...)
When the time is right, pass the ball to Crouch.
Yes, I will do my best!
(Pass the ball to Kwang Soo.)
(Kwang Soo is running.)
subtitles ripped and synced by riri13
- Right. - There he goes.
Go.
(It's time to show off their amazing teamwork.)
(Pass it to me!)
(He lets Tae Se take the ball to the centre.)
(Tae Se crosses the ball over.)
(Jae Seok prepares to shoot.)
(Will Jae Seok score for the first time in five years?)
(Excuse me.)
(Kwang Soo suddenly tackles.)
Kwang Soo does a slide tackle.
He gave the ball to the other team.
(The two worst members of the team make terrible mistakes.)
Even Ji Sung, who never criticises his teammates, is laughing.
(Even Ji Sung, who never criticises his teammates, is laughing.)
- All right. - This is a good opportunity.
(Kwang Soo might get an assist.)
Kwang Soo passes...
Kwang Soo passes, but it was a ground ball.
- Oh, no. - Why was that a ground ball?
- Why can't he kick right? - There were a lot of players.
What's wrong with him?
- He knows he can't do much. - Right.
We can't even see where Jae Seok is right now.
Covering a lot of the ground isn't enough.
The Chinese defence is ignoring Kwang Soo.
- Why isn't he running? - Right.
He passes his ball to his team member again.
- He should run. - Tae Se is tired...
because they keep passing the ball to him.
From the right flank... He's too tired.
They have a chance. This time...
He should have kicked higher.
- I'd be angry if I were him. - Right.
He said he would run inside and do a header.
Neither Jae Seok nor Kwang Soo did much.
Why are they tired? They didn't even run much.
(The two keep messing up the game for the team.)
(Right now, they need Jong Kook.)
- All right. - He's doing a good job.
He passes.
- He's doing well. - Jong Kook!
He's fast.
He sprints towards the ball.
But he misses.
Jong Kook still dribbled...
and passed very well.
- He had the control over the ball. - He did an amazing job.
He is like a professional player.
He tore through the defence.
So Yun is playing her part as the playmaker in the back.
Jong Kook.
(Jong Kook is full of energy.)
They could easily defend.
(Jong Kook gets the team back on track.)
He's helping from the back.
So Yun received the ball.
- Through pass. - Wow.
- That was a nice play. - That was So Yun's through pass.
- Ji So Yun. - There he goes.
Jong Kook. It's his chance.
It's very boring.
It's so boring...
(Jong Kook seemed to know much about football.)
Jong Kook sounded like he could play well.
(Jong Kook is looking for an opening.)
He's fully warmed-up.
He sprints inside.
So Yun passes to Jong Kook.
It's a one-on-one situation.
It's the perfect chance.
He's in front of the goalkeeper.
Jong Kook.
(He is about to kick with his left feet.)
He did it.
Jong Kook.
(He has to score a goal.)
What the... What?
No way!
(He trips.)
- This is... - What on earth just happened?
(He looked like he was dancing.)
This is unbelievable.
What is wrong with him?
(Jong Kook's teammates are embarrassed.)
This can't be happening.
- Wow. - Come on!
- What the... - This is unbelievable.
(Laughing)
He kicked the grass instead.
(Jong Kook looked like he was drunk.)
He spent all his life working out in the gym.
How could that be possible?
Ji Sung, he should have scored, right?
- Yes, of course. - He should have scored, right?
- That was a great opportunity. - He should have scored.
He should have scored.
But he fell down.
(Uncomfortable)
Switch out three players.
- Switch out 3 players. - 3?
Now? Three players?
(Who will replace them?)
(The Chinese All Stars start advancing towards the goalpost.)
Look at her kick the ball away. Ji So Yun.
They pushed her even though she's a woman.
So Yun isn't scared of pushing male players.
Jae Seok trips the other team's player.
Jae Seok tripped the player who pushed So Yun.
- He avenged her. - He avenged her.
Jae Seok tripped him.
Jae Seok runs towards it.
Jae Seok runs to the side.
They're being pushed back.
He shoots with his left foot.
Things are starting to change in the second half.
As the Chinese All Stars are pushing harder,
they seem to have the upper hand.
The Chinese team has an impressive lineup.
The legendary player Fan Zhiyi is out on the field.
In addition, there is...
Yang Chen, who used to be in a German team.
- There are a lot of good players. - Right.
- There we go. - Right.
- Shoot. - Shoot.
The goalkeeper blocks it.
That was an amazing save.
A header. Here's another chance.
He's a good goalkeeper.
Whose team is the goalkeeper in?
He's in our team.
- He's in our team? - Yes.
Right. That was a nice save.
I think he's in our team.
- Nice job. - That was a nice save.
Team Tae Se earns one point.
(Announcing the three players who will get to play)
- They're busy switching players. - Right.
They are putting...
in different players.
- Me too? - Yes, get ready.
- Should I get ready? - The director is switching players.
- Okay. - Thank you.
He told me to get ready, too.
Let's go.
Gary, Haha and Seok Jin are warming up.
They might hurt themselves while warming up.
(Seok Jin looks bizarre.)
Hey.
They know they're in trouble.
(They're switching players to turn the game around.)
Jong Kook is out.
(Jong Kook out, Kim Se Joon in.)
- He covered a lot of ground. - Right.
He did very well.
Kwang Soo is out, and Il Woo is going in.
How should we rate...
Jae Seok's performance?
- What exactly did he do? - Right.
He didn't do anything noteworthy out on the field.
We will give him a zero.
- Gary is in now. - Right.
Gary's physique is solid.
Seok Jin took his glasses off as well.
That was a very good exercise for my joints.
Seriously.
You might think I didn't do much,
but I ran so much.
(But I ran so much.)
Apparently, you were running where we couldn't see you.
- I didn't notice him. - Right.
- I couldn't see you. - You couldn't see me.
It's not easy because football is a team sport.
Seok Jin.
- What just happened? - Seok Jin.
- The ball was taken. - Right.
He tried to get the ball with his foot, but he accidentally passed it.
I've never seen the director laugh out loud before.
(He misses the ball.)
- Wow. - That was hilarious.
He tried to grab the other player by the collar.
(He tried to grab the other player by the collar.)
Thank you for making us laugh.
(Last year, he could never even touch the football.)
Tae Se is reliable.
He passes the ball to So Yun.
Gary gets the chance.
Gary is very athletic too.
He tries to pass the ball to So Yun but fails.
It was short, but it was better than Kwang Soo's shoot.
Yes.
Gary is as fit as any professional football player.
Yes. The right side is coming to life now.
Jong Tae Se.
- He passes it back to Haha. - It's a return pass.
- Return pass! - I never knew he could do that.
- I didn't know that was possible. - Right. Tae Se...
passes to So Yun. And she goes for a mid-range shoot!
It didn't go in.
The team leaders, Tae Se and So Yun are eager to win.
- Yes. - They are determined to win.
Team Ji Sung still hasn't earned any points.
It's a competition between Team Tae Se and Team So Yun.
Yes. Ji Sung played quite terribly.
Tae Se passes the ball to the other side.
(Tae Se shoots the football to the opposite corner.)
That's nice!
Haha runs fast towards the ball.
- Haha! - Haha!
(Haha sprints.)
Haha!
Oh no.
(Haha reminds us of...)
(someone else.)
Oh, gosh!
Oh no.
(He was just like Jong Kook.)
Jong Kook is out.
Yes.
Who was it?
(Haha has long legs.)
The Chinese fan is lying.
Ji Hyo is going out.
Ji Hyo is ready to go out.
Her number is 7012.
It's our first time seeing someone with a four-digit number.
Football players usually use 1 or 2-digit numbers.
Yes. Song Ji Hyo got the number 7012 because...
it means the seven members of Running Man will...
be together forever.
Super Serve, Ji Hyo is in.
- She's the Super Serve. - Yes.
- She's very good. - That's right.
(The football is passed to her.)
Gosh.
- Ji Hyo gets the ball. - Hey!
- Ji Hyo. - Pass the ball!
Pass!
She's good.
She was surprised when he approached her.
When the other team player approached her, she got surprised.
Kim Tae Young. Ji Hyo again.
Ji Hyo. She's not good, but she manages to pass the ball.
(She's slow, but she's precise.)
She passes to the Jong Tae Se in the centre.
Shoot!
It hit the goalpost.
- He's good. - It was close.
- He's amazing. - Yes.
He stopped the ball and shot it with his right foot.
It's the standard method.
(The ball hits the goalpost after his powerful shoot.)
(But he lost the chance to earn a point again.)
Now only several minutes remain.
(Now only several minutes remain, and they resume the attack.)
Kim Tae Young starts from the centre.
He passes the ball to Jong Tae Se.
Jong Tae Se is doing everything.
Seok Jin rushes towards him.
Jong Tae Se passes the ball to Seok Jin. He's in the centre.
- It's a header. - Seok Jin!
Goal!
Seok Jin is in the centre!
(He receives Tae Se's centering...)
(and ends it with a header.)
(Seok Jin is bad at most things.)
What are you doing?
(He always played the supporting character.)
(We hope he will score a goal...)
(and play the lead character this time.)
Seok Jin is in the centre!
- It's a header. - Seok Jin!
Wow!
(Will he become the leading character today?)
(It hits the goalpost.)
He gives it a try,
but it didn't go in.
What he did was a very hard thing to do.
(Everyone is amazed by Seok Jin's unexpected header.)
(He was so close to getting the spotlight.)
- He shot very well. - He was so close.
His head is on the ground.
It's too bad. He almost got it.
It's hard to even hit the ball with your head.
He was surrounded by defenders, and he jumped high alone.
If it went in, it would've been the goal of his life.
I thought he was going to score.
- Did you see that? - Yes.
I didn't know it was Seok Jin.
It's too bad.
I thought he was going to score.
Unfortunately, the goalkeeper blocked it well.
(Nearing the end, the Chinese team launches their last attack.)
The ball is passed to him. The Chinese team keeps trying.
They attack fast.
(He takes the ball away.)
- He took the ball. - Yes.
He took the ball and...
shoots.
- Okay. - Again.
- They almost scored. - Isn't that our ball now?
- Good job! - It is.
The goalkeeper did well.
Yes.
That was a good one.
- They keep doing well. - Yes.
(The Chinese team takes a corner kick.)
He passes it to his team.
The goalkeeper blocks it again. He defended well.
Team Tae Se keeps earning points for the defence.
Our team needs to earn some points too.
Did you play?
- Did you play? - I did.
(Both teams do their best until the end.)
The Chinese team keeps getting chances to score.
The score is still 1 to 0.
The match is over.
The first half of...
2016 Running Man Champions League ends.
We didn't do well today.
Please give me another chance next year.
You were so...
- Good job. - You were amazing.
(The football legends and members of Running Man played together.)
(Meeting with each other was more meaningful than winning.)
Good job, everyone.
(Running Man)
Tae Se!
(Everyone becomes a child when you play football.)
The Korean All Stars team won,
and the 90-minute match ended.
(The first half of Running Man Champions League is over.)
The game will be followed by the second half of the league.
Now,
Team So Yun and Team Tae Se each earned three points.
Team Ji Sung didn't do well today.
We will keep our eyes on the scores in the second half.
- We will watch them. - Yes. Team Ji Sung has...
a chance to turn things around in the second half.
Yes.
(What kind of mission is awaiting in the second half?)
By the way, was that a football game...
or a variety show?
Football variety show.
- A football variety show? - A football variety show.
- It's Tae Se's baby. - It's Tae Se's baby.
It's Tae Se's baby.
- Come here. - What's wrong with his nose?
- He fell. - He's so adorable.
He looks like Tae Se.
- He must've fallen. - He's cute.
(He has a wound on his nose.)
This is Tae Se's son.
He's Tae Se's son.
- His name is Tae Ju. - Tae Ju.
He's adorable.
- Il Woo is here. - Il Woo is here today.
I will do my best.
He's so competitive.
He is very strong.
(Il Woo is on Team So Yun.)
Next is Kim Jae Sung.
(Kim Jae Sung is the midfielder of Korea's national football team.)
And we have Han Kook Young.
(Han Kook Young is the midfielder of Korea's national football team.)
We have Kim Dong Jin as well.
(Kim Dong Jin is the defender of Korea's national football team.)
Is there a member among us that you resent from earlier?
- Who did you secretly resent? - The one...
- standing at the end, Kwang Soo. - Me?
- Me? - Usually guys can play football.
But I am really bad at it. I am in big trouble.
Why did the director...
let Kwang Soo play for such a long time?
Since he's tall, we thought he was going to play well.
But he was terrible.
(The national team coach is frank.)
Isn't that too harsh?
Gosh.
(The members have been chosen for each team.)
The mission for the second half is called...
Strategic Name Tag Ripping.
Strategic?
Starting now, the three teams will be dispersed into headquarters.
And you will assign a number from 1 to 5 to each member...
and put the number in the name tag.
We will probably be paired.
I am worried about this.
I think Jong Kook has the last number.
(Team So Yun)
I am worried because my number is in the middle.
Let's start.
Okay.
(Team Ji Sung)
I'm number one.
And...
- I'm number four. - For example,
if your number is three,
you can only attack the person...
with the same number as yours.
How can we know what their numbers are?
- That's tough. - If you attack the person...
with a wrong number, you will receive a yellow card.
If you make another mistake and receive another yellow card,
you will receive a red card and get kicked out of the game.
Are there hints then?
There are hints, of course.
There are hints in the boxes hidden around in this building.
With those hints, you can guess people's numbers.
In the first half, your team got...
points for attacking and defending.
Team So Yun earned three points in total.
Bravo.
Team Tae Se gets three points too.
- That's good. - We're the only team...
We don't have any points?
Team Ji Sung...
played hard.
(That's it?)
You played hard.
We have zero point.
Team So Yun and Team Tae Se get three chances.
Team Ji Sung still gets one chance.
We will at least give you one.
The most dangerous one is Team Tae Se.
- Right. - It's because...
Jong Kook is in his team.
Team Tae Se will be very aggressive.
I know. We choose Team Tae Se.
It's randomly chosen.
I picked that one too.
Please, Tae Se.
- Who is it? - Seok Jin.
- Come on. - Seok Jin is number four.
- Is Seok Jin number four? - Yes.
Are you usually lucky with these?
Jae Seok is usually lucky this these.
- It's Il Woo. - It's number three.
(Jung Il Woo, number three)
- It's your number. - He doesn't know his own number.
(Jong Kook versus Il Woo)
- That's good. - You can win.
- You can win. - We can do it.
Because I can pick one.
- It's number five. - It's Haha.
Haha is a good opponent.
- It's good. - Yes.
(Kwang Soo versus Haha)
That's good.
It looks like we'll win today.
(Who will be the last one?)
- It's Jae Seok. - He's number four.
- Okay. - Shall we help him?
I have to help him.
- Oh, gosh. - Oh, goodness.
- What's wrong? - It's Seok Jin.
(Jee Seok Jin, number four)
Why did you pick him?
Il Woo is really unlucky.
(He's as unlucky as Kwang Soo.)
- Come on. - This is bad.
Come on.
- Wow. - Tae Se.
(Jong Tae Se, number one)
Can you catch him?
- Who is it? - Kim Dong Jin.
(So Yun versus Tae Se versus Dong Jin)
How will I do this?
I'll give you a cell phone.
You can send text messages to...
your teammates to share your strategies.
You can upload your status on SNS to share...
information with your team.
- That's great. - That's awesome.
(The second half of Running Man Champions League starts now.)
Let's go search the fourth floor first.
I'm bad at searching.
It should be here.
I don't think so.
Let's check.
I think there should be a box here somewhere.
I'm bad at searching for things.
(He found a box.)
(Jong Kook: Subtract scissors from paper.)
(He saves the picture...)
(and rips the clue.)
(Ji Sung is smart.)
I found one.
It says "Subtract scissors from paper".
- Subtract scissors. - It's three.
(Jong Kook is number three.)
- Let's go faster. - We have to watch our backs.
They could surprise us from behind.
That's why we have to catch them one by one.
We have to get Haha no matter what.
- You have Haha, right? - Yes.
You have to get Haha.
(Kwang Soo and Haha are about to meet.)
(I've been waiting for you.)
- That's not it. - I'll take this.
- Okay. - It's number five.
(As soon as I saw your number,)
(I knew I would win.)
- That's great. - He's an easy target.
- He'll win. - It'll be easy.
(Haha is coming to Kwang Soo.)
I need to know the number first.
- Isn't it me? - What?
My team picked your team.
(Kwang Soo slowly approaches Haha.)
(Haha is right in front of us.)
(They know my back number.)
Wait.
(Run!)
(Haha runs as fast as he can.)
- He's fast. - He's too fast.
Catch him. You have to catch him.
No. Wait.
(Kwang Soo gets Haha.)
You can't do this. Not yet.
Come on. Really?
You're number five!
Are you number five?
You run faster than I expected.
(Haha is out.)
Haha is out.
What?
Where is Jae Seok?
- Haha is out. - Why?
Haha is out.
(Why?)
Who ripped it?
The jail is not even set up yet.
I can't believe I'm already out.
This is unbelievable.
They got me as soon as the game started.
I didn't think I'd be the first one.
(I won't play any more.)
Hey, who ripped it? Do you know?
- Who got Haha? - We need to know.
I think Team Ji Hyo did it.
Let me know if you want to share information.
- We have three chances. - Did you...
- get Haha? - Did you get Haha?
It wasn't my team.
Can we work together?
- On this floor... - Yes, we can.
We have to get them too.
Kwang Soo took Haha out.
I see. What number is Kwang Soo?
- He is... - Kwang Soo is...
- Okay. - I got it.
It doesn't matter if...
we share Kwang Soo's...
- number, does it? - Right.
- Okay. - We can.
Let's share Kwang Soo's number.
- I'll give you information too. - Sure.
We'll tell you.
Kwang Soo is number five.
- Is he? - Yes, he's number five.
You have to tell us something.
Tae Se is number one.
(Tae Se 1, Seok Jin 4, Kwang Soo 5)
That's good.
- Was that information good enough? - Let's go.
- Was that information good enough? - Someone's here.
(Did you just tell them my number?)
- I heard that. - Wait a minute.
I just heard her say something.
- Come on. - They're sharing numbers.
What were you talking about?
What was that about? Come on.
- Are you helping each other? - They're together.
Are you allies?
- Come on. - We need to know them.
(A war is about to break out.)
- Il Woo, you too? - Come on.
- Watch your back. - Watch your back.
- Wait. - Come on.
(Tae Young attacks.)
- Stop. - Hey.
- Come here. - Come here.
- Stop. - Come here.
- Be careful. - Stop.
- Hey, get out. - No.
Help me.
(Tae Se rips Gary's name tag.)
- Help me. - Hold him.
Wait.
Help me.
(Jae Seok rips Seok Jin's name tag.)
- Hey. - Help me.
You're out.
Oh, goodness.
(Ji Hyo is my enemy too.)
Hey.
- Wait. - Stop.
- Jee Seok Jin is out. - Are you out?
- Yes. - Who got you?
Jae Seok did.
Seok Jin should be here soon.
I'm so lonely.
- Jee Seok Jin is out. - That's it.
(That's it.)
I told you so. I knew he'd be out soon.
Why is Gary's name tag missing?
Tae Se ripped it.
- Do you have the same number? - I don't know.
(Why did Tae Se attack Gary?)
- Okay. - Let's rip the name tag...
of a strong player...
to find out his number and...
- receive a yellow card. - Then let's share the number.
- Go that way. - Hey!
(Tae Se waits for a chance.)
(He runs toward Gary and rips his name tag off.)
(Unless you rip the name tag of the same number, you get a yellow card.)
- Tae Se gets a yellow card. - Really?
Does he get a yellow card?
(Both teams now know Gary's number.)
(Tae Se gets a yellow card.)
(Haha and Seok Jin are out.)
- Me and you... - Wait.
- What about Ji Sung? - Ji Sung must be number three.
- That's right. - He's number three.
- I'll get Ji Sung. - Okay.
Il Woo.
(Overzealous)
(He is as passionate as he was in the past.)
What?
Calm down.
We need to think.
I think...
I know all their numbers.
Ji Hyo is number four.
She tried to get me.
- Tae Se is number 1. - Tae Se is number 1.
Tae Se is number 1 and Kwang Soo is number 5.
Seok Jin is number four and I took him out.
- Who's number 2? - So number 2 is Tae Young.
- Come here. - Let's go.
Let's go.
(Tae Se found out that Gary's number is five.)
(My target right now is Gary.)
Wait, wait.
Wait a minute.
How did you know my number? Okay!
(Jong Kook is coming.)
(Tae Young holds Gary.)
(Kwang Soo takes Gary's tag off.)
(Gary is out.)
Gary is out.
Come on, guys.
Gary!
He's out.
Gary is out.
(Oh, no!)
I got all the fives.
I'm doing so much better in the second half.
(He's proud of himself.)
Shouldn't you change your number? now?
Yes, I should.
You take this number.
(Can they change numbers?)
There's an important rule.
- Yes. - Let's say Ji Sung is number one...
and he took out the all the other number ones.
Then Ji Sung can change his number...
to whatever he wants since he's the only number one.
- I see. - Do you understand?
- There are 2 number 3s. - I see.
(What's Kwang Soo's new number?)
- Good. - That's right.
- Okay. - Let them get your name tag.
- Got it? - Okay.
Hurry up.
We can't get Kwang Soo.
- Let's go down. - Let's go down.
We should go down.
Let's go.
(Nobody knows Kwang Soo's number.)
- Let's go. - I'm not afraid of anything.
(I will have my revenge.)
You made fun of me in the first half.
Get him. Let's take him.
We'll just get a yellow card.
- No, he's number five. - I'm...
- Wait. - He's alone right now.
Hold on.
(Why are you doing this?)
- Hold on. - Come here.
- Why aren't they coming? - Hey!
- Wait. - Hey.
Do you know how many people...
How could you do this to us?
He deserves a yellow card.
Do you really not know?
- My number... - What if your number gets revealed?
I won't look. I'll just go.
Then tell us one of your team member's number.
- I'm number five. - No, what we want to know is...
Who's number two?
We know that's not true.
Your team...
abandoned you.
Why isn't anyone coming to help?
Hey!
(They're using members as bait to track the other team.)
I can hear Team Ji Sung.
- He's number five. - Do I tell you what number I am?
But this will change his number.
But we don't know if it changed yet.
- Did he change his number? - Now it's changed.
That's right.
I'll just check it.
- All right. - Because if we don't...
Wait! Wait a minute!
If you're not the same number...
Let's take his name tag off.
- Okay! - Let's take his name tag off.
- Do it. - He's number three.
(I'm also number three.)
You're out!
I'm number three!
What?
(Ji Sung was also number three.)
He's out.
(Ji Sung's in luck.)
We've got him.
You're out now.
Is this for real?
We did it.
Kwang Soo is out?
What?
Goodbye, Kwang Soo!
You can go now.
Go away, Kwang Soo.
(So unlucky of him to be tagged out)
Goodbye, Kwang Soo!
How could this happen?
- Kwang Soo! - How could he be number three?
Who tagged you out?
- Kwang Soo, - Ji Sung ripped it off.
you really have no luck.
Why did you follow us?
That was so lucky of us to have taken Kwang Soo out.
They have three people left?
(Checking Tae Se's location)
They're so strong.
Jae Sung...
(Tae Se, let's move!)
(Thanks to Kwang Soo, they now know Ji Sung is number three.)
(Jong Kook will target Ji Sung.)
Who?
(Tae Se is coming nearer to help Jong Kook out.)
What's this?
(Now is the time!)
Oh, no!
(Ji Sung takes off Jong Kook's name tag.)
What is this?
(Ji Sung catches Jong Kook.)
Yes! We did it!
(They can't believe they caught Jong Kook.)
(Jong Kook blames Tae Se.)
It's your fault!
(Jong Kook is out.)
There is Jae Sung.
Ji Hyo and So Yun.
Ji Hyo is...
Wait. What's this?
We're very edgy at the moment.
We might elbow you.
If we catch two of Team Tae Se,
then only Team So Yun will be left.
There are two girls on that team.
We have the upper hand against them.
Where are they?
Come over here.
I'll hold Ji Sung, you tag him out.
(So I'm the target?)
Come over here, Tae Se.
(Ji Sung tries to help Dong Jin by tackling Tae Se.)
Tae Se, come here.
Let's go.
I can't see!
(So Yun gets Dong Jin.)
Kim Dong Jin is out.
What?
So Yun got him.
Kim Dong Jin is out.
(Oh, no!)
(Team Ji Sung is on the run again.)
(Let's go get Jae Seok.)
We got you.
Let me go!
(Ji Hyo gets Jae Seok.)
Look behind you!
Be careful!
Ji Sung tackles Il Woo.
(Who will be the winner?)
(Who will be the last one standing?)
Who was faster?
He was quicker!
(Ji Sung's name tag is ripped first.)
(Then Il Woo's name tag)
He was quicker!
(It was a close one.)
Ji Sung is out.
Ji Sung has been taken out.
(Il Woo takes Ji Sung out.)
Let's change numbers.
(Il Woo and Ji Hyo change their numbers.)
(Remaining players)
They should...
at least give us something to do.
Give us some cross stitch to do.
Or some other craft-work to do.
Those cross stitches this big.
- Those are the most popular ones. - Give us some work to do.
- Will make those craft-work... - That would keep us entertained.
and earn a few pennies.
Yes, for real.
Have you caught your breath?
If you have, we're going to run now.
(They all meet in one place.)
Look who it is.
What is this?
Am I your target?
I got him.
No!
(Tae Young is out.)
Kim Tae Young is out.
- What? - What?
Oh, my gosh!
Oh, my!
No one knows what will happen.
I got him!
Wait!
You're too...
(Will Il Woo take Tae Se down?)
(Someone's name tag is ripping off.)
Tae Se!
(So Yun gets Tae Se.)
Oh, my!
He got caught!
Jong Tae Se is out.
The game has finished then?
Nobody knew.
You're too...
Oh, gosh!
(Will the second half end like this? Or will Team Ji Sung revive?)
Hold him.
Come on.
I got it!
(Ji Hyo gets Kook Young.)
(Final results)
(The second half of Running Man Champions League ends.)
Bravo, everyone.
Bravo.
The winning team is Team So Yun.
(Team So Yun wins the league.)
I knew this would happen.
Congratulations!
Although it was quite unfair for us, I am very satisfied with the result.
We had a real disadvantage.
We did our best.
It's a football!
(Each carrying the football received from the drones,)
(flew over here excited,)
(and fought a match with the legends.)
(A short day of a long trip...)
(filled with familiar faces and new friends.)
(Thank you, for such a wonderful day!)
(But our journey does not end here.)
(Shanghai, 1926)
(10 young secret society members arrive with a mission.)
Secret Society!
Recollect all the items.
Return to headquarters!
(But!)
(Someone is suspicious.)
(Who threatens the Secret Society?)
Ji Sung looks shady.
(The plot behind the independence fund)
(Next week, Running Man Secret Society)