Hello.
How come you get in here as if it were your car?
- Do I have a secret mission? - Please, wear this in your ear.
Wait. Listen to me, please.
What's this?
Please follow the instructions given through this in-ear headphones.
- Through this? What's going on? - Wear that in your left ear.
But this is my right ear.
What? What's going on?
Why?
What's all this?
(A car opens.)
What's going on?
(This is such an absurd way to start the show.)
Hello.
Hello. What's all this?
(Finally, they are greeting each other.)
Kwang Soo.
- Hello, Jae Seok. - Hey, Gary.
- Seok Jin, Hello. - Hi, Jae Seok.
- Hello. - Kwang Soo, stop saying 'hello'.
(There's someone.)
(You must follow the orders given to you through the radio.)
You want me to stop greeting them?
I don't hear anything.
Go five steps forward.
- What? - I don't hear anything.
(It's not so bad if the orders are like this.)
Why can't I greet them?
Go on your stomach.
- Pardon? - Go on your stomach.
(Get down, Kwang Soo.)
What is this?
(He doesn't even question.)
What are you doing?
(The members are getting suspicious of Kwang Soo.)
Five push-ups.
(The orders are getting harder.)
- Jae Seok. - Yes?
Roll forward.
Why should I?
- Who are you? Why? - Roll forward.
(Jae Seok starts off with rolling forward.)
(Plopping)
What is this about?
- Kim Jong Kook. - Yes.
Pull up your shirt.
Pull up my shirt?
No. You have to show your skin.
- Show some skin. - Pardon?
(He's surprised.)
Pull up your shirt for about 20cm.
You want me to pull it up?
20cm.
(Roar)
- Stay like this. - What do you want me to do?
- Stay like this. - Isn't it too much to do this?
It's okay. They'll blur it out for you.
What? What do you want me to do?
(It's been blurred perfectly.)
I have it up.
We have an emergency order.
Now, you must find the hidden chair number one...
and put it on the mat. That team will get an advantage.
- Kwang Soo, this is the mission. - You need to find...
(They must find the chair first.)
(They're giving the order to their trustworthy avatars.)
- You have to find chair number one. - Find it, then you have to bring...
(Avatars that understood faster leaves first.)
Hurry and find it.
Find chair number one and put it on the mat.
While looking for the chair,
say "I'm ugly" three times.
I'm ugly.
(The avatar's life is so busy.)
Run, run, run.
Where is the Japanese chair?
Chair number one. It's chair number one.
(You're not looking for a Japanese chair.)
Chair number one, not a Japanese hair.
Chair number one...
Hurry up. Find it, Kwang Soo.
I want to find it, too.
Hold on. Can you get up for a second?
- I think Seok Jin found it. - Yes.
Go and stop Seok Jin.
(They found chair number one.)
- Stop Seok Jin. Stop Seok Jin. - Go stop Seok Jin.
You can do it, Seok Jin.
Come on, Seok Jin.
Let's get out first.
Seok Jin, tell them you made an acrostic poem about the chair.
I have to do well. I made a good poem about the chair.
- Really? - Why would you do that?
- It won't be good. - What are you trying to do?
- Help me start off. - Chair.
- Chair. - Call the doctor.
- Call the doctor! - Wait...
If you steal this...
All right.
Jong Kook, get ready to throw a punch.
All right, that's all I have.
- How do I snatch this? - All right, that's all I have.
(Slapping)
Why are you being like that?
Seok Jin's master.
Put it down.
- Let's put it down. - Put it down.
You have to take the chair to the blue mat and sit on it.
- Focus. - Jong Kook, sit on it.
(Of course he tries to cheat.)
- You're disqualified. - Sit on it. Sit on it.
Good job, Jong Kook. Just kick him.
Steal it, Kwang Soo.
Hurry. You have to sit on the chair.
(Chaos)
- Haha, take the mat and run. - Go on the mat.
Let's do rock-paper-scissors.
- Run away. - Get him.
(Haha is running away with the mat.)
It's useless without the mat. Those fools.
Hey!
(He succeeds in sitting.)
Good work.
(Jong Kook is so good.)
You did well. Good boy.
Good boy. They called me a good boy.
- We have to follow orders. - It's hard.
We didn't do anything, but I'm already tired.
Jae Seok, we'll bring in your master.
Who is it? I'm so curious.
- Jae Seok, was it a woman? - She...
- She sounded a bit mature. - Really?
(Who could it be?)
- You can tell. - Could it be Ahn Moon Sook?
She wasn't that old.
(Could she be...)
- Right? - You're right.
Seriously?
- Seo Ji Hye. - Wow.
(She's an actress starring in "Jealousy Incarnate".)
- I was her teacher. - Yes, that's right.
Pardon? Do you know me?
Seo Ji Hye. Am I wrong?
- It's Seo Ji Hye. - How did you know me 10 years ago?
- I met you on a different show. - 10 years ago?
- Where? - Ji Hye has no idea.
This is embarrassing.
- What's wrong with you? - What's your problem?
You don't even know her.
- I'm embarrassed for him. - It was on a different show...
- Stop it. - Don't you remember me?
- She really doesn't know you. - She changed.
- You put me in an awkward position. - She changed.
- She's surprised. - I'm sorry.
- We've met before, right? - I'm in a very awkward position.
Haha made it really awkward.
- Do you really not remember? - Haha, stop it.
- Jong Kook. - What's wrong with you?
- Don't be so pathetic. - I remember she was on some shows.
She was.
- What? - I didn't do that many.
- "The War of Roses". - Yes, "The War of Roses".
- Is this true? - Were you in it, too?
- I was really the bomb. - Forget it. Stop being a loser.
You were in it, too?
He says he was the bomb.
- You had no presence. - I was really awesome.
(Seo Ji Hye)
(She appeared on a variety show in 2002 as a college student.)
(Haha was ignored.)
(Just like 14 years ago, he's ignored again.)
She didn't think she saw you at a place like that.
You've changed.
No...
Why are you saying that?
- Next, it's Haha's master. - Good, good.
- I hope it's someone Haha knows. - Me, too.
(Muscular)
- You said it's a man, right? - What is this?
What's with the leg?
- It's Kim Joon Hyun. - It's Joon Hyun.
Nice ankle.
Are we shooting a food show today?
- Why are you sweating already? - What?
They gave me a long sleeve shirt since it's fall.
Usually we don't have lining inside.
- Kwang Soo. - Yes.
It was a woman's voice.
- A woman? - I hope you have bad luck.
- Why? - Seok Jin or Kwang Soo has Ji Hyo.
Come on, Ji Hyo.
(They are right.)
- I told you. - It's Ji Hyo.
- You got it right. - Her entrance is so scary.
Ji Hyo came to work today.
It's going to be a fierce game.
- Kim Jong Kook. - It's a beauty.
- Is it a beauty? - Yes.
- I'm excited. - I can't wait.
- Do Yeon? - It's Do Yeon.
- Balloon. Look at the balloon. - Her arm is like a man's.
That's not Jang Do Yeon.
- Is it not? -That's a man.
- It's not her. - It's Jang Do Yeon.
- I told you. - Yes.
How great.
- She cut her hair. - Her orders were great.
- Hello. - Hello.
- Your haircut suits you. - Yes.
- Liar. - He thought you were a man.
Who said my arm is like a man's?
You look more like Goo Bon Seung with this hair.
- Really? - You're exactly the same.
(They're like twins.)
- Goo Bon Seung? - Goo Bon Seung.
- I'm curious. - I guess you can get confused.
Seok Jin, did you have a man?
Yes.
- He made him recite poems. - That poem was...
- It's Se Chan. - Se Chan.
- It's Se Chan. - Hey, Se Chan.
- Hey, Se Chan. - Again?
(They're back together again.)
Why do you complain about the poems?
It was funny, wasn't it?
(We fear for this team.)
Is there an award for the winners?
He's right. I was treated badly.
What is this?
- Who is that? - What is that?
- Blond hair. - It's an idol!
- No, no. - An idol?
(Who is Gary's master?)
Min Ho.
(Min Ho)
Why are you making him stand beside me?
Is it a penalty for Gary?
- You'll look so ugly today. - This is a penalty.
- Two handsome guys. - Get in the shot with him.
This is really a bad target.
No pose can make me look better.
I'll just let it go.
- We're treating Min Ho well. - You're so handsome.
Today's race,
as you have just experienced, is Avatar House.
It's so great.
The guests will become...
our members' masters to do the race.
There are 12 bags in front of you.
In them, there are two bags with bombs and one with gold.
Each team is to choose a bag to enter the house.
After every game, the winning team has a chance to change bags.
The team that ends up with both bombs...
will be getting a huge penalty.
It's already bad as it is.
- Go. - Go ahead.
(The bombs are in bags between 7 and 12.)
This one.
She picked one.
Did they get the answer?
As for me...
One, two, three, four, five and six.
- There's something inside. - Jong Kook has the gold.
- It could be the bomb. - It's a bomb.
The rest of you can select your bags.
- This one is leftover. - Shake it.
It's heavy. It's so heavy.
- He's good at acting. - It's heavy.
That's a lie.
(Everyone is using tricks.)
It's so heavy.
Joon Hyun is the best.
Let's move to the Avatar House.
- Okay. - Okay.
(They're entering Avatar House.)
(Avatar House)
- What is this? - What's that?
No way. We're not sitting on the small seats, right?
Gosh, they're so cute.
- Sit here, Master. - Seok Jin.
- Yes. - Escort your master.
Yes, Sir.
- I'm your master. - Yes, Sir.
- Seok Jin. - Yes, Master.
Even the chairs?
Give me some carbohydrates.
- Carbohydrates? - Give me carbohydrates.
Master, please lie down.
- Seok Jin. - Yes, Master.
How dare you. Go sit on the floor.
Yes, Sir.
Can you bring me some snacks?
Snacks? Which one?
- I want cookies. - Okay.
Don't lean on your back.
My master is pretending to be mean when he's actually really nice.
I know you're a nice guy.
My heart is beating so fast right now.
I don't like being rude.
My master is very popular right now.
- What? - My master is very popular.
- Stop it. - Why?
- Quiet down, Seok Jin. - Yes, Sir.
How old are your avatar?
I'm almost 60.
(50 Years a Slave)
- He should be set free now. - He was born a long time ago.
Shouldn't you let him go by now?
He's like an insurance at this point.
This guy is a loyal slave.
Spit it out.
You said I could eat it.
I told you to peel it for me, not eat it.
Is she allowed to beat me up?
Is she allowed to put her hands on me?
Here.
You look like a dog.
Can you do something about this?
- Poor Kwang Soo. - I'll say.
- This isn't right, you know. - Fine.
Kwang Soo's a pet.
I think I know which one of you is the master.
- Look at them. - I'm not feeling any pressure.
I'm very comfortable with my role.
They're a prince and a servant.
- Master. - Hold still.
- Please. - I said hold still.
He's obviously the prince.
Did you all check your suitcases?
- Can we do that now? - Yes.
Don't let other people see you.
You can share with your partner, but you can't see anyone else's.
You can go check it out.
- Let's go, Master. - Should we go now?
Let's go over to the corner, Master.
(He's looking around.)
(Some look relieved and others look surprised.)
(What's this, Master?)
I think we should put on an act.
We have to make a good switch.
Should I open it first?
(The key is to swap the suitcases so the team can benefit from it.)
I'm 100 percent certain that we're not carrying the bomb.
See? Oh, wait.
Oh, gosh.
(Ji Hye and Jae Seok are carrying the bomb.)
Did you have to pick that one?
- I don't have anything. - That's good.
This isn't good.
- I'll open mine first. - Okay.
(Jong Kook's suitcase is empty.)
Is that possible?
(Do Yeon and Jong Kook got gold.)
I can tell you're acting, Do Yeon.
(I'm not, actually.)
This is good. I'm satisfied.
Jong Kook got something. I'm sure of it.
(Who's the other one carrying the bomb?)
(People have finished checking their suitcases.)
This is the first mission.
- Mission? - It's an announcement.
- We shall begin "Spin the Bomb". - "Spin the Bomb"?
The winner of each round gets to swap the suitcases.
(What's going on?)
There's something on the screen.
- This is the first mission. - "Back Hug Jjajangmyeon"?
This round is called "Back Hug Jjajangmyeon".
- It's something we're good at. - Nice.
The master will have a blindfold on behind the avatar...
and feed the avatar jjajangmyeon while doing a back hug.
- This is going to be hard. - So I don't get to eat it?
The team who finishes jjajangmyeon the fastest and cleanest...
will get the chance to swap their suitcases.
Don't worry, Master. Don't go easy on me.
Just put it in there.
- It's really jjajangmyeon. - It's gan jjajangmyeon.
(Here comes freshly made jjajangmyeon.)
That looks good.
- It's all soft once it's mixed up. - This is nice.
- Is this seafood jjajangmyeon? - I'm so hungry for some.
Jong Kook hasn't had jjajangmyeon for three years.
Can he have chicken breast instead of the noodles?
Do you have any idea how much oil they use to make jjajangmyeon?
- Here he goes again. - Just eat it.
It's his 1st time in 3 years eating jjajangmyeon.
- Do Yeon, close up his mouth. - That's unbelievable.
How else is he going to eat, then?
(Will Jong Kook give up on his strict diet for his master?)
- Did you take your glasses off? - Yes.
Oh, my.
- You're going to do it like that? - You liked that?
I mean...
You look thrilled.
Can avatars have feelings for their masters?
Did you see what my master did?
- What are you doing? - That was...
- What? - Are you in love with your master?
- Oh, my. - What's going on here?
She's serious.
You look too ugly to be like that right now.
What does it have anything to do with how I look?
Why does that matter?
All I'm saying is that it's not a good look.
I'll do an acrostic poem for Seok Jin.
- This one's for him. - This should be good.
It's about jjajangmyeon.
- Hey, you. - "Hey, you"?
Are you kidding me?
Eat your noodles.
Nice one.
- That was good. - Did you like that?
- I want to try next. - Did you like that?
Who's it for?
It's about jjajangmyeon. It's for Seok Jin again.
Give it a go.
- Hey, you. - "Hey, you."
Are you kidding me?
I'll punch you in the face.
That was good.
Way to go, Master.
- I liked the last line. - I gave it a try.
- I think my master is ready now. - I see.
Try it.
Why you little...
Are you impersonating Joo Hyun?
Are you kidding me?
Can I have the noodles?
I'm hungry right now.
- Good one, Master. - Someone give him some noodles.
Let's get the first round started.
- Let's go! - Let's go!
Go, Master!
I've said it many times. You're not supposed to chew on it.
Got it.
(Understood, Master.)
- Let's go, Kwang Soo. - Let's do this.
Ready.
(We have to take first place and get rid of the bomb.)
Ready, set, go!
Let's go.
(She's looking for it.)
You're doing good.
That's too much.
(It's a big mouthful.)
(He tries a bite.)
Look where the noodles end.
This isn't "Baek Jong Won's Top 3 Chef King".
I got it.
Start eating.
Stop. Don't do that.
(Kwang Soo gets his face washed with jjajangmyeon.)
There's no time to taste. Just push it down.
(This is the last time I'm eating jjajangmyeon.)
Don't taste it.
Where are you?
(That's not the mouth, Master.)
- Just put it in there. - That's my eye.
(He's eating away.)
Stop it.
Why are you taking so long?
You're doing good, Master.
(She shoves it in there.)
Can we take a short break?
There's no time for that.
- What are you talking about? - I should go like this.
That's too much. That's way too much.
Start eating.
(Jjajangmyeon is good for cleansing your face with.)
Why aren't you eating any? Start eating.
- My throat hurts. - Start eating!
Don't bite. Just swallow it down.
Less talking, more eating.
(Jae Seok is leading, followed by Haha, Kwang Soo and Jong Kook.)
You're doing good.
(The master has good technique and the avatar has a big mouth.)
- There's so much left. - Where are you?
- Are we done? - Where are you?
Jae Seok and Ji Hyo won.
No way.
(It's clean.)
(He's done already?)
Why did you do so bad?
You didn't give me any time to chew on it.
You just kept shoving more in.
There's no time for chewing.
Do I deserve to get beat up?
- What's wrong this time? - Look at her.
Just do as I say.
What is this?
My avatar is so bad at this.
My throat hurts.
(Master, you're overly passionate.)
- Did he make you upset? - Yes.
He still looks very upset.
I can't even turn my head right now. My neck muscles are sore.
Gary was so slow.
He even tried to shove my face down to the bowl.
(His master isn't scared of getting his hands dirty.)
He pressed down on me.
I was just helping you.
You poked me in the acupuncture point.
Sorry about that.
My master likes to win.
She was like this.
She was amazing.
Do we get to swap suitcases now?
Jae Seok and Ji Hye will be given an exchange ticket.
(Jae Seok and Ji Hye are given the chance to swap suitcases.)
Let's see here.
(We should get rid of the bomb.)
You should try to get the gold.
I want gold.
Chances are Jong Kook has it.
- I don't care if you take it. - What should we do?
- We should swap one. - Okay.
Which one do you want?
I want this one.
They wouldn't let their gold lying around like that.
What are you talking about?
(They exchange their suitcase to the one that was hidden.)
- We could easily tell you had it. - Oh, really?
Is that the bomb?
We'll go with this one.
The two teams will now check their suitcases in secret.
I think the one Jae Seok had was the bomb.
That means Jong Kook has it now.
We'll all know who has what shortly.
It's probably the bomb.
My master...
doesn't care about the game. He just wants to eat jjajangmyeon.
Don't let my noodles get cold.
(This is the suitcase Jae Seok and Ji Hye gave them.)
(It's the bomb.)
I knew it.
They'll know it's the bomb once they open it.
(What did Jae Seok and Ji Hye get?)
(It's gold.)
(They got the golden touch.)
(He falls over.)
(He got too excited and got himself injured.)
Oh, my butt.
(It's quite fun to control Jae Seok actually.)
There's gold inside. How did you know?
- At first, I thought of Seok Jin. - Actually,
Actually, when we stepped forward,
- they peeked at us. - That's right. There was a hint.
- What took you so long? - Hurry up, Jae Seok.
- Come on. - What's wrong with you?
Stop setting him up and come out.
They have both the gold and the bomb.
What happened? Did she hug you back there?
- Then what's wrong? - Why are you out of breath?
- No. Nothing. - What did you do?
- What's the matter? - Why?
- He looks really happy. - What's his problem?
Now, it's time for Joon Hyun to shine.
- He will win, of course. - Stop giving me pressure.
- Come on. - It's your show time.
- It's disadvantageous to us. - I just found out that...
- Ji Hye loves to win. - I see.
At the same time,
- Min Ho loves to win, too. - That's right.
Min Ho never wants to lose.
If he gets defeated one more time,
- he will burst out in anger. - I'm sure he will.
Gosh. What should I do?
I need to practise feeding my partner with chopsticks.
And these two, I'm also sure that Kwang Soo will...
- try to revenge. - Revenge?
No, I won't. There's no way I'll do it.
- I won't. We need to win. - I think...
they will not play to win. They will play to revenge.
- We won't be able to recognise her. - Of course not.
- That sounds very likely. - I play to win.
- I'm aiming for victory. - Let's see her face after the game.
- What are these? - Why noodles?
Everybody thinks that Joon Hyun will win,
but we need to see how things go.
I will show you that women can also win.
(Please go easy on me, Kwang Soo.)
- Some can swallow this with a gulp. - Would you like some?
No, thank you.
She loves to cheat.
- She really is. - You heard her, right?
She loves to make fouls.
I almost said, "Yes, thank you."
- She may be quiet, but... - She cheats quietly.
She's so kind and nice.
- You can only use chopsticks. - Ready,
set.
(If they win, they can exchange bags with others.)
(Gulping)
(Will Joon Hyun end up winning? Let's find out.)
Set, go!
- Where are the chopsticks? - Yes, you got them.
(Come on, masters. You can do it.)
(Kwang Soo picks up a lot of jjajangmyeon.)
She can't eat those at once.
(Kwang Soo is taking his revenge.)
(Pushing)
(Seok Jin pushes Se Chan's head forward.)
- You can do it! - Slow down.
(They gulp everything so fast.)
All right. There.
You need to chew.
- You're doing great. - Don't chew. Just swallow them.
She's doing great. She's eating really fast.
- Come on. Swallow them. - She's amazing.
(But we all know who's the fastest eater here.)
(He only needs to gulp few times to eat them all.)
(Can I order some extra noodles? Thank you.)
- We can beat Joon Hyun. - Hurry up. You're really slow.
- Hurry up. We're almost finished. - You're taking too much time.
I think we're almost finished.
Come on. We can do it.
(He's the best at covering her face with sauce.)
Come on, Se Chan!
- Take a big gulp. - Come on. Swallow them.
- Hurry up. Swallow. - Come on.
- Aren't we finished? - If you are, put your bowl up.
She's really amazing.
Hurry up. Show your empty bowl.
- What are you doing? - Aren't you finished yet?
- Okay. - She's unbelievable.
- Show them your bowl. - She ate them all.
- She finished it. - Show your bowl to them.
- There they are. - Really? Is she finished already?
- I can't find any noodles. - Where are they?
- I can't find them. - Where are they?
(Ta-da)
All right. Haha and Joon Hyun won.
(Haha and Joon Hyun succeed.)
- We finished them as well. - I knew I could count on Joon Hyun.
(I should've been faster.)
- I finished it. - We finished them as well.
- That was really quick. - Do Yeon is unbelievable.
(I can't accept my defeat. How could they eat so fast?)
- That was amazing. - Do Yeon ate really quickly.
- I ate almost everything. - Gosh.
- Look at her bowl. It's empty. - She ate them all.
- She ate a lot. - That was really close.
Haha, I thought that was my hand, not yours.
- Really? - You put noodles in just like me.
- Joon Hyun is so nice. - That was amazing.
- My goodness. - Gosh. Where is Ji Hyo?
Min Ho did a great job, too. Oh my gosh. Look at Ji Hyo.
- My goodness. - What happened?
- That is so cruel. - What happened, Ji Hyo?
- It's funny. Don't wipe her face. - What happened to you?
- Take a photo before cleaning her. - Okay.
- Anyway, what happened to her? - Take a photo of her face.
Who did this to you?
Is that some kind of a face pack?
That must be a jjajang face pack.
He even tried to open my mouth with his hand. Like this.
I just tried to feed you as fast as I could.
(That's why she took her revenge by biting his thumb.)
Ji Hyo, what are you doing?
Ji Hye is really upset.
Leave her. She'll calm herself down.
- Calm down. Calm your anger. - The sauce looks like a beard.
Take your time.
Min Ho and Ji Hye are really upset because they lost the game.
- Don't get in their way. - I can see that.
- Min Ho is really upset. - They really are.
- No, I'm not. - Ji Hye did really well, too.
- That was close. - What a pity.
- That was really close. - Ji Hye, are you all right?
- You don't know her. Do you? - Come on, Ji Hye.
- Stop being too friendly. - That's all right, Ji Hye.
(Eating)
All right. Let's take out the jjajangmyeon bowls.
- Come on. The game's over. - Hey, I'm not done eating.
- Let's take the dishes away. - Let him finish his meal.
- It's finished. - Why does he keep eating?
The game's over already.
Haha and Joon Hyun will be given an exchange ticket.
(They can swap one of their bags.)
- We were so close to winning. - I'm sorry to hear that.
We will...
swap with Jae Seok and my sister's team.
- That's our choice. - What do you mean, "your sister"?
I mean Ji Hye, of course.
(Ji Hye is my sister.)
- Don't you need my opinion? - I'm sorry, Master.
We'll swap our bag with Jae Seok and his sister's team.
(He says exactly the same thing as Haha.)
He's so kind like an angel.
One of their bags must be the bomb.
- Am I correct? - Yes, you are.
I noticed something...
(I think I can feel what's inside.)
- Aren't they the same? - They must be the same.
- Is there a difference? - They must be...
- either bomb or gold. - There wouldn't be any gold inside.
I don't think so.
How can they weigh just the same?
I'll swap with this bag.
- Will you? - You're not experts at all.
- Give one of your bags. - Come and grab one.
Can I check what's inside?
(Did they swap the correct bag?)
I think this bag is empty.
- I thought both bags were empty. - I felt the same.
(Is that a gold or an empty bag? There's a 50-50 chance.)
This side.
- No. - It's empty.
(They got an empty bag.)
- It's empty, isn't it? - Yes, it is.
- Is that the bag with gold? - Yes, this is the one.
- Do we still have it? - Yes, they picked the wrong one.
(The gold is still with Jae Seok and Ji Hye.)
(It'd be the best for them if the new bag isn't the bomb.)
In my opinion...
- They tried to find a heavier bag. - It must be empty.
- It must be. - Both of their bags were empty.
- They didn't care. - Yes. Both of them must be empty.
- Good. - There.
- All right. - It's great so far.
Good.
- They are really good. - Why?
- They are so good. - They are good at acting.
- I didn't know. - That room makes everyone actors.
- That's really peculiar. - What are we doing here?
- That room changes everyone. - Everyone is acting here.
- You're so good at acting. - Master,
- I want to go in there, too. - Jae Seok. Are you confused?
- Yes? Yes, I am. - Look. They are acting now.
Why does everyone act after getting out of the room?
There must be something inside the room.
We'd also like to go in.
(Here comes the second round of Avatar House.)
This round is called, "My Avatar Can".
- What? - After checking the game,
masters can make a bid with the number which you think...
your avatar can achieve.
My master will bid?
- Trust me, Master. - Raise your hand to make your bid.
- I'm in. - I like this kind of game.
Only the team with the highest number can make their challenge.
- Let's play no matter what. - Call out only if you think I can.
Gosh. I don't think you can succeed in any game, Seok Jin.
Master, trust me.
Please trust me.
- Min Ho will... - My goodness.
Isn't she the famous auctioneer?
- Amazing. - Yes, she is.
- "What's your bid?" - "Sold!"
- "What's your bid?" - "What's your bid?"
She came all the way here. Hello.
Hello, I'm auctioneer Kim Min Seo. I will host today's auction.
(Kim Min Seo, auctioneer)
- They brought a real auctioneer. - She has an amazing voice.
Yes. Her voice is amazing.
I'll give you a brief explanation about the auction.
Only the team that makes the bid with the highest number...
can challenge the mission.
If the team succeeds,
they will be given the exchange ticket.
- Good. - Master!
- I'll trust you this time. - What if we fail?
- There must be a penalty. - If you challenge and fail,
you must open and show one of your bags to everyone as a penalty.
- That's the penalty. - Please be careful with your bids.
- Do we need to open our bags? - Is that the penalty?
- Yes, it is. - The penalty is huge.
- That's tough. - Do we need to show both bags...
- or only one? - Do we need to show only one bag?
- Yes. One. - Okay.
You're asking because one of your bags isn't empty, right?
- That's right. - That was a sharp question.
(Min Ho is a sharp detective.)
Okay. I'll tell you the first game.
The first game is...
(What kind of game will they play?)
- "Break the Bananas". - What?
It's called "Break the Bananas".
- What kind of game is that? - You only have one minute.
Please guess how many pieces your avatar can break...
- How many pieces? I see. - Do we need to break the most?
- Yes. - We have a minute.
We'll break bananas for a minute.
Please consider carefully and make your bids.
- All right. Let's see. - It's quite easy.
Let's try. Break one banana.
- It's quite easy. - It's easy, isn't it?
- Try the other way. Good job. - It's quite easy.
- What is this? - It's really easy.
It's quite easy. We can call more than 30.
My master is very strict and passionate.
Why? What's the matter?
"You can break more than 30, can't you?"
The starting bid is 10 bananas.
Auction begins now. 10.
Let's bid. Let's bid first and see how things go.
- We should bid more than 30 to win. - Yes, we should.
(They wait for others to begin first.)
- 10. - Okay. 10.
- 10. - Okay. Se Chan suggested 10.
- She already got it. - 20?
- Song Ji Hyo, 20. - You're raising too many.
30.
- It's rising too fast. - 30?
Min Ho suggested 30.
- 35. - 35 is suggested.
- You have to open your bag. - Don't forget it.
- 40. - There is 40.
- 40? - You have to open your bag.
45.
- 45? - Don't forget it.
Should we open our bags if we fail?
- 48. - Here is 48.
(What did you say?)
Please consult me in advance.
- 49. - What?
(They don't communicate.)
Min Ho's 49 is the highest.
- 50. - Here is 50.
- 50? - 60.
(She says 60.)
- What? - Gosh.
The highest if Do Yeon's 60.
I'll suggest 61.
- Hey. - This is insane.
Is there anyone else? 61 is the highest now.
Somebody needs to accept this.
No one accepts this.
Did I succeed?
If there is no one, we'll close it.
I'll give a chance to bid only to one team.
- This is nerve-wrecking. - It is.
- Now, it's 61. - 61.
- It's the highest now. - It won't do.
(Will this be finalised?)
Before I count...
70.
(She bids 70 without fear.)
Did she say 70?
- You can't change it. - What's wrong?
- If it's 61... - Do it yourself then.
There are 62, 63, 64 and so on above 61.
(My avatar is talkative.)
Even a machine can't do that much.
Jang Do Yeon bid the highest so far.
It's 70. Is there anyone else?
This is crazy. We can't bid any more.
I'll shout the price three times before we finalise it.
70, 70,
70.
Wait. 71.
(Kwang Soo and Ji Hyo bid 71.)
Why did you go so far?
(The bid was like a buzzer beater.)
I thought she called something much bigger.
Song Ji Hyo's 71 is the highest now.
Kwang Soo, you have to succeed in splitting them.
It's 71 now. Will you bid more?
- Don't bid any more. - Don't.
71.
(They're anxious.)
I'll bid 80.
(He bids 80.)
(She's surprised.)
Come on, come on. Kwang Soo, come on.
It's better to open the bag.
- Come on. - Come on.
How can I make 80 pieces?
I'll finalise this after shouting 80 three times.
80.
(He challenged Kwang Soo.)
(Should I take that challenge or not?)
81.
(She throws 81.)
(Kwang Soo and Ji Hyo bid 81.)
- It was our strategy. - Here is 81.
Why did you accept this?
If you bid 82, you'll have a chance to challenge.
- Do you want to bid 82? - She's so good.
Gosh. We need to go.
- How many? - Now, it's 81.
- Is she taking this? - You'll have a chance to challenge.
(They're waging a war of nerves.)
85.
(Jong Kook and Do Yeon bid 85.)
- 85? - Here is 85.
(They bid 85 to give away the bomb.)
I'll shout the number three times and close it.
85,
85...
(Jong Kook will have a chance to challenge in this situation.)
(Will it be finalised?)
85. It's auctioned off.
(They bid 85 successfully.)
Let's see.
I've seen that on TV...
- but it's impossible. - Is it?
- Is this impossible? - Muscles are useless.
- Our strategy worked. - Yes, it worked.
- 85? - Wow, is this it?
(85 bananas come in.)
They're not ripe yet.
I think he can do it.
He can squeeze and split them.
You need to split 85 of them in a minute.
- Jong Kook will challenge. - You need to break 4 in 3 seconds.
Jong Kook will challenge.
(Come on, bananas.)
You can do it.
(I'll wish for your success.)
(He's glaring.)
Start.
(He starts to split 85 bananas in a minute.)
You're fast. Good.
He's doomed.
- No. He's doing well. - He's so fast.
No. Tear them all.
Monkeys will be sad to see this.
- Let's blend them later. - He is really fast.
- He is fast. - He can make it.
- He is so quick. - Good job.
- Great. - You can make it.
He may get cramps in her fingers.
If there were 80 of them, it would be possible but...
Well...
- They're slippery. - There are many left.
Did he split 20?
- I think he can do it. - It is possible.
- It's because he's Jong Kook. - It's like a circus.
He can do it.
30 seconds have passed.
Bravo.
- I think he can finish it. - I think so, too.
- Gosh. - Goodness.
- He looks like a monster. - How can he do this?
- Even monkeys can't do that. - Did you call him a monster?
- He's a machine. - Since he's so good.
- How many seconds have passed? - 40 seconds.
He must be thinking of this as exercise.
(There are only a few left.)
(Cheer up, my avatar.)
- We don't know the result yet. - As time goes on,
- Jong Kook is getting tired. - You can do it.
(For my owner and...)
(to pass the bomb to others...)
It's okay.
(It's exciting.)
Jong Kook is getting tired, too.
- Five minutes are left. - Five minutes.
Everyone, get ready to laugh.
It's a failure.
(He fails to split the bananas.)
(They burst into laughter.)
(He can't split the bananas.)
- He is a fool - He is a fool
It's party time.
That was impossible.
This was impossible.
As you went over 40,
- your speed got reduced. - Right.
- It was good exercise. - If Jong Kook failed, we can't...
My master will eat those bananas.
I'll challenge to eat 85 of bananas.
You challenge to eat them?
(Kim Joon Hyun's Top 3 Chef King)
(Come here, bananas.)
Let's share the bananas.
- Okay. - With the staff, too.
It's a banana festival.
- It's really a banana festival. - Yes.
Let's share with the staff.
You can't succeed alone.
Unfortunately, Jong Kook's challenge turned out to be a failure.
(Their challenge has failed.)
(It serves you right.)
Because he failed, he has to open one of his bags.
There is a bomb in either on of the bags.
- Pick one. - I'll pick the bag on the right.
- I'll pick the right, too. - Shall we pick this?
- Let's pick this one. - Okay.
(Jong Kook, you're doomed.)
Please open it.
(What will there be in the bag?)
(It should not be a bomb.)
Is it a bomb?
(It's a bomb.)
It's a bomb.
(Location of the bomb is revealed.)
- Wow, bomb. - Bam.
But if Jong Kook comes first place, we're over.
- Then we'll be doomed. - Right.
We need to block them completely.
Now, we'll begin the second auction.
- Okay. - All right.
This time, the owners will challenge...
and the avatars will bid.
I'll let you know the next game.
It's splitting the wooden chopsticks this time.
- What? - Did it change?
The second game is splitting wooden chopsticks.
I can split it even with my bottom since I'm a comedienne.
My master can do that, too.
Can she?
- Excuse me? - Really?
You can do that.
- I can't. - She's upset.
She is upset.
My body remembers splitting chopsticks very well.
The time limit is 1 minute and we'll start from 10.
- 20. - Let's start the auction.
- 20. - I'll take 20.
- 30. - It's 30 now.
60.
Hey, you're not supposed to do that.
- Haven't you bid? - Get out.
- Hey, Kwang Soo. - You haven't bid, have you?
You'll be kicked out if you're like that.
Why are you making the game so hard?
Don't you think we can do 200?
- We can do 60. - Look at this, Kwang Soo.
You said you could do it but why are you silent?
How long have you been on variety shows?
Gosh!
- You deserved that. - Wait.
Do I have to hear that from a young boy?
He's been on Running Man for years.
You just destroyed the foundation of this auction.
- Right. - Use your head.
Why do you think we're here?
To be more careful, let's go up one by one from now.
- That's how it should be. - One by one.
Why are you doing this to me, too?
- I'll bid 53. - I'll take 53.
- 54. - 54.
- I'll go with 55. - It 55.
60... No.
She said to go up one by one.
So we can't skip numbers?
Didn't you hear what she said?
Is he a fool?
(The prince of Asia became a fool.)
- It suits him. - You're a fool.
- What are you talking about? - You're like a fool.
Fools usually look skinny like him.
He looks a little bit dumb.
- Did you say I look dumb? - A fool suits him better.
- Let's restart. - Let's go.
It's now 55. You can bid 56.
- Do you want to bid 56? - 56.
- 56. - Haha bid 56.
I can do 56.
It's 56.
I think they're doing that to raise the number.
I'll shout the number three times.
- 56, - Let's finish it.
- 56. - It's over.
- It's over. - 57.
- I was going to bid. - 58.
Jong Kook bid 58. Is there anyone who want 59?
Are there more? It's now 58.
- 60! - Hey!
(He bids 60.)
Hey, fool.
- We're going up. - We can't call 60 now.
I don't understand why I can't call 60.
- 60 is... - Why not?
60 is a tabooed number.
Why is it tabooed?
Hey, fool, I'll give it to you. So just go home.
- Don't call me a fool. - Go home.
I can't believe this.
Kwang Soo bid 60, the highest number.
Don't you want to try to bid?
- 64. - He said 64.
- I'll go with 65. - It's 65.
- Now, it's 65. - Wait a minute.
(My master will take 66.)
My master will take 66.
- Isn't that too many? - They said 66.
Isn't Ji Hye shocked?
Ji Hye will try 66 pairs.
- Let's have them open the bag. - Okay.
- Okay. - Let's take a look.
All right, let's go.
- Let's go. - If there's no one else,
we close at 66.
66? 66?
It's sold at 66.
You can do it.
No, she can't.
These are harder to grip than bananas.
How you grip the chopsticks is important.
Okay.
It's Ji Hye's chopsticks show.
- She won't make it. - It seems difficult.
It gets tiring after a while.
- Jae Seok's final bid was 66. - Right.
Ji Hye must split 66 pairs of chopsticks to succeed.
Just concentrate on doing this.
It gets tiring after a while.
(Will they win the bag of gold?)
Please start.
Start.
(Separating 66 pairs of chopsticks starts.)
She's fast.
- Keep going. - Goodness.
- Give it to me properly. - Goodness.
Did you hear what she just said?
- "Give it to me properly." - What are you doing?
- Hold the bottom. - What are you doing right now?
- Hold the bottom of the chopsticks. - Did you hear what she said?
- "What are you doing right now?" - Hurry up.
- Hurry and give them to me. - Don't hold the top.
- Split them from the bottom. - Do a better job, Jae Seok.
- Split them from the bottom. - Goodness.
(They're growing apart like the separated chopsticks.)
- Jae Seok needs to do better. - It's okay, don't worry.
We can do it.
- We're quick enough. - Only 30 seconds passed.
- They might make it. - It's possible.
Don't worry. We'll make it.
- 30 seconds remain. - We'll make it.
I'm absolutely positive.
- I told you this was possible. - They're almost done.
We can do it. We can do it.
We can do it.
(Will their wish turn into a miracle?)
- They're almost done. - We can do it.
(They have less than 10 pairs left.)
- We can do it. - In 9, 8...
- We can do it. - In 7, 6, 5...
(What will be the result of this battle?)
- In 2, 1. - Just a little more.
(With remaining five pairs, they fail.)
(They were so close.)
(Someone's failure makes others happy.)
I want to see someone succeed.
Why didn't you hand them to me properly?
- Ji Hye's mood changed a lot. - I saw that, too.
She has a short temper.
(She's very angry.)
Did you see her do this?
(Throwing away the chopsticks)
She did it at the end.
- In 2, 1. - Just a little more.
(We're doomed.)
Gosh, we were so close.
Let's see what's in their bag.
(It's time to see inside their bag.)
- I want to see someone succeed. - This is fun.
I bet there's something inside one of the bags.
I think so, too.
- I think one of them has gold. - I bet there's gold inside.
Show us the front.
(He'll open one of the bags.)
- Jae Seok. - There are some scratches.
Look at this.
There are scratches because they changed the stickers.
The sticker on that bag changed, right?
- It's this one. - That's the one.
It's that bag.
(One of the bags has gold. There must be something inside.)
(The bag is empty.)
Goodness.
There's something inside the bag on the left.
I'm sure there is something.
Didn't Jae Seok's team change the bag?
(He got lucky and avoided opening his bag with gold.)
This is today's last auction.
This auction is a game category...
which the master and his avatar...
- play together. - Come on.
- Let's do it. - It's "Couple Jump Ropes".
It's "Couple Jump Ropes".
We did this often when we were young.
How will it turn out?
- You should try it once. - Shall we give it a try?
I bet Min Ho is good at it.
Get ready, start.
(Min Ho and Gary try jumping the rope.)
- They'll make it. - This is possible.
(Their movement is swift like a butterfly.)
(Despite their drastically different looks, they have good chemistry.)
- In 1, 2, 3, 4. - Do it as if you're doing it alone.
- Look at them. - In 6, 7, 8, 9, 10.
They're good.
Gosh.
Min Ho's team can do it.
(Let's show them what we can do.)
- They're good, too. - 13, 14, 15...
16, 17, 18.
Why did you trip?
(Why did you trip?)
He should have done better.
She complains a lot.
There's something wrong with her personality.
My master is...
- a little... - She's somewhat upset.
She's upset.
You had enough time to practise.
Now, we'll start the auction.
We start at three.
Let's start at three.
- Four. - Seok Jin called four.
- Six. - Haha called five.
Ji Hyo called six.
Nine.
- Haha called nine. - It's dangerous.
- We can do 9, can't we? - 11.
- 12. - We have 12.
- 13. - We have 13.
- 14. - 14?
I say 20.
- 20? Okay, I accept. - 30.
- The highest bid currently is 30. - Let's call 30.
I'm warning you, but we won't give up this game.
We'll play it no matter what.
During the simulation...
- You seem nervous. - I'm sorry. Let's take a break.
- He's already nervous. - Pardon me.
Seok Jin, you seem quite nervous.
During the simulation, we jumped the rope 18 times.
- 41. - Min Ho should try.
- 41. - We have 41.
- Min Ho will try no matter what. - What should we do?
He should give it a try.
- Se Chan? - 42.
We have 42. Will you try 43, Min Ho?
- Will you try 43? - 43.
- 43. - I accept 43.
43 is the highest bid.
(Please stop Min Ho for me.)
Min Ho will try no matter what.
I think it's a competition of these two teams.
Ji Seok's team is trying for fun, but Min Ho's team is likely to win.
My heart is pounding because I'm so nervous.
Here's our final decision.
I call 50.
- 50? - Yes.
Is 50 the last call?
- I think Min Ho will do it. - Is it 50?
- Is Min Ho not going for it? - Min Ho should give it a try.
This is your last chance. Is the final call 50?
(You're going for it, right?)
(What will be Min Ho's move?)
It's sold at 50.
(Se Chan and Seok Jin have to try 50 jumps together.)
- Wait. - Min Ho.
- Min Ho won't do it? - Why not?
You've done boxing before.
It's been 10 years since I've done boxing.
He has a bad knee.
How can he jump 50 times with his knee?
It'd be hilarious if he trips on the first jump.
That would be amazing.
- Can you leave glasses on? - They get in the way.
- You look ugly without them. - They get in the way.
(He trips immediately.)
Stop it, please.
He should be able to jump at least once by himself.
My goodness.
How can they jump 50 when he can't jump 5 times?
Let's try it without the rope.
Let's practise.
(Not in sync)
- What was that? - Were they on a seesaw?
I thought they were on a seesaw.
- I thought so, too. - Let's make an eye contact.
(Their practice time is up.)
Stay with my pace.
It'd be hilarious if they trip on their second jump.
I'm sorry, Ma'am,
but may we start when we're ready?
Of course.
- Why would you apologise? - Why is that important?
- We'll start ourselves. - I'm not used to being called.
- Please count our jumps. - Okay.
- You can do it. - We can do it.
Let's do it.
Who's the master?
- We can do it. - We can do it.
- Let's do it. - We can do it.
(Master...)
(Avatar...)
(We can do it.)
It's like "Dad's Challenge".
Are you naming this?
"Dad's Challenge"?
- You can do it, Dad. - Go, Dad.
- Let's go. - Let's start.
I bet they'll make three jumps.
(How funny will they be?)
- It's making me nervous. - Let's give it a try now.
(Let's give it a serious try.)
- We can do it. - Let's do it.
(A golden opportunity to earn the bag of gold.)
- Let's start. Get ready. - Let's go.
(They start their "Couple Jump Ropes".)
Two, three, four...
- Six, seven. - No one predicted correctly.
(They jump in sync.)
- What's going on? - 10.
(Goodness)
Don't push me down too much.
(Everyone is in a daze.)
Don't push me down.
- Don't push me down. - 17, 18.
(He tripped.)
(Screaming)
- They jumped many times. - It was your fault.
You pushed me down too much.
Se Chan tripped on the rope,
but Seok Jin pushed him down.
- Really? - Se Chan couldn't jump.
- They're quite good. - You should have resisted.
Are you kidding me?
Let's see what's in their bag.
Which one shall I open?
They might have a bomb in one of the bags.
We should have succeeded.
- This bag. - This one?
- Do they have something in the bag? - I don't think so.
I bet they have a bomb.
Let's see.
If not, it's in Kwang Soo's.
Here you go.
- There's nothing inside. - Okay.
Good job in hiding it.
- He sounds so strange. - I know.
- What he said sounds so fake. - Kwang Soo is good at guessing.
I'm quite observant.
I keep imagining Kwang Soo with his nose running.
What are you talking about?
That's so funny.
All right. The auction for "My Avatar Can" is over.
- That was fun. - I wish you luck.
- See you next time. - Thank you.
Can we do that again?
- That was so fun. - I want to do that again.
(2 hours later)
- We will now begin the death match. - This is making me nervous.
(They'll fight over the bomb in a game of wits.)
Get yourself together.
(There are twists after twists.)
Is there another twist?
(How will this cruel race of masters and avatars end?)
(2 hours ago)
This round is called, "Find the Right Card".
Avatars have to make their way through the obstacles of the track.
Before the match starts, the masters will play a game to win cards.
They can remove the obstacles according to the cards they win.
The difficulty of the race...
depends on how many cards the masters gain.
If the avatar comes in first place,
the team is given the opportunity to exchange bags.
Some of the cards are misspelled.
- What? - Some are misspelled.
(They need to look for cards that are typed correctly.)
I see.
If you get a card that reads, "Hurdles",
they'll remove it from the race.
(What?)
My master...
gets upset easily, but she's really slow.
Does she have any good traits?
She said she was worried.
"Don't you think I'm coming off too strong?"
"How do you think I should behave?"
She's like a little girl.
I think it's too late for a change.
It's too late now.
So I said,
"It's too late today."
- It's too late to go back now. - Was she that bad?
You should try again next time.
She said she's usually not like this.
I could sense anger from her face.
She's a nice person, but she has a personality disorder.
- At least she's nice. - That's right.
She's a nice person.
(They put on sticky pants to get the cards.)
You should take those pants home when you go home.
- You look good. - He does.
Are you from Anyang?
Don't I look like a gangster?
You do.
- Look at that. - Are you...
Are you a gangster from Anyang?
Let's go, Master!
I have faith in you, Ji Hyo. I want a path of flowers!
(I'm counting on you to give me a path of flowers.)
You can count on me.
Look at all the cards.
You have to get the correct one.
I see it.
I see one.
I see it there.
What's that one?
Hey, Ji Hye.
(What am I supposed to be doing again?)
You have to get the correct ones.
(You can count on me, Kwang Soo.)
- I want a path of flowers. - Did you see that?
- I see hurdles. - There are lots.
- You have to think fast. - Get the pressure board.
- You can go now. - Let's go.
("Find the Right Card" begins.)
(It's a dance-off.)
What's that dance?
Min Ho can dance to this.
Look at Min Ho.
Look at him go.
Se Chan, copy Min Ho's dance.
(I can do that, too.)
That's good, Min Ho.
- I wish I could dance like that. - He looks so cool.
- He's good. - Nice, Min Ho.
Why aren't you dancing, Master?
- Acupressure plates. - Acupressure plates.
(The first word is "acupressure plates".)
(I got this.)
Push them over.
(He comes charging in.)
There you go.
(She gets pushed aside.)
(Looks like Min Ho found something in the middle of the chaos.)
- Way to go, Ji Hye. - Ji Hyo!
(Ji Hye is good at everything.)
- Ji Hyo! - It's over here.
- It's over here. - That's not the right one.
We got it.
It's over there, Se Chan. She has it.
- Do Yeon has it. - I got it.
- Push them away. - It's on Do Yeon's bottom.
- It's on her bottom. - Get up.
(Ji Hye doesn't give up easily.)
Way to go, Ji Hye.
- Ji Hyo! - You're doing well, Ji Hye.
- Ji Hyo! - It's over here!
(It's right in front of Ji Hye.)
(Ji Hyo comes charging in.)
(Good job, Ji Hyo.)
- We did it! - That's not the right one.
- We did it! - Where did it go?
- Where is it? - Take the card off now.
(Ji Hyo's team no longer has acupressure plates.)
(This one isn't spelled correctly.)
(So close, yet so far.)
- Gosh. - Okay!
(That's right, isn't it?)
It's wrong?
Min Ho.
(Get it together, Master.)
I think there's one more.
There were two cards.
(Min Ho gets one as well.)
You got one, too?
- Are you serious? - This is turning out nicely.
Is there one more, then?
- It's over? - It's done?
Who got it?
Master, it's over.
Get up, Master.
(She's disappointed.)
I couldn't find it.
My master is...
always driven, but she's so bad at games.
- She didn't win anything today. - Right.
If you have anger issues, you won't be able to find it.
It's not like we're the ones going on the race.
We're doing this for the avatars, right?
Can I choose not to do this if I want obstacles for him?
Is that how it is?
(What's she on about this time?)
Master, you're so slow at the start.
I'm sorry.
Get your head in the game.
- I'm sorry. - You were just standing there.
I'll try harder.
- This is your last chance. - Okay.
- Stop disappointing me. - I'm sorry.
(Haha teases his kind master.)
(Who is the master here?)
- I'm counting on you, Master. - Let's go, Ji Hyo.
- Let's do this. - Yes, let's go.
I don't see anything that says "Puddles".
I don't wants puddles.
(The second round starts.)
How many are in your group?
It's just me and him.
- Are you a party of three? - Yes.
I live alone.
- Who does? - I do.
Oh, really? I'll pass.
Fruit plate for table three, please.
(This is Running Nightclub.)
- I have to ask you to leave. - "Plunger".
- What? - Plunger?
Plunger.
(They're sprinting for it.)
Coming through.
- Master! - Coming through.
- What are you doing, Ji Hyo? - We can sit out on this one.
But it's a plunger!
So what?
Don't you want to win the race?
Get away from me, all of you.
I got it.
Remove the unnecessary ones.
Get away from me.
- What's the word again? - Throw away the other ones.
(Se Chan misses it when it's right in front of him.)
- Plunger? - That's not the right one.
- Let's see here. - We have to win this race.
(It's right here.)
- It's over there! - There it is.
(It's over there, Master.)
- Hey, Ji Hye. - It's over there.
(He eats the card with his legs.)
(They reach between his legs.)
Where are you touching?
- Where is it? - Get that.
(Meanwhile,)
(Ji Hye is confused with the misspelled word.)
(This is right, isn't it?)
That's not it. That's not the one, Ji Hye.
It's obviously wrong. Why is she confused?
- Come on, Ji Hye. - Move over.
Go away.
There you go.
(He's done it again.)
He got it again.
He found another one.
(I want the best things for Gary.)
(Min Ho and Gary have removed plungers from their race.)
Good job, Master.
(His master is on fire.)
Look at him.
(I want to do well, too.)
Ji Hye, it's right over there.
Move over.
Go away.
There you go.
- Why is she confused? - There you go. You got it.
- I got it. - Good job.
(Did Joon Hyun get the right card?)
- Where did it go? - Good job, Master.
Okay!
(Joon Hyun and Haha have removed plungers from their race, too.)
What was the word again?
What on earth are you doing, Ji Hye?
- Can't you read? - Get it on your pants.
- Is this right? - Yes.
- She got it. - You did it!
- Wait a minute. - You did it, Ji Hye.
- I thought this one was wrong. - We did it.
(It's missing a letter.)
It's not right?
It's misspelled.
- Oh, really? - No, this is right.
- It's incorrect. - No, this is right.
- Ji Hye says it's right. - It's missing a letter.
How can you get that wrong?
She got confused with the most obvious one, too.
I was confused.
What's that on your legs?
(She's collecting incorrect cards.)
- What are they doing there? - She's hilarious.
(She slaps the cards down.)
(She got everything else except for the right card.)
- Ji Hye. - I told you it was wrong.
- Ji Hye is... - I told you.
Ji Hye is about to lose it.
Take it easy, Ji Hye.
We have to do better than this, Ji Hyo.
We need to exchange the bags with gold ones.
(Come on, Master.)
We need to get our gold.
What? I was just...
We have to win the race, right?
I'm just saying, you know?
Why are you like this? We have to win this game.
- What's the last one? - Puddles.
- What? - Puddles.
Is it "puddles" or "poodles"?
- "Puddles". - Okay.
- There it is. - That one is misspelled.
(She has her own way of doing things.)
Come here, Ji Hye.
Come here.
(Master, I found the right card.)
(Got it.)
Isn't that cheating?
(The third round starts.)
(This is their last chance.)
(Only 1 obstacle remains.)
(They dance vigorously.)
You can't mess this one up.
(Let's remove some obstacles.)
Let's go, Joon Hyun!
- Puddles. - You have to do this one!
You must get this.
- You have to do this one! - You have to get this one.
- You have to do this! - Please!
(I don't want to get wet in this cold weather.)
(Joon Hyun comes charging in for the 3rd time.)
(This fat man owns this turf!)
(What's this?)
(Don't get tricked.)
It's hiding somewhere.
- Ji Hye. - You must get it!
- You have to get it! - You must get it.
(Joon Hyun stays stuck to the floor.)
Where is "Puddles"?
You should look for it instead of lying down.
(Master, I hate water.)
Where is it?
Wait a minute.
Where is "Puddles"?
- Don't let someone else take it. - Where is it?
(What? "Water Bottom"?)
That's "Water Bottom"!
(That one is misspelled!)
(He gropes everywhere to search.)
- Ji Hyo! - Get out of the way.
Move. How dare you touch me there?
Ji Hye is so competitive.
(It's a fair game.)
- Ji Hyo, focus on the game! - Ji Hye.
- Please! - I think it's underneath him.
(Everyone attacks Joon Hyun.)
- There you go. - Ji Hye, over here.
- Ji Hye, it's over there. - Grab it with your bottom.
(She puts her hand in.)
Go in!
Watch where you're putting your hand.
- Hey, what are you doing? - Come on.
(Grab "Puddles"!)
- It's stuck to your bottom. - I can't see anything.
It's stuck to your bottom.
- I know. - Get out of the way.
(I won't let you go.)
- You shouldn't take it off. - Get out of the way.
(You're worse than me.)
- Let it go. - Please let me go.
- Move out of the way. - Miss.
(Let go of his bottom.)
It's already stuck to his bottom.
- What are you talking about? - She's trying to take it off.
This isn't a race.
Lying down on the floor won't help you at all.
(She doesn't budge.)
Gosh.
Let him go.
(Please take her away from him.)
- Let's pull Ji Hye away. - She touched my bare skin.
- Pull her away now. - Ji Hye.
She put it on her bottom.
(Did Ji Hye steal the card?)
- What on earth? - Come on.
(She stuck many cards on her.)
Good job, Ji Hye.
What's the point if she stuck all the cards on her?
Ji Hye!
(Ji Hye has a strong will.)
- What's the point? - Ji Hye!
She cheated because it was already stuck on Joon Hyun.
- You're the best. - That's cheating.
(We did it.)
I'm sorry, but Ji Hye doesn't have six bottoms.
She touched my bare skin.
She lay down and pretended to be asleep.
- I have to be okay. - Are you okay?
My heart is beating so fast.
Good job, Ji Hye.
(She removes puddles for Jae Seok.)
(Current status of "Find the Right Card")
- Where are we? - It's based on your colour.
- It's based on colours. - This is ours.
You're a fool if you can't win first place.
Gary's team hardly has obstacles.
- Gosh. - This looks difficult.
(It's their last chance to exchange bags.)
- My master removed... - Good luck.
so many obstacles for me.
Gary, you can do it!
- You can do it, Jae Seok! - Good luck.
- Seok Jin, you have a chance. - Go, Haha.
- You can do it, Gary. - I'm sorry.
(Gary is ready.)
- Get ready. - You can do it, Haha.
(Please do well, Jae Seok.)
Get ready.
(Don't worry, Master. I'll protect our gold.)
Start.
("Obstacle Race" starts.)
Run, Haha. Run.
(Gary gets ahead.)
(Sticky trap slows down Gary and Jong Kook.)
(Hurdles are ahead for the teams running behind.)
(Gary, Haha and Kwang Soo are in the lead.)
(They crawl quickly.)
Go, Gary!
(Some avatars enter the hurdle zone.)
(Everyone passes through the hurdles quickly.)
(Seok Jin struggles by himself.)
- You can do it. - Gosh.
(Seok Jin's team will probably lose.)
(Meanwhile,)
(Gary is moving quickly.)
(He enters the net at the speed of light.)
(Screaming)
(Jong Kook enters the plunger zone.)
(They struggle.)
(The competition remains fierce.)
You can do it.
I can't enter the net.
(Gary faces difficulties in the net.)
You can do it.
- You're doing well. - You can do it.
(Kwang Soo gets ahead.)
(I'm glad I removed the net.)
The net is difficult to get through.
(Gary finally passes the net.)
The net is difficult.
(Without the puddles, Jae Seok moves quickly.)
(I won't let anyone take our bag of gold.)
You're running first place.
(Jae Seok moves forward.)
(Will Gary remain first place?)
(Gary wins!)
(He's half a second ahead.)
That was amazing.
Goodness.
(I was so close.)
That net was so difficult.
I almost lost the race.
You almost lost the race, Gary.
The holes in the net were tiny.
Right? I could have won the race.
(Gary and Min Ho are given the chance to exchange bags.)
- There were screws on the floor. - I see.
(Kwang Soo got injured.)
It's okay.
(Did my dear Kwang Soo get hurt?)
- That's fortunate. - He's okay.
He got a small cut.
- Goodness, look at that. - Ji Hyo is putting on some bandage.
My goodness.
Ji Hyo is so sweet, but she can be so aggressive at times.
- I don't understand her. - I'm not sure...
- what kind of person she is. - I don't understand her.
She's sweet right now.
My mum is fickle about her, too.
(Ji Hyo is very fickle.)
Gary and Min Ho, you may exchange your bags with another team.
(Which team will Gary and Min Ho choose?)
- How about Haha's team? - Haha's team?
We don't have any gold.
- You don't? - He's lying.
I normally get upset easily. I'm sorry.
- We'll exchange with this bag. - Okay.
(They choose Jae Seok's bag.)
Jae Seok's bag?
(I hope it's not the one with gold.)
- They look nervous. - Did you keep our bag safely?
Yes.
Is this our bag?
(They open the bag.)
(Here's the gold.)
- Gosh. - They got gold.
(Did his fake acting succeed?)
I bet they got gold.
I think they did.
Min Ho's reaction is too awkward.
(Jong Kook is quick.)
(What's in Ji Hye and Jae Seok's bag?)
- Is this our new bag? - Yes.
She seems upset.
Ji Hye looks very upset. I can see it on her face.
(Did Ji Hye get the right bag?)
- She looks very upset. - I'm not upset.
- Do you have a bomb in both bags? - That would be funny.
Then she has two bombs.
(This morning,)
(Gary and Min Ho chose their bag carefully.)
We have to exchange the bags carefully.
Shall I open mine first?
(Inside their bag,)
(they find a bomb.)
We have a bomb.
(When Jae Seok and Jong Kook exchanged bags...)
I'll exchange with this.
(Min Ho and Gary waited for their chance.)
(Gary and Min Ho exchanged their bomb with gold.)
(Their plan becomes successful.)
Why did they exchange with ours?
She shouldn't have said anything. She made a big mistake.
I think we got something good.
At the end, something seemed strange.
- Ji Hye got angry. - She got angry.
Also, Jae Seok's eyes quivered so much.
- I think... - We have a good chance of winning.
(Gary and Min Ho get the gold.)
(The other two teams have bombs.)
The final race is "Pass the Bomb".
When the four teams without the bomb...
find two bags of gold that are hidden,
they get to escape and are exempt from being penalised.
One of the teams has a bag of gold already.
That team has to find one more bag.
(That team is Gary and Min Ho.)
The teams with a bomb...
can give the bomb to someone else by taking off his name tag.
Only the masters can take off the name tags.
(There are only seven bags of gold.)
(Find 2 bags of gold to escape.)
Only the team with bombs can rip name tags.
(They pretend not to have a bomb.)
Let's pretend like we're looking for the bags.
- Do you mean the bags of gold? - Yes.
Other teams don't know that we have a bomb.
It's Jae Seok's team.
Who is it?
- It's Jae Seok. - It's Jae Seok.
He doesn't have anything.
- We can catch Ji Hyo. - Let's go downstairs.
They might think we have a bomb.
They might.
- We can pretend to attack. - Okay.
(They pretend as if they have a bomb.)
(She hesitates.)
(Do Yeon and Jong Kook appear.)
(They must run to survive.)
(He runs after Ji Hyo, the master.)
Run away, Ji Hyo!
I caught her. Hurry, Do Yeon.
(I'll protect my master.)
(Only Do Yeon can take off the name tag.)
- Do Yeon, you must come here. - Run away, Ji Hyo!
- It's already over. - Hurry up, Do Yeon.
Kick him there!
- Where? - Kick him there!
I'm sorry, Ji Hyo.
(Ji Hyo is at the risk of getting a bomb.)
- I'm sorry, Ji Hyo. - I'm sorry.
(Ji Hyo's name tag is ripped.)
I'm sorry. You'd do the same in our shoes.
- We're in a hurry. - Catch someone else.
(This is unfair.)
I don't want the bomb any more.
(Do Yeon and Jong Kook get rid of their bomb.)
- He's such a gentleman. - Come to your senses.
(They can look for bags of gold.)
- Why? - We need to focus on the gold now.
We have a bomb now.
I can't believe that they got us.
If you hide it like this, nobody will know you have a bomb.
(They became a new bomb.)
It could be somewhere here.
(They came down to the underground level.)
(We really want to find gold.)
Let's go this way.
(He looks around.)
What is it?
(What is it? Are you a bomb?)
- What is it? Are you a bomb? - I was startled.
- I'm not a bomb. - Be honest.
- I'm not. We're looking for it. - I was frightened.
- You guys are not, are you? - No, we're not.
- I was startled. - There is somebody.
Who? Who's coming now?
- Someone is coming. Go back. - What?
(Who else? It's me.)
(She's as fast as lightening with aggressive hands.)
(Jae Seok is fully supporting her.)
Haha, Haha.
(She tears it off.)
You guys are so fast.
I'm sorry.
It's that woman again who touched my bottom.
Goodness.
Let's hide this under here.
You have to pretend not to be a bomb.
(The bomb goes to Joon Hyun and Haha.)
We need to find the gold quickly.
(They can look for the gold now.)
Let's get out of here quickly.
Now, I feel like I'm really on Running Man.
- Now you feel it. - I feel my heart pounding.
- You do? - I feel like I'm in Running Man.
- It looks like real Running Man. - Yes.
(Peeking)
Okay. Look over there. Isn't there any?
I can hear some sound.
(What's happening upstairs?)
Sorry. I was not thinking enough.
I was not. I won't do it again.
What is it?
- I was not thinking enough. - Hey.
- They have bombs. - Just...
help get others quickly.
Wait, is it Ji Hyo?
(They run automatically.)
(The bomb is after you.)
Are you coming?
I'm okay. Keep running.
It's a bomb.
Run away.
Hey.
- Jong Kook, I'm on my way. - Do Yeon, keep away from them.
I'm following you.
(The owner has a hard time running.)
Where did he go?
Where is he?
Where is Se Chan? I lost him.
Se Chan.
Where are you?
Have you seen Se Chan?
(They lost each other while running away.)
Where did he go?
- Can I warm up a bit? - Sure.
- I'm really fast. - You are fast.
- I run so fast. - He keeps saying he's fast.
You will make me anxious.
You're fast, aren't you?
(Is this what you meant?)
Where did he go? He is really fast.
Are you Se Chan's cameraman? Where is he?
You didn't find him?
I'm going crazy. Is he off-camera, then?
(He's right.)
(He's shooting Running Man alone.)
(It's hard to find him.)
Now, I'm relieved.
- We need to find the gold. - Where can we find it?
- Gosh. - I'm startled.
- What are you doing? - Excuse me?
The bomb is coming down.
Did you say bomb?
Kwang Soo. He's coming.
He's coming again.
(They noticed the pink bomb instinctively.)
Why are you following me?
(Ji Hyo and Kwang Soo should pass the bomb to find the gold.)
Run away, Min Ho.
Run away.
(Gary tries to block Kwang Soo.)
I failed.
Come over here.
- Come here. - Get Ji Hyo.
Please block Ji Hyo.
Ji Hyo.
Tear it off. You can just tear it off, Ji Hyo.
(He desperately defends himself.)
Why are you doing this to us?
- Tear it off. - No.
I'll tickle him.
(She tears his name tag off.)
Kwang Soo, why do you tickle me?
Goodness.
- I'm sorry. - It's okay.
- But we take turns to get bombs. - You're right.
Se Chan. Se Chan.
Se Chan.
Hey. Come up.
There he is.
I found him.
You're safe. Did you lose your name tag?
No, I didn't.
I kept running away.
- Well done. - I kept looking for you.
I was looking for you, too. They're running.
They're coming up. Come here.
Come here, Seok Jin.
(We'll crush you.)
- Seok Jin, do you have gold? - No, I don't.
- Go find one. - At this time...
- Really. - Jae Seok and Kwang Soo...
See? I knew it.
Hey, Hey.
Catch him.
I told you to catch him.
(The giraffe and the rhino attacks him.)
Did you get him?
I got him for you.
You should remember this.
You have to.
- Please remember this. - You, fool. You should help me.
Fool? I didn't like you from the start.
How dare you call him a fool.
- I caught him. - You have to help me.
Let's help each other.
Excuse us.
(At the moment they wanted to rest)
(They look scary.)
- Gosh, I'm startled. - Wait.
- What is it? - Oh, I see.
How can you do this to us as soon as you see us?
We were hiding to do this.
What is that?
Min Ho, come quickly.
Gosh.
(They get bombs again.)
- We got the bombs right away. - We can't help it.
(Se Chan, Seok Jin, Joon Hyun and Haha have bombs.)
Min Ho, Min Ho.
(Right after they tossed the bombs, they find a bag.)
Did you find it?
- I found it. - You did?
I can't open it.
(It's really gold.)
Aren't we too fast?
Really? Is it over already?
Oh my gosh.
We found them too easily.
Shall we go over now?
- Should we go downstairs? - Let's go. We already have gold.
Is there anything? What is it?
Goodness. If this is gold, why don't you go out with me?
- Gosh. - Goodness.
(They don't know what to do.)
- This is incredible. - It is.
Do you want to go out with me?
But my opinion is important, too.
Then you should've told me your opinion.
- Why should I? - You should have told me.
- I thought it was not gold. - I told you. Check with the camera.
(We started to date from today.)
Is this our first day, then?
Sure. Although we can break up any time.
- Let's break up tonight, then. - This is really gold.
- You're so cool. - I don't know what's going on.
- He's incredible. - I looked just in case.
You look awesome.
He looks awesome.
He's so cool that I want to marry him.
(They succeed in escaping.)
They might be here.
Let's look around here.
(They're looking for gold.)
You need to look carefully.
(She searches where others didn't look.)
Kwang Soo.
Why?
Did you find it?
(She finds gold as soon as she opens it.)
(They need one more to escape.)
We are getting close.
What are you looking at? Is it a bag?
How did you see this?
How did you see?
She is unbelievable.
(She finds gold consecutively.)
I found it.
(She surely has lucky hands.)
Goodness.
It was so dramatic today, but we made it.
(Ji Hyo and Kwang Soo escape, too.)
We can escape, right?
(The status of "Pass the Bomb")
(Jong Kook, Gary and Ji Hyo's teams escape.)
(There are three teams left.)
It's a disaster if they both attack us at the same time.
Let's find Jae Seok.
We have to find someone first and pass the bombs.
We have to...
- focus on finding gold. - We have to.
Let's pass the bomb to Jae Seok...
and find gold.
Cheer up.
I'm exhausted, too.
I'm getting upset. Quickly.
We need to be swift.
(Ji Hye and Jae Seok try hard to find gold.)
Where can it be?
Why?
(Se Chan Attacks her.)
(Se Chan hunts her while she was alone.)
I can't hold on.
Let me tear it.
- Se Chan. - I eliminated it.
(The bombs go back to Ji Hye and Jae Seok.)
- I took it off. - What happened?
- I took it off. - Did you?
Good job.
Let's go to find gold.
This way.
Whether it's us or them,
someone has to find the gold.
This way. Come this way.
What is it?
(Welcome to the trap.)
(Joon Hyun tears the name tag.)
(The bombs move to Se Chan and Seok Jin.)
I took his name tag. Pass the bombs to them.
Let's finish it right away.
Wait a moment.
They must be waiting for us here.
- We kept waiting for you. - You kept waiting?
- Was the gold there? - I'm completely exhausted.
- Sorry, Seok Jin. - Sorry.
There it is.
(Before they started to hunt to pass bombs,)
(they already found gold in the beginning of the race.)
It's gold.
(They already found gold in the beginning of the race.)
If we find gold first and keep waiting, they'll appear there.
Let's go upstairs.
(They found gold first and hid it.)
There it is. I found it.
(So they can escape as soon as they pass the bomb.)
Let's hide.
Chase them, then let them go.
Open it.
- I'm sorry, Seok Jin. - Sorry.
- Hey. - I'm sorry.
You look like a bear, but you're pretty sharp.
We found it.
(Joon Hyun and Haha escape last.)
- We ran out of energy. - I'm about to cry.
Today's final race.
There is a death match for the owner of the bomb bag.
The owner in each team will sit at the death match table.
Why is Se Chan always so unlucky?
I don't know. Why does it always happen to me?
Seok Jin and Jae Seok. Sit under the balloons.
- Should we take off our hats? - What should we do? Take it off?
On the table, there is one bomb bag...
and one regular bag.
You must try and switch...
your opponent's regular bag with your bomb bag.
- The goal is to give away bombs. - This makes me nervous.
This is going to be a mind game.
- Master, please... - What do we do?
Why am I treated like this until the end?
- Master. - This isn't on, right?
It makes me nervous to just watch.
(The one to make the first move will win.)
Press the button.
One, two...
(Who will go first?)
Three.
(Stinging)
- Who is it? - Endure it.
(I can do anything to win.)
She's hiding it.
How did you do that?
She lifted her thumb.
- How are you so spiteful? - It's okay, she endured it.
- She's tearing up. - It's okay, she acted well.
You're the best.
- It's so funny. - I've never seen anyone like that.
- Come on the show again. - You're the best.
- You must come again. - Seriously.
She endured it by biting her tongue.
She endured the electricity.
Okay, here we go.
- Press it when it changes. - You have to press right away.
(Who will be faster?)
(Screaming)
(Yang Se Chan loses.)
(That's what I'm talking about.)
You can't endure it.
It hurts.
- That's amazing. - She's hard-core.
- She's hard-core. - She was faster.
She's scary.
- She's a scary woman. - I didn't know that was possible.
Death match will start now.
Your chances are 50 percent.
(Death match starts now.)
Please check your bags.
- We chose those. - Yes.
(The teams are checking the bags.)
- Se Chan looks cool. - Wow, Se Chan.
- He has a poker face. - He looks cool.
- You can't tell. - You can't read him.
He looks like he's in a movie.
Se Chan, look at me.
Master, just for once.
I don't think that helps.
Look at Ji Hye's eyes.
Ji Hye is scary.
She'll glare through the bags.
Her eyes are so fierce.
Is it the bag on the right?
- Right from my side? - Yes.
- Is this one the bomb? - Yes.
(Could it be?)
- Good, good. - It's not in there.
Good?
Hurry up and change it.
I'll give you another chance.
Why are you giving her a chance?
I feel like I was too harsh on her before.
- Just give it to me. - I want to give you a chance.
- I'll give you a chance. - Just give me the bag.
Hold on.
- This makes it certain. - What is he saying?
I think you're the one that needs a chance.
- I'm giving Ji Hye a chance. - He's persistent.
- It's this bag for sure. - I'm sacrificing...
Se Chan. You're making me look pathetic.
I'll give you another chance.
- This one. - All right.
This will be amazing if there is a twist.
- There is another chance? - Yes.
Se Chan is good at things like this.
- Bomb. - Right?
Ji Hye, please open the bag to check.
- Please. - Se Chan.
- Se Chan. - Does it end here?
Open it slowly.
- Se Chan, right? - Please.
(The bag is being opened.)
(This is the final match to determine the losers.)
(What was in Se Chan's bag?)
(Pass)
Ji Hye passes.
(The balloon explodes.)
(Congratulations, Seok Jin.)
(Ji Hye and Jae Seok avoid getting penalty.)
I'm so happy.
Gosh.
(Their love is still strong.)
It was so amazing.
I'm so happy.
(It was a good move.)
(You need to meet a good master.)
Let's give a round of applause for Jang Do Yeon,
Joon Hyun, Ji Hye, Se Chan...
and Min ho.
(Thank you for joining us on Running Man.)