(This is the first mission for the members and the guests.)
("Walk politely before someone who's in much higher position.")
(Find out how to say this in pure Korean words.)
(We'll give an advantage to the one who brings it to us first.)
(The answer is "napa cabage".)
(Who would be the first one to arrive with napa cabage?)
(The appointed time, 2pm, is approaching.)
(Who would be the first one to arrive?)
It says I must find this place.
Am I the first one to arrive?
(Who would he be?)
Hello.
(He is the best supporting actor and the best comedy actor of all time.)
(Yu Hae Jin is a guaranteed box office hit.)
This must be the reception desk, right?
(He's here with the napa cabage.)
I brought the napa cabage.
Am I the first one to arrive? I see.
(What would be his advantage?)
(Nice, I'm first.)
(It's good that I'm first,)
(but I think I came too early.)
(Time passes.)
I'm bored.
(Who's the second one to arrive?)
Napa cabbage is really expensive nowadays.
What is this?
- Hello, Hae Jin. - Hey.
(They arrived 1st and 2nd.)
Good to see you.
- It's been so long. - Yes.
Did you bring the napa cabbage?
Of course.
I brought one, too.
- You even cleaned it. - I did.
Look how clean that is.
That shows part of his character, you know?
He got it all clean and wrapped up.
(Same last name, different napa cabbages.)
The price of napa cabbage has gone up.
Hello.
- Hello. - Hey.
You're here already?
Yes, I am.
You've got love written all over you.
(Kwang Soo is the third person to arrive with napa cabbage.)
(A black vehicle pulls over.)
(It's Lee Joon, actor and idol singer.)
(He's as good of an actor as he is a dancer.)
- Hello. - Hey, Joon.
Good to see you.
I see you've got your napa cabbage.
Wait a minute. That's just ordinary cabbage.
It's Chinese cabbage.
I see. I didn't know there was cabbage like that.
It's the same one you brought.
How would you know when your mum does groceries for you?
- You're such a mummy's boy. - I'm not.
Gosh, aren't you too old for that?
(Someone comes running in.)
Napa cabbage.
- Hello. - Hello.
(She's startled.)
- Hello. - Is he someone you should avoid?
Did you borrow money from him?
I was really surprised to see him here.
(You didn't have to be that surprised.)
Hello.
(Her crystal clear skin is just a bonus to her good acting.)
(It's Lim Ji Yeon.)
(Is she playing American football with that napa cabbage?)
- Hello. - Hey, Ji Yeon.
- Ji Yeon is here. - Hey, Ji Yeon.
Hello.
(Who's next?)
(It's Jo Yoon Hee.)
(She's lovely and pure like the autumn sky.)
(She picked her own napa cabbage at the market.)
Is that Seok Jin?
- Hello. - I know who that is.
(He just grabs the flag.)
Did you bring your napa cabbage?
Gary's here.
- Hey, Gary. - It's Gary.
Hello.
(Jong Kook is the last one to arrive.)
- Gosh. - What?
- Can you quiet down? - Hello.
(What mission will they be carrying out today?)
It's been so long since Hae Jin was here in the show.
- That's right. - I'm a big fan.
- We missed you so much. - How long has it been?
I think it's been almost three years.
You came on the show three years ago.
It's been too long.
It really has. Joon, it's nice to see you, too.
- He's more of an actor now. - He is.
Kwang Soo has been...
very jealous of you.
What are you talking about?
Joon is Kwang Soo's role model.
He's not my role model.
- I like him and all, but... - Kwang Soo used to be an actor,
but he made a debut as a fish.
- What are you talking about? - It's all over television.
I'm a human being.
He made a debut as a fish.
- He's half human and half fish. - That's what I said.
Gosh, you're unbelievable.
Now that you're all here,
people who got the correct answer were given 10 dollars each.
The person who came first will get special benefits.
(Special benefits are waiting for Hae Jin.)
- What about all the rest of us? - Who's first?
- Who came in first? - Let me finish.
The team who came in early will share the benefits with him.
Are we sitting in the order we arrived?
We divided you into teams in the order of your arrival.
From 1st to 4th place are in the same team.
- Are we a team with only guys? - Wait a minute.
(He expresses outrage.)
Give us at least one of the girls.
Are you kidding me?
Is Seok Jin with the three of them?
- Is this the team? - That's it?
From 5th to 8th place are on the same team.
- From 5th to 8th? - Are you serious?
- Are they on the same team? - This is ridiculous.
- Are you serious? - I finally got what I deserve.
At least one the women should join our team.
- This isn't fair. - I shouldn't have worn this shirt.
Gosh.
(This team is pretty upset as well.)
We prepared a game where you can win to switch team members.
- Thank goodness. - I see.
We thank you all for coming.
You must be hungry. We'll be going to get some food.
- I see? - You're feeding us?
- Behind the door, - Are you serious?
there is a buffet for you.
- Follow me, Princesses. - Let's go.
- Princesses? - Come with me.
(What's waiting for them behind those doors?)
What's all this?
- He wasn't kidding. - It's a buffet.
(There are all sorts of food lined up for them.)
Is this for real?
- Don't dig in just yet. - There's so much food.
(We have fresh vegetables and delicious meat.)
(It's a full course menu.)
- We should start eating. - What are we waiting for?
- Look at all that. - Can we eat?
Are we allowed to eat?
They're not going to tell us anything.
I'm going with brown rice for my health.
Do we have to pay for the food later?
- I wanted to eat that one. - You guys should choose.
I think I'll have some frozen pollock jeon.
- Is there frozen pollock jeon? - Yes.
I think I'll have some noodles as well.
- I want some, too. - What's this?
- I think it's buckwheat noodles. - Can't I?
Take a seat.
- Can you eat all that? - Where's orange juice?
I got too ambitious.
Do you want some orange juice?
I think I want milk.
Can we get started? I got too much.
Are you not going to let us eat them?
Come here, Love.
- I'm coming. - Come over here.
KBS has Choo Sa Rang and we have...
- Come here, Sa Rang. - I said I'm coming.
He's Lee Sa Rang.
- Can we start? - Look at what Kwang Soo got.
- Are you all ready to eat? - Yes.
Before you begin, we'll be holding an inspection.
- Come in. - What inspection?
- What's this? - What's going on?
What are you doing?
What's going on?
(He's shocked.)
- What's going on? - Why are you taking it away?
What's going on?
Ji Yeon didn't even take much food.
She only has seaweed soup left.
Look how sad she is.
What are you doing?
Why are you taking the food away from us?
- What's going on? - I don't have anything left.
Who said you could do that?
You took away almost everything.
- What's going on? - I don't have any food left.
(On what basis are they taking away food from the members?)
Hae Jin came in first and he has less food than me.
(Where did all the food go?)
What's going on here?
(Why are they taking away my food?)
Today is Hangeul Day Special. It's called Acquire the Consonants.
(Acquire the Consonants)
- Acquire the Consonants? - Consonants?
There are a total of 14 consonants in the Korean language.
The team who collects all 14 of them first,
will get benefits that will help you in the final battle.
The consonants that you can start working with...
are the ones that are composing the team members' names.
(They're only allowed to work with the consonants of their names.)
What?
For instance, Jae Seok has the consonants, J, S and G.
- J? - J, S and G.
The Y in Yu is a vowel.
The food you are allowed to eat...
are the ones that have names consisted of your names' consonants.
- What about the brown rice? - I have sashimi.
- I have salmon. - I don't get it.
The reason for that is because...
Hae Jin brought napa cabbage.
- He got B and Ch as a bonus. - I see.
- So we're allowed to take a bus? - Exactly.
What about us? The only word we can make up is a sedan chair.
- We can do horse. - You can do horse.
- Cow. - Cow?
Do the consonants change when we switch members?
Yes, you will be able to make more combinations.
Enjoy your food.
Are you kidding me?
(They're complaining.)
We need as many consonants as we can get.
Do I have to eat this?
Do you know what kind of food he's used to eating?
(Sashimi is all he got left.)
Gosh, this isn't going down easily.
- I need rice. - I never had brown rice on its own.
It must be very delicious.
Let's get changed...
and get to the place for the first mission.
- Let's go. - Gosh.
(This is their last chance to switch members.)
- What is all this? - Are those microphones?
- It's this way. - They're microphones.
This game is called "Guess the Word".
- "Guess the Word"? - Yes.
To celebrate Hangeul Day, we prepared a quiz about Hangeul.
Two of the team members have to form the letter with their bodies...
when the staff members show you the letter.
So that's how you do it?
The other members have to guess the correct answer.
- All right. - Yes?
- Joon majored in modern dance. - That's right.
- I remember it now. - He knows how to express with body.
So I think it is a good idea for Hae Jin and Joon to make letters.
(Actor Lee Joon and Yu Hae Jin will make a great team.)
- So why don't you two make letters? - That sounds okay.
- Who should do it? - I will.
Okay. We will make letters together.
- I'll make letters with Yoon Hee. - All right, then.
- Okay. - Let's switch after a few turns.
We're not going to change any of our members with them anyway.
- We won't. - We won't even if you beg us.
- We don't want to be on your team. - We don't need any of you.
We didn't even consider changing members with you.
I knew Joon was handsome, but he seems more handsome with you around.
- Do you mean Hae Jin is ugly? - Yes. How about him?
(Is that what you really meant?)
Tell me. Are you saying that Hae Jin is ugly?
I like him personally, but what I really meant is...
Jae Suk, are you trying to say that I look ugly?
- That's what he meant, not me. - Are you sure? I don't think so.
- Don't say such bad things to him. - Stop it, Jae Seok.
- Do we have to make one letter? - Here comes the first question.
Please choose the word with the following meaning.
How do you call the answer, spoken without any regard or concern?
- Yes? Without what? - Without any regard or...
- What? - Without any regard or...
- Oh, you meant regard. - Yes, he said regard.
(It's like talking to a brick wall.)
- Yes, that's right. - Yes. Without any regard.
"Let's see..."
"Splash, splash".
"Splash?"
How do you call the answer, spoken without any regard or concern?
Number one, a needless answer.
Number two, a back answer.
Number three, a wrong answer.
Number four, an indifferent answer.
Here comes the letter.
(The answer, spoken without any regard or concern)
- In 3, 2, 1. - Gyu. We have to make gyu.
(Muddling)
- Please call out your letter. - Hurry. Climb up and make G.
- Yes. That's it. - Gyu.
(That doesn't look like G at all, does it?)
- Gyu. Here is gyu. - Gosh. What are they doing?
- Gyu? How can we make gyu? - Clime up on me. Hurry.
(They don't know what to do.)
- What are they doing? - Okay. Climb up on me first.
Climb up on me and make G like this.
- This is gyu. - Look at Jong Kook.
- Yes. That's it. - What are they doing?
- Hurry. Climb up on me. - Gyu. We made gyu.
Here. Here is our gyu.
(That's a proper gyu.)
(Green Team successfully makes their letter.)
- Gosh. - Yes. That's it.
- How can't you even do one thing? - Should we make it like this?
(They still don't have any idea to make gyu.)
- Is that gyu? Really? - You two, come out.
- Hey, come out. Let's change. - Hold on a minute.
- Here. You should turn here. - Number two, a back answer.
(Number 2 is incorrect.)
- It's not? - Gyu. Here.
- Gyu. Here is our gyu. - No way.
We accept the answer only if we can read it on our side.
(That's a proper gyu.)
- Ji Hyo. That's the opposite. - That's right.
(Blue team successfully makes the letter.)
Okay. The answer is number three, a wrong answer.
- No, it's not. - It's the wrong answer.
(Gosh, what was that?)
- What a surprise. - Hurry up.
- Look. They made it. - The answer must be number four.
(Red Team made the letter properly.)
It's number four, an indifferent answer.
(Is it the correct answer?)
- It's number four. - An indifferent answer.
(Number 4 is correct.)
- What was the answer? - An indifferent answer.
- An indifferent answer? Really? - Ji Yeon is a master.
The word "indifferent" must mean unconcerned or something similar.
I haven't seen anyone dancing like her for a long time.
(She dances when she gets the correct answer.)
- I haven't seen such a thing. - That's so old-fashioned.
(She dances like someone from the 80's.)
Ji Yeon is really amazing.
- Okay. - Their questions are quite simple.
All right, you two should come out. Let us do it instead.
- Shall we? - Yes. Let's go.
- Okay. - They were really bad last time.
- Let them give one more try. - No, we shall do it.
What is the proper Korean alternative word for "tough guy"?
- Kim Jong Kook. - It must be Kim Jong Kook.
- I think I know the answer. - Kim Jong Kook sounds correct.
Number one, wild man.
Number two, strong man.
Number three, nice guy.
- Number 4, cheerful man. - I think it's number 4.
- Do you know the answer? - One, two, three.
- Isn't it number four? - Make mu.
(They were really confident, but now they look totally confused.)
- Mu? How can we make mu? - That's right. Yoon Hee did it.
- Hold on a minute. - Climb up on me. Hurry.
- Here. We did it. - How should we make it?
(They are totally confused.)
(They are creating a new Hangeul on Hangeul Day.)
- They did it. - Grab my hands.
- Wait. Was it mu? - Yes. Mu.
- It's mu. - Hurry up.
- Climb up on me. Quickly. - Hold on a second, Hae Jin.
- Hurry. We have the answer already. - What should I do?
What do you want me to do?
(What are you doing?)
(Why are you lying down?)
- Look. - You must make Mu.
- Make a square first. - We're just going the harder way.
- That's not Mu. - Gosh.
(That is unreadable.)
(I don't know what's going on.)
(Kwang Soo gives them a hint.)
- You need a square. - Make a square with your hands.
- Come on. Just make a square. - Like this?
(That's a proper Mu.)
- Like this? - Yes. That's how you do it.
- You made Mu. - This is how you do it.
- Number 3, nice guy. - Number 3, nice guy.
(What is the proper Korean alternative word for "tough guy"?)
- I don't think that's correct. - You said number three, nice guy.
- Nice. - Good job.
(Falling down)
- Joon, are you all right? - What's wrong with you?
- Good job. - That was nice.
- That was really close. - Here comes the next question.
Among the underlined words...
Where are the underlined words?
- Where are the words? - Here, right over here.
That was really straightforward.
- Yes, he is. - You should give us the paper...
- and show us the underlined words. - That's right.
- Yes, it makes sense. - You shouldn't read them like that.
If you underlined the words, you should show them instead.
You make me curious. I'd love to see them with my own eyes.
- "Let's see..." - "Splash, splash".
- "Splash, splash". - "Splash".
Okay. I will make the question simple.
Which one of the following words is not influenced by Japanese?
- Number one, autumnal colours. - Autumnal colours?
Number two, secret promise.
- What was that? - Secret promise.
Number three, playing matchmaker.
Number four, introductory remark.
- Which one of the following... - All right.
- Hurry up. Make the letter. - Everyone saw you.
(Ha is easy to make. Which team will make the letter first?)
- Hey. It's not hard at all. - Come on. Stand here.
- Stand here, Hae Jin. - Ji Hyo, you're making the vowel.
- We made it. We did. - Yes.
- Here. - Okay.
- We're the first, aren't we? - How did they make it?
(Red Team makes the letter successfully.)
It's not fair.
- Number two, secret promise. - Secret promise.
(Which one of the following words is not influenced by Japanese?)
- Yes. - Nice.
- Yes. - Really? Is it the correct answer?
(Did we really get the correct answer?)
Now, Red Team can switch members with other teams.
All right. What should we do?
(Red Team has a chance to switch members with other teams.)
Hey. What are you doing?
(Seok Jin is completely isolated.)
- They are harsh. - Hey. What are you doing?
- What should we do now? - Are you kicking him out?
All right. We will trade you with Jong Kook.
(Do you really want to send me away?)
- Ji Hyo, don't do it. - That's too much.
- Why? What's wrong? - How can you do that?
- What's the matter? - You made up your mind, didn't you?
It's better for Jong Kook to join her team for sure.
(Jong Kook and Seok Jin change their team.)
- This isn't right. - Am I in the same team with them?
Our team is the worst. Even the colour of our clothes is gloomy.
- The three worst guys are together. - This is the worst team ever.
Use your consonants however you can...
and find all 14 consonants to end the mission.
Okay. Let's go.
(The mission ends if any one of the teams collect all consonants.)
Should we head to Tongin-dong first?
- Okay. - How should we go there?
- Let's go there by car. - Yes. Any car will do.
- We can take a van. - You're right. We can take a van.
We will get there by van.
(Nice Van)
- We have an amazing idea. - What is it?
- Yes. - We're going to call Julie.
- She's your manager. - Yes, that's Julie.
So we're going to call Julie.
(Call Julie for Help)
How about you? How will you go?
- We will... - We have J, G and E,
- so we will go there by our car. - Our own car.
- I see. - That's nice.
How about us? Can't we do the same?
(They are trying their best to combine letters.)
I haven't heard the word since I was a young kid.
The name of my manager is Kang Sang Seon,
so we will take Sang Seon's car.
- Private car sounds terrific. - Yes. Private car.
(Sang Seon's Car)
We need to find L as fast as we can.
- Why? - To see Sa Rang.
(We need to see Sa Rang for Kwang Soo.)
- Why would we meet her? - To ride her car?
- Yes. To ride Sa Rang's car. - That sounds lovely.
Come on. I'm 32 years old.
- All right. Can we leave now? - Yes.
- Okay. Let's go. - Let's go.
It's really nice to go there by this nice van.
- There are so many stuffs here. - Really?
- Ji Hyo, I'm sorry to say this, - Yes.
but I could smell cigarettes as soon as I got in.
Do you know why?
Because my managers smoke here quite often.
Your managers? I see.
- I can see pictures on the map. - What are they for?
- This one must be about singing. - Yes. Singing.
- There are some hints. - The 10-dollar bill.
- I see. - Where are we heading?
There's a place with the 10-dollar bill, and another with a microphone.
- There's a place with food, too. - This place is about food.
Do you want to go to the spot with food first?
- No, I'm fine. - Why not?
- I'm totally fine. - Sir,
- because Yoon Hee is hungry, - No, I'm not.
- No. I mean it. - let's go to Tongin-dong first.
- Stop it. Don't. - She surely wants to eat something.
(She stared at Jong Kook when she mentioned the word, "food".)
- Yoon Hee must be really hungry. - No, Jong Kook.
I'm not. I mean it.
- We should just follow our plan. - She glared at me.
- Let's go to Tongin-dong. - We should go there first.
It must be Tongin Market.
We should go there first because Hae Jin lives near the place.
Yes. He must know the place well.
Yes, a bit.
Hae Jin, wasn't your tone really funny just now?
- Yes, that's right. - Now that you mention, I get it.
- Your tone is very unique... - You speak in that tone very often.
Every time people imitated me, I didn't know I talk in such a way.
"Let me see..."
You...
- You just did it. - Seeing you imitating me...
- You just did it. - I didn't know...
if I really talked in such a tone.
Really? Actually, you do.
I think so, too.
How did you know the names of all the idol group members?
- Did you memorise them? - No, I didn't.
They had name tags and I knew some of them.
- You read a lot of news articles. - You...
- Do you know all of them? - Of course not.
That's impossible.
When I was a trainee...
Were you ever a trainee?
(Hae Jin's sad history: I practised really hard when I was a trainee.)
Hae Jin, were you really a trainee?
I received acting training when I was young.
It's when you were training.
I was really confused.
- I was still a trainee, though. - You're right.
- That's true. - Yes.
I trained in something anyway.
I was pretty startled when you said that.
I wondered what kind of idol group it would've been.
Hae Jin also used to be a trainee.
I was still a trainee.
(Hae Jin would've been a great idol member.)
- So you're still a trainee. - That's right.
We get it now.
Let's get off.
(SSJ)
- Let's get off. - Okay.
(What will they do in this market?)
- We're in Tongin Market right now. - Okay.
You must eat food worth 10 dollars.
- 10 dollars? - Look at her.
Is this really a mission? It's too easy.
But you shouldn't eat just one type of food.
- You can buy only one serving. - Can we buy bread?
- You can't buy bread. - You can't buy that.
- I can't? - No.
- Fish cake... - Fish cake.
- Gyoza. - Okay.
- Naengmyun. - Naengmyun.
We can also eat that.
We can also eat guksu.
- That's right. - Guksu.
We have more choices than I thought.
There's nothing we can eat.
Do we have to only eat food with these consonants?
- Right. - We can eat snacks.
- Good. - Snacks.
- Cold rice. - Cold rice?
Cold rice...
- I want something tasty. - What about spinach?
- Spinach. - Spinach.
There's a lot of delicious food here.
- Hae Jin, let's go first. - Let's get going.
- We never know what we'll find... - Wait!
- Yakgwa. - Yakgwa!
- Okay. - Yakgwa is here.
- Yakgwa... - Hello, do you have...
Ma'am, do you have a smaller pack of yakgwa?
Here.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
- Hae Jin, let's eat. - Good.
- It's yakgwa. - I like this a lot.
- Right. I like it, too. - It is very tasty.
- It's delicious. - Let's eat yakgwa first...
- and then some laver next. - Laver?
Isn't it a little weird?
- Let's go see what else they sell. - Okay.
- Let's eat fish cake first. - Fish cake.
- 10 dollars' worth of fish cake. - I think that'd be really easy.
One skewer is one serving.
Isn't it too small?
Let's start eating.
Thank you for giving us one more fish cake, Ma'am.
(The faster they eat, the more advantage they'll get.)
We just ate fish cake.
- Don't you want some jeon? - I want to eat jeon, too.
- Jeon. - They have jeon.
- Do you have meat jeon? - We do.
- It's here. - Please give us one serving.
- Just one serving. - Let's have sikhye.
(Green Team)
Is it tasty?
(Green Team now has 7 dollars left.)
(Blue Team has 3 dollars and Red Team has 4 dollars left.)
Hey.
What should we eat next?
Let's drink sikhye.
(Red Team's consonants are G, N, M, S, Y, J and H.)
How much is sikhye?
- It's one dollar. - Let's eat gangjeong.
Did we spend 10 dollars?
- We should buy this first. - Not yet.
Good.
- We spent all 10 dollars. - We did.
You cleared the mission.
Which one should we choose?
- What about L? - That's not bad.
- I want D or L. - I think L or Ch would be good.
- Ch? - I like L.
(Which one should we choose in order to win the round?)
- If we choose Ch... - Let's choose D.
"Tea" is the only option if we choose Ch.
- Let's select D. - D?
- Let's choose D. - D?
We'll select D, then.
Please give it to us.
(Red Team earns D.)
You succeeded your mission.
Now, you can get an attacking card.
(They get a letter and an attacking card.)
There are different kinds of attacking card.
The Looting Card allows you to take another team's consonant.
If you choose Consonant Card,
you can get an extra consonant.
If you choose Stealing Card,
one of you will become a thief. If the thief removes...
someone else's name tag, he or she can get pick a consonant to take.
You might also draw Better Luck Next Time.
- Okay. - There's Better Luck Next Time?
Let's draw.
- Yoon Hee... - Who'll draw?
- Anyone. - Ji Yeon, please.
(Ji Yeon draws a card.)
(Nervous)
Let's open it.
Are you usually lucky?
- I'm not bad. - Okay.
Let's open it, then.
(Attacking cards are very important for the final round.)
(Let's see which card she picked.)
Let's open it.
(Stealing Card)
I got Stealing Card.
(Red Team's first attacking card is Stealing Card.)
What is this?
- It's... - We should remove a name tag.
Then do we gain all the consonants?
You can pick one of the consonants.
Only if you remove a name tag.
(Great!)
- We must meet with others, then. - Right.
(Wait for us. We'll coming to steal your consonant.)
(Which team would fall victim to them?)
- Here's your sikhye. - Thank you.
- Thank you. - It's delicious.
- When is the final round? - It's really tasty.
- This is... - They're over there.
- They're right there. - Where?
- Just choose anyone. - They've completed their mission.
- Let's choose anyone. - Why don't you just go remove...
- They might do the same to us. - Do we just remove the name tag?
They might have the same card.
(They finally meet their opponent.)
- I will go... - They're here!
- What are you doing here? - Did you clear your mission?
- Everyone is here. - Did you complete the mission?
- Did you complete your mission? - Of course.
- Really? - Do you want some gangjeong?
- Did you have all the consonants? - Yes.
Do you want to try some?
(They're completely entrapped.)
- Is it good? - I want some, too.
- Did you spend all your money? - Did you clear your mission?
- We did. - Then don't you have...
- to do something? - We just completed.
- Don't you have to do something? - We just completed.
- There's corn. - Do you want some gangjeong?
- Are we having dinner now? - Sorry?
- It is... - We're having dinner now.
(We need to be quick.)
Do you want some?
Chicken gangjeong?
(There's only one chance.)
(Ji Yeon is in action.)
(She's looking for a chance.)
Chicken gangjeong...
- I got it! - What was that?
- What happened? - What is going on?
What was that? What?
(Ji Yeon successfully distracted them with food.)
- What's going on? - Hold on.
If you have the Stealing Card, you can get a consonant...
if you remove a name tag.
Gosh. That's why you gave us corn...
and chicken gangjeong.
You're too mean.
Which consonant should we choose?
What about L?
Here's your L.
Gosh, I never knew you'd be this mean to us.
That was really harsh.
Blue Team, you cleared your mission.
Tell us a consonant you want.
- Okay. - Which one should we pick?
- I think L would be good. - We'll choose L, then.
What about D?
- Among these consonants... - I think D will be very helpful.
You're right.
- Let's pick D. - Okay. Please give us D.
D?
- There are five cards. - Just pick one.
- Just avoid Better Luck Next Time. - We have five attacking cards.
- Please choose one. - Pick one.
Okay.
(Let's see which card Blue Team obtained.)
- What is it? - Stealing Card!
What is it?
(Blue Team also got the Stealing Card.)
- Stealing Card. - We got the same card.
It's the same card.
- We need to remove a name tag. - Go remove a name tag.
- Let's go now. - An opponent's?
Let's go.
Sweet pumpkin sikhye.
They also have fruit juice.
- We have to finish this at once. - At once.
It's hard to finish the mission at once.
- What are you doing here? - We're...
(Jae Seok removes Gary's name tag.)
- What was that? - It's okay.
Isn't it cheating?
You're not out. We had to do this to use this card.
So he's not out?
- Did you already clear the mission? - We did.
- Really? - We know you're joking.
No, it's the truth.
- No. - What are you doing?
You don't have to remove our name tags.
- You're so ill-mannered. - That's true.
We eliminated yours only because it was our mission.
- Let's pick M. - Please give us M.
You want M? Here you go.
It's not "Em" in "Emily" but the letter M.
(What a lame joke.)
- My goodness. - We're done for.
- We collected most of them. - We have four more to go.
(Blue Team needs four more consonants.)
- We have a long way to go. - What about...
- M? - That's not a bad idea.
- Y would be also good. - Let's choose M or Y.
- What do you think? - I think Y would be good.
- We'll need Y. - We want Y.
It's the most commonly used consonant.
- We got Y. - Good
- You shouldn't pick the card. - Let's do rock-paper-scissors.
- Rock-paper... - You can pick.
I'm luckier than you two.
(Luckier Gary chooses a card.)
I want the one in the middle.
- Gosh. - Don't open it!
- Looting Card! - This is a good one.
- It's a good one. - Do we have to remove a name card?
Do we just take a consonant?
These are the consonants the other teams have.
Let's take Red Team's M.
- Okay. Red Team has a lot. - Let's take it from Red Team.
- M. - Let's take M.
- We want Red Team's M! - We want Red Team's M!
- Okay. - We did great.
- High-five. - We have good teamwork.
- My goodness. - We're doing wonderful.
Hold on. Green Team used...
their chance card...
and took M from you.
- They took ours away? - Yes.
- They had the Looting Card. - Yes, they did.
- This is unbelievable. - Green Team used...
the Looting Card and took your M.
If they took our M...
(She's shaking her hand.)
Why did they take ours?
Does it mean Blue Team doesn't have M?
(Red Team loses M.)
Then...
(What mission will they do here?)
Hangeul...
What should we do here?
(Karaoke and jump ropes?)
The mission you'll do here is "Hop and Sing".
- "Hop and Sing"? - What is that?
I'll explain. You'll choose...
a song first and pick a consonant.
When the lyrics contain that consonant, you should jump.
- Which one should we choose? - Choose a song...
that's not difficult to sing.
How about "Rotating, Rotating, Rotating"?
- "Rotating, Rotating, Rotating"? - That's a good one.
It's fine as long as you don't pick D or K.
That's right.
Just don't pick those.
- Shall I start? - Yes.
- Is it D? - It's game over if it's D.
It's fine as long as it's not D or K.
(Let's avoid D and K.)
- It's J. - It's J.
(He picks J.)
- Shall I try jumping the rope once? - Okay.
- Okay. - That's good.
That's right.
Do you want the rope to go over you?
There's one J in the second phrase.
(J appears at the start.)
- "When the sun sets". - Shall we move the rope over him?
When the sun sets
The moon appears in the sky
The sun rises again
Flowers bloom
- Flowers bloom - Flowers bloom
Birds fly
They move
- They move - You must jump here.
(After losing their concentration, they're suddenly in a rush.)
(He gets hit.)
Goodness.
You should have jumped.
(They don't know what to do.)
Goodness.
- Why were you singing along? - I'm sorry.
- Again, rotating - Again, rotating
Rotating
- Rotating - Rotating
Everyone, sing along.
- Rotating like dancing - Rotating like dancing
Is it over?
What's the score?
(Blue Team made three mistakes.)
(They must score a minimum of 93 points.)
- What's the score? - It's 95.
We did it.
- What's the perfect score? - We lost one point.
We lost three points.
- What's the score? - Your score is 92 points.
You made it.
(Blue Team succeeds.)
By the way,
he didn't sing that well.
- He didn't sing that well. - I'm also surprised.
I think I sang quite well.
You didn't deserve 95 points.
I hardly score as high as 95 points.
I usually score 98 points, so I wondered what happened.
I wondered why I only scored 95 points.
My goodness.
Let's go with L.
This is going too smoothly.
I'll pick one.
Everything is fine except Better Luck Next Time.
Let's take a look.
- It's Consonant Card. - It's Consonant Card.
- This is amazing. - We can just acquire one.
- Do we acquire one for free? - Let's get K.
We have to get two more consonants.
- K? - What's this?
- What do we do? - We have to get two more.
- Things are going too smoothly. - They're going way too smoothly.
I'm anxious because things are going too well.
How can things go this smoothly?
We're almost done with the game.
- What else can we do? - Is it almost over for us?
What's going on?
(Consonants the teams have acquired)
It's Friend Chance.
Pick one of these questions.
You can acquire the first consonant of the person's answer.
- I see. - Wait.
We need to acquire K, so we need an answer such as "curry".
Pick the question.
Which consonants do we need?
What do you think of when you look at me?
- What's this? - One of my songs goes,
I want to eat curry
subtitles ripped and synced by riri13
Trust me this once.
- Okay, you do it. - I'll call Skull.
You'll do well.
(He calls Skull.)
- Hey, man. - Hey, man.
- Hello. - Hey, number one singer in Jamaica.
When I ask you...
a question, please answer it.
- It's a quiz. - Is this what it is?
The melody goes like this.
I want to eat something today
Here's my question.
What reminds you the most when you look at me?
(The dice is thrown.)
(No, the curry is thrown.)
Curry.
(Green Team succeeds.)
This is amazing.
Number one singer in Jamaica.
You acquired K.
What's going on with us?
Things are going too smoothly.
No one stole anything from us today, either.
No one is stealing.
What's this?
(What's the mission prepared on the rooftop of a building?)
- What's this? - A microscope?
"The 10-Dollar Mystery".
Four syllabi that disappeared.
Among the 28 letters created by King Sejong, you must find 4 letters...
that disappeared on the 10-dollar bill.
I see.
By using the consonants that you've acquired so far...
and by using the tools that are given to you,
find four letters that are hidden on the 10-dollar bill.
There's no time limit.
While one member stays in a squat position,
the rest of the members have to look for the four letters.
We can use our mobile phones.
We can use them?
- Yes. - We can use all of them.
Magnifying glass is better, Hae Jin.
You're right.
- May I start? - Get ready.
Start.
They're here at the bottom.
- Where at the bottom? - Right here.
I don't think I can last long.
(He laughs.)
This is actually hard.
(Their look is strong enough to pierce the 10-dollar bill.)
This is quite difficult.
I can't see anything with the binoculars.
I don't think I can hold it for 30 minutes.
You can't?
- Maybe for 15 minutes. - Wait a little.
How do I find them through the binoculars?
You said you'll hold it for 30 minutes.
I can't even hold it for five minutes.
It's really difficult.
(He realises it too late and regrets it.)
Give us a little more time.
(It doesn't seem easy to solve.)
- Why is it so hard? - Gosh.
Goodness.
Did you hide them?
- That's the original bill. - Really?
This is great.
This is amazing.
- I can see it clearly with this. - You're right.
- It's magnified by that much? - Yes.
Kwang Soo, this is the best to use. Look.
(Joon is almost dying.)
(Goodness)
This is incredible.
Are you done yet?
We're almost there.
These look like...
(Please hurry and find them.)
- Hello. - Hello.
This is "Hop and Sing".
Who jumps the rope?
The person who sings will jump the rope.
(In that case...)
- You do it. - Should I sing?
- I don't want to sing. - You should still do it.
Shouldn't someone else do it?
The person who sings well and has strength should do it.
(That person is Jong Kook.)
Is it me?
(He accepts the reality of the situation.)
Are we really on the same team?
I feel like I'm serving them today.
(He seems like a servant serving three ladies.)
Why don't you do it, Yoon Hee?
- What song should I sing? - Go ahead, Yoon Hee.
Why don't I sing "Before Sadness Comes"?
- It's easy to sing. - That sounds good.
- I'm scared. - What is it?
- It's D. - There will a lot of those.
There're going to be a lot in the lyrics.
There will be a lot of them in the lyrics.
What if the first word starts with a D?
- There it is. - There's already a D.
- Sing loudly. - Go.
Whenever I think of you
The last syllable.
- The last one. - That's right.
- You always seem close yet so far - There's another one.
Here it comes.
When we meet, you say you love me
- Here comes another one. - Go.
Move the rope this way.
When we part, I predict something sad
(Red Team made five mistakes.)
- It's over. - The end.
(They must score a minimum of 95 points.)
Goodness.
- You should sing once. - I don't want to.
- Do you want to sing? - Why don't you sing, Ji Hyo?
You should sing since you're brave, Ji Hyo.
I'd like to sing "Sunset Glow" by Lee Moon Se.
I'll pick one.
I'll pick a really good one.
Wait and see.
Can you please avoid B?
(Please avoid B for this song.)
It's B.
(He picks B.)
Goodness.
(Why did he pick B of all consonants?)
- Get ready. - It starts with a B.
- When I look at the sunset glow - The sunset glow
Jump at the end.
It reminds me of your sad face
I call out your name
- Only the silent sunset glows - Only the silent sunset glows
- Did she make it? - She did.
- The score has to be over 90. - Is that possible?
You lost nine points from your mistakes.
(Did she make nine mistakes?)
- I can't tell you - That one is okay.
(She forgot about the consonants after the vowels.)
Only the silent sunset glows
- You missed the ones after vowels. - That's right.
(If she made nine mistakes...)
I don't think we succeeded this time.
(The score has to be a minimum of 99 points.)
- The score is... - It's 100 points.
(Ji Hyo scores 100 points.)
I sang badly but still scored 100.
She was completely out of tune.
- The final score is over 90 points? - How is this possible?
- Anyway, we made it. - We did.
- You're good. - Good job.
We did it.
You can take a consonant you'd like.
- We'd like to acquire P. - Okay.
(Consonants Red Team acquired)
- Are you being punished? - I'm so sorry.
(Blue Team fails due to Green Team's interruption.)
Get ready, set, go.
Are they hidden somewhere here?
(They're about to pierce the 10-dollar bill.)
How do we find four of them?
I know the answer.
Did you find them?
(Already?)
(Here they are.)
- Kwang Soo, correct. - Okay!
- Did you find them? - Did you?
He found them. How did he find them?
Are they really in here?
Kwang Soo, you did a good job.
We'll take P and choose a card.
Who wants to pick?
- You may finish the game with this. - We have almost all.
- I'm not very lucky with this. - Hae Jin.
- Yes. - Pick a card, please.
Shall I?
- We're doing really well. - You may make us win this game.
If you pick the Consonant Card, the game is over.
- Do you think I'll pick that card? - Yes.
You should just avoid Better Luck Next Time.
This is awesome.
(Let's see how lucky Hae Jin is.)
Let me see.
(He's disappointed.)
Please show us.
Please show us. What did he pick?
It's Better Luck Next Time.
(He can't believe it.)
Are you sure?
Isn't it Better Luck "This" Time?
(Hae Jin proved to be unlucky as well.)
- He chose the wrong one. - What happens then?
- You picked Better Luck Next Time. - What happens now?
Why are you so happy?
I'm glad that you have two unlucky guys.
We just have one consonant left.
We could have skipped the next place.
It would've been nice if we obtained a consonant.
(Blue Team is much closer to victory.)
I wish we had the Consonant Card...
or any other cards.
(Staff runs towards Blue Team.)
(Knocking)
- They're not the culprits. - They aren't?
Another team took Ch from you with the Looting Card.
You can't use the car.
- What? - Excuse me?
(They have to get off the car.)
- They're so mean. - We can't use the car?
- Should we get off? - Yes.
- Gosh. - All of a sudden?
- I'm getting upset. - This is ridiculous.
- Me too. - Goodness.
But we were already in the car.
You're not robbers or something.
(What has happened?)
Can they really kick us out of the car?
(A minute ago)
(Green Team passed "The 10-Dollar Mystery" and picked a card.)
(Looting Card)
Target the team with the most.
- One, two, three. - Ch!
They are mean.
(They feel robbed.)
- Shall we take a taxi? - We can't.
- We can't take a taxi. - We don't have T.
Since they took Ch, we can't use a car.
They're bad guys.
(They lost C.)
We need to turn left.
- Are you sure? - Well...
Where is it?
Anguk-dong is far from here.
- Can we take a bus? - Yes, we can.
But it's complicated to go there by bus.
(Sighing)
I don't know what to do.
It's really difficult to get there.
Only if we had Ch.
(Wait, we can use the Friend Chance.)
(You can obtain the first consonant of your friend's answer.)
- "What do I remind you of?" - "What do I remind you of?"
"What do I remind you of?" "Chambada"?
- Who would call me that? - May I call Dong Hwi?
- Yes, call him. - May I?
Call him.
- Hello. - Dong Hwi.
- Hi. Where are you? - I'm shooting Running Man.
(Laughing)
- We have a question for you. - Dong Hwi.
- Hello, Hae Jin. - Hello. How are you?
I'm good.
You know I was...
- shooting on an island. - I know.
They used to call me by a certain nickname.
Gosh, I...
(Dong Hwi, please. We trust you.)
I didn't watch "Three Meals a Day" regularly.
(No way!)
You didn't? Wait a moment.
I'll give you a tip.
What do I remind you of?
You should answer to that question.
(Dong Hwi, please.)
(We desperately need Ch.)
Oh, I see.
Chambada.
(He said it.)
- That's correct. Thank you. - Dong Hwi.
- Thanks. - Thank you.
- Please give us Ch. - Ch?
This was too harsh.
Now, we can take the car again, right?
Thank goodness we got Ch back.
(Number of consonants per team)
(Blue Team is leading.)
(Green Team and Blue Team are near the Gyeongbokgung Palace.)
(Red Team is in Hwa-dong.)
- You are doing so well. - Good job.
We got the Consonant Card.
"Galgaekkun", "kkotjam"...
(If you do a proper role play with three words, it's a success.)
("Galgaekkun", "kkotjam" and "gasibeosi")
Is "galgaekkun" Gary?
- It seems to befit him. - "Galgaekkun"?
"Gasibeosi" sounds like...
Is it a marriage proposal?
- Don't you think it means "sweet"? - Sweet.
- Do you think so? - Don't you think?
Since your voice is "gasibeosi", I can have "kkotjam".
That's so sweet to hear but there is a "galgaekkun" here.
(He used "galgaekkun" correctly.)
I'll disturb you all.
(Do you want a piece of "galgaekkun"?)
- I'll disturb you all. - Is that correct?
It was close but you failed.
- Why? - I'll explain why.
- Maybe we got "kkotjam" wrong. - "Gasibeosi" means...
- "a husband and a wife". - Does it?
"Kkotjam" means "the wedding night".
(They finally realise the meanings.)
How could we guess...
Hae Jin.
(Hey, you.)
- Do you have only one left? - Yes.
We need three.
- We need to hurry then. - We have to finish.
Let's hurry.
What are these words?
I don't know them at all.
What are "sageurangi", "ttukbyeolssi" and "putnat"?
"Putnat" means "a stranger". I think so.
You're right.
"Ttukbyeolssi" is me.
Because "Ttuk" sounds like a grasshopper...
and "byeol" means a star in Korean.
(He's making up the meaning.)
- What's "sageurangi"? - Can I say that word on TV?
Doesn't it mean...
- "Sageurangi". - here?
- Stop it. - But it sounds like that.
That sounds similar to armpit.
That's the crotch.
(Oh, I see.)
Hey, "ttukbyeolssi",
- we're "putnat". - Good.
- How is it? - Do you want to "sageurangi"?
(Laughing)
(It may sound a bit weird, but not too bad.)
- This is it. We're ready. - Okay.
Ready, go.
- Jong Kook... - Is this our last pick?
We're doing the role play.
Are you choosing one of the three?
- What are you doing? We're acting. - You have to choose one?
They're coming again.
(Green Team arrives late.)
- We'll start. - We will.
When it was "kkokkoji", you used to be so cool.
But how do I look now?
You're "bingchungmatda" like a "yeorikkun".
- It's right. - That sounds realistic.
- That sounds offensive. - It's a success.
(Red Team gets it right.)
Great. We made it.
- Pick a card. - Let's do this.
You won't take ours again, will you?
- It's the Consonant Card. - By the way, why...
(Consonant Card)
(Red Team adds K and T.)
We still have to get one more.
(Right. There is the Friend Chance.)
(They head to a corner to use the Chance.)
They're finished.
(Finished?)
- We'll start. - We'll take the challenge.
If you succeed this time, you're finished.
- Hi, "ttukbyeolssi". - Hi.
- We're "putnat" but... - Yes.
please lend me a "sageurangi".
(They used the words correctly.)
- A "sageurangi". - You're correct.
(Blue Team succeeds.)
(That was close.)
- Great. - Well...
(Blue Team obtains T and completes all consonants.)
We got T.
(Blue Team will get a big advantage in the final race.)
(National Hangeul Museum)
The final race will be "Bag-Stealing Project".
"Bag-Stealing Project"?
(Bag-Stealing Project)
The last survivor should open a chest located in the final spot...
and take the object that's inside to win.
Each password number is hidden in five bags.
You'll see the bags the moment someone is eliminated.
(Every time you solve a problem, you can erase a consonant.)
Find clue boxes hidden everywhere and solve the problems.
If you get the answer correct,
you can remove a consonant entirely.
So this isn't Name Tag Elimination.
But I only have two syllables.
(Laughing)
- He has only one consonant. - If someone picks H...
Are you kidding?
Is there no tearing today?
When someone is eliminated, you can have a bag.
The person carrying the bag...
is qualified to tear the others' name tags off.
The person carrying the bag?
The person who has all five bags at last...
will be the winner today.
When you remove a consonant,
your team members will lose it too.
I see.
So the consonant is removed from the game entirely.
(What consonants do our members have?)
Let's go to your starting places now.
Okay.
I don't understand how people get it by listening to the rules once.
I don't either.
Everyone seems to understand it, but why can't I?
Is there a consonant that the other teams have but we don't?
M, R... There is R, too.
I can see that Red Team has an advantage.
(He laughs.)
I just had to eat three meals a day before.
(Eating three meals a day was so easy back then.)
I don't quite understand because I just had to eat.
You were able to sing but you can't understand this?
I'd rather pull out weeds.
(There are no weeds or meals but consonants.)
It's so complicated.
- Hae Jin... - What should I do?
In the boxes, there are quizzes...
- Just go around and find them. - You need to find the boxes.
Find the boxes.
- So I just need to find the boxes. - Right.
(I'm not very used to Running Man.)
Blue Team,
you successfully acquired 14 consonants.
Yes, we got all of them.
Here is a huge benefit that's given to you.
(What's the special benefit given to them?)
It's Save a Consonant Card.
(Save a Consonant Card)
Save a Consonant Card?
You must discuss and decide...
which consonant to be eliminated...
only when it's eliminated twice.
Which one do we have the most?
Isn't it J? There's J from Lee Joon.
- Hae Jin. That's right. - Hae Jin.
There's no J in my name.
- The three of us have it. - Let's not choose J.
How about G?
Yu Hae Jin. There's no G.
- Let's decide on J. - Let's think more about it.
- It's because... - We have J the most.
Did you decide on J?
- J is the best choice. - It is.
Okay.
(Won't you respect the opinion of a minority?)
I'm disappointed.
I'll put a curse on them.
Let's go.
Put the name tag on for Yoon Hee.
I'm sorry. Are you okay?
(Who will be the final winner of the race?)
We need to find the box.
(He searches.)
There's a box that's labelled R.
(Hae Jin looks for the box.)
- Are you looking carefully? - Yes.
Don't just walk around.
You must search.
Is it in a box?
(You can eliminate the consonants if you find the box first.)
I bet I'll be eliminated once someone finds it.
Get rid of Y.
Y? Okay. What's going on?
What's going on?
Jae Seok eliminated H.
(His prediction was correct.)
How can this happen as soon as I say it?
(Just a moment ago)
Here it is.
- Here it is. - Did you find it?
(Jae Seok finds the box within a few minutes.)
Choose a Korean word with this meaning.
A shape that became soft after being steamed.
Pusungpusung, hamulhamul.
(Choose which type of food it is and try it.)
Don't people say it's soft and slippery?
- Soft and slippery. - Right.
- I bet it's hamulhamul. - Hamulhamul.
The answer is two.
(Jae Seok chooses number 2.)
(Is hamulhamul the answer?)
- It's delicious. - It's delicious.
(Hamulhamul is the answer.)
(Jae Seok answers correctly.)
Our team is amazing today.
- We're off to a good start. - That was so quick.
- It's perfect. - It's a good start.
(Kwang Soo tried the other food.)
We should go with something we don't have.
Shall we eliminate H?
Why did you eat that?
(Is he torturing himself on purpose?)
How did you put it in this?
What was in it?
It's wasabi.
- Let's eliminate H, Hae Jin. - H?
- We have it, too. - Right.
Are you saying that's better?
We have to eliminate Haha.
- Okay. - It's because...
- we must get the bag. - Okay.
- Are you okay with it? - To get the bag?
Gosh, it's only been...
- five minutes since we started. - It doesn't matter.
- Goodness. - I don't care about that.
H.
- You're the team leader. - I know.
- We still have J left. - Okay.
Jae Seok eliminated H.
- Jae Seok eliminated H. - We have H.
We have H.
Goodness.
Haha is eliminated.
(Laughing)
Goodbye, Haha.
(Haha is eliminated within five minutes.)
(His stage name should have been longer and more complicated.)
Haha is eliminated.
(Laughing)
Gosh, I feel bad for him.
Poor Haha.
It was a bit cruel.
I know, but it couldn't be helped.
Let's look for yours.
There should be a bag.
We must...
find the bag first.
Let's find the bag
Bag, bag
I found it.
(It's a bright box.)
I've heard of norujam before.
- Nabijam? - I mean norujam.
- Norujam? - Yes.
Noru, a roe deer, is an herbivore.
Doesn't it wake up immediately when its predator appears?
Isn't it norujam?
Number one.
(Yoon Hee chooses number 1.)
I should eat some, too.
(What's the type of sleep during which you wake up constantly?)
(Yoon Hee answers correctly.)
What's in the other one?
(She's exactly like Kwang Soo.)
It's wasabi.
We must choose L...
so that we can eliminate them.
- I'll choose L. - L.
Yoon Hee eliminated L.
L?
- Yoon Hee eliminated L. - L? Me?
That's me.
We can get the bag now that we eliminated one person.
- Really? - We must find the bag.
Our team is the target.
(This is what it means when the rich gets richer, the poor gets poorer.)
(His name tag is almost empty.)
- L is eliminated. - Seok Jin.
What do I do?
(Tearing)
What did you do?
(How can he tear off his name tag so suddenly?)
- Did you find it? - What are you doing?
I have to find the bag.
(Kwang Soo was searching for the bag.)
(He looks around.)
Why did she eliminate L?
It was to eliminate Gary.
It's because...
(What's this?)
(Kwang Soo finds the bag.)
Here's the bag.
What's this?
(As he obtained Y, he can tear off name tags.)
I found it.
I can take off any name tags, right?
Our team is the target.
(He finds Seok Jin.)
- L is eliminated. - Seok Jin, what should I do?
(Seok Jin is eliminated.)
What are you doing?
(Goodbye, Seok Jin.)
(Don't take off my name tag.)
(There's a total of 2 bags to be found.)
I haven't even done much today.
Kwang Soo!
(Seok Jin and Haha from Green Team are eliminated.)
(He's planning to eliminate Ji Hyo who has many consonants.)
Hey, hey.
- Gary. - I'm the only one left on the team.
(They run away.)
(He'll catch anyone he can.)
- Is Kwang Soo taking off name tags? - Be careful.
Kwang Soo can take off name tags right now.
Really?
- Where does the elevator lead to? - I can't believe this.
(He changes his target to Yoon Hee.)
Did he take off their name tags?
(Unlike the others, she runs faster than anyone.)
She's so fast.
She's so fast. Wait.
(She runs quickly as if the fire alarm went off.)
Yoon Hee.
(She runs much faster than Kwang Soo.)
Goodness.
(She takes big steps.)
(What will be the result of this chase?)
Someone must have found the bag.
(People are searching for the bag in the library.)
Kwang Soo must have the bag.
(He searches anyway without understanding the rules.)
Hae Jin is quite meticulous.
(He finds a box instead of the bag.)
I found it.
(Goodness)
(How did he find that box?)
Choose a Korean word with this meaning.
(He feels bad for Hae Jin but continues to answer the question.)
"It's awkward and embarrassing."
(Why is being on a variety show so difficult?)
How did he find it? I passed by that spot.
Goodness.
I choose number one.
(Jong Kook chooses number 1.)
(He answers correctly.)
Okay.
That was the correct answer.
(He's still chasing after her.)
(Did something just pass by?)
What's wrong?
I found the bag.
(Really? You found the bag?)
What happens if you find the bag?
(Then what happens?)
Who found it?
Goodness.
(Hae Jin is in a completely different world.)
(Everyone is so good at playing the game.)
(Unlike Hae Jin, they get competitive.)
(Go easy on me. I only have one consonant left.)
Kwang Soo, why are you going easy on Jong Kook?
I'm doing a mission right now.
(He's another one with many consonants.)
- Did you eat it? - Yes.
I'm doing a mission.
Let me finish the mission.
I haven't made my decision yet.
- Let me decide first. - Okay.
- Let me decide first. - I don't think I'll go anywhere.
Never mind. Take your time.
Okay, wait a minute. Do I choose first?
What does Kwang Soo have?
I have a lot left.
(Hae Jin is looking for a box.)
Let me make my decision first.
- Kwang Soo, come on. - It's because I'm excited.
- Give me a second. - Hold still.
Hae Jin!
What? Why?
What do you mean "why"?
What is it?
- What is it? - I'm dying here.
- Hae Jin! - What?
Help me.
What do you want me to do?
What are you talking about? Come over here.
- Help me! - What's wrong?
- Help me! - I choose S.
Jong Kook has removed S.
- It has been removed. - Okay.
Why were you ignoring me?
I didn't know what was going on.
I got caught by Jong Kook.
- Hae Jin can't take them off. - Oh, I get it.
- You want to take his off, right? - Yes.
- I can't do it, though. - What?
He's so much stronger than me.
- Are you giving up just like that? - Hold on.
- Do you see how he's treating me? - Fine, just hold on.
There's nothing in here.
- I can't find anything. - What is it this time?
(The bell rings.)
- Jong Kook has removed S. - S?
- S? - S?
That means...
That's me, then.
(It's not good news.)
Gosh.
(Now, Ji Hyo only has Y and J left.)
(There's something there.)
(Ji Hyo finds a bag.)
I got it.
All right.
"Let me see..."
(She hides it in a secret place.)
(Hae Jin is struggling to get Jong Kook off of Kwang Soo.)
- Hae Jin! - I'm helping.
Can you try harder?
Harder? Got it.
- You're almost there. - I got it.
- Am I supposed to take it off? - Do it.
- Go for it. - Okay.
Okay.
(He's quick to answer even in a situation like this.)
I did it.
He's so strong.
Work with me.
(This is the biggest one I've caught in my life.)
We're almost there.
We're almost done.
(Jong Kook locks Kwang Soo between his legs.)
(He catches Kwang Soo off guard.)
(It's a deadly technique.)
- Help me. - Oh, right.
(Please... Please help me.)
(Let me see...)
(He's struggling.)
- Hae Jin! - Gosh.
- How's that? - Help.
(This is a variety show, not a UFC match.)
Hae Jin!
Come on.
- Gosh. - Get him off of me.
- He's amazing. - Can you...
- What? - Stop saying that...
and get his hands off of me.
(What more do you want from me?)
Please, someone come and help me.
- It's 2 against 1. - I know, right?
We outnumber him.
I didn't think he would be this strong.
("Extreme Job": Catching the Running Man Tiger)
(Here comes the next wave.)
Jong Kook, give me a break.
Hae Jin, hold on.
Hae Jin! Where'd you go?
This is too exhausting.
Let me take a break.
I have to lie down.
(He gave up working with his legs.)
- You can do it. - How's that?
You're almost there.
(He's struggling again.)
I can't breathe.
Gosh.
Stop punching me there!
(Consecutive hits to his groin make him vulnerable.)
(That's all the exercise I need for the rest of this year.)
That was crazy.
Good job, Hae Jin.
- Wasn't that a foul? - That was good, Hae Jin.
(He's sweating buckets.)
- I'm sweating so much. - Goodness.
We did great work.
(Jong Kook is out of the game. Meanwhile...)
Oh, gosh.
I found a hint,
- but guessed the wrong answer. - Me, too.
- What's that? - Jong Kook is out?
(What do you mean Jong Kook is out?)
What should we do?
Should I go for Gary first?
(Jae Seok got a question right and is thinking of his next move.)
Or should I get rid of M instead?
Kim Jong Kook is out.
(What?)
What happened?
That's good news. Kwang Soo must have done it.
(Gary also guessed the correct answer.)
- Is S out of the game already? - Yes.
What should I do?
Kwang Soo also has a K.
Kim Jong Kook is out.
I just thought of something dangerous.
I was about to remove K.
I forgot that it's in my name as well.
I forgot what my actual name was.
(Get it together, Gary.)
I think I should go for J.
(J has the Save a Consonant Card.)
There's no other way.
Yu Jae Seok has removed J.
Oh, no.
(I only have N left.)
- Yu Jae Seok has removed J. - Gosh.
(Every member of Team Red has a J in their names.)
I only have one left.
I should go for Y. I need to eliminate Kwang Soo.
I should get rid of the strong opponents first.
(Hae Jin finally managed to get a question right.)
It's Y.
That's you.
Kwang Soo, Y will be removed from your name.
- Let's go for Gary. - What does he have?
- It's R. - R?
Okay.
- R has already been removed. - Let's do K then.
- K? - Wait, no!
That's in my name, too.
I'm sorry.
(Song Ji Hyo is out.)
I'm out?
Y has been removed.
Song Ji Hyo is out.
Does the package belong to me now?
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
Keep this for me.
(The package Ji Hyo found goes to Gary.)
(Jong Kook, Ji Hyo, Seok Jin and Haha are out.)
(The only remaining consonants are K, M and N.)
(Gary can now tear name tags.)
This keeps slipping down.
(Hae Jin has Remove a Consonant Card.)
- Whom should we get rid of? - Wait a minute.
Who's left? Jo Yoon Hee and...
Lim Ji Yeon.
What should we go for? M?
Let's go with that. We don't have to do H yet.
Sounds good.
(Ji Yeon finds a box at the moment of crisis.)
"Pick the sentence with the correct spelling."
Let's see.
(Pick the sentence with the correct spelling.)
I'll go with number one, "The noodles haven't swollen."
(Ji Yeon picks number 1.)
(That's correct.)
Nice.
(Should I rip Ji Yeon's name tag?)
- Let's go look for her. - Let's go.
Give me a holler if you spot her.
(The bell rings.)
- Yu Hae Jin has removed M. - M?
(I could have removed a consonant myself.)
(Thank you, Hae Jin.)
Lim Ji Yeon has removed K.
(Ji Yeon's choice was K.)
No...
- She removed K. - What?
Lim Ji Yeon has removed K.
No!
(Gary and Kwang Soo are both out.)
Lim Ji Yeon has removed K.
(Gary wails.)
(You didn't see this coming, did you?)
(I didn't even get to eliminate anyone.)
Gary is out.
Lim Ji Yeon!
- Kwang Soo is out. - They're out.
(She's very happy.)
(N is the only consonant left.)
(I have to get rid of J that's been saved by Blue Team.)
It's not her either.
(She miraculously finds the box.)
(Pick the phrase that has the following meaning.)
Are you kidding me?
Let me think...
(She thinks hard.)
It's number one.
(She picks answer number 1.)
(If she gets this right, they're even with Blue Team.)
(That's correct.)
I did it.
Who's left?
There's Hae Jin, Jae Seok, Joon, Ji Yeon and you.
(Should I remove J now?)
(Ji Yeon has Gary's bag and is moving towards Blue Team.)
- Let's go. - There's the box!
(Joon finds the box.)
- Is that it? - "Guess the correct spelling".
"An accident broke out eventually."
Isn't it number one?
- We pronounce it like number one. - I think it's number one.
- It's probably a trick question. - I think so, too.
I think it's number two.
- It's number two. - "An accident..."
- "broke out eventually". - That's right.
(Joon picks number 2.)
(Their fate depends on this answer.)
(Will they guess it right and win?)
I don't know which consonants are left.
(The bell rings.)
The only one I have left is N.
Lee Joon has removed N.
(Oh no)
(Does that mean Blue Team is out?)
- It's number two. - "An accident..."
- "broke out eventually." - That's right.
(Team Blue came to an agreement and guessed the answer.)
- I was right. - We got it right.
(Their choice was correct.)
- We choose N. - We'll remove N.
Goodness, I can't believe I found this.
Let's remove N!
(The final round is over.)
Today's winning team is...
Blue Team.
(Blue Team wins the final mission.)
Blue Team won.
We would've lost had it not been for the Save a Consonant Card.
- What? Oh, I see. - You mean Save a Consonant Card?
You received that because you won a mission before that.
Y, M,
Try to arrange them by the number.
M, M, Y, J, J?
What is this? It seems like they represent initial sounds.
What's this? It's open.
(The firmly closed box has now been opened.)
What's this?
Isn't this the Tripitaka Koreana?
(It looks like an old book from a museum.)
It may look like an ordinary, old book,
but this book contains...
our ancestors' life threatening struggles to protect Hangeul.
It's called the "Malmoi Manuscript".
- "Malmoi Manuscript"? - Yes.
The five consonants you've found represent the initial sounds...
- of "Malmoi Operation". - What is that?
(What exactly was the "Malmoi Operation"?)
(Malmoi Operation)
The places where you carried out your missions were all related...
to the activists who tried to protect Hangeul.
(All the mission were related...)
(to Hangeul and the independence movement.)
- Isn't it yakgwa? - Yakgwa!
(What are the hidden stories of the places we've visited?)
They all were related to the independence movement,
but especially with one person.
Was it King Sejong the Great?
- It's not him. - Oh, is it not?
Here's a hint. King Sejong the Great invented Hunminjeongeum.
This person completed Hangeul and came up with that word.
- Do you mean Ju Si Gyeong? - You're right. It's him.
- He was everywhere today. - Really?
Let me tell you a little bit about him.
He had to make his own living...
because his family was so poor.
Whenever he had time,
since 7 or 8 years of age,
he made straw shoes and sold them at the market.
(But our language, Hangeul, was not present at that time.)
He thought it wasn't right.
The official language was Chinese, not Hangeul.
That's why he started to study Hangeul.
He taught students Hangeul in various schools.
He couldn't even spare time to sit down.
So he packed a bag and went from school to school, teaching Hangeul.
He went around in straw shoes and overworked himself.
Since he pushed himself too hard,
he worked himself to death at the mere age of 39.
- We were there. - That's where we sang.
That's where we sang and skipped ropes.
Ju Si Gyeong Garden used to be the place...
where he, himself,
studied Hangeul until his death.
I think it was a miracle that Hangeul didn't disappear.
Because in the 1930s,
Japan banned Koreans from using Hangeul in everyday lives.
We had to change our names. I know this is absurd,
but there were even posters that said,
"Dream in Japanese."
It was impossible to preserve Hangeul.
But Si Gyeong's disciples accomplished this miracle.
His disciples organised the Joseon Linguistics Committee...
and pleaded with the public.
They said, "Please help us to preserve our own language."
"If you remember any pronunciations or words in Hangeul,"
"please write down and send them to Joseon Linguistics Committee."
("If you remember any Korean words, even swear words, please send them.)
The whole nation cooperated.
Even elementary school students from 500 schools participated.
The manuscript gathered from all over the country is...
the "Malmoi Manuscript".
(Their hard work was created.)
They gathered the manuscripts and slowly compiled a dictionary.
But in 1942, an unexpected misfortune happened.
They collected manuscripts for 13 years,
but the Japanese confiscated them.
That's how the "Malmoi Operation" came to an end.
But a miraculous thing happened.
After our independence, the manuscript was discovered...
in a storage at Seoul Station.
(2,600 pages of manuscript was discovered at Seoul Station.)
After the Korean War,
a total of six books were published.
(The first Korean dictionary was created.)
- We've been there. - You're right.
The Korean Language Society now inherited...
the legacy of Joseon Linguistics Committees.
That's where you carried out your mission.
(The Korean Language Society)
There's a book Si Gyeong wrote before the Japanese colonial era...
because he was so upset at how people disdained Hangeul.
Here's a quote from the book.
Hae Jin, would you like to read it?
"If you ignore the spoken and written language, which is..."
"the most important aspect in protecting a country,"
"the foundation of the country will decay."
It feels as if he's speaking to us right now.
You must've had a hard time today with missing consonants.
- Yes. - But imagine if it wasn't...
just the consonants, but the entire language that was missing.
It'd be more than uncomfortable. I'd be sorrowful.
I hope we could remember their sacrifices and contributions...
to preserve Hangeul...
at least on Hangeul Day.
(Please remember Ju Si Gyeong and Joseon Linguistics Committee.)
Since today is Hangeul Day, we should try to remember them.
However, I feel guilty that...
we often forget to appreciate them in our daily lives.
Let's give a round of applause to Lee Da Ji who taught us...
such invaluable, historical facts.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
Is this a good place for a trip?
(Lee Kyu Han, Yang Se Chan, Park Na Rae)
(Park Soo Hong, Sol Bin)
We need to buy the land?
(We thought we were on a trip, but you want us to buy lands?)
(Only those with lands...)
(can enjoy this trip.)
(Collect R money...)
(if you want to buy land.)
(Sell everything you have to possess the land.)
(Next week, a special trip with fantastic entertainers.)
(No Way Out Race)