(Gary joined Running Man 7 years ago.)
(We thought he'd be with us until the end.)
("Gary leaves Running Man to focus on his music.")
("Gary completed the last filming.")
- This is the last episode with him. - I know.
(We prepared everything for Gary to leave us without shedding tears.)
(That's what Gary thought.)
(You know we can't just let you go so easily.)
(This special farewell episode might be a little nasty.)
(A goodbye party where the members hold back their tears.)
(Will Gary really be able to leave Running Man safely?)
(At a cafe in Sinsa-dong)
(There are only 6 chairs instead of 7 which is unusual.)
(Today is the last day with Gary.)
What's this? No one has arrived yet.
No one has.
I feel pretty depressed from the early morning.
- I've got the blues. - Let's go out!
Hello.
Hello!
Didn't you feel weird when you woke up this morning?
(Why are there only 6 chairs?)
(Other members also arrive at the cafe.)
(Wait.)
(She realises there are only six chairs and finds it hard to sit.)
As you all know,
- today is the last day with Gary. - I know.
From about two weeks ago,
Gary privately told all of us...
about his decision to leave Running Man.
I was going to persuade him...
before he told me the reason.
Gary has a goal of his life which he desperately wants to achieve.
Although it's sad to let him go,
I believe that we should respect his decision.
We couldn't help but understand him.
(We decided to let him go for his happiness.)
We should wish him happiness.
Then will the cameraman who's in charge of Gary quit as well?
(Will the cameraman who's in charge of Gary quit as well?)
- That's even sadder. - He's right.
- Really? - Where is Gary's cameraman?
(He cried all night long.)
Will you quit, too?
I haven't given you the money gift for your wedding yet.
- Not yet? - Gosh.
He now even has a baby!
- He has a baby. - Goodness.
- I'll give you today. - How can you do that?
I'll give you today no matter what. Please tell me your account number.
I can't believe this.
Today is the last filming day with Gary.
We pondered upon today's episode.
We thought how we should let Gary go after seven years.
So we prepared this.
"Running Man Who Cannot Breakup and Gary Who Cannot Leave".
It's like a nasty breakup.
Will we take back things we gave him before?
Will Ji Hyo cry a lot today?
Gary thinks the shooting will start at three o'clock.
He's working in a studio which is 50m away from here.
You'll pay a surprise visit and carry out a secret mission.
- What? - A secret mission?
A secret mission?
Without getting caught by Gary until the end of the race,
each member will steal an item that commemorates the time with Gary.
Each member will steal an item.
You want us to steal something?
This is a farewell episode, isn't it?
Are you encouraging us to steal?
Yes. But...
(You have to satisfy a requirement.)
The item you steal must be bigger than the item previously stolen.
The role of the first runner is important.
- Is there a fixed order? - No.
- You need to steal it secretly. - You need to be sly.
But we won't know who stole what.
Gary's studio is located on the fifth floor.
Fourth floor is where the box seats are located.
On the fourth floor, we'll check...
if your item is acceptable or not.
The item must be from the studio. It is only acceptable when...
the item is carried out without Gary's interruption.
If he interrupts you from stealing,
you must compensate twice the price of the item.
- You must compensate him. - Excuse me?
(Compensate Gary.)
Double the price?
We really might end up at a prison.
Just like what Haha said, we could be handcuffed at the end.
Anyone who fails to steal until the race ends...
will face a crucial penalty at the end.
How can we be asked to steal on TV?
Let's just say we are stealing memories.
Something to remember Gary by.
- We are memory hunters. - "Memory hunters"?
(Is that the best you got?)
Why? What's wrong?
(We are ready to hunt memories.)
This is the Rodeo street.
Yes, it is.
(They're about to meet him.)
I didn't know Gary's studio was located here.
I didn't know, either.
(Where are you going, Gary? We are on our way to steal.)
(You can't get off that easy. "Nameless Stealers")
All right, let's go!
This is it.
I had no idea. Is this it?
This must be it.
Gary's studio is tightly closed.
I can come to Gary's studio...
and go to my dermatologist.
Jae Seok, go to my brother.
- What? - Go to him.
He is worried about your wrinkles.
I know. What should I do?
(Raiding Gary's studio has just begun.)
Hello, Gary.
What were you doing?
(Did we surprise you?)
(The camera crew set up the perimeter in advance.)
(The staff acquired Gary's studio in a blink of an eye.)
(Who am I? Where am I?)
Gary, here is your outfit and your microphone.
Oh, my outfit.
Didn't you say you were coming later?
Be honest. Don't you regret resigning?
- Don't you? - I was going to start off crying.
(Gary is changing into his outfit.)
I'm quite sad.
(Why are they looking around?)
(Let's see.)
(Gary's studio has 7 years' worth of souvenirs from Running Man.)
When was this from?
Gold, silver and bronze?
What is this?
(Shall we get started?)
(The studio is full of small and big objects.)
(Can they steal without Gary noticing?)
Well, today is...
- Gary's last day joining us. - You're right.
(They shared pleasures and sorrows for 7 years.)
- Did you cry? - What?
I did feel sad.
Even I felt weird this morning.
You two should sit together today.
- That's right. - You're the Monday Couple.
Switch seats, Kwang Soo.
Ji Hyo should move there.
(As we say goodbye to Gary, we must say goodbye to Monday Couple, too.)
(Gary and Ji Hyo 6 years ago)
- Promise? - Promise.
(From the moment they began to get to know each other...)
(until this moment as Monday Couple...)
This sea resembles you.
(They have beautiful memories to cherish together.)
(Goodbye, Monday boyfriend.)
Ji Hyo is now shooting a drama with Sun Kyun.
She is having an affair on it.
(Jae Seok breaks the mood.)
Be the best actress specialising in having affairs on TV.
I have confidence in her.
(Just as he wished, she became the best.)
We deliberated a lot what to do for our last episode.
Do you know how far you ran over the course of seven years?
- How far? - Yes.
- How far we ran? - The distance during filming?
If we count the time to Dubai, then it is a lot.
How far do you think we ran?
About 20,000km?
- Seok Jin. - 20,000km?
A round trip abroad should be about 10,000km.
- We also went to Australia. - You're right.
We calculated the total distance from the first episode.
To be accurate, it is 77,093km.
(The total distance is 77,093km.)
(The total distance outside of Korea is 43,063.17km.)
(The total distance in Korea is 33,931.83km)
(The accumulated distance is 77,093km)
If you count the distance I was dragged by Jong Kook...
If you count that too then...
- I bet that distance is longer. - The camera didn't catch them all.
This brings us back to today's race.
It is "Balance the Distance".
"Balance the Distance"?
- It rhymes. - We tried.
You must collect the total distance...
that you ran during the seven years through playing various games.
The game ends only when you have gathered all the distance.
Gary, it's going to take about five months.
We have to collect 77,000km.
How do we gather the kilometres?
The game itself is quite simple.
You can choose one of the category.
The back side will tell you what kind of game to play. If you win,
you get to keep the kilometres.
But if you lose, you will have to get finger flicks.
(Whenever the members win, they will have a chance to pick a present. )
The faster you complete the distance,
the better the present Gary will receive.
Are these presents for me?
If you gather all the distance in one try,
he will get a round trip ticket to Europe.
If you complete the distance in two tries, he will get a new laptop.
If you finish in three tries, he'll get a premium Korean Beef package.
I like the last one. 15 tries or more and he has to give us presents.
That's meaningful.
For us, that could be more suitable.
(Presents to the whole staff?)
That will look nicest on television.
I mean it is also customary...
as a person who resigned.
Please select the first category.
Let's test the water first.
Why don't we try the easy ones first?
If we finish in one try, don't I get a round trip ticket to Europe?
- Then we should try. - How about we try?
- Yes, let's do it. - Let's go for 77,000km.
At once?
I have a question.
Has the game begun?
Yes, it has.
(Running Man's secret mission starts as well.)
(They must steal an object and bring it downstairs secretly.)
(Can everyone succeed?)
Let's go for the whole distance.
Let's go, let's go.
Let's go for the one that everyone has to pass.
Gary, come on. Let's go for it.
Let's do it.
Okay. If I get that ticket,
I'll buy a ticket for someone, too.
- Let's go. - I'll show you what it is.
(The game for 77,000km is...)
(What is behind the board?)
"Stand the Pain"?
(Stand the Pain)
- What is that? - What is "Stand the Pain"?
The game for completing the whole distance is...
(Please tell us now.)
- An expert will be joining us. - What?
The special helper is one of the well-known therapists...
in sports message. His name is Kim Young Joon.
(I can remember it just like it was yesterday.)
(With his amazing hands, he ruled the members.)
(Sports massage therapist, Kim Young Joon)
He is here.
(He is back to help the game.)
- Oh my gosh. - He is really here.
- Hello. - Welcome.
I'll do it.
I can do this.
My shoulder is tense.
(Everyone has to stand the pain for 10 seconds without screaming.)
- Right here? - Get Ready.
Hold on, you are using your elbow? You are not using your hands?
- Why? - It makes no difference.
Just stand the pain.
Gary, if you scream, it's over.
- He can do it. - Get ready.
- Start. - Poor Gary.
You look so ugly.
(A horrible looking squid is spotted in Apgujeong.)
- He is holding it. - Time's almost up.
You are almost there.
(With breath taking appearance)
Time's up.
(Gary succeeds in standing the pain for 10 seconds.)
This is the ugliest face I've seen in 10 years.
- That was so ugly. - What did you do yesterday, Gary?
You were shockingly ugly.
- That was something. - I can't see that face any more.
I don't want to let him go.
Please fix me up in editing.
(Is this what you meant?)
I mean among us,
he is the only one who can be funny only with his face.
I miss him already.
I don't think I can stand the pain in my pelvis very well.
No, Jae Seok. You can do this.
- I mean, pelvis is... - Jae Seok, help me out.
I can do other areas.
Jae Seok. For me, you can surely hold 10 seconds.
- Stand the pain. - Get ready.
Your 10 seconds start now.
(For Gary, I can sacrifice my pelvis.)
(I must stand the pain.)
(Please, Jae Seok.)
(Clutching)
(He endured half the time.)
(Shrieking)
(Their first attempt to complete the distance fails.)
Come on.
(Please let us know if anyone knows how to fix overly massaged pelvis.)
I thought my leg was going to fall out.
What kind of therapist are you?
Sir! My leg was about to fall off.
Look how my right leg got longer.
Look at this.
Look. It's gotten longer.
- Isn't that a good thing? - I wish my legs were longer.
Look at my legs.
(There is a simple way of fixing that.)
(Let me do the other side as well.)
Can you make the other leg longer as well?
Right there.
It hurts.
(This will hurt only for a second.)
(Resisting)
It's perfect now.
- It's a miracle. - They're exactly the same length.
That's much better.
- Finally. - You can walk now.
- This is amazing. - You can walk now.
- I got matching legs now. - We failed.
Is there a penalty?
Yes.
(They blew their chance to win plane tickets to Europe.)
You have to get finger flicked now.
- Just one of us, right? - Yes.
The person who failed the mission should get penalised.
The person who made the sound should get flicked.
- No way. - It's Gary's last day.
- Gary should take it. - That sounds good.
(Gary wins the prize.)
- What? - Let's do it.
We're doing this for you.
- Just do it. - Sounds good.
- Come on, Gary. - Just do it.
Chances like this don't come by very often.
Can you let me go with some dignity?
- What are you talking about? - This is my last day.
Which is why we have to do this.
- I'll let Ji Hyo hit me. - Are you sure about that?
- Do it, Ji Hyo. - I'm not very good at this.
I won't get another chance to get hit by you.
(Okay, Gary. I'll make it quick.)
Are you going to hit my forehead?
Hold up.
(Frightened)
Did you see that?
At least count to three before you do it.
I didn't want to put you through that.
(His Monday Girlfriend is sweet yet scary.)
Jong Kook?
Hold on.
(Why is Jae Seok calling Jong Kook?)
That's scary.
(Moments ago)
(Jong Kook stole a fan...)
(and sneaked out.)
(Jae Seok noticed that.)
(I'll be holding on to that.)
(Jong Kook pushes him away.)
(He gets slammed into the wall.)
What are you doing back there?
(Jae Seok's time of ordeal)
- What are you doing? - He bumped into the wall.
Why did you do that?
It's nothing. I'm fine.
(What are they up to this time?)
- What was that? - It didn't sound fine.
I'm really fine.
- Are you sure about that? - Yes.
(They're not going easy on each other for this mission.)
(At least Gary didn't notice anything strange.)
- Hold on. - Here I go.
Count to three.
- Wait. - One, two, three.
(Slapping)
(That was loud.)
- What was that? - Good hit.
(Ji Hyo closes the game with a finishing home run.)
(I'll let you go now, Gary.)
(It's time to say goodbye.)
- That was a good hit. - Did you hear that?
- That was loud. - Are you okay?
It sounded like something blew up.
It sounded like a plastic bag popped open.
I'm not even joking. That was really loud.
Oh, my goodness.
- Is it red? - No, it's fine.
It hurts from the inside.
- That was a good hit. - She didn't punch me, did she?
- That was amazing. - It's gotten red.
Can I pick the next person in line?
Yes.
(You can pick the next person to get finger flicked after you get hit.)
- What should we do next? - Please choose the next game.
- Let's do an easy one. - Okay.
- We should do a hard one. - Let's do the yellow one.
We should finish it off in one go.
Let's do the one with 77,000km.
- Fine. - This is our chance.
We'll do 77,000km for Running Man.
Here it is.
What is it?
(Carrying out this mission will award Gary with a laptop.)
("Mascot")
"Mascot"?
What is that?
(We have a mascot?)
For this mission,
you will be joined by Running Man's mascot.
We have a mascot?
He became the mascot of our show with just two appearances.
He's the master of sports massage, Mr Kim Young Joon.
What are you talking about?
(Are you kidding me?)
- Are you kidding me? - Are you serious?
What do you think you're doing?
(Why you little...)
This is nonsense.
Are you...
Are you serious?
I have a feeling...
everything's going to lead up to the massage.
He's our mascot?
(The mascot is ready.)
- I'll go. - Can you do me a favour?
(Jong Kook volunteers to go first in order to succeed the mission.)
This is impossible.
I can't hold it in.
Can you try some other time if you're not feeling up for it?
Let's win the laptop for Gary.
I really need it.
(Will Jong Kook be able to endure the massive pain for Gary?)
Ready, set, go!
(The mascot's massage begins.)
(He seems to be in pain.)
Look at his hands.
Look at those muscles.
(He's trying his best to hold it in.)
Look at his legs.
Mission successful.
- Where are you going? - Where are you going?
(He steals something while faking the pain.)
Where are you going?
Where is he going?
(He managed to steal something in the middle of all that.)
Where did he go?
(He arrives at the headquarters on the 4th floor.)
You have successfully carried out the hidden mission.
(Jong Kook managed to steal a toy by acting.)
(The rest of the members have to steal objects bigger than that.)
It hurts so much.
- I'm going to put my palms on you. - You have to endure it, Haha.
Go!
(Haha is up next.)
There you go, Haha.
- You're almost there. - Oh, my.
- Look how ugly he is. - You're almost there.
(Ugliness alert.)
And you called me ugly for all these seven years.
Mission successful.
(Haha succeeds.)
- Where are you going? - Where are you going?
Where is everyone going?
It hurts so much.
(He arrives at the headquarters.)
- Hello, Haha. - I didn't know it was that big.
That's the object Jong Kook brought.
Why is it so big?
That's too small. You have failed the hidden mission.
- Please bring something else. - But how?
(How did you do that, Jong Kook?)
Where's everyone going?
- It hurts so much. - I guess it's that painful.
It really hurts.
(Ji Hyo tries next.)
What was that?
Don't forget you're a celebrity.
(What was that gesture just now?)
- What are you doing? - Control yourself.
- Are you crazy? - She's gone out of her mind.
(She gets sent off by disorderly conduct charges.)
Are you crazy?
- What was that? - Why did you do that?
Why did you do that?
- What are you doing? - Are you crazy?
- Why did you do that? - Are you out of your mind?
- What was that? - She's gone mad.
- She's out of her mind. - What's wrong with everyone today?
(What's wrong with her?)
Get it together.
We should run her through a dope test.
Sit down.
- I wanted to go. - Everyone's gone mad.
I think I can endure the pain.
- I'll try really hard. - Give it a try.
- Okay. - Can I put something in my mouth?
You can't do that.
Ready.
It's 10 seconds. Set...
Can someone else go first?
(He didn't even get started and is already in pain.)
- Man up. - He didn't even get started.
- Ready, - I didn't even get started.
set, go!
(Seok Jin gives it a try.)
There you go.
(Whimpering)
- He just made a sound. - You failed.
That's too harsh.
You failed.
(I guess I'll just buy my own laptop.)
Seok Jin has failed the mission.
(Seok Jin lets out a groan and they fail the game.)
The next prize is highest quality of Korean beef.
- Gary loves meat. - Korean beef isn't bad.
We should pick more carefully. I don't want that person again.
I think we're safe now.
I doubt he's going to be in the next game.
Let's do "Staff Members".
- Okay. - Let's do that.
- Please turn it over. - Is it him again?
I doubt it.
- "Writers"? - "Writers".
It's a different one.
(That's such a relief.)
The keyword for this game of 77,000km is "Writers".
(Is it a game against the writers?)
The writers arranged a sports massage session.
(It's a game of extreme pain again.)
I told you.
- I knew this would happen. - Are you kidding me?
(This just in. The massage therapist joins Running Man as a new member.)
You should just take a seat with us.
Come sit over here.
I told you this would happen.
This is Gary's last day.
Can't you just let me go in peace?
This is too harsh.
Wait, nobody got finger flicked for the second mission.
Why would you bring that up? You can go if you'd like.
(Do you want to get your forehead checked out?)
Gary's person of choice will get finger flicked.
Can't we just decide by rock-paper-scissors?
I'll pick Ji Hyo.
Ji Hyo?
- Sounds good. - It's about time.
(It's better to get it over with as early as possible.)
Ji Hyo has a big forehead.
It's better to just get it over with.
Ji Hyo is good at taking it.
Ji Hyo's forehead is as big as a newly developed town.
- Her forehead is big. - Let Kwang Soo do the honour.
Okay.
Me?
(Kwang Soo is the best person fit for the job.)
Just know that you're going next,
and I'll be the one to hit you.
- That's fine. - Fine by me.
Okay.
I'll knock you out so you won't ever get back up.
- You won't be able to hit me. - That's the spirit.
There you go.
(It's a battle of finger flicks between Kwang Soo and Ji Hyo.)
His hand is bigger than her face.
I'm sorry, Ji Hyo.
Just do it.
(It's a hit.)
(He high-fived her forehead.)
That looked hilarious, Ji Hyo.
I'm sorry, Ji Hyo.
- I couldn't help it. - It'll look funny on television.
- Are you okay, Ji Hyo? - I couldn't help it.
I'm sorry. I couldn't help it.
I understand.
I see how it is.
- We have to succeed. - I get it.
I'm begging you.
(We have to put an end to this.)
Who's next?
- Did you get your waist massaged? - I'll take the massage.
I'm so scared.
(I need the teddy bear by my side.)
- I'm so scared. - How old are you?
- I'm too scared. - Look at him.
- Don't do this. - Let go of me. I'm scared.
- What are you doing? - Let go of me.
- Hand it over. - Goodness.
You don't need to hold on to that.
Can you give it back? I'm so scared.
I'll be by your side.
Do you feel better now?
- A giraffe is here. - He's better than a teddy bear.
A giraffe is better.
Ready, set, go!
(Haha is holding onto Kwang Soo.)
(Let's do this for Gary and his Korean beef.)
(It's painful.)
Haha didn't make it, either.
He failed.
How come you can't tolerate it?
(Sorry, Gary. I tried.)
It's a perfect forehead to hit because it's flat.
This is a great forehead to hit.
- I'll go like this. - Okay.
Her temper is...
(She slaps hard.)
(His skull might be split.)
You were in the air for a moment.
(This smashing makes him go against gravity.)
I knew she would smash him.
You are really good at hitting.
It's not easy to hit like that.
She's frightening.
That was strong.
Jae Seok, why are you taking this?
Let go of this bear.
Haha, come back.
- She was not kidding. - We have to shoot.
- I can't believe it. - You come here, too.
Wait a second.
Go over there.
(They're stopping each other.)
- This is unbelievable. - Kwang Soo, come here.
- You tried three times so far. - Yes.
Please choose the next challenge.
- Let's choose 50,000km. - We'll pick 50,000km.
- 50,000km. - Isn't it the therapist again?
Let's choose 30,000km.
- Is it a notebook, then? - 70,000km...
- 50,000 and a pass of everyone. - Shall we shake the shoes off?
- 50,000... - And a pass of everyone.
Turn that around, please.
("Hit or Miss")
- It's "Hit or Miss". - That's good.
- This is good. - I like it.
- Great. - We can manage this.
We can do this.
The game for 50,000km is...
"Hit or Miss".
"Hit or Miss" is not bad.
- It depends on the luck. - Right.
What will it be?
(Suspicious plates are coming in.)
I think these are foods that contain wasabi or something.
- They might be. - Are they dumplings?
- They look like foods, right? - We need to pass this.
- Jae Seok, - Jae Seok.
- come here and look at these. - Jae Seok.
- Over here. - Jae Seok.
- I'm going to the restroom. - The restroom is that way.
(He heads for the restroom...)
(but suddenly starts to crawl.)
(He bumps into the staff.)
(He steals something.)
(He acquired the frame among the staff.)
- Hello. - Hello.
This should be bigger than Jong Kook's item over there.
It's bigger, isn't it?
(The frame is slightly bigger than the figurine.)
Jae Seok, your secret mission is cleared.
(Jae Seok is the 2nd one to clear the secret mission.)
- Let me explain the rule. - Okay.
The game of 50,000km is " Hit or Miss".
The mission will be cleared if everyone passes.
There are seven levels of them. So you should think about the order.
It's obvious.
- It's coke. - Okay.
- Next. - Great.
It'll be difficult from now on.
- I can't distinguish them. - I can't, either.
I hate this.
I even hate regular yogurt, too.
- Why? - For it contains too much sugar.
Just drink it.
- Gosh. - What is the other one?
(He is very cautious.)
This one is yogurt.
This one is real. The colour of that one is too light.
(He's hesitating for several minutes.)
- It's the colour of real yogurt. - Okay.
(He finally picks one.)
- I think this is... - Here he goes.
- He's drinking. - This looks real.
(We didn't deduct the distance at all. We have to succeed.)
(He's drinking it very well.)
It looks okay. Are you okay?
(He finishes in one go.)
It's delicious.
I smell vinegar.
(He tried to hide it but failed.)
My goodness.
The other was the real one.
He smells of vinegar a lot.
We were right.
You picked the wrong one.
You recommended this.
(Sneakily)
(The hunters start to move again.)
You still smell like vinegar.
(They hide the stolen item under their shirts.)
Gosh. You're so mean.
You put too much of wasabi.
Have you given us these kind of foods?
You could have put just a little.
Is this what we used to eat?
What are you doing, Seok Jin?
That explains why my family said they hated my smell.
It's a failure. We'll clean them up.
(Haha hid the frame under his shirt.)
(I need to go downstairs.)
I should have made a better choice.
The next step would have been a raw egg.
What is this?
(He comes out of the room.)
(Great. I looked natural.)
Nobody noticed this.
This is Jae Seok's item.
- When did he bring it? - This is the new standard.
(When did he bring that?)
- Haha, you cleared the mission. - Yes.
(Haha cleared the secret mission.)
I think Gary will have to give gifts to 100 people.
Gary might give apples again to 100 staff members.
(They keep searching for items.)
Is this what you can wear?
Are you going to study English?
(Gary doesn't notice anything.)
- I'm looking around. - Why don't you learn from Mike?
(Seok Jin sneaks out of the room.)
You should bring something definitely bigger than this.
(Why is his belly bulging?)
I'm worried about the next person.
(He brought a big one.)
What should the next person do?
- It should be wider, too. - Wider, too?
This is what Haha brought.
- Should it be wider, too? - It should be obviously bigger.
- I thought the height is important. - We measure...
We measure the width, too.
The opinion of the staff is...
(He brought a huge one.)
Did you bring this?
(This is big enough to cover any frame.)
Hey, you.
Don't you think of the rest of us?
Compare them.
- You should think... - It can cover this.
Kwang Soo, you cleared the secret mission.
(Kwang Soo's ability to steal is amazing.)
Are you crazy?
How could you bring this one?
Now, Kwang Soo's item is the standard.
How can I bring anything bigger than this?
(Ji Hyo and Seok Jin are the ones left.)
(It's getting harder for the two.)
- Shall we start? - Let's start shooting again.
- Let's do "Hit or Miss" once more. - Good.
- Okay. - Let's do it.
Before that, someone has to get finger flicked.
(You should get finger flicked.)
- Can I appoint someone? - Yes, you can.
It's been a while since Jong Kook got it last time.
(Jong Kook, could you come up?)
It sounds good.
The sound is great.
- Who can hit him? - He still has to be hit.
(I'll see how hard you hit me.)
Ji Hyo is doing well today. What about her?
- Okay. - Ji Hyo is great.
- I can't since I'm busy. - What about Kwang Soo?
- Let Kwang Soo hit him. - May I?
Jae Seok is really good at slapping.
- It's okay. - Can I?
Are you worried about next time?
I feel sorry.
- We're worried. - That's why.
Then...
- let's play rock-paper-scissors. - I want to appoint...
- someone. - Let's play...
rock-paper-scissors.
- No. - If you appoint someone...
- I can appoint someone who'll slap. - No.
You just appointed the one who will be slapped.
(Is she cleaning up for me?)
- You mean I should hit him? - Yes.
(Well, then...)
Then I want to hit you.
(I just want to hit you.)
Why?
Then let's play rock-paper-scissors among the rest of us.
- Among the rest? - The loser will hit him.
People who didn't hit yet has to play it.
- The loser is the hitter. - Okay.
- Rock-paper-scissors. - Rock-paper-scissors.
Okay.
(Haha has to hit Jong Kook's forehead.)
He's good at this.
- He is. - He shouldn't get hurt.
He won't get hurt.
He has to perform in Vegas.
You mean the concert in Las Vegas?
- The concert in Las Vegas? - Yes.
- On November 19? - Yes.
(He promotes his concert suddenly.)
- What are you doing? - This won't be aired.
What's wrong with mentioning my concert?
Leave your hand mark.
(He has to slap Jong Kook anyway.)
It's okay to get slapped in the face.
But he hits the eyes. He can't aim properly.
(Slapping)
See? He hits the eyes.
He usually hits the eyes.
I was hit by the eyes last time.
He can't aim well.
You should have adjusted the spot.
(Just think about the concert, Jong Kook.)
This is funny.
The next person is doomed.
I don't feel confident about this.
(Seok Jin is trying a new game.)
I'll put them anywhere.
- As many as possible. - Oh my.
(It pops out.)
(Seok Jin sure is unlucky.)
- I'm sorry. - You're so bad at games.
Sit down.
(Are you talking to me?)
Is it me?
He must be scared.
You could have said nicely.
You should have said nicely.
He ordered him to sit down.
- Hit me within three seconds. - Okay.
- I'll hold you. - Gosh.
Does it have to be me?
It was Haha who hit you.
I can't hit Haha...
because we'll perform in Las Vegas.
It is on November 19, isn't it?
(You know it very well.)
- Give me a break. - Get up.
- Okay. - Come over here.
(He wants Jae Seok instead.)
- This is not fair. - It's not.
- It's not fair at all. - Sit down.
What a relief.
- I'm dumbfounded. - Words saved him.
- I'm at a loss. - Words are important.
I'm at a loss for words.
- You can't do this. - Sit down.
(Though he's upset, he reveals his forehead.)
- Take off your glasses. - I heard you have guests, too.
Goodness.
They're Turbo and Skull, right?
Get up.
(Correct. Get up.)
(Kwang Soo, come here.)
Me?
- I was hit just a moment ago. - Sit down.
- Isn't it too soon? - No.
- He can't cancel his decision. - Sit up straight.
Sit up straight.
Put your knees together.
(He got high-quality information.)
Isn't she lovely
What's that?
Why did you sing that?
Isn't Stevie Wonder also invited?
- Get ready. - What?
- You said Stevie Wonder is coming. - When?
- You said so. - That's nonsense.
- Kwang Soo is a fraud. - He said Stevie Wonder is coming.
He's a fraud.
Haha said Stevie Wonder is invited to the performance.
- Gary told you that. - It was Gary.
Gary has no idea about the performance.
I didn't know, either.
I thought Haha whispered to me.
- It was a fraud. - Gary wants to see Stevie Wonder.
You lost my trust.
Get ready and lift your chin.
Lift your chin and clench your jaws.
He resembles the mascot of a baseball team.
(Discovery of a new character)
What did you say?
I don't look like a mascot.
- You do. - I don't look like that.
You might get a chance to throw the first ball in the opening game.
I'm sorry, but I'm not a fan of that team.
Even if you aren't, you look like the mascot of that team.
- You can't change your looks. - You look like that mascot.
Get ready, Kwang Soo.
Gosh.
(Kwang Soo is in trouble.)
It's going to hurt a lot.
(Slap)
(He gets thrown to the ground.)
- That was such a hard slap. - Kwang Soo.
Kwang Soo.
- Is it okay to air this? - Kwang Soo.
Breathe.
His face turned completely red.
(Gary, why did you lie to me?)
Kwang Soo, it's okay.
Let's move on.
- Gosh, nothing is working out. - This is too difficult.
Let's try the category, "Staff Members"
- Okay. - Shall we?
- Let's pick 50,000km. - Okay.
This is "Staff Members" for 50,000km.
"VJ"?
("VJ")
What's that?
It'd better not be a massage therapist the VJ picks again.
That means you want to start a war.
The game for 50,000km is a race with the staff.
- A race? - How's that possible?
Pick three members from each team.
The 1st runner climbs up from 1st to 5th floor.
The next runner comes down from 5th to 1st floor.
- Gary should run. - From the fifth floor?
We can win this.
This is quite easy.
- Jae Seok should run. - He should.
We might finish this mission.
We have to do more.
Gary can run very fast.
- Gary is redoing his shoelaces. - The three VJ's are...
Kwon Ryeol, Ki Jin and Sung Oh.
- We'll win this one. - We already won.
Are they looking down on us?
Great, this is exactly what Gary needs.
Kwon Ryeol gained a lot of weight.
(It's an elite VJ team that's been with Running Man for 7 years.)
(Who will win the race?)
The 1st runner to start from the 1st floor should go down.
Gary will start from the first floor.
- Gary should go. - Do you run both ways?
No, you hand the baton to the second runner...
- on the fifth floor. - Okay.
One runner has to go down.
- Is that so? - Yes.
You two should climb up the stairs.
- I'll climb up. - You can come down.
- I'll go down. - 2 runners stay on the 1st floor.
- Gary should go to the first floor. - Do you have a belt?
The runners go up, down and up.
(Gary leaves to prepare himself for the race.)
I'm not going.
(Here's their chance.)
I had my eye on that.
- It's mine. - Come on.
If you take this, what about the person after you?
You can't take it.
Can you start with the shelves?
What about the poster frame?
(He doesn't have enough strength.)
- Who took the photo frame? - You can't carry it.
- Haha. - Which photo frame?
Mine was this small.
There's one here.
- Can you get off? - Do it later.
I have to do it now.
You can't carry that.
If she takes the plant, the game is over.
(While the two thieves are fighting with a plant...)
That's too big.
- Shall we practise? - Let's do it once.
(Here comes Gary.)
If she takes the plant, the game is over.
(Gary runs up to the studio.)
(Here I come.)
- It's too big. - Isn't it too big?
It doesn't matter as long as he doesn't see it.
(Ji Hyo steals a big one.)
I'll help you on the stairs.
(Ji Hyo is at risk.)
I'll help you. You might hurt yourself.
(Gary is climbing up from 2nd to 3rd floor.)
(Will Gary catch Ji Hyo stealing the plant?)
(Or will she make it safely?)
Over here.
(Ji Hyo is entering the office.)
(Will she get caught or steal the plant successfully?)
(Ji Hyo successfully enters.)
(I'm here to register a plant.)
This is good, right?
(Will the plant be bigger than Kwang Soo's item?)
It's bigger, right?
You have successfully carried out the hidden mission.
(She doesn't have to steal any more.)
Am I the only one left?
Really?
- You can do it. - You can do it.
- Good luck. - You can do it, Gary.
- You can do it. - Okay.
Are you ready?
Are you taking that?
What are you doing over there?
- Right now is the time. - Please get ready.
(He tries to steal the sofa.)
Are you moving?
It's because Ji Hyo took a plant.
- Could you help me? - What are you doing?
What are you doing when there's a race going on?
I have to do it before Gary comes up.
Can you carry it downstairs?
Why did you take a plant?
Get ready.
Gary is about to start the race.
- You can't go downstairs. - The race is about to start.
(What's happening on the 1st floor?)
(The first VJ Team member is on standby.)
He's good at running.
- Get ready, VJ Team. - I'm ready.
- Take it easy. Don't try too hard. - Start.
Start.
(VJ Team's 1st runner starts.)
We might lose the race.
(We can't say goodbye to Gary so easily.)
(He runs fast with 7 years of experience on Running Man.)
You can't go downstairs now because of the race.
(Next runner is up.)
He's fast.
(They're still trying to steal.)
What's going on? Goodness.
- Another runner will come up. - We're having a race.
Another runner will come up.
Someone will be back soon.
Let's try again.
(He runs towards the third runner.)
Just give up, Kwon Ryeol.
He should have come down much earlier.
(The third runner is up.)
(The last spurt is the only way to win.)
Someone is coming upstairs again.
(He runs with all his might for the finish line.)
He's coming up.
The record is...
54.25 seconds.
- They were fast. - We don't have time.
- That's impressive. - They were fast.
(He's in a hurry.)
It was 54.25 seconds. Are we up next?
(Nothing can stop him now.)
- The 1st runner climbs up 1st. - Okay.
- Wait. - Gary is coming upstairs.
(Will Seok Jin successfully steal the bike?)
(He can't let Gary find out.)
- I can't see anything. - This is good.
Start.
(He starts.)
(He's confident about running.)
(He sprints up the stairs at the speed of light.)
(3rd floor)
(On the 4th floor, Seok Jin struggles.)
(Run away, Gary is coming.)
(Seok Jin gets startled by the sound.)
Is Gary coming?
- Is Gary coming? - Yes.
Here you go.
Give it to me.
(Jong Kook forgets to hand the baton.)
(Seok Jin was scared to death.)
It's Jong Kook.
- It is? - Yes.
- It was only Jong Kook. - Gary is coming up soon.
Gary is coming.
(Jae Seok goes down to Gary.)
Here you go.
(Gary is up.)
(Gary starts to run.)
- Gary is coming soon. - This is your last chance.
(He hopes to succeed in stealing.)
(He's about to enter.)
(Gary climbs up from 2nd to 3rd.)
(The entrance is too narrow for the bike.)
(Make some way for me.)
(Gary is about to reach the 4th floor.)
(Will Gary catch Seok Jin?)
Gosh, Seok Jin!
(Gary sees Seok Jin.)
(Why did I get caught now?)
(I'm here to register a bike.)
(Panting)
If this doesn't work, I'm doomed.
I don't think it'll work.
(The bike is a little shorter.)
I'm in trouble. Isn't it big enough?
(If Seok Jin weren't in the way...)
- Gosh. - You're in.
(What's Running Man Team's record?)
Did we win?
- We lost. - What?
- We lost? - Your record is 58.38 seconds.
- No way. - That's impossible.
I ran upstairs very fast.
There's just no way.
I ran up so fast.
Why did he take the bike downstairs?
He was in the way.
Where is Seok Jin?
- Are you okay, Ki Jin? - Okay.
- Okay. - Seok Jin.
Didn't you take the bike downstairs?
- What? - You're acting strange.
What were you doing with the bike downstairs?
- He blocked your way, didn't he? - Yes, he did.
- Gosh. - What's wrong with him?
Why did you bring the bike downstairs?
- You're strange. - What?
- What did you do? - He was standing with the bike.
- Was he? - Were you trying to block him?
- Is he a spy? - Wait, is he really a spy?
Seok Jin, are you hiding something?
Did you encounter him on your way up here?
He was standing at the corridor with the bike, just like this.
(The timing was really unfortunate.)
(He was not stealing memories,)
Gosh, Seok Jin.
(but he was definitely stealing the bike.)
I just said "Gosh, Seok Jin." and ran past him.
(I needed something big for the mission.)
- My goodness. - Okay, I got it.
You didn't really take it, did you?
No, I told you, I didn't.
(It was too small, so I put it back.)
- That was really suspicious. - What's wrong with him?
Did you steal my gold?
No way.
Why would I do that? I'd never steal your gold.
I have no idea why he did that.
- It's time for the penalty. - I don't get it, either.
Get ready, you bicycle thief.
- Come on. Sit. - What? It's Kwang Soo's turn.
- Yes. It's Kwang Soo's turn. - Get down, Seok Jin.
Why did you take the bicycle?
- Yes. Why did you do that? - Honestly,
- I wanted to take it home. - He's strange.
- Did you try to take it? - Did you load it into your car?
- No, it's right over there. - Is it? Really?
- I've put it back there. - It isn't even Gary's bicycle.
It is his friend's bicycle.
I just asked people downstairs about its price.
You can't just take it.
I can.
- What? - What do you mean?
- You can't take it like that. - I want your glasses. Thank you.
- What's the matter with you? - No. I mean...
- My goodness. - What are you doing?
- Are you a spy? - Gosh. Here.
What are you doing with the glasses?
I'm really not a spy. Gosh.
Why are you yelling at us?
I'm talking, not yelling.
What's wrong with me yelling anyway? Is there a problem?
No. I mean that you don't have any reason to yell at us.
He's acting really strange.
- I shouldn't slap you softly. - Please slap softly.
All right. I get it.
(Slap)
He threw himself down on the floor.
I didn't slap him hard.
He's acting like a comedian.
(His reaction is clearly exaggerated.)
Do you want to become a comedian?
- What changed your mind? - He jumped backwards.
- Why did you jump like that? - Do you have a secret mission?
Did you see him jumping backwards just a moment after I slapped him?
- I did. - He actually jumped like that.
- He acted like a comedian. - He leaped like a frog.
(He reacted a moment after...)
(being slapped.)
I didn't slap him hard. You saw that, right?
He's like a comedian today.
(Seok Jin looks really suspicious.)
We had to win the race, but you ruined it.
- What's wrong with you? - Let's give it another try.
Please choose your next mission.
Let's pick 30,000km.
We must pass a mission, at least.
- Show the mission, please. - What's the mission?
- "Time Tables"? - It's about time tables.
The mission that everybody has to pass for 30,000km is...
"Wrong Time Tables".
- "Wrong Time Tables"? - "Wrong Time Tables"?
Each member has to answer time table questions.
When you answer the questions, you must give the number...
with correct 2nd digit but with the wrong 1st digit.
We must answer like, 2 times 9 is 19.
- Or 9 times 3 is 28. - How about 7 times 3 is 28?
- This is easier. - It's easier to get it wrong.
It's easier than the other way around.
(I'm sure we can pass this game.)
(I'll get it wrong to bid Gary farewell without any regret.)
- Are you going in this order? - Yes.
All right. Let's begin.
Wrong Time Tables
- Wrong Time Tables - Wrong Time Tables
What is 3 times 7?
22.
What is 6 times 4?
Thirty-throw.
(Is 6 times 4 thirty-throw?)
(What kind of number is that?)
What are you doing, Gary?
- What was that? - Do you have a special mission?
- You must be on a special mission. - What is "thirty-throw"?
What is "thirty-throw"?
- What language is that? - I lost my presence of mind.
I'm flustered because of the bicycle incident.
I just lifted it up because it was really pretty. Please forget it.
- Why did you try to steal the bike? - Why did you do that?
- You can't steal for that reason. - What is wrong with you?
- I can't stop thinking about it. - I did it because it was pretty.
Why did he bring it downstairs?
- Why did you do that, Seok Jin? - What was the reason?
- How could you do that? - Let's try one more time.
- Let's do it one more time. - This is your last chance.
He made a mistake because of the bike incident.
- We need another chance. - I'll give you a second chance.
- All right. We can do it. - Yes. Let's go.
- Don't get it wrong this time. - Yes. Be careful.
- Wrong Time Tables - Wrong Time Tables
What is 9 times 9?
84.
What is 6 times 4?
- 27. - He doesn't know the rule.
- You got the same question. - I need to get it wrong, right?
27.
That was way too slow.
All right. I'll do it properly next time.
- What do you mean by next time? - He's so shameless.
- We don't have another chance. - Come on.
- I thought that was acceptable. - Gary.
You're just as shameless as Seok Jin.
Both of you are really shameless.
Gary seriously needs to keep shooting Running Man.
- Gary, give it a second thought. - Come on, Gary.
You match us perfectly.
You shouldn't live like that.
I didn't have any trouble until now.
Gary, you belong here.
You can just use a calculator for multiplications.
- This is your final chance. - All right.
- Let's begin with Haha, again. - Okay. Stay focused, everyone.
- Wrong time tables - I feel...
- Okay. Let's begin. - I feel more pressured now.
(Seriously, let's deduct some distance.)
Let's start.
- Wrong time tables - Wrong time tables
What is 7 times 5?
32.
- What is 2 times 4? - Jix.
(Jix?)
(He's stupid enough to be part of Running Man.)
- You tried to say "6". - Was it 6?
- He said "Jix", instead. - He wanted to say "six".
- What was that? - You wanted to say "six".
I said a wrong number.
- Anyway... - What's the matter?
What did I do wrong?
- That was cute. - It was a cute six.
(He should've said a proper number.)
- That was really strange. - What on earth is "jix"?
- I said six. - You are strange.
- It was six. - Gary, just stay with us.
- "Jix". - My goodness.
I just spoke six a little differently.
What's wrong with his pronunciation?
- I said 6. - 2 times 4 is "jix".
We wouldn't be able to see him acting like this any more.
They might sound different, but they have the same meaning.
(It's the last time seeing Gary with them.)
- How could we fail? - We missed a great opportunity.
Should we try the ones which deduct 10,000km?
We shouldn't have failed "Wrong Time Tables".
What kind of present will Gary receive?
- Nothing. - We've got nothing so far.
Gary can win this Running Man Set.
What is that?
No.
Isn't it the set that we can buy at stationery stores?
It's the set containing the R flag, cue cards and R stickers.
Gary, if you get this set, set up the flag here...
so we can play Running Man games here.
Okay. We can use it that way.
- Good. - It's quite meaningful, then.
- It is meaningful. - Yes.
All right. Please choose the next game.
Let's pick 30,000km.
- "Yut"? - Good.
This is good.
(Everyone's happy with Yut.)
I'm sure I can ace this.
Everyone has to throw one yut each.
You will succeed If all yut shows the same side,
(All yut has to face the same side.)
I'm sure I can ace this.
(After 7 years together, this kind of mission is a piece of cake.)
(It's a great chance to deduct 30,000km.)
I'm really good at playing yut.
- Okay. - Let's go. Haha's first.
- Just flip it once in the air. - Yes. Just like that.
All right. Let's begin with Haha.
Everyone's yut has to show the same side facing up. Let's begin.
(Haha's yut shows the front side up.)
It might be harder than I thought.
(The front side up? I get it.)
(I just need to toss this yut lightly in the air.)
(Gary's yut shows the front side up.)
Good. Gary tossed it perfectly.
(I don't want to let you go, but I'll do my best for you.)
- That looks good. - Okay.
(Ji Hyo's yut shows the front side up.)
(We only have four more to go!)
(Did he fail?)
(Now, all Jong Kook needs is a bit of luck.)
(Jong Kook's yut shows the front side up.)
- That was really close. - Now, it's our turn.
- We only have three more to go. - All the unlucky ones are left.
(The Unlucky Trio will test their luck with their yut.)
Here comes the unlucky trio.
(Would unlucky Seok Jin be able to succeed this time?)
(Unbelievably, Seok Jin's yut shows the front side up.)
(The second member of the trio looks really anxious.)
- Here comes the super unlucky one. - You can do it, Kwang Soo.
- It's easy. - I thought I'd never have a chance.
- Come on, unlucky Kwang Soo. - Gosh.
- Come on. - We have the unluckiest two left.
- He's really nervous. - I thought I'd never have a chance.
Throw your yut at the same time.
Just toss it.
(It's my chance to show how lucky I am to everyone.)
- Okay. - Don't get too nervous.
Just toss it lightly in the air.
- Just toss it. - It's your turn now.
(I can do this. I can do this for Gary.)
(Gosh! Did he fail again?)
(Kwang Soo succeeds to get his yut show the front side up.)
(It's miraculous.)
- This is crazy. - Are you in your right mind?
- Gosh. - Jae Seok. It's your turn.
- Although you're unlucky... - You're the last.
Here comes the unluckiest.
He's definitely the unluckiest.
Can he do it?
- Just toss it. - Okay.
- It's okay, Jae Seok. - It's our chance to deduct...
- 30,000km. We count on you. - Just toss it lightly in the air.
- Just toss it. - Toss it lightly.
(Jae Seok's yut will decide whether Gary will get the R flag or not.)
(Jae Seok tries to concentrate.)
- Gary should receive something. - Toss it lightly. Just toss it.
If you fail, then Gary will receive nothing.
(Will they be able to give a present to Gary before he leaves?)
Toss it lightly and you will succeed.
(Will Jae Seok be able to get his yut showing front side up?)
(They succeeds "Yut" with all their yut showing front side up.)
- Good job. - Nice.
- My goodness. - We succeeded.
- Finally, we got this. - Good job, everyone.
- Finally, we did it. - We are a united team, indeed.
(7012 means that 7 of them are united as one.)
We are good at getting the same results.
- Thank you, everyone. - We are always good at this.
- That was close. - 30,000km is deducted.
- We finally deducted some distance. - How much is left?
- It's unbelievable. - The Unlucky Trio made it.
We can finish it if we choose and succeed the 50,000 one.
- Okay. - Wait.
- We need to clear one more mission. - I can't believe we did it.
Let's choose 30,000km first, then play another 10,000km.
Please show us what the game is.
Let's go.
- "Name Tag"? - What's that?
You need to find mini name tags.
Do we need to find them?
How small are they?
- Do you know the movie, "Ant-Man"? - Yes.
The name tags are as small as the Ant-Man from the movie.
Really?
How did you make such small name tags?
You have five minutes to find the name tags hidden in this studio.
- How about the living room? - You need to search there, too.
Can we help each other?
Do whatever you can. Just find them all in five minutes.
Five minutes? It's long enough to find them all.
Ready, set, start.
- You have five minutes from now. - Come on. We can do it.
It must be in this room.
(Let's do this for Gary.)
How am I supposed to find them?
How small are they?
I know there's one in this room.
(They can't find anything even with the help of the magnifying lens.)
Does this mean we can't see it with our naked eyes?
I think we'll be able to spot them.
It's highly likely they hid one in here.
(Gary is busy searching his room.)
Hold on.
(Seok Jin is looking for something bigger.)
(Is he going to steal the carpet?)
Ji Hyo is driving me crazy.
(Seok Jin only goes for big objects.)
Why did Ji Hyo have to steal that?
Is there one in the bathroom?
(Seok Jin steps on the carpet.)
(Are you moving?)
- Did you find it? - No.
(Seok Jin has obtained the carpet.)
This is so hard.
- Did you find it? - It's Jong Kook.
- Where is it? - Look.
- Jong Kook. - What?
- I found yours. - You found it?
(Seok Jin is about to get caught.)
(I'll take the carpet over the bicycle.)
- How small is it? - You can spot them with your eyes.
How did you find that?
- Jong Kook. - What?
- I found yours. - How small is it?
(Gary comes into the living room.)
(Seok Jin can't afford to get caught stealing again.)
It's Jong Kook's.
(Seok Jin is about to step outside.)
(Gary appears right on time.)
(He's closing in on Seok Jin.)
(What will happen to Seok Jin?)
Really?
This was the only one.
(He managed to escape.)
Can you hold the door for me?
This is so heavy.
This will work.
I'm sure of it.
This can't not work.
(The bicycle thief grew as a big time thief.)
How did they all do this?
- The diameter is 236cm. - That's it?
It's good, right?
You've succeeded.
(Seok Jin succeeded the secret mission.)
I didn't think the bicycle would be too small.
I have to pay him back now for the bicycle.
(All the members have succeeded.)
(They succeeded the mission with 8 seconds remaining.)
You've succeeded.
Where'd the carpet go?
- Where did it go? - There used to be a carpet here.
Where did it go?
The staff moved it because it was getting dusty.
The room looks so vacant now.
Didn't the room look better with the carpet?
The staff moved it somewhere.
It's not in the back of your car, is it?
What are you talking about? That's nonsense.
It got even dustier in here.
They said it's not good for the respiratory system.
(First the bicycle and now the carpet? This is strange.)
You have accumulated 60,000km.
(They accumulated that much after 7 failed attempts.)
- Let's do 30,000 now. - Let's do it.
Should we do 30,000 for "Staff Members"?
- That's the only one left. - Let's do it, then.
30,000 for "Staff Members".
(I have a bad feeling about this.)
Please turn it over.
(What's the mission for 30,000km?)
("Camera Staff")
- "Camera Staff". - What's that?
For this mission,
you will have to arm wrestle the camera staff.
(This is bad news.)
Just one of us?
Three people from each side will have a battle of arm wrestle.
- The first team to win twice wins. - Two wins?
- I'm not good at arm wrestling. - Me neither.
(Jong Kook is getting warmed up.)
We will bring out three members from the camera staff.
- This is going to be hard. - They're so strong.
- They'll break our arms. - They're really strong.
(Here they come.)
We should be fine as long as the zimizib staff doesn't come.
(Everything will be okay as long as it's not the zimizib staff.)
I think it's him.
(Gary has a bad feeling.)
(You can tell he's strong in a glance.)
(This man has a history.)
(He almost covered the Running Man Field Day with blood.)
(You'll be hospitalised with a slight nudge by him.)
(It's Mr Zimizib, Yoon Hong Min.)
- Are you kidding me? - He shouldn't be here.
(Jong Kook looks slightly nervous.)
This is too much.
(This can't be done.)
I'll introduce the lineup of the team.
There's Yoon Hong Min.
He's so strong.
- The youngest one is Suh Dong Hwi. - He looks strong.
Their last member and leader is Kang Chan Hee.
(Kang Chan Hee, Team Leader)
I'll go against him.
We'll take a win from him.
Chan Hee isn't all that.
(Mr Kang prefers technique over strength.)
Please decide on who'll go first.
(The order will greatly affect the result.)
(On the other hand, the camera staff look at ease.)
(Both teams decided on the order of the lineup.)
These are the two people for the first match.
The first player from Running Man is...
(The first player from Running Man is?)
- Gary. - Yes!
The first player from the camera staff is...
- Kang Chan Hee. - I knew it.
(Kang Chan Hee goes first.)
- We have to win this one. - You have to win.
- I can't afford to win. - You have to win.
- Don't let your guard down. - He could be strong.
- Don't underestimate him. - I haven't worked out for so long.
Look at his arms.
(He has strong muscles from holding heavy cameras.)
Look at how broad his shoulders are.
Chan Hee is pretty strong, too.
His grip is so strong.
He's been working with heavy cameras all this time.
He's so strong. I don't think I'll win.
Get ready.
(It's the battle between the leaders of each team.)
(This won't be easy for both sides.)
Set. Go.
He won.
(He's surprised.)
(That was the end of him.)
- Did you let me win? - No.
(He does prefer technique over strength.)
- What was that? - That was easy.
Team Running Man is leading by one point.
We just need one more victory now.
Who's up next?
The second player from Running Man is Kwang Soo.
- Okay. - You can win it for us.
The second player from the camera staff is Yoon Hong Min.
(It's Yoon Hong Min.)
(I'm going against the zimizib?)
What a twist of fate.
Kwang Soo isn't that weak.
(Mr Zimizib enters the stage.)
(The 2nd round is Kwang Soo against Hong Min.)
(He's very serious.)
(He's determined.)
It feels totally different this time.
This is an important match.
Ready.
(The fate of "Balance the Distance" lies in Kwang Soo's hands.)
Set, go!
(The 2nd round begins.)
(It's a close one.)
Kwang Soo is fighting back.
He's winning.
(Kwang Soo unleashes his power against Mr Zimizib.)
(We only thought of Kwang Soo as...)
(a tall and weak giraffe.)
(He's always been a troublemaker.)
I can't do this. This is the end of me.
(He's determined...)
(to give something to Gary.)
(He's trying his hardest.)
(Is he going to make the miracle happen?)
Kwang Soo is determined.
Is this really happening?
(Kwang Soo wins!)
(He did it!)
(Kwang Soo desperately wanted to win this one for Gary.)
(He's in pain.)
- He's a beast. - He's stronger than he looks.
That was amazing.
(Kwang Soo's surprising performance puts an end to Gary's last mission.)
The score is 2 to 0.
The game is over. You have succeeded.
(They successfully accumulate a total of 77,000km.)
Do I win the flag?
You will be awarded with the Running Man package.
(Gary wins the Running Man package as a reward.)
We should've done better for him.
At least, he won something.
I'll put out the flag even when it rains or snows.
What's all this junk?
You have no idea how much the kids love these things.
(They will be sold at high prices among elementary school kids.)
I like the flags.
There's another gift from the staff members.
- Really? - Is Gary really leaving?
(These are the gifts.)
- What's this? - Is it a puzzle?
They made your face with all the pictures of the past.
They're pictures of the members from episode 1 to 317.
- This is amazing. - You made my face with those?
Yes. Look at this picture whenever you miss us.
It's made of gold.
What?
Are you serious?
- What is that? - It's made of gold.
Thank you...
- for all the memories. - It's severance pay.
That's your severance pay.
Gary has been with us every Sunday.
It's time to say goodbye now.
This is his last day with us.
Let's give a big round of applause...
for all his hard work.
- Thank you. - Good job, Gary.
(Well done.)
Looks like...
Ji Hyo will have to find a new boyfriend.
I thought she'd cry. I'm a bit disappointed.
Ji Hyo should say something.
(Ji Hyo spent the most time with him as Monday Couple.)
I already talked to him in private.
I see.
I'm sad.
I'm sad to see you leave,
but I support you in all of your endeavours. Good luck.
I'll repeat what Ji Hyo said about Gary...
when Gary wasn't present at the time.
"Mondays without him will feel so empty from now on."
- She said that while crying. - When did I say that?
- I didn't say that. - I heard her say something else.
"Is Gary out of his mind?"
That's what I heard.
Gary talked about his dreams as a musician.
We hope your dreams will come true.
Thank you, Gary.
Thank you.
We'll have dinner with everyone.
Is that so? Shall we go?
Gary, please close the clapperboard to end the show.
It's your last time.
In 1, 2, 3.
- Thank you, everyone. - Let's take a photo.
(It's time for a farewell party.)
Do we go inside?
Did you prepare this for me?
(We want Gary, our boyfriend on Mondays, to stay.)
Thank you so much for the last seven years, and enjoy the food.
Thank you for everything. Thank you.
Thank you.
(We thank Gary for 77,000km of his passion.)
Enjoy your food.
(Running Man will stay with you wherever you go.)
- See you. - Thank you.
Goodbye.
(He says farewell to the members.)
See you, Gary.
- I'll see you next week. - Sure.
- See you. - Thank you.
- Goodbye. - Bye.
(He says farewell to everyone.)
(He looks around.)
Why do you keep following me?
I have to pull myself together back in the studio.
Could we record a short video message of you?
A video message?
We left the camera in your studio.
You haven't taken it yet?
- I'd like to take it now. - Okay.
It's completely empty.
(Gary's back looks sad and lonely.)
(It feels empty.)
What's this?
(There's a big present in the middle of his studio.)
(What's this?)
(He takes the card.)
"Six members excluding you..."
"were given..."
"a secret mission today."
"It was to steal an item that commemorated the time with you."
"They've returned the stolen items and only took the memories..."
"they've had with you."
(The members gave presents to commemorate their times together.)
"Here's your last mission."
"Put the items back to where they were."
They stole items that were difficult to carry...
to remember them by.
Gosh, what's this?
(Is it a present?)
They left me presents where the stolen item...
used to be.
(Kwang Soo gave him speakers Gary always wanted to have.)
(He also wrote him a letter.)
It's a handwritten letter.
"Dear Gary, I still can't believe that you're leaving."
"I regret that I haven't expressed enough of my love, gratitude..."
"and apologies to you."
I'll read it later.
If I read it now,
I might get tearful.
I won't get to see you every Monday from now on,
but we're already a family.
I'll call you more, and I hope that...
we see each other more often.
Kwang Soo, I love you.
(He's grateful to Gary for being there for him.)
Dear Gary,
thank you so much. I love you forever.
It's from Jong Kook.
(Gary and Jong Kook are close.)
"Gary, you know how I feel."
"It's so difficult to write a letter like this to you."
You worked hard for a long time. Stay healthy.
Good luck in everything you do.
We'll still see each other, so let's not be sad.
I bought you some cosmetics so please become handsome.
I hope you will transform.
Gosh, Seok Jin.
(Why did he steal this?)
(Seok Jin's present is red ginseng.)
Goodness.
Isn't this a gift he received on Chuseok?
(It looks like a Chuseok present.)
Gary, I still can't believe it.
During the last seven years, we talked about many things.
We shared a room together during mud games...
and waited for our turns to shower.
On one hand, I was angry when I heard that you're quitting.
But I also understood you, so I was confused about what I felt.
I'll have to respect your wish.
I love you, Gary.
I still remember this...
about Haha. We were in a car together.
I told him that I was invited to join Running Man.
Then I asked him if he's also joining, and he said yes.
I told him that I was worried as I've never been on a variety show.
I didn't know what I should do.
I wanted to remain a musician at the time,
but this is what he told me.
(Haha said...)
He said that if I'm also good at doing variety shows,
I shouldn't shy away from it.
I still remember him saying that.
We were in the back seat of a car at a gas station.
(Haha's words brought Gary to Running Man.)
It's very light.
Gosh!
(Haha got him three dried squids.)
Gary, I can't believe it.
When the ratings weren't that high in the beginning of Running Man,
we spent the night at Han River. We prayed for things...
to turn out well at my house. We rolled on the floor laughing.
I miss the times when we dreamed while drinking soju.
I hope you'll be healthy...
and have a wonderful family after you get married.
Let's get old together.
- I love you. - You're my role model.
I love you.
I love you. From Haha who's more handsome than you.
(He remembers each of his precious memories.)
(He finds a present from Jae Seok.)
Goodness, what's this?
(Jae Seok gave him sneakers for his new journey.)
"Gary, it's been seven years since we've been on Running Man together."
Gary, I'll think of you during next week's recording.
As I know what you want to achieve in the future,
the other members and I support you in all of your endeavours.
Call me any time you want to be back on a variety show.
Okay, Gary? See you.
It's too embarrassing for me to continue, so I stop here.
See you again. I'll call you. You did a good job.
(The only item that remains is the plant.)
Gosh, Ji Hyo.
(His heart feels as heavy as the plant.)
My dear Ji Hyo.
There are two presents from her.
She gave me an electronic massager.
I often get muscle pains because I have spinal disc herniation.
She used to massage my shoulders at times...
during the recording...
and stretched my lower back.
Since she won't be around, she gave me this.
(Ji Hyo's second present is...)
(a photo album of Monday Couple.)
I remember this time.
(He remembers a photo.)
I remember that she said I could be such a handful.
I still remember her saying that.
You can be such a handful!
We have to stay together in spirit.
(Gary and Ji Hyo looked the best when they were together.)
Gary, this is Ji Hyo.
I was very shocked when I heard that you're leaving,
so I was in a daze for a few days.
I took for granted...
that until the very end, which we don't know when,
all of us would stay on this show.
Perhaps, I was lost in that belief.
I was upset and cried,
but now that I think about it,
I realised how difficult it must have been for you...
to make such a decision.
I'm sorry about the things that I didn't know about.
I felt bad thinking about how hard it must have been for you.
Now that you won't be where you always used to be...
for the last seven years, I'll feel sad and lonely,
but I'll stay strong.
"I'll stay strong."
"If you miss us too much,"
"come back any time."
"No one can fill your place where you've been..."
"for the last seven years, so I'll leave it for you."
(They were special to each other.)
Hello, it's nice to see you. This is Gary.
I'm here to say my last farewell.
I was a singer...
that no one recognised,
but as I was on Running Man,
people started to find out about me...
and I received a lot of support.
I lacked in many ways,
but please keep watching Running Man since there are still...
other members and the staff who work hard for this show.
Please love the show as usual.
Wherever I go,
I'll try my best to live up to your expectations.
I really appreciate it. I've had a wonderful time so far.
Take care. Thank you.
(The 324 episodes, 2311 days and 77,000km with you...)
(won't be forgotten.)
(Like so, our beautiful goodbyes to Gary...)
(did not happen.)
Stop it! Leave me alone.
You're so mean to me.