(Running Man's late summer blockbuster)
Why am I going to prison?
(Survive until the end.)
(Do not go to the end.)
I'm not going to prison. No way.
What prison? I don't want to go to prison.
(Train to Prison)
I'm going to Jeonju. Why are you doing this?
Prison? Prison? Prison?
(A sunny day in late summer at Suseo Station)
Should I sit down?
(Are they going on a trip by train?)
Really?
(7 years of Running Man tells me there's something going on.)
What's all this?
- Hello. - Hello.
(What's going on?)
Here we are at Suseo Station.
- This train station will open... - KTX.
I know that.
- And start operating soon. - Oh, I see.
The trains bound for Gwangju and Jeolla-do will stop here, right?
Today, we are going on a leisure trip departing here.
We'll go on a leisure trip.
- A leisure trip? - Do you really mean it?
You get to choose the destinations.
(A journey on a train that will take you to wherever you want? )
We'll go wherever you want to go.
- A leisure trip? - Do you really mean it?
(The mountains and the oceans are calling us.)
So anywhere is fine?
Yes, as long as we can go by train.
If you say it like that, then I'm not sure where to go.
- How about Mokpo? - Mokpo sounds good.
- Small octopus, small octopus. - Let's eat small octopus there.
Mokpo is famous for delicious food.
Since Mokpo is a harbour city,
we should also go to the beach when it's still summer.
(Romantic, late summer beach)
(Wait, if it's the west...)
- Jeonju is also a good choice. - I want to go to Jeonju.
Jeonju is famous for kongnamul gukbap.
There are lots of great restaurants there.
(How about we feel the essence of quiet and peaceful Korean charm?)
How about Yeosu?
Night sea at Yeosu
(How about enjoying the scenery of the beautiful port in Yeosu?)
- Where should we go? - Where should we go?
I say Mokpo is the place to go.
- Jeonju. We should go to Jeonju. - Let's go to Mokpo for the octopus.
- What's all this? - I like Jeonju since it's close.
- What? - Hello.
(Guards enter with huge train tickets.)
Are we writing down where we want to go?
- Have you all decided? - Yes.
You just write your destination on the tickets and show us.
All right.
- Where do you want to go? - Me?
I want to visit Jeonju.
I'll choose somewhere close.
Does the train stop at Yeosu, as well?
(The walls break.)
Why? What's wrong? What?
(They are attacked by strangers.)
- What? Why? - Why are you doing this?
(Gary is forced to write something.)
- Why are you doing this? - What's happening?
(Are they being forced to write their destinations?)
- You're driving me crazy! - Hold on for a moment!
- You are making me go crazy! - I'm going to Yeosu!
I said, I'm going to Yeosu!
I'm going to Jeonju!
- What is this? - Let go. I want to go to Jeonju.
(Jong Kook is still resisting.)
(They are forced to write their destinations.)
- What is this? - I don't want to go there.
I don't want to go to prison! Why would you send me to prison?
Prison?
(Prison?)
(What's going on?)
- Prison? - Why did you write that down?
- Why would we go to prison? - Somebody help me.
(Is prison the final destination of the leisure trip?)
- Not me! - Why are you doing this to me?
(You said we could go anywhere.)
- What is this? - I'm not going to prison.
Why would I go to prison?
- I'm not going there. - I wanted to go to Jeonju.
I see that everybody wants to go to prison.
(All seven members wrote down "prison" as their destination.)
This isn't democratic.
- You will all go to prison. - What is this?
(Are you kidding me?)
You went over the line.
- Prison? - Don't mess around with us.
- Start talking. - Are you crazy?
That's what you wrote down.
We've prepared costumes that suit your destination.
- Please get changed. - Is this a joke?
- Are we wearing prison uniforms? - I can't believe this.
I thought they were the station staff members.
(What an absurd situation.)
(Will they be sent to prison now?)
(They start getting changed.)
This isn't even the right size.
(They're all the same size.)
Prisoners don't ask for things like that.
- We're prisoners after all. - This is violating my human rights.
What is this?
The pants look comfortable.
These are the refrigerator pants.
(The train to prison awaits.)
Everyone, you wrote down prison as the desired destination.
- When did we want to go to prison? - They're bullies.
- He's a tyrant. - The final destination is prison.
Before you arrive at the prison,
there might be a chance to escape.
Oh, really?
If you fail to escape and end up in prison,
you will serve the community...
by appearing on live television during Chuseok holidays.
(Live television on Chuseok?)
Did you say Chuseok?
You will be appearing on live television.
- I'm here at the Seoul Tollgate. - How does traffic look?
There is increasing traffic on the road.
The traffic on the highways is congested to the maximum level.
I already bought tickets for the vacation.
- Are you serious? - This is not good.
Going live on air is a big deal.
(It's the biggest penalty there is.)
(We have to escape.)
(Suseo Station)
(10 minutes before the departure of Train to Prison)
It's a leisure trip to prison.
(They didn't know it would come to this.)
(Escaping is the only solution.)
(They won't let us escape that easily.)
(They are moving to the platform where the Train to Prison awaits.)
Isn't that Lee Seul?
- What's she doing over there? - It's Lee Seul.
Why is she here?
What is Lee Seul doing here?
What are you doing here?
Oh, you got a job here? I haven't seen you in a long time.
Are these the numbers for our seats?
- We're supposed to sit there? - Yes.
What is this place?
(What?)
- Wait. - We're not alone.
(There are other people on the train.)
This is like a transportation vehicle for prisoners.
We're not the only prisoners.
I'm 7B.
- Where's 7B? - Where am I?
- This is mine right here. - I'm 9B.
I'm 10C.
I'm scared.
(Laughing)
9C.
I'm beside a gangster.
(Oh, no.)
(Haha has to sit beside a scary looking prisoner.)
He's not a gangster.
He got in here for urinating in public.
Oh, my.
Hello.
(Don't talk to me.)
Ladies and gentlemen, we would like to welcome you aboard.
(He's anxious.)
There's even an announcement.
You will be able to escape the train...
if all members work together and successfully complete the missions.
- We have to work together. - We are a team.
We have good teamwork.
We're working together.
We will do our best to make the trip safe and sound.
The train will be leaving soon.
(Enjoy your ride. The train will be leaving soon.)
(Running Man "Train to Prison")
(There's a mission for every carriage.)
(Quick-witted carriage)
(Bedazzling carriage)
(Passing carriage)
(Probability carriage)
(If they fail a mission, they will advance to the next carriage.)
(It means they will have higher chances of ending up in prison.)
We didn't do anything wrong.
We didn't commit any crime. There wasn't a court hearing.
One law for the rich and another for the poor.
(Close your mouth.)
(It's silent.)
(We shouldn't play around in here.)
(He's shaking his legs.)
I'm sorry, but can you cut that out?
- It's bothering me. - What was that?
Come on.
- Is there something wrong? - He keeps shaking his legs.
(Who is?)
- What? - Is this your first time?
- I'm sorry? - He has a line.
I didn't know he had a line.
- I didn't know he had a line. - Me neither.
The person next to me looks like he committed an economic crime.
- You're right. - He doesn't look the violent type.
- It must have been corporate crime. - I see.
What's this?
Gary's partner looks much better than him.
Can I get a different prisoner?
Can I get Haha's prisoner instead?
Gary, can you take off the hat for a second?
- Wow. - You look like you belong here.
You look like a real prisoner.
I thought this was the real prison for a second.
- Gary is for real. - That's hilarious.
(He only needs to take off the hat.)
(The train is quietly making its way to prison.)
- Oh, it's starting. - Finally.
(Is it a mission?)
We will now begin the mission of the quick-witted carriage.
Quick-witted carriage?
(What's that?)
This carriage is a quick-witted carriage.
Only the quick-witted will be able to escape.
Survive the game of Blue and White Flag.
- What? - Quick-witted carriage?
(Did she say quick-witted?)
- Window seats, stand up. - One.
What did she say?
(Window seats, stand up.)
- What? - Aisle seats, sit down.
Aisle seats, don't stand up. Window seats, stand up.
- Window seats should stand. - I see.
Window seats, don't stand up. 10A stand up.
(10A is supposed to stand up.)
(He casually takes a seat.)
10A has failed the mission.
- Who is 10A? - What are you doing?
He's out?
What is this? How can you be so shameless?
- We failed already? - He has no muscles.
- Is he being dragged out? - Is that what happens when we fail?
- That's it? - He's out just like that?
- What is this? - What is this?
Did he do that on purpose?
He just took off.
He didn't even care.
(Nobody knows what will happen in the Train to Prison.)
Did we fail?
Focus.
The mission will start again.
- Be quiet, I can't hear her. - Okay.
Row 7, don't stand up. Row 10, stand up.
10D has failed the mission.
Are you kidding me?
(What's up with this guy?)
What happened?
Are you a hacker?
- I thought he was the brain. - He's clearly not.
- He didn't fail on purpose, did he? - I think he did it on purpose.
- That can't be. - They seriously failed?
- He was serious. - He didn't know how to play.
The mission will start again.
9B, stand up.
8C, don't stand up. 8B, sit down.
10C, stand up.
9B, sit down.
10B and 10C, stand up together.
The one behind 10B, stand up.
(The one behind 10B, stand up.)
(Jong Kook is behind 10B.)
(Is that me?)
9B has failed the mission.
Why did he fail?
She said that the one behind 10B should stand up.
- I'm done? - He's dressed up and everything.
Wait, you're 10B?
(You're not quick-witted, Jong Kook.)
The members of Running Man have failed the quick-witted mission.
(Quick-witted carriage mission failed.)
Jong Kook messed it all up.
He's usually good at games.
You will move on to the next carriage...
and perform a new mission.
- Are we going forward? - As I said,
all members must complete the mission in order to escape.
(This is not looking good.)
(Quick-witted carriage)
(Bedazzling carriage)
- Let's move to the next carriage. - Let's go.
- Good job, everyone. - Good job, everyone.
Where should we go?
What's this?
(They get strapped something on their waists.)
What is this?
It's some kind of a pouch.
This is a popular look these days.
(What is this bag?)
Something's in here.
- Is it food? - What is this?
Can I open it?
(Can I open it?)
Oh, it's food.
(Things must be rough from here if they're already giving you food.)
(Whatever. Let's just eat.)
It's an announcement.
This is the bedazzling carriage.
All of you must enjoy the next train and pass without reaching "baek".
- She told us to pass. - What did she say?
She told us to pass without reaching "baek".
- She must be referring to our bags. - Which "baek" is she talking about?
Should we leave our bags and pass?
- What does she mean by "baek"? - Maybe it's the number 100?
- Really? - It sounds possible too.
I don't think we should say the word "baek".
(What's the meaning of this "baek"?)
(They enter the second carriage.)
- What is this? - My goodness.
(Who set up a ballroom inside the train?)
- There are some female passengers. - They are all beautiful.
I guess they're not prisoners.
Do I know her?
(One woman has brought all of these women here.)
(Is she the leader?)
(She's the dancing queen, Hyo Lyn!)
(Why is she here?)
(She showed how good she was at dancing this July with Gary.)
(So why is she here?)
(The music begins without any notice.)
(All the passengers begin dancing.)
(The women force the prisoners to dance.)
(They all begin dancing, too.)
What's going on?
(Hyo Lyn stands up.)
(Here comes Hyo Lyn, everyone.)
Oh, Hyo Lyn. It's you.
- It's Hyo Lyn. - Hyo Lyn.
- What are they doing? - It's Hyo Lyn.
Gary.
- Hyo Lyn is here. - Where?
(Gary is really surprised to see Hyo Lyn here.)
(Gary and Hyo Lyn finally meet each other again.)
What's going on?
(All the passengers just keep dancing.)
(Let's dance together with them.)
(How have you been, Hyo Lyn?)
Hey, Hyo Lyn.
It seems that you became better at dancing.
You're better than before.
What's going on anyway?
What do we need to do?
(Do you want to know what this is?)
(You know it already.)
(So what does "baek" mean?)
Oh, I don't care any more.
Oh my gosh.
(Gary is absorbed in dancing.)
- Gary enjoyed it so much. - What's going on?
- Oh my gosh. - What was it about?
Who are these people anyway?
Hyo Lyn, do you know what's going on?
(I know. That was ridiculous.)
- Lee Seul. What are you doing? - Lee Seul.
- What are you doing? - How can you treat us like this?
- What's going on? - Lee Seul.
Lee Seul, is there something in our bags?
There must be.
What? What is it?
(What was inside our bags?)
(It's a pedometer.)
There was a pedometer.
(Why did you put it in?)
What's my number?
Is it 172?
Who scored 172?
I did.
This is a bedazzling carriage.
You could've escaped if none of you were bedazzled.
You've failed the mission.
What did you do?
- You scored so high. - So it was the number 100.
Was that the reason why you told me to dance really hard?
- How could you do that? - She did?
Yes, she did.
- You must keep moving. - Really?
She says we need to move a lot.
(Don't score over 100 in your pedometer.)
Wait. Show me everyone's scores.
Kwang Soo, you scored 161.
Your scores must be high. You were close to Hyo Lyn.
Our scores are high because she told us to dance hard.
(Gary scored 180.)
Gary, your score is 180.
Well, I'm glad it's below 200.
- Total? - Yes, I didn't dance a lot.
Jong Kook danced only with his hands.
His score is too low.
I could feel the pedometer inside my bag.
(Although Jong Kook scored really low, they failed their mission.)
(Only Jong Kook and Ji Hyo scored less than 100.)
Gosh. It was close.
All of you scored over 100 except Ji Hyo and Jong Kook.
- Jong Kook's score is way too low. - What's wrong with it?
Even if I lie down and sleep, I can easily score more than that.
- How did you do it? - I had a strange feeling...
I had a strange feeling about the mission.
I can score more than 10 during my sleep.
Four is seriously too low. It really is.
Please take a sit and wait for the next instruction.
Can I talk to them while we wait?
What's your job?
We're Sistar's backup dancers.
(No wonder you were good at dancing.)
- You are dancers. - No wonder.
That was why...
they kept complaining about the music.
They said that the music was bad so it was hard to dance.
Are you here for the mission?
- Are you going to prison with us? - No.
- So are you getting off the train? - Yes.
- At this station? - Yes.
- Let's go together with us. - You leave after bedazzling us?
You and Gary should stay together for some time.
(Just wear these pants first. We'll talk after that.)
She made us dance.
- Wear these, Hyo Lyn. - That's okay.
Those are my pants, but I haven't worn them yet.
Wear those pants and stay with us.
We have two couples. You and Gary, and Jong Kook and Soo Ae.
- What do you mean? - You know what I mean.
Is Soo Ae here, too?
She might be waiting for us.
(Hyo Lyn and her backup dancers leave the train.)
- Bye, Hyo Lyn. - Bye.
- See you. - Bye, Hyo Lyn.
(I wish your successful escape.)
(They're getting near the prison every second.)
We were too excited.
It's good to enjoy what you got, but you should think beforehand.
We failed our first mission because of you.
(Don't you remember?)
Come on, everyone, we can do it.
(We've failed 2 times already.)
Next stop is the labouring platform.
(Labouring platform?)
The train will stop at the labouring platform shortly.
Running Man members, please get off the train and follow instructions.
- All right. Let's escape. - Let's escape.
- Let's go. - Yes. Let's go.
(Will they be able to escape the train at this stop?)
This stop is the labouring platform.
Everyone, get off the train immediately.
- The platform looks really nice. - You know where to sit, right?
- Yes. - Show your respect to the guards.
Nice to see you all.
- Get out of the train. Quickly. - Hurry up.
(They talk really rude.)
- Who are they? - Please take your seat.
- What? - Why are they here?
(GOT7 are the prison guards.)
(They are sharp and keen. They will be excellent warders.)
(You can't escape. Only work will bring you freedom.)
- Hurry up and get out. - When did you come here?
Please take a seat.
(Hurry up and sit down.)
- Hello. - Where should we sit?
Everyone, sit.
Get ready to work, everyone.
(Jong Kook seems uncomfortable.)
(What labouring will they do?)
You can leave if you finish stamping all of these.
You have to stamp 10,000 envelopes in a given time.
You have 20 minutes.
- 10,000 envelopes? - Get ready...
(We have to stamp 10,000 envelopes in 20 minutes?)
- That's a lot. - Start.
- Please stamp the other side. - Where should I stamp?
- Stamp the other side of envelope. - Stamp them prettily.
10,000 envelopes? Really?
My goodness.
- Stamp correctly. - We need to stamp 10,000 of these.
(Each member has to stamp about 1,500 envelopes to pass.)
It's a lot, but we can do it.
Jae Seok. Stamp like this.
Flip your envelopes like this.
It's much easier to do it this way.
- It's much faster this way. - How many minutes do we have?
You have 10,000 envelopes to stamp in total.
- Hey, Jae Seok. - We're doing great.
Jae Seok! Do it like this.
(Kwang Soo finds another trick.)
Do it like this.
- No cheating. - I'm not.
No cheating.
(What did I do wrong?)
- No cheating, please. - Don't use any tricks.
Stamp each envelope carefully. Check the ink each time.
This is a technique. It has nothing to do with cheating.
No cheating.
(Running Man prisoners are getting better at this labour.)
This is really hard.
(They have a lot more.)
(Look at Jong Kook.)
(He's working really quietly.)
Kwang Soo's method is the fastest.
Please sit down.
(We are watching you.)
We have 10,000 envelopes. So we have to stamp more than 1,000 each.
Shut your mouth!
What did you just say?
Seok Jin's angry.
- What did you just say? - Have manners!
Hey, Jackson.
(He's so into his role.)
- How can we stamp 10,000 of these? - Can I put these on the floor?
- Please sit. - How can we stamp 10,000...
(He looks shocked.)
We still have a long way to go.
(What did he see?)
You must sit.
7B, sit down.
(No matter what happens around him, Jong Kook is really consistent.)
(Seok Jin looks around.)
No cheating. Keep working.
- Don't put it in your pocket. - Why would you take it anyway?
My goodness.
(He pretends as if nothing happened.)
Kwang Soo's method works the best.
Something's written on this envelope.
(Did you find it too?)
(Staring)
(What have they found?)
(Kwang Soo also puts the envelope in his pocket.)
- All right. - Okay.
- Jee Seok Jin. - Thank you.
This is really hard.
(Security guards are everywhere.)
(What's the scheme?)
Please stamp them and keep things organised.
Guard? I'm so exhausted.
- Please hurry up. - It's really hard.
Prisoners are talking too much. Do the work.
(What did these two see?)
(A mysterious message is written on the envelope.)
(If name tag is torn while fleeing, you fail or are out for a minute.)
(Somewhere near R1 Station is a car to use for fleeing.)
This is too much.
- Sir, it's really hard. - Prisoners are talking too much.
(Jong Kook still hasn't found the hint.)
- The weather's too hot today. - Three minutes passed.
Stamping 10,000 envelopes is hard no matter how quickly you do it.
How can we stamp 10,000 envelopes?
Let's try it.
- Let's do it. - You can do it.
(Kwang Soo only pretends.)
Do it one by one like this.
Hurry up, hurry up.
Come on.
You need to start wrapping up now.
You have to finish up.
Okay.
(He's stuffing something in.)
- Seriously, it's too difficult. - Why this is...
- Haha is really fast. - Come on, guys.
- Do it faster. - Jong Kook seems angry.
- He seems angry, indeed. - This is difficult.
(Kwang Soo stands up while looking around carefully.)
Come on, people.
(He sneaks out towards the back.)
Goodness.
What's going on?
(Kwang Soo is running away.)
- What's going on? - What happened?
Take everything with you.
(Seok Jin looks around.)
(Seok Jin escapes as well.)
- Take everything with you. - Take everything.
(They run quickly.)
(The rest are in daze.)
Move out!
(Will he be caught or not?)
- Let's continue stamping. - What are you looking at?
(The guards surround the remaining prisoners.)
Work harder.
(Kwang Soo runs away at an amazing speed.)
(Jin Young catches onto him.)
(It's a major chase.)
No!
(If prisoners lose their name tags, they're sent to a solitary cell.)
(When guards lose their name tags, they get suspended for 1 minute.)
I almost got him.
- Guys, stay focused. - Come on and stay focused.
(Prisoners continue to stamp.)
(The chase continues.)
(Seok Jin runs for his freedom.)
(Will he be arrested like this?)
(He slips away.)
(His name tag is ripped.)
(Seok Jin fails to escape.)
(The guards are close to cornering Kwang Soo.)
(Why is he running in the opposite direction?)
Why is Kwang Soo suddenly trying to run away?
Seok Jin went somewhere, too.
Where did he go?
(I'm here.)
We should just work hard for now.
There must be something, but I have no idea.
(He was free for less than 30 seconds.)
This is a real solitary cell.
Oh my gosh, this is so real. Is this a toilet?
It is a solitary cell, indeed.
Oh my goodness, the toilet is here.
It's a real solitary cell.
(He is pathetic.)
- Are you tired? - I'm so exhausted.
Jackson, I'm being serious.
Look how much I've done.
(He gives him more envelopes.)
(Guard Jackson has no mercy at all.)
Goodness, I'm about to lose my mind.
- What's wrong? - Where did Kwang Soo go?
(Here he comes.)
(Runaway Kwang Soo is everywhere.)
- Wait! - What?
(GOT7 guards are right after him.)
He's too tall.
(JB, Jin Young and Mark are on Kwang Soo now.)
(Will Kwang Soo be arrested?)
(He rips Mark's name tag.)
(Mark has to freeze for 1 minute.)
(Kwang Soo is resisting so fiercely.)
(I will escape.)
- How many have you done so far? - I don't know.
You're not counting, are you?
- Why aren't you? - How can I?
Why did they run away instead of finishing these off?
We have to stamp 10,000 envelopes.
They should've stayed and finished these together.
It's like watching a video.
You should say "VOD", not "video". It's more trending.
Stop pretending as if you know all new things.
Goodness, I can picture it. It's like I'm watching them on VOD.
Please do not argue.
We're not arguing. We were just having a conversation.
How many minutes do we have left?
You have a few minutes left.
(He presses firmly.)
Let's not press too hard.
How can I not?
- He tells us not to do anything. - How can I stamp then?
(My eyes are on you!)
(Kwang Soo is still resisting.)
Wait a minute.
(He rips JB's name tag.)
(JB gets suspended for 1 minute as well.)
Come here!
(Bambam comes to help.)
We can't stamp all 10,000 envelopes.
It's just my personal goal.
Are you okay? Isn't it too hot?
(Haha also finds the hint for escaping.)
(Kwang Soo stands face-to-face with Jin Young.)
(One who's trying to stop the other versus one who wants to escape)
(I will catch you.)
(No way.)
(It's a fierce battle.)
(Kwang Soo increases his chance to escape if he tackles Jin Young.)
(I'll definitely escape.)
(Jin Young rips his name tag.)
(Kwang Soo gets arrested.)
(I was so close to escaping.)
(He arrests Kwang Soo with his strong will.)
I wouldn't have tried to escape if I knew I was going to be arrested.
Why did I even try?
(Kwang Soo fails to escape.)
Why are all GOT7's members so good?
It's because we're younger.
Be quiet!
I'm the youngest member on Running Man!
(The youngest Running Man member fails to escape.)
(Excuse me.)
This place is already full.
Is there an air conditioner?
You have to be careful or else, you might press the wrong button.
Please excuse me.
I knew you'd get caught.
(Why are only the weak members in this solitary cell?)
(Only 5 minutes remain.)
(Ji Hyo also finds the hint about how to escape.)
(She shares the hint with Gary.)
(The nice guard hasn't noticed it.)
(Whispering)
- Hey, you can't do that here. - What?
- What's going on? - No dating is allowed.
(Jae Seok also finds the hint.)
I stamped so many envelopes.
It's impossible to stamp 10,000 envelopes.
(He looks around.)
- Don't look to your side. - What?
- Do not look. - How can I...
only look at the envelopes?
Don't give each other looks.
You have four minutes left.
- We only have four minutes? - You have four minutes left.
How many envelopes have I stamped?
It's nothing.
(Suddenly)
(Ji Hyo and Gary attempt to escape at the same time.)
Ji Hyo!
What's going on?
(He looks around carefully.)
(This is my chance!)
What is everyone doing?
(Jong Kook is the only one who didn't get the hint.)
(They desperately want to escape.)
She's good at running.
(He runs for his freedom.)
(Gary fails to escape.)
Goodness.
(Meanwhile, Ji Hyo runs upstairs.)
(On the other hand, Jae Seok...)
(is fighting against two guards and Gary.)
Grab him! I won't let anyone escape if I can't.
(Bambam gets suspended for 1 minute.)
(Ripping)
(Jin Young also gets suspended for 1 minute.)
What's going on with everyone?
(Haha also attempts to escape.)
(Jae Seok also runs upstairs.)
(He'll succeed once he gets through Yu Gyeom.)
If everyone works hard, they'll be able to escape.
(He has the mind of an ideal prisoner.)
You said you won't run away!
(Yu Gyeom is fighting against 2 prisoners.)
Everyone's out, Yu Gyeom.
(Once they get through this door,)
(they'll finally see the runaway vehicle.)
Where is it? Be careful.
(Yu Gyeom tackles Ji Hyo.)
Ji Hyo!
(I'm sorry, Ji Hyo.)
Let me go.
Jae Seok has already left, so I have no choice.
- I have no choice. - No.
He escaped.
(Ji Hyo fails to escape.)
(Jae Seok, please escape.)
(Will Jae Seok successfully escape?)
(Only 1 minute remain until Train to Prison departs.)
How can I open this?
(Open the door to freedom.)
(I must stop him.)
(He will escape from this prison once he runs down the stairs.)
(What?)
Goodness.
(Bambam stops Jae Seok from escaping.)
(I was so close to escaping.)
- I was caught near the parking lot. - Really?
- Where is Haha? - Where did he go?
- What? - Did he leave?
(They can't find Haha anywhere on the train.)
Where is Haha?
I saw him going somewhere by himself...
when others were not looking at him.
Wait.
Haha succeeded in escaping at the labouring platform.
So he did escape.
(How did Haha escape?)
(No one was interested in this runaway vehicle.)
(It's Haha!)
(He gets on the runaway vehicle, panting.)
Finally, I made it.
I escaped!
(Haha made it out of the prison.)
Let's go have lunch.
(They feel dejected.)
If it were the movie, "Train to Busan",
he should be the one to play Ma Dong Seok's part.
- That's true. - Imagine Ma Dong Seok...
just sitting there, stamping the envelopes.
You should have taken the lead.
- Exactly. - You should've fought them.
- Then we could've escaped. - He's not doing his part.
We can just stamp 10,000 envelopes and escape.
- My goodness. - You're wrong.
That's not the point of the mission.
Why do I have to do that?
- I don't think it's that difficult. - My goodness.
Then, each of us should stamp 1,500 envelops.
Listen to me.
I am the Gong Yoo here.
- What did you say? - Oh, my.
- Say that again. - You're the zombie number 103.
- Gary! - You're crude oil.
(You're crude oil, not Gong Yoo.)
Crude oil? Gosh.
Jong Kook. You should lead us like Ma Dong Seok.
- The thing is... - He wants to stamp the envelopes.
If we had shared the information,
we could've just taken off their name tags.
But I knew nothing. If I knew, I would have done that.
(It's a relief that Jong Kook didn't get the clue.)
That's what you should've done.
I could've removed their name tags if I had the clue...
just like the movie!
(Haha is the only one who made his way out of the train.)
Here.
This is for Jong Kook.
(Lunch outside the train is good.)
Can you reach Haha?
- It's useless. - What's the point of calling him?
Gosh, it's meaningless.
It's not like I said something outrageous.
How can you say such ridiculous thing?
It was just an opinion.
- In prison? - He said it's ridiculous.
- We're in prison now. - Was it that wrong?
Please don't forget that this is prison.
I just wanted to know how Haha was doing outside.
How can you say, "ridiculous"?
How many missions are there that we can escape alone?
- Please stop. - Why do you ask that?
We should all escape together.
Let's carry out the existing missions first.
- Don't try to escape alone. - Sir, as I said earlier,
if you played your part, at least one of us would be out there by now.
You were just sitting there saying it's too hot.
If we keep losing our members like that,
- it'll disadvantage us... - Wait, let me tell you this.
You must not be lazy in order to escape from here.
- In "The Shawshank Redemption"... - You should just rot in here.
Let me speak. If we stick together like now,
I'm sure they'll give us a mission which is easier when we're together.
No way. The fewer members there are,
- higher the possibility of escape. - You don't know what we'll do next.
If you'll keep fighting, get off now.
- You two are too loud. - What's wrong with you?
We all ended up in here because we committed crimes.
- What's your accusation? - Crime?
- What? - Gosh.
I want to commit a serious crime in this carriage now.
(How scary.)
Goodness.
(They're getting closer to the prison while squabbling.)
Are we already there?
The mission you'll do now is "Until the End".
What is it?
("Until the End"?)
You'll take turns to complete the mission.
(The members will take turns to complete the mission.)
- Is it my turn? - Go for it.
- Gary. - Gary, you can do it.
- Okay. - Way to go!
- Go for it. - Let's go!
- Good luck. - Gary is on his way.
(Gary, show us what you got!)
If Gary succeeds...
- My goodness! - Gosh.
- What is it? - What happened?
That's too hard.
(What is that behind him?)
(Red strings with bells attached)
(The 4th mission of Train to Prison, "Until the End")
(They must pass the carriage without ringing the bells.)
(If they make the bells ring twice, they fail.)
- My goodness! - Gosh.
- What is it? - What happened?
- That's too difficult. - I don't think he can pull it off.
- We can't even cheat in there. - Are those strings?
(Gary starts the mission.)
Shall I begin now?
I think...
each of us will take five minutes in this round.
(He carefully moves his leg.)
(Goodness!)
(What a tense moment.)
(Ringing)
(Gary gets the first warning.)
(I only have one chance left.)
(He's extra cautious.)
You have to really focus to do this.
(How thrilling!)
(Will he be able to succeed?)
(Jong Kook, the second player, starts the mission.)
Can I start now?
(He's taking bold steps.)
(He enters the first difficult course where Gary rang a bell.)
I just shouldn't ring the bell, right?
(He gets through the first course.)
(In the second difficult course, he must crawl.)
(He chooses to lie down in this course.)
(He uses everything he can and moves at a fast pace.)
Goodness.
It's harder for me since I'm bigger than others.
(His muscles are the problem.)
He's taking a long time.
Gosh, he's so bulky.
He's too gigantic.
That's why he's taking so long.
He should have stopped working out.
(What is he doing?)
- Are you stretching your body? - Yes.
Why are you stretching so shyly?
Are you a chicken?
Are you pecking at crumbs?
- Goodness. - You look like a chicken.
This really helps stretch my body. It feels good.
You look like you're pecking at feed.
- Is it good? - Yes.
(Seok Jin follows Jae Seok right away.)
- That is... - My goodness.
I learnt this posture from my yoga teacher.
Put your legs together and...
(We're looking for his yoga teacher.)
- lower your upper body like this. - What is that?
(Jong Kook is undergoing the hardest course like a chicken as well.)
(He hasn't rung any bells so far.)
(He's doing fairly well despite his bulky body.)
(I'm almost done.)
(He even passes through the most difficult course.)
(Jong Kook clears the mission.)
Am I done?
- You succeeded. - Okay.
We will give you a clue that will be of big help...
in the final mission.
- This one? - That's a remote control.
- The final mission? - It'll help you escape together.
(The remote is the clue to escaping together.)
(The final destination of this train is prison.)
(There are numerous surveillance cameras all around the prison.)
(There's only one way not to get caught on camera!)
(In order for all of them to escape, they need this remote control!)
Or you can choose this Escaping Chance...
which allows you to get off at the next station.
(We will give you this Escaping Chance.)
- To me? - Pick one.
(Between the remote and Escaping Chance, which one will he choose?)
Goodness. I don't know what to do.
(Hesitating)
I think he pulled it off.
Prisoner Kim Jong Kook succeeded in the mission "Until the End".
- He made it. - That's amazing.
- Maybe it's not impossible. - Gary also made it really quickly.
It's possible.
(Did Gary also make it?)
Gary succeeded in the mission "Until the End".
Okay!
(He also succeeded.)
(And...)
Can I get out of this carriage now?
(It's time to make a choice.)
Goodness!
This is too hard!
(Escaping Chance)
- Can I escape right away with this? - Yes.
(Why is this happening to me?)
(Which one will they choose?)
- Ji Hyo, go for it. - Good luck.
- See you soon. - Ji Hyo, do it quickly.
- I'll try my best. - Ji Hyo, you can do it.
(My goodness.)
(Will stiff Ji Hyo be able to make it?)
I think it'll hurt my body.
(She enters the first difficult course.)
(She passed the first course.)
(Another hard course follows, where she has to crawl.)
(Ringing)
(The first warning)
Gosh.
(Let's calm down.)
(Ringing)
(She's flustered.)
It wasn't me.
The bell jingled because the train rattled.
(Ding-dong)
Prisoner Song Ji Hyo failed the "Until the End" mission.
Why did I fail?
Please let me try again.
(Ji Hyo fails the mission.)
(Now, it's Seok Jin's turn.)
Ouch.
It's not bad. It's better than I thought.
(It's better than he thought it would be.)
(Jingling)
Maybe I misjudged.
(He gets the first warning so quickly.)
(Jingling again)
What?
Prisoner Ji Seok Jin has failed the "Until the End" mission.
Did I fail?
(It's no surprise.)
Unbelievable.
How could you fail the mission so quickly?
(Now, it's Jae Seok's turn.)
(It's the bell that made Seok Jin fail.)
I should lower my body.
You can lower your body like this.
(He looks like he's doing a backstroke.)
All right!
(He heads towards the next course.)
(It looks like a chicken is pecking.)
(Jingling)
(He receives his 1st warning.)
I should've removed my name tag.
(He is still pecking.)
(After finishing the pecking course,)
(he meets the crawling course where Ji Hyo failed.)
(Jingling again)
(Jae Seok fails too.)
(Sighing)
Please wait.
If you give me one more chance, I can succeed.
(There is no mercy.)
Prisoner Yu Jae Seok has failed the "Until the End" mission.
(It's Kwang Soo's turn now.)
(His height will most definitely come to his disadvantage.)
(He's going faster than expected.)
How should I pass this course?
Up or down?
(It's the course where Ji Hyo and Jae Seok failed.)
(Jingling)
No, no, it's not.
I didn't fail. No, I didn't.
I was not even close to the bell.
The bell rang over there.
Wait a minute.
Oh, it's maybe because I touched the seat.
I didn't directly touch the bell so it should be okay, right?
(He rolls up his pants and gets ready to start again.)
(Jingling)
Prisoner Lee Kwang Soo has failed the "Until the End" mission.
What do you mean I failed?
Why did I fail?
(Didn't you hear the bell ringing?)
The seat made the bells ring.
I just shook the seat.
I'm not someone who fails in missions like this.
(The Unlucky Trio all failed the mission.)
(Only Gary and Jong Kook passed the "Until the End" mission.)
I still don't understand why I failed.
(The 6 prisoners gather together again.)
- I think I know. - Me neither.
I almost passed.
I almost passed it too.
The four of you have failed the "Until the End" mission.
Gosh.
If you pass the mission, you are given some items.
You could get an item that we can use...
in a group mission later...
or an escaping chance you can use right away.
Between those two, we chose this one.
(What did Gary and Jong Kook choose?)
What was the mission this time?
"Until the End" mission.
"Until the End" mission?
"Until the End"...
Because it's "Until the End",
I'll give this back to you.
I have to take this, right?
(Gary chose the item for the group mission.)
I don't know what to do. If I choose this, can I go now?
(Will he choose the item for the group mission?)
I kept telling them that we should stick together until the end.
I'll go with them until the end.
(Jong Kook also chose the item for the group mission.)
I won't surrender myself to temptation.
("Train to Prison", they are loyal until the end.)
(You must be impressed by our loyalty.)
(Jong Kook, Gary...)
- Why did you give up the chance? - Why?
You should have picked it.
If you can go, you should go.
Before we started, we said we should stick together.
- What are you talking about? - You should have left.
You should have gone home and taken a rest.
Gosh.
I want to swear at them. What should I do?
I really want to swear right now.
How could you survive with that naive mind in a tough world?
(They are at a loss.)
(Did we choose loyalty just for those guys?)
(1 hour before they arrive at the prison)
Please be on standby until the next mission is given.
(There are only two chances left to escape.)
(It's getting more difficult to enjoy freedom.)
(Now, they have to focus to avoid ending up in prison.)
(Seok Jin is fast asleep.)
(Smirking)
(Let's prank Seok Jin.)
Is that true?
(He takes the bait.)
- This? - What is it?
- What shall we do? - It's unbelievable.
- This is crazy. - It really is.
(What? What is it?)
(He is acting seriously.)
What are you up to? You're teasing me, aren't you?
(But then...)
Seok Jin, just say you're sorry.
(Is that a surprise mission?)
(The first one to remove a name tag clears the mission.)
(Right. We should never let our guards down.)
(I'm laughing outside but not inside.)
(Sorry, I'll take your name tag.)
(He rips it off.)
What? What are you doing?
Kwang Soo, you cleared the mission. Please come forward.
What's going on?
(What mission did he clear?)
What is this?
What...
When did that mission appear?
Kwang Soo that brat!
Why?
(You should have been attentive.)
Is that the mission on the screen?
Yes, it is.
When did it appear?
What? Is that a mission?
Did you see that now?
- I saw it just now. - When did you see it?
I saw it as soon as your name tag was removed.
I also saw that at that time.
(Kwang Soo is incredible.)
I'm really upset at him.
(The temptation is given to the one who completes the mission.)
You can choose the device...
or the Escaping Chance.
(It's an ordeal to choose between those two.)
(What's going to be Kwang Soo's choice?)
- It's just like you. - I won't forgive you.
How could you...
- Look at me. - How dare you?
You are so mean.
(Is he escaping just like that?)
- He doesn't even look back. - He doesn't.
See you tomorrow.
- Are you going home? - Goodbye.
You can choose between these two.
I'll go home.
Sure, I'll go home and I'll eat udon on the way.
(He chose the Escaping Chance without hesitation.)
- See you tomorrow. - Are you going home?
Goodbye.
(They're speechless.)
That's what Kwang Soo is like.
- Give him a good slap. - It's not the station yet.
It's not the station yet.
- We haven't arrived at the station. - I should go.
Where do you think you can go?
You can't go.
They can't stop me from getting off.
- You can't go. - You can't get off.
They could have chosen the Escaping Chance too.
I picked the Escaping Chance.
So you already picked the Chance over there.
You already did?
Kwang Soo has chosen the Escaping Chance.
(You didn't have to repeat that.)
What about Gary and Jong Kook?
They must feel so in vain.
(Our loyalty became useless.)
Kwang Soo will get off the train at the next station.
(Kwang Soo the Betrayer can escape.)
Members who failed the mission, move over to the next carriage.
(It's 40 minutes before they arrive at the prison...)
(and 10 seconds before Kwang Soo can escape.)
Bye, everyone. See you tomorrow.
- Just go. - Bye.
He's so annoying.
Bye.
(Have a nice trip to the prison.)
(Haha and Kwang Soo have escaped.)
Am I going home in this uniform?
(Yes, you should go in the uniform.)
(Sighing)
- A ticket to Seoul Station, please. - You should go to Yongsan.
To Yongsan, please.
(He doesn't have his manager or stylist with him.)
(It'd be better to take this off.)
(Maybe not?)
(What's with that prisoner?)
I'm no longer a prisoner.
You must wear this to Seoul Station.
Really? But this isn't a penalty.
(I should've stayed in the Train to Prison.)
It's okay when I'm with others but when I'm alone it's...
(This is so embarrassing.)
You keep making me wear these old clothes again.
(I'm fine with the fresh air out here.)
(What consoles me are boiled eggs and castella bread.)
(They're the taste of freedom.)
(There is one station left until prison.)
- Go in, go in. - You go in first.
(What is awaiting them?)
There are gifts here.
Can we have them?
(Why are there gift boxes here?)
Are you opening them for an Escaping Chance?
I didn't open it.
- This is the percentage carriage. - Okay.
Running Man members, please carefully choose a box.
- What? - Do we choose one?
(What's the percentage carriage?)
We just need to choose?
(What trap is hidden inside the boxes?)
30 percent of the boxes here are...
R boxes. 70 percent of the boxes are unlucky boxes.
(So are only 30 percent of these R boxes?)
(The box selection that'll decide the final escape begins.)
I shouldn't choose the big one.
- This is driving me crazy. - Did you choose one?
What happens if we choose the unlucky box?
Then you will be at a disadvantage for this mission.
- My goodness. - What should I choose?
I'm so bad at these things.
I have bad luck but will I have good luck today?
Ji Hyo has good senses for this.
- My gosh. - The members must take the box.
Let's leave this up to luck.
- Okay. - Leave it up to luck.
I won't change my box.
- This one. - Choose anything.
- But this is... - It doesn't matter.
- You can't help it. - Goodness.
- It's a game of chance. - We choose without reason.
It's just...
- Gosh, I don't know. - Goodness.
- Hurry up. - Just choose one.
- You chose the same one. - Gosh, here.
I don't know any more.
- What's the worst that can happen? - I'm not good at these things.
- Me neither. - Neither am I.
Please open each of your boxes.
Oh, gosh.
- Please. - This is probably an unlucky one.
Let's start with Gary.
(Will Gary get off or stay on the train?)
It's "R"!
(Gary chose the R box.)
(The unlucky percentage has increased.)
(The R box percentage decreased.)
- Jae Seok. - O, P, Q, R!
- O, P, Q, R. - R!
- O, P, Q, R. - This is unbelievable.
I'm really bad at this.
(Will he expectedly have chosen the unlucky box?)
O, P, Q, unlucky.
(Jae Seok chose the unlucky box.)
(He's a proven pure-blood, unlucky man.)
How can this happen?
(He's so unlucky.)
- This isn't a fictional character. - Gosh.
- It's not made up. - Really.
- He has an unlucky hand. - I have no luck.
- I've never chosen the right one. - He didn't even look.
(It's Jong Kook's turn.)
He's going to get an "R".
(Will Jong Kook's Chuseok be a lucky one?)
Open it at once.
(Jong Kook chose an R box.)
O, P, Q, R!
(Mixed feelings of joy and disappointment)
- "R". - It's an "R".
- O, P, Q, R. - "R".
- My gosh. - What's yours?
- I think I have the unlucky box. - This...
- Ji Hyo... - She'll get the R box.
- Of course. - It's an "R".
(Will lucky Ji Hyo be able to get off the train?)
I got the unlucky box.
- Really? - What?
Ji Hyo usually doesn't choose the unlucky ones.
Did she get the unlucky box?
(Does this mean I have an R box?)
- Does this mean that I have... - The unlucky box.
No.
(Will the oldest of the Unlucky Trio have chosen the R box?)
O, P, Q, R.
(It's a shocking betrayal of the Unlucky Trio.)
- O, P, Q, R. - Is Seok Jin getting off now?
This is a surprise.
- Really? - O, P, Q...
I've given you my unlucky hand.
I have passed on my unlucky hand to you.
(Ji Hyo and Jae Seok are headed for live broadcasting.)
Eight minutes from now, we will arrive at...
the final station of the prison battle.
The three members who chose the R box can get off here...
or stay to help the remaining members.
What do we do when we get off?
(Why must you test us?)
(Jae Seok and Ji Hyo are chosen for the penalty.)
Is there a prize if we stay to the end?
You can avoid the penalty.
- Is that all? - But...
there's no need for everyone to stay.
Let's let Seok Jin leave.
(Even if he stays, he won't be of help anyways.)
- Why are you saying that? - For the last mission...
(Please leave us and escape.)
If this is our mission...
- You're being harsh. - It's not that.
I was going to leave anyway.
You must decide now...
so that you can do a mission to have everyone escape.
Really? If we succeed in this mission, can we all escape?
- Shouldn't we all escape together? - I will just leave.
Okay.
Seok Jin said he'll leave.
- Did he say it? - He already told them.
Gary.
- If it's a mission for everyone... - I'll sit in the front.
I won't look at them.
Right. If we all succeed the mission together, can we all escape?
Gary, this train has gone far already.
I'll get off the train.
It's the same if you go home from here or the last station.
I'll get off.
- Gary! - I have to avoid...
- the live broadcast. - Gary.
- If you help us, we can all not go. - Wow.
I was going to stay but I can't after seeing Kwang Soo leave.
- Gary. - It's hard not to leave.
Is there an empty seat up there?
- Over here. - Come here.
- Why? - I'll move.
(Where are you going?)
- Ji Hyo, wait a minute. - Go ahead! Go.
Don't do this.
- Just go. - It's hard to sit next to them.
My goodness.
You two must do the live show together.
(We'll cheer you guys on.)
I'll cheer you on.
You must do the mission now. We're running out of time.
Go ahead. They'll do the mission.
(The mission is passed onto the two unlucky members.)
Okay, fine.
- It's your final chance to escape. - All right.
Ji Hyo.
It's our last chance. It's really our final chance.
(If we lose this final opportunity,)
(the Train to Prison awaits us.)
(5 minutes before arriving at Prison Station.)
This is our final chance.
Gosh, this is...
(My goodness.)
- What is it? - This is...
Gosh, this is really...
- What is it? - I guess you'll be escaping now.
(What is the final mission that'll decide their destination?)
It's okay. You'll make it.
(It's the pirate roulette.)
It's okay, Ji Hyo.
Ji Hyo has good luck.
I'll get caught for sure with this.
- Let's go. - We'll take away two knives for...
each member that chose the R box and decides to help.
But since all the members who chose the R box decided to escape,
- there will be 18 knives. - That's a problem.
- How many holes are there? - There are 24.
- You can do it. - If it pops, you fail.
The final mission of the percentage carriage.
Succeed in the pirate roulette with 18 knives and 24 holes.
You two are of one fate.
(Are we one team?)
Does that mean we have to stick all 18 of these?
(Jae Seok and Ji Hyo will escape if they succeed with the 18 knives.)
(The knives would've decreased if the others chose to stay.)
(The two must now avoid a 75 percent chance of failure.)
- You have six holes down already. - You can do it.
- You can do it. - It's okay.
Let's do it.
(The pirate roulette begins.)
- We are one team. - The others can go to the back.
Let me watch this first. You're good.
Please tell them to leave.
- Let us watch. - It's better to have us with you.
Just leave, please.
Tell them to get off now.
- Let us watch. - It's better to have us with you.
Hurry up and leave. We'll do it on our own.
Just do it. It's better with us here. You won't be lonely.
(There are 17 knives left.)
Gosh, Ji Hyo. Goodness.
- Let's just put it in quickly. - Wait, Ji Hyo.
- We're already done for. - You're right. We're finished.
- We're done. - Separate them.
- Six. - Gosh.
- Ji Hyo, we're done. - My goodness.
- Eight. - Hold on.
Wait, Ji Hyo.
Just put it in, Jae Seok. We're already done for!
- We're done. - Ji Hyo.
- Ji Hyo, I'm scared. - Three, four,
- five, six, seven, eight. - There's one hole.
(Let's go to the end.)
- Put it in now. Hurry. - There's one there.
Do you trust my instincts?
Try putting it all in except for this hole.
- Ji Hyo. - I think you can succeed.
- They just might succeed. - Ji Hyo, you might succeed.
(There are 9 knives and 15 holes remaining.)
- Look at Ji Hyo. - One, two, three,
- four, five, six, seven, eight. - Ji Hyo.
- We still have nine knives left. - Hurry up.
There are nine.
(Jae Seok succeeds with the 9th knife.)
- I think they'll succeed. - They might succeed, indeed.
- Gosh, this is unbelievable. - Ji Hyo.
I think they might succeed.
- This is unbelievable. - Ji Hyo.
(Everyone's nervous now.)
- Gosh, this is... - I'm...
- Ji Hyo, I'm counting on you. - You can do it, Ji Hyo.
- Ji Hyo's on fire today. - She can do this.
- Be careful. Don't hurt your face. - Come on, Ji Hyo.
- Did you do one more? - Oh, my gosh.
(11 holes and 5 knives remaining)
- She did it. - We're almost there.
These are all that's left. Ji Hyo there's only five left.
- Good job. - It's game over.
See this? It would have been much easier if you got at least three.
- Who's next? - Do you hear me?
- Are we getting off now? - Hold on, where are we?
(1 minute and 30 seconds away from the Prison Station)
- Time's almost up. - We're almost there.
- The train will be leaving soon. - It's leaving.
- We have to get off right now. - Watch out!
(10 holes and 4 knives remaining)
(Jae Seok succeeds and only four remains.)
Don't stick in there. It doesn't feel right.
Seok Jin, am I supposed to trust your senses?
I think it'll pop out.
Good job, Ji Hyo. There's only three left.
(9 holes and 3 knives remaining)
- You go, Jae Seok. - Let's get off the train.
- We have to get off right now. - Do it.
- We can do it, Ji Hyo. - How is this possible?
Wait a minute. If Ji Hyo and I succeed, do we get to escape?
- We go together, right? - Yes.
- Ji Hyo. - Jae Seok.
If only they got at least three, we would be on our way out already.
- Come on. - You're a selfish bunch.
I didn't think they could get this far.
- Don't think too much. - Time's almost up, Ji Hyo.
Ji Hyo, I can't do this. Can you do all of them?
(1 minute away from the Prison Station)
- Jae Seok. - Ji Hyo, you do this.
- I really can't do this. - Okay.
I just want you to know that...
(Save us from the misery, Ji Hyo.)
I can't guarantee anything.
Stick it in.
(In Ji Hyo, we trust!)
You can't tell by looking at it.
(Luck is always on her side.)
- I got it. - She got it.
I wasn't even trying to go for it.
I got another one.
(She was born under a lucky star.)
- Is this for real? - Oh, my.
(She caught the golden carp with a probability of 1 out of 2,000.)
I've got the magic pearl.
How much gold are you taking?
(She is officially the lucky charm of Running Man.)
(I can do this.)
Here I go.
Stick it in.
(She really did it.)
- Oh, my goodness. - Is this really happening?
- Just do it already. - Do it.
- There's no time. - Ji Hyo.
(They are so close to making the impossible possible.)
- There's no other way. - I don't know.
Ji Hyo.
(She's got the golden touch.)
- This is nothing! - Ji Hyo!
- I can do this. - I can't believe this.
Ji Hyo, we're almost there.
- This is nothing. - You can do it.
I wouldn't have been able to do that.
(There are seven holes remaining. Their chances of escaping are high.)
(30 seconds away from the Prison Station)
(They have to stick the last knife in before the time is up.)
(Will they walk free?)
(What will become of Running Man?)
(A minute later)
(The train has arrived at the Prison Station.)
(There are prisoners coming out.)
(Are they headed to the prison or the outside world?)
(The air is cold inside the prison.)
(The guards are waiting for the prisoners.)
(This place looks creepy.)
Everyone,
(Did they fail to escape?)
this place...
is the final destination, the Prison Station.
There was supposed to be a final mission here.
What's the last mission?
You were to find all the hidden cameras.
- I see. - That was the mission.
The moment before you arrived at the Prison Station...
(Did they end up in prison? Or are they free?)
(3 minutes earlier)
Just do it. There's no other way.
Ji Hyo!
(She sure is lucky.)
- Ji Hyo! - This is nothing!
I can do this.
(There's only one knife left.)
I wouldn't have been able to do that.
(It all depends on the last knife.)
(What will become of Running Man?)
(It's a success!)
(We're free now!)
(Ji Hyo allows everyone to escape the Train to Prison!)
- I did it! - You did it!
- Ji Hyo! - I knew I could do this.
- Jae Seok, I'm sorry. - What now?
(It's too late for that.)
It wouldn't have been possible without you.
(They succeeded with a 25 percent chance.)
This is unbelievable.
How is this possible?
- My heart is pounding. - How did you do that?
You feel that?
- I can't believe this. - Ji Hyo.
If it was me with the knife,
- it would have been the end of us. - I know.
Ji Hyo did amazing, but I made the right choice by handing it to her.
- I did well. - Does it matter at this point?
- No, get this. - I did well, too.
- It was meant to be. - This is the thing.
If it weren't for you three, we would've gotten off way earlier.
- No, it was meant to be. - It's all thanks to Ji Hyo.
- She's good. I'll give her that. - Hey.
- I can't believe this. - How is this possible?
- Stick it in. - Yes, the game is over anyway.
You try, Jae Seok.
This isn't broken, is it?
Hold on. Let me try it.
Wait a minute.
(It pops out.)
(The pirate comes right out.)
- I knew it. - You're one unlucky guy.
Did you see what happened?
- Ji Hyo is amazing. - Did you see that?
You're so unlucky.
Wow, Ji Hyo.
(Everyone escapes thanks to Ji Hyo.)
You have successfully completed the mission to escape.
- You did an amazing job. - It was all her.
Can we celebrate together? Why are you leaving us out?
- What are you talking about? - We're a team.
It was all me and Ji Hyo.
- We didn't even have to be there. - Hey, move over.
We didn't even have to be there.
Why didn't you go, then?
You could have gotten off before the final destination.
You missed it while watching others.
- Why were we just watching? - You should have said something.
- We were cheering for them. - That's right.
You will now get to go...
on the runaway vehicle.
- Can we go? - Which vehicle is it?
- Let's go. - Thank you.
You should be thankful to us.
You don't have to work during the holidays.
Some might want to work.
- Thank you, everybody. - Thank you, everybody.
Let's go.
It's time to get out of here.
- We're finally out. - Yes.
- Oh, there's a car waiting for us. - It's the runaway vehicle.
(Freedom!)
(Meanwhile, others are...)
I'll take one for the team.
They must be hungry right now.
Let's enjoy this party.
- Freedom! - Freedom!
Am I really going home?
I'm going home.
(One might think that he's getting off work early.)
(We've made the impossible possible.)
(Now we enjoy freedom together.)
Thank you.
- Give it to those two. - They deserve it.
- Good job, you guys. - Thank you.
-Thank you, everyone. - Thank you.
(Welcome back.)
- Thank you. - Thanks for coming out here.
Let's get in the car.
(It's the runaway vehicle to Seoul.)
- We're going to Seoul. - Yes, we are.
Thank you. We'll live happily ever after.
Goodbye.
(Isn't that what you say after the wedding?)
- Thank you, everyone. - Goodbye.
(What will happen to the members on their way to Seoul?)
This is the questionnaire required for today's missions.
"What's the special episode that I would like to be in?"
Oh, that scared me.
(What's going on in here?)
This room is creepy.
Do it.
What was that?
(There's someone else in here.)
I'm sweating. Who's there?
(He is here to take revenge.)
It won't be like last time.
Just do as I say!
Can you be more careful?
He's not interested.
This is a long day.
(Running Man versus The Avengers, The Battle of Revenge)