(Under the picturesque sky)
(Running School)
(There's a field where you can feel that autumn is in the air.)
- Hello. - Hello.
Hello.
(Park Mi Sun, the queen of variety shows)
- Today is Running Man field day. - Okay.
Mi Sun will be the leader of Men's Team and...
Jae Seok will be the leader of Women's Team.
I'm very satisfied.
Have I won the lottery or what?
I'm so happy.
However, you two are spies.
(Spies?)
Actually, Jae Seok is the spy of Men's Team.
No, I refuse.
I like my team. Why would I ever do that?
- Why would I be a spy for them? - Me, too.
Am I the spy of Women's Team?
You mean I must help Women's Team secretly?
It's going to be hard. I should pretend that I'm helping Men's Team.
But in fact, I should help Women's Team, right?
- That'll be your job. - But I'm not close to any of them.
- I hate girls prettier than me. - I know.
- We can do well as team leaders. - They are too pretty.
So the photos of these guys are staring at me right now.
Well, they're just mediocre.
- I'm not that... - I know what you mean.
- happy about my members. - They are her friends,
- but none of them are her type. - Exactly.
- Here's another thing. - Okay.
Among your team, you can pick a member to help you.
(Team leaders can choose another spy in their team.)
- You want me to choose a spy? - Right.
(Team leaders can choose another spy among their team.)
But the spy you chose...
may betray you depending on the situation.
(Spies chosen by the team leaders may betray the leaders.)
(They may betray their leader once before the final race.)
- You mean a double spy? - Right.
- Then I must pick a decent person. - Yes.
- Someone reliable. - You're right.
Who would be the most reliable person among these five?
- There's none among them. - Is that so?
I know.
(Whom will they choose?)
- We'll start the field day. - What?
- Let's do this. - Men's Team, please line up.
Where is Jae Seok? He must be...
happy to be out on the green.
Gary, look at you.
- Is it still on me? - It's like an accessory.
- A dragonfly is on him. - It seems to be comfortable.
I think it's there to hide the brand name.
- Is it on this side or that? - It's hiding the brand name.
That's amazing.
- You're becoming one with nature. - Today must be your day.
First, the team leader of Men's Team will enter.
Will there be a Women's Team today?
Is it going to be Jae Seok?
- Team leader. - What?
Is she going to be our leader?
- Is she going to be our leader? - Hello.
- Hello. - Hello, Mi Sun.
(Park Mi Sun, team leader of Men's Team)
(You are most welcome.)
- Park Mi Sun. Park Mi Sun. - Yes.
- Are you the leader of Men's Team? - Nice.
(They're uniting under Mi Sun.)
The last time you were on the show, you had to pay for our dinner.
Right, this is the first time after that incident.
- We split the bill together. - We shared the bill.
- You're here with me again. - I never thought I'd come again.
Since you invited me again, I should visit once in a while.
Women's Team, please enter.
Jae Seok must be very excited.
(He marches in proudly.)
It's Min Kyung.
- It's Yeon Jae. - It's Son Yeon Jae.
- It's Yeon Jae. - It's Yeon Jae.
- And there's also Yu Ra. - It's Yu Ra.
- It's Yu Ra. - It's...
- Ji Won. - It's Ji Won.
- It's Ji Won. - Goodness.
(They are beautiful.)
- Hello. - Goodness.
(Nationally loved gymnast, Son Yeon Jae)
(A beauty with lovely voice, Kang Min Kyung)
(Cute and sexy idol, Yu Ra)
(An elegant actress, Ye Ji Won)
(The national beauties are here on Running Man.)
Hello.
- Cut it out, Haha. - Hey, Yeon Jae.
It's been too long.
- I said stop it. - Yeon Jae.
- Oh, my. - Stop it.
- Long time no see. - Get back in the line.
- Nice to meet you. - Go away.
- Hey, Yu Ra. - That's enough.
Hello, Ji Won.
Go away.
It's been too long.
I'm giving you a warning.
Don't talk down to a global star.
What do you mean "global star"?
Yeon Jae is a world-class athlete.
You can't be calling her by her name like that.
How else am I supposed to call her?
- That's her name. - As for Min Kyung,
she's no longer the worst actress of all time.
Why'd you bring that up?
(Gary imitates Min Kyung's acting.)
(Do you remember this sound?)
(This was her first main role as an actress.)
(This scene became a legend.)
(Her dinosaur-like cry is the key point.)
- I still remember that one. - Don't do it.
Isn't that how it goes?
Don't do it.
- Her acting got much better now. - That's right.
Oh, I almost forgot.
Ji Won and I were in the same class,
but she keeps insisting that I'm older.
- He's older than me. - Why are you acting like that?
She was my partner as the leading actress.
- We did a drama together. - Really?
- Of course. - We even had a kiss scene.
- Are you serious? - Which drama was that?
(Do you remember our kiss?)
(They locked lips passionately at the office.)
We were a fantastic couple.
That was his first kiss after seven years.
(Their kiss scene deserves an award.)
- I have a good feeling about today. - Me, too.
- We haven't met for so long. - Today is Running Man field day.
It's Men's Team against Women's Team.
The team with the higher points will be the final winner.
- This'll be way too easy. - They don't stand a chance.
The winner will be awarded with luxurious prizes.
- Luxurious prizes? - Isn't this unfair for us?
- The teams aren't balanced. - I agree.
- The teams are divided by gender. - We don't know the game yet.
- It really depends on the game. - But the Women's Team...
Each team has a spy who will prevent their team from winning.
(There's a spy in each team.)
Spies?
(There's a spy among us?)
Lead your team to victory while avoiding the spies.
(They will be given bonus points for ratting out the spy in the voting.)
Spies?
(The time has come.)
Each team has a spy?
Why are there spies for a field day?
Why don't I ever get to be a spy?
That sounds like something a spy would say.
You're acting strange.
- Is it you, Yeon Jae? - What?
- It's Yeon Jae. - No, it's not me.
Yeon Jae, are you nervous?
It feels a bit strange right now.
I think I've spent too much time in the training ground.
I basically live in the gym, too.
- It's a different kind of exercise. - Us athletes have things in common.
One thing's for sure, Yeon Jae is a spy.
- What? - I'm sure it's her.
- Why are you all ganging up on me? - I think it's her, too.
- We're ganging up on you? - Yes.
You have a temper, don't you?
It sounded like that.
I love this team.
I love my team, too.
- This is good. - We're all friends here.
(The two team leaders are about to get some spy action.)
(Who's the other spy that each team leader picked?)
Both of the team leaders, please come forward.
I actually did something like this when I was in elementary school.
The opening ceremony will be held out by the team leaders.
Variety Ceremony.
I swear under oath.
We will try our hardest to make the viewers laugh.
We won't get scared of being taken bad pictures.
We will stand proud in front of the cameras...
and try our best for every game.
We swear that we will try our very best to make the viewers laugh.
- We swear. - We swear.
The 2016 Running Man Field Day will now begin.
Let's begin.
(It begins now.)
(Will the spies be able to carry out their secret missions?)
Let's get the field day started.
(Arcade Games)
I bet many of you have memories about field days.
Back in Mi Sun's days, they held up the torch for the ceremony.
Is she that old?
- I remember the old days. - Are you okay?
Are you okay, Mi Sun?
Did you get to shoot an arrow as well?
Am I some kind of a hunter?
- What are you talking about? - Am I some kind of a hunter?
Did you use golden coins as currency back then?
Are you sure you're not from the Joseon Dynasty?
Back then, field days weren't exclusive to students.
It was a day that the whole family came and had fun together.
My parents and grandparents would all come and play.
I remember playing a game together.
- We threw sandbags. - They were called ojaemi.
We would throw things at a basket...
and when it opened, it would read, "It's lunch time."
- You had those? - Of course.
Field days are all about cheerleading.
Ding-a-ling, tring-a-ling, you've got a call
The person on the call said White Team has won
- No, no, it's a lie - No, no, it's a lie
The person on the call said Blue Team has won
- No, no, it's a lie - It's a lie
I remember the old days.
Oh, the good old days.
We'll go on forever like this.
I'll tell you the rules of this game.
- There's a picture behind us. - Right.
We will start removing the paper piece by piece...
and you have to guess who that person is.
The winner of each round will be able to remove a piece.
Let's get the first game started.
It's called "Introduce Yourselves".
- Do we pass around the bomb? - That's right.
- Really? - You have 60 seconds.
- I'm scared. - A bomb?
I know what this is.
(Each member introduces oneself and passes around the bomb.)
(To win, the team has to use up the time before the bomb goes off.)
- Try your best. - Are you ready?
Set,
(Nerve-racking)
- Set, Go! - I'm nervous.
Hello,
My name is...
Kang Gary.
- You're going too slow. - You'll have plenty of time.
60 seconds is longer than you think.
- Hello, I'm Lee Kwang Soo. - He's going too fast.
- The weather's nice out today. - Five.
- Everyone, - Six.
- don't catch a cold. - You're taking long.
(They feel like the bomb will go off any second now.)
Hello, everyone. I'm Haha.
(They're getting nervous.)
It's a field day today.
Stay safe, everyone.
Please root for our team.
Let's go, Men's Team!
(What do you mean, "Let's go"?)
He took so long. It's going to blow up on you.
He used too much time.
I made a debut as a singer.
(He manages to sing in a tight situation like this.)
I was the best ballad singer.
Give it to me.
I made a debut as Turbo. I've been in the industry for 21 years.
I'll continue to make more appearances. I'm Kim Jong Kook.
He's out of time.
Stay healthy, everyone.
Oh, no.
The time's up.
- Go really fast. - Hello, I'm Park Mi Sun.
(The bomb goes off.)
(It blew up as soon as she got her hands on it.)
(The other team looks startled.)
Why did you all take so long?
- We didn't take long. - I didn't even get to say anything.
- We still had a few seconds left. - It blew up on me.
We had so much time left.
- We counted it ourselves. - Gosh.
- Are you serious? - It scared me so much.
(Spy Mi Sun's acting is spot on.)
We were off by three seconds.
- Let's give it a try. - They won't be able to do it.
I'm scared.
- Let's go! - Let's go!
Set, go!
Hello, I'm Yu Jae Seok.
I made a debut on 1991 College Comedy Festival.
- Why are you using up so much time? - I'm on Running Man right now.
- I'm on Running Man right now. - Pass it on.
Hello, I'm Kang Min Kyung of Davichi.
We are back with a new album.
- I think of you everyday - Pass it down.
Hello, I'm the rhythmic gymnast, Son Yeon Jae.
She doesn't look scared at all.
Thanks for having me today.
- What should I do with this? - Pass it on.
Hello, I'm actress Ye Ji Won.
I came to see Jae Seok today.
It's nice to see you, Jong Kook. I'm doing a drama with Ji Hyo.
Hello, I'm Yu Ra of Girl's Day. Nice to meet you.
You have to go faster. Go faster.
- Go faster. - Thank you. I love you.
- Don't yell out to stop yet. - Hello, Song Ji Hyo.
- Ji Hyo, don't stop yet. - Stop.
- Stop. - You have so much time left.
Ji Hyo.
(The bomb goes off.)
- You used up 40 seconds. - I told you there's time left.
- It's only been 40 seconds? - Yes.
You had to pass it around.
I wasn't sure. I got it now.
The second game is "Compliment the Opposing Team Leader".
- I see. - But I have nothing to say.
We're supposed to give that guy compliments?
Ready, set, go!
Jae Seok is the best show host Korea has ever seen.
He can be a bit boring,
but I want to live his life for once.
- Thank you. - You're the best.
(Jong Kook is next.)
Jae Seok is the best show host out there.
He's so smart and brags like there's no tomorrow.
What do you mean?
- That's not true. - That's the person he is.
Don't say it like that.
Jae Seok is a good guy.
It's irritating to have him around.
He makes me look bad.
He's such a role model.
He can be so stubborn sometimes. I'm so sick of him.
I feel like I'm standing on a cliff.
- Be careful. - Use your time wisely.
Jae Seok is...
ugly but nice.
(Jae Seok is ugly but nice.)
Ugly people are usually nice.
Pass it on.
- You still have some time left. - Stop.
(Stop.)
(Gary yelled out stop as soon as he got handed the bomb.)
Did we do it?
- I won't tell you the record yet. - That's fine.
- It was successful, then. - It didn't go off.
- I think it was a bit early. - At least the bomb didn't go off.
Keep in mind that we only used 40 second with the last attempt.
You should talk more, Ji Hyo. Let's go again like last time.
Are we supposed to compliment Mi Sun?
You must have so much to talk about.
They'll go on forever.
- That's right. - Ready, set, go!
Mi Sun is a good role model to young comedians.
- I'll start counting. - She taught us...
many lessons regarding marriage.
Did they start?
- She's a great role model... - Did they start?
who shows how to have a good marriage.
- You are showing how to love... - You're speaking for too long.
That's what I think about her.
- Take the ball from him. - What was her nickname?
- Come on. - Mi Sun is really beautiful.
She's also known for her vitality. And she even has abs.
- Really? - I admire and respect her.
- Aren't they running out of time? - She was the host...
of my first show. She was so kind and considerate.
It was great to meet her there.
I'm Mi Sun's fan. I admire her beauty and intelligence.
Why don't you give Miss Korea a try?
Please show us how beautiful you are in a swimsuit.
You look so young and beautiful.
Thank you for being kind every time we meet.
I love you.
Mi Sun, I admire your consistency...
(The ball pops.)
We failed again.
(The ball explodes in Ji Hyo's hands again.)
- Gosh. - Ji Hyo, you're not concentrating.
- It exploded as soon as I got it. - Yes. It exploded right away.
The ball exploded in your hands two times in a row.
- It exploded as soon as she got it. - I couldn't do anything.
(You could've done better.)
Jae Seok, you spoke for too long.
- That's all right - That's all right
Ding-a-ling, tring-a-ling, you've got a call
The person on the call said Men's Team has won
- No, no, it's a lie - No, no, it's a lie
The person on the call said Women's Team has won
The person on the call said Men's Team has won
- No, no, it's a lie - No, no, it's a lie
(Their cheering never stops.)
(You can't beat us.)
The person on the call said Men's Team has won
(All right. We lost.)
They ended the song.
- We won the game. - Yes, we won.
(That was really childish.)
That was a great ending.
All right. Rip one of the strips.
- Let's rip off number three. - Isn't number two a better choice?
- Okay. Let's take number two. - Number two?
We don't know which side of the face it'll show.
- That's right. We don't know. - It's the eyes.
(These eyes look familiar.)
Isn't she Uhm Jung Hwa?
Yes. I think so, too.
Doesn't she look like Uhm Jung Hwa?
- I think she's Kim Hee Seon. - All right.
- One, two, three. - She's Kim Hee Seon.
- Five, four, three, - I think she's Uhm Jung Hwa.
- two... - All right. One, two, three.
- Kim Hee Seon. - Kim Hee Seon.
(Men's Team's answer is Kim Hee Seon.)
(Can they guess who she is only with her eyes?)
- She's not. - It's wrong.
I think she's Uhm Jung Hwa.
We must win this game.
We must win this time.
They can guess who she is next time.
The next game is "Pass on the Word".
("Pass on the Word")
Everybody must wear a pair of headphones...
and deliver what the person in front of you says.
This is really fun.
You will receive a point if the last person guesses the correct answer.
- What a classic game it is. - Yes, it's a famous team game.
It won't be easy to win any points. Not even one.
You're right. Shall we begin with Women's Team?
- Yes. - Okay.
Ready? Set. Start.
(Americano)
That's too easy.
Americano.
(They're doing great so far.)
(How would Jae Seok perform?)
Americano.
(Thanks to the easy word, Jae Seok succeeds too.)
Americano. Is it correct?
(Pickled chili)
Pickled chili.
Puppy chili.
(Puppy chili?)
(What kind of chili is that?)
- Hey. - Okay.
Pickled chili.
(Somehow, Jae Seok says the correct answer.)
Gangster chili.
(Gangster chili?)
(What is a gangster chili?)
- What did she say? - She said, "gangster chili".
(That gangster must be quite hot.)
Pickled chili.
Pickled chili. Am I correct?
(That's correct.)
(Baechu geotjeori)
(This one is really difficult.)
Baechu geotjeori.
(Min Kyung is correct this time.)
(They are doing fine so far.)
(What kind of strange things will Ji Hyo say this time?)
Something... Something really spicy?
- Isn't she the spy? - She must be the spy.
Something really spicy.
(Wrong)
Time out.
Women's Team got two points.
Really?
Hey, Ji Hyo.
Can you please tell us what "gangster chili" is?
What is it?
- Do you know what it is? - It's my first time hearing.
- What is "gangster chili"? - She's suspicious.
(Is Ji Hyo really the spy?)
Are you ready?
(Can Men's Team win the second round, too?)
Set, start.
(Telepathy)
Telepathy.
- All right. Next. - He must know this. It's so easy.
- Telephony. - I knew it.
(Telephony)
- Look. He's really strange. - Something's wrong with him.
- Telepathy. - That's right.
"Kkilkki ppappa".
"Kkilkki ppappa"?
(Where did kkilkki ppappa come from?)
"Kkilkki ppappa".
(They cannot recuperate.)
- What's your answer? - Kkilkki ppappa.
(How can "telepathy" be turned into "kkilkki ppappa"?)
- Okay, I got it. - All right. Please begin.
Hidden message.
- Everybody must speak clearly... - Hidden message.
Mi Sun is suspicious, too.
Twenty-four, seven.
(Haha changes the word again.)
- What's his problem? - That's so funny.
Twenty-four, seven.
That sounds really strange.
- Is it over? - Wasn't it twenty-four, seven?
- It was twenty-four, seven. - That was amazing.
(There are spies everywhere.)
Somebody changed "telepathy" to "telephony". Who was it?
It wasn't me. It must be one of them.
- Come on. Who was it? - It was me.
- I said, "telephony". - Was it you?
- You're so strange. - It wasn't our fault.
Mi Sun, you're suspicious, too.
You spoke words too fast.
- What was the answer? - No, I didn't mean it.
- Hey. We... - That wasn't my fault.
- Excuse me. We have to... - It was Kwang Soo.
Stop bothering us! We're have a team meeting!
You'd better stay away.
- Calm down. - Stop bothering us.
Which sticker should we take off?
- Let's take off number two. - Yes. Number two.
- Let's see the eyes. - Yes. We should see the eyes first.
We need to get some points.
(Those eyes look very familiar.)
- I know who he is. - Who is that?
- I know that person. - It's Ji Hyo.
Isn't he Son Chang Min?
- Mi Sun. Don't say it. - No, he's not.
- It's not Son Chang Min. - I don't think so, either.
(Is he the Korean actor, Son Chang Min?)
- Who is that? - Yes. Let's discuss.
- Jackie Chan? - Yes. It's Jackie Chan.
- You're right. - Can I say the answer?
Jackie Chan? Really?
(Are those Jackie Chan's eyes?)
- Jackie Chan. - I'm not so sure.
- Jackie Chan. - Jackie Chan.
(Women's Team calls out Jackie Chan. Are these Jackie Chan's eyes?)
(They are correct.)
(What a bummer.)
(Women's Team earns a great turnaround victory.)
- We won. - Amazing.
(Although he's laughing, Jae Seok must be crying inside.)
- That was amazing. - How did you guess that?
(Mi Sun fails to hide her laughter.)
- She must be Jeon Do Yeon. - Isn't she?
- That's right. She's Jeon Do Yeon. - I couldn't even imagine.
- Really? - Were her eyes that beautiful?
- There he is. - He's Jackie Chan.
- That's Jackie Chan. - How did she know?
I thought it must be either Son Chang Min or Jackie Chan.
I immediately knew it was Jackie Chan.
- That was an amazing turnaround. - All right. So...
Women's Team has won the first game!
(Women's Team wins.)
That was amazing.
It's about time for us to have a lunch break.
Lunch break is the most important part of a field day.
It's time for a lunch break.
("Make Your Gimbap")
All right. We're going to have gimbap for lunch.
- Gimbap is a must-have item. - So today,
we're going to make our own gimbap.
Ingredients are hidden throughout this place.
If you open a box, you must use that ingredient inside.
You must find 10 ingredients and make your own gimbap.
It's called "Make Your Gimbap". You must make your own gimbap.
Can we not throw away some ingredients?
No, you can't
All right, let's begin. Let's go.
(How would their gimbap look like in the end?)
There's one.
I found one, but...
Just go and grab it.
(They are trying to get the box.)
(Seok Jin steals the box and runs away.)
Don't worry. There's another one.
(What's inside Seok Jin's box?)
(Gummy worms)
Oh my gosh.
There's one.
(What will the others find?)
I got one!
I got a box!
There's one.
I found another one, too.
- What's inside? - How about yours?
- I think I have the worst one. - Me, too.
- I'm sure mine is worse. - Let me see.
- What inside your box? Show me. - Oh, man.
(They picked pickled shrimp and wasabi.)
We got the worst.
(Both of them are really unlucky.)
Please...
No! Raw garlic!
This is the worst.
(How is Women's Team doing?)
I found one!
Please. A good one.
(Please...)
Gosh. I'm so happy with mine.
(She picked ham.)
There's nothing here.
We shouldn't go that way.
- I found another. - There it is.
(Min Kyung finds again.)
I missed it.
She found one more.
- I don't know what's going on. - Why?
This is crazy.
(Eggs)
Good job. Did you find one?
- Will there be some here? - There may be.
(Yu Ra and Yeon Jae are looking thoroughly.)
- There is one. - Yeon Jae, Yeon Jae.
- You found one. - Can we open it?
(What will there be?)
- It's chicken feet. - Are you okay with them?
- I love chicken feet. - Do you?
We picked nice ones.
(Women's Team acquired wasabi, eggs, spinach, skate, ham,)
(garlic, strawberry jam, cilantro, Cheongyang chili and chicken feet.)
(Men's Team acquired wasabi, pickled shrimp, gummy bear, strawberry jam,)
(marshmallow, sesame oil, biscuit, Cheongyang chili, skate and eggs.)
(They start to make gimbap with the ingredients for the field day.)
May I put some spinach?
Are you putting that much?
Chicken feet gimbap looks delicious.
Chicken feet gimbap.
I want to roll it now.
This looks so delicious.
(But something is strange.)
- We can't put them all. - Wait a minute.
Let's put some gummy bears and marshmallow.
- What about pickled shrimp? - And strawberry jam.
Who's going to eat this?
(Let me think.)
I think we're giving it to the other team...
- That is possible. - so that they can eat.
I think we have to exchange them.
- That's possible. - Listen. It doesn't make sense.
We could use just a little bit of skate for us.
You sound just like a spy.
Hey, I'm not a spy.
(They keep suspecting each other.)
(Something's fishy anyway.)
Let's make one gimbap for a penalty.
Let's make one.
Put wasabi here.
That's a lot.
My goodness.
This is for a penalty.
I see.
This is too much.
- I don't want to cut it. - I've never seen any gimbap...
with skate and strawberry jam in it.
(They put wasabi, skate and strawberry jam.)
- And Cheongyang chili. - It'll be so spicy.
I wonder who would eat this.
- What are you doing? - I made a rice ball.
(You can make a rice ball with burst gimbap and cilantro.)
It's Gagamel's rice ball.
(Who would eat this Gagamel's rice ball?)
Cheongyang chili and jam makes such an odd combination.
Skate and jam makes an even worse combination.
- Don't you like it? - It's done.
It's finished. Let's go out.
- It's perfect. - This is great.
We're all finished.
(Is it true that they'll give them to the other team?)
- Did you all make gimbap? - Yes.
In fact, fall makes people's heart...
- pound. - You're right.
It's a good season to love.
Yeon Jae, do you feel melancholy in autumn?
I feel that way in spring or in fall.
- I want to meet someone. - Right.
We're influenced by seasons.
- Spring for women and fall for men. - But...
I couldn't date because I had to practise.
Since the Olympics is over now...
Oh, really?
(Then there's a chance.)
Did you open your mind?
- Did you? - I want to meet someone.
I want to meet someone.
- I'm surprised. - What kind of a man do you like?
Tell us about your ideal type.
I just...
- Who, for example? - Is height important?
- I like tall guys. - She likes tall guys.
Do you like tall guys?
- I don't like a guy as tall as me. - But he's 2m tall.
He's 2m tall.
- What are you talking about? - He's still growing.
Why do you say such absurd things?
Don't do that.
His nose gets longer and so do his ears.
Kwang Soo is really...
Why do you talk about me like that?
He can't live without love.
If you have to choose among us, whose appearance do you like?
- Don't ask that. - Choose among you?
(Choose among you?)
Did you see Yeon Jae just now?
"Choose among you?"
This topic is now over.
- You're not the one. - Because...
Because we...
You'll be the first one to get eliminated.
There may be someone she likes.
You're the second one to get eliminated.
- You're done. - What's wrong with him today?
You guys are all eliminated.
(You're all eliminated.)
Why did you point me twice?
- You're childish. - You are.
Ask Yeon Jae directly and end it.
Among you guys?
- If you have to pick one. - According to the appearance?
- According to the looks. - I would just...
I want to meet someone.
(All of them think they stand a chance if it is among themselves.)
- Regardless of height. - I would just...
choose Kwang Soo.
I would choose Kwang Soo.
(If it's a dream, he may not want to wake up.)
- She doesn't... - You don't care about appearance.
- She doesn't care about the looks. - She doesn't.
(Kwang Soo falls in love again.)
He really likes it.
- Did you all make gimbap? - Yes.
- We made terrific gimbap. - Yes.
- It's eye-opening. - Yes.
It is really eye-opening.
- You have the worst gimbap, right? - Yes.
Let's exchange and eat them.
(Gosh)
(I knew it. The ingredients were so suspicious.)
- This is not edible. - Is this chocolate?
- No, that is healthy gimbap. - There's chocolate.
Please pick one to taste this.
- Let's play rock-paper-scissors. - Okay.
- Let's play rock-paper-scissors. - Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
(Yu Ra, Min Kyung and Jae Seok lost.)
(Yu Ra is chosen.)
- Okay. - Just try one piece.
- Let's play rock-paper-scissors. - Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
(Kwang Soo is chosen.)
(It's okay as long as it's not me.)
- It's chocolate, right? - Just try it.
- It's chocolate. - It is edible.
- It doesn't look so bad. - It'll be delicious.
- We made a great combination. - I'm nervous.
That will be better than this.
Good. Just don't breathe and swallow it.
- Hold your nose. - Swallow quickly.
(How will it taste when you eat skate and chocolate together?)
(Laughing)
(There you go.)
How does it taste? Please describe the taste.
- How is it? - I tasted wasabi at first,
- That doesn't sound bad. - but later it was all chocolate.
We'll give Kwang Soo...
something special.
- A rice ball. - A rice ball.
- Who made this? - What is this?
- Was it a rice ball? - What's that?
I thought it was something you threw away.
The jungle expert made this.
Cilantro keeps you away from mosquitoes.
I'd rather get bitten by mosquitoes.
I'll feed you.
- Skate is not bad. - It's okay.
It has all the healthy ingredients.
Cut the cilantro off.
He looks like a real giraffe with that.
- A giraffe. - Exactly.
He looks exactly like a giraffe.
- The skate is... - All the taste kicks in now.
The skate kicks in suddenly.
- You can do it. - It's not bad.
- You can eat that. - Is it raw garlic?
Is it raw garlic?
Then you are tasting all the ingredients.
They even put raw garlic.
He can taste all the ingredients.
- Right. - Try other normal gimbap now.
- This is... - Try this.
- It's good. - It's delicious.
This gimbap turned out great.
- This is tasty. - It's really good.
Come over here and try this.
Is there a spy in our team?
- I think there isn't. - Not at all.
Sure, you would say so...
because you're the spy.
(You're the spy.)
What's wrong with him?
- You look like a spy to me, too. - I also think so.
- I can see the spy in your team. - Who is it?
Seok Jin.
There are three in your team.
Thank you for your attention.
Let me introduce the third Round of the field day.
"Find Your Staff".
("Find Your Staff")
- What does that mean? - What's that?
- "Find Your Staff". - What's that?
Each team will stand on each side.
At the signal of a whistle,
run towards the bar in the centre.
Men's Team should check the blue bags...
and Women's Team should look for the red bags.
There will be a note with a key word in each bag.
Find a staff related to the key word...
and get verified at the front desk.
(Verified couples tie their bracelets together.)
(You'll win if you remove all the bracelets of the other team.)
If you don't find your staff, he or she will be eliminated.
The bags of Men's Team is hanging high.
- Yes. - It's not fair.
Haha or Gary...
(Haha or Gary...)
Yeon Jae can jump higher than me.
She can probably jump higher.
She can put her feet on my shoulder and tie her shoelaces.
Try it. Can you do that?
- May I? - Go ahead. She puts it here.
She can tie her shoelaces in this position.
- Are you sure? - She puts it here.
(She's so flexible.)
She can tie her shoelaces in this position.
(Let me try.)
(He falls over.)
(He seems to be kicked out.)
- Gosh. - You're mean.
- I wanted to help him. - Gosh.
I just wanted to help him.
- You're too harsh. - He could've been injured.
I said I helped.
I did.
- Shall we start? - Yes.
Let's put our hands together.
- Upwards? - Downwards?
In 1, 2, 3. Let's go.
In 1, 2, 3. We can do it.
- Let's help each other. - Okay.
- Can I cut in? - We don't need to hurry.
- Kwang Soo, help me please. - One bag per person?
- We don't need to hurry at all. - Ready...
(How will the spies act in this game?)
Start.
("Find Your Staff" has started.)
- It's okay. - Block them.
- Block them. - It's okay.
(They jump high.)
- Oh my. - I can't.
(Women's Team quickly gets all the bags.)
Did you take it at your first try?
Please grab one for me.
(Please grab one for me.)
I can't reach.
Go for it!
- Lift me up. - In 1, 2, 3.
- It's ticklish. - My goodness.
- What should I do, then? - You're tickling me.
One, two...
Why are you so ticklish?
It's too ticklish. I can't.
(A man with strong arms.)
Who is it?
"A man who weighs over 100kg"?
Gosh.
What?
There's no one who looks like a celebrity.
- What's yours? - Mine?
Did you see anyone who looks like a celebrity?
The youngest director?
"Someone who looks single"?
A person who looks like a celebrity?
(Their partners are revealed.)
The youngest screen writer.
(All the members now know who'll be their partner.)
Let me see your hand.
Yours is smaller than mine.
My hands are pretty big.
- Who looks like a celebrity? - How much do you weigh, Kwon Ryeol?
- I don't see any here. - Tell me now.
- Tell me how much you weigh. - Who looks like a celebrity?
Double eyelids. No, it's nothing.
(She has to find a man with double eyelids.)
I don't see any.
Does anyone here think they're handsome?
Are there any handsome guys?
Are you the youngest director? Who's the youngest one?
The one who looks like...
- Do you look like a celebrity? - It's you, right?
- It's you, isn't it? - It's me.
Let's hurry.
You're single, aren't you?
Come here.
You obviously look single.
I brought the youngest writer.
The youngest writer.
- You got it right. - Okay!
Sir.
(She has to find a person with strong arms.)
Can I cling onto your arm for five seconds?
I'm heavy.
In 1, 2, 3.
One, two, three, four, five.
I found him.
(She found the right partner.)
I found the youngest director.
The youngest director? You brought the right one.
Who is the handsome person?
You must appoint someone else.
This is ridiculous. He's not handsome.
- I might look handsome to her. - We must be objective.
It can't be subjective.
- I found him. - No way, it's nonsense.
- This has to be objective. - I think...
- we can make it. - Send him back!
- My eyes look fine. - For this show,
- we must send him back. - This part of my face is handsome.
(Let me see how handsome you are.)
My goodness.
He's not handsome.
(Ji Won and the handsome guy get bracelets.)
How can everyone here not have double eyelids?
Does anyone have double eyelids?
There's no one.
- What happened? - No one has double eyelids here.
Double eyelids...
- Do you have double eyelids? - Gosh.
- Wait a minute. - No one has double eyelids.
- He doesn't... - Does anyone have double eyelids?
- No one. - What about you?
(Will Yeon Jae end up being alone?)
- Does anyone have double eyelids? - No one does.
- This is unbelievable. - How can there be no one?
Do you have them?
I think he does.
He has double eyelids.
He just follows you although he doesn't have any.
You just follow her because it's Yeon Jae.
Wait.
Who looks like a celebrity?
I don't know anyone who looks like a celebrity.
No one looks like a celebrity here.
(He looks like he's in a hurry,)
(but he has been helping others until now.)
(All that he's been doing was helping Women's Team.)
(Men's Team, please keep up for me.)
No one looks like a celebrity.
Let's run. There are two more.
Jong Kook will come here soon.
(Let's go catch Kwang Soo.)
Jong Kook, put the bracelet on now!
(Kwang Soo is in crisis.)
Kwang Soo!
(I'm coming!)
Kwang Soo! No way!
Stop!
(Kwang Soo struggles to fight two women.)
(They rip his name tag.)
I got it!
(Kwang Soo is out!)
No way!
(Ji Won is very skilful.)
My goodness.
(Ji Won finds Jong Kook distracted.)
- Gosh. - Oh, my.
(She removes Jong Kook's name tag.)
(Jong Kook is eliminated.)
I pulled it off!
- I removed two name tags. - It's a double kill.
(Ji Won succeeds in eliminating Kwang Soo and Jong Kook.)
- Are you out? - Everyone is so sluggish.
- We all should exercise hard. - Right.
Why are the staff so bad at running?
Come to our gym and work out starting next week.
- You need some exercise. - From next week.
(Jong Kook and Kwang Soo are eliminated.)
Cling onto his sleeve for five seconds.
(Let's see if his arms are strong enough.)
- I'll start. - Start.
- Gosh! We made it before! - Let's do it again.
Have you yet to find your partner?
I found him and I clung onto his arm for five seconds.
- And he failed this time? - Yes, he failed this time.
- He's so mean. - I'm sure it was intentional.
I'm so stressed out.
(Is it Jae Seok's scheme?)
Thank you.
Thank you. Please keep it a secret.
(What did you say?)
Please don't turn away.
You're not busy now.
- I should find a strong man. - I'm not strong.
I'll cling onto your arm.
Just drop me after two seconds.
I have weak arms.
That's what I want.
Because I'm a spy.
(She whispers to him that she's a spy.)
(Is Min Kyung really a spy?)
(3 hours ago)
You'll choose one of your teammates to be a fellow spy.
- A fellow spy? - Yes.
Whom should I pick?
(Whom has he chosen to be their fellow spies?)
I'll choose Min Kyung.
(He chose Min Kyung.)
Today, you're a spy of Men's Team.
- A spy? - Yes.
(Now, she's a spy of Men's Team.)
You'll have only one chance...
to betray your fellow spy and quit being a spy.
(She's given a chance to quit being a spy.)
Then I can choose either way.
But if you lose after betraying, you'll get harsher penalty.
My goodness.
- Do you understand? - Yes, I do.
(If she doesn't win, she gets a penalty.)
(So she dragged on in the Arcade Games round...)
(and came up with a ridiculous answer.)
(She even asked the staff to intentionally fail the mission.)
(Everything was a part of her scheme.)
Be careful.
(They'll participate in "Bracelet Battle".)
We must stay together.
Wait.
We must move together.
Be careful.
(Ji Hyo is out.)
It hurts.
(Ji Won grabs Gary's bracelet.)
(It breaks.)
(Gary is out.)
You did a great job.
Wait!
(Haha attacks Ji Won.)
I got it. Okay.
I made it. Are you okay?
(Ji Won is out.)
I shouldn't have put my guard down.
Wait a minute.
(Yu Ra is under attack by 2 members.)
- It's okay. - What's this?
(Yu Ra is out.)
Gosh, this is really hard.
(Gary, Ji Won and Yu Ra are eliminated.)
- Thank you. - Now, go.
(Some haven't even started the battle.)
She looks like Sulli.
- Sulli. - This is nonsense.
- She looks like Sulli. - Go bring someone else.
What are you talking about?
- She looks like Sulli. - Next!
- What do you mean, next? - The one with bigger hands.
Hey, Sulli!
She looks exactly like Sulli.
(We apologise to Sulli's fans.)
Goodness.
This is ridiculous.
(Spy Jae Seok is doing a good job.)
(Min Kyung, I'm counting on you.)
- It's really unfavourable for us. - Wait.
(She's trying to make someone remove her bracelet.)
(Do not worry, Jae Seok.)
You're so scary.
(She's acting.)
(Screaming)
He's so strong.
(Spy Mi Sun and Spy Min Kyung are fighting.)
Hey!
(My goodness.)
(It got ripped.)
- It hurts. - Yeon Jae!
(Yeon Jae was watching for a good chance.)
(She made it.)
Yeon Jae!
Stop there!
(She's giggling.)
Yes!
(It's really chaotic here.)
Please stop. No.
(No!)
(I can't win.)
(What?)
(Spy Mi Sun is out in an awkward way.)
Goodness.
(Someone grabs Haha.)
My goodness. You scared me.
(Min Kyung's partner is doing his best to win.)
Did we win?
Goodness.
- Did we win? - He's too good at this.
- We won! - He's really strong.
- We won? - We won!
(Women's Team removed all the bracelets and won.)
(I'm doomed.)
Women's Team...
wins this round!
(It's 0 to 200.)
Gosh.
(Women's Team already earned 200 points.)
I think our team's spy...
- is really incompetent. - That's right.
- So... - We even said we didn't have one.
(She remembers something.)
You're a spy for Men's Team,
but you get one chance to betray your teammate and quit being a spy.
(She gets one chance to join Women's Team.)
So I could join Women's Team...
if Men's Team doesn't look like winning. I get it.
Yes.
(Women's Team is leading by 200 points. What will Min Kyung do?)
Do you have a moment?
Ji Won is getting suspicious of me.
- This'll just raise more questions. - No.
(Min Kyung calls over her fellow spy.)
Jae Seok, there's a mark that indicates I'm a spy on my back.
What are you doing?
The method is simple.
You need to take Jae Seok's name tag off and put it back on.
(You need to take Jae Seok's name tag off and put it back on.)
What are you doing?
(It's off.)
Hold on.
(It's back on.)
(Spy Min Kyung has successfully betrayed her team leader.)
The final race is always the highlight of a field day.
- Right. - It's the relay race.
The winner will get 200 points.
- Do we have 200 points? - Yes.
If we win, it's a tie, right?
It will be a tie and you can take the lead by winning the spy vote.
Men's Team is just doing bad regardless of the spies.
I think we're all spies here.
- They have at least three. - I think so, too.
We have too many spies here. They're so bad at the games.
People who aren't even spies are acting like one.
- We're just bad at these games. - I know.
- Are you a spy? - No.
- At least three of us are spies. - Never.
- Are you a spy? - You know I'm innocent.
- Are you a spy? - No, I'm not.
He sounds like one.
Aren't you a smuggler?
- You're on the top of the list. - He's such a spy.
- He's a spy. - Did you see that?
The pupils were like this.
(Those were the eyes of a spy.)
(His pupils are dilated.)
I thought you were Lee Kyung Kyu for a second.
- His eyes were like this. - You found a talent.
He's definitely a spy.
- This is hilarious. - The real spy must be happy.
We have so many spies on our team.
(Who's the spy on Men's Team?)
If there's a spy on our team, she's doing a very poor job.
- She's a bad spy. - I'm sure it's Min Kyung.
Me? Why? I tried really hard.
It'll be shocking if you turned out to be a spy.
I feel betrayed already.
Are you not?
(What will happen to the ex-spy who chose to betray?)
If you look at the front, you'll see the batons.
Okay.
- What's that? - Why is it so big?
- Are you sure it's not a pillow? - That's the baton?
(It's extra-large.)
(I'll give that to Men's Team.)
This might be unfair for Women's Team.
That would be a disadvantage to us.
It was an honest mistake.
- Are you kidding me? - It was a mistake.
- Sorry, kid. - Don't call me that.
(I'm sorry, it was a mistake.)
- I can't beat him. - That's enough.
You tried.
(There's a reason why they made me the spy.)
You have to throw it further than you think.
We should most definitely win.
- Are you ready? - Go, Jong Kook.
You have to do good, Jong Kook. Prove us that you're not a spy.
I can do this.
(I'll prove it to you.)
(I have faith in you, Jong Kook.)
We'll be able to tell the spies from this.
Here I go.
(You won't be suspicious any more after this.)
Oh, my.
(I can't let them take the lead after I betrayed them.)
(It went beyond the line.)
I knew it. You're suspicious.
Are you really a spy?
Is he crazy?
(Keep it up.)
(Is Jong Kook really a spy?)
Ji Won, you can do it.
It's not about kicking it far away.
Don't let it go over the line.
- You have very small feet. - Yes, I do.
(Here it goes.)
(It's nowhere close, but it didn't go over the line.)
Okay.
- Did we win? - Good job.
Is it a 1 on 1 battle?
(Good job, team.)
- Can I go? - Let's see how Gary does.
(Gary's up next.)
- There you go. - That was good.
He's leading the scoreboard so far.
(Yu Ra goes 4th.)
That's good.
(She takes the lead.)
Her shoe didn't roll.
(This is why I chose this team over Men's Team.)
- You can do it. - I think we got this.
(Seok Jin's up next.)
It's looking good.
(I have my hopes on Seok Jin.)
(Seok Jin fails.)
(Is he a spy or is he just bad?)
- I slipped. - He's so bad.
(Everyone else did worse than Yu Ra.)
Why didn't hers roll over?
(Yu Ra of Women's Team is leading.)
- She's a spy. - No, I'm not.
I think Yeon Jae will shoot it high up.
I think it'll go backwards.
(Kwang Soo is up next for the losing team.)
You're so bad.
(They're taunting him.)
- You're so bad. - You're so bad.
(I don't care if I'm the spy. I just want him to fail.)
- Cut that out. - Why?
- I can see you. - I'm getting ready for my turn.
I'll give it a go.
(He's concentrating.)
You can't do it.
(I just want to disturb you.)
Just get it over with. We don't care.
- Don't look at me. - You won't be able to do it.
Gosh, you're bothering me.
Kwang Soo, you'll do very bad.
(They keep babbling on.)
Here I go.
You're very tall.
(He turns his head away and shoots.)
That's good.
(How did he do?)
(Is this for real?)
- You're very tall. - That's good.
That's good.
(He rewrites the history of field days with that kick.)
Okay!
- That was amazing. - Good job.
(He is no longer the unlucky man.)
(Did that really just happen?)
- The game is over. - How are we supposed to beat that?
(Praise me.)
The game's over already.
(Men's Team will win at this rate.)
Yeon Jae.
(Kwang Soo is leading.)
- You did good. - You have to get it on the line.
(It's time to get back at him.)
Get back in the line.
(I'm not going to try anyway.)
- What are you doing? - I'm practising.
(We can't let you off that easy.)
- Don't you lay your hands on me. - Okay.
(One, two, three.)
(Jae Seok gets kicked in the butt.)
(I'm your team leader!)
- I'm sorry. - You crossed the line there.
(How dare you abuse our team leader?)
- I'm sorry. - Isn't that a foul?
- He just kicked me. - The game hasn't' started yet.
(Do you have any idea how much I'm trying to make you win?)
- We have to look after our own. - That's right.
(The pink barricade goes up.)
It's been weeks since I had a good team.
(Are you that happy?)
- Good job. - Why'd you do that?
(Stop bothering our team leader.)
(Jae Seok and Yeon Jae are the only members left for Women's Team.)
- Good job. - I'm sorry, Jae Seok.
- You did very good. - Here it goes.
You're the best.
(I'll go easy at first.)
(It was a very good shot for a spy.)
- Is it over? - I should've done better.
We won.
(Yeon Jae is our only hope.)
Son Yeon Jae.
(Yeon Jae is the last person up for Women's Team.)
She wins if she gets it right on the line.
You're the best, Yeon Jae.
She was vibrant and strong.
(She's acrobatic, strong and has a sense of distance.)
She did good.
(Will Yeon Jae lead her team to victory?)
- Here I go. - Do it.
(She shoots.)
(I can't let her take back the lead.)
(She failed to take the lead.)
You came really close, though.
That was close.
She did really well.
(Maybe I shouldn't have betrayed.)
Women's Team gets the big baton and Men's Team gets the small one.
(Both spies had a tight strategic battle.)
(Min Kyung quit being a spy and betrayed Jae Seok.)
I think we're all spies here.
(Who's the last spy hidden among Men's Team?)
(Introducing the relay course)
(Step 1: Hurdling)
(Step 2: Roll the gym ball to the finishing line.)
(Spin 10 times holding your nose and cross the walk.)
(Step 3: Eat a caramel and whistle.)
(Step 4: Limbo)
(Step 5: Push face through plastic wrap and scream to 125 decibels.)
(Step 6: Roll the ball, tumble and catch.)
(Step 7: Open the basket together.)
Who's going first?
- Okay. - I can't...
I can't do this.
Seok Jin is out.
I didn't know they would be that close to one another.
This looks hard. I had no idea.
(Mi Sun tries the plastic wrap course.)
(This is a bit embarrassing.)
I didn't know I have to push my face through plastic wrap.
Yu Ra, are you doing this as well?
(Should we just go back home?)
Mi Sun, I had no idea we have to do this.
This'll make us look terrible.
I think I made the wrong decision.
- We made the wrong choice. - I didn't know we'd do this.
(Sorry, it's too late now.)
(Yeon Jae tries catching the ball.)
It hurts so much.
This isn't as easy as it looks.
(This is child's play to me.)
(She drops the ball.)
Can I catch it with my feet?
This isn't easy at all.
- It's harder this way. - I figured it out now.
(In numerical order, it's hurdling, gym ball, caramel, limbo,)
(plastic wrap, rolling the ball and opening the basket.)
- Let's go! - Let's go!
(This is their last chance to take the lead.)
(This is the chance for Men's Team to get even with Women's Team.)
(For Women's Team, it's a chance to win by 400 points.)
(Please don't make the betrayal and spying go to waste.)
("Relay Race" starts.)
(They charge towards the hurdles.)
(Hurdles fall.)
(Are they hurdles or dominoes?)
I'm in trouble. What should I do?
They all fell.
It must be harder than it seems.
(Everyone's watching.)
- What should I do? - They all fell.
Seok Jin!
- Seok Jin! Hurry! - Hey.
(Jae Seok is fulfilling his duties as a spy.)
I'm winning.
(The next runners came to watch.)
(Seok Jin is like a spy even though he's not.)
This is so annoying.
Is he a spy?
Are you a spy?
I didn't know it'd be this hard.
This is so annoying.
This is really annoying.
- It's too slow. - Jae Seok is taking too long.
Is he a spy?
(Is our team leader a spy?)
When will they be finished?
This is so hard.
It's really hard.
I've never seen hurdles as timid as these.
What is this?
You're supposed to jump over hurdles.
- Are you a spy? - These hurdles...
(Suspicious)
(They're finally almost finished.)
(Seok Jin is a bit ahead.)
(I have to go faster than Kwang Soo.)
You got this!
Go!
Good!
(Men's Team is ahead in the 2nd part.)
(Stop there!)
(They arrived almost at the same time.)
(Jae Seok taking a long time on purpose.)
- Where's the zipper? - Open it!
Hurry out!
Come out.
You look like a goddess now.
(Because of Jae Seok, the other team caught up.)
Turn 10 times.
(She's very fast.)
Kwang Soo!
(You're doing great, Min Kyung.)
I'm really bad at this.
I can't do this.
You've turned 10 times.
Min Kyung.
(He seems drunk.)
(Everyone's watching this funny scene.)
- That's hilarious. - It looks so funny.
Go!
(There are drunk runners.)
(Kwang Soo puts one foot on.)
What should I do? I should go forward.
(She continues taking drunk steps.)
What will she do?
She can't walk.
She's almost as fast as Kwang Soo.
(She takes big steps.)
(Here we go.)
(They finished almost at the same time.)
(Eat a caramel and whistle)
What's that?
(Their face is covered with flour.)
My goodness.
What's that?
(He found it.)
- He found it. - Go on.
(They have to whistle after eating the caramel.)
(Whistle now.)
(It's too chewy.)
You're almost done.
Let's do this!
You're almost there.
I can't whistle.
- There you go. - Yes!
(Haha charges towards the 4th section.)
Ji Hyo.
- I can't whistle. - There you go.
(Ji Hyo is finally done.)
Ji Hyo, hurry.
- He passed it! - There you go!
(Gary passed the limbo stick at once.)
- He passed it! - Is it done?
- It's done! - Do the limbo!
Oh my.
(Men's Team's baton is handed over to a spy.)
- We should help her. - Mi Sun.
Go through it.
What should she do?
(Yu Ra, here I come.)
Yu Ra!
- Hurry. - Do it.
(Yu Ra starts the 5th section.)
- Continue. - Hurry.
You have to continue.
(Mi Sun is taking a long time on purpose.)
You're almost there.
(They're fighting with their faces.)
- You're almost there. - I can't breathe.
Use the top of your head.
Use all your strength.
(A space monster)
Use the top of your head.
- Use the top of your head. - You're almost there.
(Go through it, Yu Ra!)
- It's almost torn. - You're almost there.
- It's almost done. - You're almost there.
Please stop!
Why did you volunteer to do this?
Please stop now.
Why did you want to do this?
Why did you volunteer?
You have nothing to lose.
(She looks like she has already lost everything.)
Hold the plastic wrap.
It's torn here.
- Hold the plastic. - There you go.
- There you go. - Yes!
It's done.
(She'll pass if she gets more than 125 decibels.)
(Yu Ra is done.)
Run!
My goodness.
- Hurry. - Stop, Mi Sun.
It's torn here.
Come through here.
- There you go. - It's done.
Scream now.
(Screaming)
- Come nearer. - Come near.
- Come near. - Hurry!
- Please fail. - Yeon Jae.
(Yeon Jae throws her ball.)
(Now, she only needs to catch the ball.)
(I'll show you the beautiful moves from the competitions.)
(She caught the ball with her legs.)
You're supposed to catch it with your hands.
- Am I wrong? - With my hands?
- Catch it with your hands. - With my hands?
My goodness.
Come here.
(Mi Sun is still trying.)
(She failed again.)
Can I try again?
(Is she doing this on purpose?)
(Yeon Jae, go ahead.)
With hands?
- Oh my. - Yes!
There you go.
(Yeon Jae succeeded.)
Good job!
(We still have a chance.)
(I don't think so.)
(Will Mi Sun fulfil her duties as a spy?)
- Good job! - Continue.
Hurry.
- Good job. - Hurry.
Our female warriors, good job.
Go ahead. You can hit me.
Hurry!
Come on!
- What should I do? - Ready.
One, two, three.
(Screaming)
(Her arm is twisted.)
(She was forced to succeed.)
Are you okay?
Are you okay? You're done.
Hurry!
- There you go. - Hurry!
Hit here.
(She's pretending she's running as fast as she can.)
Go.
Succeed at once.
- There you go. - There you go.
(Jong Kook succeeds at once.)
- Hurry. - I think it'll burst.
Throw these.
Hurry!
You're doing great.
Ji Won is doing a great job.
- Throw them. - Let's do this!
(Men's Team starts throwing.)
It's okay.
Keep it up!
Look at that. We should aim there.
Aim a weak part.
Aim at the centre.
- At the centre? - Yes.
You're doing great.
There you go.
It's driving me crazy.
It's opening here.
(They might be done soon.)
- Aim here. - There?
(Jae Seok points at the wrong place.)
- There? - Not the centre?
(Don't try to fool us.)
Where should we aim?
I think it's here.
Come near.
(Mi Sun seems to be working hard.)
I'll lower it.
(She's throwing at Jong Kook.)
(He's working so hard.)
It's very sturdy.
(You're working too hard.)
It's too hard.
(She hits Jong Kook.)
(Why do I feel like I'm keep getting hit?)
(It hits Gary.)
Keep going. It's about to open.
(She's blatantly hitting the other members.)
I'm sorry.
- Are you sure it was a mistake? - I'm sorry.
(I almost got caught.)
Keep it up!
It's almost done.
- We're almost there. - Just a bit more.
(Men's Team's basket starts to break.)
Yes!
Why doesn't it burst?
Aim at the side.
(Which spy will win?)
It's done.
We're almost there. It's coming out!
(Men's Team succeeded.)
- We're done! - Yes!
(Gosh)
(I'm not smiling on the inside.)
We won!
(Why did I betray them?)
This won't break.
It almost broke here.
Yes!
What a relief!
(Are you sure?)
(It's too bad.)
What a shame!
(Are you sure?)
That was close.
(Betrayals are followed by regrets.)
(Men's Team wins "Relay Race")
(The two teams are tied at 200 to 200.)
With Men's Team...
winning "Relay Race", you're tied at 200 to 200.
We're tied.
Now,
the spies will determine the result.
- It's unbelievable. - It's up to the spies now.
Now,
it's time to guess the spies.
(This is the final vote.)
(The moment of truth is here.)
(They start discussing.)
I swear, I'm not a spy.
(I have something to tell you.)
Trust me. I was a spy at first.
(I was a spy at first.)
(Min Kyung reveals her truth.)
(What?)
But I changed.
(She even confesses her betrayal.)
(What is she talking about?)
Our team was winning at first,
so I changed.
Can you do that?
I could do that by ripping off Jae Seok's name tag.
Didn't any of you see me doing that?
Trust me.
- The other spy must have no idea. - Exactly.
(Is that true?)
(Jae Seok is left alone.)
(This doesn't feel right.)
You're not suspecting me, are you?
(Everyone's suspecting Jae Seok.)
Are you?
Isn't it too obvious?
You're mistaken.
- Come here. - I mean...
We've been talking about what to eat tonight.
You're making me look like a spy.
It feels like reading a mystery novel.
- I'm so confused. - We've decided.
You've decided, too, haven't you?
I have.
You have? Is he the spy?
For sure.
(Let me tell you. Jae Seok is the spy.)
(If they guess it right, they'll win.)
Is it possible to change the spy?
(Will they trust Min Kyung?)
- Jae Seok, go first. - Should I?
If I go first,
I think you'll talk about me.
- We were talking about what to eat. - I'll go first.
Good luck.
(Jae Seok goes first.)
Trust me. I was a spy at first,
but I changed.
(Whom will Jae Seok use to change the public opinion?)
(Song Ji Hyo)
The spy doesn't know?
Go ahead.
- Should I go? - Can the spy not know?
- Yu Ra. Trust me. - You seem to be...
suspecting me.
(Trust me and you'll win.)
(Whom will Yu Ra choose?)
(Yu Jae Seok)
My goodness. What should I do?
Can I trust her?
If it was a lie, I'll be shocked.
(She didn't trust Min Kyung.)
It's my gut feeling.
Trust me.
(Which team will guess the spy right and win?)
(All votes are in.)
Is that possible?
All votes are in.
Who is it?
We'll give you 100 points if you guessed it right.
That's generous of you.
I can't wait.
The final score...
(They're tied at 200 to 200.)
(The vote will determine the winner.)
(Which team will win?)
The final score for Men's Team is 300...
and Women's Team, 200.
(Men's Team: 300, Women's Team: 200)
(Did they fail to guess the spy?)
(I told you Jae Seok was the spy.)
Did we guess it right?
Whose name did you write?
Did you write my name?
- Did you? - I didn't write your name.
(They're at a loss for words.)
I didn't write your name.
(Why didn't you trust me?)
Oh my.
(Yu Ra was the only one who trusted Min Kyung.)
(The other 3 suspected Min Kyung.)
(Women's Team failed to guess who the spy was.)
Let me tell you who the spy for Women's Team was.
(Bitter)
- It was Jae Seok. - I knew it.
- I told you. - Oh my.
(Why didn't you trust me?)
- I told you. - She betrayed once more.
Did you betray once more?
(Welcome to the world of betrayals.)
Min Kyung.
I can't believe you.
You told the others to choose me, right?
How could you do this to us?
Ji Won. I told you it was him.
- Didn't anyone else choose him? - Only Yu Ra trusted me.
The spies for Men's Team were...
(Men's Team's spies will be revealed.)
(Did they choose Mi Sun?)
- Towards the end... - I knew immediately.
Who do you think it is?
(2 minutes before the vote)
(I should remain calm.)
Mi Sun threw the balls at us.
I got hit many times.
It gave me a hint.
(3 of them chose Mi Sun.)
(They succeeded in finding the spy.)
The spies for Men's Team are...
Mi Sun...
- Really? - Really?
- You got caught. - and...
And Haha.
- Were there two? - Were there two?
Haha.
Were there two?
Were there two spies?
(How did they become comrades?)
What is this?
I choose...
(Mi Sun chose her comrade.)
(She chose Haha.)
Haha.
(She chose Haha as her fellow spy.)
You should make Women's Team win.
My goodness.
(That's how Haha became a spy.)
(Now, they both failed their missions.)
I told you about Haha.
- I told you. - This is unbelievable.
That's why Haha kept suspecting Seok Jin.
I couldn't find a moment to betray.
We were losing the entire time.
(Many shared the spies' workload...)
(by doing horribly at the games.)
(He sometimes focused on the game to avoid suspicion,)
(but the other members were so bad.)
Is he a spy?
(Everyone is helping me.)
(I thought Men's Team would lose.)
The final winner is Men's Team.
Jae Seok succeeded his mission as a spy.
(Hurray!)
Are you happy?
- You're terrible. - Are you that happy?
Yeon Jae, don't get me wrong.
That's not it.
I knew it.
Min Kyung betrayed twice and failed,
so she'll be penalised.
(Min Kyung will pay for dinner.)
- Amazing! - Nice!
Give me a call, baby, baby
(She's dancing to celebrate it.)
No one trusted her.
Take your prizes.
(Men's Team and Jae Seok win prizes.)
- Why do you touch it? - I'm in Men's Team.
- You are? - I told you.
- What is it? - I'll take the prize today.
It's a notebook.
They're so cute.
- Are you serious? - They're cute.
- They're so cute. - They're cute.
We'll give Jae Seok another prize for fulfilling his duties.
What did he do?
Give it to me somewhere else.
Seriously.
They're all watching.
- Let me see. - That's not it.
Are you proud?
That's not it.
Why did you give it to me here?
Jae Seok is the only happy one.
Why does he get another prize?
I got nothing when I won last time!
Today's winner was me.
I made it.
(Jong Kook is jealous.)
I'm 32 years old!
I don't have kids.
Give them to your kids later.
Should I have another kid?
Thank you for today.
(They're having dinner.)
Thank you, Min Kyung.
Thank you.
(Happy)
Eat a lot.
Why did you betray us?
Seok Jin can take care of himself.
Eat as soon as it's done.
Min Kyung, please pay for the food.
Min Kyung.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
I'm sorry.
Give me a call, baby, baby
I'll order some more.
(She pays 735 dollars for her betrayal.)
This is what happens to betrayers.
(The receipt is being printed.)
Do you hear that?
It's the sound of betrayal.
(We thank Mi Sun, Ji Won, Yeon Jae, Min Kyung and Yu Ra.)
(It's a fall day in 2016.)
(The avatars...)
I'm your master.
(will have to obey...)
(their masters.)
(Avatars and their masters)
(Their mysterious game starts.)
(My Avatar Can)
(With the auction,)
(a war among the avatars has begun.)
The highest bid is 61 right now.
(The master's order is the way and the truth.)
(Control your avatar...)
(to win the game.)
(My Avatar Can)