This is Dubai.
Wow.
It's so pretty.
This place is amazing.
This is why people talk highly of Dubai.
I never thought Running Man would let us relax like this.
I love that we are allowed to freely travel around here.
Ji Hyo! I'm loving this!
Don't you love being here?
- This is tasty.
- I was surprised.
(Running Man members have fallen in love with Dubai.)
This is freedom.
(However,)
(their freedom was short-lived and the extreme mission race unfolds.)
This is really dangerous!
It's a real desert. Oh, my.
(There will be no freedom. Those who fail will receive a penalty.)
- This is nonsense.
- This is too much.
(What will happen in Dubai?)
(Running Man in Dubai)
(Incheon International Airport, late at night)
(Running Man tour?)
- Hello.
It's a nice evening.
(Welcome to Running Man Tour, individual travelling in Dubai)
Individual travelling is valid only when there is no camera.
Are we really going to be freely travelling?
Yes. Everyone, welcome to our individual travelling in Dubai.
(Please believe us. It'll be a treat.)
- Really?
- I love Dubai!
- Is this real?
- Since you have worked so hard,
we have planned a special vacation to Dubai.
- Really?
- Are we really freely travelling?
Don't make us angry from the beginning.
- I think it will be a tough trip.
- It'll be a wonderful trip.
(At that moment)
(Is he a tourist guide or a guest?)
- It's a man.
- Why is it a man?
- That gait looks familiar.
- Who is it?
- I've seen those legs a lot.
- Who?
- It must be Yong Hwa.
- It's not him.
- Is it not Yong Hwa?
- Who is it?
He looks like he has come out here before.
- Yes, he must've been here before.
- You're right.
- Isn't it Ji Sung?
- Yes, he must've been here before.
(Who could this man be?)
I'm here.
(Jung Il Woo.)
- Jung Il Woo.
Why are you going that way?
(He was remembered as the quick and competitive.)
(He swings...)
(and misses.)
(What has happened to Il Woo?)
- It's Il Woo.
- Il Woo.
- Hello.
- I was about to say his name.
His legs look unique.
I knew it was him from the beginning.
His legs look like that of a runner's.
It's Il Woo.
Il Woo, have you been to Dubai before?
- He has a strong desire to win.
- No, it's my first time.
- Is it your first time to Dubai?
- Yes.
- Really?
(Another person approaches the members.)
It's sea anemone hairstyle.
There's another person coming.
(What?)
(Shy)
Da Hey, don't hide your face.
We know it's you.
It's Da Hey.
(Goodness!)
- Hello, Da Hey.
- We know.
It's really Lee Da Hey.
It's been a while.
(She was very active on Running Man and even eliminated the spy.)
Let's get rid of him quickly.
I need to do at least something since I'm on this show.
- Hello.
- You look great.
- Thank you.
- You're right.
Isn't Da Hey older than Il Woo?
- Yes, I'm older.
- Yes.
These days, it's common to see older women with younger men.
It's been 13 years since I've known Da Hey.
- Really?
- That's a long time.
Il Woo visited the broadcasting station 13 years ago.
I had a dream of becoming an actor.
- Oh, it was before you debuted.
- He had a short haircut.
- I was really nervous.
- Was it during your army service?
I bought him...
- jjajangmyeon and jjambbong.
- Really?
- Oh, really?
- Yes.
Let's get going since we have all arrived.
I'm still not sure if we'll be able to freely travel.
Are they really going to give it up that easily?
- There's no way they would.
- It can't be possible.
It can't be.
(Whether you believe it or not,)
(aren't you excited to depart?)
I heard that in Dubai, people sell gold on the streets.
- Really?
- There are even vending machines.
- Yes.
- Let's buy some.
(Really?)
The fact that they gave us this is unsettling.
I feel like I need to memorise it.
Or maybe we'll have to go to certain locations in this book...
and carry out a mission.
This worries me. I'm so nervous.
Let's get on board.
Let's go.
(See you later.)
- Goodbye.
- Thank you.
(See you later.)
One, two, three.
(Their flight to Dubai took 10 hours and 10 minutes.)
(After 10 hours in the air,)
(they have arrived in Dubai.)
Oh my gosh!
(Despite it being dawn, many fans came to greet the members.)
(Dear Dubai fans, it's nice to meet you all.)
(It's the Prince of Asia.)
- Lee Kwang Soo!
Kwang Soo is very popular.
(Has Kwang Soo won over Dubai, too?)
(Shy)
(Thank you, fans of Running Man!)
This show is really popular.
Hi.
- Goodbye.
You're like idol stars.
- In Arabic...
- What time is it?
I think it's about 5am here.
- It's 6am.
- It's 6:13am.
- Is it already morning?
- It must be around 11am in Korea.
- Yes.
- Do you mean it's eleven o'clock...
in the morning?
- It's very clean and...
- It's neat.
very detailed.
That building is so tall.
Which one?
- That's the one!
- It's that one!
- It's that one.
- "Mission: Impossible".
- I can't even see the top.
- Oh, my.
I can't see the very top!
- It's Burj Khalifa.
- I saw it in the book.
Where is it?
- Over there.
- It was in "Mission: Impossible".
Over there. It's Burj Khalifa.
I can't see.
- That's amazing.
- Take a picture, Kwang Soo.
- Wait.
- My goodness.
- I can't see the top.
- So that's the one.
That has 203 floors, right?
- Wow!
- Gosh, that's amazing!
It's so tall.
It's a real skyscraper.
I can't see.
You need to duck a little to see it.
- This is...
- It's over here.
just amazing.
(Burj Khalifa is the world's tallest building with a height of 829.8m.)
- I really can't see it.
- I bet...
I bet you could see that when you're riding a helicopter.
It's amazing.
It's really tall.
- Really?
- It's so amazing.
How tall is it?
Gosh, that's really tall.
- Where?
- Look at that.
We must be going over there.
That's what I was told.
- Goodness.
- Really?
Have we arrived?
(He is deeply moved.)
- This is where...
- Oh, my.
Tom Cruise ran.
- This place?
- Tom Cruise.
- From "Mission: Impossible".
- It looks really splendid.
- It's that place.
It's that scene where he climbed up wearing the gloves.
Are we going up?
Can we go?
The people living up there should have their parachutes ready.
(They enter the building to get in the lift.)
- Kwang Soo.
- Yes?
What are you going to press?
There are only two buttons, ground floor and 124th floor.
(There are only two buttons, for the ground and 124th floor.)
It's right here.
It goes directly up.
- Are we going up now?
- Yes.
What is this?
The music is nice.
We're on the seventh floor.
Are we going up?
It's going so fast.
13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19...
- My ears feel funny.
- 20, 21, 22...
- Me too.
- Really.
We're on the 27th floor. My ears feels funny.
- Hold your breath.
- It's so fast.
- Goodness.
- My ears feel funny.
(It takes only a minute to reach the 124th floor.)
I swallowed eight times.
- It's scary.
- There's no...
We're on the 55th floor.
- We're on the 58th floor.
- It's going faster.
It's nearly...
We're almost on the 80th floor.
We're already so high up.
This is terrifying.
My heart is thumping so hard.
Wow, we're already here.
- The music is quite...
- It's the world's tallest building.
- Oh, my.
- We're here. It's like a scene...
from the movies.
I thought I was on a ride.
(Amazed)
This is amazing.
(In just 1 minute,)
(they arrived in a whole new world.)
- This is amazing.
- It's amazing.
(Are you ready for this?)
- It's scary.
- We're really high up.
(The sun rises above the horizon.)
It's so high.
This is unbelievable.
(They can look over skyscrapers.)
This is a scene from "Mission: Impossible".
(This is unbelievable.)
- It's scary.
- It's so high up.
I can't believe this.
It's so high.
This is unbelievable.
(They are at a loss for words.)
When shooting "Mission: Impossible",
Tom Cruise came here, right?
I got goosebumps.
It's too tall.
I'm getting tingling feelings.
- This is amazing.
- Over here. I can't get any closer.
(The splendid view of the skyline is revealed.)
Why are you trying to show me?
You came a long way.
- Yes.
As you have all heard before we departed Korea,
you will be travelling freely.
You can explore Dubai freely.
Really?
- No way.
- I don't believe it.
(There has to be something more.)
We'll hand out the itinerary first.
- Really?
- Yes.
This can't be true.
- This can't be.
- Can we go anywhere we want?
- Can we go clubbing at night?
- They have name tags on them.
- "Jung Il Woo".
- I should put it in here.
Yes, in the front.
You have the itinerary in your bag.
What is this?
What are these mysterious blanks?
- All right.
- We're supposed to fill them.
- So this is our itinerary.
- Starting from...
the tallest building in the world, Burj Khalifa,
you'll visit tourist attractions in Dubai...
- described in the itinerary.
- Okay.
- You can choose where to go.
- Can we go anywhere?
Yes, enjoy the places as much as you want.
- Look at this! What is this?
- Enjoy some food as well.
- There's ziplining!
- In your bag...
- Look at this.
- We can choose not to go.
You can choose not to go.
Who did you think would attempt skydiving?
- When you arrive...
- Is there skydiving as well?
- There is.
- Yes.
After completing your mission, you can move to another place.
Just go anywhere you want.
Have some fun and try out the mission.
- That's all you need to do.
- Really?
- There's a beach.
- When you're there...
So we don't have to go skydiving, right?
- Of course not.
- Really?
Next to each place in the itinerary, you'll see a star.
The stars indicate how hard the mission will be.
When you complete each mission,
you'll get a grasshopper stamp...
as Dubai means "Grasshopper" in their old language.
- Really?
- It means "Grasshopper".
- Dubai!
- This is...
my second home.
This is your city.
(Welcome to the land of grasshoppers.)
So... Until the desert tour starts...
- It starts at 3pm.
- If you get 10 stamps...
- Gosh.
- 10 stamps?
You'll get to stay at a luxurious resort.
- Wow.
- Really?
- The thing is,
- Without the staff?
the resort is in the middle of the desert.
- Out of the nine of you,
- Yes.
only five will get to stay there.
(Then what about the remaining 4?)
The others will bivouac in the desert.
(4 people with the least stamps will bivouac.)
(Sleeping in the desert?)
(Which unlucky 4 will end up spending the night in the desert?)
(Welcome to the desert.)
You'll bivouac in the desert.
Desert Team, gather around.
(Let's not have foolish hopes and just sleep in the desert.)
- Let's go to the desert!
- Come here.
All right. Now we have the desert team.
Those five will go to the resort.
(The unlucky 4 have formed a bivouacking team.)
Ji Hyo is included in that team.
- And...
- Wait.
These guys will sleep in the desert.
Why are you excluding yourself?
- You're our leader.
- What?
- This is crazy.
- One more thing.
We talked about a luxurious resort in the desert.
We filmed it with this camera. Wear it and you'll see.
- This is where you might sleep.
- Really?
- Describe it for us.
- Try it.
- Turn it on.
- Can I blink?
- This is amazing.
- It's moving.
If you turn left, you can see the left side.
- Oh, really?
- That's incredible.
These high-tech glasses don't really look good on you.
You should wear them all the time.
You look great.
Who is this?
Try it.
We should see it now.
Who is this?
- Who?
- Oh, my.
Is someone there?
I see a beautiful lady.
Let me see!
(I want to see it, too.)
I saw a lady.
- Really?
- Yes, try it.
- This is amazing.
- Can I try?
- Go ahead.
- Wow.
Wait. I just put them on.
Let's take turns.
It's incredible.
Give us another pair for Da Hey.
This is...
the desert where four of you will sleep.
- Oh, really?
- Take a look.
- How is it?
- This is completely desolate.
- It's a real desert.
- How is it?
- How does it look?
- There's nothing in this desert.
(Four of them will sleep here tonight.)
- Let me see.
- What is this?
I want to sleep at the hotel.
(I want to sleep at the hotel.)
I want to sleep at the hotel, too.
- Jong Kook...
- I want to sleep at the hotel.
is persuading me to go skydiving with him.
Jong Kook, are you going to do it?
- Are you going to go skydiving?
- Yes, I am.
I've always wanted to try skydiving.
Really? Then do it today, Il Woo.
- Do it.
- You two should do it.
It's decided now.
I hope you two go skydiving and then disappear from the programme.
(Let's get it over with and have some fun.)
- We will freely explore the city.
- Sure.
- Let's go.
- Welcome to...
- the land of grasshoppers
Welcome to the land of grasshoppers
(Let's go to the centre of Dubai!)
It'll be so fun.
(7am: Have breakfast and make plans)
Where should I go?
Right, we should decide.
Let's team up, cowards.
I'll start with...
JBR Beach.
I want to try Souk Madinat Jumeirah.
I'm going to go to a cafe after skydiving.
Jong Kook and Il Woo will be free after skydiving.
I envy them.
Are you going to a cafe?
Can only two people go skydiving?
Are you interested?
(Will Da Hey go skydiving?)
I'll go if nobody else wants to.
(She's willing to go skydiving!)
Will it be scary?
(Da Hey joins the skydiving team.)
(Sunglasses are a must when travelling.)
How do I look?
(They prepare themselves for the trip.)
- Kwang Soo.
- Let's take a picture.
(They prepare themselves for the trip.)
This is going to be fun.
(Should we start the journey?)
(They all depart to different destinations.)
(Running Man in Dubai)
(8am: Jong Kook and Il Woo head to the skydiving place.)
Palm Jumeirah, please.
Yes, thank you.
I had the chance to go skydiving when I was in my 20s.
But I gave that chance to someone else.
And I regretted doing so.
I thought I would have many chances to go skydiving in the future,
but I haven't had one yet.
Now that we're in Dubai,
- we should try it.
- Of course.
I never imagined I would skydive in Dubai.
Gosh, I'm really looking forward.
My heart is pounding.
Gosh. What should I do?
Why did I volunteer?
(She's starting to regret her decision.)
I can still give up. I'll go there and see...
if I can do it.
(Is she going crazy?)
What should I do?
(She can't keep her fingers still.)
Just talk to me.
(She's getting more and more nervous.)
Mum.
No, no.
I actually do better...
when I'm at the scene.
So...
Really?
Are you really strong?
Don't lie to yourself.
(Have I made the wrong decision?)
My mum says I'm crazy.
Have I really gone crazy?
(Driving through the city for 40 minutes)
(8:40am: Jong Kook, Il Woo and Da Hey arrive)
It says "Skydive Dubai".
(We're here after all.)
We really arrived here.
(Where is this place that fits best for skydiving?)
(Palm Jumeirah, the world's largest artificial island,)
(looks like a hand viewed from above.)
(Sighing)
I'm not nervous.
- Aren't you nervous?
- No.
I'm getting nervous now that we're here.
I'm having spaghetti legs.
(The trio arrive at the skydiving place.)
- What is this?
- We'll be instructed here.
- Should we go this way?
- This way.
Are we signing the agreement here?
Right, we should do that.
Are we signing an agreement?
I hate signing papers.
(You have to sign an agreement regarding safety.)
Why do we have to sign this?
This feels serious.
Really.
I'm getting nervous.
Gosh.
I'm going crazy.
Have you ever bungee jumped before?
No, I have never done anything like that.
- And you came here?
- I'm crazy, right?
I think I'm out of my mind.
- Probably.
- You haven't tried anything?
Gosh. I think she might faint.
At water parks,
they have steep slides.
- Oh, those.
- They have slides there.
Even those...
almost gave me a heart attack.
You can't compare this with slides.
- We're jumping off a plane.
- Exactly.
Have you looked out the window on a plane?
- That's how high this will be.
- Wait.
"Jumping off a plane"?
- Yes.
- Are we?
- Of course.
- Yes, we are.
- Then what did you think?
- I thought...
(I thought...)
- it'd be like bungee jumping.
- That's nonsense.
- Gosh.
- We're actually jumping off...
- an aeroplane.
- It's true.
- I had no idea.
- Really?
Are we really jumping off an aeroplane?
- Yes.
- We'll jump off an airplane.
The plane's door will be open.
- Seriously?
- What should I do?
- Did you really not know?
- Are you sure?
Da Hey didn't know we're jumping off a plane.
She thought this would be like bungee jumping.
I thought we would jump off a tall building.
Wouldn't it be the same?
How many times do I have to tell you that we're riding an aeroplane?
While the plane's flying, we'll be jumping off.
Planes go up as high as the clouds.
And we'll jump from there.
- Like airborne troops?
- Exactly.
- Yes.
It's something like that.
(I must be dreaming.)
Or you can just give up now and go straight to the desert.
(They need to invest time into preparing for this.)
Wait.
Should I give up?
I don't think I can jump off an aeroplane.
(If she wants to give up, she should decide while she still can.)
(Will she take the challenge?)
(Or will she give up?)
I'm nervous.
(What will Da Hey choose to do?)
This is crazy.
(Palm Jumeirah, sky diving)
(Haha and Kwang Soo go to...)
(JBR Beach.)
- Kwang Soo.
- Yes?
I don't want to sleep in the desert.
But it's a shame.
We have to at least take a bath.
You've never heard about how it's like in the desert, right?
I heard it's really cold.
It gets unbelievably cold at night.
I could never do it.
(He can't stay at the desert.)
Jae Seok, Seok Jin and Gary fit the desert.
- We're too...
- Stylish? How should I put it?
We fit into hotels better.
- Who does?
- Us.
Us? Gosh...
We're too sophisticated.
I thought there wouldn't be traffic in Dubai, but there is.
Dubai is five times bigger than Seoul...
in terms of area.
- But...
- What?
It's five times bigger than Seoul.
Than how much bigger is it than Korea?
Don't show off your knowledge...
when you don't know anything.
I'm sure it's smaller than Korea.
Gosh...
- You are so frustrating.
- All right.
Okay.
Can you ask in English when the shuttle bus...
for Dubai Mall departs?
- Ask what time it departs.
- You should do it.
- You shouldn't be intimidated.
Dubai Mall. Shuttle bus.
What time?
- That will do.
- Gosh...
Take it slowly. You don't have to rush.
(Enroll in Seok Jin's breakthrough English conversation class now!)
You are impossible.
Do you want me to talk to the driver?
- Don't. He's driving.
- Sir.
- Married?
- Yes, married.
Yes.
How many daughters... And how many sons?
I have two daughters.
- Two daughters?
- I will tell you...
how you sound in...
- I can manage.
- Korean.
- How does it sound?
- "Sir, married?"
(It sounds very awkward.)
(These two words have completed a question.)
- Sir, married?
How many sons? How many daughters?
Right.
- And he understood.
- That's how it sounded.
- But he understood.
- That's how it sounded like.
- How many sons?
- Gosh...
How many daughters?
(Meanwhile, they enter a mysterious gate.)
This is Dubai's... Are we there?
(Is it here?)
Finally, we arrived in Dubai.
- We arrived at the heart of Dubai.
- Let's go.
Let's go.
- This place is... Souk...
- Souk...
- Madinat...
- Jumeirah.
- Souk Madinat Jumeirah.
- What is this place for?
- It's a market.
- What?
- It's a traditional market.
- It's a market.
Look.
It's very beautiful.
(It's a stylish version of a traditional Dubai market.)
(It's filled with traditional products, antiques and food.)
- So it's here.
- This is...
Look, Seok Jin.
You may not know well since you're still a rookie.
You punk.
(Jae Seok teases Seok Jin.)
Am I a rookie?
You are less experienced than me.
You became a comedian two years later than I did.
- I did.
- That's why I'm telling you this.
- Okay.
- You must have no experience.
- So I will guide you.
- We did "Entertainment Weekly".
We were on it together.
- And you got fired.
- He got fired...
- You got fired.
- three weeks after I got fired.
- Let's go inside.
- Let's go.
It's not on the outside,
so you think it's inside.
Like I said earlier,
the temperature during the day...
is perfect right now.
- It's perfect. It's like summer.
- It's...
the perfect weather.
It's much cooler than Korea's summer.
- That's the weather.
- You have to come to Dubai now.
I am wearing three layers, but it's not too hot.
(They enter Souk Madinat Jumeirah.)
- Is this the traditional market?
- All right.
How can a traditional market be so stylish?
Please show the ceiling.
It's gorgeous.
This is...
- It looks very luxurious.
- This place is...
very luxurious for a traditional market.
Those are so nice.
(It's too beautiful to be a traditional market.)
"Gold to go".
That must be the gold vending machine.
They said there was a gold vending machine here.
- There really...
- It's a gold vending machine.
It must be a gold vending machine.
- "Gold to go".
- "Gold"...
- "The gold ATM".
They have a gold vending machine here.
You swipe your credit card here.
(Instead of drinks, there is gold.)
- This is gold.
- You can get gold from here.
This is a gold vending machine.
"Gold to go".
(They thought Ji Hyo was kidding.)
- This is fascinating.
- "The gold ATM".
Ji Hyo was right.
(What are Ji Hyo and Gary doing at this hour?)
I doubt it's going to be a legitimate desert.
I doubt we have to...
make a fire like in the old movies...
and sit with our backs together.
(Ji Hyo is in deep sleep.)
(Whom was he talking to?)
Ji Hyo. Ji Hyo.
Ji Hyo, there's the sea.
There is the sea.
There is the sea on our left.
Wow, Gary!
- That's amazing.
- We are here.
- Wow...
- This is so nice.
(The golden beach and emerald sea are seen from afar.)
Dubai is amazing.
(Jumeirah Beach is one of the most beautiful beaches in Dubai.)
Let's go look at the beach.
Look at the boat over there.
(Burj Al Arab can be seen from here.)
- Even the boat looks nice.
- It looks very nice.
(Burj Al Arab can be seen from here.)
The water is so clean.
This is crazy.
(Gary is amazed.)
(Wow!)
- Look at the water.
- Look at the colour.
(Photo time)
- That should be the background.
- Okay.
(They take a photo with Burj Al Arab and Jumeirah Beach.)
(Are they on their honeymoon?)
It looks amazing here.
It's the sea!
We came to a beach in Dubai!
Ji Hyo, you slept the whole time.
(The view instantly wakes her up.)
- Ji Hyo.
- Look at this, Gary.
Isn't it beautiful?
The clam shell looks like you.
(The white clam shell is as beautiful as you.)
The beach looks like you.
(You're like the sea.)
(Ji Hyo and Gary's hearts...)
(start to pound slowly.)
Ji Hyo, this is really nice!
- Is it nice?
- Yes!
I will go all the way there.
(They are in Jumeirah Beach and Souk Madinat Jumeirah.)
(JBR Beach)
(Where are Haha and Kwang Soo?)
This is fantastic.
- This is too pretty.
- The weather is...
- It's really pretty.
- unbelievable.
- They scream luxury.
- The buildings are...
(The slim high-rises are exuding their charms.)
Where is the beach?
It's on the right.
This is too beautiful.
(Wow.)
- It's too beautiful.
- The weather is amazing.
(A beach can be seen in front of a concrete jungle.)
This is too beautiful.
- It's...
- It's too beautiful.
JDR.
- This is crazy.
- This is...
- Hey.
(It's an area where many foreigners reside.)
This is freedom!
Kwang Soo, I am so happy. Really, I am so happy.
(They are in awe.)
I'm glad we came here.
This is crazy.
Don't look at them.
- Pretend we're not tourists.
- Act natural.
Hi.
- Hi.
- Good morning.
(They are tourists.)
We totally look like locals.
(They can think whatever they want.)
Hi.
(Kwang Soo greets the locals.)
Kwang Soo, this is really crazy.
(He continues to pretend to be a local.)
(Wow.)
This is a work of art.
(It's as beautiful as art.)
(Kwang Soo walks on the soft sand.
(He looks at a girl in bikini.)
(And he smiles.)
(He wasn't expecting this, but he's loving it.)
(He wanders around them.)
Hi.
(But they don't answer him back.)
(They didn't hear me, right?)
(Yes, that must be it.)
- They recognise me in Dubai.
- Really?
Do you know me?
(She nods.)
- Say my name.
- Haha.
(She recognises Haha.)
How do you know me?
(We can tell that she's a big fan of Haha.)
She likes me a lot.
- Do you know us?
- Yes, I know you.
I can speak a little Korean.
- Are you from Dubai?
- Yes, I am from Dubai.
They watch Running Man in Dubai? Do you watch...
- Yes. It's number one.
- Running Man?
- Is it number one?
- It's number one.
Oh my gosh!
- Where are you from?
- Dubai.
Dubai? Really?
She said our show ranks first place here.
Nice to meet you. Can I shake her hand?
Nice to meet you.
High-five!
- Hurry.
- Do you want a picture?
Thank you.
Oh my gosh...
(They take a photo together.)
Give me five dollars.
(Haha asks her for 5 dollars.)
(He's kidding.)
- Just kidding.
(They gave a Dubai fan a great laugh.)
Okay. See you.
- Bye. Thank you.
- Thank you. Bye.
This place is too nice.
(JBR Beach is the best place to relax.)
What do we do?
The weather and everything...
Hey, there's a flag over there! There's a flag in the middle...
- There is a flag.
- Oh, a flag!
- It came out of nowhere.
- That was unexpected.
I'm so embarrassed.
- How could you put them here?
- Wait.
Tell them to take them out.
- I'm so embarrassed.
- We looked totally like locals.
I am seriously in love with this place.
Gosh, I am so happy.
They must be shooting something. There are cameras.
- Are you shooting something?
- Is something going on?
They're shooting something.
We're just on a trip here.
(Are you really going to ignore us?)
- Please draw the cameras off.
- Please.
Please shoot from a distant.
What would these free people think about us?
Look how relaxed the people here are.
- Right?
- We'd look strange to them.
Someone's even jogging. Hi.
- Hi.
- She looks very healthy.
You can do it.
Look at their bright smiles.
- Right.
- No one seems to be angry here.
- Hi, brother.
- Hi.
(They greet each other so naturally.)
- High-five?
- High-five.
- Bye.
You look like a local here.
(I'm a true Dubaian.)
You're a local!
I am so happy now.
- We have two flags here.
- Yes.
You have two games to choose from.
Just choose one of them.
We'll start with the game with one star.
This game, with one stamp, is called "Gestures".
Describe the given words with your body gestures to foreigners,
and if they get 7 correct answers in 90 seconds, you succeed.
- Seven questions?
- In 90 seconds?
Please find a person to play with...
and bring him or her here. Then we'll start the game.
Please go first.
(This must be difficult.)
Can you play a game with me?
- Do you have time?
- Time?
Let's play a game.
- Okay. What's your name?
- Gosh.
- What's your name? Andy?
- Andy.
- Where are you from?
- I'm from Italy.
Italy. Wow.
You're revealing too much.
Oh, you're from Italy.
("Gestures" with this Italian man starts now.)
Way to go!
Get ready and...
start.
(He's bewildered.)
How should I describe a sloth?
(He moves onto the next question.)
- Penguin.
- Yes, it is penguin.
- Yes!
- Hamster?
It's like a mouse.
What are you doing?
What is that?
This sounds like this.
I like "hams".
- It's a tiger.
- I like "hams".
Tiger? Tiger?
- No!
- It's a lion then, a lion.
- Lion.
- No!
I like "hams".
- It must be puma.
- Puma.
It's a puma. Yes!
- No!
- Yes!
(He was tricked by Haha.)
No.
It's a gorilla.
You just said the answer.
- It's gorilla in English, too.
- Gorilla is English.
I got it. Okay.
- Start.
- Gary looks like this.
(Gary looks just like this.)
(Would he know Gary's nickname?)
Gary and this look similar.
(Gary looks just like this.)
- Kangaroo.
- It's a squid.
- No, that's not it...
It has 12 legs.
- It has 13 legs.
- That is not...
It has 30 legs!
There's no animal like that.
- 30 legs?
- It has a square-shaped head.
- Monster.
- No, it's not a monster.
- It has square-shaped head.
- It's a webfoot octopus.
- Webfoot octopus!
- Webfoot octopus?
No, that's not it!
- The answer isn't webfoot octopus.
- Webfoot octopus.
Webfoot octopus!
Thank you.
Webfoot octopus.
(Mission failed.)
- Thank you.
- Webfoot octopus...
- Wow.
- You're hilarious.
I feel strange to hear a foreigner say "webfoot octopus" in Korean.
How would you describe squid with your body?
Squid?
- You got it.
- What?
- Yes, good.
- Is that different from this?
- That's a webfoot octopus.
- Webfoot octopus?
(Kwang Soo, what you're describing is closer to a webfoot octopus.)
(JBR Beach)
(Souk Madinat Jumeirah)
What is that?
This is amazing.
- What a nice view.
- Wow, what is that?
(What are they looking at?)
This place has a great view.
I like it here.
- Look at that boat.
- Wow, look.
I want to ride that.
This place is fantastic.
(What mission would they have to clear in such a pleasurable place?)
Come look at this.
- What's that?
- There's the R flag.
(They find the R flag near the Abra dock.)
- Okay.
- What is that?
- This is Souk Madinat Jumeirah.
- Okay.
This is a water transportation called "abra ride".
- Do people really ride them?
- Yes.
Why don't you ride it and...
- take a look around.
- Really?
- Can we get on now?
- Okay.
- Hi.
- How are you?
- I'm fine.
- I'm fine, thank you. And you?
- Thank you.
- You speak English very naturally.
We can answer this automatically.
- We must be able to say this.
- I'm fine, thank you. And you?
So do we sit here?
Yes, we sit here.
I like this a lot.
How fast would this go?
(Jae Seok burst into laughter.)
He has never been a reporter in other countries.
He doesn't know what to say when he's shooting outside like this.
You sound awkward.
Have you been reporting in other countries then?
Have you? You've never done it either.
Tell me if you have.
Oh my goodness.
- You're so funny.
- This place is very nice.
Hi!
What a beautiful family!
The family looks beautiful.
- The kids are very cute.
- They are cute.
How could they all have blond hair?
The kids are blond because their mother is blond.
It's because their mother is blond. Haven't you learned about genes?
Seok Jin, this is what reporters do.
- Reporters should mention...
- All right.
- things like this.
- Their parents are blond, so...
- their children are blond, too.
- Gosh.
What's our mission today? Is it riding this abra ride?
Isn't it too easy?
- This place is...
- This place is so beautiful.
Look at this emerald ocean.
(They ride along the emerald ocean.)
- They're having lunch there.
- They're eating.
(People are having lunch near this fantastic emerald ocean.)
It's so fabulous.
This place is...
so great.
These buildings are all hotels.
(They pass under a bridge.)
I never thought Running Man would let us relax like this.
- Right.
- Thank you.
I love travelling freely like this.
- I really enjoy this freedom.
- Right.
The water is so clear.
I can see the bottom. It's very clean.
This is sea water.
- No.
- This is sea water, Seok Jin.
How could this be sea water?
Then drink some.
It must be salty.
Everyone, I'll taste this water...
to see if this is sea water or not.
Let's play the rock-paper-scissors.
- The one who loses...
- I bet you want to find out...
- if this is sea water or not.
- Is this sea water or...
- lake water?
- We'll try this water and see...
if it's sea water or not.
- Rock, paper and scissors.
(Who will taste it?)
I lost.
I lost, so I'll taste it.
We always keep our words.
- Try it.
- You shouldn't doubt me.
- Hurry.
- Okay.
Here I go.
(Seok Jin licks his fingers.)
It is salty!
(It is salty.)
- See?
- It's salty, so it is sea water.
- I told you.
- It is salty.
This water comes from the ocean.
It is really salty.
Is it really sea water?
Of course, it is.
What's our mission today?
I see nothing from here.
I see nothing either.
Come on.
I don't see anything from here. What's our mission today?
We were here before.
That is where we started.
(The ride came back to the dock.)
What's the mission? I saw nothing.
We're already back where we started.
- Thank you.
- Thank you, boss.
I feel like we've already failed our mission.
- I have no clue.
- What is it?
What is our mission today?
- Here comes the question.
- Okay.
(They are given a question.)
While you were riding the ride,
how many bridges did you pass?
(How many bridges did they pass?)
This is ridiculous.
- Isn't that too much?
- Bridges?
- You passed under the bridges.
- Right.
So how many of them did you pass?
(We surely passed through bridges...)
I'll just say any number that comes to my mind.
Jae Seok and I will say the number separately.
Please whisper the number to us.
We should just make a guess.
(We have no choice but to just guess.)
(Seok Jin whispers.)
(Seok Jin's answer is 6.)
(What is Jae Seok's number?)
(Now, Jae Seok whispers.)
Why are you asking me how many there were?
Why are you asking him for an answer??
Why are you asking...
Gosh.
- Hey, give me another chance.
- Please.
Let me say it again.
- Give me another chance.
- Please.
Let's move on to the next flag.
- How many were there?
- This is driving me crazy.
Were there 7? Or 8?
(How many bridges did they pass?)
What's the mission today? Do we just need to ride this?
Isn't it too easy?
Seok Jin, I love this place.
It's so beautiful here.
(The answer is 7.)
(Frustrated)
This is such a ridiculous mission.
How would we possibly know that?
You took us to this beautiful place and...
- True. We never expected this.
- It's ridiculous.
Gosh.
Isn't the question a total nonsense?
(They can't believe it.)
The question was seriously nonsense.
I think you went too far.
(Angry Jae Seok and Seok Jin move on to the next mission.)
Measure your height and weight, and then bring the consent form.
(These three people who chose skydiving...)
(measure their heights and weights to ensure their safety.)
Is this right?
What is this?
(Her weight has been disclosed to everyone.)
Oh my goodness.
Just so you know, I went on the scale...
- with all my clothes on.
- You even had your mic on.
And I even had the mic on me.
(No one said anything about you.)
(She becomes even more nervous after the physical examination.)
(She holds her hands tightly.)
You are not praying, are you?
You look like you're praying.
(Trembling)
I held my hands so tightly that my fingers are numb.
(Sighing)
I can't do this.
I'm leaving. I can't do it.
Don't you think I should give up?
- Why?
- I'm really scared.
I'm scared. I think I'm going to go crazy.
Gosh, that hurt.
(She bumps her bottom.)
Gosh. I'm out of my mind.
(Da Hey is panicking. Will she be able to skydive?)
I'm going insane.
Okay.
(Meanwhile, Jong Kook is putting on his gear.)
Yes. Perfect. And chin up. You will be flying forward.
Are you all right? So, we'll do something like that.
- Does it sound like fun? Ready?
- Yes.
High-five. Let's go skydive.
(Jong Kook, Il Woo and Da Hey are all ready.)
(They take a photo before taking off.)
(Although I look like I'm smiling, I'm not really smiling inside.)
Oh, goodness.
Oh, my.
- But I think you can do it.
- Okay.
But why are my hands trembling?
My hands are trembling. Really.
It would be strange not to tremble.
If you succeed this mission, you will receive 10 stamps.
If you succeed,
you will not receive a penalty.
(If they succeed, they will sleep at the finest desert hotel tonight.)
Please keep in mind that you will go in 10 minutes.
If you step out that door,
we can't take the cameras with us.
- So are we on our own?
- Yes.
(They have to overcome this on their own.)
Are we on our own?
They say it's an altitude of 3,962m.
- What?
(What? 3,926m?)
- No, they told us it's 1,219m.
- They told us it's 1,219m.
No, it's from 3,926m to 4,267m.
- What?
- Well,
- 3000m is not that high.
- That's impossible.
My face is getting hot.
- It needs to be at least 3,962m.
- We must have heard it wrong.
- Did we hear him wrong?
- Was it really 4,267m?
- We must've heard him wrong.
- I think so.
(They will go higher than Mount Baekdu which is 2,744m tall.)
- It's 3,962m.
- 3,962m?
(It's too late to change missions.)
(Wailing)
- What should I do?
- We'll be okay.
(She's lost for words.)
Really. This is going to be difficult.
(Jong Kook and Il Woo are nervous, too.)
If you can give up now we will...
I'm nervous, but I want to do this.
- I'm nervous.
- We'll give you one last chance...
- to change your mind.
- Will there be...
a pressure that is unbearable?
It differs for every person.
(Not everyone will feel the same.)
I think it'll be scary only when you jump.
- If we change our minds...
- The phones are over there.
They say we can change our minds.
This is my last chance.
(It's her last chance to back out.)
(Will she be able to do this?)
(It's an opportunity to avoid sleeping out in the desert.)
(But in order to do so, they need to jump from 3,962m.)
(What decision will she make?)
No.
No. No.
Da Hey keeps talking to herself.
She's talking to herself.
If you make a decision,
- you should go with it.
- You're right.
(I'm a woman of my word.)
No.
(Although he doesn't show it, Jong Kook is very nervous, too.)
This is insane. I'm wordless.
(I should have chosen an easier mission.)
(Here's a person who's free from worldly cares.)
(This is great.)
(Gary and Ji Hyo are still acting like the lovely Monday Couple.)
(They are having fun under the warm sun.)
Good luck!
(If they move enough sand, they will win.)
Go, go!
Okay!
(Oh, no. The basket tipped over.)
(Oh, no, Gary!)
Okay!
(It's not okay...)
Okay.
What is this?
(Team Gary wasted 20 seconds.)
(He misses.)
Hurry up. Hurry up. Faster!
Pour it!
(They have less than 30 seconds. They need to hurry.)
Give me more.
(He misses again.)
Good!
Let's do this!
Pour the sand!
(Please hold on.)
(I didn't come here to do hard labour.)
(Go, Gary.)
(They have about 10 seconds left, but the bucket isn't full yet.)
Quickly! Quickly!
(It's a close game. They need to hurry.)
We're going to make it for sure.
- We did it.
- Finished!
Oh, my goodness!
Good job.
(Gary succeeds!)
I'm sorry!
- Thank you so much!
- You're welcome.
(Gary earns 2 stamps.)
We've come all the way here. I need to do something.
What is this?
I'll begin.
(They need to squeeze water out of this wet towel in order to win.)
Oh, my.
(She is doing the mission with a newlywed bride.)
Here.
You're doing great.
Hurry, hurry!
They're doing great.
(I don't think we'll need a washing machine.)
I don't think I'll be able to do this.
(They squeeze it until the last drop.)
- I'm so tired!
- That's enough.
You won.
You have succeeded.
(Ji Hyo succeeds!)
(Thanks to the newlywed bride)
Thank you.
How could you...
do this to a newlywed?
I think you should just go to sleep tonight.
(She used all her energy.)
- Have a great honeymoon.
- Thank you.
Take care of yourself.
Thank you.
(Stamping)
- Dubai!
(Ji Hyo got 1 and Gary got 2.)
Is this really not possible?
I have no clue.
(Are they thinking about ziplining?)
I can jump.
Oh, my.
- Don't lie.
- Really.
I'll make a call and do it.
- You know you can't.
- Really.
- Look at him.
- I'm serious.
I bet my whole fortune.
Really?
Do you really...
want to get kicked out from your house by your wife?
She would really do that, you know.
I can't jump.
- We'll go and see.
- Is it at a shopping centre?
We don't even have money with us.
Why? We have 27 dollars.
What can we buy with 27 dollars?
What about with 54 dollars?
It's enough to buy something.
Yes, it is.
Seok Jin, you should buy that.
- It's cheap here.
- What?
Buy oil.
(Buy oil.)
Buy 54 dollars worth of oil.
Bring oil back as a gift.
Buy some oil.
Do you think you're making sense?
It makes perfect sense.
- Why doesn't it make sense?
- You should say something to him.
- Why?
- So should I go to...
the supermarket and buy oil as a gift?
- Is that what you're saying?
- Yes.
Are you talking about those gift sets with bottled oil?
- Should I buy Dubaian oil?
- Yes, you should.
It's over there.
(While they were quarrelling, they have arrived.)
Okay, thank you.
(The zipline is hung across the sky.)
We should get going. Wait a minute.
(He hesitates.)
It's doable.
(Are you sure this is doable?)
Which way do we need to go?
It's this way.
You're right.
Which floor is it?
It's the 28th floor.
Hello.
Who's going to jump? Both of you?
- Yes.
- Both of you guys?
Signing the consent form makes me nervous.
(Seok Jin is becoming nervous.)
Seok Jin.
If you're scared, just go back down.
What are you talking about?
You should go back down if you're scared.
My goodness.
(They finally reach the starting point of the zipline.)
Oh, my.
I don't think I can do it.
Wow, this is really something.
- I'll just go and see.
- Okay.
I'll just take a look.
Oh, my gosh!
(Astonished)
(This is the Dubai zipline.)
(They need to jump from 90m high...)
(and descend on a 600m long rope.)
Let's think about this.
- This is driving me crazy.
- It's...
scarier than I had expected.
This is no joke.
Look at that.
Oh, my.
(How am I supposed to do this?)
Gary, let's go buy some snacks.
This place is very unique.
(They visit the traditional market, Souk Madinat Jumeirah.)
This place is very fancy.
Gary, there's ice cream.
There's ice cream.
- Should we get one?
- Let's have some ice cream.
(They first spend money on ice cream.)
Excuse me,
I would like some ice cream on a cone.
I want one on a cone.
I want one in a cup.
The ice cream is on me...
- since you did so much.
- No, I'll pay.
No, I'll buy it.
- Thank you.
This tastes good!
Maybe it's tasty because we were at the beach.
Gary, what is that?
They're cutting it up as if it were yeot.
"Yeot"?
(It sounds like something else.)
Gary, look at that.
(Is this Middle Eastern yeot?)
(What is this?)
Good morning.
What... What... What is this?
It's Turkish delight.
Is it something like candy?
(Turkish Delight is Middle Eastern taffy made with nuts and sugar.)
It's like jelly.
(It's like jelly.)
Can my girlfriend have a taste?
(Can my girlfriend have a taste?)
(Here you go.)
Thank you.
I said you're my girlfriend so that he'd let you taste it.
All right.
(Chomping)
It tastes good, right?
- Wait.
- It's like jelly with nuts in it.
I think I tried this before.
- Can I get a half sized one?
- All right.
(Gary decides to buy some.)
Is it 23 dollars?
(It costs around 23 dollars.)
It's too expensive.
- Okay.
- Do we have enough money?
(Gary spent 23 dollars from their pocket money for the taffy.)
Thank you.
- Have a good day.
- Thank you.
- Gary, let me manage our money.
- Yes?
- Let me manage it.
- Am I spending too much?
You're too easily persuaded.
A fortune-teller said the similar thing.
(A fortune-teller said the similar thing.)
He said that I should let woman manage my money.
Give it to me.
(Gary needs someone to take care of him.)
Wait. What's that?
(What's that?)
- Hello.
- Hi.
- How are you?
- Fine, thank you.
- Good.
If you make a payment, I make this in five minutes.
It's made of sand. It's amazing.
Let me show you.
(Sand art made with different colours of sand)
It's amazing.
Wow!
(They're impressed)
Good!
(But...)
(it's where they have to complete a mission.)
You get one stamp if you finish the puzzle before he finishes his work.
(You get one stamp if you finish the puzzle before he finishes his work.)
Now? Do we start now?
This is easy.
- Let's do it. Do we go one by one?
- Yes.
(A match with a sand master)
Start.
Wait. Is this the puzzle?
Oh, this is how you do it.
(Oh, this is how you do it.)
- Ji Hyo, I can't do this.
- Oh, it's the one.
I can't do this.
(I can't do this.)
(He wasn't expecting to use his brain.)
Ji Hyo, I can't do this.
- I'm doomed.
- You can do it. Try.
You can do it.
Like this. This one goes here.
(You can do it, Gary!)
Well...
(I need to do something.)
Sir, I don't like that.
(She's trying to help Gary.)
I want this colour.
(I want this colour.)
(Ji Hyo is distracting him to buy Gary more time.)
- Hurry up.
- Ji Hyo... I...
(I don't think I can do this.)
Ji Hyo, I can't do this.
I can't.
Hurry up.
(While Gary is struggling, the sand art is almost done.)
Ji Hyo.
Do it slowly, please.
(Please take your time.)
(Pushing)
(What?)
Oh, it's done.
(Stunned)
Is it done?
(Gary succeeds.)
Ji Hyo, I did it.
I finished it without realising it.
Ji Hyo, I did it! Yes!
(With Ji Hyo's help, Gary cleared the mission.)
- It looks so nice.
- Thank you, Ji Hyo.
(This is why every man needs a wise woman.)
Thank you so much.
(Proud)
I might have to sleep...
outside in the desert like this tonight.
(He might have to sleep outside in the desert like this tonight.)
I might be sleeping in this desert tonight.
It's going to be like camping.
Oh my goodness.
(They have 3 hours until the end.)
- So...
- What will you do?
- Go down if you're scared.
What are you talking about?
(Sighing)
How fast is it?
It's 70km per hour.
Did you hear that?
It takes about 40 seconds to arrive there.
- Did you say 40 seconds?
- Yes, 40 seconds.
- Gosh, 40 seconds.
- Is it 70 or 17?
- It's 70km per hour.
- I see.
- He says it's 70km per hour.
- It's 600m long.
(The course is 600m long.)
We just need to hold out for 40 seconds.
Was there any accident?
Any accident?
Not today.
What?
(Does it mean that there were accidents in the past?)
(I can't even laugh at a joke.)
- Was that a joke?
- Yes.
- Are you going to do it?
- I am.
Let's sign the consent form first.
- Let's do it.
- Let's sign first.
Do you think I can't do this?
- Fine, I'll sign the paper.
- Do it.
You don't know me.
I can even skydive.
Who are you trying to fool?
- Do I sign here?
- Do it.
Sit down.
(It's like they're having an autograph event there.)
- Gosh.
- Here.
- Oh my goodness.
- Wait.
Do you have another pen with a different colour?
- Is it red?
- It's red coloured.
(He's scared of writing his name in red.)
- You must be scared.
- It's unlucky to write it in red.
I don't want to be unlucky by writing my name in red.
No, never.
Thank you.
(Signing with a black pen)
You seem determined.
Okay.
(Seok Jin signs on the consent form, too.)
All right.
(He's certainly not determined.)
Okay.
- Put your left foot in here.
- Okay.
(They put on the equipment as soon as they signed the paper.)
Oh my goodness.
(They're thrilled to death.)
We're in trouble.
- Wait.
- Wait!
I'm not going to do this.
(He's not going to do this.)
(It's too late to give up.)
What should I do?
(Nervous)
- This will be tightened up there.
- Okay.
Will it be safe?
(Will it be safe?)
Okay.
Seok Jin, I'm going for it now.
(Seok Jin, I'm going for it now.)
Jae Seok is really doing it.
Gosh! I can't do this.
(Wow)
Is it not dangerous?
(Jae Seok is going first for the X-line zipline.)
Are you sure about it?
- Seriously?
- Wait, do I have to film it?
- You should film yourself.
- How can I?
(The cameraman gives him the camera.)
My heart is pounding.
Jae Seok.
I'm going crazy.
(You should hold the camera like this.)
- It's too high.
- What do I film?
(Jae Seok and Seok Jin are going out of control.)
What about me?
It's too high.
(What am I doing here?)
Jae Seok.
(Welcome to the X-line zipline.)
This is not for everybody, you know?
(Taking off his glasses)
He is really going to do it.
(Let's do it.)
I even have to hold a camera myself.
Seok Jin.
I'm scared to death.
(He's scared to death.)
Jae Seok, let's not do this.
Come closer.
(Jae Seok is finally ready.)
Once it's hooked, there's no turning back.
(Hooked)
All right. Slowly sit down now.
- Okay.
- He's out of his mind.
Is he really going to be all right?
(Jae Seok looks different today.)
- Lean back.
- Okay.
- That camera is...
- Seok Jin.
Are you going to do this?
(Do I look nervous?)
You're about to take off.
What should I do? My son must watch it.
(His heart is pounding crazy.)
(The producer goes closer to him.)
- What?
- You have to memorise...
the following words after arrival.
- How will I remember them?
- Memorise what?
Do we have a mission on top of that?
What is this?
(While in his most nervous moment, he receives a mission.)
(Given words are Spice Souk, Gold Souk and Textile Souk.)
Spice Souk, Gold Souk and Textile Souk.
Look at his shaking legs.
Look at his legs.
(Shaking)
He's shaking.
(Deep breathing)
- This must be a dream.
- All right.
Okay.
It's so terrifying.
(He's about to start.)
Oh, my.
My goodness.
(My goodness)
Okay.
- Do you want to go?
- Yes.
- Are you ready?
- I'm ready.
Going in five seconds.
(Going in five seconds)
(You'd better be prepared for the height and wide distance.)
(Nervous)
Going in five seconds.
In five,
four,
three,
- two...
- Gosh!
In 5, 4, 3, 2 and 1.
(Go!)
Help me! Mum!
- In 2 and 1, go!
- Gosh!
Help me! Mum!
- In 2 and 1, go!
- Gosh!
Help me! Mum!
I'm sorry.
(Jae Seok is flying in the sky!)
I won't do it again. I'm sorry.
(Is he seeing his life flash before his eyes?)
(He's looking back on his life.)
I'm sorry.
I won't do it again.
(Screaming)
(Let me go back.)
(He suddenly looks so different.)
I'm thirsty.
(Welcome back, Jae Seok!)
(He successfully finished riding the 40-second X-line zipline.)
(He was terrified.)
(He wants to go down.)
(He wants to go home.)
(He's ragged.)
(Oh my gosh)
It was terrifying.
(He won on the fight against himself.)
(However, the joy didn't last long.)
Please give us the answer to the question you received.
It's Spice Souk, Gold Souk and Textile Souk.
Correct.
(He succeeds the mission.)
(He might be able to avoid sleeping in the desert.)
(Now, it's time for Seok Jin to ride the zipline.)
(He's terrified.)
Gosh.
I'm going mad here.
I can't trust the rope.
(I can trust our staff but not that imported rope.)
Gosh, why did I have to be born like this?
Oh my gosh.
I am too terrified.
I'm serious.
(Seok Jin gives up.)
(Kwang Soo joins the zipline mission.)
Oh, gosh. Wait.
(He came after finishing the mission at JBR Beach.)
(He's stiff.)
All right.
- Oh, okay.
- Sit down.
Oh, gosh.
(His voice goes up.)
He's about to ride it.
(He's scared.)
Come on.
- There goes Kwang Soo.
- Hold on.
I'm going to fall.
Gosh.
(The producer gives him the mission.)
(Why does it have to be at this moment?)
Jumeirah Beach. Jumeirah Mosque.
- Palm Jumeirah.
- Shut up!
Get lost!
(Kwang Soo is upset.)
- Are you ready?
- Go!
(He's taking off in five seconds.)
- You will leave in five seconds.
- Gosh.
- Seriously!
- He's gone pale.
- No!
- Go!
(He's like an unidentified flying object.)
(He's thrilled!)
His hat dropped.
(He's more shocked that he lost his hat.)
(He breaks into tears.)
(He doesn't want to let his hat go.)
Someone is coming.
Isn't it Kwang Soo?
(It's Kwang Soo.)
(He returned from the terrifying zipline ride.)
Kwang Soo.
(He's gone.)
You look 10 years older now.
(Why does he look more aged?)
- I lost my hat.
- Your hat?
Kwang Soo, please tell us the answer.
(He has to memorise the given words.)
Jumeirah...
(It's Jumeirah Beach, Jumeirah Mosque,)
(Palm Jumeirah and Madinat Jumeirah Souk.)
- You get five seconds.
- Was it Jumeirah Saurus?
(He gives a wrong answer.)
Bing pong?
How come your face is so pale?
Incorrect.
(He fails the mission.)
- Well...
- You failed the mission.
No way!
There must be a mission.
Maybe we have to guess how many bridges we passed.
(They continues clearing the missions as they travelled.)
Good job, Ji Hyo!
This is too difficult.
- Hurry up!
- You are close to getting it!
- Okay!
- Good job!
(They only have 30 minutes left.)
(Ji Hyo and Gary are on the lead so far.)
(Finally, they are ready to take off for the sky diving.)
See you!
We'll get going!
- We will come back alive.
- We will be back alive.
(We will be back alive.)
(They have 30 minutes left until the end of their given time.)
You jump first.
No, I will jump last.
Please jump first.
You want me to jump first? It's really okay with me.
- It's better to go first.
- Let's go.
You'll get more scared watching others go.
(They start boarding on the one-way plane to the sky.)
(She's terrified.)
(He is totally ready to dominate the sky.)
(Jong Kook's excited.)
(They ride on a plane for the sky diving.)
(How far have you been to experience Dubai?)
(The aeroplane takes off.)
(They go up with trained instructors.)
(They are very excited.)
(She's nervous.)
I'm so nervous.
Goodness!
- I now feel it's real.
- You do?
Oh my gosh.
- Are you okay?
- Yes, I'm okay.
- Take care of my friend, okay?
- Okay.
- You can do it.
- Thank you.
Anything else you want to say to the camera?
Please, save me.
Everyone,
I am...
(She's extremely nervous.)
I am going to skydive in four minutes.
Cheers!
(You can do it!)
(She screams.)
All right, guys. Let's skydive! Let's go!
(It's time to skydive!)
(He's going to check if they've arrived at the right place.)
(Green light)
(The instructor thinks it's a perfect height to jump.)
(He skydives.)
Someone just made a jump!
(The instructor skydives first for the best picture spot.)
He opened the parachute.
(Jong Kook is terrified.)
(His instructor looks very relaxed.)
(Why did I volunteer to do this?)
(We get to see the nice view thanks to them.)
(Finally, they reached the altitude of 3962.4m.)
(It's time to go.)
(He's nervous.)
(Will Jong Kook be able to make a jump?)
(Skydiving)
(Jong Kook...)
(successfully manages to dive in the sky.)
(Jumping)
(Successful skydive in Dubai)
(Variety shows are tough these days.)
(It's thrilling!)
(He looks more like a muscular flying squirrel today.)
(His parachute is released for the safety.)
(It's the view taken from Jong Kook's camera.)
(Next is Il Woo.)
(Will he make a jump at once like a man?)
(Of course!)
(He looks so relaxed.)
(Let's fly!)
(He gives off his charms, flying at an altitude of 3962.4m.)
(He also gives off his funny face.)
(He grabs the cameraman.)
(An actor never wants to lose his cameramen.)
(It's time to release his parachute.)
(Now, it's her turn to skydive.)
(Will she be able to make a jump?)
(Or will she give up here?)
(Her heart is pounding.)
(She jumps off.)
(Da Hey did it!)
(She jumped bravely without hesitation.)
(There are a lot of actresses,)
(but none like her.)
(She feels the infinite freedom after she overcomes her fear.)
(Da Hey is excited.)
(She's so relaxed that she even tries to make cute expressions.)
(Her parachute is released.)
(Brava!)
(Jong Kook who jumped first is now visible from the land.)
(It's the view taken from Jong Kook's camera.)
(Nice landing)
Welcome back, brother.
(Welcome back, brother.)
How was it?
So awesome!
- I can't say anything, man.
- Was it fun?
(He's totally satisfied.)
Tell me anything about it.
I am so happy.
- Are you happy?
- Yes.
That's Il Woo.
(The second skydiver Il Woo is about to land.)
Welcome back to the ground!
(He's back from the sky.)
Good job!
Did you have fun?
Now, you can take your goggles out.
(He's still excited.)
Where is the best place to have a skydiving?
- Good job.
- Did you have fun?
Now, you can take your goggles out.
(Da Hey nailed it. She's coming down, too.)
(It's the view taken from Da Hey's camera.)
Oh my goodness.
(An angel is descending from the sky.)
(She's screaming.)
(Perfect landing)
Give me a high five.
(They're celebrating their success, too.)
You were scared but you stay alive.
- Here you are at the ground.
- Yes, I'm alive.
Yes, I'm alive. I'm still alive.
- Beautiful! It was great.
- How was the view?
It was amazing. I loved it.
I must give it a shot again.
(I must give it a shot again.)
The world I've seen above was...
like a utopia. It was wonderful.
Mission complete!
(Mission complete!)
Mission completed!
(All of the three cleared their mission.)
This feeling is indescribable.
It was so crazy.
(He won't forget about this feeling.)
Wow, this is amazing.
- This is incredible.
- Really.
- We must do it in Dubai.
- This is crazy.
You must try this at least once...
- in your life.
- In your life.
- I am alive.
- It was amazing.
This is...
(These brave three cleared the hardest mission perfectly.)
It can't be compared to bungee jumping.
- I feel like...
- I should've tried it earlier.
- It's a must in your life.
- Right, this is a must in life.
- It wasn't that scary.
- Everyone should try this.
- These are for you.
- Right.
- Thank you.
(They get to sleep at an exclusive hotel in Dubai.)
Thank you.
I feel like I won an award.
(The individual travelling is over.)
We all nailed it.
- Da Hey, you're very brave.
- Right.
(The game has just begun. What will be waiting for them?)
(How many stamps did they get?)
(All members gathered to go to the desert.)
I need some rest now.
(Let's head to the desert.)
(Will they get a chance to make a reverse?)
I wonder what we will do next.
This is not my style, but...
(Jae Seok spruces himself up with the sunglasses to go to the desert.)
(After individual travelling, They are getting out of the downtown.)
(I might have to sleep outside if I can't turn over the result.)
(The automobiles are heading toward the desert in suburban area.)
(The members become drowsy on their way to the desert.)
(Kwang Soo is yawning very long.)
(Now there's nothing but desert.)
(Desert is vast, and the members are falling in sleep.)
(You'd better take a nap when you can.)
(They arrived at the intermediate station in the desert's entrance.)
(Half asleep and half awake)
(Why does he stop the car here?)
(What are they doing?)
(The drivers are deflating the tires all of a sudden.)
(Why are they deflating the tires?)
(You'll see why soon.)
Fasten your seat belt.
(We're moving into the middle of the desert now.)
- Is everybody ready?
- Yes, I'm ready.
(They're ready.)
Let's go.
(Da Hey is pretty excited.)
(The main game has just begun. Let's go to the desert!)
- Is air conditioning okay?
- Yes.
(Sure)
- Are you ready?
- Yes.
Let's go!
(He's grinning.)
(What will be waiting for us in the desert?)
This is the real desert. This is real.
There's really nothing out there but sand.
(Welcome to the desert. You've never been desert before, right?)
(There are only the four vehicles and sand winds in the desert.)
I see nothing out there.
You'll never find a way out if you get lost here.
Right.
That's true.
- This desert is endless.
- And nobody's here.
We won't be able to find a way out if we get lost.
(There's neither ways nor directions in this huge sand field.)
And we sleep here tonight?
(Kwang Soo is nervous.)
- This is the real desert.
- This is what we call desert.
- Gosh.
- We're right in the middle.
I've never been to place like this before.
- Look at that.
- Okay.
Wow!
I've never seen such animal before.
- My goodness.
- It's amazing.
(Antelope is similar to deer and inhabits in Africa and the Mideast.)
They look great.
They look fabulous.
- They are like impalas.
- That's what I thought.
They will run away if we chase after them.
(They might run away if we chase after them.)
(It's bumpy.)
(It's getting bumpier as they go toward the centre of the desert.)
- It's not dangerous. Relax.
- Wait.
(Are we riding a roller coaster?)
Goodness.
- It's about to overturn.
- Gosh.
- My goodness.
- Oh, dear.
It's almost overturned.
Is he heading to the cliff?
- Are you serious?
- Gosh!
(Drivers deflate tires to lessen impact in rough and bumpy deserts.)
(They automatically hold on to the handle.)
- Gosh, look at that.
- Stop!
(I just got back from the zipline.)
This is insane.
(We just came back from skydiving.)
(He doesn't even have a handle.)
I don't even have a handle.
Someone broke it.
- Do you have one?
- No, we don't.
It's broken.
Oh, gosh!
The car will flip.
Look out!
(Kwang Soo is freaking out.)
Wait, not that way.
It's dangerous.
It's really dangerous.
Gosh.
(What a scaredy-cat!)
It became almost a right angle.
- So this is Dubai.
- Now, I feel like I'm in Dubai.
(Gosh!)
(How far are we going?)
(He misses his mum.)
We'll have an accident.
Look at this.
(Screaming the whole way)
- Oh, no.
- Kwang Soo.
(Driving through the golden sands)
(They finally arrive at their destination.)
(Wow!)
- Wow.
- This is amazing.
(They're amazed by the golden sunset and endless desert.)
Don't tell me we are sleeping here.
Seok Jin, why don't you start putting up a tent?
(Seok Jin got only three stamps.)
You should get more time to sleep.
You're no better than me.
- I have six.
- There's no big difference.
Kwang Soo also got only three stamps.
You two should start putting up tents.
No, it's too early to give up.
You will be playing three rounds of this game.
The winner will get three stamps.
- I should win.
- Wow.
You can win up to nine stamps.
- So there's still a chance.
- All right.
Those who skydived are sleeping at the hotel, right?
You can just sit back and relax.
They will be sitting back and enjoying the game.
The rule is simple. We'll get ready.
(Who will be able to reverse the situation?)
(The last game for the stamps is "Shoes Race")
You will first run toward the boxes over there.
You'll choose one among them and open it.
And then?
In the boxes are various kinds of shoes which you'll have to wear.
Whoever takes the flag first with the shoes on will be the winner.
(If you win all 3 rounds, you'll get 9 stamps.)
It feels so nice to walk on the sands.
Then why don't you sleep in the sands tonight?
- Are you kidding me?
- That's a good idea.
- Are you ready?
- Yes.
Which shoes you choose matters the most.
You're right. It's random.
You have to be wearing the shoes when you pull out the flag.
Leave me alone.
- This is so annoying.
- What's wrong?
- I'll just sleep here.
- Where are you going?
- This is annoying.
- Fine.
- They're trying so hard to stop me.
- Just do it.
- Let's just do it.
- Let's start.
- Don't do it from the beginning.
- Ready.
- Don't take away others.
Ready.
(Oops)
They're so desperate.
- Gosh.
- Didn't you say you give up?
- I should at least try it.
- He's desperate.
- Seok Jin, step back.
- Okay.
Ready, go.
(Start)
(Racing)
Gary is fast.
(Gary opens a box first.)
(It's slippers)
What are these?
(Toe socks)
How do I put them on?
(Ji Hyo got flippers.)
(Kwang Soo got straw shoes.)
(Toe socks, slippers, straw shoes, high heels, sandals and flippers)
What are these?
How do I put them on?
(Struggling)
Wait.
What are these?
(Jae Seok seemed not interested, but he's the fastest to wear heels.)
(Run!)
(Jae Seok rushes forward.)
(Jae Seok is on the lead.)
(Pulling out the flag)
No!
(Jae Seok wins the round and gets three stamps.)
- I had to wear flippers.
- I chose a good one.
- What is Jae Seok wearing?
- Nice!
- Look at you.
- That's amazing.
You should've prepared bigger ones.
- It's too small for me.
- Look at him!
- You ran so hard.
- Let's go for another round.
I just need to win one more time.
- Why do you run so hard?
- You said you'd give up.
No, I never said that.
- Look at Jae Seok.
- I could've won.
Come here, Kwang Soo. We're sleeping out in the desert.
(Seok Jin and Kwang Soo are sleeping out in the desert tonight.)
- Let's just do it.
- It's pure luck.
It's okay to sleep here.
- It's no big deal.
- Have you ever slept in a desert?
When will we sleep in a desert again?
Ready.
Hurry!
Look how focused Jae Seok is.
Jae Seok is really into this game.
Ready.
(I'll win again...)
(and sleep at the hotel tonight.)
(I want to sleep at the hotel, too.)
(I have to win two rounds to sleep at the hotel.)
(Racing)
- They're fast.
- Gary is fast.
He's fast.
(It's time to choose a box.)
What is this?
(Gary chose slippers again.)
(Ji Hyo chose high heels.)
- Gary is fast.
- What is this?
(Haha chose sandals.)
(Jae Seok chose toe socks.)
He's fast.
(Jae Seok falls behind.)
- What is this?
- He got socks.
(Haha's shoes came off.)
Wait.
(Now, it's a competition between Monday Couple.)
(I don't mind sleeping in a desert.)
(Are you sure you want to compete with me?)
(They are against each other.)
Ji Hyo.
(What?)
(Flying)
(He flew to the flag.)
(What did I just see?)
Ji Hyo.
(Gary wins the round.)
(She's upset.)
He's mean.
- That was so mean.
- That's not gentle.
(He's such a jerk.)
(He used to be so nice to her.)
(Is he really the same person?)
- It's pretty, isn't it?
- It's as pretty as you.
(Sorry, I'm allergic to sand.)
- That was so mean.
- That's not gentle.
(He's so happy to win the round.)
- Are you happy?
- Shame on you.
- He swung himself.
- Monday Couple is about to break.
I was too focused on the game.
Why did it have to be Ji Hyo?
(Forget it.)
(I have sand in my mouth.)
Seriously.
(How could you do that to me?)
(Punishing)
How could you slide like that?
You threw yourself to get the flag.
I...
I couldn't help it.
(They only got annoyed and upset by playing the race.)
Gary goes to the hotel.
I'm embarrassed.
(Gary gets to sleep at the hotel.)
We'll never forget your sliding.
He completely threw himself.
In addition to that,
when he threw himself,
I got all the sand in my face.
(He's sorry.)
Jong Kook gets to sleep at the hotel.
- Thank you.
- Da Hey, too.
Il Woo gets to sleep at the hotel.
- I'm so happy.
- Ji Hyo, too.
- It's no big deal.
- Do you have any objection?
- No.
- The result is so obvious.
It turned out exactly how we predicted.
- What did I tell you?
- Our prediction...
turned out to be exactly correct.
It's the same members in Taiwan special.
It's the exactly same members.
You're right.
We went on a rollercoaster ride together.
Okay, those who sleep at the hotel...
will now head to the hotel.
- Now?
- Already?
- Really?
- It's unbelievable.
All right.
- To the hotel?
- Are we leaving them behind?
Yes. Leave them behind.
- Gosh.
- Okay.
Won't you get sick tomorrow?
- We will.
- We sure will.
We might even get into a fight.
The four of us.
Four of us might end up being three.
Exactly.
Wait and see what happens.
- I feel bad.
- It's okay. You can go.
Don't worry. You can go.
(They should head to the hotel now.)
(It's time to say goodbye.)
I feel so bad.
- Is Il Woo staying?
- Go.
I know how you feel, but you should go.
(They're going back to the civilised world.)
- Good night.
- See you.
Bring some breakfast for us.
You should bring us some food.
- See you.
- Have some chocolate.
(The survival starts.)
- Give it to me!
- Let go!
Go away.
- I haven't eaten all day!
- Give me some, too!
(They have...)
(completely adapted...)
(to the wild.)
(Let's go back to the civilised world.)
See you.
(The chocolate is mine.)
- Get him!
No!
- See you.
- Bye!
(Jae Seok, Seok Jin, Kwang Soo and Haha will sleep out at the desert.)
I even brought my swimming pants. I thought I'd stay at a hotel.
Wait.
Make sure...
you don't stray far.
You might die.
- What?
- What are you saying?
- Why do you say something so scary?
- Seriously.
Listen to me.
- What are you talking about?
- Wait.
Have you ever been in a situation like this?
- You might die.
- There might be animals.
Will there be snakes?
- What about desert foxes?
- Not snakes.
What is it called? The ones with the unique tail.
That's a kind of snakes.
But that kind is only found in North America.
- You're an expert.
- He knows a lot!
- I told you.
- He's like someone from...
the "Discovery Channel".
I'm an expert at survival tactics.
You should know that in extreme situations,
not all four of us can survive.
- We need to abandon one.
- We should kill one.
(The survival expert is bringing up the biggest risk factor.)
- I'm not kidding.
- What have we done so wrong today?
Let's abandon him.
- He doesn't do anything anyway.
- He must be useful in some ways.
It was just an example.
I was saying it so we're determined to stick together until the end.
- All together.
- Let's not give up.
- All right.
- Let's not betray each other, okay?
- In 1, 2 and 3. Let's go.
- Let's go!
(Good luck with sleeping outside!)
(Will they really not betray each other?)
(After driving quite a distance,)
(they arrived at the hotel in the middle of the desert.)
- That's really a good thing.
- You see?
I thought about it on the way here.
Although I didn't win a lot,
I always manage to avoid the worst.
- Is this it?
- Thank you.
Thank you.
This must be the hotel.
(In the middle of the desert)
- Oh my goodness.
- Really?
(The finest hotel is located right next to the desert.)
If you just open the door, you can see the desert.
(If you just open the door, you can see desert.)
- It's right next to the bedroom.
- Gosh!
This is too luxurious.
This is a feast we've prepared for you.
- Please enjoy it comfortably.
- Wow.
A feast for us?
- Is this a buffet?
- Come and take...
a glass of water for each of you.
We'll enjoy the food as we settle down.
Is it really a buffet?
- Look at this.
- It looks so pretty.
What is this? It's like steamed eggs.
I want to take some to them.
Yes, I want to take some to my mother.
(He's a good son.)
(It all looks tasty.)
It looks enough to serve eight couples.
- I think I was too greedy.
- How is it?
- It tastes good.
- This is tasty.
- I didn't expect it to be.
- It's so delicious.
So out there is the desert?
- That's right.
- I see.
I should check that out after dinner.
This place is very romantic.
It's a great place for couples.
I feel like I'm an outsider between two couples.
(What is he saying?)
Don't say that.
(They enjoyed their wonderful dinner at the hotel.)
Let's take a picture to remember this night.
Okay.
- This camera turns 360-degrees.
- Okay.
- All the staff will be in it.
In 1, 2 and 3.
(Click)
- That was short.
- Yes.
- It still captured everything.
- Really?
(Spinning around)
Look here.
(They can't take their eyes of the photo.)
- I think I'll have some more.
- You can even zoom in.
You can see me.
It's really all in that photo.
You can also do this to see just the sky.
(Tonight,)
(the songs of the shooting stars...)
(awaken the myth kept in the desert.)
(They have to follow the only light to raise...)
(Golden Grasshopper which has been asleep...)
(across 1,000 years.)
The legend of Golden Grasshopper.
(Only then, they can escape from the place.)
(Time leads straight to their lives.)
My life depends on it.
(Within the given period of time that sandglass allows,)
(they have to find nine keys...)
(and become the master of Gold Grasshopper.)
(The new story in Dubai)
(Next week, "Sand of Life")