(2016 Lunar New Year Special)
(The Fifth Official Skill Assessment)
(Running Man Skill Research Institute)
(The data collected from 289 episodes is analysed here.)
(Research overview: To hold the Fifth Official Skill Assessment)
(And to compare, analyse and assess individual's skill.)
(For the first test, send the following message to the members.)
(Beginning now, until you enter the waiting room, you are vulnerable.)
(Beware of ambush and protect your name tag.)
(What is this?)
Who?
I don't know.
Who is after it?
(Who's after my name tag?)
Someone's after my name tag?
Is it you?
You're after my name tag, right?
It's you, isn't it?
Is it attached properly?
Don't worry, I have it on me.
(Someone is after your name tag.)
If it's until I enter the waiting room,
then has it begun already?
(The game starts now.)
(He looks behind.)
(He is suddenly frightened.)
(Who? Who's after my name tag?)
(Why? Now? Just me?)
Where's the waiting room?
Someone's going to ambush me?
Oh, my.
Really?
(Really?)
Wait. What about my hair?
I need to put some makeup on first.
Wait.
Am I targeted constantly?
(Am I targeted constantly?)
Then can I knock the person out?
Is that all right?
I've been doing this for years.
Ripping my name tag off won't be so easy.
Today is going to be...
(He begins to workout all of a sudden.)
This will be fun.
Until I reach the waiting room? Where is the waiting room?
(All members have received the mission.)
(Test No. 1: Agility Test, The observation begins.)
(Kwang Soo is quick to betray.)
What's going on?
It's my first time coming here for makeup.
Someone's after me even in this moment?
(Kwang Soo is very anxious from the beginning.)
It's my first time ever coming here. Who would know I'm here?
Who?
(Who?)
Is it you?
(Is it you?)
I won't put up with it today.
(I won't put up with it today.)
You're on my radar too.
(The cameraman is also on his list.)
(Or maybe there's a guest waiting upstairs.)
Starting now?
Hello. Nice to meet you.
Hello.
- Please take a seat. - Hello.
(It is his first time at this hair salon.)
- Isn't it cold outside? - Yes.
(Most of the people here are complete strangers.)
(Thank goodness.)
(After I get my hair done fast...)
(and enter the waiting room...)
It's nice to meet you.
(What?)
Hold on!
(He was caught off guard.)
No, wait.
(Now this is what we call a test of agility.)
(The agent can go after the name tag for 10 seconds.)
Who are you?
(Who are you?)
(The 10 seconds is up.)
I fended him off.
I blocked him.
(Kwang Soo is surprisingly agile.)
Excuse me. Who are you?
(Who are you?)
Do you work here?
(Yes)
- Do you really work here? - Yes.
(You're really good.)
I've been at this for six years.
I'm sorry.
Oh, my.
He's a complete stranger.
What's going on?
(Please sit here.)
I'm sorry, but could you please stand over there?
I'm very on edge today.
(He sinks down to protect his name tag.)
Yes.
What?
(What is happening?)
What is this?
I think I was quite cool just now.
(Surprisingly agile. Potential is unknown but is simple-minded.)
(Seok Jin is full of confidence.)
I can't trust anyone.
(I can't trust anyone.)
Who are you?
Please go first.
Are you going down or up?
You're going up? Then it's fine.
(He needlessly yells at his neighbours.)
This is...
(He is startled.)
(Seok Jin is easily scared.)
(Gary has keen senses.)
Is there another person in this?
(Running)
You startled me.
(He was very startled.)
(Haha is great with tricks.)
Excuse me.
You're not a spy, are you?
(You're not a spy, are you?)
What are you filming?
I have a weird feeling about this.
(If these people are actors, it's not safe here.)
Are you really a couple?
Are you?
Aren't you strangers?
No.
Really? I am a bit on edge today.
If you're a real couple, could you hold hands?
Can you kiss her hand?
(He pecks her hand.)
- You're a great actor. - No, that's not true.
Aren't we a fine couple?
You are a great couple, but...
(Something's strange.)
There's something fishy going on.
Are you really the chef here?
- Are you? - Yes.
- Are you really sure? - Yes.
(He doubts everything.)
Excuse me,
how long have you worked here?
- I started just today. - You started today. I knew it.
It's strange, right?
You don't usually wear glasses, do you?
Are you filming me with your glasses?
(Haha doubts everyone.)
I got goosebumps all over.
I'm serious.
I'm scared.
The gym isn't usually this crowded in the morning.
There are so many people today.
(Who is brave enough to go after Jong Kook's name tag?)
(He is startled.)
Who is this person?
There's something fishy about him.
(There's something fishy about him.)
Why are there...
so many...
suspicious people in the gym today?
This is strange.
(His radar is on.)
(Someone suddenly appears.)
Goodness.
What are you doing?
Why are you doing this?
What is wrong with these people?
Are you out of your minds?
(His personal trainer, stylist and manager)
What is this?
- What do you think you're doing? - Why?
What are you doing?
Are you out of your minds?
They must be...
out of their minds.
What are you doing?
Are you after me, too?
(Are you after me, too?)
I'm in trouble.
The gym isn't safe.
(Jong Kook is strong and quick-witted.)
(Ji Hyo is lucky and is the ace of the team.)
This is really...
Why do you make me...
doubt everyone so early in the morning?
Why?
I can't let anyone pass me by without suspecting them.
Good morning.
Please, go over there.
You don't need to say hello. Just go over there.
There's no need to say hello. Just go over there.
Hurry. Okay.
I'll find my seat on my own. Just go away.
(The hair salon feels more like a minefield today.)
What is that?
(She's surprised.)
(Flinching)
(She sits down on the chair.)
Hello. Hello.
You are getting your hair done early in the morning.
Okay. I am okay.
I already washed my hair.
Don't touch my body! Go away.
You can fix my hair like this, right?
No. Go away.
Get away!
No!
No. Just fix my hair like this.
It's all right.
(She starts fixing Ji Hyo's hair.)
What's your mission?
I can't get my name tag ripped until I get to the next destination.
(I can't get my name tag ripped until I reach the next destination.)
Can I rip it then?
(What?)
You want to rip it?
- I will rip it at once. - Do you want to be done with me?
(Their friendship is at stake.)
(But her biggest enemy was even nearer.)
By the way,
I fall asleep when someone touches my hair. I'm in trouble.
- Let's make her fall asleep. - I'm in trouble.
- Let's make her fall asleep. - Gosh.
I sleep whenever I get my hair done.
But who here would target my name tag?
I am already sleepy.
(Ji Hyo reacts fast and falls asleep fast.)
(Jae Seok has small eyes, but he's very sharp.)
(Startled)
What was that?
Something's not right.
(Who is targeting my name tag?)
Who is targeting my name tag?
Oh gosh!
That surprised me.
Can we take a picture with you?
(Can we take a picture with you?)
- Can we take a picture with you? - Sure.
Go ahead.
Okay.
- Wait. - Wait.
(Flinching)
What's wrong?
Please get closer.
You are too far from her.
(Gosh, stay closer.)
Wait.
This is strange.
Wait. They are a little strange.
- It's... - One, two, three.
(Even if they are suspicious, he takes a picture with them.)
- Thank you. - It's fine.
- One more. - Okay.
- Wait. - Wait.
Why do you hold my hand?
Wait.
- Don't touch my hands. - Stay closer.
Don't touch me.
Okay.
(He stands awkwardly.)
I won't do it.
That's not it.
You keep trying to put your hand behind my back.
(Jae Seok guards himself even from fan girls.)
- Okay. Thank you. Bye. - Thank you.
What are you doing?
- Should I get in? - Yes.
Yes.
(Wait)
(Who said you can leave?)
(Give me your name tag.)
Oh gosh!
(The fan girls return.)
Excuse me!
I knew it!
I thought you were strange.
What are you doing?
I thought you were acting strange.
- Wait. - What?
- There's a problem with the audio. - What?
What problem does it have?
- There's a problem. - What problem?
- The audio isn't working. - Why isn't it working?
(Did the mic fall when I was running?)
Why doesn't it work?
(He grabs Jae Seok's name tag.)
(Will he let it get ripped?)
Hey!
(He got his name tag ripped!)
(The audio crew removes his name tag.)
(Jae Seok is out for the first time.)
Hey!
How can this happen?
You are out once.
How can he be allowed to do this? This is crazy.
So we don't know who it's going to be. The girls were acting strange.
Gosh.
I've never seen people like them in my neighbourhood.
(Even after getting it ripped off, he doesn't stop talking.)
Gosh.
It's cold.
(Gary is on his way to meet his manager.)
- Hello. - Hello.
(He meets strange fans too.)
- Wait. - No. No.
- Please take a picture with us. - No. No.
I don't take pictures.
- Please take one picture with us. - No. No pictures.
- Why not? - No.
I don't want to!
I can't take a picture.
- Please take a picture with me. - I look too ugly today.
But I look pretty today.
Then I will take a picture of you.
(His fans don't give up.)
- Gosh. - It looks nice!
No!
(The girl tries to grab it.)
You were so close!
- Come inside the picture. - You didn't take it.
In 1, 2, 3.
(Gary is very quick and sharp.)
Okay. Okay.
- Cheers! - Cheers!
Cheers!
She reached out for my name tag so quickly.
(Gary finally meets his manager after the intense fan meeting.)
- You should get on from this side. - I will ride in the back?
(He reaches out for the name tag.)
(He grabs it.)
What are you doing?
(What's wrong with him?)
Goodness.
It's a good start.
So this is how it goes.
(Kwang Soo is surprisingly doing well.)
We don't know how many times we will be attacked, right?
- I'll change your mic battery. - Hold on.
Hold on.
- I can't hear your voice. - What?
- The mic... - I will give it to you.
- The mic... - I...
(He looks around.)
I will borrow this for a second.
You know what this is, right?
(He's surrounded by enemies.)
No one is on my side.
It's okay. Here.
(I think today will be a very tough day.)
It's my first time here, so I don't know who works here.
(He is not acquainted with the workers at the salon.)
- Do you need anything? - What?
Do you need anything?
- Do I need anything? - You want something to drink?
- What? - Anything to drink?
They all work here, right?
(Of course.)
I am sorry. It's just that it's my first time here.
(But what is up with this chilly atmosphere?)
Who works here?
(He's scared.)
(The girl stares at Kwang Soo.)
Do you need anything?
(Do you need anything?)
Please don't do that. It frightens me.
You're scaring me.
(But I need something from you.)
(He got his hair done in the hair-raising environment.)
No. It's okay.
- I'll help you take it out. - This is how I wear my clothes.
(No, I always wear my clothes like this.)
No, I'll do it myself.
No, I am okay.
Please.
You look so terrifying.
(Please, leave me alone.)
I will do it. What's going on?
What's going on? Wait.
Please, just leave me alone.
Please.
(He gets up.)
What? Okay.
(Flinching)
Please give up now.
Give up already.
(He moves fast.)
I am sorry. I'm sorry.
(He's about to escape.)
Give up already.
I'll get going. Thank you.
Bye.
(He manages to escape the hair salon.)
(However, Haha is still suspecting the couple.)
(He stares at them.)
How long have you been dating your boyfriend?
(He starts interrogating her.)
(He takes a seat and starts questioning her.)
How long have you been dating your boyfriend?
- I have a boyfriend. - So how long have you been dating?
- Three years. - Three years?
(He asked her how long they've been dating.)
Where did you meet him?
At school.
When is your boyfriend's birthday?
- April 15th. - April 15th.
(He is very suspicious of them.)
Thank you. I am sorry.
(Someone touches Haha's name tag...)
(and rips it.)
(When he was suspecting the couple,)
(one of the crew memebers ripped his name tag.)
(How can this happen?)
What was that?
(He rips his name tag and leaves.)
(The suspicious Haha is out for the first time.)
This is crazy.
When you live in the world where you can trust no one,
your heart really shrinks.
(He doesn't stop talking.)
(Someone approaches him.)
Hey!
(He's shocked.)
Yoo Seok.
You can't do this to me.
No way.
Hey! Hey! No way.
(I'm sorry, Seok Jin.)
Are you really...
Hey!
(The cameraman attacks him.)
Yoo Seok,
you can't do this to me!
Hey!
(He rips the name tag.)
(Seok Jin is out for the first time.)
This is impossible. What is wrong with you?
Gosh!
Hey, how can you...
How can you be so cold-hearted?
I never thought you would do this to me.
No one can be trusted.
Are you sure you are working for our company?
(He takes it out on his manager.)
- Please get in the car. - You get in first.
(I can't trust anybody.)
(Meanwhile, Jae Seok is moving to the next destination.)
Gosh.
(Sneaky)
Hey! What are you doing?
What are you doing right now?
(Looking for every chance)
Gosh...
Are you allowed to do this?
Can you sit next to me and just rip my name tag?
By the way, where are we going?
(Where are they headed?)
We should get some coffee.
(Let's get some coffee.)
Coffee?
(Coffee?)
Why do you want coffee all of a sudden?
I won't let it slide. What do you mean, "Check the audio"?
Do you want to get checked by me?
Oh my goodness.
Is that a new store?
Come on.
(That was close.)
(They finally arrive at a cafe.)
Where do I need to go?
- That way. - Let go.
Let go. I almost hit you with my elbow.
- Is it here? - Yes.
Oh, come on.
Don't touch my back.
(I was just showing you the way.)
Is this it?
(Jae Seok arrives at the second destination.)
- Are you going to be like that? - Don't worry.
- Hello. - Hello.
You don't look like regular customers.
There's something about you.
I can tell by your looks.
(The cameraman touches Jae Seok's back.)
Wait. Hey.
(Startled)
Stop it.
You'll pay for this.
(There are enemies everywhere.)
(Turning)
(Jae Seok is startled.)
- What is it? - Can we take a picture?
- Can we take a picture? - A picture?
Taking a picture is no problem.
I'll take the picture.
(I'll take it.)
(A girl creeps up.)
Wasn't someone just here?
Right?
Didn't someone just get close?
(Someone was near me.)
Am I wrong?
(Maybe I'm wrong.)
(Another lady stands up.)
You scared me!
(A girl grabs his name tag.)
Gosh!
(She rips it off.)
Wait a minute.
(That was...)
(perfect teamwork.)
(Jae Seok's out for the second time.)
Is that valid?
This isn't fair.
Who are you? Why did you rip off my tag?
(After getting her makeup and and hair done,)
(Ji Hyo leaves the hair salon in suspicion.)
Please, do something about her.
(Please, do something about her.)
Watch the car.
Let's go.
You should protect me.
Trust me. I'm not...
- the bad guy. - Okay. All right.
You go first.
Manager.
Come this way.
(Manager, come this way.)
- Hello. - Hello.
(Hello)
(Ji Hyo's afraid someone might rip her name tag off.)
I'm embarrassed.
Why do I have to be...
suspicious of an innocent passerby?
Manager!
(Manager, please come quickly.)
Come here quickly. Now.
- Hey. - Yes!
(Ji Hyo is out for the first time.)
I knew you were going to do that.
I knew you would do that.
I shouldn't have trusted you.
(Ji Hyo may get violent under pressure.)
- Yes! - Oh my gosh.
Hey.
Wait.
Why are you doing this?
(He grabs the name tag.)
Come on, guys.
Come on.
What's wrong with you?
Why are you doing this?
Come on.
(Jong Kook is out for the first time.)
Oh gosh.
Everyone here is after my name tag.
I have to work out, but I can't.
What do you want me to do?
He's my actual personal trainer.
(Someone as muscular as he must rip his name tag off.)
Oh gosh.
(The first attack in Agility Test is over.)
(Meanwhile at the cafe)
I can't even trust the cameraman.
- Hi, Gary. - Hi.
Come here. Did they get your name tag?
Theses people...
No, not yet.
- Really? - Hello.
Come here quickly.
(Gary takes a seat.)
Oh gosh.
(Oh gosh.)
What are you doing?
Oh my goodness.
- Let's not do this to each other. - Okay.
(I should've ripped it off.)
Can we take a picture?
I don't usually take pictures.
I only take it when I look handsome.
- You're handsome. - Today, my face is puffy.
- That's funny. - Oh gosh.
Even my manager tried to get me.
- Really? - Yes.
He tried to rip my name tag.
- That's too much. - Gosh.
- He almost got me. - Goodness.
(People are watching them.)
Gary, we need to check your audio.
That scared me.
(Gary doesn't think twice. He just turns his back.)
What?
(Gary's tag gets ripped off.)
Come on.
(Gary is upset.)
That's really mean.
- Gosh. - I can't believe it.
- This is too much. - Wow.
(Gary blames others for his carelessness.)
(Seok Jin arrives at the cafe.)
Even the bodyguards are scary today.
(He rushes to get inside.)
What's going on?
I can't feel anything.
You're here.
- Hi. - Hi, Gary.
(Seok Jin is very defensive.)
- Come here. - Be careful.
(Here comes...)
(the prey.)
One Americano and...
Do you have any snacks?
(He's very defensive.)
Can you make it quickly?
(Gary and Jae Seok...)
(are playing perfect defence.)
What are you doing?
(Seok Jin...)
(showed his back.)
These people...
(Gary rips the tag.)
(Oh gosh!)
(They are brutal.)
Once you have your drinks, you can move to the next place.
- Really? - I have to get my drink.
Why don't you attack Seok Jin? Just do it.
Is that mine?
(She reaches for the tag.)
(Gary rips it.)
(That was good...)
(teamwork.)
(This is the second time already.)
- Thank you. - Here.
- Here's your name tag you ordered. - Come on.
I can't remember how many times I got ripped.
(They all have their drinks.)
I'm so hungry.
- Seok Jin, let me check your audio. - My audio?
I need to check the battery.
(Of course.)
(The audio needs to be checked indeed.)
(Audio director is here.)
(He rips the tag off.)
(What?)
(Seok Jin needs to do better than this.)
(Seok Jin is destined to be the race starter.)
I will...
get going.
- I'll see you later. - See you later.
Always watch your back.
(Always watch your back.)
(Will Jae Seok escape first?)
(Seok Jin rips the tag off.)
(Did he just get my tag?)
I was just saying farewell.
- Come on. - That's brutal.
(Jae Seok is very agile but is easily distracted and careless.)
That's really bad.
(Ji Hyo's sleeping.)
(Someone's hand touches her.)
(She wakes up.)
(How dare you?)
(Ji Hyo is angry.)
Don't rip my tag.
(At the cafe)
Can we take a picture?
- Can we take a picture? - Okay. Give me your phone.
(He crouches down.)
(What is he doing?)
Come over here.
No, this way.
Lie down.
I'm sorry.
(This is weird.)
- I'm sorry. I'm very sorry. - Okay.
In 1, 2, 3.
(They seem friendly.)
- Here you go. - Thank you.
- Can I take one? - Yes.
Wait a minute.
I'm sorry.
In 1, 2, 3.
(Everyone lies down next to Kwang Soo.)
Okay. Thank you.
(People line up to lie down and get a picture.)
In 1, 2, 3.
(This is how Kwang Soo survives.)
(Jae Seok is on his way to the next place.)
Is it over when I reach the waiting room?
You're safe in the waiting room.
Will it be over then?
Do I get off here?
(He's the first one to arrive.)
(He's very alert.)
(Suddenly)
You don't need to check my microphone.
Come on.
(Oh no!)
What are you doing?
You can't do this.
(He can't let his guard down until he is in the waiting room.)
I can't believe this.
Is this the waiting room?
You can't do this to me.
(Let me check your mic.)
My mic? What a joke.
(My mic? What a joke.)
My mic is fine.
Just one person then.
(He's defensive.)
Okay.
I can't trust anyone.
(Oh no!)
(It's Kwang Soo.)
Ji Hyo! You're here.
You. You!
Do you know where it is?
That's why I'm not ripping name tags, we're all getting them ripped.
(Moving swiftly)
Okay, thank you.
Thank you.
(Awkward)
(He only touched Haha slightly...)
(and Haha gets startled...)
(and almost fainted.)
(He's strange.)
(Sneaking near Haha)
Stop cleaning.
Why are you cleaning so hard?
Okay, then I'll go over there.
(I'll go over there.)
(Moving quickly)
(Rushing away)
What is it?
What do you want?
Why are you cleaning around here?
The look in your eyes isn't for cleaning.
(Haha has good reaction and catches on quickly.)
(Let me check your mic.)
The batteries are already checked.
(What's this? This is too easy.)
I've been checked already.
(Ripping)
I can't believe...
I really can't trust anyone.
(As soon as they arrive,)
(they are all on their guards.)
I really don't trust anyone. No, stop.
No, no.
(No, no)
No. Why? What do you want?
(Your mic...)
Okay, you don't have to come here. Cars are coming. I got it.
If you come near me, I will hit you.
You'll get hit... Wait, I'm dizzy.
I lost my balance.
(Ji Hyo's shouting stands out more than her ability to react.)
(He's on guard.)
(Let me check your mic.)
(Kwang Soo is extremely tense.)
(He sticks his back to the car.)
(Kwang Soo passes the audio staff and heads for the waiting room.)
Hey.
(You surprised me.)
(Kwang Soo senses something strange.)
(The security manager suddenly attacks in front of the room.)
- Hey, just give up. - Jae Seok!
(Jae Seok slowly slides towards Kwang Soo.)
Jae Seok, what are you doing?
Why are you doing this?
You are ripped once more.
All right, it's done.
- Jae Seok. - This is how you get stronger.
Are we going to be like this with each other?
Haven't you done the same thing to us?
- Amongst ourselves... - Come inside.
- Come on in. - He always does the same to us.
(All Running Man members have gathered in the waiting room.)
- Come inside, we're safe here now. - It's all finished now.
It's safe inside, right?
- We can't rip name tags here. - It's a safe zone.
(Agility Test Results: First place, Haha & Ji Hyo)
(The tests until now were only the beginning!)
(Missions that surpass...)
That just gave me goosebumps.
(your expectations will unfold!)
Hey, Jong Kook.
(The members aim for the extreme with everything on the line.)
I almost ripped the name tag.
(Today, the fifth most skilled member will be born.)
(They have finally arrived.)
(The Running Man Laboratory for the Fifth Official Skill Assessment)
What is this?
- What is this? - What is it?
What's going on?
(Hello)
- Hello. - Shouldn't we be careful of them?
I think we're in the future.
- Hello. - It's a tunnel in here.
What is this?
(Welcome to the Running Lab.)
- What is all of this? - Why is this suddenly happening?
Is this "Star Wars"?
(A high-tech laboratory for the Fifth Official Skill Assessment)
(It will now be revealed.)
- What is all of this? - It's the future.
- It's really nice here. - It's a laboratory.
(With cutting edge equipment...)
(and high-class workers,)
(it is a space prepared specially for the Running Man members.)
- The scale is huge. - Look at that.
(Wow)
- Look at this. - I just got goosebumps.
I feel like we're in a sci-fi movie.
What is this, "Agility skills"?
- Look, they're monitoring us. - We're in there?
- Look at that. - They're writing scripts for us.
- My goodness, you surprised me. - What is that?
(They're startled.)
(What is this strange white thing?)
- What is this? - What's that?
(A robot of the future)
(A robot like the ones in "Star Wars"?)
(It seems as if Yoda will appear at any moment.)
(Where have I seen that before?)
- I like these things. - It's cute.
I can't converse with it.
- Hello. - Something like this really exists?
- What is it? - Hello.
Is someone inside it?
Welcome to the Running Man Skill Assessment Laboratory.
(Skill Assessment?)
- It's not a joke. - We're measuring our skills today?
In order to fulfill Haha and Seok Jin's wishes,
we've prepared a special race.
(Big data consisting of 284 episodes and 6 years were used.)
(Members were assessed in agility, strength and nerve.)
(The Fifth Official Skill Assessment has been prepared using all data.)
When all of the skills have been averaged out,
who will become the most skilled member?
- It happened the way we wanted. - We'll proceed with the assessment.
- Thank you! - It's a skill assessment today?
- I really want to win this one. - Let's start from the same level.
Then Kwang Soo needs to cut down his height.
- His height... - You can just walk on your knees.
Why should I walk on my knees?
He has to reduce everything.
He has to cut his arm length too.
Then you have to attach your arms to your legs, Jong Kook.
He'll still be like metal.
- Jong Kook, play in a handstand. - That makes no sense.
Today, for the winner of the Fifth Official Skill Assessment,
a great prize will be awarded.
- A trip to London will be given. - Really?
London?
- The place Gary went to? - London?
It's better not to go. They keep recording you.
I'm not going. I don't want to go.
It's better not going on a trip from the broadcasting company.
They record you for 16 hours a day.
- Gosh. - I'd rather go to America.
The test has already begun on your way here.
- Has it? - Through the sudden name tag game,
we checked your agility level.
When we combined the reaction skill points,
the 2 members who got their name tags ripped 2 times...
- were Haha and Ji Hyo. - They did well.
- That's really good. - They didn't get caught much.
- Because I was so suspicious. - That sounds right.
Jae Seok and Gary tied for third place, getting caught four times.
- I see. - They did well.
Jong Kook got caught five times and is in fifth place.
Kwang Soo got caught six times, so he is in sixth place.
Seok Jin got caught too many times, so he is in seventh place.
Like this, the members are ranked from first to seventh place.
I'm confident in playing this game, but I don't know what color to use.
Pick up the red one!
(Always lacking a little, a player who makes wrong guesses)
(Seok Jin remains in seventh place once again.)
Follow me!
(Is he really lacking a specific skill?)
(Special research will be conducted.)
What's wrong with him?
It's been a long time.
(What kinds of tests await the members?)
- Hello. - Yes, come in.
Hello.
- Have a seat. - Okay.
(A doctor is...)
(in a hospital office?)
You have to fill out this questionnaire first.
- Okay. - Slowly read it over.
(Glancing slightly)
(He's trying to concentrate on the questionnaire.)
Wait, hold on a minute.
- What's wrong? - Wait, hold on.
- It started already? - Stop, don't do that.
No, stop!
(The doctor goes down...)
(and comes up again.)
Has the game started?
(Surprise!)
(It was this person...)
(but when Jae Seok and Jong Kook came running in,)
(there was another person under the desk!)
(One person goes in.)
(One person comes out.)
- It hasn't started? - My name tag...
(Will Seok Jin be able to catch on in this situation?)
What is he going to do?
Oh no.
Isn't it too obvious? Of course he will see it.
- My name tag... - Why are you starting already?
Wait Seok Jin, hold on.
Jong Kook keeps acting like this right now.
- Do your questionnaire. - What's going on?
- There must be something happening. - I'm going crazy.
I write my name and do I have to write my date of birth?
(Seok Jin sees him.)
(He may not be...)
(very quick-witted,)
(but shouldn't he be able to catch on to this?)
Do I have to write my age as it appears on the internet?
He doesn't know!
Seok Jin doesn't know.
He didn't catch on.
"How many hours on average do you sleep a day?"
I sleep seven hours a day.
I'm being honest. We have to be honest for this.
"How is your daily bowel movement?"
I think it's once every two days.
(Second attempt)
"Write the time and menu of your breakfast."
I eat my breakfast a bit late.
(Seok Jin is looking.)
(He has no interest at all.)
I eat breakfast around 11am.
(That was close.)
11am. The menu is...
from time to time...
My menu is...
(Jae Seok destroys Seok Jin's concentration.)
What are you doing? I'm doing something right now!
Seok Jin,
everyone else is doing the same thing.
(Embracing)
This is a war.
I was writing.
- Gosh. - Why did you do that?
This isn't right! I'm working right now.
Goodness.
The menu changes often.
(The doctor changes too.)
Bagel.
Seok Jin has no interest in this.
He thinks this is about the name tag.
"How many times do you exercise for more than 30 minutes..."
"until you are out of breath in a week?"
Four days.
"In the past week, how many times did you work on the same..."
"exercise for more than 10 minutes..."
How can he not?
(It's funny, but now it's become fascinating.)
How is it possible to be like that?
Rarely. Less than once a week.
"Did you feel depressed?"
Not really.
"The following symptoms..."
(How could he not realise that?)
He is hilarious.
- This is serious. - That's hilarious.
That's funny. Someone should have done that to me too.
Do I have any illness that I should be concerned about?
Since I smoke, could I have lung disease?
(His eyes are set on the doctor for only half a second.)
The doctors must be disappointed.
Seok Jin doesn't pay any attention to them.
Okay.
Why do you keep on dropping things?
(I have hand tremor.)
Seok Jin thought he dropped something.
(Is that really the only strange thing here?)
(Seok Jin's test ends here.)
Look at his name tag.
(Seok Jin's absentmindedness is unbeatable.)
How could he be like that?
- We should... - Let's put on an act again.
No, stop it.
No.
- No. Don't do this to me. - Why me?
No, don't!
This is quite annoying.
- You guys are still at this? - Yes.
We were doing this while you were gone.
(Then, I'll join in.)
Don't show your back to me.
The doctor keeps on dropping something on the floor.
Don't you mean the doctors?
I asked him why, and he told me that he has hand tremor.
He keeps on picking something up.
He might have hand tremor, but I think your illness is more severe.
- I think you have a severe illness. - I...
I hope after you watch today's episode,
you don't feel bad.
I think people will be sad watching this.
Let's be honest.
How am I supposed to know when he ambushes me from behind?
(How should I know?)
That's not it.
What are you saying?
(Seok Jin is so amazingly slow-witted.)
Stop it.
What is it?
- The doctor kept changing. - They kept changing.
Really?
I didn't know.
I really didn't know.
That's why he kept on disappearing.
I had no clue.
- You really didn't know? - I had no clue.
This is real. He really didn't know.
You guys must be very sharp-sighted.
That's not it.
It's normal to realise it.
- It's impossible not to realise it. - You guys must be really good.
I was concentrating on the form.
It's not about being sharp-sighted. It's impossible not to know.
(Cheer up, Seok Jin. You are only naive.)
What is this place?
(The room is filled with presents wrapped in black veil.)
- There must be something inside. - What is this?
- I think we need to touch it. - I can't.
I think this is to test our nerve.
You are correct.
I knew it.
Please listen up.
Based on the data we collected from previous tests on your nerve...
- Please bring in the data. - I don't like the sound of this.
I knew it. I have the highest scores.
From the episode of Scary Story,
the number of times we screamed, Jae Seok 13, Kwang Soo 12, Haha 10,
Gary and Seok Jin 7, Ji Hyo 6 and Jong Kook 5 times.
The number of times we moaned, talked to ourselves or said...
"Are you crazy?"
Jae Seok 33 times.
- That's unbeatable. - Seok Jin 22 times.
Kwang Soo 20 times, Haha 10 times and Gary 8 times.
When you were terrified.
"Are you crazy? You must be out of your mind."
"They're all crazy."
"This is crazy."
"Is this for real?"
The number of times we said...
"I can't do this" or "I can't go".
The person who said "I can't do this" the most...
was Seok Jin.
The person who said "I can't go" the most was Haha.
Haha said it 3 times and Seok Jin Said it 7 times.
"I can't do this."
"I can't go."
The number of times we grunted, Jae Seok 3 times, Ji Hyo 2 times,
- and Seok Jin two times. - Is this your special episode?
- You're a top ranker in everything. - I'm really...
- easily scared. - You're at the top for everything.
- This is a real laboratory. - They did their job properly.
- They really did their job. - You guys are amazing.
(The assessment on each member's nerve test is now complete.)
(The ranking of the members' nerve is in the following order.)
(Jong Kook, Ji Hyo, Gary, Kwang Soo,)
(Seok Jin and Haha in a tie and lastly, Jae Seok.)
The results of this test will be used in the future.
There are seven fish tanks under the veil.
- There are seven. - Fish tanks?
This is Ji Hyo's weak spot.
- I am really bad at this. - There are seven.
Because she hates bugs.
In here, there are beads.
Beads.
There are two beads in each fish tank.
There are a total of 14 beads.
The person with the toughest nerve, Jong Kook...
needs to get 10 beads out.
- Oh, no. - 10 beads?
- They must have prepared more. - Ji Hyo needs to get nine.
(Second in rank, Ji Hyo needs to get nine beads out.)
Third in rank, Gary needs to get eight beads out.
Kwang Soo needs to get seven beads.
Seok Jin and Haha need to get six beads each.
- And finally, - Jae Seok needs to get five?
Jae Seok only needs to get four beads.
(Seventh in rank, Jae Seok needs to get four beads.)
After you have got your assigned amount of beads out,
then we will record the time and the ranking will change.
- It's best to finish quick. - I'm good at this.
- We will reveal the fish tanks. - I just hope it's not bugs.
- Don't look. - I don't like these things.
I really don't like this.
Please be careful.
(An unforgettable experience awaits.)
(The things to test the members' nerve is revealed.)
- How about Jong Kook take the lead? - All right.
(Jong Kook starts off the nerve test.)
(I am bold.)
Can I start?
Start!
(There's no time to spare.)
He is so daring.
- What does it feel like? - I can't find it.
He looks like he doesn't feel a thing.
His arms must be too big for the hole.
Are the stuff inside the fish tank all the same?
It's difficult to find the beads.
They're timing me.
Are you all right?
(He is quick to find another bead.)
What is it?
- What is this? - Don't crush it.
What is this? Who are you?
- Is someone inside? - Someone's inside?
(He moves on with his mission despite the creepy movement.)
Get out!
Oh, my.
- You're too harsh. - Get out!
- Don't make it angry. - Who are you?
There's something inside this.
(His instinct tells him there's something inside.)
There is something.
Hey!
(As Jong Kook screams,)
(others are more frightened.)
I can't do this.
They must be crazy.
Don't make the thing angry.
There's water inside.
I hate that.
(Jong Kook doesn't stop regardless of others' reactions.)
He's nearly done.
No, stop it.
- Don't make it angry. - There aren't any beads.
(He scoops up two beads at once.)
- He's amazing. - How can he do that?
- What's that on your hand? - What does it smell like?
Two, four, six, eight and ten. I have ten.
(Two, four, six, eight and ten)
- What is it? - Goodness.
(Jong Kook manages to get 10 beads.)
I was surprised.
- You guys are up for a scare. - What does it feel like?
It was you!
Oh no, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
(Why is he apologising?)
- Is there a person? - Maybe it's something alive.
- Please go first. - Yes.
- Us cowards will wait. - Please begin.
Gary, why don't you go first?
- How many do you need to get? - You go first.
Gary needs to get eight beads.
Get ready. Don't look.
Hold on to your bowl.
I have no nerve. The data is wrong.
Hey,
from our point of view, you're a hero.
We're nothing compared to you.
How can Jong Kook do this like it's nothing?
Begin!
(Gary needs to get eight beads.)
My hand won't go in.
(His nerves fails him from the start.)
Oh, my.
(Oh, my)
Something bit me.
That's the normal reaction.
- What is this? - That's normal.
What is this?
Something bit me hard.
(What bit Gary's hand?)
(The culprit was nothing other than massage balls.)
Something keeps on biting me.
Wait a minute.
Something bit you?
- It bites you? - It hurts.
- It hurts? - What is it?
- Does it hurt? - So it bites?
Is it scissors?
(Gary successfully finds his second bead.)
Does it bite?
It's fine. Gary, be careful.
Be careful.
Go. Put your hand in.
Wait. I can't.
That's the normal reaction.
(What is this?)
Wait. This feels weird.
- What is it? - I don't know.
Gary. Gary!
It feels like a snake.
(What is this?)
(The objects inside are massage gloves.)
- Gary. - It feels like a snake.
A snake?
(Scared)
- How could you do this? - What is it?
This is normal.
- Is it real? - I want to do this one.
This is no joke.
Why?
Gary, you're doing well.
Wait.
(He screams.)
There's water inside.
Why is there water?
(What's under the water?)
(The things under the water are mudfish.)
(Gary needs to dig the bead out from a pool of mudfish.)
Look at his face.
(Gary tries hard to find the beads.)
Look at the time.
Even if it takes forever, I'm not going back.
I found it.
- What's that? - What came out with the bead?
What's on the beads?
I think I freaked out by myself.
Don't touch me.
What is this?
This is...
crazy.
I'm going to try this.
(What is in the fish tank?)
Poor Gary.
(He's got the superb sense of touch. What's his guess?)
(They are wigs.)
Is it a living thing?
(There are all kinds of hair.)
Wait!
It's better to do it before others.
There are too many. We have to do six.
A coward can't handle that number.
(Gary finds six.)
(He goes for the fifth one.)
(He is focused.)
(Please)
- What's this? - Stop doing that.
- Wait! - You're overreacting, aren't you?
Wait! I am not overreacting!
- Try it! - He's not overreacting.
Wait!
(What is the thing that's making him have a spasm?)
(It's the ginseng of the sea, sea cucumber.)
- Gosh... - Gosh, wait.
Hey.
(Its slimy surface is making him dance.)
(Gary gets one bead.)
He found it quickly.
That must be...
(He takes out the bead.)
(Gary finds all eight beads.)
He's good.
All right.
(He's worn-off.)
I want to see what was inside the second box.
What is it?
Really? Really?
(It's nothing, but when you don't know, it can give you a hard time.)
(What's inside the two boxes Gary didn't check?)
(There are stainless steel sponges.)
(And there are pasta noodles soaked in water.)
(There are different things in the eight boxes.)
(How embarrassing!)
(Kwang Soo goes next.)
- I'll start from the other end. - Seven...
- Kwang Soo has to do seven. - Gosh...
Oh dear.
- I don't know if he'll be okay. - Gosh...
Don't say things like that.
What is that though?
(Jong Kook spreads fear.)
What is this?
- Kwang Soo. - He's so annoying.
- Where did they come from? - He's so annoying.
They are the two most annoying people.
- Why did they put that there? - Ready?
Just be confident. Don't be like me.
Go.
Just put it inside.
- It's warm inside! - Put it inside.
- What is it? - Just do it.
Kwang Soo. Come on.
(Kwang Soo's first objects are massage gloves.)
- Just go deep. - You shouldn't do that.
Your hands won't reach them. Put them deep inside.
What's that?
(He overreacts to scare Kwang Soo.)
- Kwang Soo! - It's too much!
Please press my shoulder.
- Press it so I won't take it out. - Okay.
(Jong Kook presses Kwang Soo's shoulder.)
(But Kwang Soo hesitates to put his hand down.)
(There's an inner conflict.)
It's standing up. Go.
Jong Kook, press him from the back.
(The massage glove is tired of waiting.)
(It touches Kwang Soo.)
(It suddenly touches Kwang Soo.)
(Kwang Soo thinks his hand almost got eaten.)
What's wrong? Did it bite your hand?
Did it bite?
Come back.
- You are wasting time. - You've already done it.
It licked me.
- It licked you? - Come on.
It licked you?
Wait. Just go deep.
(Kwang Soo beats Jong Kook.)
(You put your own hand inside!)
It's not moving now. Do it now.
It's not moving now?
- What is it? - What is it?
What could it be?
Open your hand. Open it.
(Something inside it is targeting my hand.)
Lower it. Lower it.
Lower it. Here.
(Mum)
It's frustrating because we don't know what it is.
- It's better to do it early. - Come on.
(Kwang Soo is shaking.)
Move to the centre.
(He grabs the bead.)
I think it's better if you don't grab him.
- Stop it. - How can he do six more?
I won't do it any more.
Go to the next one.
(He finds one bead and moves to the next box.)
- This is... - What is it, Kwang Soo?
It licked me.
It licked you?
- Did it really lick you? - It licks you?
(Did...)
(this kind of thing...)
(lick you?)
- That's terrible. - Can't we wear gloves?
Where are you going? You are too far from them.
(The second box is filled with mudfish.)
You are still far away. Go deeper.
(Gosh!)
(He's making a big fuss.)
Something is stuck on his hand.
Can I watch from here? I will watch from here.
I will watch from here.
This is fun.
Now you know why I made such a fuss.
- Go inside. - It's better to get it done.
- You have to look for it too. - That is too painful.
(Flapping)
Why? What is it?
(His hand was like a flapping bird wing.)
Is there water?
Did it bite?
- Did it bite? - What is it?
I didn't even try that one.
That's the last one.
- Gosh. - I am dizzy.
Kwang Soo, just shout and do it.
(Shouting)
(He hesitates.)
(He's starting to automatically bounce back.)
This is crazy.
(Flinching)
What is it?
(Kwang Soo dances like a popping dancer.)
Is it that bad?
(Popping)
(Kwang Soo moves like popping popcorn.)
What is it?
(He skips the pasta box and moves to the next.)
- Why? - This is crazy.
I really can't do this.
But at least you touched it.
- I will do all the rest. - This is too funny.
(He skips the steel sponges.)
(Shivering)
When you can't see it, you get really scared.
You get surprised by stuffed toys too.
(Lightly tapping)
Is it pudding or what?
(It's sea pudding.)
- Pudding? - Then touch the pudding.
- Just clench your fist. - Touch the pudding.
- Just grab it. - Just grab it.
(He grabs one.)
(He's thrilled by the touch of the pudding.)
- It's making me cringe. - Time is up.
The time is up.
(Kwang Soo lacks agility, but he can do the popping dance.)
This is the highlight.
- I'm sweating. - You just have to get four.
You will be fine.
(Jae Seok is next.)
(Will he be able to...)
(stop being a coward?)
Ready.
(He has to get just four beads.)
Start.
I know him. I know him.
You have to put your hand in one go.
He won't even be able to get one bead.
- This doesn't make sense. - Go inside.
What are you doing right now?
Just put it inside.
(He already feels like he's touched the bottom of the box.)
- He... - It's all right.
You didn't even go inside.
(He hesitates.)
- Why is it hot inside? - Jae Seok!
You only put this much.
You only put this much inside.
- What's wrong with you? - But it's slightly warm.
- It's not warm. - Maybe something is breathing?
No.
- It's your heart that's hot. - It smells differently too.
- He... - Just put it inside.
Go down. No, go down more.
- No. - It's following his hand.
(Screaming)
- This is really... - Jae Seok.
(He almost has a heart attack.)
Let's do this again.
Don't trust what Kwang Soo says.
- But it's really following him. - Let's do this.
- Just go in. - Go to the centre. It's moving.
Just go in.
(The glove kisses Jae Seok's hand too.)
Something's inside.
Something is inside!
(He's going mad.)
- Something is inside. - It's all right.
Some thing is really inside!
It's okay.
It kissed my hand, didn't it?
- It follows his hand. - Jae Seok, did it bite you?
Thank goodness I took my hand out before it licked my hand.
Otherwise, it would've licked and bitten my hand.
What is it really?
- I experienced that too. - Is it big?
- I don't know either. - It licks you?
- It was... - Was it wet or dry?
- It's wet. - It's dry.
It's wet?
(It's wet?)
(Is it always wet like this guy?)
Just go to the next one.
- If you fail here... - Ready.
Put your hand inside while screaming. One, two, three!
- Isn't it upset right now? - Gary made us more scared.
Isn't it upset right now?
- Do it now. - In 1, 2, 3.
(High-five!)
(Screaming)
Did you see it?
It came to meet me.
- It came to meet me. - Did you touch its face?
It was waiting for him.
- It was waiting for me. - Did you touch its face?
It was waiting for me!
How can it jump like that?
- It jumps too? - It jumps?
Don't pick that one. That one is too tough.
- Just pass it. - I'll pass it.
- I can't do it. - This is so annoying.
(He skips the one that jumps and licks.)
Do it on the count of three.
- In 1, 2, 3. - In 1, 2, 3.
How deep is it?
You didn't even get there.
- What's this? - Let me see.
That's just sweat.
What's in there?
- What's this? - Just do it.
Answer me, what is it?
- Jae Seok... - What's wrong with it?
It's a mess. It's a mess down there.
- It's a mess. - If you touch them...
(Touching)
Don't do that. Don't do that.
You've shocked them. They are going crazy.
- They are going crazy. - I can see the bead.
There's more than one thing?
(He angrily touches them.)
(Gosh!)
Gosh!
Why do you make them fly?
- They fly? - They fly?
(They fly?)
- I can't do this. - Pass it.
What is it?
- It's something very new. - Tell us.
- I really don't know. - Okay.
- I've never seen this. - All right.
Is it something you don't know?
What is this?
It doesn't look like anything I know.
- This... - What?
(He lost his words.)
You haven't touched it yet.
What's that?
What's this?
What is it?
- What is it? - I don't know.
(Screaming)
What is it?
(Pasta can be this scary.)
I can't do it.
(Jae Seok gets zero beads.)
That felt slippery.
- What is it? - This is the best.
What are you talking about?
(He looks miserable.)
- What is it? - Oh.
Is it nothing?
- It comes out here. - What is this?
- I don't know. - I still can't tell what it is.
(It's pasta.)
(For goodness' sake)
(It was just pasta.)
Are you okay?
(He was afraid of getting bitten by pasta.)
I didn't know it was this colour.
(Jae Seok has a weak heart.)
- What is it? - Okay.
Put your hand in there.
You're not touching it.
Reach in.
(Haha is so loud.)
This is horrible.
Keep going.
(Screaming)
- This is insane. - I can't do this.
- What's this? - Go up.
- Is it a reptile? - Go up.
- It's not... - Is it an amphibian?
It's not what you're imagining.
- Grab it. - Go like this.
What is it? What is this?
- There are hundreds of them. - No.
Are these snakes?
In 1, 2, 3.
(He touches it.)
(He reached it.)
What is it?
- Hey. - Go the other way.
(He touches it.)
(He is terrified.)
- It actually moved. - That's crazy.
It moved.
It really did.
It hit my hand.
- Wow. - Come on.
- Okay. - Wait.
Oh my gosh.
(Haha shouts like a man but gets scared like a child.)
(Meanwhile, Seok Jin...)
- It seems scary. - What?
- Wow. - He found one.
(He gets one bead.)
- Keep going. - Go to the next one.
- What's this? - What?
(Seok Jin now has two beads.)
He's so brave.
(Seok Jin goes for the wig box.)
(He tries to find a bead.)
(He finds it.)
- He has three. - Good job.
(Seok Jin now has three beads.)
- He got three. - Nice.
(Seok Jin is quite brave.)
(Ji Hyo is the last one to go.)
- My head hurts. - Get ready.
- Get ready. - Come on.
They're making us touch the stuff we don't even know.
- What is it? - What are those?
- Don't lie. - Okay.
What is it?
(Ji Hyo can bungee jump, but she's scared of insects.)
- You shouldn't look. - Okay.
I think I'm going to cry.
(She is shaking.)
Why are you being so girly today?
- Ji Hyo. - Why?
- Come on. - Don't cry.
- Ji Hyo. - It's okay.
You've become so girly...
- after you got married. - It's okay.
- Come on. - I can't believe it.
- What are you doing? - Did Chen Bolin change you?
I thought you went through a breakup or something.
- Don't cry. - Kwang Soo. Or someone...
No, not you.
Jong Kook, can you put me in there?
Do you want me to put you in there?
- No. Hold my arm. - I can help.
No, I don't want your help.
- I'll grab your arm. - Okay.
- Ready? - Can I put my fist in?
- Of course. - Make it pass out.
- Make it unconscious. - Knock it out.
I think you should knock it out.
- Ji Hyo. - Just hit it.
(Whimpering)
You still have a long way to go.
Jong Kook.
- You have to go more. - Ji Hyo.
Wait!
(Screaming)
- Are you giving birth? - Keep going.
I thought...
- Come on. - I understand.
Am I your midwife?
I understand you.
(Crying out loud)
- I can't do this. - I understand you.
You just have to go in.
- Hold me, Jong Kook. - Okay.
(She touches it.)
- It's electrostatic. - It's okay.
It gave me a shock. It shocked me!
- It's electrostatic. - I saw it.
- I saw it. - It's okay.
I saw that you touched it.
I understand why you're so frightened.
- It's okay. - I feel you.
- I understand you. - It's okay.
- It's okay. - I understand.
You should go to the next one.
- Go to the next one. - Do the next one.
- It gave me a shock. - Okay.
- It's okay. - We can't help you.
(Now it's the pasta.)
- Let's do this one. - It's okay.
Did they bring it from "Law of the Jungle"?
(What is it this time?)
It's okay because this one's warm.
- Ready. - I guess it lives in warm water.
- It's okay. - It's fine.
It won't bite you. It's not harmful.
- Just go for it. - It's okay. It won't hurt you.
Why is it so humid?
(What? It's damp?)
- It's okay. - It's really damp.
It's damp inside.
Because it needs to breathe.
Just be bold and put your hand in.
You'll feel the humidity. It's not pleasant.
Put your hand in. It's something you like.
- Keep going. - Put your hand in.
- Trust me. - Trust us.
Ji Hyo, trust me.
- Haha, you are so shameless. - Really.
- Seriously. - And...
please don't pretend to be brave.
- What do you mean, "Trust me"? - Come on.
- Don't say that. - It's okay.
- Don't worry. - It's okay.
- Did you touch it? - No, not yet.
Did you touch it yet?
- Spread out your fingers. - Do it.
(She spreads out her fingers.)
- Not like that. - Not that way.
Spread vertically. That won't help.
- That was so stupid. - Come on.
- Spread your fingers. - It's okay.
Keep your wrist straight.
(She tries to touch it.)
Keep going. It's not there.
- It's not there. - In 1, 2, 3.
- Good. - That's good.
- You're almost there. - Touch it with your fingers.
(She screams...)
(and falls on the floor.)
- Come on. - It's not scary.
- Come on. - It won't bite.
- You almost made it. - Let's go to the next one.
(She cries.)
- It's okay. - Don't cry.
- Just do this one. - Just this last one.
- This is the last one. - Just this one.
- Okay. - Do just this one.
If this doesn't work, we'll stop here.
- This is your last try. - This is the last one.
- Go in. - Put your hand in.
- What is it? - It's okay.
Is this something to cry over?
Don't cry, Ji Hyo.
- Come on. - Don't cry.
- I touched something. - I will...
- throw you a towel. - Did you touch it?
I touched something.
- Do I spread my fingers? - Yes.
(It touched her.)
(Screaming)
What is it?
(She is jerking her body.)
(He throws a towel.)
(Ji Hyo gives up.)
- Stop. - Don't do it.
- No. - Come here.
- What is it? - Wipe your tears and come here.
You should stop.
You can swear now.
- Take a look. - You can swear.
They're steel sponges.
- Come here. - It's just pasta.
You've had pasta before, right?
Doesn't this make you angry?
- Seriously. - I hated the last one.
(Ji Hyo is hard to tell. She was just cute today.)
(In the order of the bravest: 1. Jong Kook, 2. Gary, 3. Seok Jin,)
(4. Kwang Soo, 5. Ji Hyo, 6. Haha 7. Jae Seok)
(Official Skill Assessment: 1. Jong Kook, 2. Gary, 3. Ji Hyo,)
(4. Seok Jin and Kwang Soo, 6. Haha, 7. Jae Seok)
We are all so tired.
- That scared me. - It's here again.
- It's Seok Jin's ideal woman. - Next up is the Strength Test.
- A strength test. - I will check your...
- rankings solely on strength. - I see.
- The strongest is... - It's Jong Kook.
- Who's the second? - I could be the second.
- That's expected. - Yes.
- Gary's the second. - I see.
- Is it me? Not Jae Seok? - Oh.
- What about Kwang Soo? - Haha.
- I see. - Kwang Soo is strong.
Song Ji Hyo.
(1. Jong Kook, 2. Gary, 3. Kwang Soo,)
(4. Jae Seok, 5. Haha, 6. Ji Hyo, 7. Seok Jin)
Ji Hyo is stronger than me?
(You're weaker than me.)
We'll test your strength.
With your arms tied to a pole,
you have to make a wrap with...
all the ingredients and eat it.
Jong Kook will get the shortest rubber band...
because he's the strongest.
(The length of the rubber band depends on the ranking.)
- That's good. - Seok Jin will get the...
- longest rubber band. - I see.
- Okay. - Jae Seok, Haha, Ji Hyo...
and Seok Jin will go first.
Ready.
Goodness!
(Jae Seok: 70cm, Haha: 75cm, Ji Hyo: 80cm, Seok Jin: 90cm)
Jae Seok is almost done.
(Did Jae Seok get the lettuce, garlic and mushroom?)
(Back to the beginning)
I got it.
(The time is measured when they eat the wrap.)
(Ji Hyo is trying hard.)
You have to put it in your mouth.
I forgot the mushroom.
Ask Chen Bolin to pass it to you.
(He's so petty.)
(They both try their best.)
It's missing meat.
(I will win against Ji Hyo.)
(Oh gosh.)
She makes it.
- Oh gosh. - She's angry.
She's really angry.
This is tough.
(1. Jae Seok, 2. Haha, 3. Seok Jin, 4. Ji Hyo)
This is too short.
- It'll be hard. - Ready.
(Pulling hard)
Go, Gary!
(Jong Kook: 30cm, Gary: 40cm, Kwang Soo: 50cm)
(Jong Kook is the strongest among them.)
(He's as strong as a tiger.)
(Reaching for the meat)
Jong Kook's doing well.
- Just a little more. - Just a bit more.
- Keep going. - Just a bit more.
(Kwang Soo reaches for the lettuce.)
- Gosh. - Go, Kwang Soo!
(Kwang Soo is about to eat the wrap.)
(Jong Kook gets it in first.)
- He got it. - Wow.
- Jong Kook did it. - He's the first.
(1. Jong Kook, 2. Kwang Soo, 3. Gary)
- Jong Kook won? - Yes.
(Jong Kook is the strongest.)
Is this really a fair game?
- Gosh. - This isn't fair.
(1. Jae Seok, 2. Haha, 3. Jong Kook, 4. Kwang Soo,)
(5. Gary, 6. Seok Jin, 7. Ji Hyo)
(Final result: 1. Jong Kook, 2. Jae Seok,)
(3. Gary, Kwang Soo and Haha, 6. Seok Jin and Ji Hyo)
(Gary, the first and secnd winner as the most skilled member)
(Haha, the third winner as the most skilled member)
(Jae Seok and Kim Yeon Koung were the fourth winners.)
(And today, a fair game will reveal the new winner.)
(The final test will begin now.)
(A school in Sangam-dong)
This place is...
As Haha and Seok Jin have requested,
today will be a standardised game to pick the most skilled one.
So the final mission is called...
Standardised Name Tag Ripping.
(Today's final mission, Standardised Name Tag Ripping)
We have assessed the data for each of your strength,
nerve and name tag ripping rankings...
and standardised the game for you.
I'm really curious.
- If you look under this... - They standardised the game.
I wonder...
- Wow. - What is this?
Wow.
Look at the size of the name tags. It's nice.
This isn't right.
- This is great. - Why is Gary's name tag so small?
- My name tag... - Look at mine!
- Why is mine so big? - It's for children.
- Don't touch them please. - Why is Kwang Soo's so small?
The item related to the strength test...
- is the sandbag you see here. - Okay.
This isn't right, the name tag size is difficult to play with.
The size of the name tags are in correlation with the...
- your name tag ripping skills. - It has wings.
- This is great. - This name tag...
is going to get ripped off while he runs.
He'll be out soon.
- It'll be easy to rip it. - Goodness.
Just tell me that you don't want to send me to the UK.
Where do you have to rip? Is it here?
How do you rip this one?
How do you rip Seok Jin's name tag? Like this?
- Use your fingernails. - Just use your strength.
- Use your nails. - This is so small.
If you want to rip this, you have to knock him out first.
- Is that okay? - Also,
there are three sets of bells for Jong Kook,
Gary and Ji Hyo.
The top three rankings in nerve will be wearing bells.
- Are they attacking? - Kwang Soo is at advantage.
Seok Jin has only that name tag?
- He doesn't even have a sandbag. - Right. He has nothing.
(Seok Jin is the most benefited from standardisation.)
This is how life is.
This sandbag is going to affect me greatly.
Just know if you get hit by the sandbag, you could die.
- Why do you think like that? - Be careful.
- I'm telling the truth. - Don't say things like that.
- I don't know what will happen. - It didn't even happen yet.
Name tag or whatever, I won't leave you guys alone.
I'm so angry right now.
Jong Kook, you look like you're going to fly away any second now.
- You've ripped so many name tags. - But...
- that could be harder to rip. - It's really big.
You'll need both hands to rip that.
Jong Kook's going to fly away.
Ji Hyo,
I can see your name tag from the front.
Your name tag shows from the front.
Ji Hyo, you might end up floating in the air.
Be careful. You might rise like hot air.
This is hard for me.
(I can just do this.)
You put those under your armpits?
- You shouldn't do that! - Don't do that.
Why would you put those under your armpits?
Let's not do that.
This is too much.
Don't rip Seok Jin's name tag in advance.
Hey, what's wrong with you?
- He's provoking me. - Goodness.
Today's game is worth playing.
Seok Jin.
Is today the day?
(Is today the day?)
- Shall we be the last men standing? - Shall we?
- Okay - It's today.
- Today's the day. - I'll look forward to it.
- Seok Jin, you can't betray me. - I won't.
(Seok Jin has a mini name tag. Haha has a 1kg sandbag and a normal tag.)
(Show us your strength, Gary and Ji Hyo!)
(Gary: second in nerves, third in strength, fifth in name tag ranks)
(Ji Hyo: third in nerves, sixth in strength, second in name tag ranks)
(Gary: 1kg sandbag, bells and normal tag, Ji Hyo: bells and large tag)
(Jae Seok and Kwang Soo will win using tricks and betraying.)
(Kwang Soo: fourth in nerves, third in strength, fifth in name tag rank)
(Jae Seok: seventh in nerves, second in strength, third in name tag rank)
(Kwang Soo: 1kg sandbag, normal tag, Jae Seok: 2kg sandbag, medium tag)
(The public enemy, Jong Kook)
(Jong Kook: first in nerves, first in strength, first in name tag rank)
(Jong Kook: 3kg sandbag, extra large winged tag and bells)
The Fifth Official Skill Assessment race...
will begin in five seconds.
Five,
four,
three,
two,
one. Begin.
(The mission has begun.)
Should I hide somewhere?
Seok Jin has a chance to win today.
I tried to rip his name tag, but it didn't come off.
(Finding Seok Jin soon will be advantageous.)
I trust you, Seok Jin.
Today, I will make...
a mark in my life's history.
I will rip Jong Kook's name tag.
(I wil rip Jong Kook's name tag.)
The wings are too big.
(The extra large wings put him at a disadvantage.)
This is a problem.
I just have to listen carefully for the bells.
Why did I have to wear the bells?
They're so troublesome.
I can't do anything secretly.
Why do I have to run away?
Bells are for people who are chasing.
My arms.
(My arms)
Something keeps pulling my arms.
Goodness. I have to find Jong Kook.
(All skill levels have been standardised.)
If I don't win today,
I'll have no excuses.
(I'll have no excuses if I don't win today.)
(Laughing)
(The complete opposites, Jong Kook and Seok Jin...)
Jong Kook.
(They meet for the first time.)
Even if he has wings, you have to avoid him.
(The wings are tucked under his armpits.)
Now that the situation is like this, I don't feel the need to run away.
Gary?
(Jong Kook avoids Seok Jin for now.)
Jong Kook.
Seok Jin, you must be happy.
I'm confident to go one-on-one now.
I think today's possible winners are...
As today's possible winner, I will go to London.
Seok Jin and Kwang Soo.
Kwang Soo, let's go inside.
(Seok Jin attempts a joint attack with Kwang Soo.)
Let's not upset each other.
You have to promise.
I promise.
How did I end up next to Kwang Soo?
Trust me, Seok Jin.
He went inside. He's in the room.
There's no other choice.
(Let's move.)
Since we all have our disadvantages,
let's take care of the people who will cause trouble first.
I think you'll be the one causing trouble.
Look at him. He's so confident.
How about a one-on-one battle?
Wow, Seok Jin.
Are you really sure?
- Unbelievable. - Oh my goodness, Seok Jin!
- Jee Seok Jin! - Jee Seok Jin!
I can't believe Seok Jin...
- This is impressive. - One on one?
Really?
We really won't help you.
That was so impressive even if Seok Jin doesn't do anything.
I feel like Jong Kook right now.
- It doesn't matter who I'm against. - You can't rip his name tag.
- Do you want to go against me? - You really can't rip his name tag.
If anyone besides Jong Kook is willing to go against me, go ahead.
Hey, Kwang Soo...
It's over if one person grabs Seok Jin and another rips his tag.
That's cheating.
(That's cheating.)
That's not cheating.
Collaboration isn't cheating.
- During official skill assessments, - Why is that cheating?
you know we always get the people with advantages out first, right?
- Get Seok Jin out! - I know.
- Get Seok Jin out first. - He's trying to fool you.
Are you going to let him fool you?
You guys are humans.
- Or fight us, then. - What I mean is...
Fight us right now.
Come at us.
I feel like I'm going to lose. Jong Kook, are you confident?
Regardless of my confidence level, I'll fight if I have to.
- Wow. - What a man.
This is a real men's fight.
- This is awesome. - He's so charismatic.
This is a fight between one with and without advantages.
I don't know what'll happen, but the last one-on-one match will be fun.
I'm curious.
I want to stay by your side today.
I hope things go well.
Shall we go for it?
I will always root for you.
Okay, I was watching for you.
Hey, Jong Kook.
(Come and see me for a second.)
Hey! Jong Kook!
Come out. I see you.
- Jong Kook. - Come out here.
Jong Kook, he is my new boss.
(Seok Jin is my new boss.)
(Laughing)
- Jong Kook. - Come out here, Jong Kook.
Seok Jin is my new boss.
Why are you using formalities with Jong Kook?
I'm still...
- a bit uncomfortable with him. - He's still difficult?
- He's still older than you? - Yes, he is.
Hey, Jong Kook.
Seok Jin is our boss.
Hey, you.
Come here.
(Have patience)
- Jong Kook. - Seok Jin,
- if you call him, he won't come. - Right?
(Surprised)
(They're frightened by Jong Kook's small movement.)
I'm not ready yet.
My mentality isn't like Jong Kook's yet.
That was the scariest moment in the last five years.
He was always on my side.
I got scared.
- I was so scared. - That was so surprising.
What a surprise.
Haha and Seok Jin formed an alliance.
The two are running around together, saying they'll rip our name tags.
- Kwang Soo, - What?
if we keep going on like this,
- We're finished. - we're finished, Kwang Soo.
Jae Seok, trust me.
(We can only trust ourselves.)
- Should I really trust you? - Trust me this one time.
Jae Seok, I'll keep my promise today.
How do I earn your trust? I'm sincere.
Do I have to live like this my whole life?
- Jae Seok. - I think you do.
What are you talking about?
Jae Seok, it's 2016.
Okay, let's go then.
(Jae Seok decides to partner with Kwang Soo after much deliberation.)
Thank you, Jae Seok.
- Maybe you're planning to... - What?
- You wouldn't do that, right? - No way.
- You did this to me before. - I'm not that kind of person.
I wouldn't betray you.
Let's walk on both sides for now.
- I... - What?
- feel much better with a partner. - I agree. Me too.
Seok Jin has too much of an advantage.
(Gary tries to join Jae Seok and Kwang Soo's alliance.)
Hey!
- Jae Seok. - Yes?
- Did you form an alliance? - Speak comfortably.
- It's not an alliance. - You made an alliance, didn't you?
If you come up now, you will regret it.
Are they forming an alliance?
Is it an alliance?
- No, it's really not. - Tell us if it is.
I don't know who he is.
No, really. I don't know him.
- Just tell us. - It really isn't an alliance.
Are you guys in an alliance?
- I was always with Seok Jin. - No, but...
he's an assistant I always kept with me.
- I want to be Seok Jin's assistant. - Seok Jin...
Seok Jin, are you the boss here?
- I'm the boss. - He's the boss.
I just came back from giving Jong Kook a scare.
- Really? - Do you want to see?
Hey, Jong Kook!
What are you doing over there? Why aren't you coming out?
Are your hands cold? Why are your hands stuck under your armpits?
Goodness, we really have to...
Seok Jin, would you like to catch Gary right now?
Should we catch him right now?
Show us how it's done, Seok Jin.
Should I catch him?
- Let's go one-on-one. - Seok Jin.
- How about going one-on-one? - Seok Jin, wait.
(Seok Jin, why are you doing this to me?)
- How about a one-on-one? - I'll be more helpful.
- Seok Jin. - Later.
I am at your service.
Well it's true he betrays easily.
I'll be of great help to you.
It's hard to choose.
He moves around so freely.
Seok Jin.
Jong Kook, are you watching this?
I've been waiting for five years to pay him back.
(My time will come.)
I'm not going to cut you any slack from now on.
They're trying to form an alliance.
- Who is? - Kwang Soo called Gary.
Kwang Soo, come over here.
He called me here. Isn't that allowed?
- You're the boss here. - You're amazing.
This is unbelievable.
- Really. - Finally,
- my time has come. - This is unbelievable.
Seok Jin is the boss.
He's amazing.
Please have mercy.
(In your dreams)
(Kwang Soo has no choice but to run away.)
This is the life of a boss.
He ran away?
Haha, go that way.
(They missed the opportunity to catch Kwang Soo.)
I missed him.
This is nerve-wracking.
I shouldn't go around with Gary.
(Kwang Soo is next in line after Seok Jin.)
I need to survive this.
This is something.
(Kwang Soo has 1kg of sandbag and a normal sized name tag.)
Okay.
I need to get Kwang Soo.
(Seok Jin needs to get Kwang Soo out to win the game.)
Hey, you.
(Kwang Soo was waiting for ambush.)
Do you want to try?
I can't keep running away anymore.
(Seok Jin and Kwang Soo are the biggest beneficiaries today.)
Why is it me?
You started it.
(They are both eager to win.)
(Kwang Soo pulls Seok Jin's shirt.)
What are you going to do?
(I got you.)
What? You had your hand here?
(Ji Hyo finds the two.)
(Gary and Haha also come to the scene.)
Whose side are you on?
Hey!
(Who will Gary, Haha and Ji Hyo choose?)
Whose side are you on?
I nearly got Seok Jin's name tag.
I nearly got his name tag.
Seok Jin!
(Kwang Soo is out.)
I got him. Okay.
Look at him.
I'm so tired.
- Kwang Soo is out. - Goodness.
- Kwang Soo is out. - You must be really proud.
- Kwang Soo. - You must be.
I know exactly how to rip that name tag.
I nearly got him.
Kwang Soo.
This is tiring.
Kwang soo is out.
- Kwang soo is out. - It's begun.
Kwang Soo doesn't deserve to win.
I got out.
- This is a dangerous place. - Seok Jin,
when we appeared earlier, weren't you relieved to see us?
Yes.
- You need to protect us. - Let's go.
(I'll be sure to pay you back.)
Seok Jin, I helped out too.
- Because I came out from that side. - Yes. That's true.
I helped out too.
Let's move on to the next target.
- How about Jae Seok? - All right.
And when we go after him,
don't do a thing.
- All right. - We won't do anything.
I think I heard my name.
(How will I get out of this?)
What's that over there?
(They are looking for Jae Seok.)
Seok Jin,
act like you're after Jong Kook.
(Is he after Jong Kook?)
As if you're Jong Kook.
Seok Jin.
(They are quick to surround Jae Seok.)
(Seok Jin gets a hold on Jae Seok's name tag.)
(Jae Seok tries to escape.)
Fine.
(Haha falls over.)
Come quick.
(Jae Seok is out.)
- No way. - We did it.
Great.
Jae Seok is out.
- Jae Seok is out. - What is this?
(Jae Seok could not win against the tight alliance.)
That was good.
Everyone against me.
Goodness.
Jae Seok is out.
- See! - Jae Seok is out.
I told him.
Next is probably Jong Kook.
(Next is probably Jong Kook.)
When Seok Jin comes to get me,
my last resort is a one-on-one.
(Jong Kook aims to have a one-on-one fight.)
My last resort is a one-on-one.
I can go up against Jong Kook.
I can win against anyone.
(I'll be waiting.)
- Kwang Soo. - You're here.
- What are you doing? - Jae Seok.
I'm knitting this scarf.
Please sit down. You need to knit a scarf.
You want me to knit a scarf?
(A scarf?)
I've never knitted before.
This is really not my taste.
I'm really bad at this.
I have more important things to do.
I need to take my revenge.
What am I doing here?
How am I supposed to make this?
It's complicated.
Place this over here.
(Knitting class begins.)
Like this.
Then pull this. You're doing well.
Like this?
After that, pull the string.
This is only the beginning.
(This is only the beginning.)
Now,
Running Man is teaching us skills.
(They both lack enthusiasm.)
Didn't I look cool walking out of this door?
If it were some other day, it wouldn't have opened.
(The luck is on his side today.)
But today, the door opened easily.
It wasn't locked. It usually is locked though.
I know.
- This is my day. - It really is.
- Who's our next target? - It's Jong Kook.
(Everyone says it's Jong Kook.)
This is great.
This spot is great.
- Jong Kook. - Yes.
Your turn is up.
I'm against four of you?
- What? - You four are together?
We said us four should be the last ones to survive.
(We're in the game alone.)
I'll go up against Seok Jin one-on-one.
All right.
- Isn't that all right? - You're amazing.
Good luck, Seok Jin.
Now is the only time to make up for the past.
- You're really amazing. - You really are.
- Let's go. - Let's go.
- I have no choice. - Don't move.
- You can't help. - We won't.
- Don't help. - Okay.
Even if I fail,
- I'll go down on my own. - Okay. I'll stay put right here.
I want to do this on my own.
Okay.
(Both players move to the battleground.)
- Go, Seok Jin. - Go, Seok Jin.
- This is best. - It's now or later.
(Jong Kook needs to be eliminated now or later.)
Seok Jin.
(I will win.)
This is impossible.
(They started off with complete opposite name tags.)
You're going to be blown away.
Hey.
Let's get rid of the strongest person first.
I think that's you.
Hey, Jong Kook.
(Will Seok Jin surprise us?)
What are you doing there?
Are your hands cold? Why do you have them under your armpits?
- Look at him. - He's the man.
This is quite something.
We look forward to your fight.
(Jong Kook has strength, I have a mini name tag.)
(We are on a level field.)
You only need to touch it.
(Jong Kook's enormous name tag is his weakness.)
What's happening?
(Seok Jin grabs Jong Kook's name tag.)
(Is this for real?)
What's happening?
(Seok Jin gets a hold of Jong Kook's name tag.)
(Will Seok Jin be able to win?)
(I've been the weakling for the past six years.)
(I will pay back for all that.)
(Which will it be? Jong Kook's strength or Seok Jin's advantage?)
(Who will be the winner?)
(He rips the name tag off.)
(Seok Jin rips Jong Kook's name tag off.)
(Goodness.)
Everyone,
I win.
(I did it.)
Everyone, I did it.
Thanks to the wings.
(Seok Jin won against Jong Kook.)
- Jong Kook, goodbye. - Bye.
Jong Kook is out.
(Jong Kook is out.)
- Jong Kook is out. - Let's go.
- This looks like a champion's belt. - It does.
You should take a photo.
- Should I? - Yes.
(Let's remember this day forever.)
(Haha and Seok Jin promised not to betray each other today.)
Seok Jin, is it today?
Should we be the last ones standing?
Let's cooperate today.
(Now is the time.)
- Let's take a photo. - Come here.
(Everyone joins to commemorate the day.)
Let's go with this.
- Is it this? - No, look at that.
One, two, three.
(What are you doing?)
Hey.
(Haha betrays Seok Jin.)
Seok Jin only has a name tag?
- He has nothing. - That's how it is.
That's just how life is.
I will go to London.
(He worked hard to protect his name tag until now.)
Come here, Jong Kook.
(I can't lose like this!)
I knew this would happen!
- Give it to me. - I...
- knew this would happen. - Grab it.
(Ripping)
Hold him.
- You guys! - It's over.
(I can't believe I trusted them.)
You guys, I can't believe this.
(Seok Jin had hoped to win in the standardised game.)
It's supposed to be today!
(Getting caught off guard always brings anger.)
(Gary and Haha's strategy)
Make him rip Jong Kook's name tag.
And then you, me...
and Ji Hyo can rip Seok Jin's name tag.
Then we fight amongst ourselves.
(Seok Jin was just a bait to catch Jong Kook.)
Oh my.
How am I going to face the other members?
(His face is getting hot.)
How will I face them now?
This is so funny. My stomach hurts.
Oh my goodness.
(Today was a good chance for a life-changing win.)
Let's get rid of the people who will cause trouble first.
I think that's you.
You, come here.
(Times when he had all the powers)
I can take on anyone right now.
Seok Jin, are you the boss here?
He's the boss here.
- Seok Jin! - He's really fooling around.
Jong Kook, are you watching?
(It is all useless now.)
- This is so funny. - My stomach hurts.
We should all know by now...
that there is no lasting friendship.
And no lasting rivalry.
But Ji Hyo, what I think...
is that you and I work well together.
- And Gary has gotten uglier. - Ji Hyo, think carefully.
Think carefully.
Ji Hyo, watch. Look at this.
If Gary and I attack you...
What's this?
- Gary... - Ji Hyo.
this is a nice combination, too.
(This is a nice combination, too.)
- Then let's all fight at once! - Okay.
- Let's go. - Okay.
Let's come together.
(Gary has a sandbag, a bell and a normal tag. Haha has a sandbag...)
(and a normal tag. Ji Hyo has a large tag.)
- Ji Hyo come here. - What are you doing?
Hey, still.
- What are you doing? - Still, you know what I mean.
Okay, I'll do it. I'll rip it myself.
- You have to rip his name tag! - I'll do it.
- I'll rip it myself. - You have to rip his tag!
(The Gary and Ji Hyo couple go in for a joint attack.)
(Haha defends his name tag by lying on the floor.)
You can't rip Ji Hyo's name tag.
(You can't rip Ji Hyo's name tag.)
(Haha suddenly changes position for a come back.)
(Ripping)
Ji Hyo, you should have ripped Haha's tag first.
I tried to grab Haha's tag,
but Haha elbowed me in my thighs.
Come on, Ji Hyo.
Goodness, my thighs hurt.
Gary is out.
I'm done.
- Haha or Ji Hyo will probably win. - You're right.
Oh man, I was used by Haha.
Wait, that hurts. Hold on.
I'm pretty good at this.
It's really nice.
I'm good at knitting.
You're really good at knitting.
Right? I'm talented.
You should open a knitting store.
Right?
- Jong Kook, you're very good. - I'll go shirtless for the poster.
That's a great idea.
Stay inside all day...
while wearing a tank top.
Sit here and knit if you want.
(Jong Kook's Knitting School)
I'm really good at this.
You have talent.
This is nice. You look very innocent.
Stop lifting barbells and just do this.
I have to put it in here again, right?
This is the beginning of Jong Kook's new life.
- Put it here... - I support you.
Jong Kook found his niche.
But really, old attachments are scary.
In that moment, how could you..
go on Gary's side like that?
I wasn't on his side.
How was that not taking his side?
- What do you mean? - Hold on.
- Aren't you being harsh? - Are you fighting me now?
(There is only one open spot for the fifth most skilled member.)
What are you doing?
What are you doing Do you think I'll fall for that again?
This is someone who will help you.
Things were always good when I partnered with him.
- That's Haha. - Wow.
- We won many times. - Whenever I partnered with Haha...
(They were always lucky and happy together.)
Are you in your right mind?
It's Ji Hyo.
Whenever we were partners, the result was always good.
(We used to be so good together.)
(Now they must collide for the one spot of most skilled member.)
You won this game before.
So you should give up and let me rip your name tag.
I'm too upset to let you rip my tag so easily.
What do you mean?
You're the one who took all the prize gold.
Ji Hyo.
(I can't give up like this!)
Why are you so strong?
She's so strong.
Look, she's bending my arm.
Oh my goodness.
(Haha attempts to rip Ji Hyo's tag with his teeth.)
You've never seen this method, have you?
You can't use your teeth like that!
(Haha is targeting Ji Hyo's oversized name tag.)
It's a first for me, too.
My hair is stuck on my name tag!
(My hair is stuck on my name tag!)
My hair is stuck!
Wait, my hair!
(My hair!)
(She can't even ask Haha to take her hair off.)
I'll take it off for you.
- I'll take it off for you. - My hair.
- My hair is stuck. - I'll take it off for you.
(Wait, I'll take it off for you.)
(Ripping)
Why is the name tag so big?
(Thanks to a large name tag with strong adhesion, Ji Hyo is out.)
Okay, let's go.
(Haha is the fifth most skilled member)
I was supposed to win today.
Did Haha win?
Haha, you are...
(I won!)
I can't believe this.
I will never trust you again.
Honestly, the most upset person here is Seok Jin.
Of course.
(I lost a golden opportunity because they betrayed me.)
- It was his chance to win. - It really was.
The fifth most skilled member...
is Haha.
- Thank you. - Congratulations.
I give the honour of this victory to Seok Jin.
None of this would have happened if not for Seok Jin.
Okay, we get it. Just take it.
Just take it.
Take this, please.
Make it a one night stay.
Haha you should go...
with your wife.
Make it your second honeymoon.
(This is why you shouldn't easily trust anyone.)
A mountain cabin invitation?
What is this?
It's a real party.
I'm the owner of this mountain cabin.
(The cabin owner's diamond necklace disappeared?)
My necklace disappeared, what do I do?
The diamond necklace?
Someone is collapsed in here.
It's a ghost murder case.
This is exclusive news.
This is the day.
The criminal is...
amongst us.
So is that why you stole the necklace?
(Solve the mysterious case and escape the mountain cabin)
The criminal is you.
(The Mysterious Mountain Cabin and Seven Detectives)