(2016, Shanghai)
(This is a beloved tourist spot famous for its old buildings.)
- This is amazing. - There's so much to see.
(The seven members have arrived at Nanjing Road.)
It's amazing.
- Look at that car. - They filmed a movie here.
Should we take a selfie here?
- Let's take a selfie. - Everyone, come closer together.
We need to take a photo of this.
- Let's take a selfie. - Get ready.
- Gary. - Let's take a photo.
One, two, three.
(January 2016, the seven members at Nanjing Road)
This is fun.
You're right.
(The seven are all together in Nanjing Road)
(90 years ago)
(1926, Shanghai, China)
(1926, the case of Shanghai Secret Society Y)
(The society was suffering from a lack of funds.)
(K, the leader of the independence movement in Shanghai...)
(was raising funds by diverting money from Japanese banks.)
(The Japanese army orders the arrest of K all over China.)
Come quick.
(The huge amount of funds K diverted are divided into six briefcases.)
(K was on his way to the Independence Army Headquarters...)
(in Shanghai with one of the briefcases.)
(The Japanese army continued to chase him,)
(and he was on the verge of getting caught.)
(K barely managed to get through the Japanese policemen.)
(Delivering the military funds safely could turn things around.)
(No matter what happens,)
(and whatever gets in his way,)
(he had to make it back to the Shanghai Headquarters.)
(Is this where his fight ends?)
(He's not afraid of getting arrested.)
(He's not afraid of getting harshly tortured either.)
(He just could not afford...)
(to lose this briefcase.)
(At that moment,)
(the fellow Independence Army soldiers appeared miraculously.)
(There is still hope!)
(K and the Independence Army overcame numerous crises.)
(They were not afraid to face anything to achieve independence.)
(However,)
(their mission was not...)
(easy at all.)
(If only we could get through them...)
(If only we could get past this...)
(They risked their lives for the great cause.)
(Nothing could bend their will of achieving independence.)
(If only they could get through this,)
(they could be so close to gaining independence.)
(They thought...)
(they almost had it.)
(K got arrested, but...)
(the five briefcases with the military funds...)
(were still hidden somewhere in Shanghai.)
(10 members of the Secret Society appear in Shanghai.)
(Yu Jae Seok)
(Lee Kwang Soo)
(Jee Seok Jin)
(Kim Jong Kook)
(Haha)
(Gary)
(Song Ji Hyo)
(Jong Tae Se)
(Ji So Yun)
(Park Ji Sung)
(On one rainy winter day in Shanghai,)
(a letter...)
(was secretly delivered to each of the members.)
"Dear members of the Secret Society..."
"Dear members of the Secret Society,"
"unfortunately, Mr K, who was delivering the military funds..."
"Unfortunately, Mr K, who was delivering the military funds..."
"got arrested by the Japanese policemen."
(Mr K got arrested by the Japanese policemen.)
"Collect all the funds Mr K hid in Shanghai..."
"and return to the Manchuria Headquarters."
"Agent J, the new director, must make it back."
"Agent J, the new director,"
"must make it back."
"More information on Agent J..."
"will be updated later."
"Come to..."
"the headquarters right now."
(Come to the headquarters right now.)
(Shanghai Headquarters of the Secret Society)
Fellows,
this is the headquarters.
(The headquarters look desolate.)
(There is one man waiting for 10 Secret Society members.
It looks so desolate.
Oh, hello!
- Welcome. Have a seat. - You are Captain.
It's been a while, Captain.
- It's been a while. - Have a seat.
- I will sit here. - I have a chair here.
Hello, I'm the director of Shanghai headquarters, Mr Go.
- You've travelled a long way. - Hello, Sir.
- It's nice to meet you. - Good job, everyone.
Good job, everybody.
It's not the time to clap your hands.
I'm sure you already heard about Mr K.
I will tell you briefly about how to obtain information...
- about the military funds. - Please tell us.
First, meet the informant in downtown...
and collect as many pieces of information as possible.
(Look for the informant with a red scarf.)
The secret code is "wo ai ni".
Then the informant will...
(The secret code is "wo ai ni".)
- do this. - That's my sign.
(In Shanghai, this sign been used for almost 100 years.)
It's my sign.
- It's mine. - Why is it yours?
It's mine.
- This has been around. - It's mine.
But when you receive a new piece of information, you must pay...
three cents in return.
- Three cents. - We have to pay too?
If you need a translation service,
look for the interpreter with a red umbrella.
Of course, you also need to pay him for the service.
- How much? - We have to pay them both?
- But we are on the same team. - Hold on.
We are trying to look for the military funds,
and we have to spend money?
We should save that money...
and use it for our operation.
This is all I can give you.
(It's going to be a long day, so drink up.)
You can complete different missions in downtown...
and earn your operation funds.
You must have already heard this.
No matter what happens, you must make sure...
Agent J makes it back to the Manchuria Headquarters.
- Who is Agent J? - Is it me, perhaps?
There are too many people whose name includes "J".
- It could be me. - Ji Sung has "J" too.
- Seok Jin has it too. - I have one too.
- Ji Hyo has it too. - I have it too.
- Jong Kook has it too. - Jong Kook has it.
- Agent J... - So Yun has it too.
- Right. - Who is Agent J?
It's not Kwang Soo.
- It's not me either. - It's not Gary.
- Us three are an exception. - It's not us three.
- Tae Se has "J" in his name too. - Right.
No matter what the sacrifices may be,
it is your duty to make sure Agent J returns to the headquarters.
- Don't forget that. - So...
what you mean is...
that some of us will be sacrificed.
That happens all the time anyway.
Now, set out to get the operation funds.
- Let's go. - Let's go.
- Let's go. - Let's go, Seok Jin.
Who's Agent J? It could be any one of us.
(The 10 members finally leave.)
(1926, Shanghai)
(Find the lost military funds and Agent J.)
(10 Members of the Secret Society)
(Chapter 1: The Secret Society Rises)
(Shanghai was the centre of independence movement at the time.)
(There are trams and old cars.)
There are cars too.
(The street scenes of Shanghai in the 1920s are recreated.)
It's unbelievable.
It's moving!
(He's fascinated.)
Of course, it's moving.
(Why are you acting like it's your first time at Nanjing Road?)
I didn't know it would actually move.
It's like we travelled back in time.
(Nanjing Road was as busy as Korea's Myeongdong back then.)
- There's a tram. - Gary, this is where they shot...
- the movie "Lust, Caution". - "Lust, Caution"?
(Many movies were filmed in Nanjing Road.)
Do you know who I am?
(Glancing)
I'll only reveal it to you.
(I'll only reveal it to you.)
I am...
(I am...)
Ha Jung Woo.
(Laughing)
(You went too far.)
He's the Hawaii Pistol there,
and I'm the Broad-shouldered Gangster.
(I'm the Broad-shouldered Gangster.)
Do you get it?
I'm the Broad-shouldered Gangster.
I think they give us the hints in Chinese.
Yes. That's why we need the interpreters.
But then...
- we need some cash first. - Right.
- Let's look for it. - There's something there!
- Where? - Isn't that something over there?
The booth, right?
(They need to complete this mission to earn some money.)
We are here for the mission!
(We are here for the mission!)
Hello.
"Wasabi Dumpling"
"Take turns eating dumplings. The one who gets the wasabi loses".
(This is entirely on luck.)
- I'll go first! - Okay.
- You lose if you get the wasabi. - We can conquer it together.
- It's okay. Go! - Go!
- It's between you and me, right? - Yes.
(Swallowing)
Okay!
It's delicious.
Hold on.
(Gosh)
(He's got it.)
All right.
Did you get it?
(Sniffing)
(The wasabi is so strong.)
(Kwang Soo is always unlucky.)
It's impossible for Kwang Soo to win this type of games.
(Jong Kook earns three cents as his operation funds.)
Let me go again.
Please let me try again with her. Do you know this game?
The one that eats the wasabi dumpling loses.
Go!
- Should I go first? - Go ahead.
(He grabs one.)
(How could this be?)
Hold on.
No way.
Maybe they all have wasabi in it.
- You really got it again? - Are they all filled with wasabi?
- Is it strong? - For real?
- Again? - I get the money, then?
My goodness.
(Ji So Yun earned it easily.)
- How could you pick it again? - I've got my money.
(I'm crying because I'm sad, not because it's stings.)
This area is too large.
(Park Ji Sung is collecting information on his own.)
I think I saw something over there.
(I think I saw something there.)
Here it is!
I have to move fast.
I'm tired.
(I'm tired.)
I'm doing this for Agent J.
I feel like my heart is failing me.
(You won't be out of breath if you talk less.)
"Master of the Ball"
"To complete this mission, throw the ball in the air..."
"and catch it after doing three turns."
It's three turns, right?
One,
Two...
Goodness.
How high should I throw the ball?
(He's reluctant but gives it a go.)
(It dropped.)
(Turning)
Hold on. Give me a minute.
(I shouldn't get this dizzy.)
I'm dizzy.
Oh, boy.
This is more difficult that I thought.
(The ball flies away.)
Where is it?
Where did it go? I'm so dizzy.
(He's not good at handling the ball.)
I need to turn really fast.
(I'm the Captain!)
(He does a triple Axel.)
Now it's gone that way.
(Now it's gone that way.)
I failed.
(Captain Park is kind of cute.)
Get set. Go!
(Haha versus Tae Se)
(Struggling)
(Tae Se is unstoppable.)
(Tied to two ends of a rope, the one who rings their bell first wins.)
Tae Se, ring the bell.
- Ring the bell. - He's playing with Haha.
- I will ring it in a minute. - Hey!
Haha is unlucky to play this with Tae Se.
(Will Haha be able to take his first step?)
- Wow. - Hey.
(He has superhuman strength.)
(Ringing)
- Hey! - Oh, my.
That wasn't even a fair game.
(Why did it have to be him?)
Get set. Go!
(Next up, Jae Seok versus Seok Jin)
The floor is slippery.
- What do you mean? - The floor is slippery.
I'm going to win.
Wow.
- I've got it. - No, I'm slipping.
(Seok Jin's almost got it!)
(There)
(He misses.)
It didn't ring.
- No, it didn't ring. - This is my chance.
(He's being dragged.)
(Jae Seok wins.)
I'm so upset!
I thought we were friends.
I had no choice.
Thank you.
(Jae Seok and Tae Se each earn three cents.)
(Kissing)
- Today's the day, my friend. - It is.
We can accomplish many things today, my friend.
(Two of them look for the missions.)
"Guess what the ingredients are in this Chinese dish in three tries".
There are three of them.
They look like pork or beef.
Let me try this one. Isn't this duck?
- Never mind. - I know what it is.
Try it. Try the smallest one.
It looks like a pig's ear.
It is a pig's ear.
You think so?
It must be. Try it.
(Is this really a pig's ear?)
Right? We've tried it before.
That's right.
- I told you so. - Give them your answer.
I got this one.
It's a pig's ear.
- I got it! - It's right.
(He guesses the answer.)
- Seok Jin. - I gave away the answer.
Give me a coin.
- Give me one too. - But this is all I have.
(They should have done their own missions.)
I have to win a game.
You don't have a single penny?
No.
I lost all the missions.
(They need coins to gain important information.)
I need to earn money quickly.
- Someone's coming out. - There is someone.
(The three of them try another mission.)
(Introducing the pride of China, Face Mask Changing)
(Flipping)
(The mask changed suddenly.)
It's Face Mask Changing.
(This is an ancient Chinese dramatic art that involves...)
He's perfect at it.
(changing masks in an instant.)
(Flipping)
(Once, twice, thrice and four times in a row)
(Ta-da)
That was shocking.
- My goodness. - That startled me.
(Incredible)
That's how you look.
(He's rather cute looking.)
(He sticks his tongue out.)
(Slapping)
(Surprise)
He has the mask on again.
- How did he get it back on? - How?
- How did he do it again? - That's why he's the master.
(Hopping)
(How did you enjoy my performance?)
I've never seen this before.
- You're incredible. - Where do you keep your masks?
(What could their mission be?)
Jae Seok joined later so he doesn't get a chance.
- Yes. - What?
(I'm excluded?)
It makes sense. You weren't here to hear the instructions.
Hello, Inspector Gadget.
Go, gadget arms.
I'm the Broad-shouldered Gangster.
He says he's a gangster.
I'm a real gangster.
I'll hit you with my shoulders.
(Be aware of Jae Seok's shoulders.)
I've only heard about such a gangster.
You're the Broad-shouldered Gangster.
Right. I'm the one.
- I have to be on my way? - Yes.
Gosh.
- Come back later. - Bye, Gangster.
(Bye, Gangster.)
- Bye. - Go, gadget arms!
See you later, Miss Seok Jin.
See you later.
"Miss"? Call me Madam.
- Sorry, Madam. I must get going. - I'm a Madam.
Here's your mission.
In what sequence...
did the two-faced mask appear?
- The sequence? - The two-faced one?
One, two, three.
(Ji Sung: second, Seok Jin: third, Haha: second)
You both picked second.
I picked a different one.
The correct answer is...
- second. - Yes!
(Correct answer is the second mask.)
I knew it.
How did you guys know?
(The mask appeared right after the first one.)
I counted how many times it changed.
I even counted how many times the fan was opened.
You counted 11 changes?
I thought it was nine times.
He held his fingers out.
- I counted 9. - It was 11.
There were 11 masks.
- But... - He's amazing.
I didn't think that would be the mission.
You just guessed, right?
- No, I knew that one for sure. - He's right.
It was white on one side and red or blue on the other.
(He's memorised the sequence and mask colours as well.)
That's incredible.
- Ji Sung, aren't you rich? - You must have won many games.
You must be rich.
(Ji Sung wins with his unbelievable memory.)
(It's time to look for an informant.)
I have to find someone who looks like an informant.
(The informant holds clues about Agent J and military funds.)
How would an informant look?
Oh my, I have no idea.
(Where would the informant be amongst the crowd?)
Oh.
Could it be that one?
(He spots a woman wearing a red scarf.)
They wouldn't just make us say...
"Wo ai ni" to nobody.
(Jong Kook searches thoroughly for an informant.)
(He spots the red scarf.)
Wo ai ni.
(He says the code word.)
The secret code is "Wo ai ni".
Then the informant will make a heart like this.
(The right person will show him a heart.)
Wo ai ni.
(He gives it a try.)
(He says the secret code.)
(A heart)
(Jong Kook finds an informant.)
(And so does Ji Sung.)
(He can buy information about Agent J and military funds from them.)
(They move to a place where no one can see them.)
(The cost of information is three cents.)
(Jong Kook acquires an important piece of information.)
(Ji Sung buys a piece of information for three cents.)
(What kind of information is inside the envelope?)
Goodness.
(It's a piece of information about Agent J.)
(What does this mean?)
It's in Chinese.
(It's another piece of information about Agent J.)
It's a man.
I should...
(The Chinese characters indicate a man.)
I should keep this with me.
I'll have to hide it for now.
I'll eventually find out who it is.
(He hides the information inside his jacket.)
(He pays one cent for translation.)
- Here. - Okay.
What does this mean?
(It's the same information as Jong Kook's.)
It means "Small eyes".
(It means "Small eyes".)
- Small eyes? - Yes.
- What? - What are you doing here?
- Yes? - What?
- What's up? - I want to know...
- what you're doing. - What do you mean?
Well...
(Wait a minute.)
- Wait. - Come on.
(Ji Sung has small eyes.)
No matter what,
you have to bring Agent J...
back to the Manchuria Headquarters.
(Agent J must escape with the military funds.)
(So far, the only information...)
(they have is...)
(a man with small eyes.)
(Who is Agent J?)
(Meanwhile,)
(Ji Hyo is not very lucky today.)
Hey.
(She gets inside a classic car.)
Where would everyone else be?
I have no money.
(I have no money, but I have class.)
Sir.
(She gets a free ride.)
I'll get off here, please.
(I'll get off here, please.)
(Thank you for letting me ride for free.)
(I got here so easily.)
Ji Hyo.
Jae Seok.
Where were you?
I couldn't get any money. So I'm on my way to get some.
(Wait a minute.)
(Does Jae Seok have money?)
Do you want to play the jujube game?
What's that?
Whoever eats the jujube first wins.
- Let's do it. - All right.
I already have some funds. I'm doing this only for you.
Thank you.
(Thank you.)
I won't forget this.
All right.
Okay.
(Whoever eats the jujube first with chopsticks wins.)
- Are you going to betray me later? - No.
I don't have any money right now.
All right.
(They have to eat this.)
Will you be in trouble if I quit and just leave?
Of course.
- Because I have no money. - Get ready.
Start.
(Start)
(They fight with their chopsticks.)
Where did it go?
(It's my jujube!)
Didn't you say...
you were going to let me win?
I said I'd come with you. I didn't say...
I would let you win.
(Jae Seok gets it first.)
(He puts it in his mouth.)
(Jae Seok wins.)
I trusted him.
How lucky I am.
- Oh, gosh. - I didn't think I'd win.
Didn't you say you'd give me a chance?
- Jae Seok. - I'm sorry.
I said I'd come with you,
but I never said I wouldn't eat it.
Jae Seok!
I trusted you!
I'll see you next time.
Okay.
(Let's go get some information.)
(Although he has money...)
I saw them around before.
(It's difficult to find the informants.)
(He found one!)
(Kwang Soo and Jae Seok fight to get the informant.)
(The informant chooses Jae Seok.)
That's not fair.
- Can she choose? - Yes.
Of course. She just did.
Thank you.
(Jae Seok buys the piece of information for three cents.)
(The information he received is...)
What does this mean?
(It's about Agent J.)
(He pays one cent for translation.)
Could you whisper it to me?
(Could you whisper it to me?)
(Agent J has small eyes.)
(There are multiple members with small eyes.)
- Do you know who it is? - No.
(They need more information.)
It's too difficult. The hint is too vague.
Is there only one Chinese hint?
This is the hint.
(Tae Se passes this mission at once.)
Thank you.
Excuse me. Wo ai ni.
(He finds an informant and gets the information instantly.)
(He wins...)
(the dice rolling mission as well.)
Thank you.
(He got three hints.)
This is my third hint.
(Tae Se is getting close to finding out who Agent J is.)
(Gary, on the other hand...)
The answer is eight.
- You're wrong. - Okay.
Ox tongue?
(He fails every mission.)
(Gary is a total opposite of Tae Se.)
I wouldn't know even if I heard it again.
(He tries hard,)
(but he keeps failing.)
My goodness, this is frustrating.
(Gary's...)
(last hope is...)
So Yun!
Ji So Yun!
Come here.
- Did you get any information? - Hey.
No. Do you want to play a game with me?
Have you played the dumpling one?
- Yes. - Have you?
- Yes. - Do you want to try again?
It'll be too strong.
- Did you win? - Yes.
Really? Let's do it one more time.
You go first.
(Whoever eats the wasabi dumpling loses.)
- I think it'll be this one. - Put it in your mouth.
(Chewing)
Don't hold it back.
- Okay. - Was it okay?
(Gary passed.)
(She chews it.)
- Was it okay? - Yes.
(Gary passed.)
Oh gosh.
(One of them contains wasabi.)
Just shove it in your mouth.
(She chews it.)
(This is the one.)
(I win!)
It's really strong.
Can she get some water?
It's okay.
You can take the money.
- Really? - Yes.
Thank you, So Yun.
This is my first money bag.
(Gary acquires money.)
It's strong.
It's really stings.
Wo ai ni.
(He finds an informant.)
(Gary buys the information for three cents.)
(It's a hint about Agent J.)
It's a man.
(He understood right away.)
Agent J is a man.
(Agent J is a man.)
(Information about Agent J is slowly being revealed.)
One, two, three.
Why are you doing this?
- I win! - No!
- Yes! - No!
(In order to find out who Agent J is...)
Yes.
(They need to get more hints.)
(The Secret Society has to find out who Agent J is.)
You can't lose this to anyone.
You must guess one of the ingredients.
(They must help Agent J escape with the military funds.)
(While they are busy finding hints,)
(Mr Go appears.)
Wait here.
I heard something's going on here.
What?
- Pardon? - Something will happen here.
- Shall I wait here? - Yes.
- Wait. - I need all the members.
(All members were called by the headquarters for emergency.)
What's going on?
- Broad-shouldered Gangster. - Fellows.
(Kwang Soo and Jae Seok are here too.)
You're Broad-shouldered Gangster?
- What? - Broad-shouldered Gangster.
Please wait here.
Aren't we a secret society?
We are out on the open street.
- We are out on the street. - Over there.
What's that?
They're wearing white.
(What's that?)
(What is it?)
(They are Japanese police officers.)
They are police officers.
They're Japanese police officers.
- What's going on? - They're policemen.
(The policemen are...)
(coming in from...)
(all directions.)
- Don't look at them. - What's going on?
Act natural.
Stand up straight. Look natural.
(They are coming nearer.)
He has something is his hand.
(What's happening?)
Why? Is there a problem?
(A dire situation)
We're in a tense situation.
They suspect me as...
We all should be careful.
Hey!
(Will they be able to rescue Agent J?)
(Chapter 2: The Target)
A suspicious...
- Look over there! - What's that?
(What is it?)
What is it?
(What challenge will the Secret Society face?)
- They're wearing white. - What's going on?
- They're wearing white. - Who are they?
- They're policemen. - It's the Japanese police.
(A group of men start to swarm the streets.)
(The Secret Society's biggest enemy, Japanese police)
- It's the Japanese police. - Why are they here?
- We must look suspicious. - We look too suspicious.
Be careful with your hat.
Act natural.
The Japanese policemen are here.
- Look away. - They're the police.
Act natural.
Cross your arms and look natural.
Why are the police...
- They're carrying something. - It must be something of worth.
He has something in his hand.
- Let's steal it. - They'll make an announcement.
See? Look.
(If you spot the Secret Society, report to the police immediately.)
(Those without an ID will be deemed as a member and will be arrested.)
The information that says...
the Independence Army arrived in Shanghai must have leaked.
- What? - There will be random inspections.
(The Japanese police will run random inspections to catch the members,)
- They'll be running inspections. - They'll run random inspections...
and if you don't have an ID card, you will be arrested.
- An ID card? - Yes.
Fortunately, I know a place that can forge fake ID cards.
- Really? - We need to forge our ID cards?
That means we have to spend money again.
On the ground floor of that building...
- is a person that can forge IDs. - How much does it cost?
It will cost five cents.
Lend me some money. I'll pay you back.
- Me too. - Lend me just two cents.
- Just two cents. - Me too.
That'll be enough for me.
What is that?
(A prison car appears in the middle of a street in Shanghai.)
What is it?
Is it a prison?
If it's a prison...
The police are over there.
(Without an ID, they will be locked up in the prison.)
(Startled)
- They're on their way here. - We need to hide.
They're right.
- The police are on this street too? - Over there.
Let's just go. Act casual.
They're coming this way.
- They're coming. - It won't work.
They've noticed us.
I can't be caught this early on.
(He runs across the street.)
I need to go that way.
But they're so many policemen on that street.
I...
(He needs money in order to forge an ID.)
I could get caught while trying to earn money.
Ji Sung, where are the games?
I'm looking for the games too.
Ji Sung, come over here.
So Yun, do you know what game it is?
(The Elephant Wrestling game)
Oh, no.
I'm going to lose this against you.
(Let's try it first.)
I can't believe I'm playing this game with Ji Sung.
It's an honour.
What am I doing here?
Get ready.
Get set. Go!
(The game begins.)
Oh, my. So Yun.
(Pulling with all her might.)
You are so strong.
I can't move.
(Korea's best female footballer vs Korean Captain)
This is hard.
(She doesn't lose easily against Ji Sung.)
Goodness.
I'm sorry.
(Ji Sung wins the game.)
Oh no.
I couldn't possibly win.
Ji Sung wins.
(They're both out of breath.)
(Ji Sung is already out of breath.)
Oh, my.
I'm sorry that I had to do this.
- That was so hard. - Thank you.
I'll give you one.
- Thank you. - You're welcome.
- Hide it well. - Now we need to go buy the ID.
It's the police. We need to hide.
Oh no, my money.
(She can't afford to drop a single penny.)
I should run.
(As Jae Seok tries to steal Ji Hyo's money,)
(So Yun pickpockets Jae Seok.)
Excuse me, So Yun.
How could you?
Are you really going to steal from me?
(Jae Seok's tries to steal again.)
(So Yun attempts again as well.)
Wait. What do you...
What do you think you're doing?
I learned it from you.
(I learned it from you.)
You shouldn't have learned to steal.
- Broad-shouldered Gangster. - All right, then.
Which way do I go?
Gary, do you have money?
No, I'm only going to check the place out.
Don't lie. I know you have money.
- Everyone, Gary has money! - Give me an ID card.
(He pays five cents to forge an ID card.)
Where is Gary?
I think he went to buy the ID card.
I know.
(The shop is full of customers.)
(Will they be able to outrun the Japanese police?)
Jang Hui Gun?
Oh, Gang Hui Gun.
(Gary manages to forge an ID.)
(He pronounces his name in Chinese.)
(He repeats it slowly.)
Are you sure that's the name you want to take?
You should change your name.
It's okay.
Why did you take that name?
- Goodness. - Goodness.
(He pronounces his name in Chinese.)
"Yu Ja Shik"?
(They both manage to forge IDs.)
It's a relief.
- Oh, my. - This doesn't make sense.
- We can't possibly make it. - Stop whining and just do it.
You need to look around.
Goodness.
Run around! Why do you think we're in Running Man?
- Gosh. - Well they at least need to...
tell us something. We don't know anything at all.
- How can we possibly... - When have they told us anything?
- Really! - Oh, my goodness.
There's something fishy about this.
Now I can relax.
(The Japanese police has reinforced the search.)
- Kwang Soo. - Yes?
- Something is not right. - Why?
Well, you know...
Did you get an ID card?
Yes, I did.
Spare me a cent.
I don't have any money left.
(The icon of misfortune is penniless.)
I don't have a penny.
- You don't have an ID? - No.
(Jong Kook holds on tight.)
(What are you doing?)
What are you doing?
Let's see what would happen.
(There is a horde of police just ahead of them.)
I can't be caught now.
Jong Kook, don't you remember how...
I helped you out earlier on?
(Something caught his eye.)
Hey!
(Look here!)
Jong Kook, you must be drunk.
- I'll take you home. - Officer!
You drank too much.
- Officer! - Why are you doing this to me?
(We're on the same team.)
He's gone.
I'm just curious what will happen.
Don't do this to me.
You can't do this to me.
- Hey! - You must be really drunk.
Officer...
(Kwang Soo forcibly seals his lips.)
(The Secret Society tries to outrun the police.)
(But the police keeps searching.)
They're all over the place.
(The police asks for her ID.)
Are you hitting on me?
(Are you hitting on me?)
Unfortunately,
I'm seeing someone every Monday.
Why? What's the matter?
The police are everywhere.
It must be the joint regulation period.
- That's a familiar word. - Isn't it?
(The Secret Society will be tied down if this goes on.)
No, I'm not.
(The Secret Society will be tied down if this goes on.
(Meanwhile, at the Shanghai Headquarters)
(A message from the Headquarters)
A message?
What does it say?
Dear Mr Go, director of Shanghai Headquarters,
we have obtained a piece of discreet information.
We have found out that there is...
a spy within the Secret Society.
(A spy?)
The spy's name includes J and S.
In order for Agent J's safety...
(On top of the Japanese police, they have a spy now.)
(Agent J needs to be protected, and there is a spy.)
- We're in trouble! - What's wrong?
Jae Seok, there's intelligence that there's a spy among us.
- What? - There's a spy.
We have just obtained information...
that there are letters J and S in the spy's name.
(The initials are the only clue.)
J and S?
(If it's a J and S...)
Could it be Ji Sung?
What?
J and S?
(The others need to know this too.)
- Did you hear? - What?
There's a spy among us.
The spy's name has the letter J and S.
Although my name carries those letters, I'm not the spy.
- Me either. - You are the spy.
You look the most suspicious.
(Ji Sung was previously a spy.)
- You look suspicious. - It's not me.
Park Ji Sung, Jee Seok Jin, Ji So Yun,
Jong Tae Se, Yu Jae Seok and Song Ji Hyo.
There's a spy among us?
(Who is the spy?)
- Why? - What were you talking about?
The initials are J and S.
Didn't you hear?
- The spy? J and S? - Yes.
Well, it's not me.
It might be you.
- Stop acting. - It's not me.
You must be relieved you're not suspects.
You can't be Agent J or the spy.
- No. - That's right.
I can be neither of them.
- We're not. - You can't be the spy.
- You're right. - Are you the spy?
You look suspicious.
- He must be Agent J. - Agent J.
He's more likely to be Agent J.
Ji Sung is the spy!
Really.
- He's sneaky. - It makes sense.
It makes sense.
It makes perfect sense.
- It's perfect. - People who look alike...
He's actually very sneaky.
They look alike.
I've been a spy once, so...
That's why you can do it again.
You can do it well.
Why do they think I'm the spy?
If I go alone, they would suspect me again.
The tone of his voice changed completely.
You know how he is when he acts, right?
I saw it.
- He pretends to be relaxed. - Right. I saw it.
(Ji Sung is suspicious.)
Hold on.
Isn't he wearing a red scarf?
I think he is.
Hello.
Wo ai ni.
(He makes a heart with his fingers.)
(Jae Seok meets the informant.)
Thank you. Thank you.
What's this?
(It's a map.)
It's a map.
Wait.
(It's the map of downtown in Shanghai.)
I will briefly tell you about how to obtain information about the funds.
Tell us quickly.
You must make sure Agent J makes it back to Manchuria.
- Who is Agent J? - Who is Agent J?
Is it me, perhaps?
(Their mission is to find the funds and to ensure Agent J's return.)
I almost missed this.
(They can check the location of the funds with the building number.)
30-1.
30.
It's across the tower.
I have to find the highest building.
That's the one.
That one.
It's that one, right?
(This is the location of the military funds.)
(Jae Seok enters the building where the funds are hidden.)
It's not here.
This is 30-1 though.
Oh!
I found it.
(He just needs to find four more briefcases.)
(Ji Sung also gets the information about the briefcases.)
Let's see.
One?
(Ji Sung also gets the information about the briefcases.)
So it's...
(He runs.)
This used to be a school.
Is it here?
It should be somewhere around here.
It's this one.
(There it is!)
(Ji Sung gets the second briefcase.)
It's money!
(If Ji Sung is Agent J, the funds will go to the Secret Society.)
(If he is the spy, the funds will be lost.)
I need to meet the other members.
(What is his identity?)
2-1. Should I go this way?
(The other members also find out the location of the briefcases.)
I have to go really far.
(Seok Jin got the map from the informant too.)
What is this?
39-2?
- Seok Jin! - He must have found the money.
Seok Jin!
Why are you running away?
- Hey! - He's betraying us.
Look at him.
Where is he going?
We should help each other.
(Is Seok Jin the spy?)
This is life.
This is life, you know.
They are all looking for the briefcases.
Are those the military funds?
(The location of the military funds are being revealed.)
Why is the spy not taking any actions?
(Agent J doesn't know that he is the Agent J.)
The spy must do something...
to get in the way.
The spy is lying low. Nobody got eliminated yet.
Why is he doing that?
The spy must have his mission.
(Perhaps he's waiting until all the funds are gathered?)
Kwang Soo, come here.
Right now,
you, me,
Gary and Jong Kook are...
neither Agent J nor the spy.
Our names don't include the letters J or S.
We are neither of those because our names don't include J or S.
He's on our side. He's our comrade.
- We have to be on the same side. - We are comrades.
Let's share the hints then.
- Let's share the hints. - I got one.
- Did you get a map? - I didn't get it yet.
There he is.
(What will their first shared information say?)
What does it say?
"Claim all the funds,"
"take the car at the designated location,"
"cross the bridge at the appointed time..."
"and go to Manchuria."
- A bridge? - There's a bridge.
- Bridge! - There's a bridge.
Let's head towards the bridge.
- Oh, that bridge. - That bridge.
I saw the bridge before.
- Where is it? - It's right over there.
- Let's go there. - We have to go there quickly.
Let's look for the bridge.
It's here.
Seok Jin...
This is it.
- Is this the church? - Hold on.
It said "the end of the bridge".
The end of the bridge?
We don't know which end it is.
- Let's cross it first. - It must be the other end.
This is the country border, so you can't cross it.
What?
That's even stranger.
- That's strange. - How can we cross it?
This must be it.
This must be the bridge.
We have the key, and we found the bridge.
Where are you going?
I came because I saw you.
(The four and So Yun meet.)
Do you have money? How much do you have?
- I have four cents. - Join us.
That makes six cents.
- What? - Six cents.
- Wo ai ni. - Wo ai ni.
Wo ai ni.
Gosh. Hurry up.
How much do you have?
Just give us one cent.
Kwang Soo, you said you have one. Take it out.
- Put them together. - Don't let her read it.
(What did you say?)
Only one of us four can read it.
I am sorry, So Yun.
We will read it and tell you the hint.
- I think I'm tricked. - This way, we'll get more options.
Thank you.
- Thank you. - It's really long.
It's not something we can figure out on our own.
We need an interpreter.
Isn't that a surname?
- Kang? - Isn't it "left"?
- So Yun, give me a cent. - It's the letter "bang".
- Please give us one more cent. - You don't have money?
No. I only have one.
- I... - Lend us some money.
Since So Yun has money,
we are sorry, but...
- We are sorry. - We're taking all her money.
We will give you our hint.
Give it to us if you are not the spy.
- It will prove that you're not. - It will prove it.
- It will prove your innocence. - You can prove it.
It's obvious that you are not Agent J.
- She's not. - This is how you rob money.
- No. - We are not robbing you.
- Please. - We will pay you back.
- Wo ai ni. - Where are you going?
(With So Yun's money, they afford another interpreter.)
(I'm coming too.)
Please read it.
(What does the hint say?)
"His wife..."
"has worked..."
"for a TV station."
It applies to both Ji Sung and Jae Seok.
Seok Jin's wife used to be a stylist too.
She was a stylist too.
(Who is Agent J?)
- It's either Jae Seok or... - Everyone knows that...
Ji Sung.
Ji Sung can be the one.
It's confusing.
(Among the six people, who is the spy?)
Then is Jae Seok...
the spy?
(Is Jae Seok the spy?)
There is a good chance.
Most likely it's either Jae Seok or Tae Se.
I think it's one of them.
Isn't the spy's mission to rip Agent J's name tag?
Isn't that the spy's mission?
(People keep wondering about the spy.)
(Meanwhile, Jae Seok gets out with the briefcase.)
Hey.
What are you carrying?
This is...
This is the funds we are looking for.
- Come here. - Let me see it.
- Seok Jin. - Yes.
(The police might see them, so they hide.)
- I think... - Aren't you the spy?
Your name includes J and S too.
Your name does too.
I know that I'm one of the suspects.
But I think...
it's either Ji Sung...
Yes.
Or Tae Se.
I think one of them is Agent J and the other one is the spy.
I agree.
Let's open that briefcase.
Show me what's inside.
No, I can't do that.
- I'll take a quick look. - I can't tell you any more.
I can hear the plastic coins in the briefcase.
I found this as everyone was suspecting me.
- Right. - I endured Jong Kook's abuse.
You know what he did to me?
Let's eliminate Jong Kook.
(Let's eliminate Jong Kook.)
Wouldn't that make us look like the spies?
What if we act like the spies?
We can just do it.
- Wait. - What do you say?
That's a very good plan.
We are not the spies, but we can act like the spies.
Since we are already being suspected,
- let's act like spies. - Let's do this.
- Let's eliminate Jong Kook. - First, let's target the four.
(First, let's target the four.)
That's a great idea.
Let's get a revenge.
- I really... - Gary, Haha,
Jong Kook and...
- Kwang Soo. - Kwang Soo.
Let's rip their name tags first.
Okay.
- Team Yu Jee. - Team Yu Jee.
It means "to maintain".
Let's maintain our friendship.
- Team Yu Jee. - Team Yu Jee.
- Cross! - Cross!
- Let's maintain... - Let's maintain...
our friendship.
- Let's maintain our... - Let's maintain our...
- trust. - trust.
- Gosh... - Let's eliminate them.
They must be together. There they are.
- Where? - There is someone.
I should rip it right away.
Haha and Kwang Soo are there.
Don't we have to rip Jong Kook's name tag first?
Gosh.
But they are together right now.
- So it's hard to target them. - They are always together.
Where did you find that?
What do you mean where?
I got the hints and worked hard to find it.
What is that?
What's what?
(Let's talk.)
(Does he think I am the spy?)
(The game is over.)
J.
- Yes. - J.
Let's get you out of here.
(What? I'm Agent J?)
Let's escape this place.
Look. His eyes are tiny.
It's even worse when he takes off his glasses.
Take your glasses off. Come on.
- I really... - His eyes are so tiny.
I...
Honestly, you think those eyes are not small?
- They are bigger than mine, - I...
- I am confused. - Let's compare the size.
- His are smaller than mine, right? - Hey, come on.
Why are you coming near me?
No. Let's just compare them.
- Don't be like that. - Come one.
Let's compare objectively.
- What are you trying to do? - Take your glasses off.
Why was your hand near my back?
Am I Agent J?
- Hey. - He's Agent J.
- Jae Seok. - It is him.
You must be Agent J.
- I'm sorry, Jae Seok. - Wait, hold on.
Don't come near me.
Excuse me.
Tae Se is the spy.
What's in your hands?
- I got a hint. - It's Ji Sung.
I don't think he's the spy.
He keeps sharing the hint.
- What is it? - What does it say?
- Hey. - What is it?
- This is... - Let's ask the interpreter.
Hello. Please translate this for us.
Show him.
What does this mean?
"Agent J can run very well on grass."
- He can run on grass? - Yes.
He must be a football player.
- Yes, it's a football player. - It's Ji Sung then.
- It's Ji Sung. - It's either him or Ji Sung.
Has your wife ever worked at a broadcasting station?
- It's not him. - It's Ji Sung.
It's not you.
- But he's the grasshopper. - He is.
(Excuse me. I'm the grasshopper.)
- A grasshopper hops on the grass. - Oh.
So it could be Jae Seok.
Grasshoppers hop on grass.
They both fit the description so well.
(I'm Captain Park of the football field.)
(I'm the grasshopper who lives on grass.)
(I'm the impala who sprints across the field.)
- His nickname is grasshopper. - And they hop on grass.
- It could be him. - Agent J is Ji Sung.
- It's dangerous here. - So Yun!
- Let's get out of here. - We are narrowing down...
to Jae Seok and Ji Sung.
One of them has to be Agent J.
Jae Seok might be the spy.
- Seok Jin. - Gosh. You...
- need to be careful. - Jong Kook's hand went for my back.
- Yes, I saw. - My goodness.
We have to...
- make a move or they'll get us. - We have to get their name tags...
- before they get the chance. - If it turns out we're not spies,
- they'll just say "You're not it." - "You're not it."
- "Sorry". - That's it.
Jong Kook will say, "Why were you acting suspiciously then?"
"Why were you on your own?"
He suspects me when I go off on my own,
but when I'm with him, he says I look at him in a strange way.
Jong Kook is the problem.
Let's get started.
(Let's get started.)
We shouldn't stand out.
(They begin their hunt!)
Let's execute our plan.
Okay.
Let's get Kwang Soo first.
(Their first target is Kwang Soo.)
Are there any more missions left?
Kwang Soo.
- Do you have any money? - What?
Do you have money?
What money? I have nothing.
You don't have any, do you?
You should look in places like this.
Kwang Soo.
Do you have...
- any briefcase... - Hold on.
(They got him on one try.)
I'm sorry.
Here you go.
We're not spies though.
- I'm not the spy. - Remember that.
- Why did you rip my name tag? - So we can protect ourselves.
- What? - You guys were doubting us.
- When did I... - Go away.
(How could you?)
(He kicks them out of frustration.)
(Kwang Soo is out.)
One down.
Let's just rip all their name tags.
- It's okay if we lose near the end. - Let's just do it.
How could they doubt us?
- Don't worry about losing. - You're all doomed!
- We are out of control. - We are.
- We are out of our minds. - We are out of our minds.
I'll seriously rip all their name tags.
We have to start now.
- Let's get started. - It'll never end otherwise.
Look. It's Tae Se.
Tae Se.
I thought you shouldn't go around in groups.
We're not a group. I just bumped into him.
Where is Ji Sung?
I have no clue. I didn't see him at all.
I don't know what to do.
I think Agent J is either me or Ji Sung.
It's either of you, right?
Yes, probably.
(He approaches Tae Se.)
What's in your briefcase?
Try shaking it.
It's just coins.
(He hesitates.)
- You had the same thing? - You as well?
Then...
Agent J is...
What? wait a second.
(Ripping.)
- I'm sorry. - I'm sorry.
- Are you okay, Tae Se? - I'm fine.
- We have to leave. - Let's go.
They'll get suspicious again.
- Did you bring everything? - Yes, I did.
Seok Jin, you've got the other one, right?
We have to get Jong Kook.
Yes, we need to get rid of him.
- Dreams come true. - Good job.
Great job.
(Our next target is Jong Kook.)
(Jong Kook is meeting Ji Sung.)
Hey! Where did you find it?
- In that building. - What?
It was one the second floor.
We've found all the briefcases then.
- Have we? - Yes. Haha!
- Yes? - We found all the briefcases.
- Ji Sung found the last one? - Yes, the fifth one.
Let's see how things are going.
You thought I was the spy, right?
No. I'm just focusing on protecting Agent J.
Be careful.
I told you I'm not the spy.
Be careful though.
I trust you. I do.
The policemen are coming this way.
Ji Sung must be the spy, right?
Gosh. This is a hostile situation.
I wouldn't have acted this way as a spy.
There's a very high chance that you're the spy.
- Me? - Yes.
- Gosh. - You're acting very suspiciously.
I'm not the spy. I swear.
I'm really not the one.
I don't know what to do.
I'm so confused.
(Who should I trust?)
Hey, Jae Seok.
- Let's not dissolve our plan. - Wait. Time out!
Time out. Time out.
Let's do this.
- What shall we do? - We are being too doubtful.
You know for sure I'm not the spy.
- I know. - Of course not.
Put the briefcases in the centre.
Gary and I will be in charge of them since we're not spies.
- All right. - We are neither spies nor Agent J.
- Okay. - All right.
We know that for certain.
Place them here. Trust us.
We'll take care of them.
You know we are not spies.
Let us take care of them.
- Good. - Let's put them in a car.
In which car will you put them?
Put them in this one.
Why did you just ask that question?
- Pardon? - Why do you want to know?
I need to know where they will be.
- Unless you are the spy... - Something is fishy here!
Doesn't Agent J have to collect all the briefcases?
- The thing is... - You can just send them away.
Why did you want to know where they will be now?
- Me? - Oh.
Something is not right.
(Jae Seok is at loss for words.)
(My intuition was right.)
(Who's the real spy?)
Load them on a car first.
- Okay. - Good plan.
It's either Ji Sung...
Those whose name doesn't include J and S should...
- put them somewhere. - Let's go.
Let's go on our separate ways.
I think it's Ji Sung.
I'm more confused now.
The hint about the grass is confusing.
(The identity of the spy is in question.)
Isn't it obviously Ji Sung?
He keeps on trying to lure people.
Yes, exactly.
That's what spies do.
Why are they all doubting me?
It's probably because I'm going off on my own.
Because of me...
There's no other way.
I need to start eliminating people.
(Seok Jin is the unsuspected spy?)
Jae Seok and I are the only suspects.
Don't look at me like that!
- I mean... - I'm not the spy.
Where have you been all this time?
When you were out of sight,
two people got eliminated.
I haven't even seen Tae Se or Kwang Soo.
I'm dying to know what happened as well.
(She's unsure.)
(Let's see.)
I should finish it off.
(What could he possibly mean?)
- Hurry! - Rip it off!
You're acting suspiciously.
I was startled.
Something's fishy!
I think Ji Sung is the spy.
We have no choice but to end it.
(Chapter 3: The Identity of "J")
Jae Seok.
The more I think about it,
the more certain I get that you're Agent J.
- I think so as well. - You must be Agent J.
But I'm not certain.
Ji Sung has been acting weirdly.
I can see in your expressions...
that you're not the spy.
You're Agent J.
It's you, Jae Seok.
- Seok Jin. - It's you.
- Be careful. - Okay.
(Jae Seok and Seok Jin maintain their alliance.)
My goodness.
(Why does Seok Jin completely trust me now?)
- Ji Sung. - Yes?
What are you doing? Why are you coming near me?
If you're planning to eliminate me by any chance,
subtitles ripped by riri13
I will not let you.
I just want to speak with you.
- About what? - We have to find Agent J, right?
- Right. - So...
Agent J has a child, and...
his wife worked in the broadcasting station. He's a man...
- Correct. - and has small eyes.
- These clues... - It's either Jae Seok...
or you, obviously.
- So we only have these four clues. - Yes.
And you still think I'm the spy?
No, I'm suspecting both of you.
So you think it's one of us?
Right. And the other one is Agent J.
That's what it comes down to.
This is what everybody is assuming.
If I start acting up, then I would look like the spy, right?
(Twitching)
Well... Yes, of course.
(He's very suspicious.)
If you're the spy, you'd better go and find...
another target.
I'll never let you eliminate me.
Hey. Is it you or me?
Who is this Agent J?
I have no clue.
I don't know if it's you...
- or me. - Do we not have any more hints?
You two make the decision then.
This game ends when Agent J is eliminated anyway.
You two just fight and end the game.
Agent J is not supposed to be eliminated though.
- He shouldn't. - I know.
Of course.
Where is Seok Jin?
He's acting weird.
What are you up to?
- I'm not being weird. - What are you doing?
I'm nothing.
- Seok Jin. - Hey.
- I'm not it. - Can I rip his name tag?
- Please? - I'm not the one.
- He is a suspect. - Right.
(Oh goodness.)
He is a suspect,
but he's the least likely to be Agent J.
- He could be the spy. - He is a suspect,
but he can't be Agent J.
- Seok Jin could be the spy. - We have to rip his tag.
No, don't do that.
- Why not? - Jong Kook,
- whatever we do, - Yes.
we just have to help Agent J escape.
- The rest doesn't matter. - Right.
- Oh, no. - This isn't good.
- Where is he going? - It doesn't feel right.
- Why is he running? - It doesn't feel right.
- It doesn't seem right. - Ji Sung, get him.
- Rip his name tag. - Well,
what do I have to do?
Ji Sung, you run fast so you should catch him.
- So Yun, we have to rip his tag. - Run!
We can't stand around.
(He runs away.)
(Is Seok Jin the spy?)
Poor Seok Jin.
(Poor Seok Jin.)
(What does he mean?)
- Rip his tag. - Go.
We can't just stand around.
Is it me? Who is it?
Just take me out then.
- I think you're Agent J. - Really?
That's my guess.
Are there any more hints?
I think you're Agent J.
- I think you are. - But you don't know for sure.
It's either...
you or Seok Jin.
So let's take everyone out...
except you two.
- We have to get Seok Jin. - Okay.
Let's go and find him.
- I think he's hiding. - What is it?
(Will Seok Jin turn out to be the spy?)
- Who is it? - What?
- Who is that? - Who?
That's Seok Jin.
(Jae Seok is nervous because he might be Agent J.)
- We need to catch him. - What?
He's running away.
(What is happening?)
Hey.
(Jae Seok attacks.)
Be quiet.
(Jong Kook is out.)
(Why did he take my tag? I was helping him.)
Take him away.
(Could it be?)
- I can't believe it. - Go.
Take that with you.
I wanted to rip your name tag from the beginning.
Jong Kook,
stay quiet.
(Is Jae Seok the spy?)
(Jae Seok is the spy!)
(All the members of the Secret Society got a mission.)
- "Dear Secret Society..." - "Dear Secret Society..."
"Dear Secret Society..."
"Retrieve all the funds that K hid..."
- "and return to Manchuria." - "and return to Manchuria."
(But Jae Seok...)
A spy?
(He was a spy.)
"You are a spy from a neutral state."
(He was given a mission to stop the Secret Society.)
"Take the military funds..."
"from the Secret Society..."
"and bring it to your state."
"If the Secret Society suspects you,"
"you should eliminate them and hide your identity."
(He has to take the military funds and get the Secret Society too.)
(Jae Seok was the spy.)
As a spy,
I need to be in their sight at all times.
They won't be suspicious then.
(He gets the military funds.)
I will take out the Secret Society.
(He plans to eliminate the Secret Society.)
Jong Kook. Kwang Soo.
Haha. Gary.
- So what if we act like spies? - Right.
We aren't spies, but we can act like spies.
Let's do it.
(Jae Seok...)
(manipulated Seok Jin.)
(Jae Seok had him eliminate Tae Se.)
Why did you just ask that question?
I have to know.
Something is fishy here.
- Load them first. - Okay.
All right.
(He makes a decision.)
I have to end it now.
(I have to end it now.)
(The spy is on the move!)
(He has to get rid of Agent J in order to win.)
(Is Ji Sung Agent J?)
(Or is it Seok Jin Agent J?)
(He doesn't have big eyes.)
(He has a kid.)
(His wife used to work for a broadcasting station.)
(He runs well on grass.)
(Who is Agent J?)
I have to escape with Agent J.
I knew this was going to happen.
I had to run away. I'm sorry.
(He still believes Jae Seok is Agent J.)
(Seok Jin forms an alliance with the spy.)
(They formed Team Yu Jee together.)
- Let's maintain our friendship. - Let's maintain our friendship.
- Let's maintain our trust. - Let's maintain our trust.
Let's get everyone else.
(Jae Seok urges Seok Jin to get rid of the Secret Society.)
(Seok Jin follows the orders.)
I think you're Agent J.
Ji Sung has been acting weird.
- Why are you two together? - Because...
- I'm probably Agent J. - I'm helping Agent J.
- Agent J! - Wait.
Wait for me. I'm not the spy.
Agent J!
(Seok Jin was completely blind.)
- Seok Jin. - What?
Why do you run away?
- They're trying to rip my name tag. - Why?
- Hey. - Why are you coming close?
I'm not the spy. Don't you remember the pact?
(He acts suspicious.)
- I know. - I won't rip your tag.
Why are you doing this?
- Why? - Get him.
- Get him. - Why are you doing this to me?
Get him quickly.
(Will Seok Jin clear up the misunderstanding?)
You are the spy!
(Seok Jin attacks.)
- What is it? - I'm not the spy.
(Everyone thinks he's the spy for sure.)
No. I'm not the spy.
He's the spy!
(He brings the attention to himself.)
He tried to rip my name tag.
- Really? - Yes.
- What is it? - They're trying to get me.
(Here's the real spy.)
Are you the spy?
I'm not.
Be careful.
I'm not the spy.
(I like to rip tags, but I'm not the spy.)
- Ji Sung. - Yes?
- Hey. - You could be the spy.
- Wait. - Anyone here can be the spy.
- All four can be spies. - I think...
- we could all be spies. - Right.
- Yes. - We could all be spies.
- Hey. - Be careful.
- We could all be spies. - That's right.
- Yes. - So Yun and I will have a match.
- Everyone, stay still. - Okay.
- Okay. Fine. - What do you think?
(Jae Seok will be at a disadvantage.)
- Oh, gosh. - Oh, my.
Don't you think it isn't fair?
- I'll use only one hand. - Let's go our separate ways.
- One hand. - Let's get separated.
(Jae Seok pretends to want peace.)
Let's get separated.
Let's not do one-on-one.
I understand how you feel.
(Seok Jin is saved by Jae Seok.)
- Gosh. - Let's get separated.
Who is it?
Am I Agent J? Who's Agent J?
(Am I Agent J? Who's Agent J?)
(Jae Seok needs to use Seok Jin.)
Oh, gosh.
What does the spy do?
We should have...
(He can't understand why everyone agreed to separate.)
We should've done the one-on-one match...
to get the spy.
If I rip Seok Jin's tag, people will suspect me.
(If I rip Seok Jin's tag, people will suspect me.)
Who is that?
It's Ji Hyo.
Ji Hyo.
(Jae Seok spots Ji Hyo all alone.)
Who is Agent J?
Is it me or Ji Sung?
(Is it me or Ji Sung?)
Are you trying to rip my name tag?
(Are you trying to rip my name tag?)
How did you know?
Did you get Kwang Soo?
- I did. - What?
(That's scary.)
- Did you get Tae Se? - Yes.
- Both of you are spies. - Correct.
(Seok Jin joins in.)
(They attack Ji Hyo.)
(Agent J, let's win.)
(They rip the name tag.)
(Ji Hyo is out.)
- I'm sorry. - Both of you.
- But we are not spies. - We aren't.
- We aren't spies. - We are just cornered.
- We don't know how it'll end. - Really.
- We might get attacked. - I'm sorry.
- This is why we got you. - Right.
Ji Hyo, you should go.
You'll understand when you watch the show.
I'm sorry.
(Seok Jin will be shocked when he watches the show.)
- We had no choice. - We need to end it.
- We have to. - Let's end it.
I don't know who Agent J is.
So Yun's coming. Let's get her.
Okay. Wait.
(Are they spies or not?)
(She's confused.)
Are you really not the spy?
All of you are such good actors.
- I... - You are...
- You are not a spy, are you? - No.
You are trying to bring me over here...
- to rip my name tag. - No.
Aren't you the one following me over here?
No.
Are you here to get me?
No, how could I...
Are you the spy?
- You are, aren't you? - That's right.
- I'm the spy. - What?
(That's right.)
(What?)
You keep saying I'm the spy.
I'm the spy.
Rip my name tag.
If I'm Agent J, you'll have to take all the blame.
- Rip my name tag. - Well,
don't come near me.
What will we do? The game won't end.
I'm not sure if I'm Agent J...
or not.
The spy knows his identity, though.
He does. But I'm not the spy,
so I'm telling you to rip my tag off.
But if I turn out to be Agent J,
everyone will blame you.
I can't let that happen.
I know. What are we supposed to do?
I am so confused right now.
I know.
Are you suspecting me or not?
- I... - You should join me.
If you are not the spy, I will go with you.
Let's go.
You are not trying to rip my name tag, are you?
No, I am not.
(So Yun gets persuaded by Jae Seok and hops on the train.)
There they are.
But I need one more cent to get this interpreted.
(He needs one more cent.)
- I... - You should bargain.
- They give a discount? - Yes.
- Really? - Ji Hyo got a discount earlier.
Talk to them nicely.
(Jae Seok fools her by talking about the coin.)
(What's Jae Seok's scheme?)
Don't give her everything.
(He gives her all the coins.)
- You can't give her everything. - What do I do?
(I got you!)
(While So Yun bargains, he rips her name tag.)
(He succeeds.)
(So Yun is out.)
I knew it.
Thank you.
So Yun.
I died.
- I... - Come here, So Yun.
- I had no choice. - You are unbelievable.
I had no choice.
I am sorry.
I'm sorry, So Yun.
- I knew it. - I'm sorry.
- I... - I am sorry,
- It's okay. - So Yun.
Go to the prison.
- You don't have to do this. - I will see you later.
See you later, So Yun.
See you later.
(So Yun is betrayed by Jae Seok and is eliminated.)
I'll see you later. I am sorry. I'm sorry, So Yun.
- Cheers, Jae Seok. - Cheers.
(Who will be his next target?)
So it's either me or Jae Seok.
Right. Agent J is one of you two.
(Ji Sung tries to form an alliance with Gary.)
I am not the spy.
Who is the spy then?
It could be anyone among the six of us.
Right.
It's either Jae Seok or me.
- But don't suspect me. - But look.
Seok Jin told me not to suspect him, and you told me the same thing.
- But now... - This is driving me mad.
- It's Ji Sung. - What?
You can eliminate me.
But I'm saying Ji Sung is the spy.
I am not the spy.
He is the spy.
- I am not the spy. - I was with Jae Seok...
- I can give him my back... - all day long.
- because I am not the spy. - I know Jae Seok well.
I am not worried about my back.
Can you do the same?
(Can Seok Jin show his back?)
I can, but I am afraid you will rip my name tag.
I just think...
Seok Jin might not be the spy.
I am not the spy.
But it's right to eliminate us one by one.
Right.
Someone has to eliminate people.
(Seok Jin attacks.)
(What?)
(Seok Jin attacks Gary fast.)
(He rips Gary's name tag.)
- I... - Why did you rip my tag?
I ripped it because...
(Is Seok Jin the spy?)
I was afraid that you'd attack first.
Why did you eliminate me?
- But I am not the spy. - Why did you eliminate me?
You are neither the spy nor Agent J.
- Why did you eliminate Gary? - I am not the spy. What?
- Why did you do that? - What?
Why did you rip my name tag?
Because he's not Agent J.
- Why rip mine? - That's why I ripped his tag.
He's neither Agent J...
- nor the spy! - Why would you rip my tag?
I am sorry, Gary.
- Grab him, Ji Sung. - Okay.
(Will Seok Jin get eliminated like this?)
Rip his tag.
(But if Seok Jin turns out to be Agent J,)
Hurry up.
(the Secret Society's mission could fail.)
(He rips Haha's tag.)
I ripped it first.
(Haha is out.)
I'm not the spy.
(With an incredible speed, he eliminates Haha.)
- Hey, I'm not the spy. - What just happened?
I got my tag ripped too, Gary.
Gosh.
- I don't care if mine gets ripped. - Okay.
But you are the spy.
I'm telling you that I am not the spy.
(Now only the spy, Jae Seok,)
(and the two Agent J candidates, Ji Sung and Seok Jin remain.)
Jong Kook, when did you get eliminated?
Both of you are eliminated?
Who ripped your tag?
Jae Seok and Seok Jin.
Jae Seok and Seok Jin are the spies.
Jae Seok is the spy for sure.
- What's up with Seok Jin? - He's not the spy.
Then why did Seok Jin eliminate me?
I'm tired.
(It's tiring to think about it.)
(He drinks the red ginseng extract.)
Drink it.
They kept sticking together.
- That's strange. - It's strange.
(The victims recover their health.)
- Right? - I hope Seok Jin is the spy.
- I hope he's the spy. - I hope he's the spy.
(Or he would look too stupid.)
(This man is hopeless.)
- What's going on? - Who's Agent J?
Seok Jin ripped Gary's and Haha's name tags.
Haha? Why?
I didn't do anything!
I just ripped their tags because they kept threatening me.
- You eliminated both of them? - Yes.
He eliminated both.
- Team Yu! - No!
- Yu! - Team Yu Jee!
- Cross! - Cross!
(They are together again.)
- What are you doing? - We formed...
an alliance a while ago, but he's suspecting me too.
Wait, aren't you the spy?
- I am not the spy. - Then why did you rip the tags?
- I just did. - Why would you do that?
They were attacking me.
Is it you?
I told you. I am not the spy.
I am not the spy.
That means he's the spy.
You could be the spy too.
I telling you with my right arm on my chest.
I can do that too.
I could easily do that too.
It's not me.
- Anyone can put a hand. - I just eliminated them...
because they were threatening me.
(It's a triangle of chaos.)
- Why did you rip them? - I ripped three name tags.
Why did you rip three name tags?
They were threatening me even though I'm not the spy.
So you eliminated the rest of them?
- Who eliminated them? - I didn't eliminate anyone.
Then...
- who eliminated them? - I...
- How would I know? - Who eliminated So Yun?
(Jae Seok tries to find out who is Agent J.)
I saw Seok Jin...
ripping the name tags of Gary and Haha.
Honestly,
(All right then.)
I saw him ripping Tae Se's name tag.
- You did? - Yes.
Are you really doing this to me?
He...
He ripped Kwang Soo's name tag.
(Seok Jin tells on Jae Seok.)
(Oh, my gosh.)
Are you really doing this to me?
You did it first.
So now, one of you is the spy.
We don't know that.
- Where is Jong Kook? - We did it to survive.
Where did Jong Kook go?
This...
Did you eliminate Jong Kook's tag?
(Many people seem to be missing.)
- I didn't eliminate him. - Did you eliminate him?
I didn't eliminate anyone.
- Did you eliminate So Yun? - No, I didn't.
Did you eliminate So Yun?
I didn't eliminate So Yun.
- You ripped Kwang Soo's. - I did.
Why did you rip Kwang Soo's tag?
Kwang Soo, Gary and Haha...
- kept doubting us. - Yes.
- But... - That's why we ripped the tags.
Agent J has no reason to rip the name tag.
I don't know. I just eliminated them because they threatened me.
He had to survive.
- I had to survive, you know? - He didn't want to go to prison...
and sit there with no purpose. Rather than going to the prison...
- Yes. - He would help the spy.
(He would help the spy.)
(What? What did you just say?)
(I didn't mean to say that.)
What did you do all day, Ji Sung?
(He changes the subject abruptly.)
You can't lie with those eyes.
(You are suspicious, Ji Sung.)
You think I'm a good actor?
You act pretty well.
Let's draw a conclusion.
Yes. Let's do that.
What do we do?
I really want to rip your name tag.
- You want to rip my tag? - I want to go with Jae Seok.
Then you will be helping the spy.
(Thank you so much, Seok Jin.)
No. He's Agent J.
I believe he's Agent J.
But I am not the spy.
Then should we rip his name tag?
(Easily persuaded)
What?
We are Team Yu Jee.
- Yu. - Jee.
- Cross! - Cross!
I think this is wrong.
- This is wrong. - I am so confused.
(He needs to hurry up.)
(Who is Agent J?)
(Is it Ji Sung?)
(Is it Seok Jin?)
(He just has to rip Agent J's name tag.)
- I am not the spy. - I am so confused.
- I am confused. - Or should I rip yours?
(Jae Seok changes the target.)
- Me? - Yes.
Then you two...
(Why are you targeting me?)
Look. I never said I should rip your tag.
That sounds right.
(Seok Jin goes closer to Ji Sung.)
Wait.
That's not it.
- That's not it. - It ends when he rips the tag.
- It's the end. - Right?
That's not it.
Think carefully. That's not it.
Then why did you say you will rip my name tag?
I just said it to end the situation.
(He laughs.)
You've been acting suspicious.
- You've been acting suspicious. - Hey!
- You are... - You said you trusted me.
Yu!
Hey!
You are suspicious.
He's such a nice guy. He can't act.
- I can't act. - How about me?
- You are an actor. - I'm...
- I'm an actor? - Let me ask questions.
- Did you rip Jong Kook's tag? - No.
- Did you rip So Yun's tag? - No, I didn't rip anyone's tag.
(Ji Sung is innocent.)
(Gosh, I'm not good at lying.)
- Did you rip Jong Kook's tag? - Yes.
(Yes.)
- Did you rip So Yun's tag? - Yes.
Come here.
(I got you!)
Wait!
(Jae Seok goes for Agent J's name tag.)
- Did you rip Jong Kook's tag? - Yes.
(Yes.)
- Did you rip So Yun's tag? - Yes.
Come here.
(I got you!)
Wait!
(Jae Seok goes for Agent J's name tag.)
Come here.
(Will Agent J get eliminated first?)
(Or will Jae Seok be eliminated first?)
(Ripping)
He's the spy!
(Jae Seok is out.)
My goodness.
He's the spy!
(They manage to eliminate the spy.)
- What did I say? - Wow.
Jae Seok is the real spy.
- Are you really? - That was so close.
(He almost had it.)
- Really? Are you really the spy? - Gosh.
- I almost had it. - Was it really you?
Gosh, that was so close.
(The Secret Society is victorious at the end.)
I was so close.
Seriously?
Yes!
For goodness' sake.
Is it time for me to retire as a gangster?
(Is it time for me to retire as a gangster?)
- How could you use me like that? - I...
- How could you? - I was after...
the reward money,
but you should use it for your country's independence.
- All right? - The funds will be used...
for a great cause.
Okay.
Please use the funds for Korea's independence.
- You took out Jong Kook. - Bye...
for now.
(Bye for now.)
Passion and romance
Are like blowing wind
(The spy makes his exit.)
(Provisional Government in Shanghai)
A message was sent from the Headquarters.
(A message from the Headquarters)
Dear Mr Go, director of Shanghai Headquarters,
attached is a portrait of Agent J.
Please supervise his safe return.
Agent J's name is...
Park Ji Sung.
(Agent J is Park Ji Sung.)
Please protect the man...
who will become the hero of our people.
(Captain Park was Agent J!)
Agent J, we did it.
We did it together.
I'm really sorry for...
- doubting you. - Don't worry about it.
I didn't think I'd be standing here.
Please don't cry on your way back.
All there is left to do is to make our way to Manchuria.
- Excellent! - Great.
(Laughing)
Code name, Agent J.
Let's put this money to good use.
Let's go, Agent J!
(The Secret Society accomplished their mission.)
I'm sorry for doubting you.
I thought you were the spy until the end.
Good job.
This is the end.
We have done it.
Well done.
(Agent J was the leader who was protected by everyone.)
The persistence of the Secret Society...
paid off as it contributed to the country's independence.
(A round of applause for today's winners)
We sent the military funds to where it was most needed.
Why are you here?
Why did you eliminate me if you were not the spy?
Why did you do that?
My goodness.
That's why we always eliminate him first.
Gary asked if we should take out...
- Seok Jin in the beginning. - Yes, right.
I should have listened to him.
I was worried he would text me...
saying "Why did you take me out?"
I'm sorry,
but you'll be the first one I'll eliminate next week.
- I agree. - You need to understand.
Please understand.
- I have no choice. - Let me have the honour.
I would rip your name tag even if you're on my team.
The two of them successfully completed the mission.
- Congratulations. - What a relief.
They're the winners.
We are all winners.
So Yun and Tae Se, say a few words.
I feel so bad for Tae Se.
Why did you rip my name tag so early in the game?
Couldn't you be a little more lenient?
- Well... - You should have been.
I wanted to be part of the climax.
He's learned a lot.
Give me just one more chance.
Then he'll eliminate us all.
Just once more. It won't be the same next time.
I had such a great time,
and I was happy to be on the show with Ji Sung and Tae Se.
I also had a great time with the Running Man cast.
But Jae Seok did scare me when he ripped my name tag.
(But Jae Seok did scare me when he ripped my name tag.)
I'm happy to have joined the show with the two football players.
You were glad.
I was happy.
I wish the best for Running Man.
- He didn't repeat after me. - Thank you.
Thank you.
Thank you to the three football players...
for sharing your time with us.
Let's give them a round of applause.
Thank you.
(Thank you for sharing your time with us.)
Someone is targeting your name tag...
on your way to the studio.
- Really? - We start now, right?
Who's after my name tag?
Oh, boy.
You scared me.
My goodness. What was that?
I'm so nervous.
I can't trust anybody.
Not even the cameraman.
What are you doing? Why are you doing this?
No!
(This is where they were headed to.)
- This is the future. - What is this?
Look at the scale of this place.
(The state-of-the art Running Man Laboratory)
(Using data from the last six years, we analysed members' skill levels.)
(We test everything from the cast's fitness to endurance.)
(Next week,)
(we decide on a winner...)
(who will leave a mark in Running Man's history.)
Are you crying?
(Tune in next week for the Fifth Official Skill Assessment.)