(Client A secretly contacts the Running Man staff.)
- It's nice to meet you.
-  Hello.
What do you think about Running Man?
I think it's about time for a transformation.
In other words, there must be a thorough change.
Jae Seok...
keeps working with SBS through Running Man.
He's very tenacious.
(He's jealous.)
And Seok Jin...
is just lucky to be there.
Haha is also barely surviving in this programme.
He lacks artistic ability...
and only works for commercial purposes.
Ji Hyo...
has good chemistry with Gary.
She tries to make Running Man funny through that awkward chemistry.
It will be funnier if Ji Hyo loses her mind...
and starts to love Kwang Soo.
You need such extreme elements on this show.
Family members gather together and watch TV on Sunday nights.
Then who will attract the viewers?
It's me. I will do it!
(I can attract the viewers for you!)
Who are they?
(The members encounter their worst enemies.)
(Who are they?)
(Mysterious people have come to teach the members a lesson.)
That's a foul!
(Screaming)
(What will become of the fate of the Running Man members?)
This is too hard.
(The Variety Avengers will teach the members a lesson.)
It's the Avengers.
So today, the guests are...
- the Avengers?
-  The set is very fancy, too.
- Avengers?
-  What are the Avengers?
Now,
the guests are here to attack you.
(They're here to attack us?)
Do we really deserve to be attacked?
Why do guests attack us every week?
Shouldn't we report this to the police?
How can we become targets every week?
Let's welcome the Avengers.
Please come in!
(Let's meet the guests.)
(Who are the Avengers?)
I will change everything.
It's me who can do that!
(What?)
(Is he sleeping?)
Is he Gyeong Gyu?
(The forefather of variety shows, Lee Gyeong Gyu)
Gosh, it's Gyeong Gyu.
Is he really Gyeong Gyu.
(This is a first time a guest has made an appearance by lying down.)
My goodness.
I've never seen anyone who lied down on stage like him.
(Goodness.)
(He shows off his slapstick humour.)
Hello!
(Screaming)
(Let's welcome the best comedian, Lee Gyeong Gyu.)
(Client A was Gyeong Gyu, the king of variety shows.)
He is the first person to appear on a show lying down.
He's the king of variety shows. It's Gyeong Gyu.
I didn't mean to come on stage while lying down.
I was just resting, and the platform suddenly started moving.
- Were you?
-  While you were resting?
- That's really funny.
-  Today's concept is predictable.
Gyeong Gyu is here today.
(Today's show isn't going to be easy.)
The good thing is, I think we can go home early today.
(Gyeong Gyu loves to finish work as early as possible.)
The first time in a long time.
He's not like that these days.
I guess I can eat dinner at home tonight.
- Thank you.
-  I'll eat dinner at home.
- Thank you, Gyeong Gyu.
-  No, you're wrong. It's lunch.
Can I eat lunch at home today?
(Gyeong Gyu's principle at work: "Eat lunch at home.")
It's 9:30am and you're saying we'll finish by lunch time?
Your aim is to eat lunch at home.
- Can you eat lunch at home?
-  We can have a late lunch.
- I've brought 6 people with me.
-  Who are they?
- They are my team.
-  So did you...
form a team for today?
- I did it by myself.
-  Variety Avengers, right?
(Variety Avengers are here with Gyeong Gyu today.)
- Get ready to meet the Avengers.
-  All right. Let's see.
Come on, Avengers!
- Please come out.
-  Come out!
(Who are the mysterious 6 that the king of variety shows enlisted?)
(Watch out, Running Man.)
- Who are they?
-  Amazing.
- Wow.
-  It's Lee Su Min.
(They are surprised.)
(Here comes the members of the Variety Avengers.)
(They are very popular and famous in variety shows these days.)
They are too tough.
(Team Avengers)
(The Running Man members must face powerful foes and fight.)
(Will they be able to overcome and win today's match up?)
- All right, Team Avengers.
-  Yes.
- You're here today with Gyeong Gyu.
-  That's right.
- What a strong team you have today.
-  Yes. You're right.
I'll introduce your personal rivals.
Who is Joon Hyun's rival?
All right. Well, Kwang Soo is his rival.
- Am I?
-  Yes.
- Kwang Soo's nickname is Giraffe.
-  Right.
Joon Hyun is an Asian black bear.
- Asian black bear.
-  Is he an Asian black bear?
I think this bear was raised in a zoo.
- He doesn't look intimidating.
-  I was raised by humans.
(He's not a wild bear. He's just a cute, cuddly bear.)
- I don't act fiercely like this.
-  He doesn't harm people.
- Please continue.
-  He's so kind.
He's from a bear farm.
(So he's not wild at all.)
He's farmed. Not caught wild.
- Not caught wild.
-  Okay.
- He's raised at home.
-  I don't eat anything...
- like salmon. I love bear food.
-  You love bear food.
- Because I'm farmed.
-  I see.
- Cho Sae Ho is next.
-  All right. He's...
the new trend in variety shows. He's a flower of variety shows.
- He's very popular.
-  A flower?
He's the flower of variety shows.
- I was originally just a weed,
-  He was a weed.
- but I'm about to fully bloom.
-  He's turning into a flower.
That's why he's the flower of variety shows.
Are you sure he's not a monkey?
- A monkey?
-  I thought of a pig.
Don't talk like that. You're discriminating him.
- Isn't that your speciality?
-  Gyeong Gyu.
I thought you were really good at making fun of others.
(Embarrassed)
I've prepared nothing special,
but Ji Hyo is older than me.
So I want to show my respect to Ji Hyo by singing a song.
Don't sing the songs that you sang last time.
Sure. I excluded them.
- I'll sing a new song. A new song.
-  A new one? Okay, please begin.
- It's called, "My Sister".
-  "My Sister"?
- Can you please stand here?
-  Me?
Yes. Since you're my rival.
Please don't feel lonely
(Slapping)
(He retreats quickly.)
- She's tougher than I thought.
-  He called her "tough".
What do you mean, "Please don't feel lonely"? I'm not lonely.
- They're just lyrics.
-  Did you see her?
When he asked Ji Hyo to come out, she said,
- "Me"? She wasn't satisfied.
-  No.
(No thank you. I don't want to hear you sing.)
She really slapped him.
- I was really surprised to see him.
-  Amazing.
My goodness.
- He doesn't seem to belong here.
-  Gyeong Gyu,
- why is Jung Jin here?
-  It's because..
- his film will be released soon.
-  Is that so?
So he was looking for a show to advertise...
his film on, but couldn't find a proper one.
- There wasn't a proper one.
-  But...
why is he mingled with variety show stars and not actors?
That's a good question.
You'd normally come with people who worked with you on the film.
- That's more common.
-  That's why.
By the way, who is the rival of Jung Jin?
- His rival?
-  Yes.
It's Gary.
- Me?
-  Yes. Gary.
- That's strange.
-  They don't match.
Jung Jin will beat Gary with his good looks.
I see. You're talking about their appearances.
One's really handsome, while the other is not.
Good to see you, Gary.
(I'm here to teach you a lesson with my good looks, Gary.)
(They are both human, but they look completely different.)
Am I being intimidated by his looks?
Is this your tactic?
Yes, you got the point.
- How can you?
-  But Gary does look ugly.
You really do look ugly compared to him.
- He makes me take a step back.
-  You look even worse.
He's using his looks.
All right. Who's next? It's you, Su Min.
(Lee Su Min, a new and young MC who is recently adored by many.)
Shouldn't she be Ji Hyo's rival?
No, not for today.
- It's not?
-  I'll match two extreme opposites.
- How will it be, then?
-  Seok Jin's her rival.
(A grandpa in variety shows vs a toddler in variety shows)
She can be my daughter.
She's really young.
If they stand next to each other,
Seok Jin will look even older than he really is.
That's why she's the rival of Seok Jin.
All right, Su Min.
(She'll introduce herself through dancing and intimidate Seok Jin.)
What's going on?
(This song sounds familiar.)
She's great.
Shy, shy, shy
(She's so cute and sweet.)
(We love you, Su Min.)
She's really cute.
She's cute.
(Gary looks proud of her.)
What are you doing?
(Sing along, everyone.)
(She's very pretty and also dances well.)
Who sings this song?
It's Twice's.
(Seok Jin looks overwhelmed.)
- She's nice.
-  She's a good dancer.
(Did you see that, Seok Jin?)
You're really cute.
(Yes, we won!)
(It seems like they forgot that she's their opponent.)
- She's really talented.
-  That was so nice.
- She can be in an idol group.
-  She's so amazing.
- What a treasure.
-  She knows that she's cute.
She's so cute.
- All right. The next person is...
-  Just like this.
- the fighter, Kim Dong Hyun.
-  Yes.
(After Su Min, here comes fighter, Dong Hyun.)
(He's intimidating.)
He looks really strong.
He's an athlete.
- Who brought an athlete here?
-  He looks really tough.
Jong Kook will have a hard time facing him.
Dong Hyun will keep chasing Jong Kook.
Jong Kook is muscular, but he's strong only on TV.
His muscles are just variety muscles.
- They're for showing off.
-  So?
- It's not the case for Dong Hyun.
-  Of course not.
- His muscles are real muscles.
-  He's...
- in a different league.
-  Is that so?
- So, here's Dong Hyun.
-  Okay.
Our last member is...
- Whose rival is he?
-  You said we'll show off...
I'm talking right now.
- You told me that...
-  That's why he's wearing those.
- Dong Hyun will punch these.
-  They're to take his punches.
I was wondering why you've brought them here.
I heard that Dong Hyun will punch these.
We'll do that after introducing all of us.
Just do as I order. Okay?
(Kicking)
(Gyeong Gyu kicks out of fury.)
He really kicked him.
- You must understand my position.
-  What position?
Go to your man, Kim Heung Gook, if you want to.
We were supposed to do it.
Go to Heung Gook!
- He's being scolded.
-  Poor him.
Who's next?
- Have you finished?
-  No.
You haven't introduced Yoo Jae Hwan to us.
- I'll sing a song.
-  Really?
- Let's hear his singing.
-  He's a musician.
- Gyeong Gyu is really funny.
-  Let's begin.
(Jae Hwan is a songwriter. Is he a talented singer as well?)
(He's quite good.)
You will rest in my arms
So just like now
- What is that?
-  What are you doing?
All right. Let's stop here.
- It's early in the morning.
-  What are you doing?
It's too early in the morning.
(He doesn't look happy.)
- Come and stand here.
-  He said, "Stand here."
- It worked well last time.
-  Stand in front of me.
(Poor Jae Hwan will be punished after singing.)
Stand still.
(Slapping)
(Gyeong Gyu slaps him using his Jeet Kune Do skills.)
He really hit me.
What was that?
He slapped my face because I made a mistake.
- Poor you.
-  What was that?
My gosh.
I was slapped because I made a mistake while singing.
(Gyeong Gyu is a really strict leader.)
He applauds you if you do fine.
- If you fail, you're in trouble.
-  All right. Who's next?
- There's no one left.
-  He was the last.
- He wants to finish quickly.
-  The first part has finished.
(The introduction has finished already.)
(Running Man vs Avengers)
(How will they compete today?)
Please show us the title of the first match.
(The fight between the two teams begins.)
We're starting right away.
Is something coming out?
(What is today's first match?)
- It's "Ssireum".
-  "Ssireum"?
(Ssireum)
All right. Let's begin the first round.
(1st round starts.)
But this match will be...
Although Jong Kook is really strong,
- his opponent is very strong, too.
-  That's right.
Although it's just a variety show, they will fight for their pride.
You're right. They are serious.
All right. For the first round,
Lee Kwang Soo will play.
(Kwang Soo is the first player.)
Okay. It's Kwang Soo.
Then his opponent will be...
the farmed Asian black bear.
Kim Joon Hyun.
(Kwang Soo vs Joon Hyun)
All right. Let's go.
- Go, Joon Hyun.
-  I'll play seriously.
- I'm serious.
-  You must wear your shoes.
Su Min wants to cheer for Joon Hyun. Can we listen to her cheer?
- Is there a cheer?
-  Yes, there is.
Our young, fine man, Joon Hyun, will play ssireum today.
Let's cheer for him so he can play better. Shall we?
- Go, Joon Hyun!
-  Go, Joon Hyun!
- That's really great.
-  Ji Hyo.
- Try it.
-  Ji Hyo, I know you can do it.
- Follow her.
-  Cheer him on, Ji Hyo.
- Just like her.
-  "Our young Kwang Soo..."
Our young Kwang Soo, I heard that you're playing ssireum today.
- Stop it.
-  So let's...
(Stop it.)
She sounded like a teacher.
Kwang Soo, step forward. Joon Hyun, step forward.
He looks like a professional ssireum player. He really does.
- Like this.
-  Look at his legs.
- Okay.
-  All right. I'll do my best.
- First round is the most important.
-  Come forward, please.
- Let's go!
-  Let's go!
It's the Asian black bear versus the giraffe.
The giraffe is no match for him.
It's the long socks versus the liner socks.
It's the white socks versus black socks.
- The fatty versus the skinny.
-  The fatty versus the skinny.
- The fatty... Yes?
-  Hey, move back.
- Do it over there.
-  Your thighs are lower than mine.
Don't make this pose in variety shows.
We don't do this. Look at your pose.
Then am I supposed to stand like this?
(He's self-conscious.)
Gyeong Gyu has changed a lot.
Back then, he'd ask, "Who are you to tell me what to do?"
I don't know what to do with my arms now.
What am I supposed to do with them?
- Do whatever you want.
-  Act comfortably.
You can do this, then.
- Ready. Take a step back.
-  Kwang Soo.
- I think Kwang Soo will lose.
-  Stand up.
- Watch your back.
-  Give them a round of applause!
- Go!
-  Let's go!
- You can do it!
-  You can win!
- Bring your leg back.
-  Let's do this.
(Joon Hyun has a huge appetite.)
(He has extraordinary strength.)
Bring your leg back.
(Kwang Soo's strong as well.)
(His strength will surprise you.)
(Tall Kwang Soo vs Heavy Joon Hyun)
(Who will win?)
They look so tense.
(The match begins.)
- Kwang Soo's quite strong, too.
-  He's strong.
- You only need one chance.
-  Look for the timing.
- One of them is tall...
-  Kwang Soo's tall.
Are you ready to face embarrassment?
What?
- I'll embarrass you big time.
-  What?
- Let's see.
-  He said, "Let's see."
- What shall I do with this giraffe?
-  "Let's see."
(Lifting)
(He's startled.)
(He lifts him up.)
(Wow.)
(He's very strong.)
(Stumbling)
Look at Kwang Soo.
(Spinning)
Stop, Joon Hyun.
This is what Jong Kook does to me.
(Kwang Soo tries to resist.)
(Joon Hyun spins around...)
(and tackles Kwang Soo.)
(Kwang Soo is in trouble.)
(Tackling)
(Lifting)
(He has powerful strength.)
(Joon Hyun dominates the game.)
(He squishes Kwang Soo.)
What are you going to do now? What's wrong?
Kwang Soo lost?
- This is humiliating.
-  Did Kwang Soo lose?
- Don't act up.
-  Did he really lose?
- Kwang Soo's done.
-  Kwang Soo, you're strong though.
This is so humiliating.
From what I saw, before Kwang Soo went down,
Joon Hyun's hand touched the ground first, no?
- No, no.
-  I was afraid I'd squish him.
I see. He would have died if Joon Hyun put his weight on him.
(He easily lifted Kwang Soo off the ground...)
(and gained his victory.)
(He evens used his hands to protect Kwang Soo.)
- I'm surprised that he lost.
-  Let's go again.
- Let's play another round.
-  Were you being serious?
- It's 1 to 0.
-  Can you not beat him?
Anyhow, the first game goes to Joon Hyun!
(Joon Hyun takes the first game.)
- This is not easy.
-  He's like a professional wrestler.
- The next match is a big one.
-  All right.
- It's the main match.
-  Who is it?
It's the main match. Here comes Jong Kook!
(Jong Kook is next!)
- Let's go!
-  You can do it!
(Jong Kook vs Dong Hyun)
(We trust you, Jong Kook.)
- Let's go, Jong Kook!
-  Come on!
- Let's do this, Jong Kook!
-  Hey, hey.
(He has a slim chance against me.)
- I'm a singer!
-  You can do it.
- I'm a singer but he's an athlete.
-  Jong Kook, you...
He feels bad for Jong Kook so he wants to make it look competitive.
- But...
-  I told him not to bother.
Jong Kook used to do ssireum, too.
He used to do it before.
- Still...
-  It won't be fun if I win too fast.
(What did you say?)
(Did I hear him correctly?)
- He's making me angry.
-  He won't go easy on you.
- Do it properly, Jong Kook.
-  You can do it.
You can't bring him down. I'm serious.
- This is the main match.
-  For sure!
- It's a big match.
-  Oh, gosh.
Jong Kook, it's not embarrassing for you to lose.
- Right! I'm just a singer.
-  Dong Hyun hasn't retired, yet.
- He's an athlete.
-  Right.
I'm pretty new to ssireum though.
You are trained in judo though.
You should be embarrassed if you lose.
- Oh, gosh.
-  Look at his arms.
I'm getting goose bumps watching them.
Give them a round of applause!
(Will Jong Kook be able to get even with Team Avengers?)
You never know. Dong Hyun might lose.
Jong Kook has played ssireum before.
- This is worth watching.
-  It's a big match!
- This is great.
-  Jong Kook can win.
- This is no joke.
-  He's coming out too strong.
(Dong Hyun's a renowned fighter.)
(He's here to taint Jong Kook's reputation.)
(However, Jong Kook wins every game.)
(He can't lose on home ground.)
(The match begins!)
- This is a big match.
-  He's strong.
(Jong Kook makes the first attack.)
(He needs to get a head start to win.)
This is a matter of pride.
(He tackles from the inside.)
(Is Dong Hyun falling over?)
(He defends himself.)
(Jong Kook goes at it again.)
- Watch out.
-  Watch behind you.
- This is really worth watching.
-  It's amazing.
(Jong Kook isn't an easy opponent to face.)
They're incredible.
- Didn't his knee touch the ground?
-  No, no.
- I think it did.
-  No way.
You really can't tell who'll win.
- You can't tell.
-  This is so fun to watch.
(I'm a UFC fighter!)
(Is Dong Hyun struggling in a match against a singer?)
(This match is unpredictable.)
(It happened in a flash.)
(Dong Hyun performed a judo move.)
(It was short but intense.)
(Dong Hyun wins.)
Are you okay?
(I'm a singer but why am I so upset?)
(This calls for a celebration.)
I've never seen him lose.
I've never seen this.
(This is a rare match to come across.)
I could see him performing the technique.
- I could see him do it.
-  Jong Kook was trying to resist,
- but Dong Hyun used it against him.
-  I didn't know that was from judo.
It was a judo move.
- He was strong, too.
-  Right?
- I should have visited Japan.
-  I know, right?
Please give them a round of applause.
- Jong Kook, you were the best.
-  You really were.
- You were amazing.
-  You almost had him.
We lost the first round.
- But there's more to come.
-  It's only the first round.
- This is the beginning.
-  Yes!
(Team Avengers wins the first round.)
The following competition is "Speed Quiz".
- It's a "Speed Quiz".
-  Excellent.
This one can go either way.
- This one is doable.
-  We're smart.
All of the members will participate.
One person from each team will wear a mouth gag.
The team that guesses the most words in 100 seconds will win.
You only get three chances to skip a word, so please use them wisely.
All right.
This will make you look like a monkfish.
(Is this how you put it on?)
You only wear it if you're describing a word, right?
- Yes, that's right.
-  That's right.
It's only for the person describing the word.
- Each team will pick a theme.
-  We must not pick a hard one.
- Go ahead, Seok Jin.
-  Sure.
Pick something easy.
- He's never lucky.
-  How would I know?
He's so unlucky. Ji Hyo should have picked it.
- I picked "Proverbs".
-  This is the most difficult one.
- I'll describe it in words,
-  All right.
- so don't worry.
-  I can't understand him.
Let's go! Let's do this.
- Let's do this.
-  Let's go!
- Let's win.
Get set.
(Lock the stable door after the horse is stolen.)
There's a horse. It's a horse.
- What's that?
-  It's a horse.
- It's "sa"?
A "sa"?
- What's that?
-  A horse!
- A horse!
-  "Seo"! What's that?
-  "Seo"!
(This is fun to watch.)
- A horse!
-  A horse.
- What comes after it?
-  Right.
What do you put around it?
- That's it!
-  Hurry.
- What do you put around it?
-  Don't you know it?
What's that? A horse...
- Pass.
-  Come on.
- What is it?
-  It's a stable door.
- All right, Jong Kook.
-  "Lock the stable door."
(Be so ignorant as to not know his ABCs.)
"Be so ignorant as to not know his ABCs."
(He guesses it right away.)
It's so obvious.
- Hey! You're good for nothing.
-  Was that what it was?
(Try to guess what it is.)
(Incomprehensible)
- That thing.
-  Kwang Soo.
(What's that?)
(Shouting)
Kwang Soo. Kwang Soo!
- "One ill word asks another."
-  Correct!
Why couldn't you get that?
(Rags to riches)
Hey!
It's a stream.
- "Rags to riches"!
-  Excellent!
(They get 3 in a row.)
- He gave away the answer.
-  You can hear him well.
(An innocent bystander gets hurt in a fight.)
- He gave away the answer.
-  You can hear him well.
Hey, listen carefully.
I can't hear him.
The whales are fighting.
"An innocent bystander gets hurt in a fight."
- Correct.
-  We're doing well. We're fast.
(There may be blue and better blue.)
- "Bad news travels fast!"
-  No.
There's someone running and another person is above him.
"There may be blue and better blue."
- You're saying the answer.
-  You can't do that.
- Stop doing that.
-  I can't guess it right, anyway.
(A pear drops when a crow flies from the tree.)
"A pear drops when a crow flies from the tree."
(So far, they've guessed 6 right.)
(Crowing)
(Cooing)
(What's this supposed to be?)
- The chicken...
-  No, not that one.
- That was close.
-  Okay!
- How many did they get?
-  What was it?
(Playing innocent)
"Playing innocent".
(That's what he meant by the noise.)
- "Playing innocent".
-  It should've been your foot.
- How many was that?
-  You got six right.
Was that 100 seconds? That's too short.
- That was enough.
-  Good job.
It looks like he's not wearing anything.
I'll put it on.
(Gyeong Gyu will describe the words.)
- He came for this.
-  All right.
Jae Seok is working hard and I don't want to be compared to him.
So I'll change my attitude.
This is the topic.
(Team Avengers' theme is "SBS Programmes".)
- Can we ask for help?
-  I don't think he would know.
- This is a problem.
-  Gyeong Gyu...
doesn't watch television if he's not on it.
- I know them all.
-  I don't think so.
Let's go!
Go. Go.
("The Its Know")
(There's a catch phrase in the show.)
However...
("The Its Know")
He looks tired.
"However!"
(You get what I'm saying, right?)
He looks tired.
"However!"
- "The Its Know".
-  Correct!
- How did she get that right?
-  I don't even know.
- This one's funny.
-  He'll never guess it.
I don't think he knows this one.
"Master of Living"?
"Baek Jong Won's Top 3 Chef King"?
"Capture the Moment, How is That Possible?"
He's describing it.
- He's describing it.
-  It's so hot!
- Your heart is burning.
-  Yes!
- Kim Gook Jin!
-  I don't know what this is.
- "Flaming Youth".
-  Right!
(Sae Ho gets it correct.)
He knew it.
("Master of Living")
This one's easy.
I'm the best!
(What kind of performance is that?)
- I'm the best!
-  Master!
- Right!
-  "Master of Living".
Good job.
- Let's go.
-  How did he get that?
- Hey, Su Min.
-  What is it?
- This one's too hard.
-  It is.
("Jagiya")
- This one's too hard.
-  What's that?
- Watch me.
-  Isn't he drunk?
- A fridge?
-  No.
"Jagiya".
- Right. Hey!
-  The whole name.
- You have to say the entire name.
-  You have to finish it.
Hey!
It's time for him to sleep.
("SBS Eight O'Clock News")
(SBS Eight O'Clock News)
- Hey!
-  It's time for him to sleep.
("SBS Eight O'Clock News")
(He imitates a news anchor.)
Hello, everyone. It's SBS news.
(He doesn't look anything like an anchor.)
"SBS Sports"!
This is SBS. The accident...
It's SBS news. "SBS Eight O'Clock News".
- Correct!
-  That was hard.
("Capture the Moment, How is That Possible?")
- You're surprised.
-  I'm surprised.
- He doesn't know.
-  Hidden camera.
- No.
-  Good one.
What was that for?
(He's confused.)
Coverage.
Dong Hyun's not sure.
- It's hard.
-  A camera.
- A camera.
-  This one's hard.
- Pass.
-  Fine, pass.
- He passed.
-  Let's go.
- Let's go.
-  Hey!
"Baek Jong Won's Top 3 Chef King".
("Baek Jong Won's Top 3 Chef King")
- Correct!
-  She's smart.
- Su Min.
-  How did you get that?
- What was it?
-  It's those people.
(Running Man)
- Running Man!
-  Yes!
- That was too easy.
-  Wasn't that too easy?
(Yelling)
- Let's go!
-  What was that?
- Was that two?
-  Is it "Capture the Moment"?
He's so bad at explaining but you still got it right.
What's this supposed to be?
You got seven right.
(Team Avengers gets 7 right.)
- They got seven right.
-  That was pretty good.
- Let them be.
-  Team Avengers takes the win.
Let's do it again.
- That was funny.
-  That was so close.
- We should play two rounds.
-  How is this "Fantastic Duo"?
- That's two people.
-  That was so obvious.
- Let's play another round, then.
-  Let's do one more round.
- Jae Hwan can go first.
-  Are we going first?
- The category is "Song Names"!
-  That's good!
- That's a good one.
-  Excellent.
- Did you put it on?
-  Stand here.
It'll be hard to guess.
This won't be easy.
He's a composer though. He must know a lot of songs.
It's still difficult.
- It's still difficult. See?
-  Hong Jin Young.
- Hong Jin Young.
-  Hong Jin Young? "Thumb Up"?
- This one's easy.
-  "Love Battery"?
- That's it.
-  Good job.
("What About My Age?")
- Is he drunk?
-  "What About My Age?"
You have to keep talking.
("Like Being Shot by a Bullet")
(Don't you recognise this melody?)
- What's that?
-  Act it out.
- You have to act it out.
(What's that?)
It's this.
I know. "You Get Shot".
"You Get Shot"?
- A bullet?
-  What comes after that?
- Something comes after it.
-  That part's over.
- That's done.
-  You get shot.
- There's more.
-  "After You Get Shot"!
- You can do it.
-  Just pass.
(It must be a new song.)
- Yes!
-  This game's over.
- This is done.
-  "Like Being Shot by a Bullet"!
"Like Being Shot by a Bullet"!
(He finally guesses it correctly.)
Okay.
How did you get it?
("Me Gustas Tu")
(He sings the melody perfectly even with the mouth gag.)
- "Me Gustas Tu".
-  Okay!
("Me Gustas Tu")
(I won't fail the team again.)
(It's a popular song by Twice.)
(Floundering)
(It doesn't sound like the same song.)
- He doesn't know it.
-  I sang it in the beginning.
- It's done.
-  What's that?
- Look at him.
-  Pass.
- What's that?
-  It's done. It's over.
- It's done.
-  Hey, hey.
("Cheer Up")
- He's thinking so hard.
-  Pass.
Fighters don't have to know it.
(His only interest is in UFC.)
How are you supposed to guess, anyway?
("I Miss You")
He doesn't get it.
- He looks so confused.
-  I miss you.
Missing you. "I Miss You".
I miss you to death
"My Goodness"?
"I Miss You."
Time's up.
Jae Hwan can't do better than this.
- Good job.
-  You were good.
Kwang Soo!
(It's Team Running Man's turn.)
(Their team is "Korean Movies".)
All right! Let's go!
- It might be hard.
-  Let's go!
- Come on, Kwang Soo.
-  Kwang Soo!
- He's an actor.
-  He knows it well.
("Veteran")
What are you saying?
That's nonsense.
(This is the catch phrase.)
"That's nonsense."
- It's not bad.
-  What did you say?
- "That's nonsense."
-  Pardon?
- You know it.
-  "Veteran"!
- How did he guess that?
-  What was it?
- "That's nonsense."
-  "That's nonsense."
(Approaching)
(What's this?)
(How do I explain this?)
It's Gianna Jun.
There's Gianna Jun and Cho Jin Woong.
- Right.
-  Ha Jung Woo's in it.
Right.
- Oh, that.
-  There's a twin!
- Hey, hey!
-  I get it.
Gianna is a twin.
Jin Woong gets shot.
- You're supposed to do this.
-  He's so detailed.
(Isn't this obvious?)
(This is a scene from "Assassination".)
Sir.
(Don't you know this?)
Come on. Don't you know this? Try to guess.
Jin Woong gets shot...
and goes down.
- Look at his face.
-  Come on!
- He's doing it right.
-  Isn't that a zombie?
Ji Hyun's a twin.
A twin!
- Pass.
-  He didn't watch it.
- Oh, come on.
-  Come on.
- Continue.
-  Do this.
"Shoot me and go."
Shoot me and go.
(It's Ahn Sung Ki's quote from "Silmido".)
- "Shoot me and go."
-  This is it.
- Shoot! Me! And go!
-  You have to get this one!
- Follow me?
-  You should get this right.
- "Shoot me and go."
-  You got it right last week.
"Shoot me and go."
- It's "Silmido"!
-  You're drooling, Kwang Soo.
- "Silmido"!
-  Correct.
- Shouldn't he wipe his mouth?
-  Keep going.
("King and the Clown")
This is great!
- Good one.
-  I know this one.
(This is a scene from "King and the Clown".)
(Fluttering)
- Good one.
-  I know this one.
(Let's wipe your mouth first.)
- What's that supposed to be?
-  I'm okay.
("King and the Clown")
- "King and the Clown"!
-  Correct!
- Okay, all right.
-  Let's make it four.
Okay.
Why would you do that?
- How many was that?
-  "Shoot me and go."
- Let me announce the results.
-  Did we lose?
Team Avengers wins.
(Team Avengers wins.)
- That's fine.
-  We'll win next time.
(Will Team Running Man make a comeback?)
- We'll win in the next round.
-  Okay!
(Team Avengers wins the first round.)
(It's lunch time.)
(There are two tables.)
- My goodness.
-  Oh, my.
(A feast is prepared for the winners, Team Avengers.)
No, no.
(There are plentiful dishes full of meat, seafood and vegetables.)
- It's budaejjigae.
-  Sit on either side.
(The losers get gimbap and a drink.)
- Can we eat?
-  I'm not on a diet.
- Hold on.
-  Thank you.
(Simmering)
Joon Hyun is filming "Baek Jong Won's Top 3 Chef King".
(Joon Hyun gets ready to enjoy the meal.)
That looks so tasty.
- It's really delicious.
-  You're like a cook.
That's budaejjigae.
I really want budaejjigae, too.
That looks so good.
He put ramyeon in it.
Gosh, look at him.
He's going to eat now.
Isn't it too early to eat the ramyeon?
Ramyeon for budaejjigae must be firm.
- Right.
-  Right.
- I prefer firm noodles, too.
-  You're so right.
My goodness.
That looks so good.
Show us how to eat noodles deliciously.
Do you want me to?
- Gosh.
-  Eat it.
It's so lovely.
(He slurps the ramyeon.)
Oh, my.
(He inhales ramyeon like a black hole.)
Wow, it looks so good.
He inhaled it all.
Please stop eating.
(He fills his stomach with water.)
Gyeong Gyu might not remember this.
It happened a long time ago. It just came to my mind.
One day, I ran into him. So I was going to say hello.
But he said, "Don't say hello," and walked away.
(Did I say that?)
My goodness.
I was really surprised.
- "Don't say hello to me."
-  I got something to tell you.
A long time ago,
I met Gyeong Gyu at a karaoke and joined him.
He was an idol to all comedians.
So I said, "Hello. I'm a rookie comedian, Jee Seok Jin".
And he said, "I don't know you."
And for about two hours,
he didn't even look at me.
I'm sure that he doesn't remember that day.
Do you remember?
(Running Man vs Avengers, the second mission)
In the second round, you'll play "Variety Football".
("Variety Football")
We'll provide each team with the same seven items.
You'll wear the items and play football.
The team that scores the most wins.
We've invited a special referee for fair judgement.
(A special referee is here to make fair judgement.)
(A special referee?)
(Who is it?)
Oh, it's you!
(Football mania Kim Heung Gook)
Hello!
(Welcome to Running Man.)
(Here comes the variety dark horse.)
Heung Gook is here!
He's like my father.
Hello.
- "Gosh, it was fun."
-  "Gosh, it was fun."
I never thought you'd be with us today.
I'm a rising variety star.
(He spared his time for Running Man.)
So you have other plans after this, right?
I have other plans.
I have to go to a radio studio.
What time do you have to leave?
I'll leave in 30 minutes.
(This cool guy is not in the same class as others.)
Each half will take 15 minutes.
So I'll leave right after the game.
You'll leave immediately after the game?
Even Gyeong Gyu hoped to go home before dinner.
- Wow.
-  What's important here is...
I will leave with everyone. But he'll leave by himself.
(It's Heung Gook's style.)
My goodness.
(Special commentators are also here.)
We have commentators for our football game.
Such prominent commentators came for us?
Please welcome Anchor Bae Seong Jae and Commentator Park Moon Sung.
Wow! Hello!
- Great.
-  Let's warm up.
- Let's begin.
-  Okay.
Please get changed.
- My goodness.
-  Do you know how to block goals?
Just stand there.
Gosh, it must be really hot.
Look at his fur coat.
He makes me feel hot as well.
Who will be the goalkeeper?
(Struggling)
I think I should put this on.
No, don't. Choose this one instead.
- Ji Hyo, wear this bee costume.
-  Okay.
I need to put balloons in it.
(Ji Hyo becomes agile in the bee costume.)
(Kwang Soo wears a big drum on his back.)
Hello, everyone. The second round will begin soon.
It's called "Variety Football".
Team Running Man will fight against Team Avengers.
(Each team has 5 players and each half takes 15 minutes.)
Each team has seven players.
But only five players can play on the ground.
The players are wearing different items and costumes.
- They're given items.
-  Right.
Who do you think is a key player today?
In my opinion,
Jong Gook of Team Running Man has great stamina.
- In Team Avengers,
- I feel like it'll be Sae Ho.
-  Sae Ho?
- Right.
-  He's wearing flippers.
(He's just a fashion terrorist.)
Anyway, the oldest players in both teams are excluded...
from the starting line-ups.
- Go for it!
-  You can do it!
(They strategically excluded the oldest members.)
Let's win!
(Finally, the players are on the field.)
(Let's go for it!)
- Yes!
-  Kwang Soo.
The first half will take 15 minutes.
(The first half begins.)
(Jung Jin passes the ball to Sae Ho right after the game begins.)
The match has just begun.
We must win!
(Waddling)
Sae Ho uses his flippers to touch the ball.
The players with flippers collided.
Now, the players in bee costumes are running around.
They are cute.
(It doesn't look like a football game from above.)
(Gosh, what on earth is this?)
(There are only variety characters on the ground.)
Pass the ball!
No. No way!
Hey, take it easy. Run slowly!
You should save your energy!
Good. That's it.
No!
Gosh, wait. Wait!
(They can strategically use their items.)
- No way!
-  No!
It's right there.
I can't see anything!
(Sae Ho is wearing a fur coat as if he's in Siberia.)
Where is the ball?
(Thanks to the items, it's nothing but chaos.)
Great! Go!
(Joon Hyun falls by himself.)
- Gosh, it's not easy.
-  Hey!
Where is the ball?
Gosh, help me!
Help me get up.
(This Asian black bear finds it hard to get up by himself.)
(Jae Hwan helps him stand up...)
(but falls instead.)
(They're Dumb and Dumber.)
Where is it? Where's the ball?
Is this really a football game?
This is even more chaotic from the beginning...
than we had expected.
- Go!
-  Good.
(Team Running Man starts to move forward.)
Gosh, why did you pass the ball there?
(They fumble and fall down.)
(Thanks to the items, it's taking them more energy.)
- Each half will take 15 minutes.
-  Yes.
But I'm not sure if they will have enough energy for that.
Just shoot, Jong Kook!
Go! Now!
I can't see anything.
Oh, no! No!
- I can't see.
-  Get the ball.
- Gosh.
-  Where's the ball?
Oh, my. I can't see the ball!
(Kwang Soo kicks the ball.)
(He passes the ball to Sae Ho in the front line.)
(Finally, it's looking like a real match.)
(It's Sae Ho's chance.)
(Sae Ho vs Haha. It's a confrontation.)
(Sae Ho, please!)
(Sae Ho kicks.)
(He misses his golden chance!)
(And he falls down.)
- No!
-  Are you okay?
Gosh, he missed his chance.
(Disappointed)
It was a nice try.
The pass was made at the right time. And he received the ball well.
But there's no off-side rule here, apparently.
I think the referee didn't notice Sae Ho's position.
- Come in.
-  Okay.
Resume the game!
Good!
Great. Kwang Soo, it's a chance!
(Kwang Soo successfully receives the ball.)
Block him!
Go block him.
(He passes the ball to Ji Hyo in the front line.)
(There is no one in front of Ji Hyo.)
Hey, help me get up. Help me.
(Team Avengers faces a crisis.)
- Shoot!
-  Good. That's good.
(Please help me.)
(Kwang Soo jumps in...)
(and obstructs Ji Hyo's way.)
(He blocked!)
(Wait!)
- Shoot!
-  Goal!
(Jae Seok makes a goal.)
- Wow, he made it.
-  He made a goal.
Jae Seok just made a goal.
Jae Seok scored the first goal.
Team Running Man leads the game 1 to 0.
(1:0)
(Jae Seok screams out of joy.)
(He hugs Seok Jin.)
(He's overwhelmed with joy.)
Great job!
(I can't believe it!)
Wow!
I thought it'd be hard to make a goal.
The goalkeeper made a small mistake.
The ball rolled to the side, but his position was great.
The goalkeeper Joon Hyun blocked the ball.
But the block unintentionally assisted Jae Seok.
(Jae Seok receives the honour of putting in the first goal.)
(His concentration on the game helped him make a goal.)
Our team players are doing great since we played football before.
That's true. They're good.
All right. The score is 1 to 0.
Now, Team Avengers must make a goal.
(Team Avengers should keep it up.)
(Jung Jin passes the ball to Su Min.)
(And Su Min passes the ball to Sae Ho.)
- Good.
-  Move forward!
(Frustrated)
Move forward!
(Sae Ho dribbles the ball again.)
(He falls down.)
(Fumbling)
(He stumbles and falls.)
(The referee blows the whistle.)
(Sae Ho, that was dynamic.)
Gosh, referee!
It's my bag, not me.
(Jong Gook's bag made the foul.)
It was my bag.
He received a yellow card.
(Jong Gook gets a yellow card.)
I think Heung Gook is especially favourable to Sae Ho.
Panel!
- Panel?
-  It means a penalty kick.
- What?
-  Just do as I say!
That's nonsense.
You can't give them a penalty kick.
Excuse me, I said just do as I say.
How can you give them a penalty kick here?
If I say it's a penalty kick, it's a penalty kick!
A penalty kick?
(Astounded)
The referee just said, "Do as I say".
- Guys.
-  That's not fair.
If you make a foul to Sae Ho, they will get a penalty kick.
- Here we go!
-  So don't do it to Sae Ho.
(Jung Jin takes the penalty kick.)
- Okay!
-  Jung Jin!
(He loses his chance to score.)
- What's wrong with him?
-  What did he just do?
It's okay.
- Let's go.
-  Run!
(5 minutes remain in the first half.)
Ji Hyo! Ji Hyo!
Kwang Soo!
- Kwang Soo's doing well.
-  Good job! Nice pass!
- I need to block it.
-  Kwang Soo!
I need to block it. I need to block it.
- I need to block it.
-  Kwang Soo!
(It's a 1 on 1 with the goalkeeper.)
Goal!
- Kwang Soo shoots!
-  It went in!
It's 2 to 0. Team Running Man scored another goal.
By the way, he scored the goal very well.
(He's trying to get up.)
(We're losing.)
- We're really good.
-  We're very good.
We've been playing football for five years.
Exchange.
(This won't do!)
Dong Hyun joined the game. And Gyeong Gyu is...
- warming up.
-  Okay. Play!
Go! Shoot!
Wait! Wait!
Wait!
- Shoot!
-  Shoot!
-  Nice!
- Shoot!
(The ball hits the post.)
(He was close!)
(His strong kick shocks the opponents.)
- He's good.
-  Gosh...
Nice! Nice!
It's not easy to kick the ball high while wearing three tubes.
(Dong Hyun changes the vibe of the game!)
- Shoot!
-  Go!
(That was a nice pass.)
(He runs across the field.)
Sae Ho shoots!
(He fails.)
(Haha blocks the ball.)
(However!)
That's too bad. Jung Jin!
- Shoot!
-  Sae Ho played defence.
(Did Sae Ho just block his own team's ball?)
(Why on earth did you do that?)
You're so good.
(Their own team is their worst enemy.)
Pass, pass.
(Jong Kook counter-attacks.)
(He's very agile.)
Kwang Soo!
- Don't move.
-  Where is it?
I can't see well.
(Kwang Soo enters, but Dong Hyun stops him right away.)
He's even defending.
- Cho Sae Ho! Cho Sae Ho!
-  The play is...
- Cho Sae Ho!
-  Sae Ho!
(Will Sae Ho succeed this time?)
(I will make sure to score a goal this time!)
- Cho Sae Ho!
-  Sae Ho!
He fakes it and shoots!
(He fails.)
I can't believe he failed to score that.
Cho Sae Ho!
(Don't cry, idiot.)
(Because of the talented goalkeeper Haha, Sae Ho fails every time.)
Good job, Haha!
The game resumes.
- Here we go!
-  It's hot.
(Gyeong Gyu ambitiously does a corner kick.)
Nice pass.
Dong Hyun shoots. Goal!
(The ball went right into the goalpost.)
Bravo!
(You are the best!)
Dong Hyun scores the goal!
Team Avengers scored the first goal, and now the score is 2 to 1.
By the way, Dong Hyun is really good.
- I know.
-  Yes.
(The current score is 2 to 1.)
- One more time!
-  You're good.
One more time, Gary!
(Dong Hyun blocks again.)
- Come on!
-  That's it.
Come on!
- Cho Sae Ho.
-  Cho Sae Ho is good.
- They are the only ones.
-  Gyeong Gyu is with him.
(Sae Ho passes to Gyeong Gyu.)
He passes the ball to Gyeong Gyu. Gyeong Gyu!
He scores another goal.
(He shoots without any hesitation.)
(Gyeong Gyu ends up scoring a goal.)
(He does a kissing ceremony.)
It's as if Sae Ho gave him the chance.
(Gyeong Gyu and Sae Ho showed amazing teamwork.)
Time out!
Time out.
(The current score is 2 to 2.)
Who put you into the fire?
(He's drenched in sweat.)
If I score just two more goals, it'll be a hat-trick. Support me.
Let's drink water, Sae Ho.
Drink some water, Sae Ho.
(Running Man members are exhausted as well.)
(He gulps down water.)
You're doing much better than before.
- Much better, right? I'll do it.
-  We have to do better.
Gary and Seok Jin can join the second half.
You can rest for a while.
That's really...
We will start the second half.
The referee is busy. So hurry up and come on out.
We must win!
If we lose here, we will lose completely!
- You have to win!
-  We have to win here!
We have a tie!
(The second half begins.)
Go, team!
- Gosh...
-  Gary!
Jae Seok is running fast. You hear the sound, right?
- Listen to the sound of his drum.
-  He's fast.
Jong Kook.
Jong Kook is good at side plays. He passes to Seok Jin!
The ball is passed. Shoot!
(Su Min blocks the ball.)
- It didn't go in!
-  She blocked it with her foot.
The goalkeeper defended well!
Su Min is really good at goalkeeping.
What is it that she can't do?
(Flattered)
Come on!
That's good!
You can do it!
(That was a nice pass.)
Gary!
(I will show you my fancy footwork!)
Dong Hyun comes to help.
(It's a back heel turn.)
- That was a nice turn.
-  It was a back heel turn.
Gyeong Gyu is really good at playing football.
(Running)
His techniques are strange, but he's good!
Hey!
(He gets upset.)
(Please cut me some slack.)
Foul. Jae Seok, you committed a foul.
- It wasn't me!
-  You committed a foul.
- It wasn't me.
-  Your body...
Your bodies didn't touch, but your drums did.
We never touched.
- We barely touched.
-  What is he doing?
- We barely...
-  What are you doing?
- You're exaggerating.
-  He is!
You keep bothering my work.
I am sorry. I am sorry.
Keep this.
- Fine.
-  You deserve it.
Okay. Play.
You will only be able to kick this way.
(It's Joon Hyun's free kick.)
- It's not going in.
-  It's not.
- Good job.
-  Good job.
Behind you, Jae Seok! Great!
- Go. Go. Go.
-  It looks like earrings.
You can give it to Jong Kook.
You can give it to him.
- Go, team!
-  Kwang Soo. Shoot!
She blocked it again.
(She blocks it one more time.)
She blocks well. Really well.
She blocks really well.
Please score one more.
Shoot!
(She's an unbeatable goalkeeper.)
- She blocked it again.
-  Su Min did it for the third time!
- Jong Kook has the ball again.
-  Let's do it again.
- You can do it!
-  You can do it!
- Hurry! Hurry!
-  Why?
- There you go.
-  He uses the chance.
- Go!
-  It went in.
(How dare you!)
(And their second chance comes right after.)
(Kicking)
Go!
(She throws herself to defend the goalpost.)
Shoot again!
- She's unbelievable.
-  She's amazing.
(She's amazing.)
She's a good goalkeeper!
She's really good.
The fun part...
about this game is watching Su Min.
Jong Kook is directing the players.
- He's good.
-  I can't see the ball!
(Gosh!)
- He got poked.
-  How can they do this?
They committed a foul.
Penalty kick.
(Su Min is in danger.)
- Do well.
-  Here we go!
Shoot! The ball goes in!
Team Running Man is winning with a score of 3 to 2.
It's a Pele Score.
You're too mean to a middle school girl.
She's only in middle school!
(3 minutes remain.)
- Watch the left side.
-  Concentrate!
(Team Avengers pass the ball to the back.)
(The ball flies.)
(And it hits the goalpost.)
Shoot!
Perfect.
Sae Ho has the second ball!
- I can't see anything.
-  Block it, Kwang Soo. Nice.
Concentrate, concentrate.
Sae Ho shoots the ball!
Jung Jin shoots the ball! It's a tie.
(He calmly finishes the game again.)
(Jung Jin and Sae Ho did it!)
Jung Jin recovered it right away and the score is 3 to 3.
This is really fun.
Yes.
Sae Ho and Jung Jin's teamwork was amazing.
Sae Ho kicks the ball well.
(It's a tie once again.)
Play!
You have one last goal to make!
(A moment's decision determines the result.)
(Looking)
- Hey!
-  We got it.
(He passes the ball to Seok Jin.)
(The ball crosses the field.)
- Hurry!
-  Take it slow!
- That's it!
-  Kwang Soo, you have to score!
- Shoot!
-  Score it.
Try it again.
(Su Min and Gyeong Gyu defend vigorously.)
- It went out.
-  Try it again.
- Seok Jin?
-  It's a mess.
Seok Jin fell.
- Go, team!
-  Let's go!
(The goalpost is open.)
Gyeong Gyu fell down! Shoot the ball now!
- Shoot!
-  Shoot it!
- No! You have to score it!
-  Right now!
Shoot!
(The ball rolls out.)
Shoot.
(Jong Kook takes a shot.)
- Hurry up and shoot the ball!
-  Shoot it!
(The ball goes in perfectly.)
(You're the best, Jong Kook!)
Shoot! The ball goes in.
- He did well.
-  He's amazing.
Jong Kook scored the 4th goal. Now the score is 4 to 3.
He did really well.
Gyeong Gyu fell with the bag.
So he made the ball pass above Gyeong Gyu.
(You're unbelievable, Jong Kook.)
Come on.
(The game ends with a score of 4 to 3.)
- Is it a tie?
-  We won.
- We won by one point.
-  Good job.
(Everyone was on the edge of their seats.)
The game ended.
Today was Running Man's "Variety Football",
and Team Running Man won with a score of 4 to 3.
Who's the best player today?
I would say it was Jong Kook.
- He scored the goals well.
-  Right.
Team Running Man wins the second round.
(Team Running Man wins "Variety Football"!)
Gosh.
- Thank you.
-  Thank you.
- Is he leaving?
-  Yes.
- Are you going home now?
-  Are you leaving?
Are you leaving?
It's been fun. I'll be going now.
- "It's been fun."
-  "It's been fun."
(Laughing)
"It's been fun."
(He tosses and catches the water bottle.)
He's funny.
- We will move to another area.
-  Okay.
- Good job, everybody.
-  Good job.
(The current score is 1 to 1.)
- What is this?
-  This is the real deal.
(The last match will determine the winning team.)
This is...
Go in.
(What will be the final match?)
(Why are they here again?)
- You're here.
-  You're here.
- Please.
-  It's big.
- The ring is huge.
-  It's huge.
- The ring...
-  The last game is...
(Falling)
- What's wrong?
-  What are you doing, Jae Hwan?
(He falls on his stomach.)
- What did you do?
-  What's wrong?
I didn't do anything.
This is the third and last round of Running Man vs Avengers.
What is it?
The current score is 1 to 1.
- Yes.
-  It's a tie.
The winner of this round becomes the final winner.
We must win.
Let's win!
The third round is...
"Running Rumble".
- "Running Rumble"?
-  A rumble?
(I've never heard of this game before.)
First, each team will decide...
the order of the players' entrance to the ring.
Once the first two players enter the ring,
- Name Tag Elimination will begin.
-  Name Tag Elimination?
And the 60-second countdown will start.
A new player from each team will enter every 60 seconds.
So the ring will fill up as time passes.
- It's thrilling.
-  This is nerve-racking.
You can't find out the order ahead of time.
Once the order is decided, it can't be changed.
Choose wisely.
This is thrilling.
(The result will depend on the order and strategy.)
I'm already nervous.
- Oh, please.
-  This is nerve-racking.
(This is a whole new level compared to the previous rounds.)
(Is it going to be Team Running Man or Team Avengers?)
- I'm a little nervous.
-  Let's go.
- Go, team!
-  I'll give it a try.
I will explain the rules.
Both teams are deciding the order now, and it is very crucial.
As you know how Royal Rumble works,
the game depends on the order of the players' entrance.
If you get unlucky, you can get your tag ripped right away.
Or the player can be of big help to the other players of the team.
Shouldn't the first one be someone who will get the tag ripped first?
- No. No.
-  Jong Kook shouldn't go first.
- No, I should go first.
-  Okay.
- Jong Kook.
-  Even if Dong Hyun comes out,
- Jong Kook can fight him.
-  Then Jong Kook has to go first.
Joon Hyun is really strong, too.
- He's unbelievable.
-  I know.
- He's strong and he's heavy.
-  And...
- He's big.
-  I don't know if I can grab him.
- He's big, so it's not easy.
-  I know.
By the way, they consider Jung Jin as the ace.
- He's got a great physique.
-  Right.
He has long arms.
Dong Hyun fights against two people at once.
Even if he's on the floor, we can't lift him.
I really don't want to lose in the Name Tag Elimination.
Yes, it's our game.
- You need know-how.
-  Right?
We are the professionals for this game.
- We have to decide the order.
-  I think...
if we rip the first person from start, we have an advantage.
- That's right.
-  A strong player should go first.
They dread Dong Hyun the most. They're wondering when his turn is.
Jong Kook must be thinking about when to come out.
Nobody can lift him.
(It's clear who's strong and who's weak.)
- All right.
-  We have to win this.
- We have to win this.
-  All right!
- One, two, three. Let's go!
-  Let's go!
- Let's go!
-  Oh, goodness.
We should shout, too.
(Shouting)
(We can't lose.)
(They will lose their voices before ripping name tags.)
"Running Rumble" will begin soon.
This is the last round that will determine the final result.
It follows the rules of Royal Rumble.
They wouldn't know this.
(They have their own ways of fixing their name tags.)
- They don't know this know-how.
-  Only we know this.
Press the name tags down.
(They know.)
- Look at me.
-  Go, Joon Hyun!
Look at me.
(They do the medical check, too.)
I will introduce the first players of the two teams.
Team Running Man versus Team Avengers.
(Who will be the first?)
Five, four, three, two, one.
(The first round will determine the result. How lucky will they be?)
They can't beat us in this game.
- Go, team.
-  Go, team.
Kim Jong Kook from Team Running Man!
(Jong Kook is the first player from Team Running Man.)
It's Jong Kook.
(The Avengers look confident.)
Kim Jong Kook from Team Running Man!
And from Team Avengers...
(Who will be the first player from Team Avengers?)
Three, two, one.
Kim Joon Hyun!
(It's Joon Hyun.)
- Kim Joon Hyun!
-  Let's go!
(It's Joon Hyun.)
It's Joon Hyun.
There's a strong chance.
- Next is Dong Hyun.
-  It's good this way.
He was standing at the gate.
Well... Size-wise, it's going to be an interesting match.
- Right.
-  Joon Hyun entered first.
Joon Hyun.
(If I rip his name tag, we have a chance.)
(He falls.)
Gosh.
- Hello.
-  Why are you the first one?
It's the Name Tag Elimination. The first round is important.
And if neither of them succeed, another player will enter.
It might become a completely different game.
There you go.
(Go, Asian black bear.)
- Let's go!
-  It's starting.
Joon Hyun.
(They undermine each other.)
Why are you the first player?
- Do we begin now?
-  Do we begin right away?
(The first match starts.)
They are starting.
Did it begin?
- Do we begin now?
-  Do we begin right away?
What's this?
(Jong Kook spots an opportunity!)
(I got you, Joon Hyun!)
Why are you so aggressive?
(Joon Hyun perfectly blocks Jong Kook.)
- That's terrifying.
-  What's happening?
(It's very interesting.)
Jong Kook lacks endurance.
Why are you so aggressive?
(Jong Kook wants to end it in 60 seconds.)
(Joon Hyun counter-attacks.)
(The name tag is right there.)
(The Asian black bear's counter-attack is threatening.)
(Amazed)
That's not easy.
(It's nip and tuck.)
(Jong Kook tries to end it fast, but Joon Hyun's holding on.)
(Tiger vs bear)
Go, Joon Hyun!
(That bear is not an easy opponent.)
(Don't underestimate the bear!)
(Joon Hyun steps on Jong Kook's foot...)
(and falls.)
- Oh, no!
-  Oh, gosh!
- No! Rip the tag!
-  Hurry up!
Hurry up!
(He was doing well until he stepped on his foot.)
(He makes strange noises.)
The mic lines are out. Jong Kook took down Joon Hyun.
(They're extremely focused.)
He ripped the name tag. It's over.
(The bear gathers all the energy he got from his bear food.)
(Jong Kook grabs his name tag!)
(The tiger has taken the bear by his claws!)
No! No!
He ripped the name tag. It's over.
(If he holds on for 15 seconds, help will be on his way.)
(Jong Kook rips the name tag.)
I did it!
(Joon Hyun is out!)
- Okay.
-  He did it!
- He ripped it.
-  He did it.
It's done.
Goodness, he's really good.
Although Joon Hyun is heavier,
- Jong Kook is stronger.
-  That's right.
I'm so humiliated.
(He's a mess.)
(The sly Kwang Soo will play next.)
- We're in a better position.
-  We've got the advantage.
- Jong Kook is really good.
-  We can't swap now.
- What should we do?
-  I think we made a mistake.
Five, four, three, two, one.
(The 60-second countdown begins.)
What are you doing?
(Lee Kwang Soo is up next.)
(What is it? Why does Jong Kook look so worried?)
- Who is it?
-  Is it Dong Hyun?
- It's Dong Hyun, isn't it?
-  It must be him.
What are you doing?
(Is the ultimate weapon, Dong Hyun, here?)
(It's Lee Gyeong Gyu.)
Come in. Hurry.
There's no other way around.
- It's Gyeong Gyu.
-  Did Gyeong Gyu come out?
That's right.
Kwang Soo came out as the second player.
- I think we made a bad decision.
-  Yes, we did.
Come in. Hurry.
Jong Kook and Kwang Soo.
Gyeong Gyu has to play against them alone.
It's hasn't started yet, but his will to fight looks lost.
Gyeong Gyu can only hope for their respect and mercy.
You're right. I think he can't even stand against them for 10 seconds.
I feel bad for him.
Shall we begin?
(The merciless second round begins.)
- Am I fighting against you two?
-  Yes.
(Easy, boys. I'm old.)
Kwang Soo, we have to do this.
(Believe in your age and experience, Gyeong Gyu!)
(Although he's old, he's skilled at martial arts.)
(Will he be able to show everyone his skills?)
(He runs away...)
(and lies down flat.)
(He lies down immediately.)
We're sorry.
(He kicks Kwang Soo in the face.)
(It may not be martial arts, but it's a successful kick.)
(As a true master of laughter, he makes everyone laugh.)
(He's as jumpy and fierce as a caught fish.)
He actually kicked Kwang Soo.
He's doing better than we thought. It's a surprise.
Kwang Soo and Jong Kook underestimated him.
(Gyeong Gyu resists desperately.)
(He smacks Kwang Soo again.)
In martial arts, we call that "ground skills".
You put your opponent on the ground and...
(Gyeong Gyu tries everything from kicking to grabbing hair.)
Gyeong Gyu is fighting really well.
(Hold on just a bit longer, Gyeong Gyu.)
(What an intense battle! Who will be next?)
Five, four, three,
- two,
-  Rip his name tag!
- one.
-  You have to!
(All the players on stage are exhausted.)
(They need help from the new players.)
Hurry, hurry!
- Is it Dong Hyun?
-  All right. The third player...
from Team Running Man is Yu Jae Seok.
And it's Cho Sae Ho from Team Avengers.
(Jae Seok and Sae Ho join.)
(Stumbling)
(As soon as he enters, Sae Ho runs for his life.)
It's Sae Ho.
(I'll join you soon.)
(The giraffe suddenly goes mad and charges towards him.)
(Will Kwang Soo successfully rip Sae Ho's name tag?)
(You're our only hope, Sae Ho.)
- What should we do with him?
-  Why is he so fast?
(He desperately lies down.)
(He uses the wriggling worm tactic.)
Why is he so fast?
(Wriggling)
(It's an incredible speed.)
Why is he so fast?
(They explode in laughter.)
He's crawling on his back.
He's focusing on securing his name tag.
(I got you.)
Hurry. You must rip his name tag.
Hold on. Hold on just a bit longer.
(He's doing his best to secure his name tag.)
- What are you guys doing?
-  Hey, hey.
- Gyeong Gyu is still holding on.
-  That's amazing.
He's holding on like a veteran.
(Team Avengers is short on numbers. They need help.)
- I think Dong Hyun is next.
-  Hold on, hold on.
(Bingo)
(I will send you all off in a blink of an eye.)
- Hold on.
-  What are you doing?
(Both Gyeong Gyu and Sae Ho are about to be eliminated.)
Five, four, three...
(We can't hold on any longer.)
(We need you, Dong Hyun.)
(I'm coming.)
(Please hurry!)
(Gary sets off to the stage from Team Running Man.)
(Here comes the powerful fighting machine.)
No.
(Ripping)
(He couldn't hold on any more. Sae Ho is out.)
(Gary and Dong Hyun are next.)
(He flips into the stage.)
(Sae Ho is out. Now, Gyeong Gyu must be protected.)
(Although they are short on numbers, Dong Hyun is here now.)
- Is he Dong Hyun?
-  Look. It's Dong Hyun.
We can win this.
Team Running Man is tense.
The four of them suddenly gathered together.
(Running Man members group up as Dong Hyun enters.)
- Are you okay?
-  Yes.
Come behind me.
(Finally, I am saved.)
Did you rip it?
Dong Hyun seems like he can beat all of them on his own.
- Gyeong Gyu is hiding behind him.
-  They can't approach him easily.
(Focus on Gyeong Gyu.)
(He is our target.)
They are approaching Gyeong Gyu.
He fell down.
What is this? I can't move my legs.
(Dong Hyun wraps his legs around Jong Kook's legs.)
Jong Kook's legs are wrapped.
That's amazing.
(Team Running Man successfully pushes Gyeong Gyu to the ground.)
Gary pushed Gyeong Gyu down.
(Gyeong Gyu is in danger.)
(No, Gyeong Gyu. I can't let you go like this.)
(Can Gyeong Gyu overcome this critical moment?)
Four, three...
(Gyeong Gyu is out.)
(It's 4 versus 1 now.)
(Who are the fifth players?)
It's time. The fifth players are coming out.
It's Haha from Team Running Man...
and Lee Su Min from Team Avengers.
(Gyeong Gyu has been heroically taken out.)
Hurry. hurry. It's Su Min.
- Wait?
-  Why are you here?
(Haha tries to rip Su Min's name tag.)
(Meanwhile, the other four members focus on Dong Hyun.)
(Swarming)
They look just like hyenas...
- gathered up for hunting.
-  It's like a lion...
- is fighting against hyenas.
-  Right.
No, don't come near.
- I got her.
-  Get away.
(Hold on just a bit longer, Dong Hyun.)
(I'm coming for you.)
- I'm sorry, Su Min.
-  Rip her name tag!
(Team Avengers is overwhelmed in number. They're in great danger.)
(Will the next player turn this situation around?)
(Please help us!)
(He falls down.)
(He falls down on the stage.)
(Ripping)
(It took only a second. Jae Hwan is out.)
(That was the fastest elimination in Running Man's history.)
Are you okay? Are you all right, Jae Hwan?
Jae Hwan tripped on the rope...
and lost his name tag right away.
- Which team is he playing on?
-  That was really ludicrous.
(Play of the day: In a blink of an eye)
Come out of there!
(Laughing)
(She can't stop laughing after watching that ludicrous play.)
(What should I do now?)
Team Avengers is still holding on. They are relying...
on the personal strength of Dong Hyun...
and Su Min's persistence.
(But now!)
(Dong Hyun successfully grabs Kwang Soo's name tag.)
(Ripping)
Kwang Soo. You're out.
- I'm out, I'm out!
-  All right, Kwang Soo.
- You're out, Kwang Soo! You're out!
-  You're out.
(Kwang Soo is out.)
Hold on.
(He's holding on with monstrous strength.)
(It's 5 versus 2 now.)
How can you harass a little girl like her?
(As long as Dong Hyun's alive, Team Avengers has hope.)
(I've been ripping name tags for 6 years. I must win this match.)
(Gary's hand sneaks behind Dong Hyun's back.)
(He successfully grabs Dong Hyun's name tag!)
There are 60 seconds left!
(Be careful, Dong Hyun!)
(Can Dong Hyun defend this? Or will Team Running Man be victorious?)
I got it! I ripped his name tag!
(Dong Hyun is out.)
(Gosh!)
Dong Hyun's name tag has finally been ripped off.
(Team Avengers has lost their best player.)
(Team Running Man is definitely on a higher ground now.)
- What should I do?
-  Hold on.
(The end is near. Who are the last players?)
(He looks determined.)
(Just hold on. I'm on my way.)
(Finally, the last members from each team enter the stage.)
(Running Man's strong woman, Ji Hyo, is next.)
(The last hope of Team Avengers. Jung Jin is on his way now.)
Here comes the last members. It's Ji Hyo from Team Running Man...
and Jung Jin from Team Avengers.
Jung Jin is very well-built.
Ji Hyo is too small compared to him.
- Our plan is wrong.
-  There's Jung Jin.
- Be careful of Jung Jin.
-  Defend well.
(5 players vs 2 players)
Watch out. There's Jung Jin.
(We have no more players to join. This is the final round.)
(Will Jung Jin be able to put an end to the match?)
They have Jung Jin.
(Jung Jin spots the absent-minded Seok Jin.)
(He makes a dash.)
Jung Jin isn't out yet!
(Jung Jin catches Seok Jin off guard.)
What?
(He claps like a seal.)
- What was that?
-  Jung Jin isn't out.
He ripped Seok Jin's name tag.
- He removed the name tag.
-  Wow, Jung Jin is very fast.
- Jung Jin...
-  It's not bad. We can do it.
Although there are three left, you can do it.
I think you can beat them.
Wow, Su Min is good at this.
Jung Jin, don't let them get you.
The competition is getting fiercer.
It's 4 to 2 now.
But if they beat one player in Team Running Man, it'll become 3 to 2.
Then, they can win.
I'll take care of this side.
Wait. Hold on.
- Wait.
-  Jong Gook...
(Jong Gook grabs Jung Jin.)
Jong Gook just grabbed Jung Jin.
He's running toward Jung Jin.
(No way!)
No.
(Jung Jin is our last hope.)
(Will he be able to survive here?)
(Jae Seok removes Jung Jin's name tag.)
No.
(3 members cooperate and beat Jung Jin.)
My goodness.
Oh, dear.
(Jung Jin is out!)
Jung Jin, you're embarrassed, right?
Go, Su Min.
Your plan failed.
(Jae Seok removes Su Min's name tag.)
Su Min is out!
(Team Running Man wins the "Running Rumble" round.)
(He's furious and resentful.)
The final winner is...
Team Running Man.
(Team Running Man is the final winner.)
Well, I think...
- Our plan was great.
-  I am sorry.
This is an award for the winners.
(Team Running Man receives gold badges.)
Today, the king of variety shows,
Gyeong Gyu...
- made us laugh a lot. Thank you.
-  You're welcome.
Thank you very much.
Next week,
I will come back with new members.
I'll create a new team.
- They weren't that good today.
-  Really?
How was it today?
It was fun.
Thank you for joining us!
(Variety Avengers won't stop here. There will be a rematch.)
(Next Week)
No! Wait!
(We haven't shot the episode yet.)
(We'll just show you how it will look like.)
(You already know what it will be like, right?)
(Suspicious R Rescue)