(On a late summer day, at Yeouido Park)
Hello.
(Is Jae Seok the first member to arrive?)
This is Jong Kook's car.
- Are you dressed in black again?
-  What's wrong?
- It's better than long sleeves.
-  It's hot. Why do you wear black?
You'll be divided into two teams and compete against each other.
- A car is coming to pick you up.
-  Really?
The guest will choose his team members.
(The guest will get to choose his team members.)
- Really?
-  That means I can organise...
my team regardless of his choice, right? I can manage that.
Organise your team? What are you talking about?
Goodness.
- I'll organise my team...
-  It means you are an outcast.
- You're just an outcast.
-  No, I'm not. It's different.
It's only that the person hasn't been chosen. Don't say it like that.
Do you remember the fight in the mud?
- We were so manly.
-  You were awesome.
- You were the best.
-  I mean it.
It was a clash between power and speed.
You were very powerful.
(They praise their own performance.)
PS stands for power and speed.
I like that. PS.
- P!
-  S! Good!
How about this?
- If only one of us gets chosen,
-  Yes.
- let's not get on the car together.
-  Of course.
(Let's just drop out together.)
- How's my idea?
-  We must keep our dignity.
If the guest is male, he'll choose Ji Hyo.
- No, Gary.
-  If the guest is female,
- she'll choose Kwang Soo.
-  You never know.
Don't say that.
- I'm so lonely.
-  What are you talking about?
(Yeouido Park)
(Meanwhile, somewhere in Yeouido Park)
(Under a cloudless sky)
(What?)
(There's a trolley in the middle of the park.)
(A map?)
(A car arrives.)
(The guest that members are waiting for is...)
Hello.
(Cha Seung Won)
(This sexy man knows how to cook.)
(The handsome middle-aged guy, Cha Seung Won, is on Running Man.)
Today's race is called "Running Map".
We have a map ready for you.
Please hop on the trolley bus...
and pick up the members.
Choose the ones you like.
How can I do that? I'd feel bad for the others.
Don't worry. It's only to divide them into two teams.
Goodness.
I don't know...
all the Running Man members,
but I know most of them.
(I have to choose between acquaintances and strangers.)
Will this take me to the members?
They're all waiting in the vicinity of the park.
What are they doing in this heat?
(They're waiting for you.)
I'm not sure what to do.
There it comes.
There must be someone.
- Goodness.
-  They are here.
Gosh, they shouldn't be together.
What is this map about?
Jae Seok.
- You can't pick both of them.
-  Jong Kook.
- It's Seung Won.
-  Seung Won.
- You are here.
- Hello.
-  Seung Won.
(He gives a big smile.)
Hello.
- You look very fit.
-  You look better than before.
- Really?
-  Yes.
Really?
Wow, Seung Won.
- What should I do?
-  Seung Won.
- Don't touch him.
-  Come here for a minute.
- Why are you touching him?
-  You don't know what may happen.
- What do you mean by that?
-  What should I do?
Let's get on the trolley.
- Wait a minute.
-  Just get on.
- Stop.
-  Wait a minute.
- What's wrong with you?
-  Let him choose.
- By the way, Jong Kook,
-  Yes?
I haven't seen Jae Seok in a long time.
Exactly. You should stay here.
- Seung Won.
-  Yes?
If you don't pick me, you'll have to deal with me.
(You'll have to deal with me.)
Come on, can't you deal with him?
- No.
-  You can defeat him.
I can't.
Goodness.
How can I defeat him?
It doesn't matter. Do what makes you feel comfortable.
- He usually takes revenge.
-  I know.
- Does he hold grudges?
-  No, he doesn't.
I'm weak when it comes to affection.
- Don't feel pressured.
-  Hurry up.
He doesn't like revenge.
It's not that.
- I haven't seen you in a while.
-  Okay, I'll get on.
- Okay.
-  Stay here.
Jong Kook, I'm sorry.
- Don't apologise to him. Get on.
-  It's okay.
- Let me go. Go on the trolley.
-  Get on.
Go on the trolley first.
(Let me apologise to him first.)
- Come on, Seung Won.
-  Jong Kook.
- I'm sorry, Jong Kook.
-  It's okay, Seung Won.
He's the type to take revenge.
Goodness.
- Why were you with him?
-  Jong Kook.
Jae Seok.
(I'm going to get you.)
- Gosh.
-  Good to see you.
- Long time no see. Have a seat.
-  I know.
- You made the right choice.
-  Really?
(It's like a ride through a safari.)
Let's talk later.
You're so soft-hearted. Why would you talk to him later?
- See you.
-  Don't look at him.
- I'm getting motion sickness.
-  It's okay.
Of course you should choose me.
- Is Jong Kook okay?
-  Of course, he is.
- Goodness.
-  Don't worry about him.
Things turned out well. Who's next?
- Next choice will be easier.
-  Don't worry, Seung Won.
The next members won't be scary at least.
- They won't make me feel awkward.
-  They won't.
- I'm usually not afraid of people,
-  I know.
but Jong Kook is scary even on television.
(Jong Kook is scarier than anything else.)
(Around the corner is the second meeting place.)
- There they are.
-  There they are.
A map?
(The members who are waiting here are...)
Is that a trolley?
(Kwang Soo, Gary and Ji Hyo.)
- It's Kwang Soo and...
-  There are three of them.
Please get off the bus first.
It's Seung Won.
Seung Won.
Hello, Seung Won.
- Hello, Seung Won.
-  Hello.
- Hello.
-  It's nice to meet you.
-  Hello.
Hey.
What I want to say is that...
- I have to choose only 1 person.
-  Out of 3 of them?
That's really difficult.
What happened to you? Did he choose you?
Yes, he chose me.
- Are you sure?
-  I'm his assistant.
- It's nice to meet you.
-  Get back on the trolley.
- This is difficult, indeed.
-  Jae Seok was with Jong Kook.
- It was really...
-  You're wise.
Jong Kook was scary.
Good luck with making decisions.
(Good luck with making decisions.)
I'm worried.
- There he is.
-  He's here.
- Jong Kook.
-  He's being ridiculous.
- That's a huge difference.
-  Wait a minute.
- How could it be so different?
-  Get on the trolley.
Remember that I'm watching you.
Hurry up, Seung Won. He's riding a black van, too.
Kwang Soo is my junior in modelling.
There's a lot of traffic right now.
I'm sorry.
- Thank you.
-  Oh no.
-  Let's get on.
- Let's go.
-  He's a traitor.
- Thank you.
-  Hurry up and get in.
- Kwang Soo.
-  Why did you pick him?
- What's wrong?
- Was he a bad choice?
-  It's not that.
- Please believe me.
-  What's wrong?
I won't make you regret today.
What if we become the losing team?
No way.
Kwang Soo is my junior in modelling.
- He is your junior?
-  Of course.
He's a junior comedian.
Come on, Jae Seok.
- Kwang Soo was a famous model.
-  He was a famous model?
- Yu Hae Jin was also famous.
-  He was?
That's what he says.
(Laughing)
- He says that about himself.
-  You startled me.
He always says that to me.
Goodness.
It seems to me...
that since you chose me and Kwang Soo,
you prefer being funny to winning.
I knew it.
What's the point of winning on the show?
- I know.
-  That's right.
They're here.
- Gosh.
-  Who's on the trolley?
- Who's on the trolley?
-  I see Jae Seok.
Yu Jae Seok.
- I'm your fan, Seung Won.
-  Hello.
Haha.
How have you been? Hello.
- I'm your fan.
-  Hello.
Let's get on the bus, Seung Won.
Wait a minute.
- He looks like he's in his 20s.
-  What should I do?
- Whom should I choose?
-  Jae Seok is here.
- Hello.
-  Gosh, I don't know what to do.
What do I do about Haha?
It's difficult to choose between the two.
We made up our minds.
We'll stay together no matter what.
What did you say?
Haha, let's go.
- Okay, Seung Won.
-  Okay.
I'm sorry, Seok Jin.
Why did you make that useless comment?
I'm sorry.
- Why did you say that?
-  Haha.
Come back out here.
- How funny.
-  You are amazing.
Seok Jin, come this way.
Just come here now.
(This is where you belong.)
That was his last decision.
(Seung Won's team gets on the trolley.)
- You made your decision quickly.
-  Put your seat belt on.
It's because...
- I know Haha already.
-  I know.
You picked your teammates based on...
your prior relationships.
(He's gone through a hard time with Jae Seok.)
It's more tiring.
(He met Kwang Soo while modelling.)
(He met Haha on television.)
(Seung Won values his relationships.)
- I'm all about relationships.
-  I know.
(Team Blue versus Team White)
(Fishing area, Naengmyun restaurant, Noryangjin, Mangwon Market)
(With entertainment leader Cha Seung Won,)
(complete the Running Map.)
(Laughter and food can be found on the road.)
(Find R Mon in various places...)
(to find out the secret to Running Map.)
You and Hae Jin make a fantastic couple.
Hae Jin is great,
and Gary is similar to him.
- They're a little similar.
-  You are right.
"Do it like this."
Goodness.
(They're definitely similar.)
"Let me see."
Imagining him here tires me out.
I'm so tired of him.
(They move to R1 point.)
There's a lot of good food here.
- These croquettes look delicious.
-  They look delicious.
- I haven't been here in a while.
-  I want some donuts.
Fruits are being sold already.
There's a lot to eat at this market.
- That looks delicious as well.
-  It's tteokgalbi.
Wow, what's that?
- It's tteokgalbi.
-  I want some.
- That's delicious.
-  It's really delicious.
- Look at jokbal.
-  It's jokbal.
- That looks delicious.
-  That's mini-jokbal.
- That looks really good.
-  I can sense what's going on.
(He trips and falls.)
(He was too busy staring at the food.)
Shouldn't we eat kalguksu here?
It's okay.
Are you just going to look at food without eating?
- Are you okay?
-  That's how I tripped.
(He was close to tasting the ground.)
(There's a flag in the middle of the market.)
What's going on?
Do we sit at the table with our team?
Sit with your team, please.
What's this?
- There's eight.
-  What's this?
- Nakji jeongol sounds good.
-  I like small octopus.
The winner gets food that's famous at this market, which is...
- modeum jeon...
-  Let's eat jeon.
- and sikhye.
-  Sikhye?
You'll play a game called "Tug for Food".
- What's that?
-  Is it like tug of war?
The person to bend the knees first while pulling the rope loses.
- That's really difficult.
-  It requires strength.
You decide the order. You compete based on the order.
Discuss in which order you'll play.
- I want to play against Seung Won.
-  Why?
I don't want to play against Jong Kook.
(No thank you.)
- Let's see.
-  Please think carefully...
- Please determine the order.
-  and determine the order.
Stop it.
He's Jong Kook's target today.
(They whisper among themselves.)
(Kwang Soo, Jae Seok, Haha, Seung Won)
We're done.
- You decided the order in secret?
-  Yes.
(Gary, Jong Kook, Seok Jin, Ji Hyo)
(The list of matches is made.)
- Kwang Soo.
-  Yes?
- Don't go easy on him.
-  I know.
Kwang Soo's feet are too big.
He has giant feet.
(He has large feet.)
- Kwang Soo, show us your strength.
-  Okay, Jae Seok.
I don't have much space to sit.
I'm also at the edge.
- I'm sitting on the pavement.
-  You're too tall.
- Don't yield to him.
-  Shouldn't he move up?
- Come on, Gary.
-  How can you do this?
I'll hold the middle.
- Get ready.
-  Wait, I'm not ready yet.
(The winning team in "Tug for Food"...)
(can enjoy modeum jeon...)
(and sikhye.)
(Kwang Soo, I'm hungry.)
Ready, set, go!
(Go!)
You're doing good.
Look at them go.
Don't bend your knees.
(This isn't a face making game.)
- Watch your knees.
-  Hey.
- That's not fair play.
-  He bent his knee.
- Don't bend your knees.
-  Watch your knees.
(He bent his knee.)
Hey.
- I won, right?
-  Why did you bend your knee?
(He accidentally bent his knee to tickle Gary's foot.)
- Why did you do that?
-  I was trying to tickle him.
- We won.
-  Yes.
- All right!
-  Gary wins.
- Jae Seok is a good judge.
-  I wan to eat that modeum jeon.
- Why did you do that?
-  Don't you want to eat that?
- I didn't mean to do that.
-  Come on, Kwang Soo.
- I'm very sensitive right now.
-  What was that about?
Next up,
Jae Seok from Team Blue...
- and Jong Kook from Team White.
-  Yes, we won already.
I didn't think of Seung Won as that kind of guy.
(The two are exchanging mixed feelings of joy and sorrow.)
I'm fine.
Good job, Ji Hyo.
- I don't mind it.
-  Ji Hyo.
- You've got a good taste.
-  I'm fine.
You don't know yet. We could win.
- I agree.
-  We never know.
This could go either way. Jae Seok works out a lot.
(I can't live under your shadow forever.)
(But the opponent is Jong Kook.)
Go!
(He roars like a lion.)
(There was no hope to begin with.)
That was quick.
(He got lifted.)
That was boring.
- Is that all you got?
-  That was really boring.
We're having fun here.
- You think you can do better?
-  Why are we playing this game?
- Don't say that.
-  I want to give it a try.
- Wait.
-  Try it, Seung Won.
- You didn't say start.
-  You try.
(Is that his wallet?)
- You didn't say start.
-  Hey, Seung Won.
Why did you bring your wallet here?
- Seriously.
-  Why didn't you leave it somewhere?
Opportunity makes the thief, you know.
- Hold on.
-  You try it.
I'm tired of losing.
This is it. We can win this one.
Go, Seung Won.
He's flexible.
I'm not that flexible. That's the problem.
Why are all the games favourable to Jong Kook?
- Why is that?
-  I won't go easy on you.
Seung Won works out a lot, too.
(Go!)
(He gets pulled all the way.)
(It was like seeing the evolution of man.)
(How dare you?)
- Move over.
-  He's angry.
Get over here, Seung Won.
He's not worth it.
(Jong Kook almost got pounded by Seung Won.)
You almost got pounded.
Relax.
I thought we had a chance this time.
Jong Kook is way too strong.
- How are we supposed to win?
-  He's unbeatable.
- Unlucky draws.
-  Exactly.
- There was no way we could win.
-  Ji Hyo drew well.
- You were good.
-  Hey, Seung Won.
- Do you feel good about yourself?
-  He's good.
- He's our guest today.
-  Hey.
(This is what Jong Kook is capable of.)
I don't believe that guy.
For the second game, I'll show you the prize first.
(They're croquettes.)
- What is that?
-  Those are my favourite.
Aren't those croquettes?
They are croquettes.
The second game is "Slap the Book".
- What is that?
-  "Slap the Book"?
- If you flip all five coins,
-  Consecutively?
you will win.
Let's go.
Show us what you got.
(They are destined to compete with each other.)
(It's the battle between Jong Kook and Jae Seok.)
(This is your chance to take revenge.)
- Jae Seok, we have to eat those.
-  Okay.
Those are ours.
- I want the croquettes, Jong Kook.
-  Rock-paper-scissors?
- Rock-paper-scissors.
-  Paper.
All right.
This should work better.
Leave it alone.
(He gives an unsatisfied look.)
- What are you doing?
-  Don't interfere.
- Fine.
-  Stop moving the book.
(He slaps the book.)
("Slap the Book" begins.)
Why do you keep switching the court?
- What are you talking about?
-  It doesn't matter.
(This is the chance to redeem myself.)
(He slaps the book.)
What are you doing?
(It got flipped to its original state.)
Have you never played this game?
- To be honest, I'm not that good.
-  The game isn't over yet.
- I knew it.
-  Flip the other ones, Jong Kook.
Have you not played this game in high school?
Jae Seok, make your hand like this.
Seung Won, I'm not very good at it.
- I'm not feeling confident.
-  At least do the hands right.
At least do the hands right.
(Four coins got flipped.)
(The person to flip the last coin wins.)
- Jae Seok!
-  This is our chance.
- This is so easy.
-  It hit my thumb.
- I can do this.
-  Hey!
(The coin spins in the air.)
- We did it!
-  I did it!
(It flipped.)
- We did it!
-  I did it!
(Seung Won looks the happiest.)
- We did it.
-  We won.
Thanks, Jong Kook.
- Team Blue wins.
-  It was all thanks to Jong Kook.
I take no credit.
I'm glad it turned out this way.
It feels even better to win like this.
- Lastly,
-  Yes.
we will be playing "Slap-Match".
It's a good game.
The winner will continue playing until he or she loses.
The prize is jokbal.
- It's jokbal?
-  I'm really craving jokbal.
He even fell down because of that.
- He fell really hard.
-  I did.
We've all played this game, right?
You know the game right, Seung Won?
- Yes, you just need to flip that.
-  The winner stays on.
- Rock-paper-scissors.
-  This is really important.
Rock-paper-scissors.
- All right.
-  Why did you lose?
- Did you do that on purpose?
-  Don't worry about it.
Whenever you're ready.
- Right here?
-  Yes.
- That's where I should aim, right?
Go.
(Here she goes.)
(She slaps it.)
(It got flipped.)
(One shot, one kill)
- What is this?
-  She's so good.
I've been practising with my dad.
- What happens now?
-  She didn't even give him a chance.
- Get out.
-  Do we keep going first?
- Do rock-paper-scissors.
-  Rock-paper-scissors.
(Paper and scissors)
Why did you do that?
Why did you show it first?
- You showed the paper.
-  Why did you do that?
- Don't show them your pick.
-  Hey, I'm the oldest here.
Move over.
I'm good at this game.
- Let me handle this on my own.
-  Hey, Seung Won.
- Don't tell me what to do.
-  We were too sensitive.
- I'm sorry.
-  Do you see how much I'm sweating?
- I can see that.
-  I'm trying really hard.
We just want you to have that jokbal.
- I understand.
-  Okay.
- She won't be able to do it again.
-  You can do it, Ji Hyo.
I know you have it in you.
- She's good.
-  Right here?
She's been practising.
- She practised with her father.
-  She's a try-hard.
Why do we play these games?
Don't let them get to you.
- Be calm.
-  Give it a go.
That's it.
(It got flipped again.)
(Hard work always pays off.)
- She's crazy.
-  What's gotten into her?
This is your day, Ji Hyo.
- He didn't even get to try.
-  Hey.
Sorry, that's not her fault.
I'm just going to order some jokbal for myself.
Do you hear me?
I have my wallet with me.
- It's not over yet.
-  Yes, the game isn't over.
This stupid game.
- Ji Hyo isn't even sweating.
-  This is stupid.
- I'll win.
-  Rock-paper-scissors.
- Rock-paper-scissors.
-  All right.
- Three loses in a row.
-  I don't believe this.
- Why did you go with paper again?
-  I didn't know.
We've all lost with paper.
- I'm a bit tired.
-  You can do it, Ji Hyo.
You can still do it.
- Hey, Kwang Soo.
-  She's perfect for this game.
She's too good.
Can you go easy on us?
- She's going to do it again.
-  Do it again, Ji Hyo.
She shouldn't have any energy left.
(It got flipped again.)
(That's disheartening.)
You make me sick.
Why is this so easy?
This is weird.
There's something wrong with it.
You should have won the rock-paper-scissors, then.
Shouldn't we do a drug test on her?
- This is our last chance.
-  He's the last one.
- You have to win.
-  I can't afford to lose this one.
You have to win the rock-paper-scissors.
- She's our new "Slap-Match" queen.
-  You're the king of "Slap-Match".
Rock-paper-scissors.
(Rock and paper)
(She's the winner.)
- What's wrong with you?
-  Didn't I say you have to win?
- This is over.
-  I'm sorry.
Don't you ever call yourself the king of "Slap-Match" again.
You said I should go for rock.
- When did I say that?
-  Forget it.
- Well, that's too bad.
-  She won all of them.
Why did you go...
- without discussing it first?
-  This is driving me crazy.
- Put an end to this, Ji Hyo.
- End this.
-  Do it, Ji Hyo.
- Right here.
-  End it, Ji Hyo.
This is crazy.
- Please, not again.
-  Go for it.
Don't listen to them.
This is the chance to knock them all out by yourself.
- Go, Ji Hyo.
-  You can do it.
Show them what you're capable of.
(Is this going to be it?)
(Or is this the beginning of a turn-around?)
(She slapped it.)
(It got flipped again!)
(She knocked them out all by herself.)
Wow, she's amazing today.
He can't do it.
Why isn't this working?
(He's mad.)
- Why can't I flip this?
-  They didn't even get to try.
- I didn't see this coming.
-  Is this it then?
What does your father do?
He must be good at "Slap-Match".
How could this happen?
(Team White wins!)
- I can't believe this.
-  This is ridiculous.
- The croquettes are here.
-  They look so good.
How could we not win a single game?
- We didn't even lose on purpose.
-  Can we have some?
- Look at this sikhye.
-  Hey, Gary.
- Okay, fine.
-  Here you go, Ji Hyo.
I don't think we're allowed to share.
Don't give them any.
We won the game. They shouldn't get any.
- It looks good.
-  Look at these croquettes.
- They look really good.
-  They do.
It's delicious.
- It really is.
-  Let me try some.
- What's in it?
-  This is good.
(She's got her eyes on sikhye.)
(He can't stop thinking about jokbal.)
(It should have been mine.)
Give Seung Won some.
He fell because of jokbal.
- It's amazing.
-  I really want some jokbal.
Open up, you.
(He's teasing him.)
How could you do that? Don't let them do that to you.
That's so childish.
- Let go of me.
-  Don't eat that.
- Please.
-  Go to a restaurant later.
No, let me handle this. Hear me out.
- I can't watch you like that.
-  No, this is the thing.
- That made me mad.
-  You should have won the game.
He shouldn't have let it touch my lips.
Why did he put it and the sauce on my lips?
- What is he doing?
-  He is teasing us.
(Jae Seok sneaks up from behind.)
Hey, what are you doing?
What are you doing?
- What are you doing?
-  Drink this. Quickly.
Hey, wait. What do you think you are doing?
- Come on, Seok Jin.
-  What do you think...
- you are doing?
-  Stop stealing.
- What do you think you are doing?
-  Stop stealing from them.
(Seung Won drinks the entire sikhye.)
- Hey.
-  Come on, Seok Jin.
Why did we play the game in the first place?
- Come on.
-  Stop it.
- Come here, Gary.
-  Gosh.
(Both teams receive a map piece.)
Thank you for the meal.
- Thank you for the meal.
-  You can't share the map piece.
- Let's go.
-  Thank you for the meal.
(They move to the next destination.)
(They move from Mangwon Market to a naengmyun restaurant.)
This time, the winning team will win cold naengmyun dishes.
You will play a game called "Zoomed in Penalty Kick".
All of you will have a chance to shoot at once...
but it will be too dull if we let you just kick the ball.
So you need to wear a pair of telescope glasses.
(What? A pair of telescope glasses?)
(Are they really wearing this?)
The goalies also need to wear them.
- So who wears the glasses?
-  Both the kicker and the goalie.
We have the Korean Oliver Kahn.
Hi. I'm Oliver Kwang.
- We have Gary Yashin.
-  Gary Yashin.
- So they are the goalies?
-  Yes.
(The Entries of the Game)
- Look at the ball first.
-  Yes.
- Look at where the ball goes first.
-  Okay.
- Kwang Soo looks like Usain Bolt.
-  You can't see this?
(They look very similar.)
- I can't see a thing.
-  Really.
- Can't you see anything?
-  You can't? Really?
- Will you be all right, Kwang Soo?
-  Yes.
- This could be dangerous.
-  Kwang Soo will block first.
(This is how they see the world with the pair of telescopes.)
- Are you ready?
-  Yes.
Set.
(Two of the Unlucky Trio are competing each other. Who'll win?)
- You're 4 steps away from the ball.
-  Four steps?
Walk four steps forward.
(An old kicker who can't see a thing properly...)
(versus a tall but unlucky goalie.)
(Who will win in the end?)
(He misses.)
(He misses the ball.)
- That's it.
-  No.
- You kicked and missed. That's it.
-  No. It's not.
- He used his chance already.
-  He didn't kick the ball yet.
(Seok Jin is trying again.)
(He scores this time.)
- Well done.
-  I scored, right?
- Did it go in?
-  Nice.
Hurry up. It's raining.
- Is it my turn now?
-  It's Jae Seok's turn.
- Go, Jae Seok.
-  Okay.
- I can't see properly.
-  What's this?
- The ball will come this way.
-  First of all...
I can see through only one side.
- I really can't see anything.
-  Me, too.
Please hand him the ball.
(They can't see much.)
Jae Seok looks like that he's wearing his own glasses.
- It goes well with him.
-  It matches.
He actually looks handsome.
(He looks like an insect.)
I'll win if I can kick properly.
One, two, three and shoot.
(He had a hard time kicking penalty shots before.)
(In Asian Dream Cup 3 years ago,)
He shoots!
(Jae Seok kicked the ball and it hit the goal post.)
- It hit the post!
-  That was close.
It was really close.
Nick kick.
(He kicks confidently.)
(Gary blocks it.)
Nice.
(Gary blocks the ball.)
- The ball hit him.
-  Goodness.
- That was close.
-  It really was.
Gary was really lucky.
- Gosh. I almost got it.
-  If you kicked to the other side...
I could see the ball until you kicked. It vanished after that.
- You can block this time, right?
-  Yes, of course.
I'm ready.
Hey, Oliver Kwang.
Kwang Soo. Lie down.
- Lie down in front of the goal.
-  Okay.
(Lying down? It sounds like a good idea.)
Yes, you can kick the ball. Look at the ball and just kick forward.
(Ji Hyo shoots.)
(Kwang Soo lies down.)
(Did he block the ball?)
It went in.
(Ji Hyo scores a goal.)
- That's it.
-  It went in.
Well done, Ji Hyo. He helped you score.
- Did it go in?
-  Yes.
It went in.
Well done, Ji Hyo. He helped you score.
- Did it go in?
-  Yes.
- If he was standing up...
-  Then he could've blocked the ball.
(Their strategy actually helped the other team.)
Why did you tell him to lie down?
You should've lied down earlier. Why did you lie down so late?
- Seung Won is next.
-  What I mean is...
Ji Hyo is lucky today.
(You guys are hopeless. Let me handle this myself.)
(I know how to kick a ball fairly well.)
Okay. I'm ready.
Go, Seung Won.
- Okay.
-  Oh, he's good.
He's good.
(He's groping around for the ball.)
(He doesn't fail to disappoint us.)
My gosh.
(Everyone behaves the same with the pair of telescopes.)
We should stand closer to the ball when we kick.
(I must win naengmyun for my teammates.)
(I'll kick you straight to the goal.)
(I was good at football in one of my films.)
(Seung Won scores.)
- Nice.
-  You scored.
-  Yeah.
- Nice.
-  Good kick.
- He scored.
-  I can't block it.
(The ball went to the corner and went in.)
- Nice.
-  You scored.
-  Yes!
(See? I'm good.)
The score is 2 to 1.
- There.
-  You can do it.
You look like you can see properly even with those glasses.
(Oliver Kwang versus Gary Yashin)
- Get ready.
-  You can do it.
(Kwang Soo is focusing really hard.)
What a nice kick.
(Gary kicks the ball.)
Nice shooting.
(Oliver Kwang catches the ball.)
Nice.
- Does your knee hurt?
-  Nice catch.
- Nice. Good job.
-  Kwang Soo blocked it.
- Nice work.
-  Why did you fall down?
Well done, Kwang Soo.
- Come on, Kwang Soo.
-  Good luck.
- Come on.
-  Let's score.
- Go, Gary Yashin.
-  Go, Gary.
- They look like aliens.
-  Let's go.
(A tall alien is looking at the ball...)
Yes, they really do.
(and an ugly alien is trying to block the ball.)
Good.
It might go in.
- Good.
-  It might go in.
(Gary blocks the ball.)
Nice.
- Nice.
-  Good job, Gary. That was so nice.
It's time to eat naengmyun.
- This naengmyun seems so nice.
-  Sorry, guys.
(Team White has won naengmyun.)
- People on the internet are...
-  Gary did really well.
(Yes. It's really delicious.)
(They are looking at them with envy, anger and hunger.)
Well done, Gary.
I really wanted to eat naengmyun.
Give Seung Won a bowl.
He came here to join us today.
I already had a bite. I can't give this to him.
All the shows that I attended with Jae Seok were like this.
- Seung Won, have this.
-  I was always tired and hungry.
- That's true.
-  Every single time.
I always give him a hard time.
- Don't you think so?
-  It often rained just like today.
- Without any notice.
-  Yes. Really.
I know the naengmyun is for that team,
but it's always like this with Jae Seok.
- It's really strange.
-  Can you please order one?
- We will share it together.
-  No, I'm sorry.
Seung Won has money.
- That's right. He can buy one.
-  Yes, I can.
Come on.
Then it's okay, I guess.
(I have enough money. Can't you see?)
- Let's have some naengmyun then.
-  I'll buy you one.
I'll buy you one.
- Really?
-  Yes, really.
- Okay. Let's have one.
-  Isn't it okay?
He's buying.
I've met my friends after a long time.
- So he's buying us a meal.
-  Yes, that's right.
- Okay. We're leaving in 10 minutes.
-  Then we should eat in 10 minutes.
- Make your orders. Quickly.
-  Excuse me.
- Can we have one naengmyun?
-  Order four. I'll pay.
- Four naengmyuns please.
-  You have to pay by yourself.
- Sure.
-  Yes. I'll pay.
- Can I order some extra noodles?
-  Yes, go on.
Order as much as you like. Order some extra noodles.
- I've never seen anyone like him.
-  Can we have one egg mari, too?
- Egg mari? It's good. Okay.
-  Yes. Egg mari.
- Order it.
-  Okay. One egg mari.
- Kimchi kalguksu is on the menu.
-  Really?
- You're amazing.
-  Excuse me.
- I'll have kimchi kalguksu instead.
-  Wait.
Let's check our order again. We're ordering three naengmyun,
one extra noodles, one kimchi kalguksu and two egg mari.
- That's right.
-  Okay. That's it.
- He's really kind.
-  Can I have some Sprite, too?
- Stop it. It's too much.
-  Okay.
Four bottles of Sprite please.
- Four bottles of Sprite, please.
-  That's right.
- He's amazing.
-  Four bottles of Sprite, please.
I've never seen anyone who bought meals in the middle of the show.
- He's the first to bring a wallet.
-  Yes, I have my wallet here.
There were only two people who brought their wallets to...
a TV show. They are Kim Gu Ra and Cha Seung Won.
Gu Ra brings his wallet with him all the time, too.
- Thank you.
-  Thank you.
- Please put it here.
-  Thank you for the meal.
(Lesson for the day: Always bring your wallet with you.)
I didn't expect this.
(It's delicious.)
- So it means that I'm not wrong.
-  You're right.
(Where is he going?)
(Here are your cups.)
- Thank you.
-  Thank you the meal today.
- My goodness.
-  Thank you.
- Seung Won is so kind.
-  He's buying us a meal today.
I wasn't trying to show off. I thought I needed to help them.
- He's so considerate.
-  He's kind like an angel.
(He's picky but kind.)
(He's so nice.)
We have our egg mari here.
I'm so touched.
He's like the Giving Tree.
It's so delicious.
(Everyone has the equal right to eat.)
- You all finished eating,
-  It's so delicious.
so we'll give you another map piece.
But we failed to get any.
Thank you.
We'll give you the map to get to the final destination,
but one of the two doesn't have the hint on it.
Please take it for now...
We need one more.
(Seung Won doesn't forget to collect the receipt.)
(You don't have to shoot this.)
(I treated them nicely today.)
We must win this round.
We almost won the "Slap-Match" round, but failed because of her.
Right, my goodness.
- "Slap-Match".
-  Gosh.
(I'm the queen of slap-match.)
- My goodness.
-  Ji Hyo was too good.
- I practised with my father.
-  Who on earth practises that?
(Ji Hyo practised with her father.)
(Her special instructor was her father.)
(He taught her to hit right in the middle.)
(This is a bad example that you shouldn't follow.)
You shouldn't do like this.
(Thanks to her father, she could win the "Slap-Match" round.)
I will practise table tennis next time.
(Her hard effort didn't betray her.)
(In the fishing quiz mission,)
(she caught a lot of fish.)
Hey, look at this!
- I got it again.
-  Hey.
(She was good at fishing as well.)
Gosh, what is it? I wasn't going to catch it.
- I haven't heard about it.
-  Gosh, look at this.
- What is that?
-  It's a carp!
Goodness, look at this!
(What? You caught a carp?)
(What a shiny carp!)
- I thought...
-  Is that a carp?
(Lucky Ji Hyo even caught a carp.)
- Really?
-  Wow!
Ji Hyo!
- I got it.
-  You've earned extra points.
Okay!
- It's over.
-  I'll give you a hint, too.
- Okay.
-  Thank you.
- Thank you.
-  Good.
Thank you.
(Team Blue earned a map piece and a hint.)
Do you get it?
(Current status: Only Team Blue has a hint.)
(What mission will they do in this fish market?)
- Hello.
-  Will we have to cook here?
- That must be our mission.
-  Is it cooking?
What is this?
- What should we do?
-  What's all this?
We'll give you the last map piece here.
The mission you'll do here is "Relay Cooking".
("Relay Cooking")
"Relay Cooking"?
Each team will have...
one person who will go shopping and three who will cook here.
One member will go buy the ingredients...
for 15 minutes.
The other three members will cook in relay for 10 minutes each.
You should decide the order among your members.
- We'll give you exactly 45 minutes.
-  We only have 10 minutes each.
The three members who will cook will wait in the room that's...
equipped with a monitor.
- I see.
-  So you can't interfere.
You'll come out of the room only when it's your turn.
Jae Seok, you're a good cook.
- By the way,
-  Fix the orders.
why don't we have any basic sauces?
You have to buy everything.
(Do we even have to make the sauce?)
15 minutes won't be enough.
(This sounds pretty difficult.)
- You'll tell us what to cook?
-  Of course, I will.
Gary should go shopping.
(Gary has lived alone for a long time.)
- First...
-  You should buy...
- Buy sugar and salt.
-  We need some soy sauce.
We need soy sauce, starch syrup, red pepper powder and so on.
These are basic ingredients.
- Buy everything that you see.
-  Don't forget soy sauce.
(I got it.)
There's a basic procedure you should follow when you cook.
Put the ingredients first. Then pour water in and the sauce.
(Ingredients should be put in first.)
What if I want to make the sauce?
I don't think we'll have enough time to do that.
- We need doenjang and gochujang.
-  Doenjang and gochujang?
Buy doenjang, gochujang and artificial flavouring.
- MSG?
-  Yes.
How will you decide the winning team?
- You'll see soon.
-  Really?
(How will they decide the winning team?)
(Hello.)
Look at him. He's cute.
(We're watching you.)
Both teams will cook the same menu.
Doenjang and gochujang.
Don't forget MSG.
Kwang Soo.
Doenjang, gochujang, red pepper powder and MSG.
(Don't forget to buy the artificial flavouring.)
It's very important...
to taste food at the proper time.
Ingredients determine 50 percent of the taste, right?
It's no exaggeration to say it takes up about 80 percent.
Fresh ingredients are the key in cooking.
Fresh ingredients can determine a dish's whole taste.
I don't know what they'll cook today,
but the role of the first player is very critical.
We need a strategy today.
One member should spend the entire 10 minutes making the sauce.
- Haha is good at it.
-  And...
I will prepare the ingredients. I'm good at it.
Seung Won will cook first.
I'll be second and Jae Seok will be the last.
Am I the last one?
- I'll go last then.
-  Good.
Who will prepare the ingredients?
I'll take charge of it.
- Are you good at using knives?
-  Not really.
We'll tell you today's menu and count down right away.
This is what you'll cook today.
(This is the last chance to obtain the last map piece.)
(What would they cook today?)
It's nakji jeongol! Start!
- It's nakji jeongol! Start!
-  Nakji jeongol?
(They're off to buy the ingredients.)
Start.
It's nakji jeongol! Start!
- Nakji jeongol?
-  Start!
- It's nakji jeongol! Start!
-  What?
- Kwang Soo!
-  Make sure you buy small octopus.
Buy small octopus, radish, spicy pepper... Gosh.
- The menu is nakji jeongol.
-  I see.
They shouldn't buy hard or tough small octopus.
They're not good for nakji jeongol.
I hope they buy fresh small octopus in dark brown colour.
What are the basic ingredients of nakji jeongol?
- Of course, small octopus.
-  Right.
- I usually add some radish.
-  Radish?
- It'd be good if they added clams.
-  Clams?
Yes. I'd also add some crown daisy.
They need to buy green onion and garlic.
When I make the sauce,
I usually put some fish sauce to make it more savoury.
I hope they also add some fish sauce, too.
(Which team will get a map piece in this round?)
- Nakji jeongol.
-  Nakji jeongol?
- Is this...
-  I don't know what to buy.
- the right way to the fish market?
-  It is.
(These two head to the fish market.)
Let's go to the supermarket first.
(He runs.)
Sauce...
I'll buy the basic ingredients first.
(Kwang Soo, you don't even know what's important, right?)
Where is he?
- Hello.
-  Hello.
- Where can I buy small octopus?
-  Here.
- Right there.
-  I'm making nakji jeongol today.
How much is it?
- It's 3 for 10 dollars.
-  I'll have 3 then.
- You need big ones for jeongol.
-  Look at this. It's big.
- Really? Then give me two, please.
-  Two?
Where is he?
He's over there.
Hello.
What do I need to make nakji jeongol?
What does he need to make nakji jeongol?
- Add mushroom and water parsley.
-  Okay.
- Water parsley and...
-  Radish.
- You also need clam broth.
-  Clam broth?
- Do I need clams?
-  You do.
Please give me some.
Give me everything I need.
- You can't ask her.
-  What are you talking about?
- I just bought small octopus.
-  He's right.
- He asked you what to buy, right?
-  I bout small octopus. That's it.
- I want everything he bought here.
-  Okay.
No way. Go away.
Please give me everything he bought. I'll come back and pay for it.
- I want the same ingredients.
-  Wait. I'm talking to her.
Ma'am, what is this?
Please give me the same.
- Wait, she's mine!
-  What are you talking about?
- I said, she's mine.
-  She's mine.
Go find your own woman.
- Please give me the same.
-  No, stop it.
I want what he bought.
Please give me small octopus!
(Ma'am, please tell me the rest of the ingredients.)
Wait. Come on.
You can't do this.
- What else do I need?
-  You also need some kelp.
(He has gathered all the information.)
- Miss, keep it a secret.
-  Okay.
(Please keep it a secret.)
Kwang Soo should get everything we need.
- He's not reliable.
-  I should've gone instead.
- He'll ask others.
-  Would he?
- He would if he has a brain.
-  Right.
He wouldn't omit the small octopus just to make this show funny, right?
Nakji jeongol without small octopus doesn't make any sense.
I want some abalones.
Please give me three abalones...
and five shrimps.
(He hasn't bought small octopus yet.)
I'd also like three spoon worms.
- How much is this?
-  This one?
It's 38 dollars per kg.
38 dollars per kg? That's too expensive.
No one puts lobster in nakji jeongol.
What do I need then? Isn't it the same as maeuntang?
(Gary is at the supermarket.)
(This is the list of the ingredients Hye Jeong recommended.)
Radish and green onion.
Should I add some bean sprouts with water parsley?
Where is water parsley?
- Do you want me to wrap it?
-  Yes, please.
- Soy sauce.
-  Here it is.
Here's ground garlic.
Where is red pepper powder?
- What are you looking for?
-  Red pepper powder.
- Red pepper powder?
-  Kwang Soo, why are you here?
Ramyeon.
Make sure you buy artificial flavouring.
(He buys ramyeon as Seung Won told him to.)
What else should I buy?
Water parsley, green onion and onion. Where's water parsley?
I'll buy everything Gary bought.
Please give me his receipt.
You're not supposed to use MSG when you cook.
You're nasty.
I'll put them in.
- Time's up for grocery shopping.
-  Yes, it's done.
Okay, let's pay for them.
- So are you done with the grocery?
-  Yes.
Please stand at your table.
- Here they come.
-  Yes.
- They bought the ingredients.
-  They are relaxed.
Kwang Soo bought a lot but Gary didn't buy much.
Kwang Soo bought a lot of ingredients.
He bought a lot.
Please show what you've bought.
I bought kelp, Cheongyang chilli,
- mushrooms...
-  Really?
- Mushrooms,
-  Mushrooms?
- radish,
-  Radish is great.
green onions,
onions,
soy sauce, water parsley...
and small octopus.
I think Gary bought proper ingredients.
There were onion, garlic and so on.
He was smart with his shopping.
- He has red pepper powder.
-  Great.
(Good job.)
Good job.
I bought ramyeon.
He wanted to use the seasoning powder.
Gochujang,
- doenjang,
-  That's right.
- bean sprouts,
-  Good.
- water parsley.
-  Well done.
Good.
And stir-fried small octopus.
(Stir-fried octopus for nakji jeongol?)
Why did he buy that?
He didn't forget small octopus, did he?
Is it okay to buy stir-fried small octopus?
You shouldn't buy ready-made food.
I don't understand him.
- Show me small octopus.
-  Kelp.
- Please, small octopus.
-  Right.
- There should be small octopus.
-  Yes.
- Is he confused?
-  Small octopus please.
- Cabbage.
-  We don't need that.
There should be small octopus.
That must be small octopus.
(Show me the small octopus.)
Crabs.
(Crabs?)
Why the crabs?
- Isn't it cheating?
-  Next is...
- Buying crabs is cheating.
-  Clams.
Crabs will make it delicious.
Abalones.
(What?)
Kwang Soo even bought abalones.
How much did he spend for this nakji jeongol?
He swept everything at the supermarket.
- Did he even buy small octopus?
-  Small octopus.
(Small octopus, please.)
Small octopus.
(Here comes the small octopus.)
- Okay.
-  Good.
- We'll use abalones, clams...
-  Okay.
and small octopus.
For vegetables, we'll use green onions and bean sprouts.
- I'll prep the ingredients.
-  Bean sprouts.
Bean sprouts and mushrooms.
We'll start the timer. The first chefs, please come out.
- It has started.
-  Please come out.
- Chop the green onions.
-  Let's go.
- Let's start.
-  It's okay.
Check how fresh the small octopus is.
We should put the vegetables in later, right?
Put the vegetables in later.
- Time is passing.
-  Boil the water first.
- Today's menu is nakji jeongol.
-  Yes.
First of all, small octopus should be tender.
Since it is jeongol,
there should be enough soup.
- That's what jeongol should be.
-  Right.
It looks easy to make jeongol, but depending on...
how you cook the small octopus,
it can be as soft as willows or as tough as a bark.
It can be tough like a branch.
So we'll wait and watch what they will make.
Boil the water first.
- Clams.
-  Okay.
- Boil the water first.
- Water.
-  Boil some water.
It's not fair to coach him.
Don't coach him what to do.
- Stop, Jae Seok.
-  They're controlling him.
Put some water.
- Put some water.
-  They should stay quiet.
Put in the water!
- You too, Seok Jin!
-  More, more.
More, more.
I can clearly hear them.
- More, more!
-  Am I their puppet?
- More. That's enough.
-  I can hear them.
- Stop.
-  Stop!
-  Okay, that's enough.
(You're my puppet chef.)
What is this?
This is not a relay.
Look. Ji Hyo poured enough water...
to make soup for jeongol...
but Haha's water is not enough at all.
You need plenty of water for that.
Ji Hyo, there are clams.
- What?
-  He bought clams.
He bought clams?
- Wash the clams.
-  Do I have to wash the clams?
- Get rid of the mud.
-  Get rid of the mud.
- Gochujang!
-  Two spoonfuls of it.
(He's putting in doenjang.)
Stop pouring now.
(Your wish is my command.)
It would be better for him to do it all.
- What is he putting?
-  What is it?
- It's doenjang.
-  It looks like doenjang.
That's too much. That's bad.
It's not doenjang jjigae.
He put in too much doenjang...
- compared to the water.
-  I know.
Open it quickly.
Okay, pour it in.
(He is remote-controlling Haha.)
More, more. Now, stop.
- Stop.
-  Cover the brand name.
Turn the ramyeon around so that the brand name won't be shown.
Turn the ramyeon. Okay.
It doesn't matter.
Be quiet, please.
Please be quiet.
- Goodness.
-  Do you own this restaurant?
- Take the plastic away from fire.
-  Be careful.
Seung Won told you to take the plastic away from the fire.
Take the plastic away from the fire.
It's dangerous.
- Dissolve the doenjang.
-  This is not right.
- Resolve it.
-  Just come out here.
Haha is just busy with the doenjang.
- It'll be doenjang jjigae.
-  Maybe.
Put in a third of a ladle of red pepper powder.
A third of a ladle is enough.
- A third of it.
-  A third.
(Haha got used to the orders.)
- Okay. That's enough.
-  Okay.
Now, put in the vegetables. Put them in.
This is not a relay.
What kind of a cooking competition is this?
This is nonsense.
It's not fair to coach a player when they play.
While preparing the broth,
you should wash the ingredients.
Ji Hyo went to wash the ingredients.
(Smart Ji Hyo washes the ingredients.)
Loot at her.
- She brought a strainer.
-  She is smart.
- Women are good at this.
-  Right.
She puts them in after washing.
(She looks feminine today.)
- She's back.
-  She's here.
What did she wash?
- Green onions...
-  She puts the clams in first.
There she goes.
She is doing great.
Did she get rid of the mud?
- Should I put in the radish?
-  Cut the radish.
- Cut the radish.
Cut them into big pieces.
- Big pieces.
-  That's good.
You're doing great.
That's enough. Put it in.
Look how well she is doing.
She knows how to cook.
- Take your time.
-  Take your time.
Don't put in too much Cheongyang chilli.
Let's see how she does.
She's good.
- She's good.
-  You're good.
You can get married.
Cut them into bigger pieces.
- Bigger pieces?
-  Look.
I was going to put these into the sauce.
- That's okay.
-  Was it for the sauce?
- It was for the sauce.
-  Good.
- She is doing great.
-  Not bad.
You need two stems of green onions.
- Two stems.
-  Two stems.
Two fresh stems.
No. I mean the ones in your right hand.
- Yes.
-  Right.
- Diagonally.
-  Cut them diagonally.
Cut them into 1cm long.
That's bigger than 1cm!
- Calm down.
-  It's okay.
Tell them they need to calm down.
Haha didn't wash anything at all.
I know. Maybe he's not going to wash his ingredients.
He just unwrapped the chilli and is now cutting it.
- You bought kelp.
-  Yes.
Cut it 10cm by 10cm.
- 10 by 10.
-  10 by 10.
10cm by 10cm.
Good.
Cut it in half.
We need some more.
- Okay, put it in.
-  Shall I put it in?
- Okay.
-  That's enough.
That's enough.
- That's enough!
-  Do as you're told.
- This soup doesn't look good.
-  That's because of the doenjang.
There will not be enough soup left.
You're right.
I'll go next.
I think you should go next.
How can I finalise the food then?
- I'll almost finish it.
-  Okay.
You have 30 more seconds left.
Put in the bean sprouts.
Just two handfuls.
That's too much.
- He said two handfuls.
-  Just two.
15 seconds!
I'll get going.
- Go, Seung Won.
-  Go, go.
You have to actually finish cooking.
You should almost finish it.
Ji Hyo preps the ingredients very well.
She is good.
Haha you should come to the table.
Time's up. It's the second chefs turn.
Second chef, please come out.
Come out.
- Drop what you're doing.
-  Okay. It's my turn.
Go, Seung Won.
(The second chef of Team Blue is Seung Won.)
(Here comes Seung Won.)
Good job.
- You're not the last chef.
-  No, I'm not.
I washed the bean sprouts.
- Hurry up.
-  Seok Jin is here.
See? Seung Won comes in the middle.
- Right.
-  The order is important.
As you said, he comes third...
to almost finalise the food and pass it onto Jae Seok.
I think so.
- The beansprouts are over there.
-  Okay.
I left them there.
- Good job.
-  It was so hectic.
-  You did well.
Now, we don't need to tell him to do anything.
Where are the bean sprouts?
Over there.
They are well prepared.
You said you wanted to know Seung Won's cooking.
Yes, I'm curious.
- How would he...
-  Let's see how he cooks.
Let's see.
I think they sell washed ones.
(He pours water to make it less salty.)
He doesn't measure.
- Seung Won added water.
-  Yes.
It might have turned into a steamed dish...
or it could have been ruined...
but Seung Won added some water.
He's working very hard.
He's working without rest.
It's like a cooking competition show.
(I will revive this jeongol at all costs.)
Seung Won isn't the last player.
- Are you putting in sauce?
-  He's adding sauce.
- That's a lot.
-  Seok Jin is adding the whole...
gochujang pack.
- He's still managing to make...
-  Right.
- the sauce in a bowl.
-  Exactly.
Ji Hyo added two of those.
- Wash the small octopus!
-  Okay.
Two minutes has passed.
Two minutes? Already?
You have to wash the small octopus now!
- The small octopus!
-  Okay!
- We're going to win.
-  Is Seok Jin in slow motion?
What's he doing?
It's very important how one handles the small octopus.
It's the most important. It's important how tender...
and chewy one can make it.
This is so difficult.
(Seok Jin barely catches up and begins to wash the small octopus.)
- Are you finished already?
-  Yes.
(Screaming)
My gosh, it's alive!
(The small octopus is still alive.)
Oh my goodness. This isn't easy.
(Seok Jin is startled.)
I was really frightened. I'm not joking.
(Screaming)
He should've left it to me.
I can wash it before we put it in.
Gosh, it's not easy.
(Seok Jin returns.)
Why isn't this boiling?
Look at the lid. Close the lid properly!
(You keep opening the lid.)
- What?
-  Close the lid properly.
If you keep opening it, it won't boil even more.
Can you be quiet?
Hurry up and close it.
- You surprised me.
-  You can't come out here.
Why is he opening the lid?
- Don't add the bean sprouts now.
-  What's wrong?
What did I do wrong? Why are they yelling at me?
If you add the bean sprouts now, won't it get soggy?
Will it be soggy?
Do you add it as a whole?
He's cutting it up.
- Goodness, he's great at this.
-  He cuts off the ink.
- Right.
-  The eyes, too.
(He chops with charisma.)
He's so sexy.
- It's a master technique.
-  Do you add it already?
It's important how tender and chewy you make the small octopus.
Won't the small octopus get stiff if you add it too quickly?
(Won't the small octopus get stiff if you add it too quickly?)
You can add it as a whole after boiling the soup.
You can cut it with the scissors after it cooks.
It's a big minus for the main ingredient to get stiff.
(It's a big loss.)
(Seung Won continues to add the small octopus.)
We don't have to worry.
- You surprised me.
-  You can't come out here.
He just adds the whole thing.
Seok Jin is just making the sauce after washing the small octopus.
The other team added the octopus too early so it may be stiff.
- Seok Jin isn't putting it in yet.
-  Right.
I'm curious to know if he simply forgot about it or if it's intended.
- This is...
-  Gary, did you buy the sugar?
Close the lid. You don't have to take that out.
- Right. I'll take it out.
-  There are too much bubbles.
- They said not to take it out.
-  Seok Jin.
Stop taking that out and just close the lid so it can boil.
Just come back.
This tastes good if you eat it now.
Just close the lid already!
- Stop it!
-  Stop.
- Close the lid!
-  He won't keep it closed.
- I have to open it to add things.
-  He's not keeping it closed again.
- Add the clams.
-  We bought the pickled shrimp.
Okay.
Where is it?
- It looks great.
-  It's in front of you!
- Oh, it's here.
-  Right.
He's so skilled.
- Jae Seok can add water parsleys...
-  Add onions and the small octopus.
(Seung Won adds various vegetables.)
(Team Blue's nakji jeongol is almost complete.)
Look at ours.
We're almost done. You can say that we're almost finished.
If it just tastes good.
I don't know if I'm making it the right way.
- That...
-  Make the sauce.
(It's up to Jong Kook to revive it.)
- Five seconds left.
-  Add the water parsley.
- The results...
-  I should wash the water parsley.
- Add the mushrooms later.
-  Jae Seok, get ready.
- Okay, let's go!
-  Change players.
- Add more vegetables.
-  Go in, please.
- Jae Seok,
-  It's already...
taste it and add just a bit of...
- the ends of the water parsley.
-  The clams!
- Just a little bit.
-  Add the small octopus last.
- Okay.
-  Just taste it.
- Taste it for flavour.
-  Okay.
- Taste it.
-  The scent is already...
- great. I'll add the clams.
-  What is this?
What's wrong with this sauce?
- What is that?
-  What...
(It looks awful as well.)
It's lacking sweet flavour.
- Jae Seok,
-  Yes?
just wash five clams in the kitchen.
- Good. Just five.
-  That's enough!
That's plenty. Don't add too much.
You'll fall! Be careful.
(Jae Seok is washing the clams for the nakji jeongol.)
The clams should've gone in earlier.
- They should've put it in earlier.
-  That's right.
The clams should be added first like Ji Hyo did...
- to create a hearty taste.
-  Right.
Make the clam broth first.
- He's not going to add the sauce.
-  You can add more!
I'm going to add more!
Are you going to change it to a non-spicy soup?
I'm curious as to when he will add the small octopus.
You have to add the small octopus and water parsley now.
Put it in as a whole.
- Do I add it as a whole?
-  Just put it in as a whole.
- Just put it in.
-  Cut it after it cooks.
- Put it in. Good job.
-  Add one more!
- You should cut it first.
-  Put it all in.
- Don't you have to cut it first?
-  No. Just put it in.
You usually cut it with scissors after it cooks.
The ink bursts if you cut it first.
(The small octopus is added last.)
Did they add the octopus now?
- It's tender when it's added last.
-  Small octopus...
- isn't supposed to be added first.
-  Close the lid. It has to boil.
It has to boil for three minutes and we're done.
Doesn't this look like a dish from a skilled restaurant?
- You're right.
-  Doesn't it?
It looks like it's from a very famous restaurant.
- Jae Seok, taste it for flavour.
-  Okay.
(Team Blue's nakji jeongol is almost complete.)
- The small octopus is done.
-  It tastes good.
- It tastes pretty good, Seung Won.
-  Does it taste good?
It tastes good.
- There are 30 seconds left.
-  I usually eat blandly.
I wanted to make a clear soup like that.
Okay. Let's make ours clear and not spicy.
Yeonpotang tastes better than nakji jeongol.
- There are 20 seconds left.
-  I can...
I can make this taste so much better if I add one more.
Of course, you can.
- Four, three...
-  Should I add red pepper powder?
two and one.
Time is over.
(Who will be the winner in the small octopus cook-off?)
(Time over)
We said that we have panellists here.
- Yes.
-  We'll have them join us now.
- Do we have judges?
-  Please come in.
Who are the panellists?
- What?
-  Isn't that...
- Who is it?
-  Again?
- Hye Jeong.
-  My goodness.
When did you get here?
- Come over here.
-  Please come here.
Come here.
- When did you get here?
-  Hello.
- Hi.
I'm watching you carefully.
(I've had my eye on you.)
They've been watching you guys cook the whole time.
- Is that so?
-  Yes. They were inside.
- So everything can be judged.
-  My gosh.
Can you tell us your exact standards for evaluation?
My first standard is whether or not...
- the completed dish is edible.
-  That's right.
So it's not whether or not it tastes good.
It's a bit difficult to discuss good taste here.
That's my first standard.
I watched Seung Won very carefully today.
It should be enough that he's handsome,
but he's taking away our jobs by cooking well too.
He cooks very well though.
What surprised me was...
the way he cleaned and organised the area like professionals do.
- Not anyone can do that.
-  You're right.
(This is me.)
- But just one thing is...
-  Don't laugh like that...
- in front of Hye Jeong.
-  that he cooks a bit arrogantly.
He pours the red pepper powder with the entire bottle.
If you make a mistake, you can pour too much.
It was nice to be able to catch a fault in him.
It was impressive to see Jong Kook wiping his hands when he came out.
You are right.
That's the least he can do.
(It's a given.)
He should do that at least.
- Okay, Hye Jeong.
-  Yes.
- Please give a fair evaluation.
-  Hwan, you should try some too.
(How will Team Blue's taste?)
- If you try it, it tastes decent.
-  Right.
- It smells nice.
-  Doesn't it?
We did well.
(How well did Seung Won's skills seep into the dish?)
- This is the right colour.
-  Right.
(It's delicious!)
It's delicious.
Haha did well. His throwing in of doenjang helped.
- She said "throwing in".
-  It helped to match the flavour.
It's true.
- It's so delicious.
-  Seung Won added red pepper powder.
This created a great harmony between the doenjang and gochujang.
(Exclaiming)
- The doenjang is delicious.
-  Isn't it?
The small octopus isn't stiff either.
- It's unexpected.
-  Right.
This dish is edible.
(This dish is edible.)
- Great. We can eat it.
-  It's edible!
In terms of meat, it's like grilled meat instead of seasoned meat.
- I see.
-  It looks good.
- We avoided any kicks in flavour.
-  I see.
Isn't it okay?
How did they make it?
Isn't it hearty?
I personally don't like adding salt.
- Adding white radish...
-  Yes.
made it extremely refreshing.
We also added the small octopus last.
It must taste refreshing.
The small octopus is more tender than Team Blue.
- That's right.
-  We put it in last.
- That's what we were aiming for.
-  Ji Hyo also added the clams first.
The soup brewed out from the clams and made it more refreshing.
I have a slight cold right now, but I feel like my cold has disappeared.
(The clam soup healed her cold.)
It's a great dish for healing.
Both of these dishes are edible.
The delicious nakji jeongol that we usually eat is here.
- But that side...
-  Yes?
Team White had less ingredients and Team Blue had more,
- so there's an advantage with that.
-  Right.
(Which team's dish did the panellists like more?)
But I still choose this team.
(Blue Team wins "Relay Cooking".)
- We won.
-  Hurrah.
We won.
(He bows to express gratitude.)
- Thank you.
-  Thank you.
-  You did a good job.
- It's delicious.
-  Thank you.
- Try some.
-  I want some soup.
- Gary, try some.
-  It's delicious.
Yes, it's very delicious.
(Small octopus looks nice and chewy.)
Kwang Soo.
- Ours is delicious.
-  It is.
It's really good.
- I love how it tastes.
-  It's delicious.
- Try some.
-  I love how it tastes.
(Spicy nakji jeongol is appetising.)
- I love this taste.
-  Kwang Soo would love it.
- This is very good.
-  It has an interesting taste.
Both of them are delicious.
(Today, they put their cooking skills to a good use.)
You just finished your mission.
Once you get the last piece,
you can discuss and figure out the final destination.
We'll give you the last piece when you get to your car.
At the final destination, you'll find a map platform.
With the maps and hints you collected today,
you'll be able to complete the map.
(The 2 teams obtained hints and map pieces during 4 missions.)
- We need 1 more.
-  We need 1 more to complete.
(With one more piece, the outline of final destination is revealed.)
- There must be another piece.
-  We need one more.
They're giving us the last one.
- Here's the last piece I mentioned.
-  Okay.
Here you go.
It's a hint. Find out what it is.
- Is that it?
-  Yes.
- Here it is. Take a look.
-  Take a look.
Shall we start moving? Let's get going for now.
- Does it work?
-  Let's start moving first.
- Do you see something?
-  It's Yeouido High School.
- Isn't that Hangang...
-  It's Hangang Park.
It's under Wonhyo Bridge. There's a road underneath you can take.
Like C, the hint we got has M on the back.
It must be a similar hint.
- I found the final destination.
-  Where is it?
- I found it.
-  Here it is.
Where?
- Yeouido High School.
-  It's Hangang Park.
It's Yeouido, Hangang.
This is certain.
- "Yeouido, Hangang"?
-  Yes.
We found it.
- Is that the destination?
-  I knew we'd find it.
Go to Wonhyo Bridge after passing 63 Building.
- It's that part of Hangang River.
-  It's close to Wonhyo Bridge.
- Is that it?
-  I think so.
- There's a cruise ship dock.
-  That's it.
- There it is.
-  We should hurry.
- There's a puddle of water.
-  Get out of the car first.
There's a puddle of water.
- Just go.
-  Shall we go now?
- Start running.
-  To where?
- It's that way.
-  Is that it?
This is the place.
Is the other team already here?
They arrived early.
- They are here.
-  Hurry up.
This place is it.
Where is it?
(They must find a platform and place the completed map.)
Where is it? Where?
Is this it? Wait. What's this?
It's my first time running on Running Man.
- It's my first time running.
-  Is this it?
What's this?
- We must place the completed map.
-  Put the map together.
- Don't we need another piece?
-  Which one is it?
- It's like this.
-  That's at the bottom.
- Does it go here?
-  This is right.
(Will Team Blue win by blocking Team White's interruption?)
Does it go here?
- We need one more.
-  This goes at the bottom.
We have to find one more.
- We must find it.
-  We must find one more piece.
(Wasn't the map complete before?)
Which one is missing?
(Where is the missing puzzle piece?)
(A rectangular map needs another piece when put in a square form.)
Do we have to find it?
You don't have one hint,
so you don't know the secret to the last piece.
- You'll find R Mons at this place.
-  R Mon?
Hold R Mon...
and put this against it.
You'll see a clear R on a real R Mon.
The fake one will say "Fail".
- Where? Oh, I see it.
-  It says on here.
You must find the right R Mon. If you find it quickly,
- I'll give you the last hint.
-  Okay.
I understand.
Many R Mons are scattered all the way to the playground.
- Okay.
-  You must go now.
Let's go.
Where are they?
I'm bad at this kind of game.
(Among 30 R Mons, 3 of them are real.)
Here's one.
(He finds one R Mon.)
(Is this the real one?)
Kwang Soo. It says "Fail".
(Fail. Try again.)
There it is. We found one.
Let's take a look.
Is it there?
(Am I real or not?)
It says "Fail".
This isn't real.
(Where are the real R Mons?)
It says "Fail".
Here it is.
(This one says "Fail".)
(This one says "Fail", too.)
- Hello, Gary.
-  Hello.
Move it out of the way.
(Catching real R Mon is as difficult as a mobile phone game.)
(They work hard in vain as R Mons appear and vanish quickly.)
"Fail".
We're in trouble.
That's not the one.
There's one.
(Everyone runs toward one R Mon.)
"Fail". Gosh.
Here's one.
(Is the one on a seesaw real?)
Hello.
Let's see.
(It's the real one!)
(I saw it and found it.)
Seung Won.
Did you find it?
The other team got something.
They must have found one.
(He tears it off.)
It says "CMI".
(What does "CMI" mean?)
What does "CMI" mean?
(The last secret to the map is hidden in CMI.)
- Did you find it?
-  I found it.
- It says "CMI".
-  What?
- "CMI".
-  It just says "CMI".
That means music.
- That's right.
-  What?
(CMI seems to mean music.)
CMI refers to music.
- What was that?
-  Is that in order?
What were the letters we got before?
Which letters remain?
- There aren't any.
-  We found C and M.
(It's R Mon.)
This one has to be real.
(It seems like the real one.)
This one looks different.
It's supposed to say R, right?
- Gary found one.
-  Where?
He's over there.
Do I tear it off?
(He tears off the sticker.)
"CMI"?
Is this the hint?
- Did you find it?
-  This is the hint.
It says, "CMI".
- C?
-  M and I.
Cha Seung Won.
- What?
-  Does Cha start with a C?
- What's CMI?
-  It's not Cha Seung Won.
(Let's go put the map together.)
Kwang Soo, bring it.
Bring it, Kwang Soo.
- Kwang Soo.
-  What's CMI?
- Did you get the three letters?
-  Yes.
You can find out the secret to the map.
- What's CMI?
-  The answer is in those letters.
What could it be?
This is where we cooked. This isn't the fish market.
Market?
Market? Cold?
Isn't it "I'm Cha"?
- I said it's "I'm Cha Seung Won".
-  Isn't it "I'm Cha"?
- Let's go there.
-  What do we do now?
We have to do something with CMI.
Isn't it "I'm Cha"?
(Cha Seung Won? Music? What on earth is CMI?)
Isn't it short form of microphone?
MIC for microphone?
(Wait, if it's a microphone, isn't it something we're wearing?)
Find a microphone.
- A microphone? Where's the map?
-  It's here.
Isn't a microphone hiding somewhere on us?
Microphone.
- Roger.
-  Roger, copy that.
-  It fits perfectly.
- Microphone.
-  It's MIC.
(He talks gibberish.)
(Does the map appear when I do this?)
- Roger.
-  MIC.
- Isn't it right?
-  Check this out.
Wait a minute. MC Yu.
It's MIC.
I think it's microphone.
You are so close.
I was surprised by how far you got.
The other team probably found out.
(They must stop Team Blue from figuring it out.)
- They haven't figured it out.
-  No, they didn't.
CMI, CMI.
See if there's anything on your microphone.
Check your microphone.
(He searches the microphone pocket.)
(Is it in Seung Won's pocket?)
They're coming in the back. Be careful.
I don't think it's in there.
Wait.
(Wait.)
(He found the last piece.)
(The last map piece was in the microphone pocket.)
Kwang Soo.
(What's the secret of the map?)
(You win once you take the flag.)
(They finally figured out the secret of the map.)
(Where is the flag?)
- Where's the flag?
-  Do we look for the flag?
What's going on?
(At that moment,)
(a flag rises from afar.)
What's going on?
(He starts to run.)
- What is it?
-  The flag is up.
- Take it.
-  Take it now.
They're after us.
(Let's catch them first.)
What's going on?
Jae Seok.
(Everyone's goal is to take the flag.)
- Get it.
-  It's up.
(Will they take the flag or lose it?)
- The flag is up.
-  Run for it.
- Hurry.
-  Pull it out now.
-  Hold it tight.
- All right.
-  I got it.
No, this one.
(Seung Won gets the flag.)
- Kwang Soo.
-  Jae Seok!
Did you find it in Seung Won's microphone?
- It was right here.
-  You mean the missing piece?
Right. I removed this and it was right here.
- Wow.
-  You're amazing.
You did a great job.
- Wow!
-  Good job.
We made it.
- Goodness.
-  I'm about to cry now.
- Seung Won.
-  Seung Won got the flag.
He's the final winner today.
What?
We're a team.
Seung Won is the final winner.
(What are you talking about?)
We let him get the flag.
- We even held it for him.
-  We came here first.
Please look at this.
- Every microphone had a piece.
-  Wait.
- But it is...
-  Please read this.
(The one who gets the flag becomes the final winner.)
My goodness, we're a team.
- Is he the winner?
-  Yes.
- We told you.
-  Why...
Why was mine put in weirdly?
Why did you insert the piece like this?
Thank goodness you didn't find yours.
If you did, you would've betrayed us.
- It's right here.
-  Right.
You carried it with you the entire day.
Really?
Kwang Soo, you...
Therefore, Seung Won is the winner of the Golden Compass.
- My goodness.
-  This is ridiculous.
I thought our team was the final winner.
Guys, take your microphones off.
Goodness. It was a hint.
Frankly speaking, I'm not that happy.
I don't really know what's going on.
- I'm holding it because it's mine.
-  Seung Won!
You're very selfless.
No, I really didn't mean this.
I was going to get the flag,
- but changed my mind for you.
-  He's right.
I wouldn't have known if not for Kwang Soo.
I think Kwang Soo should get the Golden Compass.
Give me that Golden Compass.
This is the Golden Compass.
- Will you give it to Kwang Soo?
-  No, I'll take it.
- It's okay, right?
-  Yes.
- What is this?
-  It is...
This is the Golden Compass.
- Thank you.
-  I didn't know about this.
- Good.
-  Please give a round...
of applause to Seung Won!
You must be very lucky.
(Congratulations, Seung Won.)
I'm no longer a criminal!
What have we done wrong?
(That's how everything began.)
Welcome aboard the Train to Prison.
A trip? Why do I have to be locked up?
- Why did you do that to me?
-  Just put me behind bars.
I have a bad feeling.
Let's escape when we get to Cheonan.
(They struggle to escape from the train.)
I'll hide this inside my cloth and run away.
- What are you doing?
-  You can't do this to me.
- Goodness.
-  Is this the end of the escape?
(Train to Prison)