(This Week's Special, Descendants of the Sun)
(They received orders to appear on Running Man.)
- Oh my goodness. - She's a good dancer.
(Kim Ji Won's charming dance)
Is it not me?
(Manly Jin Goo's unexpected charm is revealed.)
(The guests took off their badges and put on name tags instead.)
(It's a race that's more difficult and intense than that in Urk.)
(Descendants of the Sun versus Running Man)
Give me a second.
(Sergeant Major Seo and Lieutenant Yoon's heartfelt love story)
(Their unfinished story will be continued today on Running Man.)
(A Running Man Special, Descent of the Sun)
I heard Jin Goo is coming today. We are like brothers.
Stop acting friendly with him all of a sudden.
- Are you close to everyone? - Haha, please tell them.
They don't believe me.
Jae Seok and I helped him a lot when he was getting married.
- Really. - It's true.
- Jin Goo will agree, too. - Listen to him.
- We helped him. - All right. Let's ask him.
- Let's ask him when he shows up. - Go ahead. Ask him.
- I brought special friends today. - What are you doing?
(Why are you suddenly acting like the host?)
- Are you the host? - What are you holding in your hand?
- Stop it. - Why are you holding the cue cards?
- Hey, stop it. - You're not the host.
I wasn't confident.
How dare you take the cue cards?
You were waiting for a good time to begin, weren't you?
- What is this? - I thought it was great timing.
- Look at this. - Wasn't my timing nice?
Doesn't he look like a host at a meet and greet...
for "Descendants of the Sun"?
- Right. - He looks like the host.
(He's working two jobs.)
- Why am I the host? - The meet-and-greet host.
I am a cast member!
Oh, gosh.
When will you start? Just start.
"Korea is mad for this man."
"Hallyu"...
- Can't a voice-over artist do it? - He's so bad at it.
- What's wrong with him? - He's really bad.
"This captivating man enchanted not only Korea but also China."
- "He's the hero of Korean dramas." - You will lose your voice soon.
"I will regret all the times I ran away from you."
Acting really doesn't suit you.
- Acting is not your forte. - It's my favourite line.
Stop it now.
"This man came to steal women's hearts!"
- Jin Goo! - It's Jin Goo!
(He's the man who captured women's hearts.)
(Sergeant Major Seo comes to Running Man.)
- My goodness. - It's Jin Goo.
- Jin Goo. - Hey, Jin Goo!
(Korea is mad for Sergeant Major Seo.)
(Jin Goo acts as a masculine man who sincerely loves one woman.)
- Hey, Jin Goo. - Jin Goo!
Jin Goo!
Welcome, Jin Goo.
(His military outfit looks pitiful.)
- Jin Goo! - Move, Seok Jin!
- Jin Goo. - I am a big fan.
- Welcome. - I've been your fan.
It's nice to meet you.
- Look at him. - Gosh.
First of all... Stop it!
- Let me take a picture. - Stop it!
Don't post it on your SNS.
- Goodness. - It's a secret photo.
Jin Goo is here.
Please say hello to our viewers first.
Dear viewers of Running Man, it's nice to meet you all.
I am a fan myself, and I finally got to visit Running Man. I'm Jin Goo.
Jin Goo!
He did this.
Oh, gosh.
Salute.
(They say the same word, but it feels completely different.)
This is how he does it.
- Just don't do it. - By the way,
I have a question for him. Did you hear him?
Did Jae Seok really help you get married?
- Of course. We got him married. - We were the deciding factors.
- Haha as well? - They played a significant role.
See, it's true. He said it.
And I have something to say here.
A long time after I got married, I went on "Happy Together"...
as a guest, and he gave me a wedding gift with money.
Is that right?
- So I did that. - Yes.
I'm glad. I was actually wondering...
if I paid the congratulatory money or not.
I'm really glad.
- I'm glad. - Jin Goo.
I will give it to you today.
Did you not give it to him yet?
- He's my brother. - All right.
Who is the next guest?
"An angel"... "With great beauty came to Running Man."
He's terrible.
- He didn't prepare well. - Wait.
- Can you be more prepared? - What's this?
He's the special host for this episode.
- What is he doing? - I even saw him reading the script.
And he still does it like that.
- Hurry up. - "Her charms will entrance you."
Kim Ji Won!
- It's my first time meeting her. - Me, too.
- Ji Won is beautiful. - I can't wait to see her.
(Finally, an angel has arrived on Running Man.)
(Kim Ji Won)
Did you ever think about what you want to do outside of the military?
Don't you take your outfit off unless I do it myself.
(The angel of Urk, Yoon Myeong Ju, comes to Running Man.)
(She is an angel.)
She's beautiful!
- She became more beautiful. - She's the best!
She got prettier!
She's so pretty!
(The beautiful angel is here.)
Ji Won, you became even more beautiful.
- She's unbelievable. - It's my first time seeing her.
Call her Ms Ji Won.
It's just Ji Won.
(It's a burdensome escort from Kwang Soo.)
You are so beautiful.
- Hello. - She's beautiful.
Ji Won is...
She's truly beautiful.
- What happened? - Wait. Let's rearrange ourselves.
- Can you go to the end, Seok Jin? - No!
- Why would I do that? - It just looks...
- They are beautiful, and... - You can just cut me out.
- But really... - It just looks bad.
- You ruin the picture. - And why did you wear that jacket?
Gary, can you come here?
- Stay with Ji Hyo. - I am too embarrassed.
- Why? - Gary, take off your hat.
No!
(His bare head is revealed.)
(Everyone is in shock.)
- What's wrong with Gary? - What happened to him?
- Gosh... - He shaved his head.
I don't know why I shaved my head today.
(It suddenly looks like the movie "Silmido".)
I apologise.
Ji Won, please say hi to our viewers.
Hello, I am Kim Ji Won who played Yoon Myeong Ju.
I am so thankful.
(Angel Lieutenant Yoon reports her attendance.)
- I am so thankful. - She's more beautiful in person.
- She's very pretty. - How is she...
How is...
Her eyes are...
- Her eyes are huge. - She's beautiful.
- She's like a cartoon. - She's so beautiful.
- There's one more guest. - Is there someone else?
"She's 2016's hottest rising star."
- Who is it? - It's Eunseo from Cosmic Girls!
- Eunseo? - It's Eunseo.
(It's Eunseo from Cosmic Girls!)
(A mysterious girl has come to Running Man.)
(Cosmic Girls came to Running Man!)
- Eunseo! - She's from Kwang Soo's agency.
Oh, gosh!
- Cosmic Girls! - Yes!
It's Eunseo.
(Eunseo from Cosmic Girls)
(Cosmic Girl Eunseo is on Running Man.)
- Come here, Eunseo. - Oh, goodness.
- She's so young. - Wait.
Wait a minute.
I am very glad that Eunseo is here.
But how is she related to Jin Goo and Ji Won?
- Is there a connection? - How are you related?
I represent...
(I am a representative...)
(Was she on "Descendants of the Sun?")
(Or is she a soldier's daughter like Lieutenant Yoon is?)
I represent the viewers of "Descendants of the Sun".
- I see. - I see.
She must've prepared to answer this question.
- What? - She knew we'd ask her this.
Hold on.
Did you help her get on the show because she's from the same agency?
- Did you talk her into this? - No. No.
- He's the lead actor. - We are all colleagues.
- How so? - We shot a music video together.
And they were in "Descendants of the Sun" together.
- With Jin Goo... - You...
- Kwang Soo is the best. - Now you can help someone.
You're in the position to help someone else now.
- He's a big shot now. - It's not like that.
I'll say this though. Focus on helping yourself.
(Jae Seok gives a cutting remark.)
- I will stick around until the end. - Take care of yourself first.
- Why humiliate me in front of her? - I am sorry.
- He says he's sorry. - Eunseo...
- Eunseo joined us on Running Man. - She's lovely.
- We have three precious guests. - Yes.
- They are my best mates. - We already introduced them,
but we will introduce each of them in detail.
I normally don't interview guests.
- But today is special. - It's special.
- First, Jin Goo. - Yes.
You became much more popular. Can you feel your popularity?
How is it? Please tell us honestly.
I started using SNS.
(He began using SNS.)
But you usually don't do that.
- You must have a lot of followers. - I'm just not good at it.
Jin Goo is on SNS?
- It doesn't suit him! - I know.
I started it,
and the reaction was intense.
How many followers do you have?
I think as of today, I have around one million followers.
- Wow! - Wow!
It took Seok Jin three years to get that many!
It took him three years!
It took him 50 years.
After the drama ended, how have you been doing?
After the drama ended,
I watched all the airing episodes,
and now I am watching replays at home.
- You're immersed in it. - You're immersed in the drama.
- She's immersed in it. - You haven't gotten out of it yet.
She doesn't want to get out of it.
- I'm watching it all the time. - She hasn't gotten out of it yet.
How is it, Ji Won? Actually,
she rose to stardom through TV commercials.
She shot many TV commercials.
- She shot a lot of them. - "I picked a star in the sky."
The best one is not the recent ones. That star one was the best.
Can you show us how you did it?
(The drink commercial that made Ji Won famous)
I picked a star from the sky
I picked the moon from the sky
I will put them in your hands
It's been such a long time so I don't remember it well.
But you were so lovely in that commercial.
(They force her to start by clapping their hands.)
I picked a star from the sky
- Her voice is amazing. - I picked the moon from the sky
I will put them in your hands
- Bravo! - Wonderful!
(Jae Seok is captivated.)
(Her angelic voice captures the men's hearts.)
Oh my goodness!
Her voice is angelic.
- The next part is "Beautiful days". - Beautiful days
I didn't know about this.
There's my childhood friend, Seung Joon.
There's my buddy, Joong Ki...
- and my buddy Jin Goo. - Why are they your buddies?
- I'm here, too. Aren't I? - I know.
You're here.
Don't keep talking as if you were one of the cast on the show.
I'm sure you were jealous.
You are the president of Joong Ki's fan club.
What are you talking about?
- How can you say that? - He's...
busy being a celebrity and a fan club president.
I am not the president.
- And you work as an event host. - That's right.
- He... - Why am I the event host?
I heard he went to the after party for your drama.
It wasn't the after party. It was a cast party.
- At the time... - Wasn't it strange to have him?
- Was he there? - He asked, "Was he there?"
He must've been drunk.
- He's pretty invisible. - I was there!
- He's tall, yet... - Were you there?
- He's tall, yet he's invisible. - That's hilarious.
They had no idea you were there.
- I was... - Do you not remember him?
- Where did you go? - Ji Won?
- I don't remember him being there. - Really?
(Their memory of Kwang Soo has been deleted.)
- Don't do that. - What happened?
I was there with the chairman of the production company.
- That's scary. - I see.
I've never been so surprised since "Whispering Corridors".
- I remember it. - He was there.
What's with this reaction?
- Why were you there anyways? - So...
- don't go there. - It wasn't your place to be.
All the bosses were there at the time,
- so we were too nervous. - That's why they needed him.
- They needed him for comic relief. - But even so...
- Even if you were nervous... - They needed him.
You are being too harsh.
- Why would you say that? - Since it's a difficult situation,
they needed him to make them laugh.
- Like a clown? - That's harsh.
Don't you think that's too harsh?
- You were a laughing stock. - Why call him a laughing stock?
- That's so funny. - Seok Jin, you are too mean.
Let's talk about Eunseo now.
- She's a member of Cosmic Girls. - I know them.
- I know them. - They're a girl group.
Please sing...
- us a song of Cosmic Girls. - Show us.
- I will sing a part of it. - Do we have music?
("Mo Mo Mo" by Cosmic Girls)
- This is not my part. - It's "Mo Mo Mo".
(It's not her part, but she dances perfectly.)
This is my part!
She doesn't just swing her arm.
- She's so cute. - It goes like this.
(I am a Cosmic Girl.)
- She's so lively. - Seriously.
Jin Goo danced to Red Velvet's "Dumb Dumb" on the drama.
- Right! - Yes!
- That's right! - I remember.
(Sergeant Major Seo's version of "Dumb Dumb".)
Jin Goo, you should show us.
- Dumb Dumb Dumb Dumb - Do you have the song?
That's right. You danced to their performance.
- That's good. - Go, Jin Goo!
- Jin Goo, let's go! - Jin Goo!
Jin Goo, let's go!
(I'll show you if you really want to see it.)
(Here comes the dancing machine.)
(He looks disciplined.)
You've changed a lot, Jin Goo.
(His hips have edge.)
(He's a "Descendent of the Dance".)
- Good job. - That was good.
- Hey, Ji Won. - That was cute.
Ji Won. While we're at it,
- could you dance for us? - She knows how to dance.
- Is that right? - She dances well.
Please give her the music.
- How do I do this? - Go ahead, Ji Won.
You can do it.
This is "Bombastic".
- Let's go! - Kim Ji Won! Kim Ji Won!
- Kim Ji Won! Kim Ji Won! - Watch her.
- Wow. - What's that?
Ji Won, what's that?
Kim Ji Won! Kim Ji Won!
(She does a triple combination of hearts.)
What's that?
(She finishes with an arrow of love.)
(Ji Won's heart dance will be the hit of the year.)
(Ji Won has captured their hearts.)
- She's so cute. - She looks pretty when she does it.
- She's so cute. - That's how it's supposed to be.
- It's pretty when a woman does it. - She's so pretty.
(All hail Ji Won.)
- She's so pretty. - This is it.
That's great.
- Can you do it? - What?
- Of course. - Can you do this?
- Really? - Of course.
Isn't this simple? Shall we try it together?
Cue the music.
First up is Haha.
In 1, 2, 3, 4.
(He puts on a neat heart performance as a dancer.)
- Good job. - Ji Hyo!
- Song Ji Hyo! Song Ji Hyo! - That's good.
(She's cheerful and bubbly.)
(She's pretty.)
Let's go.
(Here comes Seok Jin.)
(He's slower than the music.)
Seok Jin, please dance to the music.
- What are you doing? - What is that?
- What was that? - Go, Gary!
Come on! Show your style.
That's right. Good job.
(He makes a dynamic turn.)
Next is Kwang Soo.
(His movements are stiff.)
(What's that?)
Okay.
- Let's go, Jong Kook. - I don't like doing this.
You still need to do it. Copy Ji Won.
- Kim Jong Kook! Kim Jong Kook! - He's embarrassed.
- Kim Jong Kook! - You're not doing it properly.
- I told you to do it properly. - I don't like doing this.
Let's go Eunseo.
- Jin Goo is last. - Eunseo! Eunseo!
- Eunseo! - Let's go!
Good job!
Jin Goo is next. Jin Goo!
In 1, 2, 3, 4.
(This is a real man's heart dance.)
He's cool.
That was good.
(This is how a man dances.)
You looked like a soldier, Sergeant Major Seo.
Ji Won, show us one more time.
(Let's see how the original looks like.)
She's so pretty.
- She's so lively. - That's pretty.
- Good job! - Gary, you should go.
Show them.
(He's exposed.)
(He resembles a North Korean soldier.)
- Look at him. - Look at his head.
- You shaved your hair well. - Hey.
Did Gary always look like a criminal?
- I shouldn't have shaved my head. - Your clothes match, too.
- He looks like a prisoner. - He does.
He's like "Papillon".
Today, we have Jin Goo, Ji Won...
and Eunseo from Cosmic Girls with us.
Isn't it great to have them on Running Man?
- I look forward to today. - It's spring.
This surely is a spring special.
What shall we do today?
Once I call your name, please step forward.
- Seok Jin, Ji Hyo and Gary. - Okay.
This team is the funny one.
We can't be the funny team without Kwang Soo.
Okay. What? "Loser"?
(What is this Loser's Sticker?)
- What's that? - Is this why we ran in the morning?
- There was something to it. - Was it a win or lose?
(This morning at 10am, Incheon Songdo Hotel)
(Jae Seok arrives on set as usual.)
Oh, dear. Hello, Hwan Jin.
- It's a special episode. - What's with that face?
(He runs away.)
(You must catch the producer and write the answer on his arm.)
(Solve the problem below and write the answer on the producer's arm.)
(The race began immediately.)
(Why are you doing this from the early morning?)
(He caught him.)
(Jae Seok completed the mission.)
(Today's race began like this.)
"Solve the problem..." What is this?
(What exactly was this mission about?)
(Just run.)
Come on!
He's too fast.
(They had to run as soon as they arrived on set.)
(Scurrying)
(Everybody completed the mission within various times.)
(What was Jong Kook's strategy?)
(He took the opposite route.)
What?
(He found a weak spot and went for the producer.)
Ta-da!
(They all succeeded.)
You're too fast.
Was I?
So are we the funny team?
- Are we the funny ones? - We must have lost.
You have received Loser's Stickers.
- Really? - Why?
Watch this clip to gain a better understanding of it.
- There must be something behind it. - Why did we lose?
(This person looks familiar.)
(It's Argus!)
Hey, guys.
- Isn't that Gary? - Isn't he from the drama?
It's Argus!
(What is David McInnics doing here?)
- It's the bad guy! - He's so cool.
- He's handsome. - "It's the bad guy"?
Hey, guys.
Are you surprised to see the Loser's Sticker on your chest?
In six hours, you shall meet me...
and receive a deadly punishment.
- A deadly punishment? - Oh my goodness.
He's scary.
But don't worry.
If you do better than the Red Sun hiding amongst yourselves,
you'll be able to return home safely.
The Red Sun is amongst us?
Is somebody hiding among us?
The mysterious Loser's Sticker on your chest...
means that you were slower than the Red Sun in completing the mission.
During the six hour race, if you lose...
or get a lower record than the Red Sun,
you will receive a Loser's Sticker.
If you want to survive,
find the Red Sun as soon as possible...
and stop his victory.
And of course, if the Red Sun ends up with the lowest record...
he or she will be facing a deadly punishment.
You may be wondering what that punishment is.
So I'm going to do you a favour and give you a little sneak peak.
(The cries are frightening.)
- "My mum just came along..." - This is not for everybody.
(It's not recommended by experienced users.)
- Is this for real? - I can't do this.
(You'll realise why this is the most extreme ride.)
(This will become their reality if they don't defeat the Red Sun.)
- I'm stressed out. - This is so stressful.
Let me help you by telling you what the Red Sun's mission is.
The Red Sun will receive a Loser's Sticker on his chest...
each time he or she doesn't complete the mission in the top three.
Let's hope I don't see you in six hours.
- How cool. - Wow.
- Argus! - So the Red Sun is in the group.
- That's right. - Isn't it you, Jae Seok?
- You're clever and funny. - So he was faster than these three.
Simply put, he or she was faster than these three.
- Really? - So it's not them.
- So we lost to the Red Sun? - Yes.
- Is that right? - So that means it's not them.
So the Red Sun is amongst us.
Today's shoot will go on for a total of six hours.
There's a set time.
That's why we named this race Descent of the Sun.
Is it because we won't be filming after the sun descends?
You tried so hard.
No wonder you dressed me like this.
- No wonder. - I want to take this off.
You have only six hours. Please get ready...
and move to the next location.
- Yes, let's go! - All right!
(Who will be the last one to smile?)
I'm so embarrassed.
- The atmosphere is so nice today. - It is.
- It's so nice. - We're wearing spring colours.
I really hope days like this continue.
(Chuckling)
Stop it.
What did you say?
It's too bad we are only shooting for six hours.
Can't we just do 60 hours instead?
I took a selfie with Ji Won.
(They're Jin Goo and Ji Won's fans.)
- That's not wise. - How annoying.
- Ji Won is really nice. - She is really nice.
- She's innocent. - Jin Goo is very nice, too.
Jin Goo really is.
- Eunseo must be nice, too. - We have to see about that.
- Isn't it your first time on TV? - It is...
my first time being on a show by myself.
- Right. - Tell them it's your first time.
Actually, it's my first time.
- What are you asking her to do? - Are you the CEO?
- Are you the CEO? - No, we belong to the same agency.
So the first game is a couple's game.
- It's a couple's game. - Is it?
We don't have many options.
The competition is fierce.
- Gosh, this is sensational. - Right.
- It is intense indeed. - Gosh.
Before we start the game, we'll have a play-off...
- to decide partners. - Okay.
I found out that everything I like starts with "S".
Samgyetang, samgyeopsal,
ssomaek and Seo Dae Yeong.
(The men must name 5 words with the same letter in 5 seconds.)
Isn't it surprising?
Let's begin now.
- We'll play "Five Words Race." - Okay.
The woman who will go first is...
- Kim Ji Won. - Yes!
(Yes!)
- Great! - Awesome!
(This is the moment we've been dreaming of.)
- Where are you going? - Hello.
- Sit down, please. - Sit down.
Do you all want to be her partner?
- Why did you make her first? - Must we play the final round now?
- This isn't right. - It's nothing but the final round.
As we have you here as a guest,
Please appeal your bombastic charms to us.
Show us your bombastic charms.
- Bombastic - Right.
Come on.
(Please show us your charms.)
- Make some hearts. - In 1, 2, 3, 4!
(Cute)
(She makes them want to copy her.)
(Bang!)
(Lieutenant Yoon sends them her heart.)
- She sent it to me. - No way, it's me!
- It's me! - No, she was looking at me.
Do you have someone that you wish to be partners with?
(Is there anyone here that you want to be partners with?)
Yes, I do.
(She has someone in mind.)
That should be me!
- We'll begin now. - Okay.
You have 5 seconds, and you should name 5 words.
- I think... - Get ready.
there will be a lot of dirty plays this round.
It's good that I didn't sit there.
- I don't think Jae Seok can win. - You can't beat us.
Jae Seok won't be able to move.
(Jae Seok is between two difficult players.)
- I like words that start with "S". - Okay.
(Ji Won chose "S".)
(Jong Kook and Kwang Soo grab Jae Seok.)
Grab him! Don't let him move!
(Sorry. I think we're going to be late.)
- They're done. - They are.
(Haha manages to come in first.)
I'll begin the timer.
- I'll begin. - Okay.
- Apple, I love you... - In 1, 2, 3, 4, 5!
(Did he come to play or confess his love?)
- Get out of my way! - You're out.
- This is just a game. - Oh, gosh.
- My goodness. - I said, "I love you".
- In 1, 2, 3... - Human, love, desert...
- Why does she count so slowly? - four...
- She's counting slowly. - five.
- Sorry. - What is that?
- Accident, president, apple... - In 1, 2, 3, 4, 5.
(Jong Kook says one word...)
(and Ji Won begins to speed up her counting.)
You failed. Jong Kook failed!
Jong Kook!
(Everyone! Ji Won doesn't want Jong Kook to be her partner.)
That's great!
- Jong Kook failed! - Jong Kook!
(It's Seok Jin's turn.)
That was great!
Jong Kook...
- Love, Madam... - In 1, 5.
(That was a time warp.)
- He looks stupid. - Does 5 come right after 1?
- Hey. - What was that?
She said 1 and 5. What is that?
This is impossible.
- Gary... - I didn't ring the bell yet.
- Boatman, love, situation... - In 1, 2, 3, 4, 5!
(It's clear that she doesn't want Gary either.)
- Crawl back. - Go back to the end.
- Go back. - Ji Won!
Ji Won is full of surprises.
Let's give it a shot.
Let's go.
- Salt, syrup... Is it not me? - In 1, 2, 3, 4, 5.
(Is it not me?)
(It's not you.)
- It's not? I thought you wanted me. - It's not you.
It's not me, is it? She didn't even count one for me.
- This is driving me crazy. - She counted so fast.
- Don't flatter yourself. - It was me all along.
- Goodness. - Count really fast, okay?
Gosh.
(Is Jae Seok the one that she wants?)
- I'll go now. - Okay.
I hope she counts really quickly.
- One... - Lo...
(Laughing)
- Why are you not counting? - Count!
- I can't because it's so funny. - What are you talking about?
It's not funny!
- It's not funny at all. - Deer, lion...
- Two... - I love you.
You can't say, "I love you".
(Jae Seok is subdued.)
Keep counting!
(Jae Seok's time is up.)
- Gosh, who is it? - Oh, my.
- It's me! - You want Jae Seok.
- Ji Won, wait for me. - It's Jae Seok.
She wants me!
- Why is it him over me? - It's Jae Seok.
- What's wrong with you? - What are you doing?
- What was that? - It's Jae Seok.
- It's me. - We all gave it a shot.
- I like words that start with "Ch". - "Ch"?
- Congratulate. - What starts with "Ch"?
There is no point going to her.
Wait. What are they doing?
Did you see that?
(Screaming)
(In the jungle, giraffes hunt those separated from their group.)
- You chose "Ch", right? - Yes.
- In 1, 5! - Dentist, okay.
- I'm sorry. - It's...
- It ended so quickly. - I'm sorry.
This is a good exercise.
(Jong Kook bravely gives it another shot.)
Look at Ji Won.
It's clear that she doesn't want you. She's not even looking at you.
- No. - Ji Won isn't looking at you.
- In 1, 5! - Congrat...
(Is that a newly coined word?)
- Pikachu! - Good.
- He said, "Pikachu". - Gosh.
- You're pretty obsessive. - This is nonsense!
He's pathetic.
- You're an obsessive guy. - She...
didn't even count from one when it was my turn.
Jong Kook is obsessive.
- We all failed. - Spit,
- You're right. - dance, gun.
- I'll start. - Okay.
You can only say words with one syllable.
(He's determined.)
One...
(Kwang Soo hits Ji Won's neck.)
(Kwang Soo tried to stop the timer.)
Hey! What are you doing?
- Gosh! - Dentist, seven...
Hey, why did you hit her?
- Why? - What are you doing?
Are you okay?
How could you hit Ji Won's neck?
- Hey! Ji Won... - Gosh.
- Are you okay? - You're not sane, are you?
- My goodness. - You can't do that to her.
How could you hit her?
- I am sorry. Are you okay? - Gosh.
She kept counting even though I hit her neck.
- My goodness. - Are you okay? I'm sorry.
- It's okay. This is so funny. - Are you okay?
She's crying.
- Are you okay, Ji Won? - She is startled.
Ji Won, I am sorry.
- Kwang Soo. - You made her cry.
- That was really mean. - Kwang Soo!
(Who made Ji Won cry?)
Ji Won.
Are you out of your mind?
We finally got her to come on our show. How could you do that to her?
I never thought he'd hit me.
I think she wants Jae Seok.
Okay. Dental floss,
- She already made up her mind. - toothpaste,
- toothbrush and... - He is so arrogant. It's annoying.
- You're so annoying. - Why?
- What do you mean? - Four.
Periodontitis...
and gingivitis.
(Great!)
My goodness.
(Jae Seok and Ji Won are the first couple.)
I like Ji Hyo. You look pretty today.
- Let's start! - Ji Hyo is so pretty!
- All right. - Ji Hyo has very bright skin.
There aren't many female members left.
You all know Ji Hyo well, right?
- She is very precise. - Right.
- Okay. - Good.
I like someone whose name starts with "J".
(Did you say name? Not word?)
(Was it a mistake? Or did she really mean it?)
(My name also starts with "J".)
I like someone whose name starts with "J".
Did you say "J"?
Ji Hyo...
(Smiling)
(A man starts moving immediately towards her.)
Jin Goo is the only one who's going.
(Although everyone was ready to start,)
(they gave up immediately after Jin Goo began to move.)
Jin Goo is the only one who's moving.
(They lost their will to fight.)
(Here comes Prince Charming.)
Jin Goo, Ji Hyo, Jee Seok Jin,
- One. - Earth and truth.
Correct!
I knew she'd do that.
Thank you.
(Jin Goo and Ji Hyo are the second couple.)
- This is ridiculous. - Now...
- Eunseo! - It's Eunseo!
- It's Eunseo's turn. - Eunseo!
I am Eunseo.
- I'll be right there, Eunseo. - Eunseo...
Please, Eunseo. Eunseo!
- I like words that start with "O". - Okay.
- It's "O"! - Hold on.
Gosh, look at him!
(Haha tries to be fast.)
What is that? Wait.
(See you later.)
It's "O".
(Haha doesn't give up.)
(I'll escort you to the side.)
I'm waiting for "O".
Let me think.
Let me go. It's me. You want me to come, right?
- Eunseo, it's me, right? - I'm looking at only one person.
Dad, mum, aunt, uncle and Lee Kwang Soo.
- In 1, 2, 5. - Dad, mum, aunt, uncle...
- and Cosmic Girls. I'm done. - In 1, 2, 5.
She said 1, 2 and 5.
Did you say 1, 2, 5? How dare you!
- Haha, you're pitiful. - Accept your defeat.
- Get up. - Dad, mum, Lee Kwang Soo...
Dad, mum, aunt, uncle and Lee Kwang Soo.
There's no point in practising. Just do it.
- Five. - Dad, aunt...
(A quick goodbye)
She skipped to five.
- Go to the end of the line. - Don't you know how to count?
Don't you know how to count to five?
I can do it.
I think Kwang Soo will succeed this time.
- Dad, brother, mother, milk... - One.
- and Cosmic Girls. - Two.
(He succeeds.)
(They're disappointed.)
Well done.
(Kwang Soo and Eunseo are the third couple.)
- There are only guys left. - I thought it would be Kwang Soo.
(There are 2 male couples and 3 co-ed couples.)
- What is this? - There's something there.
- What is this? - I see trays.
It looks blocked.
- Trays? - What are they for?
It seems like "Tray Noraebang".
(There are cushions and trays.)
What are we doing here?
(The first game is "Tray Quiz.")
- Do we just stand here? - It must be like "Tray Noraebang".
(It's their first chance to figure out who the Red Sun is.)
(The Red Sun must be revealed in order to avoid penalty.)
- Two hours have passed already. - There are 2, 4 and 5.
- The time flies. - I agree.
I guess women will sit over there.
- Of course they will. - Right?
- So only men will be penalised. - We'll get hit.
- It makes sense. - Of course.
The game is "Tray Quiz."
Female members will sit in the front and answer quizzes.
Male members will sit under the tray...
and will be hit if the answer is wrong.
- I see. - That's why there are trays.
If the female member thinks that she knows the answer,
she must sound the proper buzzer to have a chance to answer.
For the first quiz,
the women must sing and dance...
- to answer the quiz. - Nice. Eunseo has an advantage.
- We're at an advantage! - Really?
Are they going out front to dance?
The first question is...
about a romance movie...
- called "Music and Lyrics." - I know this movie.
In the movie, Hugh Grant says to Drew Barrymore that...
"You're the best something in my life"...
when he makes his confession.
What is the word that replaces...
- "something"? - I don't know.
- Do you have any idea, Ji Won? - The best something...
- I have no idea. - Hold on.
- What was the quote? - It was "You are the best..."
- That's how I normally speak. - Okay.
Shall I begin?
From the top to the bottom
You can't sing your own song.
You are so lovely
- Accepted. - That shouldn't be accepted.
"You're the best..."
"hit song in my life."
- He dressed like a woman. - I'm sure he's wrong.
- It's definitely not. - Oh, really?
(Haha gets hit.)
- I'm not getting hit by the tray. - "You're the best..."
"You're the best copyrighted star in my life."
- How about "the source of income?" - Worth 15 dollars?
It's 15 dollars?
Try "lyricist".
"You're the best..."
Go, Ji Won!
I'm afraid that it's too old.
Nobody nobody but you
Is she singing "Nobody"?
- Nobody nobody but you - It's so old.
Isn't the song too old, Ji Won?
The song is not accepted.
I don't like anyone else
(How about this?)
She's doing great.
(She's cute.)
- Nobody, nobody - She dances better than I thought.
- Nobody, nobody - Accepted.
"You're the best lyricist."
Is it not correct?
- I'm sorry, Jae Seok. - That's okay.
Please look at me
What is he doing?
- Please look at me - That's scary.
- I have already - That's not acceptable.
- Why not? - Why?
- Why'd you hit me? - It's my turn.
(Here comes Ji Hyo's long time favourite "Hot Issue".)
- Are you singing that song again? - Hot issue
Accepted.
"You're the best melody in my life."
Is it wrong?
- The word "melody" makes sense. - Are you all right, Jin Goo?
(He's still smiling.)
- I'll give you a hint. - Okay.
The answer is really similar to Jong Kook's answer.
- What was his answer? - What did he say?
- What was it? - What was your answer, Jong Kook?
What did you say?
Wait. Jong Kook looks like a thug.
He was sitting like this and staring at me. That was scary.
Jong Kook, why did you do that?
(Jong Sook is a beautiful thug.)
- What did Jong Kook say? - Why did you do that?
(It's Jong Kook's time to dance.)
"You're the best..."
"hit in my life."
(The best hit)
(It's correct.)
- It hurts so much. - Oh my goodness.
I knew that was coming.
- What? - It's time to change the buzzer.
The women...
must act cute.
- Yes. - She is good at that.
She is an expert.
- She's really good at it. - I'm not good at this.
- Don't worry, Eunseo. You're good. - Ji Won, it's your specialty.
- That one's for you. - Don't worry, Ji Won.
- You're made for this. - This is hard.
- Is it my specialty? - It is.
- Really? I didn't know. - It's not fair.
Ji Won seems like she's still acting...
for the drama, "Descendants of the Sun".
She speaks like a soldier does.
That's how she normally speaks.
- How should I do it? - What should I do?
Ji Won, it's your specialty.
It will be a "Nonsense Quiz" this time.
- Yes. - Great.
- I'm not good at this. - You can do it.
- Nice. - I'm good at this.
- What's another way to say, - Say?
- "Gary went to a hot spring?" - This is so easy.
This is really easy. Just go out.
- In other words? - I've seen this before.
- Jin Goo will get hit a lot. - I had a horrible dream.
(Ji Hyo tries to act cute.)
- Isn't that too old? - What is she doing?
- Can I kick her instead? - Hold on.
- "Gary went to..." - Do something else.
- Can I kick her? - Don't do it.
You know, I really love you
(Ji Hyo is learning some new techniques.)
- I really like you - Eunseo!
- How much? This much - She's lovely.
I really like you this much
(I really like you.)
(They're amazed.)
- That was so charming. - Now she needs to answer.
- What's the answer? - She's just lovely.
Gary went to a brook.
What did you just say?
A brook.
- A brook? - Go, Ji Won.
Gary went to a brook.
Gary went to a hot spring.
I had a horrible dream.
- You're my nightmare! - Come on!
I think I will, too.
- All right. - Stop it!
(She acts cute.)
Accepted.
Gary is so hot.
(Gary is very hot.)
(Oh, my.)
- What did she say? - She said that Gary is so hot.
"Gary is so hot."
That was funny, Ji Hyo.
- Ji Hyo. - That was a good one.
(Ji Hyo abides by the broadcasting rules and regulations.)
- That's so funny. - That was great.
- How about "Gary's so scary?" - That was a good one.
That was clever.
- It makes sense. - Gary is...
"Gary is so hot" sounds nice.
I don't think so.
Where should I look?
Go, Ji Won.
One plus one is lovely
(She's so lovely.)
- Two plus two is also lovely - She's really good.
- Three plus three is also lovely - Ji Won's really good at this.
(I can't believe this.)
- You should stop at five. - Five plus five is also lovely
That's great.
Look at all the staff members. Look at their eyes.
- What's wrong with you guys? - Come to your senses.
"Gary became a new man."
- "Gary became a new man." - Gary's new now.
- It's not the answer. - Isn't it?
It's really difficult.
- I'm so sorry. - It's difficult.
- Do you need a hint? - Yes.
Think of a synonym for "hot spring".
- What is this? - Hurry up!
- I know the answer! - Hurry!
One plus one is lovely
- Two plus to is also lovely - It's not acceptable.
Three plus three is also lovely
(We want to erase this from our memory.)
No way.
That's the answer. Come on.
- I think so, too. - It's right.
- I know the answer. - A synonym for "hot spring".
- What is it? - What's the synonym?
Please give it to me
(Please give me.)
(I will give you some punches.)
You need to be hit.
- I know the answer! - What can be the answer?
- Hey. - Wasn't I cute?
- Wasn't I? - Please give us more hints.
- Just tell us the first letter. - The first letter.
- Only the first letter. - Give it to us.
One plus one is lovely
- Just the first letter, please? - No way, Seok Jin.
- He's so cute! - Not at all.
- He really is! - He's not cute.
- He's dancing like a zombie. - Oh, my.
Do you think he's cute? Do you really think so?
I can believe him.
That's not cute at all.
- My goodness. - Just tell us the first letter.
- All right. I will. - Oh, no.
- Get ready, Eunseo. - The first letter...
- It's "S"! - starts with "S".
I know the answer.
I got it!
It's your turn to act cute.
(Is he really trying to be cute?)
- Give it a try. - Smile.
What's the answer?
- Act cute. - Please give me!
- What's the synonym? - You know I
You know, I love you
- Ji Hyo is accepted. - Why is she accepted?
- I get it. - Another word for hot spring?
(What's another way to say, "Gary went to a hot spring?")
Spaghetti.
(Spaghetti)
(It's correct.)
(They dodged the tray!)
Oh, my head!
(They dodge and pretend to be hurt.)
Oh, my.
(It hits him again.)
- What are you doing? - It was spaghetti.
I wanted to say "spaghetti" as well.
- That was close. - "Spa" was the word. I see.
- Spaghetti was the answer. - Spaghetti.
Female and male members will change positions.
- Great. - Okay.
- Okay, Ji Won. - All right.
- Don't worry. - I'll count on you.
- You mustn't fail. - Get ready.
- Good luck. - Okay.
I guess Jong Kook is the Red Sun.
That makes sense.
- He was trying so hard. - Our partners can be the Red Sun.
We have to be cautious.
If the Red Sun is continuing to score points...
Wouldn't the team with the best score have the Red Sun?
Then the game's over already.
But trying hard doesn't guarantee a good score.
(The Red Sun must be in the top three.)
Among the animals that appear in the song "Tiger's Birthday",
which animal made its visit to celebrate the tiger's birthday...
and played the violin?
- I know the answer. - I have no idea.
(He tries to act cute.)
Come on!
- Ouch! - Why not?
- Why isn't this cute? - Are you all right?
- The sound was very loud. - Violin.
- I'm farting! - No way, Haha.
Wasn't it cute?
Go ahead.
(He acts cute.)
(Step back, Gary.)
Why are you stopping me?
I know the answer!
(Everyone is trying to be cute.)
Look at me!
- I'm being cute! - Look at me.
(It's manly cuteness.)
- Look at my dimples. - Don't you look in the mirror?
(It can't be any worse than this.)
If you don't, then show me your face every morning instead.
Show me your handsome face.
(Where am I? What am I doing?)
Have you ever thought of other careers outside the military?
- I can do this! - Lovey-dovey.
(He strives to be the cutest man in the world.)
- Look at my lovely dimples! - One more time.
This is crazy.
Lovey-dovey!
- What's that? - Why did you say that?
- You pass! - Come on.
No way!
- How is that cute? - I even showed my dimples.
- Say it loudly. - Fox?
I think it's the answer.
(Correct)
That wasn't cute at all.
(He is content.)
What is the pure Korean word...
for "love"?
I will give you a hint. It's a name of a girl group member.
I know this.
- It's a pure Korean word? - A word for "love"?
- Music, please. - Give him music.
- Give him music. - Come on.
(This time, they need to dance.)
(Wriggling)
(What kind of dance is that?)
- What's that? - That's strange.
(He dances slightly.)
(And at the right moment,)
(he dances more slightly.)
- What kind of dance is that? - That's a military dance!
- Don't do that. - What is that?
- My dimples! - What's wrong?
(This time, it's Gary, the hip hop warrior.)
(He becomes Mr Ugly once again.)
It's nothing.
(He does the mollusc dance.)
You have to pass me.
- Pass me! - That's great, Gary!
Pass.
It's two syllables, right? "Ari".
- Yes. - "Ari".
- It's not that one? - "Ari" from "Arisoo".
It's the Korean word for love?
(Or is it that?)
(The dance machine begins to dance.)
Come on!
(Here he goes.)
(She's excited.)
That's it!
(Let's go!)
That's so old!
(He's full of vitality.)
- That's really strange. - Oh, dear.
- Okay. - You pass.
I would be really annoyed if he's my boyfriend.
I'll be embarrassed to be seen with him.
That's why he dated tall and ugly girls in high school.
That's true.
Why are you talking about things from last week?
- Why did you bring it up? - I just thought of it.
(What's the pure Korean word for love?)
"Ara".
Did he just say "Ara"?
(Incorrect)
- I will give you a hint. - The sound...
It's a four-member girl group.
- What? - It's a four-member girl group.
Are they active these days?
Haha got it.
(Haha starts dancing.)
It should mean "love".
- "Love"? - That's it!
Go, Haha!
- Pass. - I know what it is.
- It's a four-member group. - I got it.
He got it.
Think carefully and tell us.
- What's the word for "love"? - "Dasom".
(Dasom?)
(Correct)
I am sorry.
- We are in the same agency. - I just guessed.
- It was "Dasom". - "Dasom" means love.
Gosh...
This time, you have to throw your shoe.
- Shoe? Okay. - Yes.
Here we go.
This is one of Shakespeare's famous quotes.
"An actor is this era's something."
- Which word replaces "something"? - "Something"?
- You know it. - An actor is...
- this era's... - This era's...
(Dropping)
- You're out. - You're out.
What's the problem?
(She gets hit.)
- This is no joke. It's okay. - I'm sorry.
- It's about an era. - Try it.
- You pass. - I got it.
Mirror.
- Gosh... - That's it.
Gosh, I knew it!
No way.
It hurts!
(Things are working out well for me today.)
(Jong Kook is unusually lucky. Is he the Red Sun?)
(Is it Ji Won, who is always passionate?)
(Or is it Jin Goo, who has a suspicious look in his eyes?)
The person I am calling should come forward...
- and get... - Many people must've failed.
- a Loser's Sticker. - This is...
- Lee Kwang Soo. - He has to get it.
He always fails for no reason.
Why would you say that?
- He always fails. - Gary.
- Gary failed. - This is bad.
- Kim Ji Won. - It's not me?
- Why did she fail? - Why her?
You will find out soon.
- There must be a different rule. - The rule is different.
- It must be an individual play. - Jee Seok Jin.
I failed again.
They are determined.
- It's Seok Jin's day. - Next is Ji Hyo.
- I failed. - What's the basis?
I'll tell you the basis for the selection.
- I didn't fail? - I didn't fail either.
Those who got hit more than the Red Sun failed.
(Those who got hit more failed.)
- I got hit more than... - You didn't get hit, did you?
- No. - Did I get hit a lot?
Did I get hit a lot?
So we got hit more than the Red Sun?
So getting more answers was not important.
- Did you get it? - No.
I got goosebumps. Can I get goosebumps?
(There are two possible reasons for getting the sticker.)
(Seok Jin, Ji Hyo and Gary failed twice.)
(Descent of the Sun)
- Let's go. - Okay.
- I failed twice. - I failed once.
- It starts now. - You have to get three objects...
and go to the designated area.
Is the camera rolling all the time?
Yes. It's rolling all the time.
It's so fascinating.
Here we go!
Let's go!
- It's difficult. - It is difficult.
(Ji Won is in a happy mood.)
I will search which objects include the word "won".
(They look for objects that has the words "won" and "goo".)
There are things.
(She's fascinated again.)
(She's easily fascinated by many things.)
- I found it. - Did you find it?
Brewed coffee.
(Bingo!)
That's a good one.
First-aid kit, grilled eggs...
and grilled ice cream. There are many.
- Gosh... - There are so many.
Grilled eggs.
(The couples need to hold hands.)
- Did you get the car key? - Yes.
Good. They often steal other teams' car keys.
I am a fan of Running Man, so I know.
(Jin Goo is well-prepared for Running Man.)
Gosh, it's a perfect day to sit down and...
- have a cup of coffee. - I know.
- "Sungrasses"? - "Sungrasses"!
Will "sungrasses" do?
- No. - Does that not work?
(But Ji Won wants it.)
You can get a sweet potato latte. One sweet potato latte, please.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
This is a one-piece dress, right?
- This will do. - I will take this.
Monkey mug.
- Monkey mug. - Let's get this.
- This is cute. - We will take this. It's 1 plus 1.
This is a one-piece dress.
(The couples are busy getting their shopping done.)
- That's good. - That's good.
(They take pictures of expensive items.)
All right.
(They are only given 100 dollars for the mission.)
Heels.
Ji Won, you are good.
- You're smart. - I'm good, aren't I?
- Heels will do. - Heels.
- What else? - Oh, gosh.
There we go.
Insert it and take a picture.
- Okay. - Here we go.
(He takes a picture of it.)
- There we go. - There we go.
- We got it. - We got it.
(Time is up.)
- They are here. - People are here.
Jin Goo, are you good at lying?
- I'm bad at lying. - Today...
(Kwang Soo bursts into laughter.)
Are you the Red Sun?
I don't even know how you become the Red Sun.
I don't understand the rules.
If he turns out to be the Red Sun...
- That will give us the chills. - That was a good explanation.
- I think it's Ji Won. - It's...
- What's going on? - Why did you take so long?
You found that. We couldn't find it.
- We made a conclusion. - We know who the Red Sun is.
- We're sure. - Us?
It's Kim Ji Won.
- It's not Ji Won. - I have the sticker.
Even if you have the sticker, you can be the Red Sun.
The second mission is over.
I will announce the ones who did worse than the Red Sun did.
- Oh, dear. - They will receive stickers.
- First is Jee Seok Jin. - Okay!
Seok Jin always gets picked. Do you just hate him?
- Accept him now. - I won though.
- The next one who failed is... - Maybe it's Gary?
(Who's the other one?)
It's Haha.
(Haha also got a Loser's Sticker.)
Why did we lose?
- I have no idea. - I have absolutely no idea.
The last one who failed is Lee Kwang Soo.
- He's a betrayer. - Who failed?
But he finished second.
I know.
- I can't guess it. - What's the basis?
You failed because...
Maybe we got the same items?
You paid more than the Red Sun did for the items you bought.
(They are the ones who paid more!)
It's the price. You paid more than the Red Sun did.
- But they are... - Isn't it strange that...
- Jae Seok didn't get any stickers? - They bought only cheap ones.
(They only have one hour left.)
- It's time for the final mission. - Is it?
The final mission is "Master of Cheesy Acting".
(This is their last chance to find the Red Sun.)
The couple should choose a famous quote from the drama.
You will also choose one famous scene.
You will start with the famous quote...
and end with the famous scene.
The couple who acts the best will get extended time...
for the ending mission at our discretion.
You're given 40 seconds.
For the ending mission, you'll put on gloves and open the box.
The female has to wear the wing inside and say, "I am an angel."
If you exceed the time, cold water will fall on you.
So you must open the box as quickly as possible.
- It's behind you. - "I am an angel."
That's Ji Won's line.
It is Ji Won's line.
- "I am an angel." - "I am an angel."
Before we start the actual mission,
we will first watch Ji Won and Jin Goo...
- acting a scene. - They're the originals.
(Jin Goo and Ji Won will show an example.)
- Will they do it? - Be quiet, everybody.
- Come to the centre. - Please come forward.
This is the scene.
(What scene will they enact for us?)
Standby and cue!
(As soon as they're cued,)
(they're immersed in the scene.)
Where are you going?
Are you running away again?
I asked if you were running away again.
(This famous quote stole the hearts of many viewers.)
Sergeant Major Seo Dae Yeong. I have been ordered to return...
(She slaps him mid-air.)
(They act in perfect synchrony to the original scene.)
To Korea.
Tell me to wait.
Tell me you're taking a step back as a strategy.
Tell me you'll come back at all costs!
(He grabs her.)
(He hugs her.)
(I would have regretted every moment I was away from you.)
(They can't believe what they're witnessing.)
- Say it! - Tell her!
- Say something! - Do it!
- Say it! - Don't make us wait!
- Say it! - Come on!
- Hurry! - I'll go back in a heartbeat.
- Say something. - Say it.
Isn't this too cruel?
- Let's do the exact same thing. - Okay.
- I remember this scene. - Me, too.
- "Where are you going?" - "Where are you going?"
We're going to do this.
- We will. - It's ours!
- It's ours. - I want to say that line.
- Where are you going? - There's a lady here.
Are you running away after stealing my heart?
(You stole my heart.)
(Where are you running off to?)
I'm going to the internet cafe.
(Do you play StarCraft?)
Why is it any of your business?
They knew we were watching them and still acted in front of us.
They were immediately absorbed in the scene.
That's incredible.
Ji Won is so good. So is Jin Goo.
Let's try it ourselves.
We have to be enthusiastic if we want to earn extra time.
That's right.
(She smiles like a little girl.)
- Let's go. - Let's go!
(At the sound of the cue, her facial expression changes.)
Standby.
Cue!
(This is the scene they'll act out.)
Are you...
(This line stole every woman's heart.)
still sexy...
in the operation room?
Are you...
still sexy in the operation room?
(Jae Seok is too focused.)
I became sexier in the time we didn't see each other.
Roger.
Right now, I...
(He's very involved.)
- Come on, Jae Seok. - "Right now, I..."
- Why are you doing that? - Can I...
go there?
I'll be waiting.
- He looks silly. - Look at his face.
- What's with that face? - He must be a fool.
(The sun shines brighter than usual.)
Knock, knock.
(Are you here?)
(Are you the sweet voice behind the radio transmission?)
What do you think?
Am I even sexier in real life?
(Am I sexier in person?)
(Slapping)
(She received the message,)
(but his face doesn't cut it.)
I shouldn't have seen your face.
(Hitting)
(She strikes him with the radio transmission.)
(She rejects him.)
Did you just hit me with the radio transmission?
Are you allowed to do that? Are you?
I'm sorry.
- You have 60 seconds! - 60 seconds!
- No way. - That doesn't deserve 60 seconds.
(They received the longest time thanks to Ji Won.)
- That's unfair. - Isn't this biased towards Ji Won?
(The producer is the judge.)
(The gloves are too circular to provide any grip.)
His lips protrude so it's easy for him.
- He has the upper hand. - It's easy for him.
They almost got it.
(Underneath the wrapper...)
(lies another wrapper.)
The next one. Next one.
He's ripping it.
- He did it. - I think they'll make it.
They're pretty close.
No, they won't make it.
All right!
(They finally open the box.)
- Here! - They got it.
Watch the time!
We don't have much time.
You have 10 seconds left. In 9, 8,
- and 7... - I'm an angel!
Success!
(They succeed.)
We didn't get wet!
(She does a victory ceremony.)
I'm annoyed.
- Good job. - Thank you.
(Jae Seok does his ceremony.)
- That was good. - Good job.
- Thank you. - So...
She's an angel.
- It doesn't look easy. - My goodness.
Next up...
(Next up is Jin Goo and Ji Hyo.)
They have an advantage, too. They're both actors.
This will be something to watch.
Look at Jin Goo's face. He's already into it.
Standby.
(What scene will they act out?)
By the way,
you look similar to being pretty.
Cut it out.
(This line turned every woman into a princess in a fairy tale.)
(He thought it was corny back then.)
(But now, he has to do the same.)
(He stops her first.)
(He has to say those sweet words now.)
You look similar to being...
(Slapping)
(She slaps him out of nowhere.)
She's so good at slapping people.
(This is the difference between a drama and a TV show.)
- What? What? - Hey...
- What? What do you want? - Hold on for a second.
Don't tell me he's going to tie her shoelaces next.
Please don't hit me...
I'm sorry. Please don't hit me...
All of a sudden? Is he tying her shoelaces?
All of a sudden?
(This scene...)
(was one of the most memorable scenes from the drama.)
(He unties her shoelaces...)
All of a sudden?
(And runs away)
(He was just faking it.)
- He's running away. - Hey, stop it!
(Jin Goo's quick wit stood out.)
- You have 50 seconds! - 50 seconds!
(They earned an 10 extra seconds as a bonus.)
- You're at 49 seconds. - They're taking their time.
I guess you want the penalty.
They're going to get the penalty.
(Jin Goo shows his manly side.)
What is this?
(This is the same urgency he showed in the earthquake zone.)
Hurry, hurry!
He opened the box.
- It's open! - They're close!
Watch the time.
I'm an angel!
Success.
- That's amazing. - He's very manly.
This is fun.
Let's watch this team.
My strategy was always to run away.
(Slapping)
- Did you just hit me? - I did.
(Love fights are scary these days.)
You have 50 seconds!
This isn't working!
Do this first.
- Time's over. - There's more inside!
(Splashing)
(The waterfall fell on their heads.)
Cue!
You should take care of me if you touched me.
(Splashing)
(Wait...)
(She punches and slaps him.)
(A romance turns into action.)
That came out of nowhere.
I thought we had a different plan.
You have 40 seconds!
It's not just one. There are about three more inside.
Time's over.
(They barely unwrapped the box.)
(Splashing)
(This is too early in the season for a water park.)
- She's a ghost. - Eunseo!
Yes! I'm okay!
- I'm sorry, Eunseo! - I'm okay!
- Eunseo! - Yes!
(He's not very reliable.)
Standby. Cue!
(He's acting coy.)
Should I apologise or make a confession?
(An apology or a confession?)
Get down.
(I need to teach you a lesson.)
(He's worried Haha will become a troublemaker.)
I said, get down.
(This is a different kind of a date.)
- What's that? - Isn't he crazy?
(Shaking)
- He's going to use a toy hammer. - That's scary.
I think it's going to hurt.
(Striking)
(The hit makes him shudder.)
This looks more like a scene from "The Chaser".
Should I apologise or make a confession?
(He flashes a heart.)
Apologise.
(Sullen)
I am sorry.
I love you.
- You won't do that again, right? - Of course not.
I am sorry.
(I forgive you.)
Did you smoke?
I said, did you smoke?
Get down.
(I'll help you become healthier, Sweetheart.)
He's a smoker.
He smoked.
- I told you to quit. - I'm sorry.
He hates smokers.
He does.
I smoked with him.
Get down.
Me?
- Did you two smoke together? - What?
Did you guys smoke together?
Yes.
Ouch!
Seok Jin smoked with us, too.
- You know I'm 50 years old. - Just get down.
You are a woman.
Are you going to quit smoking or not?
- She is a woman like you. - Get down.
Look at him.
That's funny.
(Jong Kook hits Jae Seok as a warning not to start smoking.)
It hurts so bad.
Gosh.
- This was the most painful one. - Gosh.
- I love you. - I love you.
(- Please quit smoking. - I'll try.)
You have 60 seconds.
(As they earned extra 20 seconds, they have 60 seconds.)
(They earned that much time with their great anti-smoking campaign.)
I can't put the gloves on.
(Jae Seok runs away with the box.)
(Catch me if you can.)
Where are you going? Stop there.
They're going to catch him.
(Give it back to me!)
How many seconds do they have?
I am sure they can't make it. It's over.
It's over.
You failed.
They unwrapped just one.
Come here and receive the penalty.
- Four seconds left. - They're hitting the box.
(He hits through the box!)
(Astounded)
(The box is torn.)
What is that?
You failed!
- Oh, my. - You failed.
You failed.
- Come here. - Come over here.
This is not how we play this game.
(Stop there, Jae Seok.)
(Laughing)
We could've made it if we had three more seconds.
(All they needed were 3 seconds.)
Jong Kook, I think Jae Seok ruined everything.
- Take him there and hit him. - Go in.
- I didn't... - Come with me.
- It's not... - Come here.
(Come enjoy the waterfall with us.)
- Jong Kook, Jong Kook. - Stay still.
- Wait. You can't do this to me. - Yes, we can.
You can't do this. What are you doing?
(Jong Kook ties Jae Seok up with his t-shirt.)
You can't do this to me!
What are you doing?
My goodness.
Hey!
(Waterfall)
(He's soaked.)
(Jae Seok got doused with water after trying to interfere.)
My goodness!
(The final mission is complete.)
All right. You've finished all of the missions.
If I call your name,
come and get your Loser's Stickers.
What would be the criteria this time?
- It's the final round. - Who'll get the stickers?
- Kim Jong Kook. - Me?
- Haha. - What?
(Haha gets a Loser's Sticker.)
- Jee Seok Jin. - Again?
- Gary. - Me, too?
What did they do wrong?
- Why me? - What is the criteria?
When you were acting,
we monitored your heart rates.
And the losers had the lowest heart rates while acting.
- The Red Sun must be a woman. - Right.
Ji Won was really good.
Then did the Red Sun not rank in the top three?
You got the stickers because the Red Sun didn't place in the top three.
(They received Loser's Stickers as the Red Sun didn't place in third.)
(Descent of the Sun)
Who do you think is...
the evil Red Sun?
You had a long day.
It's been six hours.
- Wow. - There's nothing.
- It was fun. - We all did our best.
So who is the Red Sun?
I'll announce who the Red Sun is along with your rankings.
Who is it?
Look at the screen behind you.
- Who is it? - Here.
- I can't wait. - The Red Sun will get the gift.
- Who would it be? - I think it's Jong Kook.
If you rank lower than the Red Sun, you get penalised.
But if you rank the same or higher, you're exempted.
I hope it's Gary.
The person who ranked fifth is...
I think the last round was not...
- It's Seok Jin. - Seok Jin lost four times.
It's only me.
If you're the Red Sun, you'll receive the penalty alone.
(Is Seok Jin the Red Sun?)
- He's not the Red Sun. - He is not.
I passed.
- This is fun. - Let's see who lost three times.
(Is Gary the Red Sun?)
That's right.
So it's not Gary either.
- They weren't the Red Sun. - It's not the three of us.
It's Ji Hyo or Jin Goo.
(Is Jin Goo the Red Sun?)
- You were so nice. - Is it you?
- Right. - We'll see.
He said, "We'll see."
Lee Kwang Soo, Ji Hyo and Haha.
If one of us isn't the Red Sun, we'll receive the penalty.
They are not the Red Sun.
(Kwang Soo, Ji Hyo and Haha all passed.)
- They passed. - Then it's him.
This is driving me crazy. Gosh.
I feel much better to have you as my penalty partners.
- Join us. - We should be together.
- Come with us. - If it's Jin Goo...
Will you show us the rest at the same time?
(Who got 1 sticker?)
- It's Jong Kook and Ji Won. - I look great in that photo.
- Is it Ji Won? - Is it Ji Won? No way.
(Is Ji Won the Red Sun?)
(She showed her breath-taking cuteness...)
(and a perfect acting performance.)
(Did she try her best...)
(because she is the Red Sun?)
- Is it Ji Won? - Is it? No way.
(It's between Ji Won and Jong Kook.)
It can be Jong Kook.
(Is the Red Sun either Ji Won or Jong Kook?)
(Are one of them the Red Sun?)
(Jong Kook and Ji Won pass.)
- Really? - We all will get the penalty.
(Wailing)
Let's all receive the penalty.
(Everyone except first place will be penalised.)
- Is it Jin Goo? - So we have Jin Goo,
- Jae Seok... - I'm sure it is Jin Goo.
- Is it you, Eunseo? - It's Jin Goo.
We can't go home tonight.
- Who will be the Red Sun? - It's Jin Goo.
(Who is the Red Sun that completely deceived the others?)
- Who is it? - It's Jin Goo.
- Is it Eunseo? - Is it Jae Seok?
(Who is the Red Sun?)
Who is it?
(Shocking)
(Jin Goo is the Red Sun.)
(Jin Goo, a big fan of Running Man, fooled everyone.)
It's Jin Goo!
This is unbelievable. He deceived us all.
- Right. - He said he didn't know anything.
It was really fun.
This is unbelievable.
- I can't believe this. - He said he didn't lie.
(How did Jin Goo become the Red Sun?)
The Red Sun is clever, mysterious and...
(The Red Sun is clever and mysterious.)
uncanny.
(This morning, 30 minutes before the shoot)
(The first person to arrive on set was Jin Goo.)
Hello.
Jin Goo, your code name is...
"Red Sun".
"Red Sun"?
(Jin Goo's code name was Red Sun.)
You need to hide your identity.
What you do will become the standard for ranking.
(He had to hide his identity.)
(The operation began as soon as they began filming.)
You should kick your shoe as far as you can.
Okay.
(The sneakers Jin Goo was wearing were the Red Sun's shoes.)
These are the Red Sun's shoes.
(Although they look like ordinary shoes...)
I'll take these off...
and put this inside.
(They had Red Sun marks inside them.)
(Although he wanted to try, he couldn't because of his sneakers.)
Red Sun,
you must rank at least third in every mission.
If you fail to do so, you'll also receive a Loser's sticker.
(He did everything he could to rank third or above.)
Women?
Correct.
You got it.
(His strong power came from his desire to clear his missions.)
I am an angel.
Correct.
(Am I doing okay?)
Can you do it?
We'll see. But I'm pretty confident.
Are you the Red Sun?
I don't even know how you become the Red Sun.
He sounds like he's telling the truth.
It's not easy to understand.
(He skillfully acted and fooled those who suspected him.)
I am the Red Sun.
Are you surprised?
(He was the Red Sun.)
Running Man is one of my favourite programmes.
And they gave me a big mission from the start.
Yes.
I was the Red Sun.
Red Sun.
What is that? Is that a sign or something?
- You had that in your shoes? - Yes.
You can have it.
We should do body searches before we start from now on.
It was so much fun.
- Gosh, it makes me angry! - Why?
(After sunset,)
(it's time for the penalty.)
(It's a type of fear that they've never experienced before.)
("You won't be in your right mind.")
("All you will want to do is escape.")
(This pirate ship is famous in Incheon.)
(It brings you hardcore fear with its speed, angle and height.)
(This frightening pirate ship waits for the Running Man members.)
(Wolmido Island, Incheon)
There's a pirate ship.
I think this is too harsh.
It's too harsh for us.
I can ride anything except that.
Do you think we'll ride the pirate ship?
(Sorry, but you must ride the pirate ship.)
(This pirate ship in Wolmido Island is scarier than real pirates.)
(And...)
(a man waits for them.)
(Who is he, sitting in front of a pirate ship?)
(David McInnis)
Okay, that's enough. Yes or no?
(A single answer will determine it all.)
Are you ready to face your punishment?
(Yes or No. Your answer will determine it all.)
It's a yes or no question.
(Yes or No. What is your choice?)
Did you find the No Man of this year?
I think the No Man is here.
(The competitive Kim Sung Kyun)
(The fiery-tempered Go Ara)
(The best detective of 2016, Lee Je Hoon.)
(Next Week's Special is Race to Say No.)