(Unlucky person)
(An unlucky person is attracted to unlucky events or energy.)
(This time, they will pick Korea's unluckiest person.)
(They can't be unluckier than this.)
(Jung Jung A is 1 in 6 million people to be bitten by an anaconda.)
(An initial member of Running Man, Lizzy only suffered and left.)
(Nam Chang Hie is one of the unluckiest entertainers.)
(Kim Tae Hee's little brother Lee Wan is another unlucky man.)
Who's the unluckiest man? Announcing in 1, 2, 3!
(Unlucky)
- Hello.
-  Hello.
- The First Unluckiest Festival.
- Hello. Hello.
-  The First Unluckiest Festival.
- The unluckiest...
-  They are feeding us.
- They are feeding us again.
-  The unluckiest festival.
Unlucky, unlucky, unlucky
Isn't this a festival for us?
- I am very unlucky.
-  And...
after hearing all the complaints, I made changes.
Did you allow your manager to put on some music in the car?
I told him to put on some music, but he refused.
- He kept refusing.
-  Maybe you've become distant.
- Gosh, I am...
-  And...
Put on some music.
- Put on some music.
-  Bye.
Put on whatever music you want to listen to.
Make sure you turn up the volume.
Let me hear how loud it'll be!
- Go on.
-  Put on some music.
Come on, play some music.
Let us hear some music.
- Bye, Jae Seok!
-  Bye!
- Bye.
-  Bye.
(Jae Seok is always willing to listen to your complaints.)
- Gosh...
-  Gosh...
Kwang Soo, why are you the only one dressed differently?
- Kwang Soo is...
-  He got sponsored.
- We are all wearing...
-  Casual outfits.
He used to wear hats, but after becoming a prince, he stopped.
- What? That's not true.
-  I am telling the truth.
And he only wears long coats.
- I love long coats.
-  He only wears them.
- I wear these to sleep, too.
-  You and Joong Ki are different.
Stop talking about Song Joong Ki!
(He doesn't want to hear Joong Ki's name.)
(He's burning with a sense of rivalry.)
Don't mention Song Joong Ki in front of me.
- Let's have a brainwave test.
-  Come on.
- Kwang Soo, you're just...
-  We might be able...
- a fellow comedian.
-  to see his brainwaves.
Why do you keep denying it?
Stop talking about Joong Ki!
- You are a comedian and an actor.
-  You are a member of Running Man.
- Yes.
-  Yes. You're a fellow comedian.
Why do you try to compete with Joong Ki and In Sung?
Many young comedians look up to you.
- Yes.
-  Too many people are discouraged.
You should start paying the monthly membership fee of SBS comedians.
(We should have a rival special with Kwang Soo and Joong Ki.)
- Gosh...
-  Isn't today's special...
for Kwang Soo, Seok Jin and me?
It's for the three of us, isn't it?
Haha is pretty unlucky, but he's luckier than us.
I'm in the shadows thanks to them.
Honestly speaking, you're one of us.
- Wait.
-  I am...
- Ji Hyo is the luckiest one.
-  Right, she is.
Then it's Jong Kook.
- Gary is all right.
-  Isn't Gary just ugly?
Hold on. I am sorry.
I feel like hitting you three times a day.
- He just looks unlucky.
-  Let go of me!
- Yes.
-  The unluckiest situation would...
- Being lucky just for today.
-  be being lucky just for the day.
It's because the unluckiest person will win today.
And you won't get any attention.
Last week, there was a question many people asked.
They wanted to know who the unluckiest member was.
So we prepared this special.
Today, we're going to have The First Unluckiest Festival.
All right!
There's no tension at all. It's one of these guys.
- Being really unlucky is...
-  The answer is given.
- getting lucky today.
-  That's right.
Among the members, three people will be leaders.
Each leader will cast unlucky people from the entertainment industry.
I see.
You will join the festival with them,
and the unluckiest team will be chosen.
- And then?
-  And the unluckiest person...
in that team will become the unluckiest man.
- Okay.
-  All right, I see.
So we will pick the unluckiest person from the unluckiest team.
- Right?
-  So today, it's good to be unlucky.
- Right.
-  You have to meet a good leader.
- The unluckiest man wins.
-  He will be the hero.
We will pick the 3 leaders from the 4 unluckiest members.
The three members who are relatively lucky will wait at the lobby.
Do we just have to wait?
From second floor to 11th floor, there are a total of 10 floors.
Among the 10 floors, 5 floors will have penalties.
The remaining five will be penalty-free.
Each of you will choose three floors, and...
the three people who get the most penalties will become the leaders.
So the unluckier ones will become the leaders.
- Bye.
-  See you later.
- Go, Kwang Soo!
-  Okay. See you later.
As long as I don't get penalties... Or is it better to get them?
- You will choose three floors.
-  Okay.
- We'll start bottom up.
-  From the second floor to the 11th?
(On 5 floors, the penalty team awaits.)
(On the other 5 floors, the lucky team awaits.)
- 10th floor.
-  10th floor.
(Kwang Soo chooses 10th floor.)
Next is the seventh floor. The lucky seven.
10th floor, seventh floor and...
(Kwang Soo chose 10th and 7th floors.)
Maybe there is no penalty on the second floor.
- Second floor.
-  10th floor,
- seventh floor and second floor.
-  Yes.
You can get on the lift and press those numbers.
Is it good to get the penalty?
(Welcome to the luck test lift.)
Please.
10th floor.
Seventh and second floors.
(Will he prove how unlucky he is?)
Here we go.
(He arrives on the 10th floor.)
The beginning is important.
Right?
(Will Kwang Soo get unlucky as usual?)
Hello.
(A man fills the lift with chalk dust.)
(Kwang Soo showers in chalk dust.)
Gosh, stop!
Okay! Okay!
This is the penalty, right?
Okay.
Penalty...
This is the penalty, right?
(He smirks.)
Okay.
So I got unlucky on my first choice.
I got unlucky on the 10th. I'll go with the seventh.
I guess I am really unlucky.
(He arrives on the 7th floor.)
Is this the seventh floor?
(Will he get unlucky again this time?)
Seventh floor.
(What's this?)
What?
(Oh dear!)
Wait.
I got my makeup done less than an hour ago.
Thank you. Today, I should feel happy about this.
Thank you, everyone.
Thank you!
(He has two penalties so far.)
It doesn't...
(Why am I not happy?)
It doesn't feel so nice.
This is the last floor.
I don't think there will be a penalty on the lowest floor.
Here we are.
(Will Kwang Soo get lucky this time?)
(Or will he be punished for the third time in a row?)
It's the second floor. What is this?
(Rushing)
What is this?
(He is showered with kisses.)
(There is love in the elevator.)
(Run towards Kwang Soo's lips!)
(Gosh!)
You little...
(Kwang Soo was penalised with a man's kisses.)
(Kwang Soo received penalties on all three floors.)
Did I get penalties on all three floors?
Was it on all three floors?
(Against the odds of 12 to 1, he was penalised 3 times.)
- What happened to your face?
-  What happened?
I'll definitely be chosen as the leader.
(Kwang Soo was penalised on all three floors.)
I chose three floors,
and they all had penalties!
(You're such an unlucky person.)
- Did you go first?
-  You never disappoint me.
- You had your makeup done.
-  Yes, I did.
- You're so unlucky.
-  Gosh, Kwang Soo.
They did this to your face even though you had makeup on.
- Yes, they did.
-  My goodness.
I bet I'll be the leader.
- When you showed up all dressed up,
-  That's right.
I knew something like this would happen.
I'm worried about Jae Seok.
(The second candidate, Seok Jin)
Why are the walls covered with plastic?
Why are they covered? This doesn't feel right.
I'll just go with my gut.
I shouldn't think too much.
The ninth floor.
(Seok Jin chooses the 9th floor.)
I'll just go with my gut.
(What will be waiting for Seok Jin?)
(Seok Jin's first choice turns out to be a lucky one.)
Should I be happy or not?
Okay.
Is this a good thing or a bad thing? I'm confused.
The seventh floor.
Shouldn't I be unlucky today?
Why was I hoping to be lucky?
We're on the seventh floor.
(Wish me bad luck!)
(Will he be penalised as he wishes?)
What's this? This is the penalty.
Please don't draw on my face.
(He begs.)
(Drawing a moustache)
Is it removable?
Gosh! Please!
(He was lucky on the 9th floor and unlucky on the 7th floor.)
I look like a cunning man.
(His moustache makes him look cunning.)
I hope I won't spend the day looking like this.
(Unfortunately, you will.)
The third floor.
I shouldn't have chosen the seventh floor...
as the number seven is considered lucky.
(Unlucky people tend to regret too late.)
(They're on the 3rd floor now.)
(How will his last choice turn out?)
Okay.
(Seok Jin is lucky today.)
Wait. I don't think I'll be the leader.
Right?
I won't be able to be the leader.
(It doesn't seem likely that Seok Jin will be the leader.)
I should have been penalised all three times.
(For now, Kwang Soo is in the lead.)
I was penalised only once.
I received two flower necklaces.
Gosh, I'm wearing too many flower necklaces.
- Look!
-  Seok Jin!
- He didn't get any penalties.
-  Did he not?
(Seok Jin is being unusually lucky today.)
I received two flower necklaces.
That means you passed.
- Is that so?
-  Did you get only one penalty?
Yes. How about him?
- He was penalised three times.
-  I'll be the leader.
He was penalised all three times.
Three times? Is that true?
Kwang Soo, I admire you.
That's unbelievable.
He's amazing.
I'm scared of myself.
We should see if Kwang Soo is possessed by some evil spirit.
- What are you talking about?
-  You never know.
It might be true.
- Look at Haha.
-  Haha also seems fine.
- How many do you have?
-  Did you get none?
- He wasn't penalised at all.
-  I have two necklaces.
- Are you wearing two necklaces?
-  Yes.
I'll choose fourth, sixth and ninth floors.
(Haha chose 4th, 6th and 9th floors.)
(He was penalised once.)
Seok Jin, you're amazing.
Kwang Soo was penalised all three times.
- Really?
-  He was penalised three times.
You're such an unlucky person.
- Don't say that.
-  How can this be possible?
You're perfect for variety shows.
Jae Seok is taking long. He must be getting penalised.
You're right. Receiving necklaces doesn't take long.
Receiving penalties takes long.
I have a question about the guy who kissed me.
Was he supposed to grab my bottom?
(The man even grabbed Kwang Soo's bottom.)
- He wasn't, was he?
-  He's here.
Jae Seok is here.
(What happened to Jae Seok?)
He's wearing one flower necklace.
(How was Jae Seok?)
We're on the seventh floor.
What is this?
Is this the penalty? What are you doing?
(He was penalised on the 7th floor.)
(The 5th floor)
Is this a lucky floor?
(He got 1 penalty and 1 flower necklace.)
(He was penalised for his third choice.)
(Unlucky)
Congratulations, you'll be the leader!
You'll be the leader.
Did you choose the seventh floor?
Yes, I did.
It's lucky seven!
- It's a lucky number.
-  I knew it.
No one can beat the three of us.
- But you're the unluckiest.
-  You're the one.
I don't want to be one of them.
- Seven is a lucky number.
-  Look at you three.
We really are unlucky.
Seok Jin and Haha have the same score.
- Take these boxes.
-  Okay.
Take these boxes.
(One of them is empty.)
One is empty, and the other has something interesting in it.
The one who has something inside the box becomes the leader.
- Oh, really?
-  Really?
All right, let's go.
Exchange them if you want.
(He changes his mind easily.)
- This feels right.
-  One...
One, two, three.
(They're opening the boxes.)
(Who will be the third leader?)
Oh, I got something.
Mine is empty!
What's that?
(Seok Jin is the third leader.)
This is unbelievable.
It's because they exchanged them.
You can't do anything about your bad luck.
This is amazing.
Am I supposed to put this on my head?
Seok Jin seems to be enjoying this.
No, I'm not.
- He looks very happy.
-  Are you jealous?
My head!
(The stockings tear.)
They got torn!
- Look at him.
-  Haha, like this?
I can't look at him.
What's that?
- That's too ugly.
-  He looks so ugly.
- He looks like Frankenstein.
-  Hey.
He's so unlucky that even the stockings got torn.
- They really did tear.
-  I can't believe that.
It's amazing.
Help me. It hurts.
It's really hard...
to choose.
Stand behind the leader you want.
- Goodness.
-  Welcome to the world of bad luck!
One, two, three.
Come to me...
- Come on!
-  if you want bad luck!
- Come to me.
-  Trust me.
-  Come to me.
Welcome to my world.
- Will they choose?
-  Two,
three.
(Please pick me!)
(Whom did they choose?)
(Gary and Ji Hyo chose Seok Jin, Jong Kook and Haha chose Kwang Soo.)
(No one chose Jae Seok.)
- Yes!
-  Nice!
(Kwang Soo and Seok Jin can have two more members.)
You should choose the oldest.
Do I have to invite four people then?
- Our leader is great.
-  How can I be so unlucky?
- I love my team.
-  You should choose the oldest.
Go find people to recruit.
Hurry up.
(Unlucky)
Wait. What should I do?
How will I find four people?
In addition, I have to find unlucky people.
Someone did come to my mind.
He's the unluckiest person in the world.
(Who is the first person Jae Seok thought of?)
Hi, Jae Seok.
I need your help.
- Do you need my help?
-  Yes.
(He agrees to help right away.)
I think we should meet fist.
- Sure.
-  Where do you live?
- I'll text you my address.
-  Okay.
Now, I know where I should go.
So let's go.
Fine. I'll prove that...
I'm the unluckiest.
If we're to find someone unlucky,
even though we're the ones left...
No way.
Lizzy was one of the Running Man members in the very beginning.
There were many other members.
- Run!
-  Stop!
-  Chase Joong Ki!
(Song Joong Ki was one of the members, too.)
Joong Ki became successful after leaving Running Man.
Joong Ki became very successful.
But Lizzy was a member back then, and...
- She's doing all right, too.
-  Just imagine.
Imagine she stayed with us.
Her life would have changed.
I'd say...
we should ask Lizzy's opinion.
How are you doing, Lizzy?
(They're going to ask Lizzy to be on Running Man again.)
I've missed you.
Oh, hello?
Wait, is this Lizzy?
Yes, this is Lizzy.
- What are you doing?
-  What are you up to?
I'm lying on my bed.
Don't you know what time it is?
Lizzy, don't you know what time it is?
Lizzy, don't you have any work to do?
Not much.
(She has a lot of free time.)
I do have some work, but it's not much.
Lizzy, actually, we're shooting Running Man right now.
- Oh, really?
-  Yes.
Today, we have to invite...
the unluckiest people.
- Lizzy, we're sorry about this.
-  Lizzy.
You were the first person we could think of.
I'm really sorry about that.
Lizzy, how about we get together today?
- What do you think?
-  Are you talking about drinking?
- No.
-  No...
Please stop making me sad!
- Lizzy.
-  Do you drink often these days?
Lizzy...
- Poor Lizzy.
-  Lizzy.
- You're number one.
Lizzy, I love you!
- He said, "I love you."
-  I love you, too.
- Okay.
-  I'll get ready.
Okay, Lizzy.
- Please wait a minute.
-  All right.
Who is the unluckiest person that we know of?
How about we call Hong Jin Ho?
- Jin Ho?
-  Good idea.
- Is he unlucky?
-  He was never number one.
- He could never be.
-  Then let's call Jin Ho.
If you think about it, wasn't Gary born unlucky, too?
Gary wasn't born without luck. He was born without looks.
(He was born without looks.)
(He's the ultimate ugly guy.)
Do you know people who are unlucky?
- I know one.
-  Who?
She's a singer.
But she knows that she is unlucky.
So she chose her agency name as Untus, which sounds lucky.
(So she chose her agency name as Untus, which sounds lucky.)
- She wanted to become lucky.
-  Really?
- Really.
It's really Untus.
- She wanted to be lucky?
-  Yes.
- Who is it, Gary?
-  It's Wax.
(The singer is Wax.)
- She said she was unlucky.
-  When I heard...
her name for the first time, I didn't like it.
Wax makes things slippery.
- That's right.
-  Isn't it?
She was known to be so unlucky that Shin Dong Yeob told her...
to change her name to "Waxing".
(Perhaps "Waxing" could have been a better name.)
He thought the present progressive form would be better.
He thought maybe "Waxing" would bring her more luck.
- Not "Wax", but "Waxing".
-  Right.
All right. Wait.
(Wax is first on their list.)
Who else is there?
Myung Ho is also unlucky.
Myung Ho is really unlucky.
- I don't usually...
-  Who is Myung Ho?
- Park Myung Ho.
-  Park Myung Ho.
- We were in Honeyfamily together.
-  Myung Ho is...
The moment you see Myung Ho,
you'll realise how unlucky he must have been.
To start off, his strength is even...
weaker than a woman's.
- You're right.
-  Aren't I?
If he were a vegetable,
he would be a water parsley.
(A water parsley would fit him.)
- Isn't that right?
-  You're right.
- You're right.
-  He's light like a water parsley.
He's not like a garlic stem.
No, he's not like a garlic stem.
He's not strong like a leek.
But he's weak like a water parsley or bracken.
- You're right.
-  He's wavering.
- His rapping is also like that.
-  Yes.
Let's call them over and pick the unluckiest person.
I should have brought some money.
I should buy them a meal at least.
(Glancing)
Do you have any money?
No.
Oh, my.
Think about it.
I'm not just asking for it. I'll pay back.
Think before you say no.
(We've known each other for so long!)
I really don't have any money.
You're like a sheep.
Or a mountain goat.
(He's a fox disguised as a sheep.)
My goodness.
(Jae Seok arrives at the first team member candidate's house.)
(They are nearly done with parking.)
There isn't much space on this side.
What?
Could you park again?
I think the door is going to touch that car.
That's more than enough space to get off.
It's an expensive, foreign car.
You're so high-maintenance. This is why...
we can't engage in a chase.
(The nation's show host is waiting for...)
(one of the unluckiest men.)
Oh, my.
(He's here. Who is he?)
- Chang Hie.
-  Yes, Jae Seok.
(The unluckiest man Jae Seok knows is Nam Chang Hie.)
(He's a comedian that is active in both entertainment and dramas.)
Are you sure?
(Is he really unlucky?)
What do you think today's theme is?
- Today?
-  Yes.
- Teen stars?
-  What?
I debuted when I was in high school.
I'm sorry.
We're really unlucky.
- Today is about being unlucky.
-  What?
- Being unlucky?
-  Yes, being unlucky.
You've been trying so hard.
It's been a while since you debuted. How many years has it been?
- It's been 17 years.
-  And you live in that house...
- with Sae Ho. And he's doing great.
-  Yes.
Do you think that you're unlucky?
- I think I am very unlucky.
-  Give an example.
Another broadcasting company...
offered to cast me for a programme.
I'd be the host that asks questions to the comedians...
as if it were the civil service exams from history.
- But?
-  But that...
was edited out completely. It wasn't aired at all.
- They stopped shooting suddenly.
-  Why?
I don't know. Director Kim Tae Ho stopped us.
- Not here.
-  He wanted to stop shooting.
Not here. It's not because of you.
- It's not because of you.
-  It's not entirely because of me.
It's not because of you.
The recording didn't go very well that day.
- And so...
-  Yes.
at the end of the year,
there are awards ceremonies. At an award ceremony,
they told me I would be given an award...
- for being entirely edited out.
-  Right.
- They invited you.
-  Yes, they invited me.
But that too was entirely edited out.
(He really has no luck.)
(Nam Chang Hie in Team Jae Seok, the unlucky man who gets edited out)
- There's another fellow.
-  Who?
(Who?)
- Jung Jung A.
-  Jung Jung A.
- The icon of anaconda?
-  That's correct.
- She was doing great.
-  Yes, she was.
She might have reached her peak, but then she was bitten by an anaconda.
Who would have guessed?
Yes. That is very unlucky.
- Yes, Jae Seok.
-  Jung A.
- Hello.
-  Where are you?
Me?
Are you with someone?
I'm paying my monthly rent to the owner at the moment.
- I see. Jung A.
-  Yes.
Could you text me your exact location?
I'll be waiting nearby your house.
(See you in front of the house.)
Jung A is also...
(He suddenly feels sorry.)
- Jung A is also unlucky.
-  Yes.
Do you know anyone...
that is known to be very unlucky?
(His team is not full yet.)
- Lee Wan.
-  Lee Wan?
-  Are you saying that...
(What?)
Are you saying that Kim Tae Hee's brother, Lee Wan, is unlucky?
Isn't it unlucky to have been born as Kim Tae Hee's brother?
- Why?
-  All the men in Korea...
and in the world dream of getting to know Kim Tae Hee.
- What? Give me a break.
-  We have hope.
Do you think you can get to know her?
I could.
We can at least dream of it. You never know.
Oh, my.
But he can't.
- You're right.
-  Yes.
You're right.
- It's very persuasive.
-  It is, isn't it?
- He can't go out with his sister.
-  Right.
(Do you think it's unlucky to live with Kim Tae Hee?)
It can never happen.
Let's go.
But are you sure we aren't intruding?
- Seriously.
-  Wax may be...
- We're suddenly visiting her.
-  She goes to a fancy place.
(Who is waiting for Team Seok Jin?)
I think the person's over here.
- Isn't that Wax?
-  Yes, it is.
Wax.
(A woman is fixing her makeup.)
(Wax is the queen of ballad.)
(But Gary says she's unlucky.)
- Over here.
-  Wax was fixing her makeup.
(Just like the title of her song)
- Wax was fixing her makeup.
-  She was really fixing her makeup.
Why is your name Wax? It sounds so slippery.
It was all right in the beginning.
- Your song was a hit.
-  Wax...
was lucky in the beginning. But her middle age luck is bad.
- No.
-  Why would've you say that?
- The middle period of her career.
-  Wax.
Do you have a boyfriend?
Not at the moment.
- Your luck with men...
-  I'm not lucky with men.
You don't? Who's the man that you're closest to?
Hong Seok Cheon.
(He is the safest man to be around.)
- Seok Cheon?
-  Yes.
Her biggest drawback is that she always tries to beat me.
(Laughing)
She's trying to target a lucky person.
That's right. So Gary always tells me...
that I was born unlucky.
He says that.
I want to test her.
All right.
- Let's do a test.
-  I'm really...
famous for being unlucky.
I have one that I want to pick.
- This one.
-  I chose that one.
- Is that so?
-  I wanted that one.
Do you want to switch?
- No.
-  I chose that one.
I really wanted that one.
- Is that so?
-  Yes.
I'm easily influenced. Should we switch?
- Should we?
-  Yes.
Okay.
Was that even worth it?
Is it worth switching between unlucky people?
Flip over after I count to three.
- One, two, three.
-  Two, three.
(The oldest unluckiest person)
(Born to be unlucky versus the oldest unluckiest person)
(Who will be the unluckiest?)
She really picked that.
- You're really unlucky.
-  She's easily influenced.
- Why did she switch?
(Seok Jin is happy that he won.)
- She even switched.
-  I told you...
- that she is unlucky.
-  She beat me.
I acknowledge you.
- I acknowledge you.
-  I am easily influenced.
If I didn't switch, I would have won.
Of course. Try it with Gary.
Here. Wax, go first.
(Now it's a match against lucky Gary.)
This one.
- I'll pick this one.
-  Now...
Will you switch?
- Do you want to switch?
-  I won't switch this time.
She's so stubborn with me.
- I want to beat Gary.
-  One, two, three.
(Gary wins.)
(Wax loses two times in a row.)
She can't beat me!
- She can't.
-  She didn't switch this time.
(Maybe she was really born unlucky.)
- You'd have won if you switched.
-  Yes, you're right.
We've come to the right person.
(Will she be the rising unluckiest person?)
I'll do it.
- Each hold one.
-  We each have to pick one.
And show it.
(Only one of the spoons is unlucky.)
- Pick one.
-  I want this one. This one.
That one? Are you sure?
- Do you want to switch?
-  No, I won't.
- Do you not want to?
-  I will go with my first choice.
(She picks one without delay.)
- Oh, my.
-  It's the unlucky one.
(Oh, my.)
- Wow. I have goosebumps.
-  I told you.
- Me, too.
-  I've got goosebumps.
She's always stubborn with me, but ends up being unlucky.
How could she pick this?
- There's no need to carry on.
-  This is enough.
You're the winner.
- You're definitely a top candidate.
-  This doesn't make me...
feel that great.
Look here.
There were two of these.
(A true unlucky person avoids the two R spoons.)
I will use up all my unlucky energy in Running Man today.
- Great.
-  Use up all your unlucky energy.
- Use it all up and start fresh.
-  That's great.
- We would like to cast you.
-  Yes.
- Right, we have no choice.
-  You're very unlucky.
(Am I doing it right?)
Should I feel happy?
(Wax in Team Seok Jin, she gets unluckier when with Gary.)
I think she is in a coffee shop near here.
- There she is.
-  She said she'll be waiting there.
-  She is Jung A.
She intentionally dressed that way, didn't she?
She hasn't changed at all.
Where are you going?
I was waiting for a driver because my car broke down.
- Is that so?
-  Yes.
I am going to play badminton with Lee Moon Se tonight.
Why did you bring your racquet? You will play at night, won't you?
Because I have nothing to do before that.
I came out early.
I live right there.
- Where?
-  Right beside the red building.
- Really?
-  Yes.
Why don't you come over to my place?
(What did you just say?)
Why not?
The balcony at my place is pretty big.
- Okay. Let's go then.
-  Let's go in.
(Jung Jung A in Team Jae Seok, first actress to be bitten by an anaconda)
- You have a puppy.
-  Yes.
But you don't seem to hold her in your arms often.
Right. I don't hold her in my arms at all.
That's why...
Although I don't keep a puppy at all,
she seems to feel comfortable in my arms.
She really does.
I think she will come with you to your place if you ask her so.
Right.
Others might think you've been here before.
She likes you so much.
Gosh.
Many will find this suspicious.
- True.
-  You live near here.
- Right.
-  We've met a few times...
before you got married.
I used to give you rides to the video rental shop.
Yes, you did. When we used to belong to the same agency,
- she gave me rides to the shop.
-  I see.
- She dropped me at the shop.
-  Okay.
I asked him what he rented, but he never let me know.
He put the video tapes inside a plastic bag and never showed me.
- He always had a plastic bag...
-  I didn't want to drop the tapes.
- Oh, you didn't want to drop them.
-  Right.
Anyway, we have a problem.
We need two more members in our team.
Can you contact Lee Wan now?
- Let me call him now.
-  Lee Wan?
- Yes, please call him.
Yes, Lee Wan. It sounds promising.
Do you mean the brother of Kim Tae Hee?
Do you personally know him?
I'm a bit worried. He might have changed his phone number.
But let me call Wan.
- Is he younger than you?
-  Yes, one year younger.
(Chang Hie tries to contact Lee Wan.)
Hello?
Wan.
- It has been a long time.
-  Hello, it's Chang Hie.
- Of course, I know it's you.
-  Hey.
Thank you for answering my call gladly. Here is my bow.
(Chang Hie becomes polite.)
I...
- Why would you bow to me.
-  I miss you.
Where are you now, Wan?
- I am home.
-  I see.
- Let me get someone on the phone.
-  Here. Hello?
- Hello?
-  This is Yu Jae Seok.
Oh, hi.
That is exactly how I felt.
I can see how nervous you are. Please relax.
Calm down and listen to me, please.
- I...
-  It's because you're on the line.
(Getting a random call from Jae Seok)
- Chang Hie said...
-  Yes.
you're very unlucky.
- Me?
-  Yes.
- Please tell him why he is unlucky.
-  Okay.
Wan, you're unlucky...
because you can never see Tae Hee as a woman while other guys can.
Right?
I see.
- That is why you're unlucky.
-  Yes, you're unlucky.
(Wan, you are not lucky.)
Well, I never thought Tae Hee was pretty.
- That's nonsense.
-  No way!
You will be surprised when you meet my cousin.
(You'd know that Tae Hee is pretty if you meet my cousin.)
You'd better meet my female friends.
My goodness.
Don't you want to test yourself if you're lucky or unlucky?
Now it sounds tempting though.
(We've got you!)
Then, Wan.
- Yes?
-  We should meet first.
Will you come to my place?
Yes, we will pick you up near your place.
Well, will I be okay?
Yes, you'll be okay.
It will be okay.
Don't worry.
Okay. Today, we'll meet him.
- Lee Wan!
-  Thank you, Wan.
- Thank you. See you soon.
-  Thank you.
- All right.
-  We finally got him.
- There's one more to call.
-  Who?
- Kang Hyun Soo.
-  Oh, I know Hyun Soo.
You mean V.One?
(Do you remember Kang Hyun Soo?)
It's over now.
- I don't care any more.
-  Stop shooting. He said it's over.
Move the lighting and microphones to this side. He doesn't care now.
(Are we meeting the Kang Hyun Soo from 15 years ago?)
I know Hyun Soo. He is a friend of mine.
Let's call Hyun Soo then.
He's busy running a lot of business, but they don't work out.
Doesn't he have an event agency?
- It's not doing well.
-  Hello?
- Hyun Soo.
-  Yes, Jae Seok.
Where are you now?
I'm on my way to replace my car tires to new ones.
Why is this funny?
This unlucky guy will change the tires today.
- So...
-  What happened?
So you're free today.
- Sorry?
-  You're free today, right?
- I'll replace my tires first,
-  Yes.
and my car's check engine light is on.
So I have to get it checked.
Hyun Soo, do you know Jung A?
- Jung A?
-  Yes.
Park Jung A?
(Do you mean Park Jung A?)
Jung A said you're her friend.
I only know Jung Jung A and Park Jung A.
I meant Jung Jung A.
Yes, she is a good friend of mine.
Can you join us for shooting today?
- Well...
-  Yes?
- I don't look good now.
-  It's okay. We all look bad today.
- I look even sick today.
-  I look much worse than you.
- Then, okay.
-  We became five easily.
I feel like I'm running an employment centre.
It just happened.
- Is it here?
-  I think so.
Let's call her.
Let me see. Oh, this building must be right.
- Hi.
-  It's Lizzy.
- Right.
-  Lizzy!
Lizzy!
(It's nice meeting you, Lizzy.)
- Lizzy.
-  Lizzy.
- You're here.
-  Gosh.
- Lizzy.
-  Hi.
(We've met our unlucky original member in 5 years.)
(A tear-jerking moment to meet everyone)
(She was a high schooler when we first met her.)
What?
- Hello.
-  Hello!
(Lizzy was with us when Running Man started 5 years go.)
(And now you're our guest.)
What happened?
Jin Ho is here, too.
- Hello.
-  Hi.
Are you also an unsuccessful person?
- No.
-  No, we're not unsuccessful.
Lizzy, it's not unsuccessful.
- It's unlucky.
-  It's unlucky.
- I got it now.
-  We're not unsuccessful.
- You got it?
-  Yes.
Hello.
(Lizzy in Team Kwang Soo, the original member of Running Man)
I am so happy to be with you here, Lizzy.
- Right.
-  Long time no see, Lizzy.
Old memories come to my mind.
What makes you the happiest nowadays?
I feel happy at night.
- Why?
-  Because I can sleep at night.
- I see.
-  I have nothing to do...
- Poor Lizzy.
-  even if I wake up early.
Please don't say that, Lizzy.
- I feel like crying.
-  Haha, you should apologise to her.
I am sorry, Lizzy.
- It's okay.
-  It's my fault.
(Poor Lizzy, you're having a dire time.)
Twinkle, twinkle
- Twinkle, twinkle
-  Why are you singing suddenly?
- She scared me.
-  Looking at the stars
Is this a sad song?
I just realised that it is a sad song.
- Gosh.
-  I need to drink now.
- My goodness.
-  It's so sad.
Lizzy, I love you.
Lizzy, I am sorry.
That's what love is
What am I doing?
Gosh.
(At this rate, she could easily be the winner.)
- Gosh.
-  Oh, Lizzy.
(Let's take a look at what Seok Jin's team is up to.)
You should hide now.
Please hide now.
Myung Ho doesn't know anything now.
We called him all of a sudden.
He just woke up five minutes ago. He will come out, knowing nothing...
because we told him to do so.
So we will hide our cameras...
and our name tags.
I can't wait to meet him.
- Have you met him before?
-  No, not even once.
Myung Ho is here.
- Is he? Where?
-  There.
Where is he?
- Gary.
-  Myung Ho!
(Park Myung Ho was the leader of legendary Honeyfamily.)
(Charismatic Park Myung Ho is coming.)
Gosh.
(Who are you?)
(Looking sloppy)
Hello, Myung Ho.
Myung Ho, look at your legs.
Why are your legs so skinny?
They look so weak.
He rapped at my wife's birthday party.
Please rap for us now. Go!
(Please show us how you rapped at the birthday party.)
(Let's see what this legendary rapper showed at the party.)
Myung Ho is here
He came here with hopes of finding his dreams
(Why would he look for his dreams at Seok Jin's wife's party?)
- It is so funny.
-  Goodness.
He never says no when people ask him to rap.
- Right.
-  Let's take him now.
How much do you weigh?
I used to weigh 62kg, but after I got conned...
- He got conned.
-  I'm not lying.
- We need someone like you.
-  Gosh.
We've been looking for someone just like you.
You're a very competent candidate today.
Do you always carry water with you?
- Oh, water.
-  I have a serious panic disorder.
(I have a serious panic disorder.)
(Busker with panic disorder?)
He always says that he suffers from panic disorder.
(We want to know who this rapper really is.)
I've known Gary since I was 19.
I used to like straightforward rapping style.
But Myung Ho told me to use nasal sound when I rap.
Like this. He kept telling me to do so.
No, it's the swing.
With Gary and Gary and I
It had the swing.
- Okay.
-  Do you really have panic disorder?
Yes. I am still dizzy.
(He's dizzy because of his panic disorder.)
I am serious.
Do you watch Running Man?
Honestly, I don't own a TV.
(He doesn't own a TV.)
Poor him.
Let's win and...
- use the gold to buy him a TV.
-  Let's buy him a TV.
He fits perfectly into today's special.
I can't even be compared to him.
- His unluckiness is another level.
-  Right. His level of unluckiness...
- is on another scale.
-  Let's test him.
- You can test him.
-  I can do it.
- I think I'll pick "unlucky".
-  There are two cards.
Honestly, I hope he will pick the "lucky" card.
- Me too.
-  But...
- I feel so sad today.
-  I hope I pick the "lucky" card.
- Today, it's...
-  Pick one card, Myung Ho.
- Pick one card.
-  It's darkness.
Things are not working out for me.
- Pick one.
-  Gosh...
- You chose that?
-  Yes.
Check it.
Gosh...
(He picks the "unlucky" card.)
I shouldn't be laughing.
I am right-handed, so I was going to pick the right one.
But I thought I would just go with the left one.
I won't do it.
I am going to cry.
(He's about to break into tears.)
(He's probably the unluckiest person ever.)
Gosh, we have no choice...
but to cast you. Great.
I cannot not cast him.
(Park Myung Ho in Team Seok Jin, the unlucky hip hop musician)
- It's Mikey!
-  Isn't he the one?
- Yes.
-  Mikey!
He's not the Mikey you used to know, right?
I think I should resign and rest today.
But you don't have any work.
- Right. I don't have any work.
-  You should come with us.
- You can ride the crew's car.
-  That's okay, right?
Hyun Soo.
Nothing too bad happened, right?
- I need to look for a place.
-  Is that so?
So your lease contract has expired.
Actually, I have one year to go.
(He still has a year left in his lease contract.)
(So why are you looking for a place?)
We need to give him the team uniform first.
(He gets the team uniform.)
Give me an extra large size.
Hey, you see...
I'm not selling clothes right now.
- He's not selling clothes.
-  Look.
I'm sorry, Hyun Soo, but I am not selling clothes.
(Team Jae Seok casts Kang Hyun Soo.)
It's like we are fans waiting in front of a celebrity's house.
Where did Hyun Soo go?
He's in the car. He's getting changed.
- That looks like him.
-  You should join us.
It's Hyun Soo.
- Hyun Soo!
-  Yes.
(Why did he go past us?)
- He got changed.
-  Where are you going?
They told me to park my car and join you.
This is Lee Wan's place. Where are you going?
Tell us where you are going.
I thought you were in the shoot.
He thought we were in the shoot.
There... There he is. He's out.
- He's coming.
-  He's Wan.
- Right?
-  It's Wan.
(Finally, Kim Tae Hee's brother, handsome Lee Wan is coming.)
There he is.
- He's out.
-  He's so handsome.
- Hyun Soo, hurry and move your car.
-  I can see that from afar.
(Jae Seok rushes Hyun Soo to move his car.)
- Move your car!
-  Move your car!
- Stop blocking our view!
-  Get out of the way!
- Move. Move your car, Hyun Soo.
-  What is he doing?
- Gosh...
-  Why would you go there?
Hyun Soo.
(Is he doing this out of jealousy?)
Gosh...
It's good that we chose him. Kwang Soo's role is perfect for him.
Gosh, look at Wan.
Hello!
He's unbelievably handsome.
- Hello.
-  Hello, Wan.
- Goodness.
-  He's so handsome.
Hello.
It's been a while.
- Gosh...
-  He's like a work of art.
Wan, you...
- You just came out of the house.
-  I took a shower.
- He washed his hair.
-  He washed his hair and came out.
I can smell the shampoo.
But he looks too good.
(He just took a shower, but he looks as if he went to a salon.)
Tae Hee is calling me right now.
- Really?
-  It says "My sister".
Really?
Hello?
Yes.
- His sister is Kim Tae Hee.
-  What?
His sister is Kim Tae Hee.
Can you ask her this question?
Hold on. I will put him on the phone.
Someone has a question for you.
(He gives his phone to Jae Seok.)
Hello?
- Hello?
-  Tae Hee.
I am Yu Jae Seok.
(Jae Seok introduces himself to Tae Hee.)
Yes, hello.
Oh gosh!
I can't believe it!
- It's my luckiest day!
-  It really is his luckiest day.
It's the luckiest day for me!
No, it's the luckiest day for me.
- How...
-  I can't believe it!
I really can't believe it.
- Today, we are...
-  Yes.
You are not on a shoot, are you?
We are on a shoot.
(They are shooting Running Man.)
What are you shooting?
We are shooting Running Man.
- Is that right? Oh dear!
-  I wanted to ask you something.
Today's a special about unlucky people.
(It's a special about unlucky people.)
- And...
-  Yes.
Chang Hie said Wan is unlucky.
He's unlucky because he cannot be your lover in this life.
- In that sense, he's unlucky.
-  I see.
Thankfully, he agreed to join us today.
I see.
So he just came out, and...
when he was about to leave with us, his sister called him.
And it turns out his sister is Kim Tae Hee.
(It just so happens that his sister is Kim Tae Hee.)
I really didn't know. He never told me he's going on Running Man.
Gosh...
- By the way.
-  Yes.
Are you usually lucky or unlucky?
I think...
- I think I am very lucky.
-  Is that so?
Of course. I consider myself lucky.
If you were unlucky, we were going to fetch you right now.
(If she was unlucky, they were going to get her as a team member.)
- Anyway,
-  Please invite me next time.
It was so nice to talk to you, Tae Hee.
It was nice to talk to you, too.
Thank you for letting me talk to you unexpectedly.
Tae Hee, you are the best.
You are our angel.
Thank you so much. I hope to see you next time...
- on a show.
-  Right.
Okay. Thank you.
Thank you.
Thank you!
Wait.
I don't think I will be able to walk the dog.
We were supposed to walk the dog together.
- Gosh...
-  How beautiful would that be!
You are so great.
You walk the dog like this?
With your hair like that?
(Like this?)
Your sister is Kim Tae Hee.
You will walk the dog with her with that hair?
- Isn't that too much?
-  Really?
Wouldn't that be too beautiful?
Gosh, Wan. Thank you.
I am sorry, Hyun Soo.
- You're here.
-  He just came.
(When did you come?)
I'm a bad guy.
- For a moment,
-  Don't hit yourself.
if Tae Hee said she was unlucky,
I was going to give her your place.
I am sorry.
- You were going to send him home.
-  I am sorry.
We can shoot a commercial together if you are sorry.
I am sorry.
Anyway, let's go with Wan.
I am so thankful that Wan agreed to join us.
- It's no problem.
-  Thanks.
- Thank you.
-  It's not easy.
All right.
(Team Jae Seok is moving to the final destination, Mokdong.)
All the unlucky people are here.
You know what I was jealous about him?
- His sister.
-  His sister.
It said "My sister" on his phone.
(Kim Tae Hee is saved on his phone as "My sister")
In that moment, I felt so sorry to my brothers.
I have two little brothers, and they don't tell people about me.
Hyun Soo, is your sister beautiful, too?
- My sister is in the province.
-  Okay.
- She stays with my parents.
- And she works.
-  I didn't ask about her life.
(He asked if she's beautiful!)
- That's not what I asked.
-  Right.
Right. So please answer my question.
- Chang Hie, do you have siblings?
-  I have an elder brother.
- I see.
-  Right.
- You won't ask more questions?
-  What?
What should I ask about?
- You could ask about him.
-  There is nothing...
There is nothing to ask.
There's nothing to ask.
Siblings look alike.
- How about you?
-  I have two little sisters.
(He feels guilty.)
- You have 2 sisters?
-  I have 2 little sisters.
- Okay.
-  Are they beautiful?
Don't ask.
They are happy.
(They are happy.)
Appearance is not important.
- I...
-  Gosh, Wan.
I envy Wan.
(Everyone is jealous of Wan.)
- But you are married.
-  I know.
How nice is it? His sister is Kim Tae Hee.
- His sister is Kim Tae Hee.
-  It's very nice.
- When I was in school,
-  Yes.
I was never beaten up by upperclass students.
All the school gang leaders liked my sister.
That's great.
(Thanks to his beautiful sister, he had a comfortable school life.)
But when she sees Wan,
she must be proud that...
- her brother is so handsome.
-  Right. Wan is handsome.
- And his sister is beautiful.
-  They are both good-looking.
- They must be happy.
-  They must be proud.
Gosh...
She must be proud of her handsome little brother.
He's got this nice hair that drapes down.
And he walks the dog like that.
- He's like Prince Charming.
-  Yes. It's charming.
(At 5pm, everyone arrives at the final stage.)
- We don't need to take anything?
-  Of course.
Let's get off.
- Today, the unlucky person wins.
-  That's right.
(The unluckiest celebrities will compete against each other.)
(Whenever they make a decision, things will burst, break and crush.)
You can't get eliminated now.
(Who will be the first unluckiest person?)
(Unlucky)
- The First Unluckiest Festival.
-  What?
- It's for the unlucky people.
-  That's right.
We are all gathered here for the festival.
- We will do a simple test.
-  Okay.
- Of course.
-  Why did you put Jin Ho here?
- How can you treat him so badly?
-  What do you mean?
He chose to sit there.
He chose to sit there? What do you mean?
- That's not it.
-  Jae Seok.
- Jin Ho is...
-  Yes.
- pretty unlucky, too.
-  Right.
- But he looked at other people,
-  They are too unlucky.
- and he gave up.
-  He gave up.
- He dropped out.
-  Is that right?
- Now that I'm here,
-  Yes.
I've realised how happy I am.
(He realised how happy he is.)
- He had a healing experience.
-  It made him happy.
He came here, and he realised how happy he is.
- It turns out I'm a happy person.
-  You can't complain.
- Everyone.
-  It's crazy.
Let's do a simple verification.
- Why is Lizzy here?
-  Jae Seok!
- You know why.
-  You know why I am here!
- I am sorry.
-  I got fired.
Lizzy, I am sorry.
- Okay.
-  She made Nana...
to be picked as the world's most beautiful girl.
- Lizzy did that?
-  She did that.
- She brings good luck.
-  She does.
Why do I never seem to go up?
- What do you mean?
-  Why am I in the same place?
Lizzy.
- Don't say that.
-  Lizzy.
You did seem to talk a bunch of random things.
- It's been too long.
-  I'm okay.
She must be nervous.
Mikey, aren't things picking up for you?
You recently had a concert.
It ended six days ago.
- Six days ago?
-  I've been home ever since.
- Ever since the concert?
-  Yes.
- To tell you the truth,
-  That's too bad.
I've always wanted to be on Running Man.
- Really?
-  He told me all the time.
But to be on television, I should wash myself.
- Of course.
-  But I don't have hot water.
- It's true.
-  He uses hot water next door.
That was why he smelled like an old man.
Don't be too specific.
- Please, don't.
-  When I met him...
Don't describe in detail.
I hugged him, and he smelled like an old man.
Please stop.
Chang Hie is on my team.
He was the first person I tried to invite.
Of course.
- He's living with Sae Ho.
-  That's right.
Aren't you living at Sae Ho's apartment?
It's not that I'm living at his apartment.
I pay rent, too.
- Oh, really?
-  Of course.
We're sharing the apartment.
- They're sharing it.
-  Are you sure?
- Isn't it just Sae Ho's apartment?
-  They're sharing the apartment.
- Are you sharing the apartment?
-  Yes.
- It's not his apartment.
-  Is it a shared apartment?
Can't you show that to us?
- What do you mean?
-  The movie, "Ip Man".
- Do you mean actor Donnie Yen?
-  Yes.
- Oh, Donnie Yen.
-  Show us.
Actually, he has mimicked Donnie Yen...
on many other programmes.
(He has mimicked Donnie Yen on many other programmes.)
- He does it well.
-  But it was always cut out.
- This is Donnie Yen from "Ip Man".
-  Donnie Yen.
(Donnie Yen is a star who represents China.)
- Doesn't he look just like him?
-  That's hilarious.
(He looks exactly like the actor.)
It's Donnie Yen.
He looks exactly like him.
Are you sure you're not Donnie Yen?
- You look exactly like him.
-  He's amazing.
-  You really do.
Chang Hie was the first person I met today.
- Chang Hie invited Lee Wan.
-  Really?
- We...
-  Why is Wan here?
Chang Hie called Wan after three years.
I was very happy to hear from him.
The thing is...
I'm a positive person.
I've always considered myself lucky. But Chang Hie...
tried to convince me that I'm unlucky.
He suggested I should...
- test my luck here today.
-  I agree.
That's why I'm here.
He was actually going to... Do you know who his sister is?
Of course.
- His sister?
-  Do you know who she is?
Actually, he was going to...
walk his dog with her this evening.
Shouldn't we be there instead?
- We shouldn't be here now.
-  I can go.
- I could get a dog right now.
-  Do you see?
I'll go get a dog now.
Look at his hairstyle.
He was going to walk his dog in that hairstyle.
- We should have seen that instead.
-  I should've gone.
He was going to walk his dog in that hairstyle.
- But he came here instead.
-  Exactly.
But his sister is Kim Tae Hee.
How can he be unlucky?
But Wan doesn't think so.
People say...
my sister is pretty,
but I don't understand.
(He doesn't understand why people say Kim Tae Hee is pretty.)
- He doesn't understand.
-  I can't believe that.
Kwang Soo! He's not talking about your sister.
My sister looks exactly like me!
She's the long-haired version of me.
Go back to your seat.
- Anyway...
-  My sister has a moustache!
(His sister is growing a moustache.)
She's a girl, but she has a moustache.
Stop.
Calm down.
- Come on.
-  That's why.
- I can't believe that.
-  That's why he's unlucky.
- We could say he's unlucky.
-  I understand.
Also, we have Jung A here.
Everyone knows her.
She's also known as the Anaconda Lady.
(Anaconda Lady)
She's the only lady who got bitten by an anaconda.
Isn't she the only one in Korea?
That's right.
Where did you get bitten?
It bit my arm.
I thought it would rip my arm off.
It could.
I managed to pull my arm out,
but its teeth got stuck in my arm.
Its teeth must've been decayed.
- What?
-  What is he saying?
That must be why they came off.
Anacondas can have cavities, too.
A tooth doesn't have to be decayed to come out.
- Are you sure?
-  Yes.
Would you like to try?
(Should I pull out one of your teeth?)
What are you talking about?
- Why would you pull his tooth out?
-  Goodness.
(Seok Jin's teeth are on the line.)
- He was curious.
-  Why?
He wants to see.
- You're scaring me.
-  He's curious.
All right.
So these are on my team.
- Next, Team Seok Jin.
-  Well...
Myung Ho told me about his life.
It was so...
(Would you like to know about him?)
(In "Breaking Walls" earlier,)
(the luckiest one was to be eliminated.)
(When everyone else broke through the walls,)
(Myung Ho was left alone.)
(He's definitely the unluckiest one.)
I told Gary before.
When we were doing the 100 versus 100 Special,
I told Gary to invite Myung Ho.
- I tried to.
-  Then why?
Myung Ho, why didn't you come before?
The thing is, I'm sick.
(I was sick.)
I'm really sick.
Why is it so sad?
- It's true.
-  I shouldn't laugh.
You look healthy.
- I'm really sick.
-  What's the problem?
I've been too stressed out.
I used to weigh 62kg, but now I weigh only 49kg.
I used to see him a lot.
Compared to the past,
- Is he a lot thinner now?
-  he has become very thin.
I made a debut on September 23, 1995.
- The band's name was "Honey".
-  Right.
The song was called "A Kid Called X".
We made a debut at around the same time.
Can you rap for us?
You were born in a small town
To a poor family
You don't seem to be sick at all.
(He doesn't seem sick at all.)
- I'm not sick when I rap.
-  He's not sick when he raps.
You said you have heart problems.
- How can he rap like that?
-  I thought he was sick.
- I'm really sick.
-  He doesn't have panic disorder.
- He seems fine.
- You look very healthy.
-  Are you really sick?
He insists he has panic disorder, but he talked so much in the car.
Actually...
You can even do a freestyle rap right now, right?
I can do a freestyle rap, but I don't think people will understand
They think rap has to have rhymes
This is rap to me, but people never understand
Why is that?
I don't know why
(This is what freestyle rap is.)
Why? Would Seok Jin know?
Would Jae Seok know?
I can't seem to understand
Why is that?
(His introduction is over.)
All right. Now,
we should decide who will represent each team.
- Do we need representatives?
-  Let's play a simple game.
(The first round of The First Unluckiest Festival starts now.)
(Unlucky)
(Round 1: The Battle of Aces)
- This is a flour game.
-  What kind of game is it?
Flour?
You will say numbers from 1 to 31.
Our staff...
will pick a number.
(The one who says the chosen number will win.)
The one who says that number will win.
- The one who says that number?
-  Exactly.
We'll go up to 31.
The one who is penalised wins.
The one who gets the flour wins.
The unluckiest will win.
- Really?
-  Okay.
Are we to continue until 31?
- The unluckiest wins.
-  We need one from each team.
Please send out your aces.
We'll choose Hyun Soo.
(Team Jae Seok chose Hyun Soo.)
- Don't worry about getting hit.
-  Okay.
- You can get hit with the flour.
-  We choose Mikey.
Here comes Mikey.
(He hasn't succeeded in anything else than Turbo.)
- Good luck!
-  Good luck!
Go, Mikey!
(Team Seok Jin chose Gary.)
Show us how unlucky you are!
- Show us!
-  Good luck!
We have the representatives here.
The unluckiest is the luckiest today.
- That's right.
-  I can't believe this.
- The unluckiest wins.
-  This is amazing!
- I'll pick a number.
-  You have to focus on...
- Okay, go ahead.
-  getting unlucky.
- The one who gets the flour wins.
-  If you believe...
you will choose the right number, then you will win.
- Ready.
-  Please.
- Please!
-  Start!
One, two.
Three.
- Four.
-  Say as many numbers as you can.
(Say as many numbers as you can.)
Five, six, seven.
- Good job.
-  Then, 8, 9, 10.
It must be near.
They've come far.
11, 12, 13.
(It should burst about now.)
14, 15, 16.
17.
- 18.
-  It's until 31.
19, 20.
- Didn't he say 4 numbers?
-  21, 22, 23.
- It's almost over.
-  Wait a minute!
(Panicking)
He said, 21, 22, 23.
- Will Gary win?
-  Not many numbers are left.
- Wait!
-  31 is the last one.
- Say as many numbers as possible!
-  You need to win!
- Should I say many?
-  Yes, you should.
Mikey could get the flour!
- You need to get it right!
-  Say as many as possible.
- Oh, I need to win, right?
-  Yes, that's right.
The one who gets the flour wins.
24, 25, 26.
(What will happen?)
- Say as many as possible!
-  It didn't burst!
(Only five numbers are left.)
- Say as many as you can.
-  27, 28, 29.
(It popped!)
(The balloon burst!)
28, 29.
(We won!)
- We did it.
-  We won!
We did it!
(Too bad)
Our guest won.
You're so unlucky!
I've never won something like this.
It's a good thing, right?
- Of course, it's a good thing.
-  You won.
(The whole team is happy.)
(Staff picked the number 28.)
- Say as many as you can.
-  27, 28, 29.
(It popped!)
(He's happy to be covered in flour.)
(They're sad that they weren't covered in flour.)
Too bad.
It's all thanks to Gary.
Hyun Soo, you're so unlucky.
- What's this?
-  I can't believe it.
(Gary and Hyun Soo are out.)
We're in trouble. What should we do?
We have four left.
Team Kwang Soo is amazing.
- Of course!
-  Yes!
No one can be unluckier than Kwang Soo.
The whole team is benefiting from his bad luck.
I didn't know we would ever play this kind of game.
His bad luck is beyond imagination.
(Today, the unluckiest is the luckiest.)
(Unlucky)
(Round 2: Team Battle)
Now, it's a team battle.
The winning team doesn't have to eliminate anyone.
- One person for second in place.
-  One needs to be eliminated.
For the third in place, three people need to be eliminated.
If Team Seok Jin eliminates two people,
- you'll be near to losing.
-  We'll only have one person left.
That's right. We will invite three people from each team.
- Please come forward.
-  Okay.
Three people, please step forward.
- Let's go.
-  We can do it.
- Okay, we can do it.
-  Three people, please step forward.
- We need to be in first place.
-  I'll go first.
- Let's go.
-  Lizzie, you go.
- We need to be in first place.
-  We just need the first place.
We used to do this often. There are nine wooden sticks.
- I believe in you, Kwang Soo.
-  You're out if it breaks.
- You're out if it breaks.
-  Yes.
Ji Hyo, which one will you choose?
- The one that doesn't break, right?
-  Yes.
This is very confusing.
- I'll choose the last one.
-  Okay.
- Please hold onto it.
-  The one that doesn't break?
Next.
The fourth one from the left.
- I'm not sure about that.
-  One that doesn't break.
- It's this one, right?
-  Yes.
- The one that doesn't break.
-  The stick that doesn't break.
I'll choose the second one from the back.
Okay.
- The unluckiest person...
-  All three of ours could break.
-  Yes, all could break.
The unluckiest comedian.
- The unluckiest.
-  Yes.
- The second one from the back.
-  Okay.
- Please don't touch.
-  Lee Wan?
(Even Lee Wan is serious.)
- The one on the far left.
-  This one?
- It looks highly breakable.
-  Here you go.
The second one on the left.
- Okay.
-  Yes.
I think all three won't break.
- The white one.
-  This looks breakable.
- Will it?
-  The white one?
I'll go with the one on the right.
- This one?
-  No, the other one.
-  Yes.
- Here you go.
-  I have no choice?
No.
We'll go at the same time.
- Everyone.
-  You can do it.
- Kwang Soo, do you want to switch?
-  I think this might break.
- One.
-  I'm scared.
Let's stand wide apart.
This is making me nervous.
If it hurts you, you pass.
I want to be hurt.
- What's that?
-  Please hurt me.
- Please.
-  I want to bleed from my head.
- Hurt me.
-  Let's go.
Why is Lee Wan here?
- Why is he here?
-  Why?
Why is Lee Wan here?
- We'll go at the same time.
-  It is worth enduring.
- One.
-  It'd hurt.
(One)
Two.
(Two)
Three.
(The moment of fate)
(Smashing)
(The sound of wooden sticks breaking resonates.)
(Ji Hyo, Seok Jin and Jung A chose the broken wooden sticks.)
- What is this?
-  I'm alive.
(Team Kwang Soo all survived.)
What is this?
- All of our members made it.
-  We all survived.
- They chose the wrong ones.
-  I was really scared.
Look at them.
That team is awesome.
- How could they all live?
-  That's awesome.
- Did they all survive?
-  They all survived.
- Really?
-  That's amazing.
- I thought mine would break.
-  Wax is our only hope.
- Really.
-  Oh, no.
- She is very unlucky.
-  She's unlucky.
The remaining six will move on.
(The 6 that survived will move on to the next game.)
- They're amazing.
-  Team Kwang Soo.
- I didn't even have a choice.
-  No one is out.
- It's amazing.
-  Oh, my goodness.
(Unlucky)
It's the second round.
Lee Wan is the only survivor of our team.
He's quite unlucky.
- You never know.
-  Yes, you never know.
There is a sword in each sheathe. If you draw a sword,
there will be something embarrassing inside.
- So you win if it's embarrassing?
-  Yes.
(You need to pick 1 of the 3 swords which is embarrassing.)
(The last survivor, Wax chooses one.)
- Hold onto it.
-  Okay.
- Lee Wan?
-  Be unlucky.
(Be unlucky.)
- I'm blessing him.
-  That's right.
- He needs to be unlucky.
- He needs to be unlucky here.
-  Yes, that's right.
- You need to be unlucky.
-  It's not a bad thing to say here.
Lee Wan, you're unlucky.
Chang Hie, you're lucky.
- It's bad to say one's lucky.
-  Chang Hie, you're lucky.
And Lizzy?
Lizzy will be lucky.
- Now.
-  I think this is a good one.
- Wax, you'll be very unlucky.
-  Now.
Starting with Wax, say, "You, take my sword."
- "You, take my sword."
-  She'll be unlucky.
- We'll go in order.
-  Okay.
You, take my sword.
(There's nothing inside.)
Take my sword.
(Flying)
- Look on the floor.
-  Oh, my.
(A leek flew out.)
- Wax.
-  The unluckiest person.
(She passed by drawing a leek.)
(Slapping)
(That was unexpected.)
- You're number one.
-  Aren't I unlucky?
- I'm unlucky.
-  You really are unlucky.
(I was hit by a leek, shouldn't I win by default?)
(Go, Wax.)
She is truly unlucky.
- She's truly unlucky.
-  Really.
You're a strong candidate to win.
- How did that get him?
-  You're right.
Wan is very unlucky.
He could have caught the leek with his mouth.
Wan, this is a great fit for a historical drama.
- Your hair, too.
-  You're acting.
- Right.
-  He looks lucky.
(You...)
Take my sword.
(You, take my sword.)
(It's a sword.)
- Oh, no.
-  He picked a sword.
Oh, no.
(It looked like a scene from a historical drama.)
(A perfect sword came out like a scene from a historical drama.)
It would have been great if a leek came out.
Really.
A stem of a garlic should have come out.
- He is really unlucky.
-  It's a pity.
You look like you're really disappointed.
I got hit with a leek.
Wan looks disappointed.
He drew a sword, and he's disappointed.
This makes you competitive.
- He wanted to go to the next round.
-  Yes.
Our team can't all lose.
In Donnie Yen style.
Donnie Yen style.
- Donnie Yen style.
-  He looks exactly like him.
He looks exactly like him.
You, take my sword.
(It's a normal sword.)
Oh, no.
- Then two of us will pass.
-  Oh, my.
What is that?
(Then 2 of Team Kwang Soo will automatically pass.)
- Two of us will live.
-  Two of us.
- They are very unlucky.
-  This scares me.
There are three unlucky ones?
- You, take my sword.
-  You, take my sword.
(Screaming)
- Take my sword.
-  Take my sword.
(Lizzie drew a snake.)
(Kwang Soo drew an octopus arm.)
I'm getting goosebumps.
What is that?
You're really amazing.
- Really.
-  You're really amazing.
You...
- You're really unlucky.
-  He's really unlucky.
- Really.
-  He's amazing.
- He's amazing.
-  I was going to pick that.
But I switched at the last minute.
This is scary.
- He really unlucky.
-  He's amazing.
Our team has lost.
(Wax versus Kwang Soo and Lizzy)
How could this happen?
You can do it.
- Let's win this round.
-  Okay.
- Next.
-  You're unlucky.
- Now.
-  Let's win this.
Up against Kwang Soo is the rising star,
- Wax.
-  She is very unlucky.
- I didn't even imagine.
-  She is truly unlucky.
There are 2 raw eggs among the 3 eggs.
Okay. Kwang Soo is known to pick raw eggs.
Kwang Soo, Lizzy and Wax please come forward.
Go, Wax.
- Will it be one of them?
-  I'm here thanks to you.
(There is only 1 raw egg among 20 eggs.)
- It always goes to Kwang Soo.
-  Kwang Soo picks the one.
(The first one picked was the raw egg.)
(Oh, my goodness.)
What's that?
He can't pick it again.
- It'll be amazing.
-  Then he is definitely unlucky.
(The second one he picks again is raw.)
- It'll be amazing.
-  Then he is definitely unlucky.
(Smashing)
Oh, my.
How could you be so unlucky?
No, that means he's lucky.
(Raw eggs were the beginning of Kwang Soo's unlucky path.)
There are two raw eggs.
Lizzy, please pick first.
- I'll...
-  Wait.
Okay, it's better that you go first.
- She isn't unlucky.
-  Next.
- Kwang Soo.
-  Please go first.
Don't pick, Wax. Kwang Soo is unlucky.
- You shouldn't pick that.
-  He's right.
- Why are you trembling?
-  I'm nervous.
- You can do it.
-  Kwang Soo has no choice.
- He's afraid.
-  Yes.
- Why are you trembling?
-  Wax.
- Don't pressure yourself.
-  I feel burdened to win.
- You shouldn't.
-  Okay.
Just be yourself.
- Okay.
-  Kwang Soo, you look very calm.
Eggs are my friend.
Raw eggs.
We say that even the boiled eggs become raw eggs...
- when Kwang Soo picks them.
-  They turn into raw eggs.
It's a miracle.
Crack it hard on your head.
Okay, 1, 2...
(Two)
Three.
(Smashing)
(Wax picked a raw egg.)
Wax.
(Lizzy picked a boiled egg.)
(Kwang Soo obviously picked the raw egg.)
- It's Kwang Soo.
-  He's amazing.
(He's amazing.)
It didn't break.
(He is always the unluckiest.)
(Goosebumps)
Wax is amazing.
Wax and Kwang Soo are both amazing.
(Wax and Kwang Soo are the top two unluckiest.)
- Oh, my.
-  Really.
- Let's win.
-  It's getting heated.
- He doesn't look happy.
-  This is so funny.
The atmosphere is heating up.
- How could this happen?
-  Really...
The unluckiest...
Myung Ho is very happy.
Why?
He has recovered from his illness.
He has fully recovered.
You are witnessing the miracle of a full recovery.
Let's give a round of applause for the two that made...
Myung Ho leap up from his chair.
(This is the spirit of The Unluckiest Festival.)
You are amazing.
This is fun.
- I respect you, Wax.
-  Wax, you are amazing.
- This is...
-  Kwang Soo is amazing, too.
- Kwang Soo is amazing.
-  They even live in the same flat.
- They're neighbours?
-  We're neighbours.
- They're amazing.
-  Don't touch, you'll get unlucky.
(This is the last match between the two.)
- Now, you two are left.
-  They'll shoot against each other.
Kwang Soo is known to be a champion in this area.
- Of course.
-  He is truly one of the unluckiest.
Even his name sounds like the word "unlucky".
- He is truly...
-  My name, too?
He already has a reputation for being unlucky.
- Right.
-  But a new, strong candidate,
Wax, has appeared.
- I never expected that.
-  Me neither.
This is the first time I'm this happy for being unlucky.
I know.
This is the exact intention of this special.
Being unlucky could make you happy.
- That's right.
-  Yes.
Kwang Soo, many people are envious of you.
I feel that you are afraid of yourself.
I never thought I was this unlucky.
I really didn't.
- I didn't know.
-  Really.
- He is very unlucky.
-  Yes.
Really. Please choose one.
(Final Team Round: Unlucky Inkgun)
- The second one.
-  You chose the second one.
- Good.
-  He chose the second one?
(One of them has ink inside.)
One has ink inside, while the other has water in it.
I see.
- If you get ink on your face...
-  Good.
The one who gets ink on his or her face will win.
- Go!
-  Gosh.
- It makes me nervous.
-  You win if you're shot with ink.
- One!
-  Wax, way to go!
Two!
(Two)
Three!
(Three)
(My goodness.)
(Kwang Soo's face is covered with ink.)
(Kwang Soo's team wins in this round.)
What is this?
- Gosh.
-  So he chose the right one.
Kwang Soo doesn't look happy.
- This is scary.
-  I thought his gun was empty.
- It is scary.
-  This is scary.
- I even got goosebumps.
-  Gosh.
- It is so scary.
-  Right.
So Kwang Soo's team won!
(Kwang Soo did a great job, and his team won in this round!)
- You have to be on the right team.
-  Right.
- Gosh.
-  I couldn't believe it.
(Poor me)
(Ji Hyo, Lee Wan and Chang Hie are out.)
I think Kwang Soo is amazing.
- He is.
-  Right.
We've known that he is amazing for a long time.
It's time for Jin Ho to play his role.
- Yes!
-  What can I do for you?
"What can I do for you?"
(Is it my turn now?)
(During break time a while ago)
This is a banana-flavoured chocolate pie.
(Members are taking a short break while eating snacks.)
We should eat now.
Is this a new product?
(One guy seems to be obsessed with snacks.)
I've never tried this banana-flavoured one.
He is serious.
(He is getting energy from sweet snacks.)
- "What can I do for you?"
-  I was about to go home.
- No, just sit there.
-  Really?
(Just sit there.)
Is that what he has to do?
Just sit there.
We will play games.
- Leaders, please come out.
-  Okay.
- The leaders.
-  I'm nervous.
- Kwang Soo is so cool.
-  He is too strong.
- I trust you.
-  He is strong.
I can never beat Kwang Soo.
We three will drink beverages.
- The one who drinks bitter one...
-  Really?
can recruit Jin Ho as your member.
- Wow, really?
-  That's nice.
- Kwang Soo, you can do it!
-  He'll win.
Let's go.
This looks tasty.
- Good.
-  I'll drink this one.
- Right.
-  You chose what looks tasty.
- Okay.
-  Good.
- I chose this one.
-  This looks...
- This looks...
-  Let's drink.
This looks tasty.
One, two...
(One of them is herbal medicine.)
(Which unlucky guy will be able to recruit Jin Ho?)
Two, three.
You can do it, Jae Seok.
(Gulping)
- Gosh, is this true?
-  No way.
- Please, stop.
-  Really?
(No way. Stop fooling us.)
(He is not lying.)
- Gosh.
-  Really?
- No way.
-  Is this really happening?
(He can't pretend because the herbal medicine is too bitter.)
- My goodness.
-  Is yours herbal medicine?
- Oh, my.
-  Really?
- Spit it out.
-  He drank coffee...
- and mine is grape juice.
-  Spit it out!
Amazing! Lee Kwang Soo!
(Amazing Kwang Soo chose the herbal medicine.)
- What is this?
-  It's unbelievable.
- Wow.
-  How can this happen?
- My goodness.
-  You're scary now.
- You're so scary now.
-  This is so bitter.
- It is really bitter.
-  We chose...
the beverages with different colours intentionally.
You did intentionally?
(Scary)
- Kwang Soo, you're amazing.
-  No one can beat him ever.
- No one can defeat him.
-  Right.
Jin Ho, good for you.
- Great.
-  Finally.
- Kwang Soo.
-  You're in our team now.
- Good.
-  You're in our team.
There are six members in his team.
- Unbelievable.
-  Gosh.
- I don't think we can win.
-  How can this be possible?
- He must be very unlucky.
-  Right.
- If you lose at last...
-  Yes.
after winning in a row like this, it means you're super unlucky.
- Right.
-  That is the worst.
- Gosh.
-  If you lose at last...
(Will Kwang Soo be able to become the super unlucky guy?)
It was close.
It was close, right?
(Seok Jin won against Jae Seok.)
- I did good.
-  I am sure he can't win this time.
All right.
- Let's do rock-paper-scissors.
-  Okay.
- Rock, paper, scissors.
-  Rock, paper, scissors.
(The one who chooses wasabi pie wins.)
His bad luck has come.
Now I feel his bad luck.
- Jae Seok lost...
-  I know how unlucky you can be...
- You know...
-  He started losing.
once I start losing, I can be unlucky the whole day.
- Right.
-  Yes.
- Don't let your guard down.
-  I am very unlucky, too.
- You should try your best.
-  You know how unlucky I can be.
- Jae Seok.
-  Jae Seok can be very unlucky.
Good luck.
- Jae Seok.
-  Gosh.
That's like a curse to say now.
Go for it, Jae Seok!
- Yu Jae Seok!
-  Yu Jae Seok!
-  You can do it!
- Good luck!
-  Go for it, Jae Seok.
Kwang Soo is very good at this.
(Kwang Soo is setting another record of how unlucky he can get.)
(Jae Seok is another who has experienced much bad luck.)
That would really mean unlucky.
- It's fun.
-  Please.
One has banana cream inside and the other one...
Gosh.
(What is this?)
Kwang Soo got it!
- It's incredible.
-  Kwang Soo!
- Gosh.
-  It's unbelievable.
- Oh, my.
-  Spit it out.
Kwang Soo, don't swallow that. Spit that out.
My goodness.
(He can't swallow the wasabi pie.)
(Even the staff who prepared the pie are amazed.)
(This probability is 0.15 percent.)
- My goodness.
-  Gosh.
You don't have to eat it.
- Okay?
-  Spit it out.
How can you never lose?
- Is this really possible?
-  Spit it out.
- How can this happen?
-  It looks tasty.
- Things aren't going right today.
-  He's too strong.
Kwang Soo wins every game.
Kwang Soo won!
- Yes!
-  There are six including Kwang Soo.
- Now...
-  Gosh.
My team is out!
- Are you okay?
-  We did nothing today.
- We were too lucky today.
-  Right.
- This is really frustrating.
-  Are you all out?
I am sorry. I am lucky today.
- Please give him water.
-  You're so unlucky.
I should've let handsome Lee Wan sit in front of me.
My goodness.
- Wow.
-  Can this really happen?
- He is the unluckiest guy.
-  There must be something to him.
I and Kwang Soo have become a little close.
I think I should keep a distance from him.
(Why am I so unlucky?)
(Jong Kook, Jae Seok and Jung A are out.)
- Now it's time for the final round.
-  Okay.
Team Seok Jin has two surviving members.
To win, you should beat all five in Team Kwang Soo.
We can do it!
We have numbers from 1 to 9.
Wax, please choose one.
- I am nervous.
-  Five.
- She chose 5.
-  Number 5.
It's ink cushion.
Please choose the opponent player, Wax.
What about Jin Ho? He is not that unlucky.
Jin Ho hasn't done anything so far.
- What if he loses right away?
-  I want to play, too.
- Jin Ho.
-  I'll choose Jin Ho.
Good. Go, Jin Ho!
Jin Ho now plays his first game.
(Here comes Jin Ho, who has always been in the second place.)
- You can do it!
-  Good.
Jin Ho isn't exactly a lucky person.
- Actually, it depends.
-  All right.
Jin Ho somehow survived.
He could've just gone home.
- They even gave him taxi fare.
-  Bad luck is good luck here.
- Do they put it on their faces?
-  One of them is ink cushion.
Please bury your faces in them.
She has to choose the ink cushion in order to win.
- If I have a choice,
-  Yes.
- I want this one in front of me.
-  This one? Okay.
- I want the same one.
-  Decide by rock-paper-scissors.
- Rock-paper-scissors.
-  Rock-paper-scissors.
Rock-paper-scissors!
(Increased tension)
- Wax chose the first one.
-  Oh, please.
(Wax chose the first one.)
(Careful)
- Hold it still.
-  Hold it with your hands.
Right. And...
Be brave and bury your face in it.
- Bury your faces at once.
-  I'm scared.
- You can do it!
-  Go for it!
- One, two...
-  It's your first try.
You can't lose here.
- One, two, three!
-  Go!
Rub them on your face.
- Wax.
-  No!
(Look at Wax's face)
- Wax won.
-  Praise her.
(Praise this unlucky lady!)
- Jin Ho lost.
-  Is it on my face?
Is the ink on my face?
- Gosh.
-  No way!
I only just joined the game.
Jin Ho is out.
- Go and sit there.
-  Gosh.
- Could she recognise it?
-  You're incredible.
I should have gone home earlier.
(Jin Ho is very unlucky in another way, too.)
- Wax is strong, too.
-  Who is next?
Which number will you pick?
- I think she will beat them all.
-  Three.
- Three? Good.
-  You can do it!
Lighting up the lighter.
- Who...
-  Who do you want to play with?
- I want Mikey.
-  Mikey!
- Good.
-  Beat one by one.
I win if mine doesn't work, right?
- Right.
-  All right.
You will win if your lighter doesn't work.
- I want the second one.
-  The second one. Wait.
- Then, I'll choose the first one.
-  Okay.
- Does it have to work to win?
-  No, it shouldn't work.
Why don't you understand the rule?
You win when things go wrong.
- Now I got it.
-  I won't look at my lighter.
Will Wax be able to win again?
One, two, three!
(Will Wax win again? Or will Mikey become a new hero?)
(Everyone is nervous.)
Three!
(Wax lost and Mikey won.)
(Mikey from Kwang Soo's team won!)
- You did great!
-  We made it!
(It's hard to defeat Kwang Soo's team.)
(It's good to be here!)
- Good.
-  Great job.
I must be very unlucky.
- Mikey is so unlucky.
-  Right, he is.
- Mikey, choose one number.
-  My goodness.
- Number 6.
-  Yes, number 6!
- Six!
-  Whipped cream.
- It's whipped cream.
-  Seok Jin.
- If Seok Jin loses here...
-  If I lose,
- I will admit my defeat.
-  You know we have many players.
If Seok Jin loses here, Kwang Soo's team will win.
- Right.
-  Then...
we will find the first unluckiest person from Kwang Soo's team.
You will draw a number now.
Then you should spin the roulette as many times as the number you get.
- Okay.
-  Good?
Okay. The same number.
If you pick the same number, the cream will fly to your face.
Yes. And you pass.
- You pass when you get the cream.
-  Please pick a card.
So it's good to get hit by the cream.
- That's right.
-  Right.
- Please reveal your number.
-  It's one.
- You get to turn it just once.
-  Oh, no!
- What?
-  Is that good?
- It's okay.
-  Who?
- Just once.
-  Five.
- You can turn it five times.
-  He did it.
- He did it.
-  If I get it, it will prove that...
Prove that you are really unlucky.
All right. Please stick your face out a little more.
- Great.
-  I have to turn it five times.
Five times.
The chances are too low.
There you go.
- One, two...
-  One, two...
Three.
(Flinching)
Four.
(He could get it once.)
(Will he get it?)
- Oh no.
-  Gosh...
(Both teams are safe until 6 turns.)
- Oh dear.
-  Just turn it once.
- This is crazy.
-  Stick out your face.
- One.
-  If I lose...
- That's it.
-  If I lose, it means I'm unlucky.
Seok Jin is next.
- You are innocent.
-  You are counting, right?
(It's a good thing to get cream on his face.)
- Two.
-  It's coming.
(They can't help frowning their faces.)
- Three.
-  It's coming.
- Four.
-  It's here.
(The misfortune always comes unannounced.)
(The crew chose the number 27.)
(He gets slapped with cream.)
(Slapping)
(He's happy.)
(Our leader is so unlucky!)
- Bravo!
-  Seok Jin passes!
(They are sad.)
We are going up.
- Bravo.
-  Good job.
- I'll go with number 4.
-  Number 4!
- It's ripping plastic wrap.
-  It's ripping plastic wrap.
Get set. Go!
(Seok Jin chooses a strong one and fails.)
(Their jaws drop.)
The winner is Seok Jin!
- The winner is Seok Jin!
-  Yes!
Seok Jin succeeded.
I choose number two.
It's picking farting cushion.
Can't they just fart if they think they will lose?
- You can do that.
-  Right?
- You will win then.
-  Then it will sound the same.
Three.
(Seok Jin's cushion farts.)
(Farting is Seok Jin's specialty. Seok Jin wins!)
- Yes!
-  Nice!
Is he winning?
Seok Jin goes to the finals!
(Seok Jin wins three rounds and goes to the finals.)
- Yes!
-  Yes!
You are the best!
(He proves to everyone how unlucky he is.)
Seok Jin is not an easy opponent.
He's unbelievable.
- He's no easy opponent.
-  All right.
- He's really unlucky.
-  He is.
(Now only Kwang Soo and Seok Jin are surviving.)
Now, it's the competition of the kings.
It's the competition of the century.
I think we've been wasting time.
After all, these two are going to compete.
They could've competed from the start.
(They should've competed from the start.)
You've confirmed it.
Many people came out here in the early morning...
and worked hard. But it was all for nothing.
But at least now we know that we are not so unlucky.
- Yes.
-  We are happy.
- We are happy.
-  Really.
- Everybody,
-  Yes.
we invited you here because you seemed to be unlucky.
- But you are lucky after all.
-  Yes.
After playing those games,
we must realise how lucky we are.
- Yes.
-  We are happy.
- Of course.
-  Realising that is the purpose.
- You just need to realise that.
-  Yes.
The unluckiest person would be the one who doesn't fall into the mud.
If one of these two...
doesn't fall into the mud,
then that person...
is really unlucky.
- That would be tragic.
-  We have to win.
Since you came this far, you have to win.
The person who doesn't win is the unluckiest person.
You are right.
- Finally, it's the final game.
-  Oh dear.
They will play rock-paper-scissors and choose the chair to sit in.
- Rock-paper-scissors.
-  Scissors.
(Seok Jin wins.)
That's luck, too.
- Seok Jin.
-  Did he win?
- I will follow my gut feeling.
-  Okay.
- Winning is being unlucky.
-  Yes.
- Please go to your position.
-  I chose this.
- Me, too.
-  Me, too.
- I chose this.
-  I chose this, too.
- I chose that.
-  We chose this, too.
- Is it muddy water?
-  Is it cold?
- Kwang Soo is ready to dive.
-  It's Kwang Soo.
I trust Kwang Soo.
I want to win now!
- Okay!
-  Let's go!
Who will be the first unluckiest man?
(It's the match of the century.)
We will soon know who he is.
I am scared.
Why is this making us nervous? This is crazy.
It's really nerve-racking.
Please give it up for the two contenders!
(The unlucky guests passionately root for them.)
Come on!
Let's go!
(The countdown starts.)
One!
(Is it going to be Seok Jin who's writing a new legend?)
Two!
(Or is it going to be Kwang Soo who reached the spiritual realm?)
(It was the viewers' most frequently asked question.)
Three!
(Who is the unluckiest member?)
(Who will be the unluckiest man?)
Three!
(Seok Jin's chair breaks.)
(Seok Jin falls to the muddy water.)
(It's Seok Jin.)
I love you!
(Oh my gosh.)
- Yes!
-  I love you!
(The first Unluckiest Man is Jee Seok Jin.)
All right!
Seok Jin is the first Unluckiest Man!
- This is crazy.
-  He's soaked.
- Kwang Soo, you're unluckier.
-  This is crazy.
- He's really unlucky.
-  Yes.
-  It's Kwang Soo who's unlucky.
- He was so close.
-  He was almost there.
(Do you think you are unlucky?)
(Don't worry. Kwang Soo is there for you.)
(He smiles.)
Many people agreed to come out...
even though we called them announced.
We prepared them some gifts.
- Really?
-  Yes.
-  It looks nice.
- What are these?
-  They look nice.
They look very nice.
I am sorry, but that looks better than this.
(Seok Jin wants to switch.)
(Seok Jin wants to take the souvenir instead.)
It really does.
You should leave now.
- Move up.
-  Take your trophy and leave.
Gosh, they look nicer.
Can't we do this again next week?
This is really fun.
The first Unluckiest Man is...
Jee Seok Jin! We will see you next week!
(The first Unluckiest Man is Jee Seok Jin.)
Go, Seok Jin!
(One man who is like spring approaches Ji Hyo.)
Oh, gosh! I can't believe it.
(She finally meets Bo Gum.)
- I would love that.
-  I would love that, too.
Can you take me to the shoot?
(It's every man's crush, Seolhyun.)
This is driving me crazy.
(She asks him to do her a favour.)
Gary.
I want to keep this fantasy.
It's nice to meet you!
You want me to shave my beard.
You are a gangster, aren't you?
I can't do that!
- This is awesome.
-  Oh dear.
- Is this awesome?
-  Yes.
This is unbelievable.
I love it.
(Next week, Strange Spring Outing special is coming up.)
(Running Man)