(Previously on Running Man)
(Will you be together or apart?)
(Their decisions resulted in terrifying outcomes.)
(This nerve-wracking challenge depends on probability.)
(Will the probability take them to somewhere nice or bad?)
It's Probability Race. This game can get you 50R coins.
We are at Nambu Market which is a famous place in Jeonju.
(The mission in the market will be "Find the Consonants".)
We took each consonant from the name of the market. You must...
buy 5 things with the consonants. You must use at least 2 of them.
(They must buy 5 things, but 2 of the consonants must be used.)
- What are those? - We need to wear them?
You will wear one of them and start your mission.
The thread of the clothes will be unraveled.
That's how far we'll be able to go.
Yes, the distant you will travel will be limited.
- We can't go far. - That sounds fun.
- This time... - We need to split.
- We should be apart. - Of course.
- This makes sense. - We can't do anything about this.
- That's right. - Why don't we start?
I'll go first this time.
- Kwang Soo, which one do you want? - I want the third one.
Okay.
I can already feel the misfortune.
Two, three, four, five...
- Please, be large. - Get the small one.
- Get the small one. - Be the small one.
(What will unfortunate Kwang Soo face this time?)
(What a surprise. He gets the costume in large.)
Yes!
But this isn't all that great.
- It is. - He can go far.
Going far is better.
- Can you go back to your place? - Move, Kwang Soo.
- Can a man celebrate? - Move.
- Go back to your spot. - Why would you celebrate?
- Let me celebrate. - You don't need to.
It's not necessary.
- What number was Kwang Soo? - Three.
- Okay, I choose number one. - Okay.
(There's less chance to get a large. It'd be good to draw a medium.)
Small, small, small.
Small.
- Small. - Small.
(I knew it.)
This is so strange.
(The unlucky guys approve of Jae Seok's bad luck.)
Only one of the three of us gets to be lucky.
That's right. Only one of us can make it.
- Only one of us can be lucky. - Just one.
- Okay. - I'll break the jinx.
I choose number two.
(It's time for Seok Jin to draw.)
Please be large.
(Unlucky Seok Jin has been quite fortunate today.)
- Okay. - He got the large one.
(Seok Jin gets large.)
- You just get a longer distance. - It's not that big of a deal.
(He only gets lucky with things that aren't very important.)
It'll take that much more time to come back.
I'm going next. I choose number four.
Number four?
(It's time for Jong Kook to draw.)
- He got the small one. - That means we get the medium ones.
(Jong Kook gets medium.)
Regardless of the size,
I wouldn't be able bear the sight of Jong Kook wearing it.
(Jong Kook in a bikini will be an eyesore.)
Imagine him dressed in that.
Automatically, Ji Hyo and Haha will get the costumes in medium.
Gosh.
(Size of the costume and the amount of cash in possession.)
I only have five dollars. They can do whatever they want.
Will you even be able to do the mission with five dollars?
I'm going to take my time and look around on my way out.
He's so cheeky. Gosh.
(Jae Seok is carefree with his 150 dollars.)
Gosh, he makes me mad.
(What can I buy with 100 dollars?)
(The threads are tied to a pole.)
Please tie the threads.
Ready, set, go!
(The mission begins.)
- It unravels so fast. - It does.
- Look at this. - We're in trouble.
It's unraveling.
Even with the costume in large, this is going to be hard.
(The moment the thread breaks, you're out.)
- Hold on. - This isn't looking good.
(Will they be able to cover the area with those costumes?)
It's almost gone now.
The thread is...
(It's tight already.)
This isn't going to work. Hold on.
I don't have much left. I can't go any further.
Jae Seok. Jae Seok.
What?
(Whose thread is that?)
- Whose is that? - That's mine. Hey!
Wait. That's mine. Hey!
(Seok Jin has a mishap while shopping.)
What are you doing with my thread?
(Wait, this isn't mine.)
Ma'am, do you have mushrooms?
How much is this?
All of it?
Can I get just one of them?
How much is that?
- You want three of these? - Yes.
- I can't charge you for three. - You have to take my money.
- Should I put them in there? - Yes.
I'm sorry. Thank you, Ma'am.
Thank you. I got mushrooms.
(She purchases 3 mushrooms.)
- Mushroom. - It's over there.
(Jae Seok has 150 dollars.)
Where are they?
I can't go further than the thread allows me.
(He's got the money, but not the thread.)
If the thread breaks, it's game over.
I can't go further than the thread allows me.
- How much are they? - A dollar for three.
- A dollar? - I'll get them for you.
Thank you.
I can't go any further without the thread.
(A kind person buys the mushrooms for him.)
Thank you.
Thank you very much. Goodbye.
Come look over here.
I can't go any further.
(The threads are getting tighter.)
(Jong Kook's costume is almost gone now.)
Did you say two dollars?
If the thread breaks, it's game over.
I can work with this.
Where's the shop keeper?
Hello. I did it.
What? Oh, right, the change.
Thank you.
I did it. Let's go.
(Jong Kook purchases Korean socks.)
(Meanwhile, Seok Jin only has 5 dollars to spend.)
There are pants here.
How much are the cheapest pair of pants?
Five dollars.
The cheapest one is five dollars?
(The cheapest one costs his entire saving.)
There's sujebi. Do you have sujebi on the menu?
You do? How much is it?
- It's 6 dollars. - Did you say 6 dollars?
(The price has gone up at the market.)
Sujebi is six dollars.
Do you have Korean socks?
(Kwang Soo has a big costume, but not a lot of money.)
Hello.
Do you have soju?
This is distilled soju.
Okay. Can you...
- But it's already been opened. - That's okay.
I have to pay for this.
Thank you.
(What a frugal celebrity.)
Needle.
Hello. Do you have needles?
(He goes to a props store to ask for a needle.)
Thank you. How much is it?
For a single needle?
- Yes. - I'll take a dollar.
Thank you.
(He's a celebrity who deals in used items.)
Thank you very much.
(Kwang Soo purchases soju and a needle.)
I got two items.
What's next?
(Let me take a look in your basket.)
What have you got in there?
What's in there, Seok Jin? Let me take a look.
Do you want to exchange things?
Okay. What do you have?
- Copying paper? Pants? - Soju.
- Pants. - We should buy pants.
I gave you too many hints.
Aren't you the father of the twins?
(Aren't you the father of the twins?)
(Aren't you Lee Hwi Jae, the comedian?)
I'm not Lee Hwi Jae.
I'm not him.
Is there a stationery store around here?
Where's the stationery store?
- There are so many things here. - Five minutes remaining.
There are five minutes remaining for the mission.
- I need to get one more thing. - Okay.
(Haha bought mushroom, octopus, pot, and Korean socks.)
Thank you.
It's two dollars? I'll have one of these.
I'll have the box.
This is nice.
(Haha finished purchasing and is on his way back.)
I have to get there quickly.
(What's this?)
It won't untangle.
I finished the mission.
(He's stopped by the tangled threads.)
This might break.
Hold on.
I have to go, but it won't untangle.
It worked. Where do I go?
(It was close, but he's back after purchasing 5 items.)
I did it.
Thank you very much.
I got them all.
(Jae Seok is on his way back.)
Hello.
Oh, no.
(The thread breaks.)
Kwon Ryeol...
Mission failed.
Kwon Ryeol stepped on it.
This isn't fair. He stepped on it.
Kwon Ryeol stepped on the thread.
I'm sorry, but you have failed the mission.
I said Kwon Ryeol stepped on it.
(You're supposed to tape me, not step on my thread.)
Hey!
He stepped on it.
(He's sorry and embarrassed.)
Gosh, Kwon Ryeol.
What's wrong with you?
I know this is your money, but how could you do this?
(Kwon Ryeol ruined an almost successful mission.)
Follow me for now.
Kwon Ryeol, you...
(Laughing)
(Is this funny to you?)
("Find the Consonants" is over.)
(The result of Market Tour)
(Items purchased and the amount of R coins they have)
(Only Haha and Kwang Soo succeeded the mission.)
I'll inform you on the amount of R coins you currently have.
Jae Seok has 20R. He gets Jeonju Seasoned Laver Set.
Seok Jin has 10R. He gets Jeonju Handmade Paper Fan.
Jong Kook has 40R. He gets Crude Liquor Set.
Haha has 80R. He gets Tteokgalbi Set.
Ji Hyo has 30R. She gets Crude Liquor Set.
Kwang Soo has 90R. He gets Tteokgalbi Set.
If only I had 10R more.
- What did you say? - If only I had 10R more.
(If he had that, he could've gotten a laptop.)
(It's time to exchange the R coins for the prizes.)
We'll give you prizes according to the R coins you have.
Before that, there is one last choice to make.
- What is it? - Will you...
combine the R coins or will you be apart?
(Will you combine the R coins or will you be apart?)
We should combine our coins and go to Europe.
- We should combine them. - This is an obvious choice.
- We have to combine them. - I mean...
- We have to combine them. - There's no need to think.
(The poor want to combine the R coins.)
We have to go for the big prize.
What good will that be?
What am I supposed to do with this?
I'll buy you one.
You have to dream big.
Let me hit you on the forehead, then.
It'll be unfair without it.
I'll do Jong Kook. I'll give you 90R for that.
- Come on. - Just do it.
- I'll give you 90R. - Let him hit you.
I'll buy your forehead for 80R.
I'll top that with 10 more.
- What did you say? - I said 10R.
Haha said 80 and I said 90.
He has 10 more than me.
I'm saying that I have 90R and Haha has 80R.
- Fine. Let's do it. - Okay.
- Let's do this. - Give it to me.
I don't understand why I have to do this.
- I'm not doing it. - Come on.
What are you going to do with a Crude Liquor Set?
I don't want to do this. Why do I have to get hit?
I don't want to do this.
Why should I let you hit me?
Because of the way you're behaving.
(Don't you know why?)
That's why I want to hit you.
You always hit me.
I'm willing to pay 90R for a chance to hit you.
(Dazed)
- I have 40R. - We could go to LA with this.
- Which is why I'll give you 50R. - Calm down.
- Let's do this. - Let's combine the coins for now.
I can't promise anything.
(The winner gets a plane ticket to Europe.)
(A dud means everyone loses everything.)
Who'll spin the wheel?
- I will. I'm unlucky. - Okay.
- He won't win it for himself. - Okay, you spin.
He's unlucky.
If you get a dud, the crew will collect the prizes.
- I'll spin. - Okay.
On 1, 2, 3.
(Who's the one lucky person Kwang Soo will select?)
We all stand a chance.
(Will someone win a plane ticket? Or will they lose everything?)
It's me.
- It's me. - Haha!
(Really? Haha?)
(They thought the wheel stopped, but it's still moving.)
No, no!
(Stop! The next cell is a dud!)
(It landed on a dud.)
(No way.)
Wasn't it me?
Did you nudge the wheel?
(He's innocent.)
Sorry, Haha.
I didn't nudge it!
Calm down.
Let's try spinning the wheel again.
I really didn't nudge it!
(The dud brought out their best manners.)
I bet someone will win now.
Because it doesn't count.
- This is an unlucky day. - See?
Haha won.
(Oh dear.)
Gosh, Haha.
Good on you, Haha.
You almost won.
- I'm very impressed. - You almost won.
What a pity.
This isn't the end of it.
Head to the guest house and fight to win...
- your last chance. - Let's go.
We lost everything. Absolutely everything.
(Jeonju Tour Part 2)
(The Culture Institute is a great example of our culture.)
(There are yet more prizes on the table.)
- Look. - There are more prizes.
Is it not over yet?
We have nothing.
- They keep tossing us bait. - We really have nothing.
I had 90R.
You must be upset about losing everything.
- We are. - Pick whichever donut you want...
- and eat it. - Can we eat one?
- Are they filled with wasabi? - No.
Are you sure?
(We're suspicious.)
Can we eat them?
(But we'll eat.)
We're being sorted into teams.
(Let's eat when we can.)
(Jae Seok chose a chocolate donut.)
Eat a red one.
No, I prefer chocolate.
They're sorting us.
I don't want to be on his team.
(Grab)
(I'll avoid the tiger and join the chocolate team.)
(The tiger can go to the strawberry team.)
We'll begin the part two of the tour where you can...
make up for the prizes you lost.
You'll be split into two teams...
depending on the color of the donut you ate.
Really?
- See? - The unlucky guys unite.
(The Unlucky Trio unites)
I wanted a chocolate donut.
While eating my chocolate donut, I thought,
"How will I fare with these losers?"
But then I prefer them to you.
(Better the losers than the tiger)
Is that what you really thought?
I thought...
You are now in 2 teams of 3.
- The Unlucky Trio's back. - How did this happen?
Because you've all been unlucky today, the Jeonju Fairies...
are here to share some of their luck with you.
(Jeonju Fairies? Who are they?)
(Who is this huge welcome for?)
(Who are the fairies of luck who have come to help the members?)
(It's the hugely popular group Blackpink.)
(They topped the charts shortly after their debut.)
(They're as talented as they are beautiful.)
I can't believe I got to meet Blackpink.
They really are fairies.
- Welcome. - Hello, we're Blackpink.
- They look so chic. - They're awesome.
YG Entertainment cares about looks now.
It's "Playing with Fire"!
"Playing with Fire"!
("Playing with Fire" by Blackpink)
This is incredible.
I can't believe this.
(They light the whole of Jeonju with their chic looks.)
They look much better in real life.
I can't pick.
Look at them.
They look like dolls.
(She smiled at me.)
(Just looking at them washes away the unlucky feeling.)
They have the city look.
- They look so haughty. - No way.
- Look. - Look at them!
(Naive but brazen)
- They're so pretty! - Unbelievable.
Their faces are tiny.
(Our love is like playing with fire)
- Their faces... - This is incredible.
(They're lighting fires in these men's hearts.)
I can't take this anymore.
(We'll join you for the latter part of your tour.)
- That was great. - Well done.
(We love you so much.)
It's great to see you.
I'm a fan.
- Hello. - Hello.
They look so pretty.
They're amazing.
They look like celebrities.
More so than we do.
- Unbelievable. - Their faces...
They look like celebrities.
Instead of saying they're pretty...
Haha said they look chic.
- Their faces... - They look different.
Please welcome Blackpink!
(The Blackpink fairies will help them forget their misfortunes.)
- That was amazing. - That was great.
- This is crazy. - Okay, then.
Blackpink already split into Team Black and Team Pink.
- Really? - Already?
- Who's on Team Black? - Me.
- Okay. - Lisa and Ji Soo.
Jennie, you're with me.
Jennie, perfect. We got you and Rose.
- Hello. - This is perfect.
Well done.
Part two of the tour is a "Good out of Evil" mission...
where each team gets one more chance to win prizes.
- Great. - Everyone?
That sounds great.
After each game, both teams place a bet to win more R coins.
You can win from 2 times to 10 times more R coins.
- Let's go to Europe. - Let's do this.
- We can go. - It's possible.
If we win...
(He said Europe.)
Lisa, do you like Europe?
- Yes. - Do you?
Her reaction's so cute as well.
The winning team can bet twice...
and the losing team can bet once.
Each member of Blackpink will pick a lucky bag.
A bag contains 40R, 2 bags contain 20R and the other has nothing.
Oh no.
- It's okay. - Don't worry.
(They're new to this kind of game.)
I have a question.
- Are any of you really unlucky? - She is.
- She is. - Really?
- Is Lisa unlucky? - Why?
- You're on the right team. - Too bad.
- We're very experienced. - Join the club.
(Meet the rest.)
- Nice to meet you. - Say hello to your friend.
- We're all very unlucky. - You're on the right team.
Come forward and pick a lucky bag.
- Pick one. - Any of them will do.
Any bag will do.
It doesn't really matter.
- What if I picked the wrong one? - Is that the one in front of you?
- There's something inside. - Let's have a look.
- We'll start with Jennie. - Jennie.
On 1, 2, 3.
- How much? - 20R.
Well done.
- Next up is Rose. - Rose.
- Please, please, please. - Zero!
(Rose won 30R)
She won 30R!
That was incredible!
That was great.
Well done. Well done.
(They feel it. They feel the force of misfortune.)
20R and 0R.
Our team...
I'm not even surprised anymore.
- Team Pink starts off with 50R. - Okay.
Team Black starts off with 20R.
(Prizes: Plane ticket, laptop, tteokgalbi,)
(crude liquor, seasoned laver, paper fan)
(Jeonju Magistrate's office is 130 years old and equal to City Hall.)
Hello.
Sit over here, Ji Soo. And Lisa.
You can sit over there.
(It's like a bed of flowers.)
That will do.
We don't need these.
(He kicks out the unwelcome guests.)
What are you doing? What was that about?
- I'm filming with Blackpink. - Are you?
There are so many cameras.
Have you never been on a show with this many cameras before?
- There are so many. - Are there?
Rose, can you do the slate for us?
Rose, can you do the slate?
Say, "This is the slate. 1, 2, 3."
This is the slate. 1, 2, 3.
(Blackpink's first slate)
That was perfect.
Can you close the door?
(There's no more room.)
- Let's go to Europe. - Why did you close the door?
Not everyone's here yet.
You don't even have a cushion.
Where is it?
What's wrong with you?
What's his problem?
I don't have a problem.
You need to hurry up. Don't make the stars wait.
- Blackpink's really busy. - Why is the door closed?
(Everyone's present at last. What will the first game be?)
The first game is "5 Seconds Q and A".
- "5 Seconds Q and A". - What's that?
(Q and A session involving luck?)
A member from each team will sit facing each other wearing a helmet.
They will take turns asking each other a question.
You have to give 3 answers within 5 seconds to pass.
If you fail to ask a valid question or answer...
Remove 1 of the 3 sticks from the loser's helmet.
One of the three sticks will make water pour...
from the bottle.
(There is a 1 out of 3 chance of getting wet.)
I better not get picked.
- Gosh. - That's cute.
- What's that? - Goodness.
(Do you want us to wear this?)
We'll all get wet.
- Goodness. - The amount of water...
- There's too much water. - This is just...
- Only 1 out of 3 will spill water. - Yes.
Water will pour out as soon as we remove a stick.
- Our team... - Jae Seok is in that team.
- Seriously. - Our team's full of unlucky people.
- What am I going to do? - We're already lost.
- What should we do? - Lisa's at a disadvantage.
What about you two? Are you lucky?
- Are you lucky? - I am.
- Really? - She's really lucky.
- She's the lucky one. - I see.
Whenever she plays a game, she wins every time.
- Really? - If she wants something,
even when she's losing, she'll win in the end.
- Really? - She's amazing.
- Let's start the game. - Okay.
The team who wins three times first will be the winner.
- Three wins. - I see.
- You have to ask good questions. - It's not that hard.
You have to do well.
First player from each team, please come up.
(Who will be the first player from the unlucky team?)
Kwang Soo will go first.
- Why me first? - All right.
Kwang Soo, come on.
- What about your team? - It's Jong Kook.
- Who? - Me?
- Me? - Of course.
Go and crush him.
(Kwang Soo versus Jong Kook)
(Shut Jong Kook's mouth with difficult questions.)
I will do it.
- From the start? - Of course.
Crush him.
Three female celebrities you really want to date.
(Gosh.)
Song Hye Gyo, Kim Tae Hee... Gianna Jun.
(Time's over.)
(Kwang Soo gets a chance to remove a stick.)
Why can't I think of their names?
- Go right ahead. - Why couldn't I...
Why couldn't I think of any actresses' names?
Go right ahead.
(Kwang Soo fails.)
You should've picked the middle one.
He's right.
Name three four-character idioms you like.
Go-jin-gam-rae, jin-tae-yang-nan, and gyeol-cho-bo-eun!
(Kwang Soo is so smart.)
He's really focused today.
Name three female celebrities you dated.
(Gosh)
- One... - Gosh.
(How can you ask that question in public?)
- What? - Okay.
- Stop. - Oh, no.
- That was scary. - Are you mad?
- Goodness. - Are you crazy?
What? You could've named just anyone.
You can name anyone.
- Just anyone. - Can I?
- Yes, name anyone. - That's right.
- Pull it out. - Okay.
(If he doesn't succeed, he'll get asked another question.)
(He has a 50-50 chance. What's it going to be?)
(Kwang Soo fails again.)
- You're really unlucky. - What?
Seriously, you're unlucky.
It's getting really interesting. This is great.
(His eyes are burning with anger.)
- Wait. Don't look at me like that. - Okay.
- Be nice. - Okay.
(I'll finish you off with this one question.)
(With what question will Jong Kook attack?)
Name three actresses you worked with and dated.
(Name three actresses you worked with and dated.)
(Breaking news! Kwang Soo reveals his dating history!)
Kwang Soo.
(I wanted to keep it to my grave.)
It's okay. Those were just names. You just said some names.
Kwang Soo. You simply talked.
Kwang Soo. You just made them up.
- It was harmless. - I'm not sweating.
- What? - It meant nothing.
- What's wrong? - You just said some names.
- You just said some names. - You're good at this game.
- Kwang Soo, do it. - Go.
- Use your anger. - Do it.
Name three reasons why you like Yoon Eun Hye.
- She's pretty. She's rich. - One, two...
(Jong Kook is knocked out.)
- Get up! - You did it!
- You did it. - Why did you lose?
- Get up. - Pretty and rich.
- Goodness. - Because she's sexy.
- Because she's sexy. - You're so materialistic.
- Kwang Soo, pull it. - This is crazy.
(There's only one stick left.)
- It's pouring down. - Yes!
(Jong Kook's face gets showered with cold water.)
Lee Kwang Soo wins!
(Team Black is leading with 1 point.)
This game is hard.
We're good.
Hey, guys.
- Great! - Nice!
Next up is Ji Soo!
Oh, no.
Ji Soo! Ji Soo!
Okay.
(Ji Soo versus Rose)
- This... - Wait, Ji Soo. I'll do it for you.
- This... - Wait.
(He's showing off his manners.)
All three of us are trying to help her.
- Kwang Soo. - Her face is so small.
This much strap is left because her head is so small!
- Kwang Soo had no space. - What do you mean?
- Don't move your head too much. - Be careful.
Pull your hair back so your face shows.
(The men are trying to get her attention.)
Do you want to pull your hair back and wear the helmet again?
Okay.
- You're so nice. - I'm just helping...
because it's dangerous.
- Okay. - Now,
- let's win again. - Ji Soo and Rose. Start!
Name three countries you want to visit.
Australia, Thailand, and Japan.
- Hey, Rose. Don't be too nice. - He's right.
- That's not how you do it. - Get it together!
- Come on. - I'm sorry!
All right.
What took you so long in the bathroom yesterday?
I pooped, brushed my teeth, and washed my face.
- Good job. - Great work.
- Good job. - Nice.
- That was good. - Great.
Rose, go.
Name three celebrities you like from YG.
G-Dragon, Tae Yang, and Seung Ri.
- Nice. - Not Dae Sung.
- Poor Dae Sung. - Sorry, Dae Sung.
- Not Dae Sung. - Dae Sung, she didn't pick you.
Poor Dae Sung. He wasn't picked.
Say three complaints you have for our boss.
- Okay! - "Why don't you love me a lot?"
I don't know.
(Time's over.)
- Nice! - Did you hear that?
(A labor and management question worked.)
- This is it. - Great.
- It's okay. - Fine.
- The water started spilling. - Let's get it at once.
You got the heart of your boss.
(I'm saved.)
- No. - Not yet.
(That's too bad.)
- Okay. - Okay.
Name three male idols from YG you don't want to be friends with.
G-Dragon, Dae Sung, and Seung Ri.
- No! - Wait a minute.
Tae Yang and Dae Sung got switched.
- Dae Sung, don't be upset. - No. Wait.
She said Dae Sung instead of Tae Yang this time.
Dae Sung, please don't be mad.
Dae Sung, you're the best.
- Ji Soo, you need to win. - She's witty.
- Ji Soo, let's go! - Crush her!
Why do you fight with Lisa so often?
Because she ignores me, pretends to be cool,
and says mean things.
Because she ignores me...
(Lisa's getting attacked over here.)
Okay. Good job!
I think she's too honest.
- Do they really fight a lot? - No, they don't.
We're friends. That's why we bicker.
Name three male celebrities you want to date.
(Who is the man that stole Ji Soo's heart?)
Haha, Kim Jong Kook, and Lee Kwang Soo.
Hey, I'm taken.
Not me.
- I'm sorry. - No.
- No! - I'm sorry.
(Kwang Soo is touched.)
- Ji Soo, that was good. - Kwang Soo's happy.
Tell me three proverbs you like.
(Tell me three proverbs you like.)
"It's a piece of cake."
(It's a piece of cake.)
(Time's over.)
(With the proverb question, Ji Soo gets to remove a stick.)
- Yes! - Good job!
- You did it! - Nice!
Remove the middle one.
Yes, get the one in the middle.
(There's a 50-50 chance. Will it spill water or not?)
- There it goes. - Water's spilling.
- It's spilling. - There it goes.
- There. - Gosh.
- It's cold. - Team Black wins.
(Team Black wins with 2 points.)
- Ji Soo, great job! - You're the best!
- You did really great. - Jennie, avenge her.
Lisa, come out.
(Lisa versus Jennie)
- It's over if Lisa wins. - That's right.
(I'll finish you off with one question.)
(I guess you don't know me well.)
She wins every time.
(Testimony: She wins whenever she plays a game.)
(She never loses. Jennie is the Queen of Victory.)
(Up against Jennie is Lisa, the unlucky member of Blackpink.)
(The unlucky versus the lucky. Will there be a surprising result?)
Name three complaints you have about Blackpink.
(Name three complaints you have about Blackpink.)
(Jennie knocks Lisa over with one question!)
- You should say it. - Say it.
She's just too nice.
- That's why. - Lisa, you're too nice.
Lisa, this is it.
(Will she pull out the right stick at once like she says?)
(It's a one shot, one kill.)
(She's the lucky girl!)
She's the Queen of Games.
(She was born to play games.)
She's the Queen of Games. She's really good.
(Team Pink wins a point.)
- Seok Jin will play this time. - Okay!
(It's Seok Jin from Team Black.)
I think Seok Jin's going to be attacked.
(Seok Jin versus Haha)
- Let's go. Nice to meet you. - All right.
- Nice to meet you. - It's only a game.
Ready, set, go.
Three things that make you regret getting married.
It's frustrating and... Gosh, I'm about to lose it.
(It came from the bottom of his heart.)
What am I going to do?
How could you...
You can't ask a question like that from the start.
- Hey. - Hey, you.
- Hey. - Oh, gosh.
- How could you? - I'm sorry.
Come on.
- My goodness. - I can just pull one out, right?
(Will he succeed at his first try?)
- It wasn't the one, right? - The water isn't dripping.
- The water isn't dripping. - I passed, right?
(Haha fails to pull out the right one.)
- Let's go. - That was good.
Tell me three female celebrities you want to meet right now.
(Tell me three female celebrities you want to meet right now.)
Shin Ji...
(Shin Ji from Koyote?)
Shin Ji, Gianna Jun, and...
(He runs out of time.)
I couldn't think for a moment.
What's wrong? You could've just named anyone.
I don't know. I couldn't think of any names.
Why did this throw you off?
Why did I name Shin Ji out of the blue?
How are you doing, Shin Ji?
(He summons Shin Ji.)
- Which one do you think it is? - Let's get it right.
- Let's get it right. - Let this one be the last.
- I think it could be this one. - This one?
- You can't possibly know. - We picked the left before.
- Let's go with the right one. - Okay.
- Please. - Please be the right one.
(The level of water doesn't change.)
- That wasn't it. - He never listens.
Everyone could've known that wasn't the right one.
Let's go.
- Tell me... - Tell you...
three mathematical formulas you like.
Pythagoras' theorem,
apple formula, and lunch formula.
(Where did the lunch formula come from?)
- What formula? Lunch formula? - Lunch formula.
- Lunch? - Yes, lunch.
What is lunch formula?
I hope we get through this one more time.
(Should I let the water splash on him?)
Please.
(There's a 50-50 chance. Will he succeed?)
I don't think it's the right one.
- You need to lower your head. - Lower your head.
- I don't think it's the right one. - Lower your head.
(I hope he won't be unlucky this time.)
(No way.)
(It seems like Seok Jin's reputation won't be changed.)
(The score is 2 to 2.)
I can't believe it.
(Is it my turn now?)
Now, it's the final.
- Okay, Ji Hyo. - It's Ji Hyo's turn.
We meet at the final.
(Which team will win the game?)
(Last Round is Jae Seok versus Ji Hyo.)
I hope we win.
(I'm going to start.)
- I'll start now. - Okay.
- I hear that you have a boyfriend. - Okay.
Tell me three reasons why you like your boyfriend.
He's sexy, rich, and handsome.
(How can she be so composed?)
(Although she doesn't have a boyfriend, she handled it well.)
Well done. That was great.
- Okay. - Tell me...
three adult films you saw recently.
"Madame Ae Ma 1", "Madame Ae Ma 2", and "Madame Ae Ma 3".
(He watched the Madame Ae Ma trilogy.)
(Jae Seok recommends watching the complete series.)
- Good job. - How did he do that?
- You re-watched the classics. - I sure did.
You watched them all. Did you watch them on tapes?
- When did you see them? - "Madame Ae Ma"?
- I watched all three of them. - Are you sweating?
- Are you sweating, Jae Seok? - I am not sweating.
- This is just water. - Don't picture the films.
- Stop thinking dirty thoughts. - Kwang Soo,
this isn't sweat.
He tends to watch the classics again.
He loves the classics.
Tell me three proverbs you like.
"Mend the barn after the cow is stolen."
"Fishermen..." What was that?
(I didn't see that coming.)
You were thinking of four character idioms, not a proverb.
What you said was an idiom.
But why do I feel like I'm being punished?
(The helmet seems to be defected.)
Something's wrong with this helmet.
Our helmet is weird.
- As I said before... - Get it right at once.
- We never picked one from there. - If we get it, the game's over.
We never picked one from this side, Jae Seok.
If we pull out the right one, the game is over. It'll be our victory.
We never tried one from that side.
Let's do this!
(He pulls it out.)
(If the water drips, then Team Black wins.)
(Jae Seok fails to pull out the correct one.)
(My goodness.)
Seriously, she's so lucky.
(She survives.)
How is that possible?
Can we change the helmet? It's running out of water.
- Is that so? - Yes.
(Water's running out even though he didn't get the punishment.)
(The helmet is as unlucky as its owner.)
- Okay. - All right.
Are you doing this on purpose?
(Why do I feel like I'm being played?)
I'm being punished right now.
The water keeps dripping.
Why is it dripping?
(You might think he's sweating.)
- I mean... - Hang in there, Jae Seok.
Come on, Ji Hyo. Hurry.
Isn't he sweating way too much?
- Just do it. - Here it goes.
(What is Ji Hyo's counterattack?)
Three reasons you like "Infinite Challenge" over Running Man.
(Three reasons he likes "Infinite Challenge" more than Running Man)
(We are watching you.)
I've been on the show for a long time.
(What is this?)
(Don't speak.)
(Loyalty is more important than victory.)
- Hey. I was trying to... - What are you doing?
I could've just said anything.
(Team Pink gets a chance to remove a stick.)
Here we go.
Which one should I pull? Jennie, what do you think?
If we lose now, it's so unfair.
- I'm not sure. - This one?
- The one in the middle. - We are so lucky.
- The center one? - That one? Let's go with that.
It might not be the right one.
- I hope so. - Ji Hyo...
(What is Ji Hyo's choice?)
- We survived. - We're safe.
(Awesome! We survived.)
That was good.
(I can't believe we lost our chance.)
- No way. - That's okay.
- Wait. - I think that was the right one.
(Water's dripping all over his face.)
(Is the helmet defected or did Ji Hyo succeed?)
- The helmet is defected. - No, we got the correct one.
- It's just the helmet. - Water isn't dripping.
- The helmet is defected. - Hang in there.
- It's been like this. - No, we pulled the right one.
(Ji Hyo succeeded.)
- We won. - It was right.
- Come this way. - Come here.
Good for us!
- The helmet was like this before. - Yes, it was.
(After careful examination, the helmet isn't defected.)
- There's no more water. - Take it off.
I knew it.
It's the helmet's fault.
Kwang Soo, this is so unfair.
- Well done. - Good job.
Great work, everyone.
(The final score is 2 to 3 and Team Pink wins.)
This means...
Team Pink wins "5 Seconds Q and A".
(The victory goes to Team Pink.)
(They obtained an advantage for the final match.)
We'll go outside and start betting.
We've prepared a special way of betting.
Team Pink will have two opportunities to bet.
Team Black will have only one opportunity.
(Team Pink gets two chances since they just won.)
With this game, you can improve the quality of the prize.
It's "Bet on the Shoes".
("Bet on the Shoes")
- Bet on the shoes - Bet on the shoes
We have a massive black and pink checkerboard in the front.
You are to kick the shoe three times.
You can predict where the shoes will fall in.
Then you can bet your R coins.
(They will bet on the place the shoes will fall in.)
There are three probabilities.
Out of 3 tries, if 2 of the shoes go into the pink box...
and one of them goes into the black box,
whoever bets on pink will win.
If you bet on pink, you'll get twice the coins you bet.
If you bet on all pink or all black,
you'll get three times as many as the coins you bet.
(As long as all three shoes fall into the black boxes)
(If one shoe falls into R box, the reward will be quintupled.)
(If two shoes fall into R boxes, it will be multiplied by ten times.)
(Two R boxes will get me ten times as many as the coins I bet?)
Team Pink will be able to bet on two probabilities.
Team Black will bet on only one probability...
since your team lost.
You will throw behind the white line.
You will throw three times.
(What will their fates be?)
- Let's line up by teams. - Let's go.
How many coins do we have?
- We have 20. - We have 20R coins.
R box will multiply the bet by five.
(Since it's difficult to land it in R boxes, the reward is bigger.)
Only rich people can bet on it.
- That's right. - Goodness.
How about aiming for the R box?
- We shouldn't be too risky. - Right.
- It's only our first betting. - Let's be safe.
- Right, we should be safe. - The first one should be.
Where are you going to put yours?
- We'll split the two. - Come on.
What is that? You're playing safe.
What's the point of betting?
Right, it's pointless then.
Betting is relative.
This is a good strategy when we're playing against them.
We need to secure more coins and we'll bet more later.
You guys are so petty.
- You're so petty. - Yes, you are.
You're pettier.
How can you be so petty?
(They're acting immature.)
What do you want to do? It's up to you, Ji Soo.
- Do as you please. - No, you should do it.
We're all bad at it, Ji Soo.
- We should choose one of the two. - Right.
That's a safe bet.
- We'll go with black. - We are betting 10R coins.
(Team Black bets 10R coins on black.)
Team Pink will throw first.
- Let's go. - Rose will go first.
Don't be nervous. Just don't let it land into R box.
- Relax. - Anything but R box?
(It can fall into anywhere but not R box?)
- Rose. - Rose.
- Let it fall in a black box. - Get ready.
- You can start. - Good luck.
You can do it.
(The first shoe...)
(is flying.)
- Is it black? - That's it.
(It lands in a black box.)
That was great.
(The probability is getting higher for black.)
(Pink boxes will help only our team.)
- That's okay. - I'm sorry.
If another one goes into the black one, then that's it.
(If the shoe falls into a black box, it's over.)
- Please. - Fall into a black box.
- If only it lands in a black box... - Let it be black.
- Please let it be black. - You can do it, Jae Seok.
- This can be the last throw. - That's right.
Jae Seok, good luck.
(Jae Seok is the second one to pitch his shoe.)
(Where will his shoe fall?)
I have a feeling he'll make it.
No, he won't.
(It falls in a pink box.)
(How can I let it fall into a pink box?)
(He again shows he's not a good kicker.)
We're going to win.
Goodness.
(Even his foot isn't lucky.)
He just went without saying anything.
All we have to do is put it in a pink box.
(No one can predict the score at this point.)
- I think you can kick gently. - Gently?
Relax. Don't be nervous.
(In order to win, the shoe must go into a pink box.)
- Jennie. - Kick it to the black box.
(The fate of both teams depends on her shoe.)
- Don't think about it. - Please go into a pink box.
(Will it go into a pink box?)
(Or will it go into a black box?)
- Please go into a pink box. - You got it.
- Please, go into a pink box. - You got it.
(Where will it land?)
(After the shoe rolls around, the shoe falls into...)
- Please. - We got it.
(The shoe falls into...)
(a pink box.)
(Two shoes go into pink boxes and one shoe goes into a black box.)
(Pink Team wins the bet.)
(They're disappointed.)
(Thanks to Jennie, Pink Team wins a chance.)
(Crying)
Ji Soo lost her mind for a moment.
(She doesn't care anymore.)
I'm sorry.
(We won 20R.)
(Black Team wins 10R and Pink Team wins 50R.)
(It's time to eat a meal that's special to Jeonju.)
It looks delicious.
(Are there only dried laver and soy sauce?)
- Is this all? - These are Jennie's favorite.
- Really? - I love rice and dried laver.
I love dried laver very much.
- I don't need other side dishes. - Really?
In this game, you get to taste local dishes in Jeonju.
It's called "Jeonju Meal 31".
("Jeonju Meal 31")
- It's "Jeonju Meal 31". - 31.
For each round, you can win one side dish.
It's provided to the winning team.
The game rules are simple.
You lose if you call out a specific number.
Each team will give me an even number from 10 to 31.
You can't call out the addition of the 2 numbers divided by 2.
It doesn't require math skills.
- No one knows beforehand. - It's completely random.
Our team is at a disadvantage.
- Why? - Why?
Let's not play games based on luck.
We've never been lucky.
You're also bad at games that require strength.
We aren't physically strong.
- Games based on luck may be better. - You may be right.
A member from each team will take turns to call out a number.
Every time you call out a number, you'll pour hot sauce.
Does someone have to eat it later?
The player who loses...
(You eat the hot sauce if you lose.)
Hey!
Isn't that too cruel?
Oh, no.
The player who loses must take a bite of the food with hot sauce.
The winning team will receive a side dish.
- Okay. - All right.
(The winning team gets a side dish and earns 40R.)
What's the first side dish?
- I have to eat that. - It's tteokgalbi.
(They're desperate to eat it.)
It looks so good.
(Jeonju tteokgalbi arrives.)
(The prize for the first round is Jeonju's special tteokgalbi.)
Please give me a number each.
- You're up, Kwang Soo. - The first round will be easy.
- Tteokgalbi smells amazing. - It's great.
- Gosh. - Steam is rising from it.
A member from each team should sit in the front.
- Ji Soo will go. - Okay.
(He gets embarrassed.)
I thought he said my name.
(Ji Soo from Team Black plays against Jennie from Team Pink.)
- It's a fight between two women. - Do you know how to play it?
- Do we call out three numbers? - Yes.
You can call out up to three numbers.
You already know the rules.
(Why are you asking when you know?)
- "You already know." - She's starting her attack.
(Jennie suddenly attacks her.)
Of course.
(It's a war of hot sauce between two ladies.)
Play rock-paper-scissors to determine who goes first.
- Rock-paper-scissors. - Nice.
- Ji Soo will start the game. - Ji Soo, do not lose.
You'll eat the hot sauce.
Start pouring, Ji Soo.
(The game starts.)
One, two, three.
Four, five, six.
(They pour a lot.)
- It's okay to pour until 10. - Seven, eight, nine.
That's a lot.
10, 11.
- They've come far. - It's okay.
- Ji Soo, be careful. - I said 11.
- 12, 13. - Gosh, be careful.
- I can smell the sauce from here. - Do it slowly.
There's a lot in the bowl.
14.
You're doing well.
(Whoever loses will numb her taste buds.)
15.
(She's hesitant.)
Wait, isn't it okay until 20?
16.
17.
(She hesitates for a moment.)
It's okay.
- This is driving me crazy. - I can't do it anymore.
You're in trouble now.
18, 19.
(Jennie said two numbers. Did she say the losing number?)
- She said two numbers. - She's doomed.
- I think the next is the one. - This is great.
- 20. - 20?
(If Team Pink also gave 20, the losing number is 20.)
(Is 20 the losing number?)
What?
I think you'll lose next.
What, 20?
The real game starts now.
21.
(Is 21 a safe number to call out?)
She lost.
(They're playing a dangerous game.)
(The losing number is 21. Team Black loses the 1st round.)
(Good job, Ji Soo.)
That was great, Ji Soo.
Great job, Ji Soo.
- I won. - You did it.
You gave me 22 and 20.
- The losing number was 21. - Good job.
That's right, but we couldn't have known.
Team Black may take tteokgalbi.
- It's okay, you did well. - It's going to be delicious.
- I'm sorry. - We won tteokgalbi.
- He's already eating. - Can we eat now?
Seok Jin, please eat later.
- We must eat later. - Are you talking to me?
- What are you doing? - When will we eat?
Why are you eating the side dish first?
Gosh, what are you doing?
Don't put it back if you took a bite of it.
(He couldn't wait to eat.)
Goodness, Seok Jin.
Excuse me, Kwang Soo.
- Do I eat it now? - Can he eat it for her?
Can someone else eat it for her?
- May I eat it now? - Can he do it for her?
I could eat it for her but...
Come on, Kwang Soo. You can eat it for her.
(Kwang Soo, please take my tortilla with hot sauce.)
(He's in a daze.)
Of course I can eat it for you but...
(Only you can eat this tortilla for me.)
- His eyes are quivering. - Tell her no.
- No. - Don't do it.
She's trying to use you.
Look at her in the eyes.
She knows that she's pretty.
(She knows that she's pretty.)
- You can't do that. - No.
- You can't do it. - Listen, Jennie.
You don't like Kwang Soo, do you?
She might like him.
I'll give you the answer if he eats it.
- No. - She'll answer if he eats it.
In 5, 4...
- No, don't do it, Kwang Soo. - Don't eat it.
- You shouldn't eat it for her. - No.
- Kwang Soo is so cool. - No.
Please eat it for me.
(Please eat it for me, Kwang Soo.)
No!
(Will he stay loyal to his team or choose love instead?)
Please, please.
(His mouth is wide open.)
- Okay, I'll do it. - He's going to get hurt.
- No way. - Just take one bite.
- Don't eat all. - Just take a bite.
- Kwang Soo is amazing. - I poured so much sauce.
- He ate the whole thing. - He's so cool.
- He didn't need to eat all. - He's amazing.
Poor Kwang Soo.
What an amazing man.
My goodness.
Jennie, you must answer the question now.
- Don't say that you hate him. - Why would she hate him?
(It's okay, Jennie. You can tell me the truth.)
(She stands up.)
She ignores and leaves him behind.
(He hasn't swallowed it yet.)
- Just eat it. - Good job, Kwang Soo.
- Good job, Kwang Soo. - You're amazing.
- Won't you answer the question? - That was great.
Thank you.
Isn't Kwang Soo a great man?
He's such a great person.
She used you, Kwang Soo.
You do things that are unnecessary.
Here's the second side dish.
- Is that it? - It's a kind of soup.
Don't I get anything for eating the tortilla?
- Is that it? - You ate it only for Jennie.
It's fulvescens galbitang.
- I've never had it before. - It's fulvescens galbitang.
- It's very delicious. - It looks so good.
- Fulvescens. - I love that dish.
This sauce is perfect for Seok Jin because of his nose.
- Tabasco? - It's Tabasco.
The sauce is Tabasco, and Seok Jin has a big nose
(It's Seok Jin's favorite sauce.)
(He loves it.)
He can't smell how spicy it is.
The smell is so refreshing.
- Get ready. - Play rock-paper-scissors.
- Rock-paper-scissors. - Rock-paper-scissors.
(The number is only shown to the viewers.)
Make a bold move, Seok Jin.
- One, two, three. - Gosh.
(He pretends to be strong.)
- What are you doing? - Either way,
- it's a war. - It's a war.
- Is that what's going on? - Don't do that.
- Keep it edible. - Four, five,
- six. - No one can eat that.
(She pours in a lot of hot sauce.)
(For whom are they playing the game?)
- Okay. - Stop it, Ji Hyo.
Is this how you'll play it?
One of you has to eat that.
(He flinches.)
- Seok Jin got a little scared. - Seven.
(I'm manly. I will go as far as I can.)
(Goodness)
- Seok Jin got a little scared. - Seven.
(He puts it back.)
(He quickly decides to end the competition.)
I told you that he's scared.
- When he saw Ji Hyo get aggressive, - He got scared.
he was afraid that he might have to eat it.
That's what he imagined.
- Seven? - Yes, seven.
Eight, nine, ten.
- Eight, nine, ten. - There's no need to do that.
You're the one who declared war.
- 11, 12, 13. - "There's no need"?
He pours drop by drop.
Wait a minute.
(He has such a unique personality.)
- He's a coward. - 14, 15, 16.
Say just one number.
(Let me think.)
(Come on, just try me.)
17.
- It's okay. - 18, 19, 20.
Aren't you scared at all?
"Aren't you scared at all?"
What is he talking about?
- What are you talking about? - Say just one number.
21.
(Team Black's number is 26.)
I'm starting to forget.
- Half of the bowl is filled. - It's drenched.
That's a lot of sauce.
No one can eat that.
(There's a trace of the bloody battle on the bowl.)
- The loser has to eat that. - 22, 23.
(Only a person will be the one to eat the spicy tortilla.)
- We're still not there? - Just do one.
Just do one.
(They don't hesitate to put more hot sauce.)
You should go up to 27.
(He goes to 26.)
Why did you only pretend to pour the hot sauce?
- You didn't put any on there. - He faked it.
- I did pour it. - No, you didn't.
(Ji Hyo is brave.)
(Team Black's number is 26, but it went over 27.)
Are we still not there yet?
- What number did you write down? - Just do one.
- 28. - No, Seok Jin.
(Seok Jin will get to play with fire.)
(Team Pink wins the second battle.)
I told you to go up to 27.
- That was the number? - How did you know?
I had a feeling.
We should've listened to Ji Soo.
(Seok Jin ruined an almost-won victory.)
He started it.
(Seok Jin tries Jeonju's tortilla.)
It looks funny.
It's all right. It's not that spicy.
Go, Seok Jin.
(Jeonju's hot sauce puts Seok Jin on fire.)
Let's move on.
(Team Pink won the 3rd round. Team Black won the 4th round.)
We have to eat that. It's good.
- It's your turn, Kwang Soo. - That looks good.
- It's yellow corvina. - It's really delicious.
That looks so good.
- Should we start? - Yes.
- One, two, three. - Let's go, Jong Kook.
(But Kwang Soo has made it look much spicy.)
I think 16 is the number. 15.
I go, 16 and 17.
There you go. You should've done one more.
(Team Black's number is 18.)
(It always gets messy when these two collide.)
Maybe they wrote down the same number as us.
- 18. - What?
- What? - 19.
What is this?
- What's going on here? - Please.
- Please. - Did you write down a big number?
- Did you say 19? - Yes.
What should we do?
I go 20.
(Jong Kook gets to play with fire.)
(Team Black wins the fifth round.)
(Team Black's number was 18. Team Pink's number was 22.)
I got yellow corvina for Lisa.
For Lisa.
(She's excited.)
- Bring it over here. - My fish.
(Goodbye, yellow corvina.)
(It's rare to see the Unlucky Trio celebrating a victory.)
(Let's get this over with.)
Today's not going very well for you, is it, Jong Kook?
We'll eat it for you.
- It's okay. - Why do you like Yoon Eun Hye?
(Have you ever gotten beat up with a tortilla?)
- What did he say? - I don't know.
I'm just asking out of curiosity. Who did you like more?
Don't answer that.
Don't answer that. There's no point in answering.
You should ask him another question.
- Who did you like more? - Don't answer him.
Aren't you curious which celebrity he liked the most?
I already know.
Jae Seok. What are you doing?
- He was just kidding. - I know.
- I know that. - You already know?
(He takes a bite of the tortilla.)
My fish.
- The tour isn't over yet. - As a result,
Team Black will get 40R.
(Team Black now has 50R. Team Pink now has 70R.)
And Team Pink will get 20R.
(Team Black got tteokgalbi, boiled pork, and yellow corvina.)
(Team Pink got marinated crab and seaweed galbitang.)
Thank you for the meal.
Thank you.
(It's dinner time with Black Pink.)
(Savoring)
(Everyone gets one seaweed galbitang each.)
- They all get one each? - It looks so good.
Can we have one of those?
No way.
- There's meat in here. - There's so much meat in there.
Look at the meat.
It's called. seaweed galbitang. Of course, there's galbi in there.
- I wasn't expecting this. - I have four pieces.
(Jae Seok fetched a bowl.)
(It's so satisfying.)
What was that?
- What are you doing? - Try it, Ji Soo.
You'll shoot a commercial if you do this.
- Show them what you're capable of. - How do you do it?
(Awestruck)
She killed it.
- She killed it. - Break the stereotype of idols.
That was good.
- You should do a dialect. - This is delicious.
(I don't know how.)
Do you not know?
Lisa is from Thailand. How do you expect her to know dialects?
Seok Jin said to Lisa,
"You should do a dialect."
- I was giving her chance. - Do you take her as Robert Harley?
It'd be funny if she went like, "That's so refreshing."
"That's so refreshing."
It'd be nice to hear her speak in Jeonju dialect.
The rules are the same.
You can bet on whichever one you want.
Are we allowed to bet on only one spot?
- For Team Pink, yes. - Right.
We can bet on two different spots.
We'll bet 10R on "All Pink".
(Team Pink bets 10R on "All Pink".)
We'll bet 20R on "Black".
(Team Black bets 20R on "Black".)
What's the other one?
And we'll bet 5R on "All Black".
- That's right. - Why there?
- We'll take the lead if we win. - Let's go.
- Let's go. - We need to land it on "Black".
- That's right. - You two should play.
Oh, no.
- Go after one another. - Use slippers.
- Should I use slippers? - Yes.
- You can do it. - Go, Ji Soo!
- You can do it. - I'm under so much pressure.
- It's okay, Ji Soo. - I'm afraid I'll keep failing.
- Don't worry. - You'll be able to do it.
(The only lucky one in the team, Ji Soo, threw her shoe.)
- Black. - It's on black.
(If it lands on a black tile, it'll favor Team Black.)
(The fate of Team Black lies on Ji Soo's shoe.)
It's on black!
(Black)
We did it.
It's on black!
(Ji Soo has done it again.)
We did it.
(Bitter)
- We did it. - Ji Soo is amazing.
- She's so good. - Come over here.
Stop doing that.
(Ji Soo and Lisa are quite playful.)
Stop teasing us.
- We can't go for "All Pink" now. - That's right.
- It's over. - You have to stop us now.
We have to stop them from winning.
(Team Black bet 25R in total.)
(Rose of Team Pink will try to stop Team Black from taking the lead.)
- We'll stop them from winning. - Go for the black tile.
- Black. - Pink.
- Pink. - Go for the black tile.
Black.
(If it lands on a black tile, it favors Team Black.)
(If it lands on a pink tile, Team Pink will be at mercy.)
(Where will Rose's shoe land on?)
(It's black again.)
- Black. - It's black.
(Team Black is ecstatic.)
- It's okay. - Yes!
- Oh, no. - It's not your fault.
We're almost there.
It's either "Black" or "All Black" now.
(Regardless of the result, Team Black's bets are a success.)
- We did it. - No.
For us, it's better if they get "All Black".
- That's right. - They'll only get 15R, then.
However, if it lands on R, you will get nothing.
(If the shoe lands on R, they will fail their bets.)
- Lisa. - Just avoid the R.
No pressure.
- R is good. - Black.
- R. - Black.
(All she needs to do is to avoid the R.)
(Lisa's shoe will decide the result of this game.)
(If it lands on a pink tile, Team Black will get 40R.)
(Wait, it's flying towards the R tile.)
(No way.)
(If it lands on the R tile, Team Black will lose everything.)
- R. - Black.
- R. - Please.
(Will the unlucky guys continue to be unlucky?)
(It landed on the R tile.)
(Among all the 64 tiles, it landed on the R tile.)
(Let's go, Team Pink.)
(Lisa made history with her bad luck.)
(She's even unluckier than we are.)
This doesn't even make sense.
They lost everything.
(She's the unluckiest of all.)
How is this even possible?
- Oh my goodness. - They lost everything.
(The two teams fail their betting as the result.)
How is this even possible?
How can something like this happen?
I've never witnessed such bad luck before.
It's okay. We have more than 20R that we started with.
She's so positive.
I like your attitude.
Wait. Are you sure it's okay?
(The amount of R coins they currently have.)
The final mission is "Odd-Even Name Tag Elimination".
- "Odd-Even Name Tag Elimination"? - It's a Name Tag Elimination.
Eliminate the name tags of your opponents and add up the numbers.
The team to make number seven will become the winner.
Each team will have numbers of 1 to 5 on their name tags.
People with even numbers will wear red hats.
People with odd numbers will wear blue hats.
Guess your opponents' numbers and eliminate their name tags.
If you take the name tag off, you will obtain its number.
The team to make number seven will become the winner.
However, you will immediately lose if the added sum goes over eight.
(You will immediately lose if the added sum goes over 8.)
This will be hard.
- We'll have to be smart. - I'm really nervous.
Let's say the numbers you got are 1 and 3.
In order to make 7, you need 3, but it's already been used.
In such occasions, the team with the bigger number will win.
If you both have the same numbers, the team to finish first will win.
We'll have to be smart about this.
Go to your headquarters and discuss each other.
(Their last bets are at stake on this final race.)
(Time-out)
Even though we lost 25R,
- It's okay. - Ji Soo and Lisa...
- helped us come this far. - I know.
You're impressive.
It's because they're very good.
What happened was a miracle.
If we continue being like this,
it'll be impossible for us to win.
We'll lose everything.
We could take off the name tags to make a total of seven,
- but let's make a trap instead. - That's right.
- That's a great idea. - In my opinion,
- the other team will play safe... - There isn't any specific number...
- that's important. - because they have nothing to lose.
Team Pink might pick two even numbers.
You're very smart.
They'll take off the name tags from the ones wearing a red hat.
They won't care about the rest.
- They might take off 5. - What about 5?
I'm sure they're also confused, but here's the problem.
Let's say they obtain two.
There are only two even numbers.
They're the most likely targets.
The probability is 50 percent.
- That's right. - We must think.
Let's just play it randomly.
Really?
- No specific number is important. - If he had been younger,
I'd have scolded him now.
I'd have punched him, too.
- It's because... - I think it's better this way.
it's the best way.
The person who's most likely to be eliminated...
should get a big number like five.
To make it least confusing, drawing straws...
is the best.
Then the other team can't predict our numbers.
- Really? - Shall we do that?
We can't predict what will happen because it isn't a strategy.
(Which team will win "Odd-Even Name Tag Elimination"?)
- Will this be okay? - We won't have a strategy?
("Odd-Even Name Tag Elimination" starts.)
(The time limit is 30 minutes.)
(They keep their guard up.)
Be careful.
(Is that Team Pink?)
- Are you okay? - I feel confident.
(Team Black...)
(approaches Team Pink up close.)
- Are you okay? - I feel confident.
(He wants to catch at least one.)
(Ji Hyo comes out while being oblivious.)
(Jae Seok attacks.)
What happened?
(Jae Seok takes one name tag.)
What are you doing?
(Ji Hyo's number is one.)
- Did you start already? - It's one.
- Ji Hyo's number is one. - It's okay, Ji Hyo.
- I'm going to catch you. - Wait.
(Jae Seok gets counterattacked.)
(Roaring)
- Try to run away. - Wait a minute.
Catch him.
(What will happen to Jae Seok after his sudden attack?)
(Tearing)
Catch him.
(Jae Seok's number is 5.)
- I'm sorry, Jae Seok. - His number is five.
We should give something to the other team.
- Do you let them take it off? - To increase their total.
Here you go.
I'll take number five and attack them to increase their total.
(Their plan is to make the other team's total bigger than eight.)
I think he did it on purpose.
It's number five.
(Team Pink can't attack easily now.)
(Current score)
(Team Black has one.)
(Team Pink has five.)
(Team Pink's target is Seok Jin and Lisa.)
Ji Soo, we got one, and Jae Seok is eliminated.
- Did he take one? - Be careful.
We got number one.
(Team Black needs to make 6 to win.)
I'll go alone first.
If they get you, they'll lose.
I'll go alone.
Shall I come with you?
(Team Black must protect their even numbers.)
- I'll go with Kwang Soo. - Let's make them confused.
(The ones with odd numbers go first.)
- Gosh. - It's scary.
What should we do now?
- Who should we attack? - Our targets are red hats.
- Red hats? - Yes.
It's confusing.
- Which one should we attack? - It's either 2 or 4.
- It's between 2 and 4. - Let's take off all the name tags.
Did Team Black take one? We don't need to attack them.
(The ones in blue hats attack.)
- No. - No.
(If Team Pink takes off 3, they lose immediately.)
(Shall I take it off or not?)
Why aren't you taking mine off?
What happened?
(She took it off.)
- I told you not to take it off! - Yes.
(Haha's number is five.)
(Team Black takes off 5 after 1.)
- We did it. - I told you not to take it off.
It's okay.
My number was five.
- They're doomed. - It was perfect.
Team Black is doomed now.
I let them take mine off.
If we take off one of theirs...
(It's going according to our plan.)
- That was amazing. - They can't attack us anymore.
She fell for it.
- We're going to win. - Good job.
(Team Black can't take off any more name tags.)
- We won. - The game is over.
(What should we do?)
I told you not to take it off.
- I told you not to. - Why did you do it?
- I took it off. - Our total is six.
- Six? - What happened?
Our total is now six.
- They can't run very fast. - We can't take off any.
- We can't take off any. - We can't anymore.
(Team Black has 6. Team Pink has 5.)
We can't take off their name tags anymore.
We can't let them take off ours for 30 minutes.
- That's right. - For 30 minutes?
Either they take off a big number or don't take off any.
Neither of the two can be attacked, and we'll keep running.
Do we attack one of the red hats?
Don't we lose if we take off number four?
- We're at an advantage. - Right.
Is it Seok Jin or Lisa?
(All they need is number two.)
Maybe it's Lisa.
(Which one of them has number two?)
(They have 10 minutes left.)
- We have to keep running away. - Do we tie if they take off mine?
- That's right. - Right?
You two aren't important.
Team Pink will attack either me or Lisa.
(Team Pink's target is an even number.)
- Isn't that right? - Yes.
- Shall we move separately? - No, we should stay together.
Stay together.
Gosh, they're coming.
Let them come.
- Start running. - We must run away.
(Team Pink chases them quickly.)
(I'm a dinosaur.)
- What? - It's Lisa.
- It's Lisa. - Take hers off.
- It's either Lisa. - Or it's Seok Jin.
Take it off.
- Did she take it off? - Who could it be?
- Who could it be? - Do you have number two?
- I think it's Lisa. - It's her.
I think Lisa has it.
(Seok Jin is left on his own.)
(Jong Kook has his eyes on him.)
You have 10 minutes left.
Jennie.
It's Seok Jin.
- It's Seok Jin. - No, stop it.
(Our target is Seok Jin.)
It's Seok Jin.
No, stop it.
Get away.
(It's over if Seok Jin gets caught.)
(Jong Kook heads towards Seok Jin.)
(They need 2 to make a total of 7.)
(Is it Seok Jin or Lisa?)
(They run after Seok Jin.)
Get away.
Seok Jin.
(Tearing)
(Jong Kook takes off the whole name tag.)
(What's the number behind Seok Jin's name tag?)
What's going on? Why did they take off Seok Jin's?
(Team Pink's fate depends on...)
(the result of Jong Kook's decision.)
I think it's four.
(Is it 2 or 4?)
(Seok Jin's number is four.)
(Team Pink loses with a total higher than 7.)
(Team Black's plan worked.)
(30 minutes before)
(Seok Jin chose number 4.)
They won't know whose to take off, so how we act is important.
- It's Lisa. - It's her.
(He pretended to have number two.)
(As he moved away, he led Jong Kook to attack him.)
(Jong Kook fell for the bait.)
(Team Black's plan turned out to be a success.)
We got them.
Our plan worked.
Our plan really worked.
(Team Pink fell for the trap.)
It was Seok Jin's acting.
Good job.
(Members with even numbers brought victory to the team.)
For "Odd-Even Name Tag Elimination",
Team Black wins.
(Team Black wins.)
It's not over yet.
- We have another game left. - Of course.
Team Pink will make their bet first.
Good luck with how you calculate.
We're going to bet everything.
To win the flight ticket to Europe...
- This isn't enough. - Do you mean all black?
- Isn't this not enough? - No.
- We need to make this bet. - We do.
- Shall we bet on this? - We'll need to bet 50R.
All right.
We don't have to bet 50R.
We can bet just 40R.
(They plan to earn 5 times the amount by betting 40R.)
Let's bet 40R and see what happens.
- Okay? - That sounds good.
- Let's keep 20R. - Okay.
Let's give it a try.
We might win Jeonju Seasoned Laver Set.
Let's make a bet for the last time.
40R on placing a shoe on the R square?
- Isn't that disadvantageous? - Just make any bet, Lisa.
It doesn't matter which you bet on.
Team Black will make their bet after throwing a shoe.
- Just make it into any square. - Okay.
Lisa, please throw the shoe.
If she throws it into the R tile, we'll put the next one in 2R.
- To make it 10? - The next should be in 2R.
(Team Black's bet depends on where she throws in her shoe.)
- You can do it. - Go, Lisa.
(To where will she throw her shoe?)
(Will it make it to the R tile again?)
It's going towards the R.
It's a black square.
(It's in a black square.)
Should we make it "Three Black"?
What would we get?
- We'll get Tteokgalbi Set. - Tteokgalbi Set?
It's because it multiplies. Let's go for "Black".
Let's go for "Black".
- Let's win tteokgalbi at least. - Okay.
We should win tteokgalbi at least.
We'll cook it when we get back to the dormitory.
(Team Black makes a bet of 25R on "Black".)
- Let's bet 25R coins. - 25R coins?
We are done betting as well.
- Jong Kook, you can do it. - Yes, you can.
- Don't think too much. - You can do it.
- You can do it. - It will be hard for him.
It's okay as long as it doesn't go into the R square.
- No way, he'll make it. - Kick it like that.
- Is he aiming? - Just don't make it land in R.
- It's impossible to aim. - Right.
(Their fate depends on the R tile.)
(Where will Jong Kook's shoe land into?)
(Is it the R square?)
(Stopping)
(Some shout with joy and other with sorrow.)
It went into the black tile again.
That was so close.
- We need a pink box. - We almost had it.
- We need it to go into a pink box. - Right.
(So far, two shoes fell into black boxes.)
- We need a pink square. - This time, we are kicking.
(With one pink tile, their betting will be successful.)
Your shoe went into the pink box before.
- You do it again. - You can do it.
- I'm sure you'll get the pink. - You can do it.
(Jae Seok gets ready to kick.)
(He shoe kept landing on pink squares before.)
(This is the time for him to get his groove on.)
- He can do it. - It'll go into a black box.
(No way. I can't let it fall into a pink square.)
(Will he be able to hold up his reputation?)
(They're chanting a spell to make it fall into a black box.)
(Don't let it influence you.)
(He gets ready and concentrates.)
- It'll be the R box. - R box is the worst.
- Let's go with the R box. - Yes, we should.
Yes, let's go with the R box, Jae Seok.
Why don't we make it more interesting?
I don't feel confident.
I am not confident anymore.
- What's wrong? - Kwang Soo,
- I can't do this. - You'll be okay.
- You can do it, Jae Seok. - Ji Soo,
- I don't feel confident. - I have a feeling you will do well.
- You get the pink box. - That's more likely.
- I have a good feeling about this. - I'm going crazy.
(He's getting ready.)
(He stands behind the line again.)
- Let's get the R box. - You'll get the R box.
(I won't let them influence me.)
- You can only get the pink box. - Get the R box.
(He kicks his shoe.)
(The fate of two teams depends on this shoe.)
(With which team...)
(will Queen of Victory side?)
(The shoe falls into the black box.)
(I can't believe this.)
- We won. - Awesome.
(The last shoe went into the black box.)
(Your misery is my happiness.)
You should've strongly argued that you weren't confident.
Don't volunteer if you can't deliver.
- When did I volunteer? - You didn't get the pink box.
My goodness.
- I mean... - Our plan never works.
We can't never have it our way. Why is that?
- How is this possible? - We're sorry.
- Don't worry about it. - That's okay.
We're fine.
(Team Pink takes Jeonju Seasoned Laver Set with 20R.)
- You should take them all. - I have so much.
What am I going to do with all these?
- Take them. - Yes, please do.
- Enjoy them. - Thank you.
(Jennie gets enough laver sets.)
We are truly the unlucky team.
Let's try this again with the same team.
- They don't seem so happy. - It was a lot of fun.
Let's give a round of applause for Blackpink.
(Thank you for working so hard on a cold day.)
- Thank you. - You're the best.
- Let's meet again. - And...
we filmed in Jeonju for two weeks.
- We had a lot of delicious food. - It was amazing.
- Jeonju is beautiful all year long. - That's right.
Thank you for your cooperation.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
(We'll strive to be better.)
(Welcome)
(I prepared you a present.)
(I prepared a curse for you.)
(The curse of a bad Santa)
(The winter of 2016)
(The curse of a bad Santa visits Running Man.)
I am not joking.
(Don't let the innocent faces fool you. What is the truth?)
(Christmas with Bad Santa)