(At a cafe in Hannam-dong)
(Nice music is playing here.)
(Who are these beautiful women listening to music?)
Look at Kwang Soo. He's all dressed up again.
- Hello.
-  Are you going somewhere?
Why?
- Are you a choir member?
-  What are you talking about?
(His suit has the same colour of pigeon, a symbol of peace.)
What happened to your hair? It looks awful.
Why did you part your hair like that?
- Please don't do that.
-  What?
- You look like Ahn Jae Wook.
-  Right, in "Star in My Heart".
You also look like the Superman from Dr Slump.
(Jong Kook perfectly resembles the cartoon character.)
My goodness.
- Hello, everyone.
-  Hi.
- We invited six beautiful ladies.
-  Really?
- You'll play with them today.
-  Yes!
It's because Ji Hyo isn't here today.
- That is right.
-  Ji Hyo isn't here.
That means one of us will be her partner today.
Right. One of us will be unlucky.
You'll become a couple with one of them.
- Really?
-  So we'll meet our destiny.
(Where are the members' partners?)
(They're right above them.)
(They came early and each chose music they like.)
(Those who choose the same music will become a couple.)
- That's not easy.
-  We must have same taste, then.
- We'll play the music they chose.
-  Okay.
If they play "Hot Issue", you know who chose the song.
It's Ji Hyo, then.
- I'm nervous.
-  Please, listen carefully.
They chose their favourite songs.
(This song?)
- I got it.
-  It's Ji Hyo.
- It must be Ji Hyo.
-  I think I know...
- who chose this one.
-  It is Ji Hyo.
- Really?
-  That's right.
- Why?
-  It can only be Ji Hyo.
I'm sure Ji Hyo chose this song.
- Young people don't know this song.
-  Ji Hyo thinks this song suits her.
(Who is this beautiful girl?)
- It can't be A Joong.
-  It can't be.
- The next one.
-  Okay.
("Seoul Life" by Rose Motel)
- I don't know who chose this.
-  I will choose this one.
I like this one.
The one who chose this song must be on the older side.
This is...
- Who chose this song must be old.
-  But the thing is,
young idol singers might listen to these songs more.
I'll play the next song.
Is there any hip-hop music?
("Twinkle" by TTS)
(Haha is excited.)
- This is a little...
-  I'm sure it's a trap.
- It's a trap.
-  I like TTS.
- I like it.
-  This is a good one.
I think we should choose old songs.
This is hard...
because this song was released about 3 to 4 years ago.
Isn't it someone who pretends to be young?
I think we must listen to all the songs to figure it out.
Maybe "Hot Issue" is really there.
("I Need a Girl" by Taeyang)
- Taeyang?
-  It's Taeyang.
Taeyang?
This song is great.
- I'm sure an idol chose this.
-  It's a nice song.
I'm sure there's a twist. Don't be fooled.
Girl group members like Taeyang.
- This song would be a good choice.
-  No.
(There must be hidden traps.)
I'll play the next song.
("Romantic Cat" by Cherry Filter)
- This is my favourite!
-  I love this song.
- I love "Romantic Cat".
-  I'm sure...
there are three traps Ji Hyo laid.
This feels like Ji Hyo's.
(Do I look like Ji Hyo?)
She likes this one.
Let me play the last song.
- There are so many traps.
-  This is so confusing.
It's already the last song?
This is a bright song.
It's very vibrant. Don't you think someone cute chose this?
This is music for clubs.
But I feel like it's an old lady who chose this one.
- I think so, too.
-  This is so old.
I want "Seoul Life".
I want it, too.
- I was going to choose it, too.
-  I like "Seoul Life".
- I want it.
-  I want "Seoul Life".
I was also going to choose "Seoul Life".
You all can choose the same one.
- Right.
-  If that's your taste, it's okay.
I'll choose "Seoul Life".
Why?
Why does everyone want that song?
- I like that song.
-  Gosh!
I think you all are trying hard not to be Ji Hyo's partner.
- How could you...
-  If it's not her, it's all good.
Everyone here is okay if it's not Ji Hyo.
- It's time to make a decision.
-  Please choose one song.
- "Seoul Life".
-  "Seoul Life".
I want "I Need a Girl".
I will choose "Romantic Cat".
- I want "Seoul Life".
-  Again?
- Too many competitions.
-  So you all don't want Ji Hyo.
Good.
Okay. Then,
the ladies who chose "I Need a Girl"...
and "Beautiful Girl" will come out first.
- Oh, my.
-  There they are.
They are idol group members.
- My goodness.
-  I knew it.
She's pretty.
(How can my taste be the same with an idol member?)
(Who are these beautiful Running Women?)
Gosh, Mi Joo! Mi Joo is here.
- It's Mi Joo.
-  Se Jeong is here.
(Se Jeong is a member of a famous idol group, Gugudan.)
(Beautiful Mi Joo of Lovelyz is here as well.)
- Mi Joo is here.
-  Come again?
- What?
-  It's Mi Joo!
- Se Jeong is here!
-  I like Mi Joo!
- You are...
-  I chose the wrong song.
So idol group members are here!
- My goodness.
-  They are here!
- What is this?
-  It's good.
They chose "Beautiful Girl" and "I Need a Girl".
- Great.
-  They chose the songs.
I was going to choose "Beautiful Girl".
We'll listen to "Beautiful Girl" again,
and the one who chose it will go back to the second floor.
- I was going to choose that.
-  All right.
- I never knew you'd come here.
-  They're so bright.
Mi Joo is so pretty. It's Mi Joo.
- Is she going up again?
-  No!
- Here comes Se Jeong.
-  This is bad.
I met Se Jeong on Saturday.
- Hello.
-  She's Jae Seok's partner.
Hello.
Se Jeong, you should've chosen "One Man".
(That was a nice joke.)
You two will become a couple.
(Jae Seok and Se Jeong are a couple.)
- Did you choose the same song?
-  Yes.
Why did you choose this song?
I was on "Kpop Star 2" before,
and I sang this song there.
I see.
(She's cute.)
(This girl has become a star now.)
- But...
-  I missed it, gosh.
The lady who chose "Seoul Life" is coming next.
Now I understand how things are going today.
Those who chose "Seoul Life" and "Mi Mi Mi" will come down.
I want to see who chose "Mi Mi Mi".
- Let's invite them.
-  Okay.
(They chose "Seoul Life" to avoid being a couple with Ji Hyo.)
Gosh.
- Wait.
-  Who is it?
They are totally different from the first two.
She's Jae Suk.
- It's Jae Suk.
-  Gosh.
- Jae Suk!
-  Hello.
- Long time no see.
-  One of them chose "Seoul Life?
Ji Hyo, you chose "Seoul Life"?
- Are you serious?
-  You chose it?
- Gosh.
-  I know you did.
(Guess who chose "Seoul Life".)
- Hello, Jae Suk.
-  Jae Suk!
- They're like my family.
-  Who chose "Romantic Cat"?
I love this song, though.
This is a great song.
Great!
("Seoul Life" is Jae Suk's choice.)
Then,
did Ji Hyo choose "Mi Mi Mi"?
- Hello.
-  Hello, Jae Suk!
- It's been long.
-  She's cute.
- Anyway, Jae Suk...
-  What is this?
- is Jong Kook's sister-in-law.
-  Our Jae Suk.
She and Soo Ae are like sisters.
Jong Kook, Soo Ae is doing well.
- Are you okay?
-  I don't know.
Good.
I wanted to console him.
Did he get dumped? They didn't even have a date.
- Did she dump him?
-  Is it already over?
Soo Ae never considered it.
Was it just for the show?
(I'm not smiling inside.)
She made him have a crush on her.
The one I will choose is...
Hey, you.
Me?
Hey, think about it one more time.
(Hey, think about it one more time.)
We already were in the same team before. Think about it again.
- I want Mi Joo.
-  Come here, you brat.
- Wait a minute.
-  Goodness.
We'll be the winner in the end.
Now, those who chose...
"Romantic Cat" and "Twinkle" will come out.
"Romantic Cat" and "Twinkle".
Please, come down.
Who are you?
(Who are you?)
Who is it?
(Who are these beautiful ladies?)
- She's Tuna Lady.
-  Tuna Lady is here!
- Really?
-  Tuna Lady!
- Tuna Lady is here!
-  Moon Sook is here.
- My goodness!
-  Tuna Lady!
- Gosh.
-  Moon Sook is here!
- Hello!
-  That's Moon Sook!
(Noh Sa Yeon and Ahn Moon Sook)
- Tuna Lady.
-  Tuna Lady is here!
She's back because it's summer.
- Moon Sook is here, too.
-  Hello, Moon Sook.
They chose "Twinkle" and "Romantic Cat".
I can't really say who's good and who's bad.
Let's see...
if Sa Yeon is a romantic tuna.
(Who chose "Romantic Cat"?)
I think it's Moon Sook.
- They're not going up.
-  Is it Moon Sook?
Where are you going?
(Where are you going?)
- No one wants Seok Jin.
-  They both are...
- Please, hold on.
-  Wait.
They don't want Seok Jin.
Where are you going?
(We don't want unlucky Seok Jin.)
- They don't want Seok Jin, either.
-  They went back up.
- I do understand them, though.
-  Right.
I think...
She's coming back down.
It's Moon Sook.
(Moon Sook chose "Romantic Cat".)
(They have the same taste in music.)
- Ahn Moon Sook!
-  Yes!
- You look so pretty today.
-  You look beautiful.
You look beautiful today.
- You look lovely.
-  That's right.
- She does look beautiful.
-  You look gorgeous today.
It's been five years since I joined you last time.
Yes, I remember. It was during the summer.
And it was summer, just like today.
It's also funny that my life hasn't changed at all since then.
(Her life hasn't changed a bit for the last 5 years.)
- It has been the same.
-  It hasn't changed at all.
And I'm sick of this man, too.
(She's already tired of seeing Seok Jin.)
(Moon Sook and Seok Jin will play together today.)
You made me dress up. You should match me with a single man.
Those guys are not as nice as you think.
Please bring them down.
(The remaining women have chosen one of their belongings.)
(The man who picks them will become their partners.)
- They are here. Can you open it?
-  Okay.
What are they?
There is a fan. A small fan.
These socks seem worn out.
Don't idol singers wear these often?
They also use small fans.
Please choose one each.
- I'll be the last to choose.
-  Okay.
- I'm not choosing the earrings.
-  You know how unlucky I am.
Here.
- He got a good one.
-  Do you like it, Jong Kook?
Can I have the other one?
- Congratulations.
-  Why did you give this to me?
- Those might be Sa Yeon's.
-  We don't have time.
- You're wasting time.
-  Why did you give these?
- She sprayed perfume.
-  Hurry up.
Come on.
(Who are the owners of these three different objects?)
Ladies, please come down
Sa Yeon is wearing her earrings.
- That's a relief.
-  Hello.
- Hello.
-  She's wearing earrings.
- Welcome.
-  We've been waiting for you.
They are all wearing earrings.
I'm wearing earrings, too.
We have Mi Joo, Ji Hyo...
and Tuna Lady.
- Please show them what you chose.
-  Okay.
- One, two, three.
-  One, two, three.
All right. Who's the owner of this small fan?
(It's so difficult to read their faces.)
All right. Who's the owner...
of this small fan?
- Please stand beside him.
-  Yes!
(Screaming in happiness)
(It's the Tuna Lady.)
- Yes. Yes, I got him.
-  It's so amazing.
- No way.
-  It's really amazing.
- They are the best couple.
-  What an amazing couple.
Wow, what a match.
- They're the final boss for today.
-  They're the best couple at games.
- You should be smiling, Jong Kook.
-  I am.
- I am smiling.
-  You're faking it.
All right. We have Kwang Soo and Gary left.
You must be looking forward.
If I get Ji Hyo...
- Why?
-  I prefer someone else, too.
- She can have a different partner.
-  I'm sure she feels the same way.
It would be unlucky if we were paired.
- That's right.
-  I'm fine with Ji Hyo.
I don't care any more.
- All right.
-  I'm not changing my opinion.
It just scares me.
We have earrings...
and a pair of socks.
Please stand next to the person who has your belongings.
One, two, three. Go.
(Go!)
- Ji Hyo is smiling strangely.
-  Yes, she surely is.
- Gary!
-  No!
- Why did I pick last?
-  Calm down.
(Kwang Soo is touched to be paired with Mi Joo.)
- Gary. You must be happy. Right?
-  Look at Kwang Soo.
- Kwang Soo seems really happy.
-  He's so lucky today.
(Gary and Ji Hyo are a couple for today.)
- Gary.
-  Yes?
Ji Hyo is so happy to be with you.
- Let's do well.
-  Let's love again.
(Will the once Monday Couple rekindle their love?)
(Running Women are here to conquer.)
(Gather as many Running Balls as possible...)
(to have an advantage at the final race.)
Sa Yeon, I think this is the end of us.
(Women's Name Tag Elimination will be played for the first time ever.)
(Here comes the strong ladies.)
(Running Men versus Running Women)
We have a simple test for you to take...
before we move for the first game.
What is it?
- What's that?
-  It's a punching machine.
- What is that?
-  Is it a punching machine?
- It feels like I'm at an arcade.
-  Okay!
Do you seriously want Mi Joo to punch that thing?
This is not a game for the ladies.
This is...
- You lost some weight, didn't you?
-  Yes, I did.
- Do we have only one chance?
-  You must hit the centre.
We all know that Ji Hyo always strikes first.
- That's right.
-  Yes. She always strikes first.
She always strikes first.
- Really?
-  Yes. She's really strong.
I feel nervous.
- Go, Ji Hyo.
-  Why is she wearing pyjamas?
Just look at her.
(Her stance looks good.)
She knows how to hit.
Shouldn't you take off your bracelet?
- Remember the good, old days.
-  Get ready.
(Remember how you used to punch?)
- She knows how to punch.
-  Go.
(She punches it.)
(Ji Hyo gives it a crushing blow.)
- That was a good punch.
-  I hope it goes over 500 points.
- 500 points?
-  Amazing.
498 points. That was a nice punch.
- Next.
-  It's Mi Joo's turn.
- How should I punch?
-  Mi Joo.
- Can she score 300 points?
-  What are you doing?
- Gosh.
-  What's wrong?
- What's wrong?
-  It's tight around my shoulders.
- Her dress is not comfortable.
-  I thought she was stretching.
- She seems strong.
-  Don't grab your wrist.
- Cover your entire hand.
-  It'll prevent it from twisting.
Take care of your Tuna Lady instead!
- Because Kwang Soo was...
-  Why do you care about her?
- She has Kwang Soo.
-  She could get hurt, that's why.
You're really strange.
- She won't hurt herself.
-  Goodness.
- I'll do it now.
-  Yes.
Look at that punch.
(She gives it a good punch.)
- 420 points?
-  The number keeps rising.
- Really?
-  Amazing!
530 points?
(Although she's thin, she's quite strong.)
Although it seems like she didn't put in much force,
- she put her weight in it.
-  She's been hiding her strength...
- She has been hiding it.
-  because she's an idol singer.
I think she can score over 700 points.
- I'm nervous now.
-  Sa Yeon.
- I thought it was 70 points.
-  She can score over 700 points.
She's been hiding her ability.
Stop talking about Mi Joo.
- I'm sorry.
-  Sa Yeon's mad.
(Glaring)
That was too much, Jae Seok.
Good luck, Sa Yeon.
- You should apologise to her.
-  Well, I...
Aim for the centre.
Just put your weight in.
(She slightly misses her punch.)
- She missed it.
-  Let me try once more.
527 points?
She missed it and scored 527 points.
I missed.
You lost your grip while punching.
I did. Can I try one more time?
- I don't know if you can.
-  I'm upset because of Mi Joo.
I'll punch one more time thinking about her.
- You can't.
-  You only care about Mi Joo.
- It's all Mi Joo.
-  All right. Just once.
When you punch, you should put all your weight in the punch.
If not, you'll slip.
That's it.
(Lady Tuna's powerful smash)
- That was a strong punch.
-  I think it'll be over 700 points.
- That was really close.
-  700 points?
It's 583 points.
- That was a nice punch.
-  You did well.
The last punch was...
- Don't worry. It's nothing.
-  Jae Suk is...
She is most likely to win.
- We played against her before.
-  She can't be rivalled with anyone.
She can't be rivalled.
- You only need one hand.
-  Jae Suk is really...
You should warm up more.
(That was a loud, powerful punch.)
(That's surely her whole-hearted punch.)
- What was that?
-  Amazing!
(She scores 689 points.)
- 689 points?
-  What is that score?
- What was that?
-  Did I do well?
Yes, you were amazing.
You should warm up more.
(Look at that punch.)
(She's in a different league.)
- Did you see that swing?
-  It was just...
She put all her weight in it.
- She hit the bull's-eye.
-  She put her weight in.
- It's so clear.
-  You should punch with your body.
She should be playing at the Olympics!
- You shouldn't punch like this.
-  She shouldn't be here.
- Thank you.
-  Jae Suk, you should be in Rio.
But our Se Jeong is really good at punching.
- Wait.
-  It shouldn't be "our" Se Jeong.
You're in different teams.
You're friendly to everyone.
- You're so strange.
-  No, I mean it. She is...
really good at punching.
- What are you talking about?
-  Take care of your Tuna Lady first.
- Look, Se Jeong.
-  Punch with your weight behind...
- your punch.
-  Grab your hand like this...
- Go! Take care of your partner!
-  Stand here, Se Jeong.
Jong Kook!
(You little jerk!)
Gosh. Today must be my unlucky day.
The fan makes her face look bigger!
(The fan is too small for her.)
It's your fault, Jong Kook.
It makes her face look bigger!
Sa Yeon, get under this fan.
Come under this big fan.
(This fan will surely make her face look small.)
Hey, stop it.
- We should treat her like a queen.
-  Jong Kook.
Take good care of her.
- How could you use this fan?
-  I was just being nice.
- It's really funny.
-  Se Jeong.
- Can you do it now?
-  Yes.
She looks weak.
My goodness.
Nice punch.
(Se Jeong's gives it a right hook.)
- 420 points?
-  It's going higher than that.
- It's 500 points.
-  She got 591 points.
That's good enough.
Here comes an ex-professional taekwondo player.
(Next is Moon Sook.)
- I'm looking forward to this.
-  I'm nervous.
Moon Sook, punch like this.
This dress is really uncomfortable.
You can pull your dress up a bit.
- Wait.
-  No. Not like that.
- Stop it, Moon Sook.
-  What are you doing?
What do you think you're doing?
It's my dress. Why do you guys care?
- It's too much.
-  Isn't this just okay?
- Her dress is quite long.
-  This machine is little low.
(She punches it.)
(She gives it a powerful smash.)
- That was great.
-  She used one hand.
- It's 553 points.
-  That's really good.
Do you want to do it again?
We all expected this outcome.
Punching, posture and power... This game was for Jae Suk.
She knows how to punch.
I think she's stronger than some men.
(Jae Suk and Haha are first place.)
(Ji Hyo and Gary are last.)
All right, everyone. For the first game,
we'll play "Running Women's Arm Wrestle".
- You're playing against Jae Suk.
-  I guess only the women play.
We divided you into several classes.
It doesn't make any sense.
You'll play against appropriate opponents.
- Go beat Se Jeong.
-  But...
- Relax. It's okay to lose.
-  Let's go.
She looks like she could be my daughter. I'm sorry.
- Jae Suk, let's go!
-  Get ready.
- Let's have a good match.
-  Haha is really annoying.
Get ready, everyone.
- She doesn't look so determined.
-  That's it.
- Grab her.
-  Gosh.
Just fall down, Se Jeong.
- Yes. You're doing nice. Good.
-  It's a one-sided match.
(She screams and falls.)
(She sounds like a dolphin.)
Hey, Se Jeong.
- I feel guilty for winning this.
-  That's was cruel.
- I'm sorry, Se Jeong.
-  Were you excited?
I think you screamed in excitement.
(I screamed without knowing.)
- Oh well.
-  It's so hot and tiring.
- I'm really tired.
-  It was inevitable.
- There was nothing you could do.
-  Next players are...
- Ji Hyo and Mi Joo.
-  Go, Ji Hyo.
Go, Mi Joo. Go.
Se Jeong should've played against these two.
Mi Joo, you only need to try once.
Ready.
- Go hard, Ji Hyo.
-  Ji Hyo seems really relaxed.
Look at her relaxed face.
- This is quite...
-  She's good.
Push, Mi Joo. Push if you can't pull.
How did Jae Suk do this so easily?
(Screaming)
(Mi Joo is out.)
She collapsed while screaming.
(I may have been like that, too.)
- Next.
-  Let's go!
- Seriously, Gary...
-  Ahn Moon Sook.
This is a big match.
- Let's go.
-  You can do it!
(They start off by intimidating each other.)
This really is a big match.
It's almost the final.
- I can't predict the result.
-  Let's go!
They are surprised by each other.
Ready...
(Moon Sook vs Sa Yeon)
Who's going to win?
As we expected,
- Push to your right.
-  they are...
It's like a match between a dragon and a tiger.
It's intense.
Moon Sook! Attack inwards.
To the left.
Pull her.
(Moon Sook attempts to make a sudden attack.)
(How dare you?)
(Sa Yeon counterattacks.)
(Swift)
Pull her towards you!
(She successfully counterattacks.)
(Sa Yeon wins.)
Drink some water.
(The match ends with Moon Sook on the floor.)
(I can't beat her at all.)
(The semi-final, Ji Hyo vs Sa Yeon)
- Hey, she even beat me.
-  She is toying with Ji Hyo.
(Sa Yeon wins with just one move.)
(Tuna Lady is on a winning streak.)
She defeated all four.
Now, it's your turn.
(The final, Sa Yeon vs Jae Suk)
- Let's go.
-  You can do it.
- Loosen your arm muscles.
-  It's nice to use my power.
- Loosen up.
-  That feels good.
(This is a true variety show.)
(A fair play is expected.)
Ready, set...
- I can feel their energy.
-  Let's go.
(Startled)
I can feel her great power.
- She's surprised.
-  Both of them are surprised.
Only the strong can recognise each other.
All they did was hold hands.
I've never seen them this nervous.
My heart is beating really fast.
She wasn't nervous when she was playing games with us.
- I'm sweating.
-  I think Jae Suk will win.
(It's like a fight against themselves.)
- Ready...
-  Go, Jae Suk.
This is the final.
- Set.
-  They're the representatives.
Go.
(The match starts.)
- Sa Yeon isn't an easy one, either.
-  Look at them.
Sa Yeon isn't easy at all.
It's a close match.
(Sa Yeon attacks first.)
(How can she attack in that posture?)
It's a close match.
(It was a swift move.)
(Jae Suk let go of Sa Yeon's hand while pretending to defend.)
(Jae Suk is the final winner.)
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry, Sa Yeon.
(It's the historic moment when a new legend emerges.)
You're no longer the strong one.
I haven't seen her so embarrassed like that.
- After the game...
-  Please move a little bit.
she got up and said,
"She is out of my league."
(Jae Suk is out of Sa Yeon's league.)
Jae Suk.
I didn't know she would lose.
You are the best.
(A new legend of variety shows is born.)
(Haha and Jae Suk are the winners.)
(Currently, Jae Suk and Haha have four Running Balls.)
The second game is called "Gather the Running Balls".
You will need to gather the Balls from different spots.
Try your best to gather as many Running Balls as you can.
- Okay.
-  Let's go!
Let's go!
(She looks innocent and happy.)
(I'll try to get a lot of Running Balls.)
(There are five different spots where they can obtain the Balls.)
Guys, let's go to the snack bar.
- First...
-  Wouldn't it be an eating game?
Although we might lose, we will be able to at least eat.
Let's nourish our bodies first.
- Let's just eat first.
-  You're right.
- We're on a winning streak.
-  Is the camera on now?
- It isn't, right?
-  It is on.
- I brought some food.
-  Go ahead and eat.
- Is the camera on? Then...
-  You can eat freely.
(She is hungry.)
The camera's on, so go on and eat.
We're going to a snack bar in a few minutes.
- Really?
-  Yes.
- Let's eat there too.
-  First, we'll go to...
(Eating is always good news.)
They're so eager to eat.
They are different kinds of food.
I will eat with my guard down.
After eating some bread, you usually...
- crave tteokbokki.
-  You're right.
Tteokbokki goes well with bread.
In order to eat tteokbokki...
Bread is just an appetiser, right?
- Eating is like a relay.
-  It shouldn't stop midway.
- It's like handing over the baton.
-  It's like breathing.
"Breathing"?
Appetite is like breathing.
Food is like a relay.
- I have good breathing skills.
-  It's an endless marathon.
She has good breathing skills.
She has good breathing skills?
I really do.
Wow, this car runs nice and smoothly.
- Really?
-  Oh, I shouldn't have said that.
(Laughing)
Moon Sook, I feel like I'm with my uncle.
(I feel like my uncle is my partner.)
- I got my license in 1988.
-  In 1988?
(They depart from Itaewon to Dongdaemun-gu.)
- Let's go to the billiard hall.
-  Okay.
- Let's go.
-  Great.
I wonder what the mission will be.
It's been a long time since I came to one.
(What kind of mission will be given on this blue table?)
What kinds of food are you reminded of in a billiard hall?
- Jjajangmyeon.
-  Jjajangmyeon.
Please bring two bowls of jjajangmyeon.
- Oh my goodness!
-  Really?
- That's so great.
-  I'm hungry.
The mission here is "Mouth Billiards".
You blow the ball to the other team's net.
The team to score two points first wins the game.
The winning team will obtain one Ball and jjajangmyeon.
I definitely got to eat jjajangmyeon.
- We'll start when you're ready.
-  We are ready.
Ready...
(Dominate the game with your great lung capacity.)
Set.
(Blowing)
(Wind blows from every direction.)
- We are almost there.
-  Block it.
(Gary tosses it to the front.)
Oh no.
(The ball is headed towards Seok Jin's net.)
(Ji Hyo spots a chance to score.)
Go, Ji Hyo!
(Gary and Ji Hyo score a goal.)
That's Ji Hyo.
(She's the striker of Mouth Billiards.)
Do you have a long tongue?
How in the world...
are you so good at blowing?
(I can't blow for too long because it makes me dizzy.)
You said you would speak like a real lady.
- It's not important any more.
-  Is it not?
(Nothing is more important than winning.)
- All right.
-  Get ready.
Let's go.
(The game restarts.)
Good.
(Spitting)
Come on, Moon Sook.
(She aggressively attacks by spitting and shoving her face in.)
- Attack.
-  Kiss him!
(You provoked a sleeping lioness.)
Score it!
(Blowing)
Come on, Gary. Don't back off.
(Startled)
Moon Sook!
Why don't you just kiss him?
(The other teams enter.)
(Their faces are so close to each other.)
Gosh, what are they doing?
It looks somewhat erotic.
Erotic?
(Gary makes a long distance shoot.)
Defend.
(Seok Jin gets a chance right after the crisis.)
(She quickly blows.)
(Ji Hyo's surprise attack leads to a winning goal.)
(Seok Jin and Moon Sook score 0, Gary and Ji Hyo score 2.)
(She is at a loss for words.)
It was awesome.
- Ji Hyo, that was great.
-  She's sweating.
Congratulations.
- Jjajangmyeon...
-  Let's give them jjajangmyeon.
(The winners are blessed with jjajangmyeon.)
It smells great.
Jjajangmyeon always goes well with billiards.
(Monday Couple starts nice and smoothly.)
(Jae Seok, Se Jeong, Kwang Soo and Mi Joo head to the snack bar.)
Sorry, but why don't you go to another spot?
Mi Joo, this is the only team that we can compete with.
I think that's right.
Usually, Haha is quite weak,
but not today because he is teamed with Jae Suk.
She is really strong.
So this team is the easiest to win against.
- We...
-  Oh, here we are.
- This is the place.
-  Se Jeong, get in quickly.
Okay.
You guys come in later.
- Jae Seok.
-  I want to get in.
- Hello.
-  Se Jeong, grab a seat.
Sit down and brace yourself.
- We are now...
-  I guess we'll eat something.
The mission you have to complete here is...
- "Exercise and Tteokbokki".
-  "Exercise and Tteokbokki"?
Move the tteokbokki...
to your partner's dish using the hand grip chopsticks.
Then the partner has to eat it using the fork dumbbell.
How many kilogrammes will it weigh? That's...
Do you think you can do that, Kwang Soo?
- Wow, this is...
-  Oh, this looks heavy.
(Which team will have the honour of being the weakest?)
Ready, start.
Should I use only one hand?
- Yes.
-  It's not easy to pick them up.
Kwang Soo.
These chopsticks are really hard to use.
(She enjoys the tteokbokki.)
(She is eating well.)
- It's hard.
-  Help yourself.
- I'm hungry, Kwang Soo.
-  This is hard.
Goodness.
- Yes?
-  Why is this so hard?
(Frustrated)
(Struggling)
(It drops again.)
Help yourself.
- I'm so hungry.
-  Here you go.
Goodness.
- Here you go.
-  I know how to pick it up now.
All right!
It's spicy.
No, it's not spicy at all.
- Goodness.
-  Just swallow them.
- You must really like tteokbokki.
-  I do.
(Se Jeong must've been very hungry.)
Mi Joo, we have to beat them.
(The spiciness is catching up to her.)
Se Jeong, we need to win.
- It's too spicy.
-  Just put it in your mouth.
It's not spicy.
(The game is about to end.)
Mi Joo, we don't have much time. Hurry up.
(Which team will be the winner?)
- Stop.
-  Gosh, time's up.
How many pieces did you eat?
Mi Joo ate 7 and Se Jeong ate 8 pieces.
Jae Seok's team wins.
Jae Seok and Se Jeong obtain one Running Ball.
How many more did they eat?
(They lost by just one piece.)
It's spicy but delicious.
(The winner is given the chance to try cheese tteokbokki.)
There are even rice balls.
(She seems elated.)
(Rice balls make her happy.)
- Enjoy.
-  My goodness!
(She smacks her lips.)
(The cheese is stringy.)
I feel bad for the other couple.
(Let's drink some water to forget about our hunger.)
(I also want a bite of the chewy cheese.)
Se Jeong, you must love tteokbokki.
- I really love it.
-  Do we have to go somewhere else?
Shall we wait until someone comes? When will they come?
(What's Kwang Soo and Mi Joo's fate?)
(The place to play billiard)
- Let's go.
-  Would you like to play?
- This? We give up.
-  We might pass out if we do.
- I'm really dizzy.
-  My head really hurts.
(I'll show you the real diaphragmatic breathing.)
Don't touch this.
You'd better not touch this, okay?
No one can't touch this. This is mine.
- Get ready.
-  All right.
(The game starts.)
(A competitive match)
(I'll show you my strength.)
(She bumps her chin.)
(She only bumped into the ball slightly.)
She crushed it.
(It's crushed appallingly.)
(She has a secret weapon that destroys anything she touches.)
It's completely broken.
I can't get up because I'm too embarrassed.
(Here comes Ha Jae Suk's power.)
- Look at that.
-  Goodness.
(The game resumes after they change the ball.)
(They blow back and forth.)
(We only hear them blowing.)
(Jong Kook blows hard to shoot.)
(Dashing)
(Blowing)
(It passes the goal line.)
- It's in.
-  It's in.
- That was a goal.
-  Wow.
You're impressive.
(Tuna Lady gathers all her energy today.)
(Tuna Lady tries to shoot again.)
It's in.
It's a goal.
- Great.
-  It's in.
You're impressive. You play well.
(Jong Kook and Sa Yeon earn one Running Ball.)
(Guests waiting for a Running Couple are at this cafe.)
There they are.
Who are they?
They're so cute.
- Hello.
-  Goodness.
(It's a strange man with two cute girls.)
He looks familiar.
(His silhouette is familiar.)
Hello, Gil Gang.
- Hello.
-  What brings you here?
-  I was with family and got caught.
Really? Goodness.
They're Gil Gang's daughters.
Gosh, they're so pretty.
They're the judges of this mission.
- I'm nervous.
-  I see.
Gil Gang and his daughters will evaluate the mission at this cafe.
- It's a dramatic play.
-  How does it go?
There are script A and B.
You earn a Running Ball based on Gil Gang's evaluation.
- I'll pick script A.
-  It's not up to you.
I'll give you script B.
- Gil Gang never disappoint.
-  What are you doing?
Gil Gang sure is strict.
- Goodness.
-  I'll give you script A.
Tell Dad to give us a good score.
(Please, put in a good word for us.)
Are you ready, Gil Gang?
- Yes.
-  All right.
- Now...
-  If it isn't genuine, I'll give...
- zero points.
-  We'll be good.
Be quiet and do it.
Please start "Running Theatre".
Get ready, and go.
I didn't know what you'd like, so I ordered a shrimp burger.
(The first difficulty, "Wasabi Burger" scene)
(The two are sitting across from each other.)
(Goodness!)
(Actress: What are you trying to do?)
What are you trying to do?
(A sudden attack of wasabi)
His nose is cleared up.
Jae Seok's nose is cleared up.
(Put a piece of lemon in her mouth.)
I'll kill you if you tell on me or anyone who finds out.
(She's losing her consciousness.)
Goodness.
(I feel them just by looking at them.)
(The second difficulty, "Furiously Exhaling" scene)
(She can blow well after the wasabi cleared her nose.)
Don't underestimate me.
(The third difficulty, "Water Slapping" scene)
(She screams in excitement.)
(He aims the gun at her then shoots her.)
(He shoots water.)
Shoot me before you go.
I'm tired of these games.
Goodness. Let's break up!
(She screams.)
(Goodness)
- In 1, 2, 3.
-  Gosh.
- Oh, no.
-  Goodness.
(His head spins.)
Are you okay?
You hit me so hard.
- Are you all right?
-  What's going on?
- Se Jeong.
-  Are you okay?
- You didn't crack...
-  Why didn't it break?
this gourd. You should have cracked it beforehand.
It doesn't break even when I do this.
Gil Gang gave you a fail, so you failed.
- Gosh.
-  The gourd didn't break.
Look at this. It's impossible to break this.
- What if I break it with my head?
-  If so, I'll accept that we failed.
- Really?
-  Yes.
- Yes, I'll accept it.
-  Your children might get hurt.
Be careful of the children.
(He breaks it with his strong head.)
(What?)
It's a gourd that breaks easily.
- It's pretty fragile.
-  Se Jeong didn't hit him hard.
I can't help but accept that we failed.
(Come back after rehearsing more.)
Action.
(Gary and Ji Hyo start their "Running Theatre".)
You jerk. What happened?
How could you do this without telling me? How could you?
(The gourd rolls off.)
What did I do wrong?
Have a seat. Do you know how much I suffered...
because of you?
(Breaking)
(His bottom hurts as he gives everything into his acting.)
You're horrible.
I'm okay. Stop crying.
Here you go, Ji Hyo.
(Give that to me.)
(She blows her nose.)
She failed.
Something came out of Ji Hyo's nose.
Did my nose run?
Try it with your left nostril.
The other nostril may not work.
Keep going. We can film that part separately.
What are you talking about?
I wish my heart would get hard instead.
(The third scene is "Fist of Rage".)
(He punches.)
(She holds the board and he smashes it.)
Do you smell something burning?
What? What's burning?
(She splashes water on him.)
Who are you throwing water at?
I don't care.
- Who are you throwing it at?
-  What's burning?
- My heart is burning right now.
-  Is it your heart?
(They hug and pop a balloon.)
They failed.
(Popping)
(His heart turned into ashes.)
- He'd better not pass them.
-  In 1, 2, 3.
(What did the judges think of Gary and Ji Hyo?)
(He has a discerning eye.)
Yes, thank you.
- Is it true?
-  How can they pass?
How can they pass?
- They acted realistically.
-  What about us?
Didn't we also act realistically?
- The gourd didn't break.
-  Oh, my goodness.
- Here you go.
-  Okay.
How is this possible?
(Cafe to the hair salon)
This mission is called "Colourful Limbo".
One of you are to lift your partner and go under the limbo stick.
The couple that passes the lowest limbo earns three Running Balls.
However, every time you try, you must do something...
which is getting a colour spray treatment from the hair stylist.
- Let's try it once.
-  Gosh.
- I'll lift you. Let's try it.
-  I don't want to.
Can I make myself lighter?
Mi Joo, you can't be that heavy.
- We just had some food.
-  Come on.
I'm scared.
- One.
-  I won't breathe.
- In 1, 2, 3.
-  In 1, 2, 3.
(She falls down.)
(A counterattack of a girl group member)
I don't think I can lift you.
Try it once. It'll be fine.
- Let's try it.
-  Okay.
Please make it look pretty.
Okay.
It looks so good, Kwang Soo.
Are you spraying green?
What's going on here?
I can't do this.
Isn't this a limbo set?
- Here you go.
-  What's this?
- Are you done?
-  Yes.
- Are you really a hair stylist?
-  I'm sorry.
How could you do this so carelessly?
- You look very good.
-  What's wrong?
- How can he lift me and do that?
-  The colour won't fade.
(Kwang Soo tries at 75cm.)
What are you doing?
(He struggles.)
Wow, goodness.
- I'm sorry. Must I continue?
-  He can't do it.
He can't do it.
- Wait a minute.
-  Shall I tilt my head?
(He reaches a limit.)
I have to lift my leg off the ground.
I can't lift it.
(They squirm.)
(I guess this is the end.)
What are you doing?
How low is this?
(He changes his plan to move 1mm at a time.)
- It's okay, I got it.
-  There you go.
Can you lift your legs?
You may be able to make it.
Let's see.
Don't move your legs so much.
Why did you try 70cm?
- I passed the stick.
-  They might make it.
- That could work.
-  They want to use up the energy.
He might fall on his bottom. Will they make it?
(Unfortunately, Kwang Soo and Mi Joo fail.)
Go on.
That was a close call.
- We'll try now.
-  Seok Jin doesn't have to lift her.
- Woman may lift the man.
-  How could I let her?
Sir, Sir, Sir!
Sir!
- What's that?
-  What are you doing?
You look so cute.
Excuse me, Sir.
You're cute.
- You look cute.
-  The colour's like doenjang jjigae.
- I do look passionate.
-  But isn't this...
- Moon Sook, it's better this way.
-  Isn't this too much?
- Before...
-  Put your arm around me.
(He gives it his all.)
What have you been eating, Moon Sook?
I have big bones. It's my bones.
Most women say it's because they have big bones.
Right.
(My bones are very big.)
I think it's going to fall.
(It's okay if you have big bones. Trust me!)
You can do it, Honey.
- Slowly.
-  Be slow.
You can do it.
(Moon Sook, do you trust me?)
(We are a flaming youth.)
You got it.
(Seok Jin succeeds.)
(Go on and play the music! Seok Jin is the best.)
(Seok Jin and Moon Sook succeed at 90cm.)
Moon Sook, you're light.
I held a cotton puff.
We'll start immediately.
Can we do three tries at once?
Look, it's Gary and Ji Hyo.
Is this limbo?
- It is.
-  Let's start now.
We're going to win.
(Kwang Soo tries again.)
- We can do this.
-  Say, "start" first.
- Start.
-  What's up with my hair?
How high is this?
This is easy, of course.
- If you succeed, the rank changes.
-  It's hard from here.
- It gets difficult now.
-  You must stand up.
- It's difficult to get up.
-  It's limbo.
- Do you win when you stand up?
-  Yes.
Smack me once.
(She obliges.)
(He's awake now.)
- One more time.
-  No, it's okay. This is good.
(It was a miraculous touch.)
- He's done.
-  You're almost there.
- You're good. Stand up now.
-  Get up.
Don't look. Just stand up.
(Will Mi Joo's slap work?)
Stand up. Good, okay.
(Lifting)
(Kwang Soo and Mi Joo succeed at 80cm.)
How high was this one? Was it 80 cm?
(Kwang Soo and Mi Joo are currently in 1st place.)
(Running Theatre)
I'm your aunt.
Yeon Soo, where's the origin of your last name?
What group are you from? From what line? Generation?
- I'm from the 29th generation.
-  I see, Sir.
I'm first.
- I'm very...
-  That was quite...
Auntie.
Please take good care of me.
- They're my aunts.
-  They're so cute, really.
Ready, action.
I didn't know what you'd like, so I ordered a shrimp burger.
Let's eat.
It looks delicious.
(I hate that we must eat this while knowing.)
(The two are sitting across from each other.)
(Her nose is painfully refreshed.)
(Laughing)
My tongue is numb.
Goodness, I'd rather live alone.
I'd rather live alone. Let's break up.
(This is a true Running Woman's gourd breaking.)
(She hits his head with the gourd and leaves.)
- How did we do?
-  In 1, 2, 3. Great job.
(They succeed.)
Are you okay?
I got hit on the side of my head.
Action.
You jerk.
(Breaking)
What happened? Why didn't you tell me?
Where? Do you see?
(The fire has been extinguished.)
(It's powerful acting.)
My heart has changed.
- Did they do well?
-  How was it?
In 1, 2, 3.
(They passed.)
Thank you so much. Thank you.
- You're the best.
-  Goodness.
Three more.
(Eating)
(She eats...)
(and eats.)
(The barbell...)
(makes an assist.)
Haha and Jae Suk.
(Haha and Jae Suk win.)
We did it.
(They finish a meal through the mission.)
(Ji Hyo and Gary come first with 7 Balls.)
(Seok Jin and Jae Seok's team come last.)
Let's go, hurry. Good.
(They try 75cm.)
(They pass the bar with ease.)
Gary.
- Grab onto me.
-  Okay.
You got it.
Do I have to get up now?
Get up.
(He uses his lower body strength.)
(Gary and Ji Hyo succeed and come 1st place.)
Do you want to try 70 cm to be safe?
Okay, let's do that.
Let's do 65cm. 65cm.
- Gary, this is too low.
-  We can do it.
It's best to succeed here so we can get three Balls.
Let's go.
In 1, 2, 3.
(They pass with ease thanks to their good teamwork.)
Lean down more. I'll grab you.
You did it.
(They pass the bar at once.)
You did it. Gary, you can do it.
(After 6 years together,)
(Gary and Ji Hyo are the best at couple games.)
(They showed unbelievable power in front of 300 people.)
(Today, they show off their great chemistry once again.)
- Gary, get up.
-  Wait, a little more.
Stand up.
(He puts in all his might.)
(They set a new record.)
Yes!
(They are always the best duo.)
(Gary and Ji Hyo are 1st, Kwang Soo and Mi Joo are 2nd.)
- There won't be a difference.
-  Really?
- Should I just stay still?
-  In 1, 2, 3.
(He's in shock.)
(Wait a minute, Sa Yeon.)
Hey, you're making her embarrassed. Jong Kook!
(He lets go of her.)
Are you going to let her fall like this?
- No, it's not that.
-  Let's do it again.
Are you going to let her fall like that?
(Let's try again.)
- Let's do it again.
-  What?
Try lifting me one more time.
Try up to here.
We're going to practise.
This is your last try.
(Straining)
(Is she a tuna fish or a whale?)
- Hurry and stand up.
-  I can get up.
I can get up but I'm thinking about passing through.
I'm sorry.
(Leaning over)
Jong Kook!
(He lets go of her again.)
Are you going to keep dropping her like this?
My goodness. You should rest here.
- Gosh.
-  I wanted you to rest.
- I didn't see you that way.
-  No, it's not that.
- I thought you could lift me.
-  Try it again.
- I can stand up.
-  Really?
- Sa Yeon, can you excuse us?
-  I can get up.
I'll try it with Se Jeong.
- Okay, good.
-  Are you okay?
- He got it.
-  I'm okay.
- Hold on.
-  We have to go down.
(He begins with a smooth pick up.)
(Only the beginning was smooth.)
(Should I rest, too?)
- Wait a minute.
-  At least try to go under.
Wait a minute, please.
Sit. You have to sit completely.
Se Jeong, go out first. Good, you go first.
(You first, Se Jeong.)
- You can let your hands go.
-  Okay.
Good job.
(It won't be that easy.)
They can't do it.
Se Jeong.
You can go. Go alone.
(I don't think I can go any more.)
- This is difficult. I'm flustered.
-  Goodness.
That's it. Goodness.
(Jae Seok and Se Jeong fail.)
- You did well.
-  This is hard.
- Good job, Se Jeong.
-  It's hard to go under.
I think 65cm is too low.
Can we practise a bit more?
I don't think we can.
Let's try again. You're good at this.
- Let's go.
-  Okay.
I'll go out first like they did.
- Let's go out. Let's do it.
-  Okay.
Great.
Look.
(They barely...)
(pass her head.)
I'm going.
(She hits the bar.)
(She makes a double K.O..)
Sa Yeon, this isn't a lawn.
(This summer, a tuna appears on the blue ocean.)
Sa Yeon, may I try it with you?
- Really? Are you sure?
-  Yes.
Jae Seok exercises a lot.
It'll feel like you're carrying two Se Jeongs.
My gosh, Sa Yeon.
(I was wrong.)
Goodness, I'm sorry.
- Stand up.
-  I'm sorry.
I don't think I can do it.
Get up.
Try moving.
- You can do it.
-  Try it at least.
- I can't go another step.
-  Try it once.
- Hurry.
-  This is the best I can do.
(I think this is where it ends.)
(Falling)
Oh my goodness.
(Why can't you guys hold me?)
- I'm sorry, Sa Yeon.
-  You did well.
It's my first time.
(She lives up to her name.)
- You tried.
-  We got weaker.
- Right. We got weaker.
-  We...
(Jae Seok's lower body gives in.)
It's not that serious.
- She's not that heavy.
-  I didn't drink water today.
- I didn't have any water.
-  What are you talking about?
- It's because I'm dehydrated.
-  It's not that bad.
- Let's give up on this.
-  Let's go.
- We can't succeed here.
-  Let's go to the Photo Zone.
- Let's take our baby.
Gosh.
(Sa Yeon leaves after showing off her superior weight.)
(We will take three photos at the Photo Zone.)
What do you do at the Photo Zone?
Step on me and go up.
What should I do?
(Photo Zone begins.)
What should we do? Goodness!
- Get away.
-  My gosh.
- Go, go.
-  Jump.
- This doesn't work.
-  We can do it.
- I can't do it.
-  Get on.
(We can't use that method.)
(3 photos are taken.)
You have to do this. Go like this.
(Gary and Ji Hyo are clearly visible.)
(Is this a ghost?)
Oh my gosh!
Look at that.
(Gary and Ji Hyo succeed.)
I think luck is on our side today.
It's our day.
(I have a good feeling about this.)
(Meanwhile, in the billiard room)
We have a chance.
Hello.
(Their rival, Jae Seok and Se Jeong appear.)
You must have been to the hair salon.
What is that?
(They're good in styling.)
- You must have been there.
-  Of course.
I told you. Today isn't our day.
- Nothing goes as I planned.
-  Exactly.
How many have we got?
Can I tell them?
- Don't tell them.
-  Really?
- How many?
-  I think they got about three.
(Laughing)
- How did you know?
-  Really?
We got three.
How did you know?
I'm sorry about this. I was so surprised.
The bag is bulging.
- You're amazing.
-  You're lying, right?
We need to win this, Mi Joo.
How many have you done?
We're ruined.
(Blowing)
(It's a close game.)
(Kwang Soo attacks.)
(It fails.)
This is scary.
(Hitting)
(Jae Seok's attack almost had them lose a point.)
(Is that how you want to play it?)
(Hitting)
Wait. What are you doing?
What are you doing?
(I'm just returning the favour.)
(Blocking)
- That's cheating.
-  It's just...
- It's not cheating.
-  Where are they?
- It was a mistake.
-  You cheated.
- It's a penalty.
-  I'll receive the penalty.
- Okay.
-  Over here.
You can't eat from now on.
- This hand won't be able to eat.
-  Yes.
You can punish it with a slap.
(He hits the hand hard.)
It needs to learn a lesson.
That's it.
I won't use my right hand.
Help me out.
It's a penalty kick.
It's all right to have a goalkeeper.
- There's no point, then.
-  We can have a goalkeeper.
- Wait, give me your hand again.
-  Why?
(Fighting)
- You can't be there.
-  We need to have a goalkeeper.
(Kwang Soo gets ready for the penalty blow.)
(It's not on pause.)
(I'm concentrating hard, Mi Joo.)
(Kwang Soo catches them off guard.)
It moved.
It didn't. I was breathing out.
(Kwang Soo misses his penalty kick.)
It was from my nose.
(It becomes heated again.)
(Blowing)
(Half spitting)
(They keep cheating.)
It's so hard.
Mi Joo!
Throw-in.
(Then I'll throw it in.)
- That's cheating.
-  Isn't throw-in allowed?
- Throw-in isn't allowed?
-  It's a penalty.
- Penalty.
-  Penalty kick.
I'm tired.
(I won't let you.)
(Gripping)
(Poking)
(Jae Seok misses his penalty kick.)
(That's too much.)
I'm sorry.
- My goodness.
-  Is it usually like this?
(The game continues.)
(Gagging)
(He's out of breath.)
This is the end for Jae Seok.
(Now's the chance.)
(Kwang Soo succeeds.)
(Kwang Soo and Mi Joo win.)
Team Kwang Soo wins with a score of 1 to 0.
(They scored miraculously in the end.)
We will go back to the gym.
("Gather the Running Balls" is over.)
(The number of Running Balls each team gathered)
With the Running Balls that you gathered,
we will draw a lottery for Revival Cards with Ahn Gil Gang.
We won't tell you the result.
(Revival Cards could turn the final results around.)
(Who will be the lucky team?)
It's now time for the final mission.
The final mission is...
"The Link between You and Me".
- When we begin,
-  Link.
Running Women should go right.
Running Men should go left.
(The starting point for men and women are different?)
You can't see nor meet your partner.
(We can't meet our partners?)
Ladies will start Name Tag Elimination 10 minutes early.
After 10 minutes, men will start.
If your partner gets eliminated...
during the first 10 minutes,
you cannot participate in the game.
You cannot participate.
(It's a real link.)
(The result of the final mission depends on Running Women.)
(If the woman is eliminated, the man is eliminated instantly.)
- The whole team gets eliminated?
-  That's it.
If the man is eliminated, the woman will be eliminated as well.
Your lives are linked.
- The team gets eliminated.
-  We don't meet?
You can't meet.
(They win if they survive and stick their name tags on the overpass.)
Does revival apply to the whole team?
You'll be revived together.
If someone gets a hold of you, you need to go like this.
Like this.
You need to push and strip it as quickly as possible.
- Okay.
-  Speed is most important.
- You need to go like this.
-  From the sides? Okay.
You got it?
Only one survives in the end.
You need to betray them.
- Okay.
-  Don't trust anyone.
- You need to use full power.
-  Okay.
(Seok Jin and Moon Sook plan to use their power.)
(What?)
I ripped both sides of the Velcro.
(Moon Sook ripped his clothes as well.)
- Isn't this too harsh?
-  Oh, my.
Moon Sook. I'm worried for your team.
Do we have an extra t-shirt?
All right. Ladies will go right.
Will it be decided with one game?
(She's waiting impatiently.)
I'm nervous.
(She sighs heavily.)
(She looks around.)
(She's looking for a place to hide.)
(Her movements somewhat resembles Kwang Soo's.)
I won't fit in here. I'm done for.
I'll hit anyone who comes this way with this towel. Can I do that?
- Hitting isn't allowed.
-  Really?
(She might knock someone down.)
I'm not allowed to hit anyone?
I'll be hiding here.
I'm going to rip the name tag as soon as the door opens.
Can I knock them out and rip their name tags?
Can I?
(Running Women are ready.)
They're beginning. Okay.
Sa Yeon will be hard to beat.
(Sa Yeon needs to be eliminated.)
It will be chaotic on the men's side.
Sa Yeon needs to be eliminated.
I'm a little worried but Se Jeong is fast.
She seems to be good at sports.
Jae Suk is here to win.
(He's worried about Jae Suk.)
I hope Jong Kook gets eliminated.
(Jong Kook is warming up.)
She needs to choose her allies well.
If she pairs up with Jae Suk, they'll be unbeatable.
Hang in there.
(You have to hang in there to betray them.)
Jae Suk. Hang in there.
The ladies need to do well.
I need to survive until the end.
(Running Women are our hope.)
Running Women Name Tag Elimination will begin.
(Running Women Name Tag Elimination will begin.)
Five, four, three,
- Oh, my.
-  two and one.
The race begins.
I'm nervous.
(Where should I go?)
Which way should I go?
(She goes down the stairs.)
(Jae Suk appears.)
(Running)
Jae Suk.
(Jae Suk, join me.)
Where did she go?
(She is ambushed by Jae Suk.)
Wait.
(Let's talk this out first.)
Please don't forget me.
- I'm sorry.
-  Jae Suk. Wait.
Wait.
(She pushes her.)
- She's so strong.
-  Jae Suk.
(Se Jeong attacks back.)
Se Jeong, you have a Revival Card.
- I don't.
-  You do.
- Jae Suk.
-  She's so strong.
Jae Suk.
There's no good in beating a weak person.
I'm the weak person.
(Men's fate depend on the women's competition.)
She's so strong.
(She runs away.)
She's really strong.
(If Se Jeong's out, Jae Seok is also out automatically.)
(Where are Sa Yeon and Moon Sook?)
Be careful.
(Did the best players become allies?)
You'd better be careful from now on.
(She's being careful.)
(Ji Hyo and Jae Suk check each other out without attacking.)
- Jae Suk.
-  Where are you headed?
Will you take off my name tag? Do you have a Revival Card?
If I do, why would I be here?
I'd rather rest. Look at me sweating.
Let's not take off each other's name tag for now.
Will you take off mine?
(Okay, I'll trust you for now.)
(She catches them.)
(Sa Yeon and Moon Sook spot Ji Hyo and Jae Suk.)
(Let's go and attack them.)
(She turns off the light.)
(Tuna Lady turns off the light by mistake.)
(Goodness!)
She gave me a fright.
You startled me.
- Wow.
-  The game is nip and tuck now.
Where are the little ones? Only the strong players are here.
Let's start with the younger ones.
- The younger ones?
-  Whom should we become allies with?
Shall we get rid of...
- the weak ones first?
-  Let's do that.
- Shall we get rid of them first?
-  Then the four of us can fight.
Okay, then we'll play fairly.
Why don't we pair up and go this and that way?
- One should go that way.
-  We have to stay focused.
Let's play after we get rid of the weak ones.
- Do you promise?
-  Yes, I promise.
If you betray us, you'll have a hard time in your career.
Okay? Do you understand?
The 4 of us will attack the other 2.
It's okay because their male partners...
- Seok Jin has to win.
-  You have only three minutes left.
- Let's hurry.
-  Hurry up.
- Let's do it before men start.
-  Where are they?
- Do we go downstairs?
-  Yes.
- Let's go downstairs.
-  Okay.
You can't take off my name tag.
Then it won't be fun.
- My partner is Seok Jin.
-  Okay.
It's Seok Jin, I see.
Three minutes are left for Name Tag Elimination.
Three minutes?
(Do they still have three minutes left?)
Is the announcer drunk?
(Mi Joo is at risk, but why doesn't the time pass?)
He sounds drunk. How is that possible?
My moustache grew while we were waiting.
(Mi Joo, please stay alive.)
Brace yourself for today.
It's time now.
(The predators' partners are relaxed.)
Jae Suk.
I expect Sa Yeon to take off two name tags.
I think I should.
(What's the current situation at Running Women's race?)
(Se Jeong and Mi Joo formed an alliance.)
(They're startled.)
(I hear the others' breathing.)
What do we do?
- Sa Yeon, hurry up.
-  Okay.
(The predators slowly lay a siege.)
(Her name tag is exposed.)
(She slowly approaches.)
(She reaches her hand toward Moon Sook's name tag.)
(What are you doing?)
I just laid my hand there.
- I'm serious.
-  What are you doing?
You scared me.
Gosh.
If you don't keep your promise,
I'm going to say bad things about you everywhere.
(I'll get my chance again.)
(The predators are still looking for the weaker ones.)
Did you find them? Where are they?
(At that time)
(She reaches for Jae Suk this time.)
(Gosh)
(Tuna Lady, you shouldn't do that.)
- What's going on?
-  You can't do that.
- You can't do that.
- You can't do this.
-  Come on.
- I just wanted to try it.
-  Gosh.
How can I trust anyone in this world?
You can't do this.
I just wanted to try it.
Let's let Sa Yeon experience what it feels like.
I'm dizzy.
Gosh, I'm dizzy.
You started it.
I said I just wanted to try it.
(She tears it off.)
(Sa Yeon is out.)
Jong Kook is out, too.
(You have no mercy at all.)
- I'm sorry, Sa Yeon.
-  I'm sorry.
(Tuna Lady is out first.)
- Did you see that?
-  Sa Yeon is out.
(In that case...)
(Jong Kook and Sa Yeon are out.)
Jong Kook and Sa Yeon are out.
(Did I hear something wrong?)
No way.
(This is so futile.)
What's going on?
Jong Kook and Sa Yeon are out.
- What?
-  Jong Kook and Sa Yeon are out.
Who?
Jong Kook and Sa Yeon are out.
(Thank goodness.)
What on earth?
(This is so unexpected.)
- Jong Kook and Sa Yeon are out.
-  Wow.
A strong player is out. Who took off her name tag?
(Everyone seems happy to hear the strongest couple got eliminated.)
What if they have a Revival Card?
Jong Kook, you must head to prison now.
Can't I stay here?
This is the same as prison.
(He's sent to prison even before the race starts.)
- You must go now.
-  I can't believe it. What happened?
(What happened, Tuna Lady?)
Did you see what happened to Sa Yeon?
- Let's eliminate the others first.
-  Okay.
- It's for real, right?
-  Yes.
Running Men's Name Tag Elimination starts.
- Let's go upstairs.
-  Men's Name Tag Elimination starts.
- Men started, too.
-  Five, four...
- three...
-  Men also started.
- Men play their own game.
-  Right.
- We may be sent to prison suddenly.
-  Why?
We may be sent to prison if our partner's name tag is taken off.
I'm in trouble because of Seok Jin.
Running Men's Name Tag Elimination starts.
(Running Men's Name Tag Elimination starts.)
I must hide.
I didn't expect that to happen.
(Jae Suk's partner Haha is at risk.)
Which couple has a Revival Card?
- Seok Jin, did you hear the news?
-  Yes.
- Didn't Sa Yeon...
-  She got eliminated.
Don't suspect me.
- Don't suspect me, either.
-  I'm really not the one.
- Are you sure?
-  Yes.
- Do you have a Revival Card?
-  No.
Please don't run around.
- I'm dead if I get eliminated.
-  Really?
You know I only have four.
- Seok Jin.
-  Hey, Kwang Soo.
(Kwang Soo joins them.)
- Did you know Sa Yeon's eliminated?
-  Yes.
- Let's attack Haha first.
-  It doesn't matter.
-  Why?
He's partners with Jae Suk.
- Haha?
-  Yes.
This game is over once Jae Suk and Sa Yeon are eliminated.
Don't do anything foolish.
We must not.
- I'm being serious.
-  I'll keep my hands together.
I'm eliminated if you take off my name tag.
I'm really eliminated if you take off my name tag.
- Me too.
-  I'm being serious, Kwang Soo.
- I'm being serious.
-  Me too.
(Kwang Soo who always plays tricks)
(Seok Jin who's ready to follow)
(Gary who's sometimes an ace)
(The three of them team up.)
(Jae Suk's partner Haha is the first target.)
Which floor was Haha on?
He could be on the second floor.
He's either on 2nd or 3rd.
Kwang Soo and Mi Joo are out.
(Kwang Soo and Mi Joo are out.)
Who is out?
- Kwang Soo.
-  Kwang Soo.
Do you feel it's unfair?
Goodbye, Kwang Soo.
(Goodbye, Kwang Soo with his fingers locked.)
I'm locking my fingers because I'm embarrassed.
(He's sent to prison with his fingers locked.)
(One minute ago where Running Women are)
- Let's go.
-  Will we be here all night?
- Don't do it.
-  Let's go.
Will we be here all night?
(The predators are attacking the prey as a team.)
- Let's go.
-  You called us here.
Ji Hyo.
No.
(Their hunting starts.)
Ji Hyo.
(They show too much love to Mi Joo.)
(She screams.)
(The girls are at risk.)
No, don't do it!
- Oh my.
-  Tear it off.
That's right. Take it off.
(She tears the name tag.)
(Mi Joo is eliminated.)
- That was crazy.
-  I'm sorry.
Kwang Soo and Mi Joo are out.
(Kwang Soo and Mi Joo are eliminated.)
(What great news.)
Why are they eliminated?
Somebody must've ripped Mi Joo's name tag.
Se Jeong is impressive then.
Wow, she's impressive.
(What if Se Jeong wins at this rate?)
There's Kwang Soo.
Jae Seok and Se Jeong are out.
Goodness.
(Jae Seok is eliminated.)
I didn't do anything.
I was just about to start.
I was just...
(It was his quickest elimination.)
Gosh.
I was just about to run away.
I was about to get started.
You must head to prison.
I'm going to lose my mind.
No, don't.
Don't, don't.
(Playback of what happened)
No, don't do it.
- Why not?
-  I'm really exhausted.
(Se Jeong resists with all her might.)
(Tearing)
(But she failed.)
I'm sorry.
Goodness, it's so unfair.
Please let me participate for just two minutes.
You're already eliminated.
(Se Jeong, see you in prison.)
It must be fun.
(He wants to participate.)
I used to like it very much.
- Did you get the sign?
-  Yes, I did.
(Only three teams remain. They must stay alert at all times.)
(Ji Hyo has her back towards me.)
(She's off guard.)
(This is her perfect chance.)
Haha and Jae Suk are out.
- Who?
-  Haha and Jae Suk are out.
No way!
Gosh.
Goodness.
(What happened to her?)
Haha!
What was all this for?
That pretty girl...
(What did I do to Se Jeong?)
You must go see her now.
I'm about to cry. Can I cry here?
(Poor girl.)
Gosh, I can't believe this.
Gosh.
- This is unbelievable.
-  "This is unbelievable".
You must win.
- What is it?
-  It's over now.
Wait. Hold on.
Remove at least one more person, Jae Suk!
Remove Gary's name tag.
Stay still.
(They remove Haha's name tag.)
(Haha and Jae Suk are out.)
Who's left now?
(Only two couples survived.)
(Seok Jin and Moon Sook vs Ji Hyo and Gary)
Let's go for another round.
When three members cornered me, I was so scared.
- Right.
-  Right.
- Se Jeong.
-  I think it's reality.
I have been harassed by 6 members for the past 7 years.
- Gosh.
-  Se Jeong.
One person harassed six members.
(This is the truth.)
Gosh, that's ridiculous.
- Why?
-  You must tell the truth.
Who has the Revival Card?
- It's either Gary or Seok Jin.
-  It's one of those two.
- I think...
-  I think it's Gary...
because the way Ji Hyo acted was so suspicious.
- Ji Hyo is so crafty.
-  That crafty Ji Hyo...
- She's crafty.
-  Ji Hyo is so crafty!
She acted very strangely.
Ji Hyo is so crafty!
Gary has become a skilful actor now.
- Today,
-  He kept a poker face.
Gary and Ji Hyo looked strange today.
What about you? Do you have the Card?
If we had one, we'd be already out.
- That's right.
-  Okay.
Take some rest.
Okay. It was a hard day.
You should give up now.
Now, I'm a canned tuna.
(She is very exhausted.)
Then who are the ones that are still left?
Is it only Seok Jin's couple and us?
(Only 2 teams survived.)
Seok Jin should survive somehow.
What if we lose before we even start fighting?
(If either one is out, the couple fails.)
(Meanwhile, in the men's stadium...)
Gary, we must do something.
You're right.
Before Moon Sook finds Ji Hyo...
It's locked.
(Moon Sook, I trust you.)
(She spots Ji Hyo.)
(Seok Jin vs Gary)
(Moon Sook vs Ji Hyo)
(Their battle will determine the winning couple.)
Let me take yours.
I'll make you be in the spotlight today.
(Your future will be prosperous.)
(Will the fierce Moon Sook and Seok Jin win?)
(It won't be that easy.)
(This 7-year-old couple has great chemistry.)
(Will the Monday Couple have the honour of winning?)
(This final battle...)
(will determine the winner of today's match.)
(The couple to place their name tags on this overpass wins.)
(Who will be the final winners?)
(What?)
(Is that Gary?)
Ji Hyo, you did a good job.
You did a good job, too.
- Ji Hyo, as you said...
-  I said I was prepared.
Yes!
- Good!
-  Good job.
(During the final battle...)
(Ripping)
(Gary removed Seok Jin's name tag.)
(Moon Sook was a little late.)
It was close.
(Seok Jin and Moon Sook failed.)
- Seok Jin and Moon Sook are out.
-  Okay!
- It was so close.
-  Ji Hyo!
I'm sorry, Moon Sook.
(The couple who received the Revival Card...)
(was Gary and Ji Hyo.)
(Gary and Ji Hyo started the mission with the Revival Card in hand.)
(However, they won without using the Revival Card.)
(Gary and Ji Hyo are the final winning couple.)
I love that this show doesn't contain an inch of trust.
- I can't believe anyone.
-  Right.
I heard that it's you who started the betraying chain.
(The Running Women had a long day.)
- To the winning couple...
-  What is it?
(They receive a golden badge and a golden tiara.)
Thank you.
(Jealous)
It was...
Jae Suk!
Thank you.
(Thank you, Running Women, for joining us today.)
(3 late summer blockbusters)
Game of Emperor's Throne.
When the moon overlays the sun, the new emperor will be chosen.
(Lee Joon Gi, Kang Ha Neul and Hong Jong Hyun)
I will destroy them. You won't survive.
(There is 1 throne but 10 princes.)
(They fiercely struggle to hold the throne.)
The sun and the moon,
set us free!
(And...)
(the secret of the throne is revealed.)
(Who will travel through time and hold the throne?)
(Game of Emperor's Throne)
(Game of Emperor's Throne, Running Map and Train to Prison)