(Previously on Running Man...)
This is the last shooting with Gary.
I know. Goodness.
("Gary leaves Running Man to focus on his music.")
I support you in all of your endeavours.
- Good luck. - Okay.
I had a great time with all of you. Please take care.
Thank you.
(Like so, our beautiful goodbyes to Gary...)
(did not happen.)
(We wouldn't let him leave us so easily.)
- Gary! - Gary!
(Gary, we still need you.)
(We need Gary to fill in his lack of presence.)
It's Monday. Let's go for shooting.
My goodness.
(Let's begin Lack of Gary Trip.)
(At Dosan Park in Apgujeong)
(A week after Gary left, on a sunny day)
I was startled when I saw the preview.
So Gary believes he quit the show, but we haven't let him go, right?
Will he really show up today?
They made the preview very nicely. It made me so curious.
(Like so, our beautiful goodbyes to Gary...)
(did not happen.)
Stop it! Leave me alone.
You're so mean to me.
Will he really come?
Even if he does, he won't get paid, right?
- He'll be our guest. - A guest?
He'll get paid as a guest.
Thinking of our long friendship, he doesn't need to be paid.
Why don't you also...
get paid for only three episodes a month?
Gary quit voluntarily, so this must be a follow-up service instead.
- I see. - You got it?
He quit the show voluntarily.
- What is this? - He's here.
- Is he here to sell things? - What is that?
- Gosh. - Jae Seok.
(A mysterious street merchant, a local Jae Seok)
(If you are sad after Gary left, I'll make you happy.)
We won't buy any!
(We won't buy any!)
I said we don't need any!
I hate him.
- We don't need any. - Look at him.
- Is he a guide today? - What is that in your hand?
- It is... - Is he a guide for sightseeing?
- Everyone. - Yes?
- This is... - Is Gary inside?
(Gary to-go)
- That's ridiculous. - He's like a street merchant.
I think Gary will come out of it.
By the way,
I'll take you around...
Apgujeong-dong as your guide today.
We'll visit places where we have memories.
- Places with memories? - Yes.
You mean the places with your memories?
Our memories.
- Why do we have to go with you? - It must be just your memories.
I'll feed you and everything, so just follow me.
- Just follow me. - We have money for lunch.
Do we look like beggars?
- Seok Jin. - Yes
(He forces others to wear uniforms.)
- Ji Hyo. - Yes.
I might also have memories in those places.
- I think so. - Right.
Everyone, are you all sad after Gary left?
- I am. - Right, he's not here.
- Goodness. - I almost forgot.
- You all are cruel. - Goodness.
I knew it.
- So we prepared a race... - Yes.
where you can dispel the sadness.
It's called Lack of Gary Trip, "Get Some Air".
"Get Some Air"?
- Please just let him go. - Goodness.
- Gary... - Let him live freely.
- You're so clingy. - Just let him go!
We thought you all feel sad after he left.
So we prepared an Apgujeong Tour...
which Jae Seok recommended.
Before we begin...
(Look what we've prepared.)
There's a fixed plan.
- Chinese restaurant! - That's famous.
- You know this restaurant. - The food there is great.
I think you told me about it.
They ignored you, right?
- Right. - You have a sad memory there.
I cried a lot back then.
This is a place with a sad memory.
I wanted to go to this restaurant often,
- but I was financially strained. - The dishes there were expensive.
We couldn't go often because the food there was expensive.
This restaurant is well known for serving tasty dishes.
This is a cafe I went a lot.
- You know which one it is. - Which one is it?
What's the name of it?
I know! They have great cakes.
- You know, too, right? - I do. They have tasty cakes.
- Many celebrities visited there. - Right.
- There were so many celebrities. - Right.
Next, we'll go to a karaoke.
And it has become rare, but...
- Photo stickers? - Yes.
(So nostalgic)
It's widespread these days again.
- It's increasing. - Right.
We all have been to Han River. It's a must place for dates.
Wait a second.
(Jae Seok shouted directly at Seok Jin's ear.)
- Gosh. - Why are you using it?
Do you need it in the first place?
This is what other guides use.
- You all know that, right? - It's too loud.
I like that. Keep using it. It actually hides your mouth.
- You're right. - Covering his mouth looks better.
Why don't you use this, too? It will make your eyes look bigger.
(Speak for yourself.)
- Are you serious? - Yes. Get one, just like me.
My goodness.
Why don't you hide your ugly big nose with this?
- He's making a good use of it. - Hey, stop it.
Anyway, this is today's course.
- Okay. - We will visit a number of places.
I could've introduced more places, but I'm sad I can't.
I'm sorry that we don't have enough time to visit all those places.
You couldn't bring us there because we can't film the place.
(Because such places are not appropriate to broadcast.)
- Oh, was that what you meant? - What are you talking about?
- Am I wrong? - Such places aren't opened yet.
- I'm pretty sure they aren't. - Are you out of your mind?
- So they must be closed by now. - Anyway,
you must finish all the course in six hours.
- In 6 hours. - What? 6 hours?
After six hours,
you will be penalised according to the number of uncompleted courses.
Do we have missions in each place?
They penalise me more than my school teachers did.
We will provide you with...
money, a phone and a car for your mission.
- Really? That sounds nice. - Will you provide us a car, too?
As you know, lacking is the theme of today's tour,
so we will give you six dollars each.
Because as of 2016, the minimum wage in Korea is 6 dollars per hour.
As there are six of you, we will give you 36 dollars altogether.
36 dollars for all of us?
- Yes. - Are you serious?
- What can we do with 36 dollars? - We can barely pay for our lunch...
- with 36 dollars. - We can't pay all with 36 dollars.
The remaining battery of your phones is seven percent.
- Is it to represent the members? - Our phone?
- Are they serious about this? - For your car,
I'm sure that the petrol warning light is flashing.
- We don't have gas, either? - Why are you doing this?
Why are you so harsh?
- What's the reason? - Apgujeong is small. Let's walk.
- We have a time limit. - Ji Hyo's right.
- We have to move as fast as we can. - I see.
You have to pay for the parking if you decide to ride the car.
- Are you serious? - We can talk out of it.
What do you mean?
- Let's talk to the manager. - Don't park the car.
- Run the car around the place. - We don't have enough gas.
Let's keep one person in the car.
We don't have petrol.
People will take photos and report us.
Why don't we sell the car?
- Where can we sell it? - That's a good idea.
- It is a nice idea. - Let's sell the car...
Instead, you will be given a mission at each destination.
We will give you some advantages with the fees you need to pay...
if you successfully complete the mission.
Before the tour, let us take your wallets and phones.
- I need to check the stocks. - I didn't bring my wallet here.
- Are they serious? - Are they really taking our phones?
(The staff members collect their phones and wallets before the tour.)
- I didn't bring my wallet. - Why do you check my pocket?
- It will be really fun. - All right. Let's go.
- Let's go, everyone. - Don't betray us today.
I swear I won't.
- I'm not a thief. - Really?
I can't trust you.
(Will they be able to complete the tour without any problems?)
- Check the battery. - We're really running out of it.
- I mean check the petrol level. - We don't have much gas left.
- Is it nearly empty? - Yes, it is.
- We're running out of gas. - What we should do now is...
The phone's running out of battery. It has only 6 percent left.
- Turn it off for now. - Should I?
- Turn on the power saving mode. - Yes. I should.
Yes. Turn on the power saving mode. Keep the brightness to minimum.
All right.
I'm hungry. I'm really starving now.
How should we park the car?
I think they have valet parking.
We have to pay for it, too.
- We have a mission there. - Let's get in and see.
All right. Let's get in there.
(They arrived their first course, the Chinese restaurant.)
- This restaurant is really old. - Yes, it is.
- This restaurant is quite old. - I haven't been here for some time.
I remember this place.
- Hello. Good to see you. - Hello.
I feel hungry already.
- It smells really delicious. - I can smell the food already.
- Gosh. - The smell is really nice.
I want to eat a lot today.
Forget the price. The menus are worth every cent.
Before we begin, please choose the menu.
- You cannot enjoy if you care... - Do we have to choose one?
- What is this? - Please choose one.
- Is between A and B? - Yes, it is.
- Let's choose A. - A sounds better.
We must choose B, then.
We must choose the opposite of Kwang Soo's choice.
I want A.
Then let's choose A.
The Unlucky Trio chose A.
- What should we do? - Jae Seok.
Let's do rock-paper-scissors and let the winner choose.
- Okay. - Rock-paper-scissors?
- All right. - Rock-paper-scissors.
- Rock-paper-scissors. - Rock-paper-scissors.
- Rock-paper-scissors. - Who's the odd one?
- Jong Kook is the odd one. - You're the problem.
It's not ending because of you.
- Rock-paper-scissors. - Is it really my fault?
- Is it? - Okay.
(Finally,)
(Jae Seok and Seok Jin win.)
- Rock-paper-scissors. - Okay.
- Rock-paper-scissors. - Okay. I'll choose A.
(Seok Jin chooses menu A.)
Shall I open it now?
(It doesn't feel good...)
Menu A looks nice.
(Menu A is filled with typical Chinese Restaurant dishes.)
It looks good.
- Menu A is better than menu B. - Okay.
- Good job. - All right.
- I'll tell you the price. - Okay.
Menu A costs...
29 dollars.
(What?)
Menu A costs 29 dollars.
After paying, we would only have 7 dollars left.
- Wait. How about this menu? - How much is Menu B?
- Menu B costs 9 dollars. - Gosh.
- Wait. - I should've chose B instead of A.
- Must we eat the menu we choose? - Do we have to pay 29 dollars each?
- It's 29 dollars altogether. - Altogether? It sounds nice.
- Let's go for it. - Let's eat first and think later.
- Let's have an extra jjajangmyeon. - We must eat.
- No, we shouldn't. - I don't care any more.
No.
- No. - Let's eat first.
- Seok Jin chose it already. - No, we must not.
- What do you mean? - If you win a mission here,
you'll only have to pay half the price.
- Yes. - Now, it sounds good.
- Good. - Yes. We can afford it.
- All right. Let's eat. - By the way,
- Let's eat and think later. - this is the place where...
Seok Jin and I used to visit.
We ate here often.
Seok Jin, where did you live back then?
- Suyuri. - I lived in Suyuri.
Why did you come here in the first place?
I was living in Suyuri, too.
This is where the youngsters used to hang out.
It's like you, who live in Anyang, coming all the way to Apgujeong.
It's different. I don't come here to hang out.
You watched a movie with Kwang Soo last time. Didn't you?
- Yes, you did. - Oh, gosh.
You did, right? You were wearing a mask...
- My goodness. - and a hoodie to cover your face.
You were wearing shorts, too. Wasn't it you?
- How do you know that? - I was wearing shorts, but how?
- The photo doesn't show my shorts. - One of my friends told me.
A guy who certainly looked like Jong Kook was covering his face.
He knew right on the spot that it was you, Jong Kook.
- Our figures must be distinctive. - I guess so.
- Last time in Anyang, - Yes.
it was after shooting Running Man.
I was in Anyang. I covered myself with clothes completely...
- and entered a restaurant. - The one you usually go?
Yes. I was sure that I was completely covered,
but people recognised me. People laughed when they saw me.
I thought, "How do they know?"
I thought it was because of my stylist, who dyed his hair yellow.
So I blamed him. "People found out because of your hair colour!"
How did people really find out?
I had my name tag on my back.
(Everyone could find out who he was without any effort.)
- You covered yourself completely. - Yes. Completely with my clothes.
I was eating hot soup. I sweated a lot.
- Did you sweat? - Yes.
It was winter. I was wearing a thick winter jacket...
- with my name tag on. - That's why people laughed.
- Hello. - Thank you.
- I recognise you. - Do you still work here?
My goodness.
- Hello. - Do you still work here?
- How long have you worked here? - For 31 years.
- 31 years? - I know him.
He was the waiter here 20 years ago.
- Amazing. - Really.
- So he worked here for 31 years? - Unbelievable.
Thank you.
Gosh.
- Are you a manager now? - Yes. I'm in charge of this place.
- He's the manager now. - Of course.
He served us 20 years ago. I can still recognise his face.
- That's amazing. - Yes. I remember you, too.
- Do you remember us? - I'm on your side.
- You are? - Do you mean, you're our fan?
- He must be nervous. - He seems so.
- He is nervous. - Usually,
he's very calm and confident.
He must be nervous to stand in front of the camera.
When he said he was on Jae Seok and Seok Jin's side,
I first thought he was the substitute for Gary.
(It would've been surprising if he really was.)
- It's good to see him again. - It's really nice.
- You still serve your customers. - Back then,
we were not famous. You wouldn't remember us.
He may remember you as terrible customers.
- No, we weren't. - If 3 of you ordered only 1 dish...
We were so poor. We couldn't order many dishes.
- How did you know, Jong Kook? - I was correct, wasn't I?
I once visited here with 3 other friends and ordered only 2 dishes.
- It happened to me, too. - You didn't have enough money.
If you were poor, why did you come here in the first place?
- Am I wrong? - He came to eat jjajangmyeon.
- I wanted to eat jjajangmyeon. - Why did you come all the way here?
Also...
Their tangsuyuk looks different.
It looks sumptuous.
- It really is. - It looks delicious.
- Thank you. - All right. Let's eat.
- Can I have some? - This jjajangmyeon looks amazing.
- We have jjamppong, too. - This jjamppong looks delicious.
(They are served a full course of Chinese cuisine.)
- Do you want this? - Yes. Let's swap the dishes.
- We made the right decision. - Let's order another jjajangmyeon.
I want to taste both jjajangmyeon and jjamppong.
- Side dishes taste great, too. - Yes.
You can't have more than one bite.
- Can't I eat twice? Really? - Come on. I never tasted that one.
- I haven't eaten it yet. - You ate twice. Didn't you?
- Stop eating. - Ji Hyo, you should eat instead.
- I haven't even tasted it yet. - Seok Jin is acting greedy.
- You must stop eating this. - Let Haha eat.
Look. This dish is really small.
- Hurry up. - Stop eating, you jerk.
Did you just call me "jerk"?
- You had it already, Seok Jin. - Hey.
- Don't be greedy. Let Haha eat it. - What are you doing?
- Stop it. - Give it to Haha. He should try it.
- Haha. - You ate this jjamppong too much.
Hey. I haven't tasted it yet.
- Seok Jin. Let me eat some. - Here, Haha.
What do you mean? You ate this jjamppong already.
Don't you think you had enough?
- Please. - Hey. Stop it.
Stop it and wait there. I'll give you some.
Seok Jin, come on.
- That's enough. Go. - I'm 32 years old.
- You're 32? So what? - I'm as young as your son.
- That's too much. - Yes, I know.
- You can't be his son. No way. - Come on, Seok Jin.
- You're too old to be my son. - You know what I mean.
- Just give me some more. - All right.
- I'll give you more. - His son is in middle school.
Shall we order some extra rice and mix with the sauce?
- That sounds like a good idea. - I'm still hungry.
Is plain rice okay?
- It reminds me of my old days. - Your old days?
- Yes, let's go for rice. - When we were young,
few bowls of jjajangmyeon weren't enough to satisfy our hunger.
- So we ordered extra rice. - We mixed rice with sauce.
- That's right. - A cup of rice is one dollar.
We'll add it to your bill.
It costs only 50 cents if we pay half the price.
We must eat well for today.
This jjajang rice tastes delicious.
(They find it really delicious because they are hungry.)
(Goodness)
It was a great idea to order extra rice.
Have a taste. This tastes amazing.
This rice is so good.
(With 30 dollars, they find true happiness.)
- This tastes amazing. - It's delicious.
(Was jjajang rice always this good?)
- It's amazing. - This tastes really delicious.
How was your meal?
Not enough. The meal was too small.
It was great.
If you're done eating, then it's time to settle your bill.
- How much is it? - You have to pay 30 dollars.
- How much do we have now? - 36 dollars.
If you succeed this mission, you only have to pay half the price.
Will you accept the challenge?
- Yes. - Of course.
- We don't really have a choice. - That's right.
Doesn't it feel like something's missing without Gary?
Not really.
To be honest,
- this is much better. - There's more food to go around.
Gary eats a lot, too.
Gary likes jjajangmyeon.
He does.
For the half-price mission,
you'll have to...
(What do they have to do to get a discount on their lunch?)
You'll have to call Gary.
("We Want to Hear This")
You'll have to call Gary and get him to say something.
(We have to call Gary?)
(It's only been a week since we said goodbye to him.)
The phrase you have to get out of him is...
(What is it?)
- this. - "I want to do the show."
This won't be easy.
The battery's running out.
It already went down by one percent.
- We only have five percent left. - Let's do this.
I don't think it's impossible.
We should tell him we have a special guest.
- What about Seol Hyun? - Okay.
- Ji Hyo could pretend to be her. - Say hello to him.
He'll easily tell it's her.
- He'll know for sure. - Let's try it.
We have to come up with a proper plan first.
(30 seconds is the time limit.)
He might not pick up since he doesn't know this number.
Hello?
- Gary. - Gary.
Hello, Gary.
- We have Seol Hyun with us. - Hey, Gary.
Hello.
- Hello. - Where are you, Gary?
What are you up to?
I'm at my studio.
- You are? - Gary.
Seol Hyun came on the show as a special guest today.
I can't believe it.
- Are you serious? - Yes.
She wants to say hello.
Is Seol Hyun really there?
Hello.
(Hello.)
What was that?
That's Ji Hyo!
(That's Ji Hyo!)
I told you he'd know.
- Was that the best you could do? - Gosh, Ji Hyo.
It sounded nothing like Seol Hyun.
You have failed the mission.
We failed the mission.
I told you to plan ahead.
I told you.
- We failed? - We needed a plan.
We did have a plan.
You call that a plan?
- What was that? - "Hello." That was so you.
You're not going to fool anyone like that.
You have failed the mission. Would you like to try again?
- Yes. - Yes, of course.
If you want to try again,
you have to give us one of your belongings.
Take my jacket.
- Just one? - Yes.
- I'll give you this. - Take Jong Kook's jacket.
We should be upfront with Gary.
- Are we doing the same mission? - I think that'll be for the best.
- We should just ask him. - Go like this.
Gary. Listen carefully.
We want you to be on the show.
- How about you? Let's do that. - How about you?
- Get the answer out of him. - We're running low on battery.
We should ask him right away as soon as he picks up.
- Hello? - Gary.
- Yes? - Sorry we lied about Seol Hyun.
We'd like to tell you something.
- We don't have much time. - Ask him.
I want to do the show with you. How about you?
(I want to do the show with you. How about you?)
(Will Gary give them the answer they're looking for?)
I want to do the show with you. How about you?
(Laughing)
I want to do the show, too.
(Half-price mission successful.)
We did it.
- Thanks, Gary. - The phone's dying.
- Hang up. - I have to go, Gary.
- The phone's almost dead. - I'll call you later, Gary.
Just hang up.
The phone's running low on battery.
- We did it. - Nice.
(The 7-year-long friendship proved its worth.)
- That's how you do it. - Yes.
- He knows what we want. - We can read each other's minds.
- He read our mind. - The lunch bill is...
15 dollars with the discount.
- That's a lot of money saved. - Let's order jjajangmyeon.
(They got a discount for the food but not for the parking.)
- We need three dollars. - For the parking.
The parking fee is three dollars.
- Three dollars? - Can we get a discount?
- It'll be additional three dollars. - Thank you.
- Thank you. - Thank you for the food.
The parking fee got increased.
(Apgujeong Tour)
(The 2nd course is dessert in a cafe.)
Are we getting dessert now? This is nice.
We're eating again?
How much do we have left, Ji Hyo?
We have 18 dollars left.
- That's quite a lot. - We still have 18 dollars?
There's only 16km left on the gas.
Don't step on the brakes too hard.
- Apply pressure gradually. - This is going to be tight.
Can we get two dollars worth of gas?
This sure is a lacking trip.
My stomach isn't even full.
Is that the place? We're here.
- Jae Seok. - This place changed its name.
The parking is going to cost us all our money.
We shouldn't take the car, then.
Someone should stay here.
Do you think I enjoy doing this?
- Let's go. - They have delicious desserts.
I know this place.
- It looks pretty. - It does.
What do you call those things again?
They're called crepe cake.
- Crepe cake. - They're famous desserts.
- I love crepe cake. - Let's go.
They look delicious.
You have to choose between Table A and Table B.
What should we do?
- Let's go with Table A. - We should go with B this time.
- B is the good one. - Let's go with A.
- We should go with B. - They're trying to trick us.
- Let's go with Table A. - Let's do that.
(When in doubt, go against Kwang Soo's choice.)
I have a good feeling about this.
(The members choose Table A by the window.)
- This way. - Okay.
Look at this place.
- It still has the same decorations. - It does.
Did it look like this from long ago?
They didn't change anything.
- This place looks the same. - How are the two tables different?
(This place kept its memories over a long period of time.)
(The dessert menu for Table A is crepe cake and ice Americano.)
- Do we sit here? - "Window seats".
- We get a crepe cake. - This is good.
- This is good, right? - Two glasses of ice Americano.
- What's the other menu? - Go take a look.
What does it say?
This one is ice Americano and ice latte.
This is the better one.
- I told you. - This is nice.
- It's a lucky day. - I have a good feeling about today.
- The price of Table A's menu is... - How much is it?
- 19 dollars. - What?
Just kill us.
- Haha. - What?
Calm down, Haha.
- I lost my temper for a second. - 19 dollars?
Why are we in Apgujeong? We should've gone to Anyang.
How much did you say again?
What are you talking about?
This is 19 dollars, and we only have 18.
You know what? Once you put the desserts in your mouth...
- We'll be happy. - We have a soft spot for desserts.
- We're simple like that. - We are.
Again, there is a half-price mission.
- Before we start, - Give it to us.
- let's get the desserts in here. - I'm so hungry.
- Hello. - It looks good.
Hello. Thank you.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
It looks so good.
Can we get half of that for half the price?
(The layers of the crepe cake are full of sweet and fruity flavours.)
(The americano is full of rich flavours.)
(Just by looking, it melts the hearts of the customers.)
That's not how you eat it.
You're making us look bad.
I'll show you. Have you never eaten crepe cake?
- That's not how you do it. - That's too much.
- Stop it. - That's not how you eat it.
Please stop ruining it.
You have to cherish it the way it is.
(It's a war of forks.)
Just eat it whole.
- Move your fork. - You eat it like this.
Why'd you take it apart?
There's a reason why they're all stacked up.
You only eat one layer at once.
Stop ruining it.
- Just eat it. - Gosh.
- This is how you eat it. - Just eat your dessert.
Let's just finish it and get on our way.
I want to go home and rest.
Stop nagging me.
- I thought you were a travel guide. - Just buy another one to-go.
I've had enough of you.
(Jae Seok never had worse tourists.)
It's already gone.
- That was quick. - It's so good.
Hey. Put it down.
(Licking like a giraffe)
Seok Jin.
We have to share this.
- Don't hog the coffee. - You should respect the elderly.
I'm really thirsty.
This is sad.
(I'm the oldest one here in case you've forgotten.)
It's so good.
I wish I could have just one more bite.
(Quiet)
(He wants to say something.)
It's too strong.
(The cream tastes better when it's melted.)
Seok Jin just ate from the plate Kwang Soo licked on.
He was just licking on the plate.
Did you not know?
- I forgot about that. - He forgot about Kwang Soo.
He just ate from what Kwang Soo was licking on.
I know we're family and all, but...
Even my mum doesn't do that.
(Is that why it was melted?)
This is a fancy place. How did you afford it back then?
(He's flustered.)
We only ordered one.
He's so pretentious.
- Why did you used to come here? - This reminds me of the old days.
I wasn't well off, but when I came here,
I ordered two pieces of cake for take-out.
- You took them home? - Yes.
I'd take them home...
and finish them by myself.
(I ate them by myself.)
By yourself?
You didn't share with anyone?
My parents didn't like creamy food.
- They don't eat this kind of food. - So you ate them by yourself?
That's right.
You bought two pieces of cake just to enjoy them by yourself?
- You came all the way out here? - It's a long way from home.
You went through all the trouble to come out here?
- You came all the way from Suyuri? - That's right.
I didn't live in Gangnam back then.
I remember an episode from the old days.
We were at a cafe in Apgujeong, and he asked me to lend him my car.
Why all of a sudden?
He came back after a while.
I had to change the engine the day after.
- Why? - The thing is...
- It was an old car. - My car was really old.
You weren't supposed to go over 50km per hour.
- That's ridiculous. - He went over 70km per hour.
- That destroyed the engine? - I told him.
Jae Seok. I'll lend you the car, but you shouldn't go over 50km per hour.
You can't call something like that a car.
- It was such an old car. - That's a sad story.
It was a really old car.
When he bought the used car,
it was already on the verge of getting scrapped.
I was almost broke, but I had to get a new engine.
- You did that? - On a used car.
You were just unlucky.
What are you talking about?
- You were speeding. - I wasn't.
Do you feel like you're missing something?
- Yes. - Yes.
It's such a tight budget.
A piece of cake is too small to share with six people.
- We may fight over it. - And...
the van will stop soon. It can run only about 10km.
I see. You mean we must be missing Gary because there are only six.
I forgot him again.
It's good to be without him when eating.
For the chance for half price, you'll do the same.
- Call Gary. - Again?
We said goodbye to Gary last week.
I even cried.
She cried.
Kwang Soo also cried after the shooting.
I don't understand why you cried and made a scene.
He cried that night.
- Why? - He cried alone a lot.
He wailed.
Why did you?
When it became dark...
I sent Kwang Soo a photo of all of us...
and he sent me a photo of himself crying.
- What are you doing? - Are you showing off?
You're just showing off. It's not because you're sad.
You broke up with a girl, didn't you?
Why do you bring that up suddenly?
Call Gary this time...
and pass the speed quiz.
You should get 6 answers in 60 seconds to pass.
It's about capitals.
We can say Seoul is "this" of Korea.
No. He should answer the capitals of the countries.
"Capitals" is the subject.
- Is it the subject? - What was he thinking?
- Subjects like animals or capitals. - Wasn't it the first question?
(He's now too old to understand the rule at one try.)
What are you talking about?
- Gary! - Gary!
- It's a quiz about capitals. - A speed quiz.
What's the capital of Germany?
Pardon? Please say one more time.
- The capital of Germany? - Yes.
- Berlin? - Correct.
What's the capital of Kenya?
(It's a difficult one.)
Isn't it Kenya?
- No. - No.
That city reminds me of an old man in a lobby in Korean.
Bragging?
(It's a creative yet wrong answer.)
It's not Niagara.
An old man in a lobby.
(It's a childish hint.)
It has three syllables.
- Naironi. - No, it's not.
- A lobby. - I said a lobby.
- Oh, Nairobi. - That's correct.
What's the capital of Egypt?
- The capital of Egypt? - Yes.
It's over.
I don't know what it is.
- Think of the Blue Marble game. - He doesn't know.
- Think of Kai of EXO. - Kai.
- Kai? - It sounds like "Let's go to Kai."
(The hints are ridiculous.)
Your challenge failed.
- You failed. - Gosh, Gary.
- It's too difficult for Gary. - Too difficult.
- It's hard. - Sorry, Gary. We have to go.
Gary, I'm sorry. We're running out of battery.
Pick up the phone quickly.
This is driving me crazy.
We'll try again.
Only three percent of the battery is left.
Frankly, it's too hard for him.
- It was too difficult. - It sure was.
- We've seen Gary for a long time. - Let Seok Jin answer this.
(The phone rings.)
- It's Gary. - Why did he call?
- We don't have enough battery. - Gary, we don't have battery.
What is it, Gary?
What are you guys doing?
Sorry.
- Gary. - Just do as we tell you to.
Pick up the phone quickly. You're not busy on Mondays.
- Gary. - Hang up. We're running out.
I think you want to join the shooting, don't you?
Since you called us back.
- You want to, right? - I'm curious.
- You must be. - He says he's curious.
We can't talk for long but I'll call again.
Answer your phone quickly.
Bye.
If you give me an item, I'll give you another chance.
- What should we give him? - A coat.
Give him mine.
(An item gives you another chance.)
We don't have anything to give other than that.
It's the second chance.
(Second challenge starts.)
- Hello. - It's food.
- It's difficult. - Gary.
- It's pasta made with garlic. - With oil.
- How does he know? - It's a type of oil pasta.
It's made with garlic.
- You know this. - Four syllables.
Made with oil.
- What? - Goodness.
Something Lee Sun Kyun makes.
- He only eats Korean noodles. - Lee Sun Kyun?
Gary, it sounds like Ali.
- Aglio olio. - It sounds like Ali or oli.
Aglio olio.
Is it aglio olio?
- Yes, aglio olio. - Is it correct?
These foods are too difficult.
It's salad made of two words.
- Two words? - Named after the emperor of Rome.
The salad the emperor of Rome liked.
The salad the emperor of Rome liked?
The pronunciation is similar to "I hate it" in Korean.
- Caesar? - Right. Okay.
- This is crazy. - I don't feel like doing it.
I've never heard of this kind of pizza.
I've never heard of margherita pizza.
- What is this? - Margherita?
Gary, we have to cancel this.
This is too hard. How could he know margherita pizza?
- Try to explain it. - And there's not much Gary knows.
- This is difficult to answer. - How does he know aglio olio?
What's wrong with aglio olio?
Just give him another coat.
(Haha gives his coat.)
Seok Jin never gives up his.
I'm cold.
(It's the third challenge.)
What's the Korean noodles you eat at a party?
- Janchi guksu? - No, no.
- You're not doing it right. - Come on.
It's food made with glass noodles.
- Oh, japchae. - Correct.
What's cream pasta with bacon?
The name sounds like laughter.
- Carbonara? - That's right.
This is something I really like.
- It's kimchi made with cucumbers. - It's made with cucumbers.
Pickled cucumbers?
No. It's kimchi.
(The hints are too obvious.)
It's kimchi.
- Cucumber kimchi. - That's right.
What's japchae made with chilli peppers?
- Chilli pepper japchae. - Correct.
- Explain well. - What's gimbap from Chungmu?
Gimbap you eat in Chungmu.
- Chungmu gimbap. - There you go.
What's the traditional cookie you like?
The pronunciation itself sounds like "weak cookies".
- Not strong but weak cookies. - It's yakgwa.
- Yakgwa is right. - Okay.
What's something similar to sujeonggwa?
Birak is the famous brand for this.
- Sikhye. - Okay.
- Time's up. - We made it.
The mission is cleared.
(They can pay only half.)
- I liked your explanation. - Thank you.
(Kwang Soo's explanation was the best.)
Since you cleared the mission, you can pay only half of 19 dollars.
It's 8 dollars and 50 cents, then.
No, it's 9 dollars and 50 cents.
(Math isn't his strong point.)
Math has...
Seok Jin, just go home.
- Drink something and go home. - Math has changed a lot.
If we spend almost 10 dollars and pay for valet parking...
We need to fill our van with gas, too.
Could you give us an extra hour to earn some money?
We're extremely short of money.
This is too harsh.
We should sell our autographs.
It's not just lack of money. We're in poverty.
I don't think it is appropriate but...
can't you just take some money from them?
(Go back to your old self.)
I know it's not appropriate but...
For now, we can go to the next destination with the gas.
(I have an idea.)
I know an inexpensive gas station.
It is difficult to drive to the gas station.
(We all know those kinds of stations.)
There are a lot in our neighbourhood.
There is one near Ilsan that is far away from here.
- I know one, too. - There is one near Jayuro.
There must be one near Jayuro.
The gas price in Cheongju is really low.
Do you think they'll give us?
(They leave for the third destination.)
How much is it for valet parking?
- It's 3 dollars. - Why is valet parking so expensive?
- It's so expensive. - I can't believe it's 3 dollars.
(They have 5 dollars and 68 cents.)
If we're out of gas, we'll leave this van behind.
We only have 5 dollars.
It's not fair for us to pay for valet parking.
- Give the money for valet parking. - Right.
I feel nervous without money.
(They head for karaoke.)
We can go 10km more.
(The gas gauge makes them nervous.)
- I feel uneasy. - How about asking Gary...
to use this van for a while?
- We're short of gas. - Let him fill this up.
We did all give him gifts last week.
(Gary should pay us back.)
I thought Gary had prepared something, too.
You're supposed to park your car in a parking lot.
- Is there a parking lot? - Yes.
We don't need valet parking service.
What are you talking about? We need to pay a parking fee, too.
It can be free if we use the karaoke.
- Free? - That's possible.
It would be free if they validated parking.
That sounds possible.
(They need to save every dollar.)
Do they validate parking?
- Is it free if we get it stamped? - Yes, for an hour.
- An hour? - Okay. Thank you.
- Hello. - Hello.
This is the third destination.
We're at a karaoke.
This mission is called "Score 1,000".
("Score 1,000")
To move to the next destination, you have to gather 1,000 points.
You can use Sing to Gary Cards here.
- What is it? - What is that?
While other members are singing,
each of you will go see Gary...
and do the Sing Along Relay.
We'll give each of you two dollars if you succeed.
(They'll get 2 dollars every time they succeed.)
Then we can earn up to 12 dollars.
We should locate Gary first.
Hand me the phone.
I'll call Gary.
(It is critical to find out Gary's location.)
Gary, this is Seok Jin. Where are you now?
At your workroom?
- At his studio? - I see. I just wanted to know.
(He is so obvious again.)
I'll go.
- Hurry up. - Come back in a hurry.
(He goes to see Gary.)
If you eat something, we'll notice right away.
- All right. - Please don't.
Is this the way out?
(The time assigned at the karaoke is 30 minutes. He should hurry.)
- Where are the microphones? - Where are they?
(The mission begins.)
Here are the microphones.
What is "Fear"?
It's a song by Mino.
(They choose "Fear" without fear.)
(His voice is too low.)
I think you're out of tune.
I think it's off key.
(Jae Seok is worse than Haha.)
(He raps with the groove.)
I bet he thinks he's doing well.
(We didn't know...)
(that we had hip hop running through our veins.)
(They're copying everything they can.)
(Tae Yang's part is approaching.)
(I am a Tae Yang of Running Man.)
(They missed their cue.)
(Look at these two.)
(The two guys in their 40s are attacking us with hip hop.)
(Their singing makes others full of fear.)
(But they seem to be very satisfied with themselves.)
(They're hurting our eyes and ears.)
(He screams.)
(The 4 minutes felt like 40 minutes.)
What are you guys doing?
- The score is 86. - We sang so well.
It's a high score.
You should start singing the next song already.
Hurry up.
(Seok Jin finally arrives at Gary's studio.)
I'm sorry, Gary.
You quit Running Man,
but that doesn't mean we allowed you to quit.
You're still in our hearts.
Where's the doorbell?
(Will he meet Gary and accomplish the mission?)
(Gary's friend, DJ Panda)
- Hello. - Gary.
(He hasn't seen Gary for a week and missed calling his name.)
I'm sorry, Gary. I'm sorry.
Gary, you're on Running Man.
Today is Monday. We have to shoot Running Man.
- Why are you still here? - You startled me.
- You startled me. - Why are you still here?
Today is Monday. Let's go shoot.
Wait a minute. This is so hectic.
- What's going on? - It might be over for Gary,
but it's not over for us yet.
Gary is always in our hearts on Mondays. Let's go.
I quit Running Man last week.
- Why are you here? - I know you quit.
We don't have much time, so please help us.
- What's going on? - Listen.
Ring, ring, ring, ring
(You've been on Running Man long enough. What's the answer?)
Shrug, shrug
All right, we got it, right?
(Seok Jin succeeds.)
- Was that it? - They will keep coming.
- Here? - Yes.
- Gary. - Please let me work.
Gary, Running Man may be over for you,
but you're still with us in our hearts.
- Gary. - It's good to see you but...
- I'll be back every week. - It isn't awkward, though.
Right? Ring, ring, ring, ring
Shrug, shrug
Okay!
Thanks to you, I earned two dollars.
Did we succeed?
- Yes, we did. Thank you. - Where are you headed?
- I don't have time right now. - Are all of you nearby?
- Yes. - Really?
We keep wandering around your area.
We keep wandering around.
You keep calling me, so I can't have my meeting.
I know you quit, but we think you're still with us.
- Keep that in mind. - Goodness.
(They're engrossed in singing that they don't care about Gary.)
Keep falling
(Excited)
(Unfortunately, they don't have enough swag to sing the song.)
(Do you know hip hop?)
You feel pain
(The others who watch them feel embarrassed for them.)
(Jong Kook joins the group.)
(The singing gets more exciting.)
(Kwang Soo ruins the mood.)
(Let it be a high score.)
What's the score?
(The score is 98.)
- We're so good. - We're almost there.
This is a great place.
- Where is Seok Jin? - This karaoke gives high scores.
- What's "Footsteps"? - That's Kwang Soo's favourite.
What kind of song is this?
This is Kwang Soo's favourite song.
- What are you doing? - Kwang Soo.
He always sings this when he's in love with someone.
It's "Footsteps".
(He dedicates this song to her.)
I wonder who she is.
(As the sun sets, the footsteps lead me)
(He's completely absorbed.)
This song is...
one of the top five men's favourite songs.
It's a song by Emerald Castle.
I wonder if I still have
(For now, forget about the Kwang Soo we know.)
(At this moment, he's a real man.)
The time
- Press 503. - This song?
(The others aren't listening to his singing.)
I'll sing "Last Love" next.
I believed
Even that was
Seok Jin is back.
You're up next, Haha. I made it.
- Haha, you should go now. - Who's up next?
- Go, Haha. - What did you bring?
Gary gave it to me. Can't we eat it?
- Gary gave it to me. - Go, Haha.
(Kwang Soo's song reaches its climax.)
From the beginning
(Kwang Soo wanted to sing the refrain.)
No! No!
(Laughing)
Please!
(The tour guide, Jae Seok, does all the main parts.)
Didn't we shoot Running Man here before?
(Knocking)
Who is it?
Goodness, please stop coming.
- Hello. - Why did you lose so much weight?
Did I?
- Gary. - What?
I told you last week that I wanted to see how you were doing.
- We also talked two days ago. - Since I cried...
and said farewell, shouldn't it be over?
It goes up and down, then repeat
(The answer is "Joy and sorrow repeat".)
Joy and sorrow repeat
- Bye. - Are you leaving already?
Have a drink before you go.
I have to go back to the other members.
- You'll just leave? - You're still on the show,
so don't move out of the studio without our permission.
- We still need you. - Okay.
- I'm leaving now. - See you.
(At the karaoke, the members are singing terribly.)
(He exaggerates his movements while singing the high note.)
(Kwang Soo, please stop singing.)
(Jae Seok reserves the next song to save time.)
(He pretends to look good.)
We have 11 minutes left. What's next?
- How much time do we have? - It's 93.
- That's amazing. - We must hurry.
Jae Seok, Gary's studio is farther than you think.
You must go now.
You don't have time to say hello. I started the mission right away.
- Go now. Hurry. - Jae Seok, you should sing.
Okay.
Don't say hello. Just start as soon as you get there.
Gosh, I wanted to sing the next song.
I must choose a song that Gary would know.
(He'll sing a song that Gary knows.)
I don't have time. Gary.
The song goes... Oh, hello. Gary.
You seem so compassionate
(The answer is, "So I like you".)
So I... What did you say?
Come on, Gary.
- You seem so compassionate - So I
Hold on, it's your song, "Your Scent".
Don't you know your own song, "Your Scent"?
Gosh, what's wrong with you?
Seriously, what's wrong with you?
I can't remember the lyrics out of the blue.
What? What's wrong with you?
Can you give me another chance?
Please give us another chance.
Please, Kwang Soo came all the way here.
Then take off your shoes.
- Okay. - Take off your shoes.
- Wear these. - Give us your shoe.
- What? - Give us your shoe.
You're taking my shoe away again?
If you want another chance, you must give us your belonging.
- He used to betray me on the show. - Why should I?
Now that I'm in this position, I feel so much at ease.
This is so unfair.
(Is this necessary?)
- Did you not sing on purpose? - No, I really couldn't remember.
- May I take these slippers? - Yes.
(He gives up a shoe and gets another chance.)
Gosh.
Until that day when Mount Baekdu is worn away
And the East Sea's waters run dry
- You should have done this sooner. - Ouch!
Why didn't you sing earlier?
He always attacks me instead of thanking me.
- Are you leaving? - Gary.
I'm not smiling because I'm happy.
(With 3 hours 24 minutes left, here's what's going on.)
(They tired themselves out too much in the beginning.)
(Everyone seems tired.)
What's the score?
- Here it is. - Here it is.
Here comes the score.
Kwang Soo is back.
- We only have a minute left. - I'll do it.
- Here. - Let's stop now.
If you fail, you have to give them something.
- What? - They took my shoe.
- Why? - Why did you fail?
Gary didn't remember the lyrics to "Your Scent".
- Really? - Give us more time.
- Come on. - You were so close.
The total score is 946.
If we didn't fail that time, we would have made it.
Don't karaokes usually give extra minutes?
We'll give you 30 minutes for 3 dollars.
I'll go to Gary's studio.
Go, Jong Kook.
- I'll get going. - Sing something easy, okay?
- Is he in the studio? - Yes.
- It's so far away. - Gosh.
Ji Hyo, you should sing.
It'll take Jong Kook...
- about 15 minutes. - Goodness.
Is it okay for us...
to keep visiting Gary when he said farewell last week?
He seemed flustered.
Wasn't he happy to see you?
He was.
(He was still happy to see us.)
(Aren't you happy to see me again, Gary?)
- You're lovely - There we go.
We made it, didn't we?
- When Dad goes to work - Kiss, kiss, kiss
Wasn't that too easy?
- He's back. - We should sing...
- Hello. - Are you back already?
- I wasn't that fast. - You should sing now.
(With 5 members succeeding, they earned a total of 10 dollars.)
(The last member to visit is...)
Gosh, Gary.
(It's Ji Hyo's turn.)
Last week,
I cried a lot when we said goodbye.
It's so embarrassing to see him again.
(Who knew they would meet again so soon?)
(She wanted to stay strong, but she couldn't.)
I'm sad to see you leave, Gary.
I support you in all of your endeavours. Good luck.
(So are you doing well?)
- Gary! - Hey.
- Gary! - Who's this?
- Gary, how have you been? - Ji Hyo.
- Hello. - How have you been?
(He looks awkward to see her again.)
How are things going?
Why aren't you wearing the clothes? Put them on now.
- Don't say that. - Let's go to work.
Hurry up.
Take a seat, Ji Hyo.
You should take a break.
To be honest,
it was very embarrassing to come here.
- Why? - I cried a lot last week.
- It's too early to meet again. - You...
When we met in private, you cried more.
That was...
She didn't say a word for 20 minutes when we met in private.
I really cried a lot that time.
- I texted him because I was angry. - I thought...
I thought she cried because she was sad to see me go.
She cried because she was angry.
I was upset.
She was thinking, "This jerk..."
Ji Hyo, how are things going?
I'm curious to know which team's winning.
There are no teams today. We are all poor together.
So we all need to earn money today together.
- Is this a group game? - Yes. Do you have some money?
(Do you have some money?)
Don't you have any money?
Do you have a lot of money?
I do have money.
How much do you have? Let me see.
- I actually have some money. - Gary.
Give me the bill that has a different colour from the rest.
- Do you mean this one? - Yes. That one.
- This isn't a 50-dollar bill. - I know it's not.
- This is fine. - Is a five-dollar bill okay?
A five-dollar bill is fine. It's already mine.
If I could, I want to give the whole wallet to you.
- Ji Hyo, will you marry me? - Come on, Gary.
- Is this how we'll meet every week? - I think so.
I was feeling...
a bit nervous when I came to see you.
(I was nervous to come see you again.)
(Ji Hyo, by any chance...)
Do you want to go back to being Monday Couple again?
- No. - Okay.
The girl who can't say goodbye
The boy who can't leave
We don't love each other
So we can't be together
Is that it?
Was it a mission?
Let go. I thought you were singing it for me.
Now that you're done with this, are you going to leave me now?
Are you going to call me next time when you record the show?
Put on your outfit already.
(Everyone succeeds in Sing Along Relay.)
- Didn't everyone succeed? - We all succeed.
This is a hit among senior citizens.
(The game is over, but karaoke isn't.)
Let's hurry.
(Hold on. He begins to sing passionately.)
Whose song is this?
(She stops the song.)
I feel empty
(You are the guide. Lead the way.)
Ji Hyo, I should...
- finish the song at least. - Ji Hyo is so decisive.
I need to finish singing the song.
- Ji Hyo. - You are determined, Ji Hyo.
Jae Seok, you should sing it while we're moving.
- You can sing it in the car. - Let's go to Andong Station.
Use that microphone.
(Sing Along Relay is completed.)
(Moving onto the mission at Photo Zone)
Is this it?
- There's a photo booth right here. - The photo booth's here.
- It's here. - It's right here.
It's been so long since I've been here.
I've never taken pictures here even when I was young.
- How much is it? - They're starting to turn up now.
- Yes, they are trending again. - I only took my passport photo.
You've never taken pictures at the booth?
- Only for my passport picture. - How much is it?
In order to take the photo, it costs four dollars.
No. I won't take it, then.
- Isn't it two dollars? - Is it that expensive?
The price went up.
- Sir. - Four dollars is a lot.
- Again, there is another mission. - What is it?
With this mission, you can get a full refund.
- This is great. - We have to get this.
- Let's go. - Now we are talking.
Take a picture from this booth.
If you manage to put a picture on the back of Gary's phone,
we will give you a full refund.
If you are going to keep bringing him in, then reinstate him.
- Let's just bring him back. - This is too much.
It'll be better to just hire him again.
Do we have to do it in secret?
- Did you say it's four dollars? - It's expensive.
- Come on. - It must really cost four dollars.
It's been a while, though.
- The photo will be so bright. - Ji Hyo should be in the middle.
- Should I be in the middle? - Let me go to the back.
It's been a long time since I took a photo here.
- Hit the button for a clear photo. - Come in.
We can even write 7012 on the photo.
Is that so? Then we have to write it down.
- Lower yourselves a little. - Make sure everyone's in the frame.
- Hey. - The camera...
- Move back a little. - I can't see myself.
- Move a little. - Sit down.
Move back.
Okay. We're ready.
(Everyone's crammed into the frame.)
Smile.
(Smile)
One more.
(They are the cutest.)
That was good.
Do a different pose.
(There is even a spot for Gary.)
What is that?
How many takes do we have left?
Two more takes left.
You stood up right before the photo was taken.
- We have to choose four photos. - That's it.
- We have to choose the pictures. - That's what the number was for.
This one...
- Not that one. - Stop that.
How can you choose that one?
Why would you pick that photo?
Come on.
- You can't even see me. - Let's decorate.
- I'll decorate it. - Hey, you.
- Hey. - That's great.
- That looks nice. - What are you doing?
- Why are you drawing that? - That's good.
What kind of a picture is that?
I want to have one, too.
That's not a runny nose.
It looks like a noodle's coming out of my nose.
- The tour with Jae Seok is not bad. - It's not bad, right?
- This is fun. - That's right.
- Let's go to Gary. - Let's stick it on his phone.
- How does that sound? - Great. Let's go.
- Should we go to his studio? - Yes, let's go to the studio.
- Let's go. - Let's raid his place.
- Is it okay to go, though? - If people saw us...
How many times are we going to his place today?
I think we are being a bit too clingy.
I feel sorry for Gary now.
It's like we're going there...
- after a breakup. - Exactly.
This is just like his song,
"Can't Breakup Girl, Can't Breakaway Boy".
It's the same as calling and going to the house after breaking up.
It's like keep clinging onto that person.
(You are watching how the song is turning into a reality.)
Jae Seok.
Why is there a dog?
- A dog? - This dog is really cute.
Gary, what is this dog doing here?
- This dog is really cute. - Why are you...
This looks like a cat.
Why is there a dog?
What kind of breed is this?
Gary, we feel sorry to barge in like this.
- No, that's okay. I like it. - What were you doing? It's Monday.
You look a bit down than before.
You are bugging me a little.
Are you sure it's not a cat?
- Isn't the dog cute? - Isn't the dog the cutest?
- The dog is so gentle. - I really like this dog.
The dog is so calm in Jong Kook's arms.
- Is the dog violent? - Hurry up.
No, the dog's not violent.
This is Gary's wallet.
This is his laptop.
Get someone to put the photo on his phone.
Let's put the photos on his stuff.
That's it. This is great.
(She sticks a photo on the laptop, and he puts one inside his wallet.)
I don't know if he's going to take these off later.
(The sticky photos are papered all over Gary's belongings.)
Can you spot it easily?
(Even his phone is papered with the photo.)
Didn't you stick it upside down?
7012.
It's 7, 0, 1 and 2.
(They complete the mission and manage to get a full refund.)
(Pet lover Jong Kook has no interest in the mission.)
- The dog was about to fall asleep. - Sorry.
Hey, try to treat your colleagues like this.
- Do you hear me? - This is a new side of him.
Have you ever treated Kwang Soo this way?
I'm no better than a dog.
- You've never been nice to them. - Hey.
It's because you don't look as cute as this dog.
I kind of look like a dog.
Come here. I'll take care of you.
(Come here, my little puppy.)
No. Don't treat me like this.
I'm doing it exactly the same.
- This is not what I meant. - This is the same.
I mean this is...
- He looks very comfortable. - Seriously,
you can be loved, too.
Is it a male?
- Yes, it's a male dog. - Were you scared?
Did they scare you?
- My goodness. - Why?
- I think the dog is scared of you. - Jong Kook,
you scared me.
Goodbye.
Come here.
(Barking)
(Apparently, the dog can treat people differently.)
- The dog almost bit you. - Usually,
this dog doesn't bark.
- The dog really almost bit him. - Did you see that?
Did you see how the dog moved away from him?
The dog barked.
The dog is really adorable.
- The dog is really cute, indeed. - Okay, we should get going.
Should I go stand in my spot?
We just came to say hi.
Is that really it?
There are no secret missions, right?
We completed all the missions before.
- Let's go. - We're going now.
Hey, Haha.
- We came because we felt sorry. - I'll walk you out.
- No, that's fine. - We really came to greet you.
You really don't have a secret mission?
- Is this it? - Yes.
If you want something to eat, let me know in advance next time.
It's only finished when the show is finished.
(Mission at the photo booth is completed.)
(Next stop is Han River.)
If we go at this pace, the parking fee will be expensive.
- I forgot about that. - That's right.
- Here's our ticket. - We still have to pay a little.
The first hour is free.
- So the fee will be two dollars. - Is it?
- It's only 2 dollars. - It's good the 1st hour was free.
- Thank you. - Bye.
We even have a five-dollar bill.
- Ji Hyo, we need more gas. - She is so economical.
- Jae Seok. - Yes?
Isn't it embarrassing to put in only a litre?
- We have no other choice. - What are you going to say?
We just need to say we only want two dollars worth of gas.
Here you go.
- Ji Hyo, you are embarrassed, too. - You need to do it.
It will only literally take one second to fill the gas.
It'll take not even one second.
- The gas is expensive here. - Yes, it is.
- We could use our coins. - We need diesel.
- Hello, aren't you Jae Seok? - Hello.
We only have two dollars for the gas.
- Only two dollars? - Please.
I'm sorry.
(You must feel baffled.)
You must feel baffled. I'm sorry.
I apologise. We don't have enough money.
It's done already.
- Is it done? - It's all done.
He put in 1.2 litres.
Wow. That was more than I expected.
- With 1.2 litres... - How far can you go with that?
- Why isn't the arrow moving? - It will.
- Did he put the gas already? - He did.
- The arrow will move soon. - Did he put some?
- Can you check one more time? - Was it two dollars worth of gas?
That won't even get a free water, right?
Forget I asked.
- That's okay. We'll come back. - We'll put in a lot of gas, then.
But he did bring the free water bottle out.
- Please, just take it. - No, you don't need to.
We'll be okay. That's fine.
Okay, then. Thank you.
- I'm sorry. - Goodbye.
- I feel bad. - I was getting thirsty.
I feel horrible.
Pass the bottle after you're done.
But I don't think the arrow's moving.
- I'm sure they put in the gas. - Can we move at least 6km?
- The car won't stop, though, right? - No, it won't.
That extra litre makes me feel relieved.
- I do feel different. - I feel like the car got stronger.
- He gave us more than a litre. - It was 1.29 litres.
But I...
don't feel like Gary left the show since I saw him today.
I know.
We said goodbye last week and here we are again.
It feels like just another mission.
(Right, Gary?)
(Seok Jin falls asleep...)
Stop that.
(on his way to meet Gary again.)
Do you think the car will stop midway?
No. I doubt it.
(He's looking for Gary in his sleep.)
(Glancing)
Sir, you can't sleep there.
(Is that you, Gary?)
(You're not Gary.)
We're supposed to be working here.
- He fell asleep? - I told you we're low on gas.
Couldn't you wake me up more gently? You scared me.
I was wondering why it was so quiet.
Were you sleeping?
- Yes. - Gosh.
I wanted to get some sleep, too.
What do you think you're doing?
I'm trying to save up my energy.
That was a bad timing.
How can you fall asleep?
I was about to ask if he's sleeping.
- You should know better. - You scared me.
- We're even low on gas. - That was funny.
There's only 1km worth of gas left.
(They finally arrive at the Han River.)
We have to pay for parking again.
- How much do we have left? - Welcome.
We have about 10 dollars left.
Everything costs money.
That's so true.
It's just like what our parents said.
Everything costs money.
(They have 10 dollars and 68 cents left.)
It's gotten colder.
Goodness. You're wearing a jacket.
Can I exchange this for the other pair of my shoes?
No.
(He's been missing a shoe for the past 2 hours.)
There are only six bicycles here.
(Does the mission have something to do with bicycles?)
This mission is called...
"Bicycle Ride" where you can ride a bicycle around here.
- I'm freezing to death right now. - It's cold.
Somewhere around this park,
there is an R flag you have to find in order to complete the mission.
But it's so cold.
The price for renting the bicycles is...
two dollars per bicycle.
- What did you say? - Are you playing with us?
(You're a robber not a director.)
Are you looking down on us because we're broke?
We still have shopping to do.
How much do we have?
However, you'll also get...
- a chance to save money. - How?
(There's a hidden mission for getting a refund.)
Go to Gary's studio...
(Gary again?)
- Again? - Stop it already.
- We're going there again? - How many times do we have to go?
- From here? - You're driving me insane.
You have to steal his bicycle.
(You want us to steal the bicycle again?)
- What bicycle? - What are you talking about?
- He doesn't like us doing that. - He caught me last time.
(A week ago)
(Seok Jin got caught red-handed stealing Gary's bicycle.)
(The owner stood guard to protect his bicycle.)
Why are you making us steal his bicycle?
Why can't you just leave him be?
Gary's gone now. Accept reality!
I don't want to say goodbye again.
Do you know how embarrassing it is?
I don't want to do this any more.
Do you know how many times we said goodbye to him?
- That's right. - We did it over and over again.
I said goodbye to him four times now.
(Flag Team, Bicycle Team)
(After paying for the rental fee, they have 4 dollars left.)
We're really low on gas.
We have to stop at a gas station.
We should.
Was his bicycle still there?
- Yes. - Really?
- Did you see them there? - It's right where you left it.
This is embarrassing now.
I wish he's not there when we arrive.
Let's say he's there.
How are we going to steal it?
I think you should lure him out.
Why should I do that?
We have to pay for parking.
- We might not have to. - We should.
- How much is it? It's one dollar. - One dollar.
(This is just great.)
How much do we have left now?
(They have 3 dollars and 68 cents left.)
Everything costs money.
- That's right. - Wait, the gas.
We have to stop for gas.
There's a gas station on the way. It's better to do it now.
You're right.
That means we have to go there again.
Can we get two dollars' worth of gas? We don't have much money.
- Two dollars? - I'm sorry.
(They stopped at the gas station for two-dollars-worth of gas.)
I'm really sorry.
(Do we have to go through with this again?)
This is 57 cents.
I don't think I can do this. I'm too embarrassed.
I should have sat in the back.
There might be other gas stations around.
- This is the same place. - I know.
We don't have a choice. Let's go.
This is so embarrassing.
It's a different guy this time.
There he is again.
Hello.
- Can we... - Two dollars, right?
(The rumour has spread already.)
Things are worse than before.
Can we get a litre of gas?
Can we get a litre of gas with a dollar and 48 cents?
- One dollar and 48 cents. - We're really sorry.
- Are you paying cash? - Yes.
- You can keep the change. - We're really sorry.
(They have 2 dollars and 13 cents left.)
- We're sorry. - Thank you.
This is going to be so awkward.
(They're searching around the Han River on bicycles.)
Where's the flag?
(They have to hurry in order to do the next mission.)
I think they hid it somewhere around here.
Yes, in the fields.
This is a good place to hide things.
(They're on a search.)
How far do we have to go?
- We're here again. - My goodness.
(The Bicycle Team arrive at Gary's studio.)
What do we say to him?
(There's no time to be embarrassed.)
(They have to focus on the mission.)
(After Seok Jin's failed attempt to steal his bicycle,)
(Gary's been heavily guarding his bicycle.)
(Breach the security system and steal the bicycle once and for all.)
(What's their plan?)
(Ji Hyo will tightly mark Gary.)
- Gary. - Gary.
(We're here again, Gary.)
(How is Ji Hyo intending to keep Gary busy?)
- I thought we were done. - Hey, Gary.
- We were. - Isn't it over?
- We were just passing by. - Gary.
We have a mission.
(Why would you say that, Ji Hyo?)
Did you see the photo stickers we put on?
I did.
- Did you? - You have to find the hidden ones.
(We have to find them.)
- How many did you find? - We have to look together.
- How many did you find? - I found three.
- Only three? - There should be three more.
- At least three more. - We have to look for them.
(They follow Ji Hyo's lead to trick Gary.)
How many did you find in this room?
I found these.
(They spot the bicycle.)
There aren't any more left in this room, then.
(Keep Gary far away from the bicycle.)
We have to look in the other rooms.
- Were you surprised to see us? - Leave this room alone.
It's not like that.
- What are you talking about? - Weren't you surprised?
- I was. - I thought so.
(Let's go somewhere else.)
(They have marked the bicycle.)
You said you wanted to shoot with us.
I still do.
(They manage to keep Gary's attention off the bicycle.)
Maybe it's on the gift Kwang Soo gave me.
(Let's get to work.)
Is it this one?
What's in this room?
Let me take a look.
(Gary let his guard down.)
(Take him to another room already.)
(Now is the chance.)
(It's his second attempt to steal the bicycle.)
(Ji Hyo has her eyes on Gary.)
Weren't they in here before?
In this room? I can't remember.
We're running out of time.
- Did you say six in total? - Yes.
(Something's not right.)
(Wait a minute.)
(Did Gary become suspicious?)
Gary. What's that?
(Where do you think you're going?)
(Ji Hyo stops him from leaving.)
(I can't hold him for much longer.)
Kwang Soo. I'll hand it over to you.
Go.
This is unbelievable.
(Get moving.)
I think someone went in that room.
I was in that room with Jae Seok.
I'm talking about the other room.
(It's the room with the bicycle.)
(This is getting close.)
(She has to come up with something quick.)
- Oh, really? Hold on. - Yes.
You're up to something, aren't you?
It's not like that.
I can tell when you're pulling something.
(We have to leave now.)
(Gary is getting closer.)
You're up to something, aren't you?
(Get the bicycle and leave.)
I can tell when you're pulling something.
Come over here quickly!
Quickly!
- We have to look in this room. - Come on.
- You have to come now. - Now?
- Sit tight, Gary. - What's going on?
- Come here. - Why?
(Something smells fishy.)
Why?
They're coming after us.
(They try to leave the site pretending someone's after them.)
You did a mission just now, didn't you?
- No. - Yes, you did.
I'll come back later, Gary.
They did something.
What did they do?
What's going on?
They're making me paranoid. It's so stressful.
What did they do?
(There was a bicycle there just 10 minutes ago.)
(It's in the thieves' hands now.)
Put it in there.
Let's hurry.
(They'll be able to get a refund for the rental fee.)
- How much time do we have left? - This is crazy.
If it hadn't been for Ji Hyo, we'd be doomed.
- Wasn't it a good strategy? - Yes.
- Wasn't it great? - It was good.
Good job, everyone.
(They're excited to head back.)
I can't find where it is.
Where is it?
Where am I?
This is already Dongjak Bridge.
Gosh, is that the flag?
(He biked for 5km.)
They put it so far away.
(Bicycle Team finds the flag.)
They hid it so far away. How could anyone find it?
There must be a reason why she brought me here.
Why did she lead me here?
(Gary is so oblivious.)
(He pretends to be smart and starts searching.)
(He doesn't notice that his bicycle is missing.)
The photos are still here.
I found it.
(He finds the photo sticker that's been there for a while.)
Didn't I find the right thing?
There must be more items to find.
Let me check my things.
Who could it be?
(Who is calling him at such an important moment?)
- Hello? - Gary.
I'm sorry, but something urgent came up.
We had to leave because they told us to go somewhere.
I found one more photo.
He found one more?
Goodness.
Yes! Gary said he found it.
- Did he finally find it? - He found it.
Where did you find it?
(Gary is working on a fake mission.)
- Was it in the wallet? - That's a difficult one to find.
Do I need to find anything else?
That's good for now.
Tell me now because I'm stressing out.
Do I have to do a mission right now?
There are six items to find.
Do I have to let you know when I find them?
Yes, but I'll call you back.
Oh, all I have to do is find them?
Yes. I'm sorry, but I have to go.
I'm in a hurry. Sorry.
- Okay, talk to you later. - Bye.
Gosh, what's going on?
(He feels uneasy.)
This is more tiring than being a Running Man member.
He said he found another one.
Goodness.
What I told him to do didn't make sense.
He said he found another one.
I just can't believe that Gary quit Running Man.
He should just continue like this.
- He could continue... - I know.
working with us.
- Gary is hilarious. - He really is.
(See you often, Gary.)
(They have 1 hour left.)
- We succeeded the mission. - All right.
Here's a refund for the bicycle rental fee.
- What's the last part? - It's shopping.
Here's your last mission. With the money you have left,
buy something for Gary.
- What on earth are we doing? - Come on.
Why do we keep bothering Gary?
- Goodness. - What's wrong with you?
Buy him a couple item to finish today's mission.
- Goodness. - What's a couple item?
- It's some type of couple item. - Do we buy seven?
- Is this the place? - It's the first floor.
It's a stationary store. Let's go.
How about pens?
How much is it?
(They must buy 7 items with 8 dollars.)
- It's 50 cents. - 50 cents?
How about this? We used to play marbles as kids.
- Couple marbles? - What do you think?
Should we get one each?
We can buy seven of these.
- That's a good idea. - Isn't it?
- Is it 50 cents each? - Is it really a good idea?
- Are you sure? - Yes.
- Playing marbles... - Is this a prank?
- Are marbles a good idea? - We played them before.
- We played marbles a lot. - We played many games.
- That was one of our games. - There's a couple marble game?
Sir, how much is this?
How about this for 60 cents? There are 7 of these.
Gary often uses pens.
I don't think Gary would wear that around his neck.
- He'll play with these. - Would he play with marbles?
I don't think so.
When Gary sees it...
He doesn't have time to play marbles when he has to practise music.
These are better.
- These can be... - Marbles?
used as decoration in the house.
As decoration?
- Look. - Couple necklaces exist,
but not couple marbles.
How about a table tennis ball?
A couple table tennis ball?
- We play a lot of table tennis. - You're a genius.
We play table tennis.
Each of us can paint the ball.
Let's get couple necklaces or pens.
Let's get pens then.
(They decide to get pens.)
Is it 60 cents each?
Gary would better wear this pen.
Here it is.
(If they give the pen to Gary, they'll finish today's mission.)
- Does Gary even know it's missing? - No, he doesn't.
- Are you okay, Kwang Soo? - Yes.
(They bring back the bicycle they stole.)
(Did Gary notice that the bicycle was missing?)
Gary.
Why did you take my bicycle?
Did you not know?
(He's shocked and scared.)
When did you take it?
Didn't you know?
Gosh, what are you doing?
We took...
- your bicycle. - I'm really sorry.
Today's episode was recorded without Gary.
Yes, he was with us.
What is he talking about?
Wasn't I the main guest today?
He was the main guest.
You finished all the missions within six hours.
(They succeeded the missions.)
Today was difficult.
Six hours was enough time.
With Gary's help...
Without his help, we couldn't have made it.
- Five dollars helped us a lot. - Really?
- Seriously. - You helped us a lot.
- He gave us five dollars. - Gary,
you can keep this.
- What is it? - It's the change.
- Come on, it's okay. - You should take it.
- Ji Hyo. - Keep it.
I didn't help you to take this money.
Keep it.
- Should I keep it... - Come on.
- as a souvenir? - That sounds good.
- You should keep it. - It's not that much.
Did you give him today's souvenir?
- I will now. - Gosh.
- You haven't yet? - It's our couple item.
(Haha sounds shy.)
You haven't given it to him yet?
- Here you go. - It's a souvenir.
- I see. - All of us have one each.
We'll be wearing it the next time we come back.
Do we become one when we do this?
- Like this? - Like this?
(See you in the Milky Way after a year.)
Shouldn't Ji Hyo cry again?
- Well... - She texted him at 3am.
"Gary, I miss you."
(She was too drunk to type.)
It was 3am.
She probably sent it after drinking a lot.
Is she going to sing...
a sad song for him?
- What is it? - It's nothing.
"There's no one as innocent as you."
- Is that what she wrote? - Yes.
- Let me see. - Here it is.
Do you see it?
Ji Hyo, what's wrong with you?
It was just that day.
She used the word "love" a lot that day.
She should have treated him better.
You should have treated him better.
I did treat him well.
- I did, didn't I? - You shouldn't brag.
By the way...
Well...
- Let's get going. - Okay.
Let's go.
Are you sure you're leaving?
Let's go already.
How many times do we have to do this?
- I'm so tired of it. - My chest is bruised.
How was it for you today?
I really enjoyed it today.
- If you pass by my studio, - That sounds good.
you should stop here for a meal.
That would be great.
Do you remember the Chinese restaurant?
We can order delivery from there.
- We couldn't eat enough today. - I'll order delivery next time.
- Okay. - Can you order the food now?
My goodness.
- All right, let's go. - See you.
We're really leaving this time.
- Are you really leaving? - Be a guest on the show every week.
I'll take the bicycle.
You might as well take it.
If the bicycle disappears one day, just know that it was me.
- Okay. - I'll take it later.
I'll assume that it was your mission.
- See you, Gary. - See you.
(They're like one big family.)
(Can you return the microphones?)
Give all of them to me.
- Bye, Gary. - Bye.
- Return this for me, too. - What?
This one. Bye.
(Return the mission bag, please.)
They don't fail to amaze me.
Don't take away the money they gave me.
Let's wrap up. One, two, three.
Thank you.
The director and I hugged tightly last week.
Shouldn't I feel sad?
(All six members of Sechs Kies are back.)
(Hwangwoo Seul Hye)
(Sechs Kies and Hwangwoo Seul Hye are perfect together.)
(These are idol singers with 20 years of experience.)
(It's a competitive battle with the men's pride on the line.)
(However...)
(One of them is a food thief.)
(Catch the world's worst food thief.)
(There's a shocking twist behind the food.)
Why are you making us eat on the street?
- Gosh. - We look like paupers anyway.
(Food Thief Race on Sunday next week at 6:30pm)