(Mysterious Hunters)
Why are you doing this to me?
Now, Kwang Soo should...
- No way!
- Haha, get Kwang Soo.
Please leave me alone!
There's no way out.
(They're chasing after you.)
I'll never get caught. It's not possible.
(What happened to the Running Man members?)
(6 hours ago)
(Yeouido Park, Seoul)
(What is this mysterious structure in the middle of the park?)
Hello. Good morning.
You have to wear this.
Goodness.
Gosh, what is this?
(They're asked to wear eye masks.)
What's this?
Why must I wear this?
- Do I have to wear this eye mask?
- What is this?
Where am I going?
Where are we heading to?
(Where will they be guided to?)
Why do I have to wear an eye mask?
- Hello, Gary.
- Hi, Kwang Soo.
- Are you wearing an eye mask, too?
- Yes.
- You're here.
- Let me take this off.
- Hello.
- Can I...
take this eye mask off?
Can I take it off?
I'm scared, I'm scared.
(What is this room in the middle of the park?)
What's going on?
Hello?
- Where am I?
- Where is it?
Do I take a seat here?
- Do I sit here?
- Where am I?
- There are rooms in Yeouido Park.
- Is this right?
Kwang Soo, be quiet!
Jae Seok.
What's this sound?
(Suddenly)
- What was that?
- Are there doors, too?
- My goodness.
- What's this sound?
- What's the sound?
- I think they closed the doors.
What's going on?
- Please take your eye masks off.
- What?
- Do I take it off now?
- Can I take the eye mask off?
- What is this?
- What's happening?
(They are given...)
What's this? What is it?
(A box and a card.)
What's going on here?
(Now, they must fight temptation.)
"A vault hidden in Seoul has 7,000 dollars in it."
- "A vault hidden in Seoul..."
- "Has 7,000 dollars..."
"If none of you open the boxes, everyone will get 1,000 dollars."
"But if any of you open the box, that person becomes the Prey..."
"and can get the 7,000 dollars that is in the vault."
"If the Prey fails to open the vault, the Prey will get a penalty."
7,000 dollars?
Don't open your boxes!
Let's all get 1,000 dollars!
Don't be greedy!
(Will they resist the temptation?)
You won't be able to get all of the money anyway!
Can we open the box now?
- Don't open it.
- Don't do it!
You know what they want from us.
If you're unsure, don't open it!
- Kwang Soo!
- No, but...
Seok Jin, don't open your box!
Can I open it now?
Gosh, I want to open it!
This is driving me crazy.
(Mysterious Hunters will be chasing after them.)
(24 hours ago)
(An unidentified vehicle arrives.)
(A mysterious man gets out of the van.)
(Ahn Sung Ki)
(He's a renown actor with an acting history of 60 years.)
(He has great searching skills due to his roles as a detective.)
(Cho Jin Woong)
(He's well-fit as a Hunter due to his roles from warriors to police.)
(Kwon Yul)
(With his youth and sharp senses, this actor is a handsome fighter.)
(Who's the last Hunter?)
(Han Ye Ri)
(She may seem fragile, but she embodies great power and stamina.)
Oh, no.
(These four Hunters are here to chase after the Preys.)
We must win.
- Hunters, let's go!
- We can do it!
Let me explain the mission you will complete today.
You'll be Hunters...
and catch the Running Man members.
(We have to catch the members?)
The members will be tempted to betray each other.
You'll chase the members who decide to betray.
If you succeed in catching them, we'll give you this Golden Badge.
What percentage of gold does it have?
Is it 99.9 percent?
He was in "Silmido"...
and you acted as a former table tennis player.
- And you're very tenacious.
- Of course.
- You were in "A Hard Day".
- Right. I never give up.
- You can count on me.
- Okay.
When I was here last year,
I didn't eliminate anyone's name tag.
I intentionally let them win.
But people said that...
I failed to eliminate any name tags and went to jail.
But that was my intention.
Today, however, as a Hunter, I'll make sure to win.
Let me wear my sunglasses.
(I'll be different today.)
I think...
it won't be easy.
But we must trust each other.
In 1, 2, 3.
- Hunters, let's go!
- Let's go!
(1 day before the hunt.)
(Sung Ki does a simulation chase at his house.)
(He reveals his house to viewers for the first time.)
(Ripping)
This is harder...
(This is not easy.)
To rip than I thought.
(He's fascinated.)
(He starts training.)
I'll be hiding like this.
(A standard technique to remove the name tag)
(This is called the Leech Technique.)
(I'm exhausted.)
(He hides himself.)
I'll hide myself in corners like this.
(This is called the Hiding Technique.)
And I will...
lower my body like this.
(Hiding Technique: One must put down his title and crawl.)
This is difficult.
I think Jae Seok is really great.
I think it'd be better to avoid him...
than to confront him.
Jong Kook...
is a hard opponent to face as well.
However, I think Seok Jin...
will be the easiest to face.
And as Kwang Soo is really tall,
I'll attack him from a lower angle.
Although it might be a bit embarrassing,
I'll attack him below the legs.
My right side looks better.
I should've sat like this.
(It's a bit late to regret now.)
Dear Running Man members,
you'd better be prepared.
Tomorrow, we, Hunters, will be there to hunt you down.
(Be prepared to be hunted.)
Running Man.
(Head Hunter Ahn Sung Ki)
My mission is to kill you.
(Sung Ki is ready to carry out his mission.)
(D-Day)
Today,
we're fully prepared.
(Jin Woong also looks very determined.)
So the members must be prepared, too.
No, I'm not nervous.
Seriously, I am not.
I'm not nervous.
I don't pick my nose when I'm nervous.
Don't worry.
May I stop by the restroom?
Is it because you're nervous?
(You seem nervous.)
What do you mean by that?
(I just want to prepare myself for the race.)
You should know me by now.
Anyway, you'll see.
I'll teach the betrayers a big lesson.
I'll see you soon.
(Running Man members, you'll be arrested soon!)
Hello, guys. You're here.
It's good to see you.
Hello.
Look at the set-up.
- Please explain this to us.
- This is...
- Please sit here.
- If you look at the monitor,
it shows the rooms where the members will be tempted.
I see. The "Room of Temptation"?
You'll watch them live as they hesitate in the rooms.
(They can watch the members in the rooms.)
- That sounds fun.
- Right.
(The members don't know that the Hunters are watching them.)
It's starting.
My goodness.
They're our Preys.
(Will they be able to fight temptation?)
Who do you think will betray the others first?
Kwang Soo.
(Ye Ri thinks Kwang Soo will betray first.)
I think...
Jong Kook won't betray.
Because he can beat others with his strength.
I think it will be Gary. It's hard to grasp what's on his mind.
Right. Gary is difficult to read.
I think Gary is poker-faced.
We all can get 1,000 dollars each!
(Among the members...)
This box...
(Who will open the box first?)
Can I open it?
Can I...
(Lured by temptation, he reaches for the box.)
Don't open it!
- Don't open it.
- Let's take 1,000 dollars each!
- You know how this works.
- Don't get greedy!
- Wait.
- Seok Jin, don't open it!
I'll open...
(He opens it.)
(There's a mission card and a note with strange numbers.)
"You've unlocked Pandora's Box. You're now a Prey." I'm a Prey?
- He opened it.
- Seok Jin opened it.
(This is interesting.)
He opened it. Oh, dear.
- That makes Seok Jin the first.
- Right, he's the first Prey.
"If you're eliminated before opening the safe, you'll pay..."
Pay? I have to pay a fine?
Why would we have to pay?
- Wait.
- Don't open it, Seok Jin!
- Seok Jin!
- Don't open what?
The box in front of you!
- I already opened it.
- What?
- Seok Jin!
Did you open it?
You should've read it before opening it. Can't you read?
I just opened it.
- We should catch him fast.
- That's right.
(Kwang Soo chooses to betray for 7,000 dollars.)
If Seok Jin opens it...
Kwang Soo opened it.
Kwang Soo became a Prey.
- Why did you open it, Seok Jin?
- Really.
- Why did you open it?
- You only had eight hours.
- Why would you open it?
- Now we can't share...
- 1,000 dollars.
- You could've waited eight hours!
Gosh, I really didn't open it!
I have no choice now.
(More members start to betray.)
- Jae Seok opened it, too.
- Look at this.
Hurry up and open it! "When the door opens with a siren,"
"the Hunters will chase you!"
What's this? "The location of the safe and..."
(All 7 Running Man members open the box.)
"You'll find the location of the safe and the password..."
"if you go to the place in the photo."
"If you open the safe before getting eliminated, you get 7,000 dollars."
This is crazy. What is this?
(They must find the locations using the photos.)
But these are old photos.
This is ridiculous.
(They must find out the location of the safe and the password.)
(This is the car plate number they need to escape.)
- Did they all open the box?
- Hold on.
- We will find out where they are.
- Yes.
We must catch them all.
Arrest everyone.
(A moment's decision made them the Preys.)
I'm in trouble.
- I'm going to lock the door.
- Goodness.
(Avoid the mysterious Hunters and obtain 7,000 dollars.)
- What's going on?
- We have to go.
Gosh, why do I always have to be chased?
(The door opens as the siren rings.)
- I'm going to lock the door.
- I'm going now.
- What is this?
- We must catch them all.
Do we have to run away?
We have to run away.
- Where are we?
- Jae Seok.
(They start running.)
Who is...
- Where do I go?
- Who is...
Wait! My shoes!
(Without knowing who the Hunters are, they just start running.)
- Be careful. I don't know.
- Run fast!
- It opened.
- There it is.
(Seok Jin's location is shown on the screen.)
- Let's go.
- Who's...
- Run fast!
- Where do we go?
Wait, my shoes!
(Will they get arrested or will they open the safe?)
- Who's hunting us?
- Run faster!
I don't know.
(7 Running Man Preys vs 4 Hunters)
Where is the car?
- It's all Seok Jin's fault.
- 71?
- I already saw what was in it.
- 1771.
- Hurry up!
- Is this the car?
- 1771.
- Is this it?
(They must get to the car in order to escape.)
- Where is the car?
- "61 Heo."
- Why did you open the box?
- Hey.
- I didn't see the paper.
- Why did you open it?
- Don't do it!
- It's here!
- Where?
- Where is it?
- Drive!
- Here it is.
Drive fast! Hurry up! Don't let them come in!
Get out.
- Hey!
- Go away.
- Hurry up and move.
- No!
- Go to the back.
- I will go to the back.
- Go.
- Will one person do?
Hey.
- I'm nervous.
- Why did you open it, Seok Jin?
- But...
- Why did you open it?
- Anyway,
- This wouldn't have happened.
- You shouldn't have done anything.
- Let's look at the photos first.
- We have to find the place.
- It's Hangang Bridge.
- Isn't it Hangang Railway Bridge?
- Hangang Railway Bridge.
- It's that place near the bridge.
- It's there.
- Is it Miari Ridge?
No, isn't it the ridge near the Hangang Railway Bridge?
- Miari Ridge is...
- I see. The location...
- Aren't there four locations?
- There are four locations.
Did you look it up?
(Hints about the safe are at these locations.)
(Using the hints, they must find and open the hidden safe.)
Let's go to the place that's easiest to find.
I think we need to go to one place to find more hints.
- We can't know everything.
- The Hangang Railway Bridge it is.
- All right. Let's go.
- Here we go.
I'm honoured to serve you, Detective.
It's an honour.
We're on Olympic Expressway.
- We're on it, right?
- Yes.
Anyway, we have to catch Seok Jin...
to get hints. We have to catch him.
Then we will go to the areas nearest to there.
- And they'll all be on the GPS.
- Right.
If we pass through this, it's Gongdeok Intersection.
They will move like this. So if we go straight like this,
- we can block their path.
- Block them.
I think they're near Nodeul-gil.
- You are right.
- Right.
You are right.
Let's divide into two teams.
One team can go arrest them.
And another team can watch their movements.
- Let's go on a stake out.
- Right.
I feel reassured to be here with two ex-detectives.
(Cho Jin Woong and Ahn Sung Ki of "Veteran" and "Two Cops")
- Should we enter this way?
- Shouldn't we enter over there?
They wouldn't be tracking our location, would they?
- The Hunters are...
- No way.
- Perhaps our mobile phones...
- We should turn them off.
If you think you will get eliminated, you have to...
try to make more people get eliminated.
- Then the fine will get smaller.
- That's right.
- So...
- I'll warn you. I won't die alone.
This is the dilemma.
- Right.
- I think the park is that way.
- No, it's...
- Why are you so sure?
Looking at the river's shape...
- You can tell by looking at that?
- Of course.
A river's shape doesn't change.
Isn't that a lie?
- Look.
- You can tell by the river?
The river meanders like this.
- Gosh, this is ridiculous.
- I can't work with you guys.
- Let's split up.
- I am pretty sure about this.
- Hey, listen to him.
- This is frustrating.
- Look. The river bends like this.
- I give up.
It could be Gangnam.
- This is Hangang Railway Bridge.
- It's here, then.
- Enter that road.
- Shouldn't we exit to Noryangjin?
Let's enter it.
- Let's go there even if it's not.
- I'm certain it's not this place.
As Haha said, let's go even if it's not the right place.
If that map is right, isn't it this way?
- It's this way.
- The bridge is here.
I think the place Jong Kook mentioned before...
- could be right.
- Where was that?
- Seonyudo Island?
- Yes.
- Look over there.
- What?
- It's here!
- Hey.
- It's here.
- Look there.
It was here! Do you see?
- I was right!
- I told you it was the north!
Amazing. So we found it?
I was right about the river meandering.
- You're right, Gary.
- Right?
- I can't believe it.
- I've been to Han River many times!
- How did we find this place?
- I lived in Ichon-dong...
- for years.
- We are unbelievable.
- Be careful, everyone.
- Be careful.
Get off first.
Aren't we supposed to find the hints?
Goodness. Hurry and look for the hints.
- The Hunters might be here.
- Do you think so?
This is amazing. How did we find this place?
(The Preys get out of the car and one camera films them.)
We have to find them. There are hints here.
They arrived.
It's the parking lot.
- In Ichon-dong?
- Yes.
It's the parking lot at the bank of Han River.
Look at this.
- All the members are there.
- Is that so?
Jong Kook, Haha, Seok Jin and Ji Hyo.
I think we need to sneak in there.
Do you have the video? We should predict where they...
might park their car and which direction they might walk.
We must catch one person first.
That means we have to catch them...
- before they get back in the car.
- Yes.
(The Preys are searching the banks of Han River.)
(He spots something and sprints.)
(There is a flag.)
- Gary found something.
- Really?
(There is a flag.)
It's here.
(What mission must they accomplish?)
(The mission card)
"Find three codes and go under Hangang Bridge."
We have to find three codes.
So this is how it looks.
- So it's there.
- Right. That side.
- We should go down there.
- Okay.
(Shall we begin the hunt?)
It's such a beautiful day.
(It's a perfect day for hunting.)
(Jin Woong specialises in acting as a detective.)
They went to the opposite side. They went towards Wonhyo Bridge.
(From mystery crimes to chases, Ahn Sung Ki is ready for anything.)
(Be prepared, Preys.)
(Hunters vs Prey. What will happen to them?)
Ji Hyo, it's here.
If we move like this, we will get noticed.
- I know.
- They will see us.
We will hide, too. Should we shoot from a distance?
That's good.
- And we shouldn't be like this.
- Right. Let's not stay here.
- Let's move inside.
- That's a good idea.
I should check what's inside.
(They go inside the dock.)
Where are you going, Jae Seok?
It seems dangerous, but why am I following him?
- We didn't check this place.
- There's something inside.
(They must find 3 codes to get the hint for the safe.)
(What is this?)
(They see something and begin to walk faster.)
These are life vests.
Will we wear these and ride the boat?
What's "R2"?
Why do the stickers have "R2" on it?
(It's not just R but R2.)
- What's this?
- What's "R2"?
(Not knowing that the Hunters are here, they're collecting the codes.)
- This is the hint. This is it.
- But what is it?
We are supposed to get three hints.
Eight.
It's stopped at eight.
Today's my day.
- Come here.
- Wait. "R2" is...
- It says "R2" on these life vests.
- There's 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9.
Why are there so many?
There are 9 life vests. There are 8, 9.
- It's R1 and R2. We need one more.
- R1 is 8 o'clock.
Why don't we catch them like this?
Yul, will you go along the river?
- Do you want me to?
- Yes.
(They group into pairs and take two different routes.)
- Ye Ri, can you go over there?
- Over there?
We should move outside of the pavement.
(The Hunters speed up the hunt.)
Keep yourself on this side.
(Jin Woong plans the strategy and leads his team members well.)
Where are they?
Do you know where they are? Did you see them?
Were they over there?
Are they over there?
Thank you.
I guess R2 refers to the number of hints. Don't you think so?
(The Preys are still looking for more hints.)
(A picture frame?)
We only need to find R3.
We need to find 3 in total. We've found 2 so far.
Couldn't there be something on the second floor?
- Have you been there?
- I couldn't find anything there.
(Jae Seok hurries to the boat.)
Which one do I need to wear?
(He successfully collects 3 hints.)
Why are you wearing it?
(Now, he must go under Hangang Bridge.)
Hey! What are you doing?
- What's going on?
- You need to...
- find the hints before you come.
- What are you doing?
(Meanwhile, Seok Jin has found R3 as well.)
What is it? Can we ride the boat now?
Hey.
- What are you doing, Seok Jin?
- I know the hint, too.
- Do you?
- Yes.
- Hey, Jong Kook.
- Are you on the boat already?
The hint must be inside.
- We can leave now, Sir.
- Let's go.
Somehow, the Unlucky Trio has gathered again like this.
- We mustn't betray each other.
- You know,
now we're on the same team. We're on the same boat.
- No way.
- He doesn't know the hints.
I think it's 8, 2 and 9. It's 8, 2 and 9.
- It's okay because I know now.
- I can't...
- believe this.
- We mustn't betray each other.
Honestly, we don't have to.
We really don't need to betray each other.
What? Where are we? There must be something around here.
They said we should go underneath Hangang Bridge.
(There must be something nearby.)
Although we're the Unlucky Trio, we must win something this time.
- We should.
- We can do it.
- Look!
- What is that?
(There's something there.)
R1 squared...
Can you please drive slowly?
- Can you turn around?
- Please turn around.
- Sorry.
- I saw it. I saw it.
I can read the signs briefly. R1, R2 and R3.
They are 2, 9 and 8.
So what's R1 squared?
(The clock indicated 8 for R1.)
It's R1 squared?
It must be...
- It's 8 times 8, so it's 64.
- 64.
- Calculate. We need a calculator.
- 64 and...
- The square root of R2 is 3.
- Three...
- minus R3 cubed.
- Minus.
(The number of people in the picture was 2, so R3 is 2.)
So 2 times 2 is 4. 4 times 2 is 8.
Eight? 8 times 8 is 64. So 64 plus... No, 64 minus...
Did we calculate the root correctly? The square root of 9 is 3, right?
I'm not sure about square roots.
(We didn't think we'd have to do maths on Running Man.)
- Am I right? 61 minus 8 is 53.
- It's 53.
Is it 53?
The answer is 53.
- All right. Let's go.
- Please start the engine.
We should take the train.
We should take the train instead of driving a car.
- We must part now.
- Yes, we should.
Excuse me, where is the closest subway station nearby?
I think we should just go to Miari Ridge.
Shall we?
- Should we go by car?
- Yes, we should.
I think we should run now.
Are they over there?
(The Hunters surround and approach the Preys.)
Lower your stance.
(Yul and Ye Ri lower themselves and draw near.)
This way.
Look. 12 minus 5 is...
(The Preys are about to leave.)
- It's seven. So seven and...
- Wait, Gary isn't here yet.
Hurry up.
- There they are.
- Who? Where?
There. Right there.
(The Preys are right over there.)
There. Can't you see people gathered around over there?
There are quite many.
What? What's wrong with this?
I can't start the car.
(They don't have the car key.)
- I think he took the key. No?
- You're right.
- Jae Seok took the key.
- Did he take the car key?
- Did he?
- Is it not in the car?
There they are.
(Sung Ki and Jin Woong spot the Preys, too.)
- There they are.
- Who are they?
I don't feel so good.
We must look around.
There is some kind of security...
(I think there's something around here.)
(They run down boldly to approach more quickly.)
(He's careful.)
(Let's see...)
- There they are.
- They are all there.
(They're all gathered over there.)
(The exploration is over.)
- Okay.
- Are we ready?
It's time for the hunt.
(The time for the hunt has come.)
- Something is wrong.
- What's going on?
There's nothing but a river.
Are they trying to catch us all at once?
I can feel that someone is watching me. That's how I feel.
They are all over there.
(They are watching...)
(us!)
- Are they near?
- Where are they?
They must be around to catch us.
- I think so.
- Yes. I feel like that, too.
- We've got nowhere to run.
- Something's wrong.
- We must run to the sea.
- There's nothing but a river.
(He runs swiftly and hides behind the staff members perfectly.)
Jin Woong!
Jin Woong! I can see you well.
That's Jin Woong. Jin Woong.
Come on. Jin Woong.
I can see you so well.
- Jin Woong, we can see you clearly.
- Was it you?
You're clearly visible.
(185cm is too tall of a height to hide behind someone.)
- Long time no see.
- He was hiding.
Hey, Jin Woong. Wait, I'll talk to him. Jin Woong.
We don't know the hints. We missed the boat and we know nothing...
- about the hints.
- Who knows the hints?
Jae Seok, Seok Jin...
- Hello.
- and Kwang Soo are not here.
- They will come back on a boat.
- It's okay.
- They must come back.
- They are down the river now.
- Are they coming here now?
- They are.
- Go and ask them.
- Really.
- You can wait here.
- Wait. Then...
- Okay.
- We know nothing about the hints.
We can't do anything if we don't know the hints.
- Excuse me, Sir.
- Is there...
another person over there?
Where is he?
Is there someone else?
(Who is he with?)
- He's Ahn Sung Ki.
- It's Mr Ahn Sung Ki.
What?
(Oh my goodness.)
- Hello, Mr Ahn.
- He's really Mr Ahn.
- Goodness.
- This is amazing.
Hello, Mr Ahn!
(They never imagined that he would come.)
(It's Sung Ki's first time to be on a variety show.)
Line up, everyone.
- Wow.
- We should stand in line.
(Jaw dropping)
- Wait, how do I wear this?
- Good to see you, Mr Ahn.
- Hello, Jong Kook.
- Hello, Sir.
Hello, Mr Ahn.
(They show respect to the great actor.)
- So...
- Please let me explain.
- We didn't find all the hints.
- We're lost right now.
- We didn't get anything.
- Jae Seok and the others...
- Those three people abandoned us...
- They betrayed us.
and went out to find another hint under the bridge.
- We're stuck here.
- So far,
I've watched a few episodes of Running Man...
and the people here are all nice.
- Thank you.
- Am I?
- Who's not here? Kwang Soo is not.
- You're right..
- Kwang Soo, Seok Jin and Jae Seok.
I've been on Running Man before. They are abandoned and it means...
- they are all useless.
- You're right.
- Catch Jae Seok.
- Anyway...
- Yul.
- There's nowhere we can go now.
- I don't mean that.
- We're friends, right?
- Yes, we are.
- They know the hint,
- so you must catch them first.
- She's right. We're stuck here.
- The dock is right over there.
- We have limited time.
- Really?
- Yes, so we must move quickly.
- You're in a hurry.
Yul, I think we should split up here.
(He thinks it's best that they split.)
- Yul.
- Yes?
I think we should move now, quickly.
The dock is over there.
(Ripping)
(He floats like a butterfly...)
(and rips the name tag like a bee.)
- Why did you do it?
- That's okay.
(Gary is out.)
- How can I put it on again?
- We don't need it.
It doesn't really matter.
There you go. I told you that we don't need this.
I told you. We don't need your name tags.
- Calm down.
- So we'll become your spies.
- I really mean it.
- All right. Come here.
- Don't rip it off, Jin Woong.
- No, you shouldn't.
(Ripping)
This is how you become our team.
(That's how you become our team.)
Why did you rip it off? I'm out now.
He has to get changed if he gets his tag ripped.
- Really?
- Are you still drunk?
You shouldn't come to work if you're drunk.
(This doesn't look good. I must run.)
What have you done?
- I wanted to rip off your name tag.
- What are you doing?
- Jong Kook is out now.
- He's really strange.
What is he doing?
- Okay, let's go.
- He's so strange.
Sung Ki, I think you should persuade them...
- with your warm image.
- That's right.
That's the most effective.
- We should persuade them and...
- Okay.
we should go together. We can't beat them with our strength.
Sung Ki, let's act friendly to them...
and rip about two name tags here.
I watched a few episodes and the people here are all nice.
- Thank you.
- Really?
- He knows the truth.
- You're right.
(While the Preys were off-guard, Jin Woong winked.)
(Jin Woong signalled Yul.)
(Gary was the target. They distracted Gary...)
(and suddenly ripped his name tag.)
(While everyone was confused,)
(he didn't miss the chance and ripped Jong Kook's name tag, too.)
(He easily eliminated Jong Kook from the game.)
He's really strange. What is he doing?
(With a perfect plan and incredible acting, their plan has succeeded.)
(Jong Kook and Gary are out.)
(Haha catches on and quickly runs away.)
(Haha, don't leave me behind.)
Haha is running away.
Where is the car?
(Haha's in a rush.)
(Surprise! Hunter Ye Ri ambushes him.)
There he is.
He's there. I can see him.
He's over there.
(Ji Hyo hides behind Jin Woong.)
(It's a fierce chase.)
Why are you running? You told me you're not but you're running away.
- I got really scared.
- What?
- Let's talk later.
- Why are you suddenly running away?
My goodness.
(Ji Hyo hides herself in a staff's car.)
I mean it.
(Ye Ri continues to chase Haha.)
(She's not giving up.)
(She's been chasing Haha for 1.3km.)
I can't run any more.
(She's exhausted.)
He runs really well.
(After a long chase, Haha finally escapes from Ye Ri.)
(She's more like an athlete than an actress.)
(Meanwhile, Ji Hyo successfully grabs a taxi after hiding.)
Hello.
First of all...
(She's out of breath.)
I'm on the run right now.
I have...
to get out of here first.
When will we reach Miari Ridge?
- Goodness.
- It's really far.
Are we near Yeouinaru Station?
- Why are we going around together?
- I have no idea.
It just worked out this way.
It was the three of us last week, too.
- It's the three of us again.
- My goodness.
We're ahead of the game.
You just got a free ride. We found the clues.
- You almost fell behind, Seok Jin.
- Let's take the stairs.
You got on right before we left.
Come on.
Don't go around in groups like you're impalas in a meadow.
- You just keep following me around.
- I'm just listening to you.
It's because I'm scared.
- They're coming!
- Where?
(Startled)
(Where? Where? Where?)
(They run away in a heartbeat.)
You saw what they did, right?
- My goodness.
- Let's not do this to each other.
This was what I was talking about. This is part of your nature.
- You're these kinds of people.
- Why did you push me?
- You pushed me and ran away.
- I was really scared.
(Will they survive until the end?)
Oh, gosh.
(The first hint is 53. Where are they headed next?)
Something's ringing.
It's so hot.
Let's get going.
- Why?
- I got a hint.
What is it?
"Yeon". That's where the safe is located.
- I got it, too.
- It says "Yeon".
- It starts with "Yeon".
- Let's go.
(Once they find the correct location of the photos, they get a hint.)
Green? What's "Yeon"?
(Their first hint is "Yeon".)
- What's "Yeon"?
- Not a lot of places have "Yeon".
There's Yeonnam-dong and Yeonhui-dong.
- Let's grab a taxi.
- All right.
- Where to?
- Let's go to Miari Ridge.
- There's a lot of traffic.
- Watch your backs.
We don't know who's chasing us.
(They must find the hints...)
(before the Hunters find them.)
- Let's get on.
- Should we get on this one?
Sure.
(They must hurry to find the last hint.)
Hello.
- Miari Ridge, please.
- Miari Ridge?
Is this how it used to look?
This isn't easy.
It looks similar. There are the stairs.
I think it'll be hard to find.
It's just a normal village. How are we supposed to find it?
It can't be in Busan, right?
- Maybe. There are a lot of stairs.
- It says Dongrae, though.
"Dongrae Supermarket"?
(It clearly reads "Dongrae Supermarket".)
The photo looks like it was in the 50s.
- This is it!
- What?
- You're right!
- It's Hongje-dong.
- Wow, Kwang Soo.
- See?
- You found it.
- How did you find it?
I looked up "Dongrae Supermarket" and this came up.
- That's what you searched for?
- I see.
- I told you to try it.
- That's awesome.
- Let's go there right after.
- It's right!
No, we should go to Hongje-dong first.
- Sorry, can we go to Hongje-dong?
- Is it in the area?
- It's actually closer.
- Take us to Hongje-dong, please.
This is awesome.
(How are the rest of the members doing?)
- Hello?
- Where are you?
We're headed towards the next place. Where are you?
Jong Kook and Gary got eliminated already.
- They did?
- Really?
They are one of the Hunters now.
Haha and I managed to run away.
What happened after?
Jin Woong, Mr Ahn Sung Ki,
Kwon Yul and Ye Ri are the Hunters.
And Jong Kook and Gary went to their team.
- What about you and Haha?
- Oh, my.
- We don't know where to go.
- Hey, hey.
Look up Dongrae Supermarket in Ant Village, Hongje-dong.
Ji Hyo, go to Miari Ridge first.
Find a hint there and we'll trade information.
Didn't you go there yet?
- We couldn't.
- We didn't have time.
Stop lying. Be serious!
Go there first. You should go to Miari Ridge.
- Didn't you go there, Jae Seok?
- You should head there.
- Didn't you go there though?
- No, we didn't.
- I'll be on my way then.
- All right.
- Sure.
- I told you we didn't go there!
- If in any case,
- I said it hundreds of times...
and you didn't even listen to me!
- I wasn't lying to you!
- Ji Hyo.
- How many times did I tell you?
- She hung up.
Don't hang up on me!
She hung up a while ago.
Wait, Mr Ahn is on our show?
- Mr Ahn comes on variety shows?
- He's on our show?
- He has a name tag on his back?
- Is he really here?
- I've never seen him on shows.
- I'm not mistaken, right?
- Oh my goodness.
- Is it the Mr Ahn I know?
- Is it the guy who said "Shoot me"?
- "Shoot me."
- It goes like this.
"Shoot me".
"Add cream to the coffee. Don't mix it."
That's the most important part.
Show him the picture. He might recognise the place.
Where is this? It looks like a hospital.
- There's a person on crutches.
- Hold on for a second.
(Hold on.)
(Let's see.)
My duty is not to send you off but to kill you.
(They are scared.)
(He plans to gather all of his experience and catch the Preys.)
This looks like Marronnier Park.
- By Daehangno?
- Right.
- Really?
- It's the College of Liberal Arts.
- He's amazing.
- He knows everything.
- He knows it all.
- That's amazing.
- There's a guy on crutches.
- Right.
It looks like Seoul National University Hospital.
- The one by Marronnier Park?
- It's in Daehangno.
- I think it's by there.
- They must be headed there.
They must be at Dongsung-dong or Miari Ridge.
- Should we split up then?
- Yes, we should.
- Where should we go?
- We'll go together.
- Let's do this!
- We can do it!
- Have you done this before?
- This is my first time.
Once you get absorbed in the games, you get competitive.
You'd think it's just a variety show...
- but you get into it.
- I...
When you see others run away, they get on your nerves.
I think you'll naturally get into it.
Seok Jin is passing by Hongje Station right now.
- Hongje Station?
- He's headed to the intersection.
- I guess he'll take that way.
- What's near there?
(There must be something near Hongje Station.)
- Good luck.
- Thank you, Sir.
Let's post this on the internet.
Are we at the right place?
I looked up "Ant Village".
I don't think we're at the right place.
- Wait. This is a dead end.
- We have to go 3.5km more.
- This can't be right.
- Seok Jin.
(There's an iron fence.)
How could this happen?
- What did you look up?
- I looked up "Ant Village".
- Is this wrong? Is it different?
- My goodness.
If we stay here like this, we'll be caught in no time.
Let's get on another taxi and go to the supermarket in Ant Village.
Where are we?
We're giving too much time to the Hunters.
- Let's take the bus.
- We have to get on number seven.
- Jae Seok.
- We take number seven?
Trust me. You just need to follow me.
- Hey.
- We take number seven from here.
- I got this.
- Come on.
- We'll get off at the last stop.
- Seriously.
(They listen to Kwang Soo and wait for bus number 7.)
- The Hunters have a car, right?
- Of course.
We can't give them so much time. It's all your fault, you punk.
How did we get here again? Let me ask you that question.
- We got here thanks to you, but...
- I know...
we got this far because of you, but the Hunters might be ahead of us.
- Replay the camera again.
- Who found R1 and R2?
I found R2 and you found R1. You didn't know about R3.
I saved you guys when you were hanging off a cliff.
Did you know what R3 was?
You would have been out if it wasn't for us.
You would have been absorbed by them.
They would've used you again.
You would have been done if you were on their side.
(I feel lonely.)
You should consider yourself lucky for being on the leading team.
Who's the leading team?
I'm the main lead here.
This is the leading team because of me.
- From the look of it,
- It's because of me.
- I'm the lead in this episode.
- I did all the work.
- The cameras are all focused on me.
- What are you talking about?
- Look at the cameras.
- You're supposed to focus on me.
- Hey!
- I know.
Turn your camera around. Why are you focused on him?
No way.
(What's that?)
Hey, hey. Hey!
(Is it a Hunter?)
(Jae Seok and Kwang Soo run for their lives.)
Come here, Kwang Soo.
- It's not them.
- It's not?
- Oh, my. It's not them?
- Did you see them?
Why did you guys run?
- It's not them.
- It's not?
(Herbivores must be fast to survive in the wild.)
- Hey.
- Oh, gosh.
(They also require sensitive eyes and ears.)
We're progressing pretty well.
(The crisis has brought them closer together.)
I hope they didn't pass here already.
- We're around here...
- Right.
- and they're still here.
- They haven't moved.
They're in the same area.
- What could be there?
- There's...
a mountain village by there. It's near Segeomjeong.
- Is there such a thing?
- There used to be.
- Sangmyung University is there now.
- I see.
- Is it a mountain village?
- Yes.
I don't think they would have found it.
- Did they have a new hint?
- It wouldn't have an obvious spot.
- Oh, gosh.
- Should we have taken a taxi?
It would have saved so much time if we took a taxi.
- We took a detour.
- The Hunters will be on us.
We can't give them enough time.
(They're out of time and energy.)
I'm tired.
Do you think he can give us a ride?
Excuse me.
(He's our lifesaver.)
I'm sorry, but are you on your way to Ant Village by any chance?
- Would it be okay with you?
- Is it all right?
- Thank you, Sir!
- Thank you.
- Thank you so much.
We were waiting for the bus, but it didn't come.
- I think we're almost there.
Isn't that Dongrae Supermarket?
We're looking for Dongrae Supermarket right now.
The murals are beautiful.
(Ant Village, Hongje-dong)
(Ant Village is finally revealed.)
(The murals tell colourful stories of each household.)
(There is a hint hidden inside this village.)
- There's the R flag!
- There it is!
- We're here!
- Hurry.
We can get off here.
- Thank you.
- Thank you! Thank you very much.
(They arrive at the second destination.)
- There's the supermarket.
- Take care.
There's the supermarket!
- Jae Seok.
- Come here.
"Find Mr Kim Jae Pyung. If you ask him what the password is,"
"he'll give you an object instead of an answer."
- It's Mr Kim Jae Pyung.
- How are we supposed to find him?
How are we supposed to find Mr Kim?
(It's like searching for a needle in a haystack.)
Maybe it's the owner of the supermarket.
Sorry, do you know a Mr Kim Jae Pyung in the village?
- It's Kim Jae Pyung.
- He lives down there.
- Where?
- It's over there?
- He lives by the senior centre.
- Thank you.
- Thank you!
(They move fast.)
Okay. Thank you.
We have nowhere to go if they come after us.
We have nowhere to run.
Think about Jong Kook being with them.
If we meet them, we're done for.
(If the Hunters come, they are trapped.)
- We're fast.
- We got here faster than I thought.
(They have "Yeon" and number 53 as their hints.)
What if they're staking out here?
This is so intense. I'm so nervous.
- Hello.
- We're looking for Mr Kim.
(Have they found Mr Kim's residence?)
- Is it you?
- They're people on television.
- We are.
- Are you Mr Kim Jae Pyung?
That's me.
- Hello.
- Nice to meet you.
Can you give us a hint?
Is that it?
- Thank you, Sir.
- Thank you.
- We were looking for you.
- Take care of yourself.
- Thank you.
- Please be healthy.
(Why did Mr Kim give them a hint?)
- Is there a hint inside the book?
- There must be.
Is this a map of the village?
- Page 25.
It's too risky here.
(The front page has a bunch of unknown numbers and letters.)
What's 16L and 4W?
The 16th line?
("P" is for page, "L" is for length and "W" is for word.)
- That's the 16th line.
- It's "Two".
- It says "Two".
- "Two".
- It says "10".
- That's 20.
- It says "7".
- That's 27.
- We had 53 before.
- It's 53 and 27.
- 53.
- Let's get going.
- 53 and 27.
(They have "Yeon" and number 53 and 27.)
- I don't believe them.
- Let's go through this area.
To get to Seoul National University Hospital, you take a left.
Are there any old buildings left at the hospital?
This is the building. It's on your right.
I think they're there.
- The security team is there.
- It's the right way.
We're at the right spot.
- You were right.
- I knew it.
You can never beat a veteran.
He's amazing.
(Follow my lead.)
How did you know just by looking at an old photo?
- It was in black and white.
- I used to come here a lot.
- There was a theatre here.
- I see.
They would never imagine that we're here already.
This is the right place.
- It's right.
- Exactly!
- Right?
- It looks exactly like the photo.
It looks exactly the same.
It's still the same building. It hasn't changed at all.
"Former Administration Building of Seoul National University."
- You're awesome.
- He's incredible.
It looks exactly like the picture.
So this used to be the main building?
It was the main building when they took the picture.
Let's call the other team and see how far they got.
Somebody is near us. Haha is close to us.
Wait a second.
I'm scared to go anywhere.
(Haha approaches Daehangno.)
(He's busy searching the web.)
It's the Seoul National University Hospital.
Thank you.
We took a taxi so we must be ahead of them.
(Haha believes he's the first to arrive.)
(The Hunters are waiting right across the street.)
I'm definitely faster than them.
He's coming near us.
- All right.
- Welcome.
(Haha barely escaped. Now, he crawls back towards the tiger's den.)
(Welcome to the worst place you could ever be at.)
We'll surround him like this.
(But Haha is nowhere to be seen.)
(Why isn't he showing up?)
- Jong Kook.
- Yes.
You can go that way and I'll go around.
Sure.
- Is he still in the same spot?
- Yes. Let's move towards him.
I think there might be...
- Why isn't he moving?
- He might have gotten off...
but doesn't know where to go.
Haha is not moving.
Right, he knows that we can track him down.
- No way.
- Check the GPS.
You have a GPS?
(Is Haha trying to trick them?)
- Haven't you seen Haha?
- Haha?
He took the subway.
He took the subway?
(The subway?)
(He's dazed.)
He left a while ago.
He did, right?
(What just happened?)
This is perfect.
This is great.
(Why is Haha on the subway?)
If we are going to do this,
why don't I just head back to Ichon-dong and get the hint?
I'll be back in the same spot for the second time today.
(He plans to go back to Ichon-dong and find the hint he missed.)
Thank you.
We took a taxi.
(He gets off first since he knows that they can track him down.)
(As soon as he gets off, he heads straight to the subway station.)
What's more incredible about this...
is that you cannot track people when they're underground.
(The GPS doesn't work underground.)
Hey, is he gone?
Haha took the subway.
- Did he?
- Yes.
- From here?
- Yes, and...
we cannot track him once he enters the underground space.
He knows that we have the GPS.
He asked me if I had a GPS before.
My goodness.
(This is a game of wits. It's not an easy pursuit.)
- Look!
- So 8 times 8 is 64.
- Use a calculator.
- It's 53.
What's this?
(Ji Hyo gets a hint at Miari Ridge.)
"Find a card that's missing."
(She has number 19 and "Hee".)
- Are you Mr Kim Jae Pyung?
- Thank you.
- It's "10".
- It's 27.
- It's 53 and 27.
Right.
(Haha currently has no hints.)
(Jae Seok, Seok Jin and Kwang Soo have completed their mission.)
- How are we supposed to get down?
- Should we...
steal the staff's car?
Oh, dear. We can't do this on our own.
- Jae Seok.
- We need a car.
- If we take a taxi...
- Let's just take this car.
- Can we take this?
- May we borrow this car?
Sorry, Sir.
(They have to get away no matter what.)
It's so hot.
(What's the Unlucky Trio's next target?)
- What?
- Why?
It's the Korea Arts and Culture Education Service.
- Where?
- It looks exactly like the photo.
- This is it, right?
- Let me see.
- This is it.
- Let's see.
- It looks exactly like the photo.
- You're right.
Is it the Korea Arts and Culture Education Service?
Excuse me, Sir. Do you know where this is?
- Hurry up.
- It's the College of Liberal Arts.
It's in Hyehwa-dong.
- What is it again?
- He's right.
He's right. It's Seoul National University.
It's Seoul National University Hospital!
- This is it, right?
- Let me see.
(He searched the internet in detail.)
- Let's see.
- I'm on a roll today.
- We have to stick together.
- It used to be...
the former administration building of the university.
It's the Korea Arts and Culture Education Service.
- Did you find it?
- It's here.
- Kwang Soo.
- I found it!
You're awesome. It's your day today.
You're awesome.
What's this car doing?
- Jong Kook! How did you get here?
- We finally run into you.
We are looking for the flag.
- We're looking for the mission.
- Really?
I think it must be inside.
We have to go this way.
- There are tents.
- Is that the right building?
- It must be inside.
- There are so many tents.
- Let's go inside.
- I think it's this side.
Go on SNS and search hashtags for Ji Hyo and Running Man.
Do it for all of them.
Hashtag Miari Ridge.
- I found it.
- Gary's calling.
It's Hyehwa!
- They're in Hyehwa?
- They are!
- Who's there?
- Jin Woong is there.
- How did you know?
- I found him via hashtag!
- See? What did I tell you?
- Turn the car around!
- My goodness!
- Miari Ridge it is!
- It was posted 3 minutes ago!
- What were they doing there?
He's roaming the streets with Mr Ahn.
We can't go there!
- Would they come if we're here?
- They won't.
(The entire team wanders about.)
- Here's the flag.
- Here it is!
- Here it is.
- Mr Ahn.
There's the flag here.
They're all here.
- Are they?
- They've arrived.
We have to get them in one shot if possible.
(The Preys are heading to Daehangno.)
We can't take the car through the streets.
We're here.
- It's here.
- This is the building.
That's the building from the photo. This is amazing.
- This is it.
- It is, right?
That's the one we saw in the photo.
We'll let them come in...
- and corner them together.
- Right.
Hide well so that they can't see us.
(Sung Ki and Ye Ri hide in the basement.)
(They plan to drive the members from each floor.)
I hope he successfully escaped. But we never know.
Oh, my phone is ringing.
Who is it?
(Kwang Soo's phone starts ringing.)
- Who is it?
- Hello?
- Hello.
- Hi.
(Who is she?)
(Is it a trap made by the Hunters?)
We've recently launched...
our new black garlic extract in Uiseong, North Gyeongsang-do.
(It's a telemarketing call.)
(She says she will even send him a free sample.)
How does that sound? Hello?
I'm sorry. But I'm busy right now.
- Okay.
- Bye.
Bye.
Goodness.
Gosh.
I thought...
- it was Ye Ri.
- Right.
Because it was a woman.
I thought we were receiving a mission.
- The call was from Uiseong?
- Goodness.
Do we have to go to Uiseong?
- Wait.
- Black garlic extract?
(While the trio is distracted by the telemarketing call...)
Okay.
(Hunters are preparing to entrap the Preys.)
(Yul goes to the rooftop to watch them.)
I think they're not here yet.
It's too quiet, right?
(Jin Woong is waiting at the entrance.)
(And he locks himself in.)
Wait, it's locked.
(He has locked himself in.)
My goodness. What should I do?
(He calls Yul for help.)
- Hello.
- Yul,
I'm locked up in the men's restroom on the first floor.
Please come down here and open the door for me.
Okay. I'm on the rooftop now. I'll make my way there.
(He desperately hopes that the Preys aren't here yet.)
Jin Woong is locked in the men's restroom.
(He hears noises.)
(The Preys must be near.)
We have to find the place on the photo.
It should be around here.
(The Unlucky Trio carefully approaches the building.)
Watch out.
(Yul runs to the second floor.)
Jae Seok's here.
- Watch out.
- He's wearing a white shirt.
(Jin Woong also senses the Preys near him.)
- Jin Woong.
- Yul, go up now.
(Jin Woong calmly tells Yul to hide.)
Okay.
(The Preys are right in front of the building.)
(Jin Woong also hides himself to hunt them.)
(But he only finds himself in the restroom.)
What am I doing here?
Look at this.
(The Unlucky Trio secretly enters the building to get a hint.)
There it is.
It's here. It's right here.
Hey, I think someone has been here before us.
- The mission card is gone.
- The mission card?
(Jin Woong hears them talking.)
(Finally, our Preys are here.)
What happened here?
The mission card is gone.
Forget it. Let's get going.
(They head to the basement as the Hunters expected.)
- Is there another floor below us?
- I don't know.
(The preparation to hunt...)
(is complete.)
Is it here?
I don't know.
It's not here. Let's go.
(They're totally entrapped.)
Look over there.
There are cameras.
(They're nervous.)
(Hunters are also on alert.)
(The hunt is about to begin.)
They're rats in the trap.
(They're rats in the trap.)
Gosh.
(You got a phone call.)
Silence! Gosh.
Hello... What?
They just went down.
(Whispering)
- What?
- They just went to the basement.
What did he say?
Come down.
How do I turn this to vibration mode?
- Wait.
- See who's there.
(Come one more step closer to us.)
(Hunters!)
(Their hunt begins.)
Run. Gosh.
My goodness! Jin Woong!
(Jin Woong has been waiting for them.)
(Where are you going, Jae Seok?)
Where are you going?
Gosh, Jin Woong. Please.
Jin Woong, let me go!
Jae Seok, you know I love you.
- Gosh, please!
- I love you.
(Jae Seok is caught by Jin Woong.)
You lost your name tag already?
Hurry!
(Yul also joins the hunt.)
No way!
(Yul removes Seok Jin's name tag. Seok Jin is out.)
- Hello.
- Hi.
It's good to see you.
Hello.
Kwang Soo is the only one who's left, right?
He ran away.
(Ye Ri chases after Kwang Soo.)
My goodness.
(Kwang Soo vs Ye Ri)
Kwang Soo, please say hello to me.
Hello!
Gosh, I can't run any more.
(Kwang Soo is sprinting.)
Let me just get your name tag.
(Ye Ri doesn't give up on him.)
It's a dead end. It's locked.
(He is trapped.)
Ye Ri.
Please listen to me.
(He changes his strategy.)
I'll give you all the hints I obtained.
Here they are. They have all the information.
- I'll give you these.
- Just give me your name tag.
No. Because...
- Let me have your name tag.
- Later.
Listen to me.
(Peeking)
(He diverts Ye Ri's attention and runs away again)
Can I go down?
Not that way.
You're in the women's restroom. Get out now.
You can't go in there.
Shame on you.
(Come on out.)
- You're in the women's restroom.
- I had no choice.
Please give me your name tag. Just give it to me.
You're nothing but a rat in a trap.
- Wait.
- Give me your name tag.
- No.
- Hold on.
- Give it to me.
- Wait a minute.
Jin Woong!
Give me your name tag.
(And...)
(he starts running away again.)
(The second round between Ye Ri and Kwang Soo begins.)
(He has never been this fast before.)
(Ye Ri also runs at a high speed.)
I can't do it any more.
(Kwang Soo is too fast for Ye Ri.)
(It was really close.)
My goodness.
Where's everyone?
(Kwang Soo had a narrow escape.)
(He's out of breath.)
(It was a long and rough escape.)
(Seok Jin and Jae Seok are caught by the Hunters.)
(Sung Ki is up on the rooftop.)
Kwang Soo came here, right?
(Kwang Soo came here, right?)
(Nodding)
Let me make a phone call.
Is he up there? Where?
(Jin Woong arrives as well.)
She said Kwang Soo was here.
(Kwang Soo is here!)
What?
Ye Ri isn't here.
She said Kwang Soo came here.
There are about three escape routes here.
(They lost trace of Kwang Soo.)
She must've mistaken Yul as Kwang Soo.
(Kwang Soo is catching his breath.)
I need to get out of here.
I need to escape.
I have to run away now.
(He moves for the next mission before he gets caught.)
I need to run away from here.
Let's get going.
Let me call Haha.
(He urgently calls Haha.)
- Haha.
- Yes.
Jae Seok and Seok Jin are out.
- I see.
- We should meet.
We no longer need to wander around.
Let's meet and share our hints, and go for the final mission.
Okay. Let's share the hints.
- Where are you?
- What did you get?
I promise to share my hints.
I'm having lunch now.
I haven't eaten anything yet. Where are you? I'll go there.
We should hurry.
Okay.
I'm near Samgakji.
Okay. I'll take a taxi, then.
(They make a deal.)
Let's...
stay in the car.
We'll let him in once he shows us the hints.
If not, he can't come with us.
- I'm sure he's lonely now.
- Okay, we should do that.
We should hurry. They might get here before...
- we finish eating.
- I need to get in a taxi.
Where is he now?
- We can follow his GPS.
- He's not far...
- from here.
- All right.
When Kwang Soo passes by,
you can feel it.
He's exactly on Ehwa Intersection.
- Ehwa Intersection? Over there?
- Yes.
I should catch a taxi.
(The GPS locates him precisely. They close in on him.)
Taxi!
(Kwang Soo catches a taxi to meet Haha.)
Hello.
Please go to Samgakji.
- Where?
- Samgakji, please.
- Samgakji?
- Yes.
- He can go this way and go up.
- Right.
- He can go up using this path.
- Look at the opposite side.
- Someone is running.
- Where?
This way or that way?
- On the left side.
- The opposite side.
Isn't that person just working out?
I should give up Daehagno.
- They're there!
- They're right behind us.
Sir, please ditch them. Oh, gosh.
(The Hunters are following Kwang Soo close-by.)
(Where is Kwang Soo?)
Wait.
It's them. They got into a taxi.
- Wait.
- Stop.
- There.
- Right there.
- That one.
- Get off.
- No. Wait.
We have to get out. They're at a red light.
They locked the door anyway.
- They locked the door.
- They did.
(The Hunters manage to follow Kwang Soo's taxi.)
- They locked the door.
- Follow the car.
- The GPS is very precise.
- They locked the door.
- They are turning right.
- They're turning right.
They didn't see us. Or did they?
- They saw us.
(Kwang Soo is close to getting caught.)
How can we meet here? This is crazy.
How can we meet here?
How can we meet here? I even caught a taxi.
If I got in the next taxi...
(No matter what he does, he has no luck whatsoever.)
- He locked the door.
- He looked back.
- You are dead.
- That's right.
You're dead when you get caught.
I'm so scared. What do I do?
Hey.
Give up what?
Why are you doing this to me?
(Gary calls Kwang Soo.)
Kwang Soo, just get off. It's over.
It's over now, Kwang Soo.
What will you do? Will you keep going?
I will give you 30 percent of the share.
(He offers 30 percent of the share.)
Please stab Jae Seok's leg.
Jin Woong...
Jin Woong is just about to open the door.
- He's ready.
- Please, Gary.
- I know.
- There's nothing you can do.
- Kwang Soo.
- Jae Seok.
Don't even bother doing that.
Please. Please stop it.
- Just surrender.
- Please leave me alone.
It's like you're on a bike without brakes.
And you're going downhill, too.
Hey, Kwang Soo.
You have to surrender now.
You know, Seok Jin and I feel very much at ease.
Jin Woong and Mr Ahn are very good people.
If I knew it'd feel like this, I would've turned myself in earlier.
I would've surrendered from the very start.
- They will stop here.
- They did.
They stopped. We have to get off.
- This is good.
- Good. Let's get off.
- Get off.
- Please open the door.
- Jae Seok, you stay in the car.
- I'll stop right next to the car.
(He stays low.)
(Jin Woong the Hunter gets out of the car!)
Please lock the door!
Sir! Sir! Please don't open the door.
If you open the door, I will die.
If you open the door, I'll die.
(Let's go, Kwang Soo.)
If you open the door, I will die.
Sir, you can't open the door. Please don't open the door.
Sir, please don't open the door.
I'll report to the police!
I will report you to the police!
I should run now.
This is it! Let's make a right!
Hurry up and please turn right!
- We might lose him.
- Hurry up!
(The Hunters start to chase him.)
Haha, I am running away right now! Please turn right!
Please, Sir!
What?
(He must be very busy.)
Sir, please turn right. Just enter anywhere.
(If he can avoid them, he would go anywhere.)
Where are we?
Please enter.
- The last moment was...
- We were so close.
- Yes.
- It was so close.
Right.
We could've had a beautiful shot. It's too bad.
- Haha. Yes.
- Hey.
So did you ditch them?
I did. I did.
- Are you sure?
- Yes.
- He's there.
- He's still inside.
- He intentionally came in here.
- This is good.
- Did he get off?
- It looks like he did.
(They are just a few steps away from each other.)
Please exit, Sir. Please get out.
Haha, I will... I will...
(The Hunters are here.)
I will call you again.
Haha, I will call you again.
(Come here, Kwang Soo.)
I think I can ditch them. I will call you.
I will call you.
(Do you think you can ditch us?)
Please, Sir.
(Please don't open the door.)
You have to escape. Please reverse and...
- Come on.
- I...
(The car is totally surrounded.)
It can be a beautiful shot. Come with me.
(Is this really the end?)
Please reverse, Sir. You have to save me.
Jin Woong!
I am going to meet Haha. Come with me!
I'm going to meet Haha!
What? I'm going to meet Haha.
- Where?
- At Samgakji.
No.
He's in Yeouido. He's bound to come here.
I know what you're thinking.
He knows this. He knows that he shouldn't come here.
So are you trying to exchange the hints with them?
We're supposed to share them, but first,
I'll take you to Haha.
Haha is calling me right now. We have to catch him anyway.
Sir, please escape when you get an opportunity.
(He's desperate.)
(He's just about to get caught.)
- Hello?
- Hey.
- You're caught, aren't you?
- No, I'm not.
I'm still in the car. The doors are locked.
You're stuck, aren't you?
The driver is reversing the car.
(The Hunters block Kwang Soo.)
They are just outside the car.
(Kwang Soo's only hope is to meet Haha.)
- Kwang Soo.
- Yes, Haha.
Just give me the hints.
If I am about to get caught, I will give you the hints.
We ditched them.
- Kwang Soo.
- Please stop. Should I exit?
- I think you should.
- Should I walk through that door?
Please pay him.
(He finds an exit.)
Please reverse a little bit.
(He has to sneak out without getting caught.)
(What is he doing?)
I have to go out that way.
(He uses the opportunity and runs.)
(It's amazing that he found this path.)
He's running away! He's going up!
He's going up!
- He's going up! Up!
- Up.
(The Hunters are caught off guard.)
(He has to get out alive.)
(Jae Seok the Hunter dashes upstairs in a flash.)
I don't know where he is.
There he is!
(Breathing heavily)
(Kwang Soo's self-recorded footage)
(Jae Seok gets close, but he misses Kwang Soo.)
(Sprinting)
(Kwang Soo ditches his camera and runs away alone.)
(The panting of the Prey and the Hunter fills the street.)
(He lost Kwang Soo in a busy street.)
(Meanwhile, Jae Seok is one step behind.)
Oh gosh, it's Jae Seok!
(He's running with all his might.)
(Jin Woong the Hunter is slightly worn-off, but he still runs.)
(Panting)
Where did he go?
(Seok Jin has no intention of running.)
Did Kwang Soo go this way?
I see. Thank you.
He's desperate, so he runs well.
- He's desperate, so he runs.
- It's because...
he got out of the parking lot and went around the hill.
He went out like this.
- The hill was very long.
- I know.
Did he go this way or that way?
- This is...
- Now the GPS is useless.
It is useless.
- Where?
- It's not here.
The GPS is with the cameraman.
We no longer have the GPS.
We should tell Mr Ahn and use...
Kwang Soo, I'm sorry, but you are done for.
(Kwang Soo escapes to an abandoned building.)
Kwang Soo, say it.
Haha.
Kwang Soo, you're done for.
I got out.
(Really?)
Haha.
(You're something, Kwang Soo.)
- Haha.
- Yes. Talk to me.
- Say your last words.
- I'm dying.
I ran with just one camera.
There's no cameraman.
- There's no cameraman with you?
- Right now...
I'm inside some abandoned building.
You're in an abandoned building?
(Gasping)
I will go to save you, but I think you're done for.
So tell me quickly.
Tell me quickly.
We will find the prize and give you a share of it.
Haha, that's not it.
(What is it?)
Nobody knows that I am here.
I won't get caught.
I couldn't get caught.
Tell me about the Hongje-dong hint. What is it?
(Haha's only interest is Kwang Soo's hint.)
Can't we meet up first? Can't we do it together?
(Kwang Soo is desperate.)
Please take me in.
- You must be really lonely.
- Haha.
I've been alone the whole time.
- Okay.
- I'll go to the War Memorial.
- Okay. Bye.
- Okay.
(They decide to meet at the War Memorial.)
(It's tense.)
It sounds like he really went inside an abandoned building.
(Haha and Ji Hyo are very relaxed.)
Haha, we have to make a wise decision.
Will we go to save Kwang Soo and die together?
(Will they risk the danger and save Kwang Soo?)
Or will we abandon him and go find the hint ourselves?
Sir, is Hongje-dong far from here?
- No, but you must decide quickly.
- Okay.
Then please head to Hongje-dong.
(I'm sorry, Kwang Soo.)
(Meanwhile, Kwang Soo knows nothing about what's going on.)
Viewers, please give me some strength.
Justice always wins in the end.
So please give me strength, everyone.
(He runs away while making a fuss.)
(He runs through narrow alleys, reaches a major road...)
(and dramatically catches a taxi.)
(Friends, wait for me. I'm coming.)
What should I do? What should I do now?
(He spots Jin Woong.)
Who is that? It's Jin Woong.
It's Uncle Jin Woong!
(Oh my goodness.)
You're right. I'm old enough to be your uncle.
Goodness.
How can you make an uncle run like this, Kwang Soo?
He's right in front of me.
(I can't be caught like this.)
He's right next to me now.
(I can't lose you like this.)
Hello, everyone. It's Kwang Soo here.
I'm holding a camera in my hand right now,
but I'm not sure if this camera is working properly,
so I'm leaving a short video clip like this.
I'm not with the cameraman any more.
I barely survived by myself alone.
Should I keep recording this video? What should I do?
(The hunt is not over yet.)
(Hunt down the traitor that tricked everyone!)
(Escape from the Prey's grasp.)
(The secret of the chase is revealed.)
(July of 1953. The clue for the chase is revealed.)
(Kwang Soo knows the secrets.)
(The close to an unending chase)
Nobody knows that I'm here. I won't be caught.
It's impossible.
(What will be the fate of the Preys?)
(The women of fate are coming.)
(Next week, these beautiful men and women will please your eyes.)
(Park Shin Hye)
(Lee Sung Kyoung)
(Kim Min Seok and Yoon Gyun Sang)
(Oh, My Queen!)