Running Village is renowned for its beautiful rivers and mountains.
There are seven affluent heirs in this village.
Haha, the heir to a fur merchant.
I enjoy jazz...
and coffee...
Jamaican Blue Mountain.
This is amazing.
Prepare my brunch.
I want cheonggukjang.
What should I have for dinner?
Perhaps, the centre heel of shank.
[He's like an old man.]
[Who lives next door?]
[Luxurious]
[Lee Kwang Soo, the heir to a real estate tycoon]
Where am I?
I remember now.
I had too much wine at last night's party.
So I fell asleep in my dog's house.
Ouch.
(Kwang Soo, a party maniac, has a friend who's exactly the opposite.)
(Yu Jae Seok, the heir to an esteemed family)
Who gave you the permission to film here?
Get out.
I said, get out.
Wait a minute. Johnson.
Johnson.
(They have butlers and even private pilots.)
Hello? Captain Choi.
Please refuel the jet.
How long will it take?
Three minutes?
It shouldn't take that long.
(He's taking a chartered plane to visit his neighbour, Gary.)
Yes, hello?
I'm going to...
the States to study music.
Yes, I know.
I know you can make me a king. But...
I don't want to be tied down by you any more.
(The free-spirited Gary is...)
Hello? Father. This is your daughter speaking.
What?
You want me to marry him?
(A forced marriage)
Why are you doing this to me?
He may be very wealthy, but...
we don't belong together.
Yes, hello?
How is the investment going?
Put 270 million dollars in the Dubai account.
Actually, make that 300 million.
I'll use the leftover money for lunch.
Also,
I'm going to eat hot pot in Shanghai. So prepare my jet.
The third jet. The third jet.
The new model. The one I just bought.
The one that you can fold.
This guy can't do anything right.
What is that?
I'm too busy for this.
What...
Who is this invitation from?
(He receives it and then hands it right back.)
Take it. I don't need it.
- Take it. - Read it.
(He's annoyed.)
"This is an invitation."
"Dear Running Man,"
"You have been chosen as the heir to the House."
"Come to this location to take part in the Game of the Heirs."
"Take part in the Game of the Heirs."
The Game of the Heirs?
What?
I'm already an heir.
I don't need to play games.
Well, let's go to the party.
(The seven heirs have been invited to the House's Game of the Heirs.)
I was bored anyway. Let's go.
Where do I have to go?
(Game of the Heirs, the House.)
(Episode 1: The beginning of the Territory War)
This isn't my house.
It's been 20 years since I last saw this house.
Did you see that just now?
So that I don't suffer...
That's why...
- Hello. - Hello.
- Hello. - Wow.
This is a nice view.
Is this the House?
Is this it?
- Oh, come on. - What is this place?
This house is quite impressive.
Let's go.
Is this the entrance?
(The seven heirs enter the House.)
- I don't want to take my shoes off. - What is this place?
What is this?
(The hardwood compliments the luxurious furnishing.)
(The House is a large, three-storey house.)
What is this place?
(However...)
Why does the floor have grids?
- It's for the game. - Isn't this for hopscotch?
They're for the game.
I think we're going to play hopscotch.
- What's going on? - What's going on?
The entire house is divided into squares.
(What is the secret behind this house?)
- What the... - What is going on?
What's with the grids?
- What's going on? - What's with the grids?
- Isn't this for hopscotch? - I think you're right.
We're going to play hopscotch.
The entire house is divided into squares.
Here...
(All who enter this house...)
(must play the game, whether they like it or not.)
(What exactly is the House's Game of the Heirs?)
- Your... - What?
(What?)
What is this...
(There is someone in the House.)
Hello.
- Hello. - What brings you here?
Heirs, please come out to the front yard.
- To the front yard? - To the front yard?
- The front yard? - But...
But...
It's such a cold day.
What are you doing without...
- a coat in this weather? - Where are my shoes?
- This is such a... - What...
brings you to this place?
- She's beautiful. - What?
(Lim Ji Yeon)
(After debuting in a movie,)
(she excelled in many dramas and variety programmes.)
(The charming actress, Lim Ji Yeon, played diverse roles.)
I will continue to try my best. Thank you very much.
Ji Yeon, what are you...
- doing here? - Right.
Don't do that.
(Let me put this on you.)
Please.
(He threw it away.)
(She doesn't need...)
(Kwang Soo's clothes.)
I got this from a sponsor.
Come over here.
She's beautiful.
She looks even prettier...
- in person. - What brings you here?
I am Lim Ji Yeon, the proxy to the heir of the House.
And I will be your hostess today.
Oh, you're today's hostess.
I will now explain the rules...
- of the Game of the Heirs. - Right.
- The game itself is very simple. - Right.
The House is currently divided into 119 pieces.
You claim your territory by covering the floor with your floor piece.
Then, by participating in various missions,
you can steal other people's territory to expand your own.
(The first hopscotch game ever in Running Man)
I will begin by giving each of you a House Deed.
- A House Deed? - Yes, if you get all the deeds...
and claim the entire territory of the House, you win.
The House Deed.
(They can inherit the House by obtaining all seven House Deeds.)
If you take away...
- someone's House Deed, - I'm not interested in it.
you will own that person's territory...
as well as the House Deed.
(When you obtain the House Deed, you earn that person's area too.)
The person who loses the House Deed will be eliminated from the game.
(You're out once you lose the House Deed?)
(You become the servant of the person who took the deed.)
During the game, you may only move within your area.
We can't go to another person's area?
If you must go through another person's area,
you need to pay a toll.
How much is the toll?
- We need to claim the pieces first. - Everyone will get...
the same initial capital.
- Kitchen and the bathroom. - You'll be given 30 R-Money.
- How many? - 30 coins.
- You're standing the nearest. - 30...
- Why can't you hear her? - Even I can hear from here.
- You're standing right next to her. - Why can't you hear her?
- Seok Jin needs... - We can hear everything.
- a hearing aid. - He can't hear anything.
- I was lost in her beauty. - Buy a hearing aid with R-Money.
Her voice deafened my ears.
- Her face is just too beautiful. - You need a hearing aid.
- All right. - Okay.
I will get all the House Deeds...
and give them to you, Ji Yeon.
Gosh.
What's up with your voice?
Everything you see is yours.
I wish you...
luck, everyone.
- That was lovely. - Shoot again.
(She shoots hearts to Seok Jin.)
You can't step on my land!
Give me three coins each!
This is a scam!
You swindlers!
(The Territory War has begun.)
You stepped on my land.
I have my land!
(Who will earn all seven deeds and inherit The House?)
(The first mission will determine the initial area of their land.)
Ji Yeon, I came first.
Ji Yeon.
- Ji Yeon, aren't you cold? - Everyone,
- please come out to the front yard. - It's so cold.
- You're completely ignoring me. - Ji Yeon.
- Hey! - Your health comes first, Ji Yeon.
- Am I invisible? - Ji Yeon!
- Ji Yeon, here. - You will freeze to death.
- Ji Yeon, it's freezing. - Your outfit is not...
- appropriate for this weather. - Here, Ji Yeon.
Please go on.
- Please go on. - Okay.
Now, the first territory fight of the heirs will begin.
It's Seven-member name-tag-ripping...
- Race. - What? We have to rip...
- the name tags again? - Yes. You will line up...
according to the given order.
Then you will rip the name tag of the person in front of you.
We will rip the name tag while running?
You will be ranked according to the order of your elimination.
- Okay. - Okay.
(The last person remaining will rank number one.)
According to the game result...
(Gary's face cracks her up.)
What? Why is she laughing?
He reminded you of squid, didn't he?
Ji Yeon.
- He reminds you of squid. - He reminds you of squid, right?
The squids cost 28 dollars per bag.
- You like it, don't you? - Gary's sells it at a cheap price.
It's my first time making a stranger laugh with my face.
- Ji Yeon. - Yes.
- Depending on the game result, - Yes.
the initial area of your land will be determined.
- So, please do your best. - Okay.
- I see. - It's a very important game.
She talks so well.
- She explains the important rules. - Yes.
I will now pick the person who will stand on the first spot.
Please do.
You should go inside if you can't take the cold weather.
Spots are spaced at equal distances.
- Kim Jong Kook. - It's the worst.
Right.
- We can't catch him. - It's Kim Jong Kook.
- I knew it. - I'm on Spot One.
- How can we catch him? - I stand there?
Do I stand there? Okay.
Please don't make me get Spot Two.
- I hope it isn't me. - Is it Spot Two next?
- Please be careful with your hand. - I just have to avoid Spot Two.
- Is it Spot Two now? - Please.
I just have to avoid this one.
Oh, it's me!
(I just have to avoid this one. Oh, it's me!)
(He's in front of Jong Kook.)
Oh, dear.
(Seok Jin is most likely to be eliminated first.)
Why did it have to be me?
- Why me? - Bravo.
- Good timing. - It's brilliant.
- I have a good feeling about today. - Good job.
Spot Three is perfect.
Please let me get Spot Three.
Spot Three goes to Ji Hyo.
You go there, Ji Hyo!
- You go to Spot Three. - Where are you going?
- Spot Three. - Now it's Spot Four.
It's not bad.
- It's Haha. - Yes!
Yes! It's perfect.
Spot Five goes to Gary.
(He has to fight with Haha again.)
I will go and catch the squid.
Spot Six and Seven are bad.
(They will be either chased by Gary or Jong Kook.)
Both spots are bad.
Let's see.
- Jae Seok. - Gosh!
No!
(Kwang Soo automatically gets Spot Seven.)
It's the spot I hate the most!
(He will be standing in between Jae Seok and Jong Kook.)
Wait. I don't know about this.
What do you mean?
- I don't know. - What do you mean?
You are going to fail first.
I'm standing on the straight line.
You have to do well at the start.
My name tag could fall when I run.
You're right.
- It's going to fall while running. - Hey.
- It won't. - It's only fair..
- like this. - What are you doing?
Gosh.
The tag needs to be on like this.
When Ji Yeon blows the whistle...
Hey! Your spot is right here. Where are you going?
- Hey! - Okay. Okay.
No cheating.
Ready.
(This game will determine the initial area of their land.)
Run!
(The game starts.)
(Seok Jin)
(Jong Kook chases Seok Jin.)
(Kwang Soo chases Jong Kook.)
(Jae Seok chases Kwang Soo.)
(Gary chases Jae Seok.)
(Haha chases Gary.)
(Ji Hyo chases Haha.)
(They run along...)
(the food chain.)
(Screaming)
(There's a strong chance Seok Jin will be eliminated first.)
Hey!
(Ji Hyo is far away.)
Stop there!
(Speeding up)
Ji Hyo!
(Jong Kook rips Seok Jin's name tag.)
(He's about to be caught.)
Ji Hyo!
(Kwang Soo caught up with Jong Kook while he was busy with Seok Jin.)
(Jong Kook is out.)
(Jae Seok is right behind him.)
Wait!
(Kwang Soo tries to fight.)
Hey!
(Thanks to Kwang Soo buying time,)
(Haha rips Gary's name tag.)
(Several people got their name tags ripped in an instant.)
I...
You're late.
(When there are two people left, they can rip each other's tag.)
- Hey! - Look at Ji Hyo.
She's still running.
(Her endurance level is high.)
(But he's exhausted.)
Ji Hyo's so strong.
Are you running a marathon?
Please finish the game now!
Is this a marathon?
(Now it's an endurance battle.)
Please finish the game now!
Is this a marathon?
Please finish it now.
Ji Hyo's unbelievable.
Haha's finally spurting.
- Look at him. - Hey!
He's really slow. He's slow.
Your shoelaces are loose.
(He's already worn off.)
The order is really important.
He ripped my tag.
(Haha wins.)
I did it.
- Haha won. - The little one won.
All right.
Gosh.
- What? - You can never do it alone.
Gosh!
(At this counter, they will get the R-Money and floor pieces.)
Go to the bank counter...
and get your R-Money and floor pieces.
(These colourful floor pieces will mark each member's territory.)
- This is the initial capital? - Only the land.
It's the initial capital.
This is the initial capital, right?
- That's right. - Aren't your hands cold?
- My hands are cold. - Ji Yeon, you must be cold.
- Here you go. - Thanks.
You get yellow floor pieces.
They give us floor pieces?
He got yellow ones.
- Is this for my land? - That's right.
(Haha will get 30 blue floor pieces.)
Here you go.
It's mine? Wait.
Gosh, he got so many.
I have the most.
He's a genius.
Okay.
(Haha got 30 floor pieces.)
I will decide where to put my House Deed first.
(He will first choose the location of the House Deed.)
(Where should I hide it?)
Each member will get a House Deed.
If you take the floor piece...
- with the House Deed, - I'm not interested in it.
you get to claim that person's territory...
as well as his House Deed.
You get to claim that person's land as well as his House Deed.
And the person who loses it will be eliminated from the game.
(Moreover, he will become the servant of the one who took it.)
(It's going to be an intense strategy fight.)
If you take all the seven House Deeds and...
claim all the lands, you will become the final winner.
The House Deed.
(So it's important to hide the deed in a strategic place.)
There you go.
(Nobody will find it, right?)
I want some ramyun.
(He will decide where to put the rest of the 29 floor pieces.)
I will mark my land now.
(He starts from the kitchen.)
This is Haha's.
Haha.
Eight, nine...
and 10. I wrote my names on all the pieces.
11.
11. I'll jump over here.
14.
15.
(He even takes the bathroom on the second floor.)
30. I'm done.
Brilliant. I took possession of all the bathrooms.
(In order to go to the bathroom or the kitchen, they have to pay Haha.)
(Haha can freely move around the two rooms as well.)
I can play the piano too.
(It's Ji Hyo's turn.)
Gosh.
Gosh, I knew it.
(He took the kitchen too.)
My strategy is amazing.
I basically got both floors under my control.
I took possession of all the bathrooms.
- Gosh... - I will take the room.
You are so mean to take the bathrooms.
You can just pay the toll.
(You can pay R-Money to walk past.)
This is mine.
You can have the living room.
(The entrance and corridor are aligned for an easy exit.)
(The shortest way to the second floor has been made.)
I'll put my House Deed here.
(The House Deed should be hidden well.)
There's none left.
You guys... Seriously.
There's nothing to take.
Should I take the bed for now?
Let me take the bed first.
If I can't take the toilet or the kitchen,
I will take the bed.
People usually don't want these areas in the corner.
(Haha has also hidden the House Deed.)
This is so evil. Who did this here?
This, here.
Don't step on my land!
- Was it you? - Please don't step on my land.
Who's land is this?
- It's my land. - They've done it over here as well.
There is nowhere to stick this.
Right, here.
(Jae Seok takes up the space on the second floor.)
I didn't know this was such an important game.
Do you ever know and act on it?
(How can you say such harsh words?)
- How can you talk like that? - Should I show you some land?
If there is some land, please show me.
This piece is already taken. There is another one.
- This one here. - I should probably buy this one.
- It's very warm here. - Yes, proceed quickly.
There are some pieces left.
(The only remaining area is the corner in the kitchen.)
I forgot about the kitchen area.
(Jong Kook takes 10 pieces in the kitchen.)
(Nearly every piece is taken.)
(Seok Jin can only take up to six pieces.)
What is this?
Do I need to pay, starting now?
- Seok Jin! - You are okay for now.
- There's nowhere to go. - No, where do I...
Seok Jin, you only have these extra pieces in the corner left.
You only have those near the air conditioner.
- Can I take this? - Yes, you can.
- It's okay, right? - There's no more land.
I'll take this.
Stay there and when we start the games, you can leave.
- But if I stay in there... - The important thing is...
Compared to the second floor, the land here is much better.
- There's more upstairs. - But I should still...
look around more since I am here to buy land.
- There is no more land here. - Jong Kook, here.
I've taken these.
There's actually no land left.
There may be more upstairs.
- There's some land over here. - Where?
There are two pieces.
Where?
Here? Is this all that's left?
- There are two pieces. - Can you use the bed?
Of course.
Wait, do we have to hide the House Deed?
Just put it over here.
I'm not that stupid.
I will place it over there.
My House Deed.
If you need the toilet, now would be a good time.
Yes, I agree.
That's right, I should go to the toilet.
An early visit to the toilet.
(What will happen in The House?)
(119 pieces in The House have been claimed.)
(Episode 2: The World of the Heirs)
This game must be advantageous for those who have more land.
(Ringing the bell)
What was that?
- Let's go. - Let's go downstairs.
Ji Yeon, I was the first person to arrive.
- Hello, you are here. - Hello, Ji Yeon.
- That's my land you are on. - Here.
Have you all chosen your lands?
- Yes, you can come to my land. - No, stay there.
- You can't do that. - Can everyone gather around here?
- Do we gather in the lounge? - Is it okay to step here now?
- Yes. - We can step on it now.
I will now explain the Basic Rules.
You'll start with 30 R-Money coins.
The toll price is three R-Money coins each.
It's three R-Money?
We have to pay three coins to pass?
I have a question.
- What if I go from here to here? - Go on.
Do I have to pay 6 coins because I took 2 steps?
- No. - No, three to move in the area.
And if you move elsewhere, you pay three more.
- Like this, to a different area. - That's how it works.
So I think to move around in this area, you have to spend 10 coins.
- I have a question too. - What if you use the stairs?
You can go up the stairs like this right?
- Surely. - You just stepped on the floor.
(Ji Hyo's area has been trespassed.)
You stepped on my land. That's my land.
- You stepped on it. - That's my land.
Hey.
- This might fall over. - You're on the light blue area.
(Everyone is keen on protecting their land.)
You stepped on my land. That's my land.
This might fall over. Be careful.
And when you buy land, each piece will cost you...
30 R-Money coins each.
- We can buy land? - Okay.
And when you sell, you can sell each piece for 10 coins.
(What?)
Ji Yeon, be careful how you pronounce "10 coins".
- Be careful. - It is 10 coins.
- Were you a troublemaker before? - No, I was not.
- Right, when you sell... - I knew it.
When you get hungry, you can order food.
- Oh, you can do that? - Yes.
Pizza costs 15 R-Money coins, and chicken costs 10 coins.
Do we only get two options?
Yes, there are only two options.
I can't eat those.
Well, do you want chicken breast ordered in?
- But still, you know. - There's ramyun over there.
- I want some yukgaejang. - We can have that, right?
- Within our areas. - Yes, if it is your area.
Yes. Only if it is within your area.
When the bell rings, the game will begin.
If you just stand by...
Okay. Thank you, Ji Yeon. Bye.
- Who wants some ramyun? - Thank you.
- We start from now on, right? - Yes, we start now.
(Hopscotch of the Heirs begins now.)
Everyone, you cannot step on each other's lands, okay?
I don't care now.
- I'm tired. - I don't care.
Goodness.
I do apologise but since this is my land,
can you film elsewhere?
Be nice to my cameraman. He's my cameraman.
Exactly, I'm telling him to go because he is not my cameraman.
(Nothing to say.)
I'm sorry, but whose team are you on?
If you are on Ji Hyo's team, please film over there.
This is trespassing.
We are all quite sensitive at the moment, so please do understand.
Right. Goodness.
(This is nice.)
I'm going to go to the bedroom, okay?
I'm going to lie down for a bit.
(Let me have some of my own bedtime.)
(Sighing)
Seriously.
(Jong Kook has to lie on the floor, unlike Haha.)
I'm good here, but because we have to leave the door open,
the cold air comes in here.
I can go over there, right?
- To where? - From here to there.
- You have to jump. - You'll have to jump.
If you step elsewhere, you know it is three R-Money, right?
What are you going there for?
- Because I want to go over there. - Yes, that's right.
(It is necessary for the toilet.)
Give it a go.
Wait.
(Oh, no.)
(He falls on both Jae Seok's and Ji Hyo's areas.)
- Come over here, now. - That's three coins.
That's unfair.
- Blocking the path to my land. - Pay me three coins.
- Give me three coins. - The first one to pay!
- It's three coins. - Yes, give it to me.
You lied on my land.
I can't go anywhere if you are going to be this stingy.
It's three coins, please.
I should sit by here whenever people go to toilet.
Yes, you should do that.
- This is so unfair. - I can go to the toilet.
I can take this way.
Where?
(Walking along the wall, tip-toeing.)
What if I stand here?
(Crashing)
Give me 3 coins! 3 coins!
It's 3 coins for me! 3 coins for me!
(Seok Jin stepped on three areas all at once.)
Hurry up, give me my R-Money.
(Why did I try?)
It's like Jayu-ro.
This is the best place ever.
- This is the best. - That will earn a lot of money.
This area is the best.
Hurry up, give it to me.
Who put oil on the wall over here?
Give it to me.
- I feel so stressed. - Kwang Soo needs to pay, too.
No, I fell here.
You fell on mine too.
Gosh. Here, three coins.
You need to give them another three coins too.
If you can't reach,
I will pass your money. Pay me one coin as commission.
That's so evil.
You guys cannot reach each other, right?
- This guy is strange. - You are such a rip-off.
I'm not ripping you off. This is what landlords do.
Throw it, throw it.
(Catching)
I caught it.
Give me the rest two coins.
I'll give you 2 but I will keep 1.
I paid three coins.
Right.
- What is wrong with him? - He's like a loan-shark.
I'm not a loan-shark.
(Talking sound)
Everyone seems to be enjoying themselves.
I feel like... I have no dream.
I lost all my motivation because I have no dream.
I don't feel the urge to do anything.
This is why hope is important.
Shall we have some ramyun?
Let's have one when we are a bit more hungry.
He is in a very good spot.
I can just go and cook some, right?
Yes, you can.
(How will he enter the kitchen when it belongs to Haha?)
He linked them all the way up there. That's great.
(Trying to defend)
You can't push me. You can't do that.
No, wait.
Can you push like that?
It's not like I don't have my land here.
Come on.
See what happens when you step on my land. Jong Kook's here.
Hey, let's just cook some ramyun together.
- Let's have some together. - In the end, we'll have to...
Excuse me.
Rich people.
- Rich people. - Let's have some together please.
Let's have some together.
(Ramyun was here earlier.)
- Pay up. - There's no ramyun here.
There's no ramyun?
Kwang Soo.
Someone stole the ramyun.
They stole it from the beginning.
What are you looking for?
Are you looking for this?
(Oh my goodness!)
Do you think you can cook without using my kitchen?
I won't use your kitchen. I'll just eat uncooked ramyun.
- Will you? - Yes.
I can't believe him.
- I'll take this. - There's no more area left.
I can put it under this, right?
(When the others were busy,)
They'll never use this.
(Jae Seok steps into the kitchen.)
(He spots ramyun and instant rice.)
(What shall I do with these?)
(He steals them right away.)
It's okay because the game hasn't begun yet.
Isn't it okay to take them now?
These will be useful later.
(He tidies up the area.)
It doesn't matter that they're in his area now.
Finders keepers.
Nobody else can take theses.
- I can't believe what you did. - Seriously.
Give me one instant rice.
I'll give you some ramyun, if you'll share.
No, that's okay. Just eat it uncooked.
- Don't you want them? - No, thanks. I have microwave.
- No, thank you. - We'll all starve.
Do we really need to be this dirty?
Can't we just live in peace?
Can't we?
(Let's just live peacefully.)
- Jae Seok. - Yes?
I'll cook you some ramyun, if you give me one instant rice.
Don't you think that's unfair?
Those were originally mine. They were in my area before.
Well, that was when we could...
walk around freely.
- That was before the game started. - What do you mean?
- Come on. - Do you want to get locked up?
Come and catch me then.
You're driving me crazy.
- Shall I go get you? - Pay the toll then come get me.
- Goodness. - I'll cook you ramyun.
Okay, cook ramyun for me then.
- All right. - Let's all eat together.
- Yes. - It's sad being so poor.
(Jae Seok passes the ramyun to Haha.)
Let's cook seven since there are seven of us.
- I should've been near the kitchen. - Darn.
Should I just not feed them?
- Let's not. - Don't feed them.
Why should we feed them?
- Right. Don't. - I can't go far.
He won't feed us.
- What? - Haha won't feed us.
I'm sorry.
(Sorry, I changed my mind.)
- What are you saying? - Let's not feed them.
Hey, you!
(You can't do that!)
They lied to us!
You little thieves!
- How could you? - Pay the toll then!
This is an issue of trust.
Hey. Are you really...
- not going to give us any? - This is not right.
Look who's talking about trust.
Wait a minute.
He doesn't even have any land. Why is he over there?
I can't believe him.
- Jae Seok. - Yes?
I'll let you step on my land, so go persuade them.
He can't step on your land. You'll have to carry him.
I'll give you a piggyback ride.
How?
Why not? Come here.
- You can't. - I want to eat.
- Wait. - That's not important.
Hey, Ji Hyo.
Hey.
- Hey, Ji Hyo. - I'll drop you here.
You stepped on it!
- I'll drop you here. - Hey.
- My land! - You stepped on it!
- Give me three coins. - Blue land!
- Three coins. - Hey.
- Ji Hyo. - Give me three coins.
(You betrayed me!)
You should've landed on your feet.
- I carried you. - I can't believe this.
I get it now.
This is war.
No, I didn't mean it.
Hey, Ji Hyo.
- No. - Give me three coins.
- Hey, Haha. - I'll give you ramyun.
- Just sit down. - Tell Seok Jin...
and Kwang Soo to apologise.
Come out and say sorry.
Where would I go?
- Okay. - Just say sorry first.
- Go. - Tell them to come here.
- Get up. - Go apologise.
(Oh, no!)
(Kwang Soo pulls Seok Jin.)
(They both fall.)
(Kwang Soo falls down with Seok Jin.)
Hey, get up.
- Get up, Kwang Soo. - Come on.
I can't believe you guys.
- Hey. - How could you do that?
- Hey. - Come on.
- I'll give you free ramyun. - Okay.
If you want to eat, come to the table.
- Okay. - Can I eat if I go to the table?
- Let's eat. - Can I eat if I go there?
Of course.
What are you doing?
I don't have much money.
I think you can make it.
I have to get there.
What is he doing?
Let's put this in.
He can make it.
(He slowly makes his way to the table.)
(Panting)
Haha, I'm here!
(He is cautious.)
- Wait, Ji Hyo. - Is Kwang Soo there?
- I made it. - Please carry me.
(Can I get a ride?)
- That's great. - Oh, boy.
- Thanks. - Take me too.
- Move over please. - Give me a ride too.
(Ji Hyo carries Seok Jin this time.)
For goodness' sake. You're so heavy.
Quickly.
I'm here.
Please take your seats.
Can I sit on the chair?
Shall I go on the table?
- You can't use the chair. - This?
- Why not? - You should...
eat on the grass.
Okay. We'll have to eat on the grass.
- Stand up. - What are you doing?
What's this?
(I'm going down.)
- What's this? - Hey, Kwang Soo.
- He slid. - Oh, boy.
(Kwang Soo screams.)
(Haha steps on Kwang Soo.)
- Okay. - He stepped on it.
- Pay three coins. - He's squandering his money.
- Pay three coins. - Hey.
You don't even have that much money.
He's too indulgent.
- You've been here too long. - Who's that sitting over there?
- Hey. - Are you eating uncooked ramyun?
He must be really hungry.
- He's been sitting there. - Hey.
- That's his spot. - I have nothing to lose.
- I'm going. - Jong Kook is dirt poor.
Just be a slave.
He doesn't have any land. What's he doing there?
It's driving me crazy.
He must be very hungry.
- I can't believe he's eating that. - I know.
- What is he doing up there? - Come down.
Let's do something.
Let's play a game or something.
(I want some action.)
I have nothing to lose.
It's ready.
Here it comes.
(It seems like everyone has been starving.)
- It's delicious. - It's good.
It's really delicious.
- It's good. - It's delicious.
- Who wants some more? - I do.
(Everyone is busy eating.)
(But Jong Kook prepares himself mentally for the next game.)
- This is great. - Take some more.
- Hey, Jae Seok. - Yes?
Just pay the toll and get in here.
Just pay two coins.
- Don't be stingy. - Exactly.
He's actually right.
- Just do it. - Pay the toll.
Let me pay just two coins.
- This orange one here. - My land?
- Yes. - Okay.
- Two coins. - Wait, one coin for this one.
What are you doing? Are you renting out my land?
- No, I wasn't. - Come on.
- You can't do that. - No.
- I'm already here. - I'll take two coins.
- Will you? - Yes.
- Don't be like that. - You can't do that.
- Let's share. - This is great.
You have to spend your money.
What Gary said is so true.
- What? - I shouldn't be stingy.
(Jong Kook didn't spend any money yet.)
That is so true.
Jong Kook is clever.
He didn't spend any money, eating uncooked ramyun...
to avoid the toll.
(Jong Kook didn't move at all for an hour.)
He could become a slave later.
He'll regret not spending any money...
when he becomes a slave.
Hurry up and finish eating. Let's go play some games.
- Okay. - I have nothing to lose.
(I'll show you what I can do.)
[Episode 3: Jong Kook Strikes Back]
(It's time.)
- Let's go. - Give me three coins.
Come here. This is my land.
- Okay. - Ji Hyo.
- Ji Hyo. - Yes?
Can you carry me please?
- I made it. - It's cold.
(He's being careful not to step on others' lands.)
What's all this?
Everyone, please come on out.
Here comes the great landowner.
Hello, everyone.
- Hello, Sir. - Hello.
- He has the most land. - Yes.
I can't take this any more.
(Jong Kook is feeling competitive.)
- Are you all here? - Yes.
You will play a game and have your rankings determined.
Rankings 1, 2 and 3 will get the right to steal others' land.
- What? - Stealing land?
(It's my chance to take over.)
- That's right. - How many pieces?
You will play "Bubble Wrestle" game.
(If you win, you can steal other people's land.)
- You will all wear bubbles. - Okay.
- You'll push each other out. - I see.
By the way, are you hosting TV shows now...
instead of acting?
(She feels embarrassed.)
- You're good at it. - You are.
- You're good at this. - Aren't you...
hosting some other show?
- Yes, I host "Section TV". - That's right.
- Right. - That's why you're so good.
- That's why. - The way she talks...
- is so lovely. - I see.
What did you say?
The way she talks is lovely.
- Hey. - Just say she's lovely.
- Stop that. - Just tell her she's lovely.
- Did she just slap me? - Cut it out.
- I'll tell you the rules. - Okay.
- All seven of you will play. - She's good.
The last one standing on the first round will rank number one.
The last one standing on the second round...
will rank number two.
- I see. - How many pieces can we steal?
The first winner can take five.
- I see. - That's a lot.
- The first winner gets five. - The runner-up gets three.
- Can I take whichever ones I want? - You can take five pieces.
- A House Deed could be in there. - I could take it.
- That's great. - The third winner gets one piece.
If you lose your House Deed, you instantly become a slave.
- If the winner... - Then get ready.
- Get ready. - What?
- What? - What?
(What kind of a hostess is she?)
You have to talk a bit more before we start.
You have to talk more.
You just want to go in because you're cold, right?
In "Section TV", you're supposed to just move on, but...
- we aren't like that. - That's right.
- Right? - Right.
I'm going to turn the table around.
(I'm going to turn the table around.)
(What?)
- I'm sorry, but... - Are we in...
- a war right now? - He's scary.
This isn't "Nameless Gangster".
- We're just playing hopscotch. - Right.
I thought I should give it a shot.
(He is prepared to turn it all around.)
Your feet can leave the circle.
But if your bubble leaves the circle, you are out.
Get ready.
(The first winner will win five pieces of land.)
Begin.
(Round one begins.)
(The members are standing inside the circle.)
Take this.
(Jong Kook's preemptive strike on Seok Jin)
(Trembling)
Who was that just now?
(Jong Kook attacks Jae Seok.)
(Attacking)
(Jae Seok is out.)
It was Jong Kook again.
(Seok Jin)
Is that you, Gary?
(Kwang Soo falls out of the circle.)
(Lee Kwang Soo is out.)
(Jong Kook attacks Haha.)
Ouch.
(Jong Kook viciously attacks Gary.)
(Gary is out.)
Get up. There you go.
(Now Seok Jin, Jong Kook, Haha and Ji Hyo are left.)
(After Jong Kook and Haha's attacks, Seok Jin is out.)
Come on, let's do this right.
How can I possibly win?
Ji Hyo, let's team up.
(He's waiting for the right moment.)
(Jong Kook, Haha and Ji Hyo are left.)
(Jong Kook attacks Ji Hyo.)
(Haha attacks Jong Kook.)
He might win.
This match is a real toss-up.
(Ji Hyo and Haha fight.)
(Haha is being attacked.)
Wow.
(Song Ji Hyo is out.)
Get up.
(She's lost her mind.)
Goodness.
- He can't... - Get up.
possibly win.
- Jong Kook is going to win. - Just get out of there.
Get up!
(He sounds very angry.)
- I feel hopeless. - I'm going to lie down for a bit.
- He's eating uncooked ramyun. - I'm going to eat nice, hot steak.
(Haha, it was fun while it lasted, wasn't it?)
I'm going to turn the table around.
Get up!
(He sounds very angry.)
Get up.
I'm getting mad.
You know how this is going to end.
Get up.
- I told you to get up. - Just walk out of there.
Just get out of there.
(Goodbye, landowner.)
(Haha is out.)
Set me down!
(Jong Kook won five pieces of land.)
It's over.
(Jong Kook is now in first place.)
Round two.
Get ready. Begin.
It's better to be at the centre.
(Kwang Soo is going for Seok Jin.)
Hey, hey.
Not now. Now's not the time.
(Kwang Soo attacks Seok Jin.)
Not now.
Ji Hyo, attack him.
(Jae Seok attacks Seok Jin.)
(Seok Jin is out.)
Hey!
Hey, watch out. Watch out over there.
(Haha quickly runs around.)
Don't come near me.
(Haha and Ji Hyo crash into each other.)
(You dare attack Ji Hyo?)
All right.
(Unable to dodge Gary's attacks, Haha is out.)
(Crashing)
Wait a minute.
Jae Seok is out.
(Jae Seok is out.)
- You're out. - This is...
Maybe Gary or Kwang Soo...
- Gary and Kwang Soo. - Right.
You guys should attack Kwang Soo.
- Let's go. - Let's go.
- Ji Hyo has the most land. - Attack.
Gary, Ji Hyo has the most land.
Gary.
(Gary has his back towards Kwang Soo.)
(Now is the perfect opportunity.)
- Wow. - Attack him.
Good job.
(Gary is out.)
Ji Hyo, you have to win.
Go, Ji Hyo.
Hey, Kwang Soo.
You can't let Kwang Soo win.
(The winner of this round takes three pieces of land.)
- Take this. - Ouch.
(Kicking)
- Get up, Ji Hyo. - Ouch.
She's outside her bubble.
(She trips him.)
Ji Hyo.
(Ji Hyo is on a rampage.)
- You... - No, don't do that.
- Hey. - That's not how you play.
Ouch. Save me.
Ouch.
(I said, no fooling around!)
I'm going to run away now.
Get in. Hurry up.
(He's waiting for...)
(Never mind. He rammed right into her.)
(Falling down)
(Ji Hyo is out.)
- What on earth was that? - Really...
- That was cheap. - Yes!
- What on earth was that? - He really was...
- That was cheap. - Yes.
- You shouldn't play like that. - That was very cheap.
(Kwang Soo is in second place.)
But this is a very...
- strange situation. - You have a lot of land, right?
(In the third round, only Gary and Ji Hyo are left.)
This is a great showdown.
(The winner will take one piece of land from someone.)
Ji Hyo.
I'm sorry.
She's still not out yet.
- Ji Hyo always made it to the end. - Right.
(He chose land over love.)
- Ji Hyo. - She's out.
- She's out. - I'm sorry.
(Ji Hyo is out.)
- Right. - Good job.
- That was manly of you. - Right.
- Good job. - Yes.
(Jong Kook is first, Kwang Soo is second and Gary is third.)
I bet you're all nervous.
It's a long shot, but...
I might be able to claim the kitchen.
First, I'll take the two pieces that...
- What? - are next to Seok Jin.
- For now... - On the second floor?
No, on the first floor. Because...
when we were talking, Seok Jin...
said the second floor is worthless.
When I told him that the deeds were on the second floor,
he paused for a moment and then said,
"Oh, the House Deeds are on the second floor."
He said that.
So I think there...
must be a deed hidden somewhere on the first floor.
So, to take his deed...
- Jong Kook. - Yes.
Why would I hide my deed on the first floor?
- The first floor... - It's on the first floor for sure.
Do you think I would've hidden it there?
- Well, I think... - Do you...
Why would I hide such an important...
- thing there? - Yes, on the first floor...
I'm 100 percent sure it's there.
- You... - Do you...
think I'm that stupid?
- On the second floor... - Hey,
- Kim Jong Kook. - Yes.
Just go rest in the bedroom on the second floor.
That's just great.
- Just take the second floor. - No.
I'll take two pieces.
- On the first floor? - Yes, for now.
- That's just great. - That's just great.
Get out of there.
Move, so I can rip it out.
- What are you ripping out? - Your floor piece.
- Put it on top... - Think it over.
- No, that's okay. - Think it over.
- If his deed is there, it's over. - Right.
Why would I put such an important...
- Yes. - thing on the first floor?
He sat there for a while.
Here? Over here?
- It's not on the first floor. - I got it.
Even if it's not there,
I still get the land.
I have nowhere to sit now.
Go to the second floor, then.
- I think it's here. - The second floor.
I'm very curious.
(Seok Jin repeatedly said that it's not here.)
Who would I put it on the first floor?
Exactly. I...
(What is the truth?)
(The House Deed)
(It's really there.)
- Wow. - Oh, no.
- Oh, no. - Jong Kook...
(Jong Kook takes all of Seok Jin's land.)
(Is this really happening?)
Oh, no. Jong Kook...
took all of it in one try.
Oh, no.
(Jong Kook found it in one try.)
- He knew exactly where it was. - Wow.
- Wow. - How did you know?
My butler
- Wow. - My butler
You can call him either butler...
of his slave
- Slave, slave - Slave, slave
Unbelievable.
He's amazing.
- How did you know? - He's amazing.
I was torn between two pieces.
- But I knew it was this one. - The second floor...
When I said the second floor is...
(Now Jong Kook has six more pieces and 16 in total.)
- Then... - I think that...
There's still a lot left.
Because Kwang Soo's territory is small...
- I recommend his... - I have eight pieces.
- That's... - We should take his land.
- Yes, you should take his land. - No.
I know where Jae Seok's deed is.
- Really? - Yes.
- Where is it? - It's on the second floor.
- It's on the second floor. - Let's go.
- Should we look upstairs? - Yes.
Let's go.
(Jae Seok doesn't grabs Jong Kook.)
- Wait a minute. - I know where it is.
This is really...
- Wow. - Over here.
- We should check upstairs. - Yes, we should.
Jae Seok doesn't have a lot of land upstairs.
- Really? - Yes.
This is too much.
Congratulations in advance.
- Here it is. - Right.
The four pieces over here.
- Over here. - I see.
One, two, three, four, five. It's one of these six pieces.
- If I were Jae Seok... - This is...
going overboard.
- He only has six... - If I were him,
- I would put it here. - Wait a minute.
- Let's gauge his reaction. - Excuse me.
(He wants to talk with Jong Kook.)
I know where Kwang Soo's deed is.
(He knows where Kwang Soo's deed is.)
- Really? - This way.
Let's go.
Wait. Wait there.
Forgive me. Forgive me.
- I know. - Let's not do this to each other.
- What's wrong with you? - I am sorry.
- Why would you do that? - I'm sorry. I was mistaken.
- Is it on the second floor? - What?
- Is it on the second floor? - Yes.
Kwang Soo's land is over here. You have a good chance here.
- This area and... - There aren't many.
- This area and this area. - You know.
- Yes. Yes. - Kwang Soo.
- There's one here too. - It's not here.
- There's one here. - Yes.
- There's one. - Wait!
A while ago, he said, "It's not here."
- There's one here too. - It's not here.
- He took a breath and... - I forgot where I put it.
- then said it's not here. - I forgot where I put it!
- There's a good chance it's here. - Yes.
It will be crazy if he gets this one right too.
There's a very good chance that it's here.
- Is that right? - Sir.
(There is a strong chance that the House Deed is here.)
So do I rip this piece out?
- No. No. - Why not?
- Please don't. - What?
This piece is just by itself.
- Should we give it a go? - Wait. I will do it.
Don't get your hands dirty, Sir.
Okay.
I will do the dirty work for you.
Did you just call his hands dirty?
I think you said he shouldn't touch it with his dirty hands.
(Will his House Deed be here?)
- Are you okay with this? - Let's see what's underneath.
(It is not there!)
(Kwang Soo got away with his excellent acting!)
- It's too bad. - It's too bad.
Let's go with the green one then.
Since this person gave me the wrong information,
- I will go to his land. - That's right!
subtitles ripped and synced by riri13
You are the best!
This is why people say you are the best!
Don't be fooled, Sir.
- He's very daring. - His life turned upside-down.
I think...
You disloyal man!
- Master! - It's your fault.
- In my opinion... - When Jae Seok was entering,
- he kept staring at this spot. - He did?
(What are you talking about, Sir?)
He's amazing.
- He kept staring at this area. - It was so obvious.
Seriously.
- This is crazy. - You are very sharp.
- You are very sharp. - Isn't this too much?
He kept looking at this area.
- He's very sharp. - Jae Seok...
Look how many people you are taking down after winning once.
You did look at this area...
- when you were entering. - Let's go.
- Let's go with this one. - It's so nerve-racking.
We will go with...
- this one first. - It's so nerve-racking.
- I will rip this one out first. - No way.
(Will there be a House Deed underneath this piece?)
This is not it. This is not the one.
(There is nothing underneath.)
- All right! - How many are there left?
(Now Jong Kook has only one chance left.)
- Is this the last chance he got? - Then what are you waiting for?
- I feel bad for Jae Seok. - What do you mean by...
(Jae Seok whispers something to Jong Kook.)
All right then!
(He's nervous.)
- What do you mean by... - All right then.
- All right! - Consider the probability.
Let's go get the winner's land!
- Yes, let's do that. - I will do that.
(He chooses to take Kwang Soo's land.)
Master.
- Should we go this way? - Master, I think...
- Should we go this way? - The piece wouldn't be by itself.
It should be underneath one of these pieces.
I think this corner is useless land.
- So there's a greater chance. - There's a great chance it's there.
- I thought that too. - Will you let go of the green land?
- What? - You don't want the green land?
I think my chances are low with the green land.
- I have a better chance here. - I have many downstairs.
Look. This piece is attached to the floor very neatly.
- Right? - Which one?
You are right!
Don't block the lighting.
- Only this one. - It's me.
- Only this one is very clean. - Yes.
All the other ones are very loosely attached.
Is it because he's standing here?
He didn't put much effort into sticking others.
He stuck this one...
- very neatly. - Right.
- Should we go with this one? - Let's do it!
- Do you want it? - Yes!
- Wait! Listen to me! - Let's do this.
- Listen to what I have to say! - Why?
Why do you keep picking on me?
- Let's rip it. - Why do you keep picking on me?
- You're a traitor. You're disloyal. - Should we do it?
- Why do you pick on me? - Here we go.
Look!
(Is the House Deed here?)
(House Deed)
(Kwang Soo is down.)
- Kwang Soo is down! - Really?
- I told you. - Master! We got him!
It's all because of you!
It was unusually neat.
Why did you make that piece so neat?
I'm saved.
- I'm saved. - Why just that one?
- I'm saved. - Why don't we go with the green?
(Jong Kook claims Kwang Soo's land!)
Haha looked at the floor and asked why that piece was so neat.
My master is so good.
(Farewell, my dear land.)
(Jong Kook now owns 28 floor pieces.)
Are you trying to threaten us or what?
- He suddenly became rich. - Gary is here.
Don't you have to put this on first?
- I will put it on. - Wait.
- How many pieces do you own? - What?
I'm not sure.
A rich person never keeps track of how much he owns.
(He's Jong Kook's pet.)
- You're the master. - Right.
If only I were lucky...
It's better now to have fellow butlers.
There's an area I've been eyeing on.
- I kept my eye on this one. - Oh, that one.
- Yes, that one. - I like this land too.
This land looks nice.
I will tell you this.
On the first floor, I came in after Jae Seok.
The producer said, "Jae Seok, choose where to put your House Deed."
He said, "Okay. Hold on." He went upstairs,
and then he went outside right after.
- Here you go. - Thank you!
- Thank you! - Good lad.
- What a good lad. - Thank you.
- Then I choose... - What is your name, lad?
- I will choose this. - Oh, Kwang Soo.
- I will choose this one. - You choose that one?
Gosh, Kwang Soo.
- I won't forgive you. - That's not it.
I don't think that's the one. His acting says it.
- Gosh. - This one has a different colour.
- Master! - Choose this one first.
By the way, this piece is very wrinkled. Look.
Is it wrinkled?
Look. All the other pieces are very flat. Look.
This one is very wrinkled. Look.
- What happened to this one? - This one is different.
- The colour is different too. - Okay!
- Its colour is different. - I will do a survey.
Who thinks I should go with this one?
- I do. - I do.
I will go with this one.
Why is this one so wrinkled?
- Look at that one. - You're giving me wrinkles!
Hey!
- This is it then. - That's it.
This must be it!
(Will there be the House Deed underneath that piece?)
I'm safe!
- Maybe it was this one. - I'm safe!
- Maybe it's the one next. - I'm safe.
Try it again later.
(It's too bad.)
- I'm safe. - Gosh.
- He acts so well. - I won't forgive you, Kwang Soo!
(Gary failed to obtain Jae Seok's deed.)
Gary almost got me.
(Who will be the final winner?)
(Kwang Soo and Seok Jin became slaves.)
(Episode 4: Opportunity Rises after the Crisis, then the Twist)
Gosh.
(Seok Jin and Kwang Soo's lands are now Jong Kook's.)
I'm miserable.
I became miserable.
It's too bad.
It was a chance for me to get another fellow butler.
Wait. How do I have so many pieces now?
- You have a lot. - Oh, dear.
It's all ours, Sir.
Should we go for a walk?
- This is big. - Let's go.
- You could jump to that part. - We can walk around it now.
Gary almost got me in big trouble.
- Now that there are so much red... - We need to take him down.
(Right then, the bell rings.)
We need to take Jae Seok down.
- Fried chicken! - It just got delivered.
- The chicken is here. - It just got delivered.
Thank you. Shouldn't you be eating with us?
- You owe me 10 coins. - Right. 10 coins.
Master, they ordered the fried chicken.
- Please pay her 10 coins. - No, why should I?
- I didn't order it though. - You...
- I didn't order it. - Earlier you said...
- I didn't order it either. - I gave it to you earlier.
I didn't order it, and I don't even eat fried chicken.
Let's just go ahead and eat it.
- Thank you. - You have to pay first.
You have to pay her now.
When will you pay me for the fried chicken?
Hold on, Ji Yeon.
Give her at least some money.
- Give her two coins. - Bring the chicken here.
- Here you go. - We ordered it together.
- Okay. - I paid her.
Thank you.
Thank you. You're not eating?
- Please have some. - Have a drumstick.
- Eat one. - Not the drumstick though.
"Not the drumstick"?
- Why would you say that? - Gosh...
How could he say that?
How about a wing?
- We will now... - Yes.
begin the individual floor piece scramble.
- How does it go? - What is this now?
- We have to do this. - Let's do this.
You will play a game with the one who owns the land you want.
Then decide how many pieces you will bet...
and which game to play. The game will be one-on-one.
If you win, you will take the land you wanted.
If you lose, the opponent will take your land.
And if those floor pieces include the House Deed,
- then it's over? - That's right.
(It's a good chance!)
It doesn't matter because if I don't get it this time,
someone else will get it anyway.
- The next person who wins... - All right.
will take your land for sure.
- It's on the second floor. - Gary.
(Jae Seok is desperate to obtain more floor pieces.)
(He needs to seize this opportunity.)
You are allowed to use the Lim Ji Yeon Chance.
- Really? - Yes. I will play the game...
for you, and if I win...
- You will play the game? - Yes.
If I win, you get double the amount of the floor pieces you first bet.
If I lose, the chance will be gone.
- The chance... - Are you good at playing games?
Yes. I have nothing to lose anyway.
That's not what I meant.
You see, I almost have nothing.
Trying will be too risky.
Trying might put everything to an end.
I think you can trust me on this one.
- You sure? - What games can you play?
What games do you usually play?
Well, I play a variety.
Which ones are you good at?
Speed? Strength?
- I like speedy games. - Or testing your knowledge?
Oh, I like that too.
Her knowledge is good too?
- Is that so? - You're given one chance each.
- Lim Ji Yeon Chance. Sounds good. - Hey, this...
is really good.
You are like a hosting machine.
You have no emotions whatsoever.
You just host like that.
You are a machine.
How is it possible to host...
without any unnecessary comments?
She is very accurate and punctual.
We will start the game from now on.
What did she just do?
- She's good. - She is like a machine.
Very well performed.
Here is the menu book to choose games from.
Okay, thank you.
Let's have a look at it together.
You guys go...
and have a look.
(Jae Seok is carefully choosing from the game menu.)
There is the Invisible Chair game.
- Is that so? Right. - Yes.
Nothing looks easy.
I had a look at it earlier. I think I saw a tickling game.
I will pay Light up the Fire game.
With a plastic bottle,
- Light up the Fire game. - you have to make it stand to win.
Sorry?
(Who will be the opponent?)
Jae Seok.
Play the game with me.
- Will you bet five coins? - You shouldn't gamble.
Okay, I'll bet five coins.
You have a deal.
Good.
On top of that, I will...
use the Lim Ji Yeon Chance.
- You can ask me to play for you. - Really?
Yes, instead of the player, I will play the game. And if I win,
you will have the chance to steal twice the amount of land.
(This is the time to bring up the competition.)
I will use the Lim Ji Yeon Chance.
(Laughing)
(Are you being serious?)
I will use the Lim Ji Yeon Chance.
- That's good. That's good. - What is that?
(Jingling)
What's that?
- What is this Ji Yeon? - So if...
Jae Seok wins, he can take...
- 10 pieces from you. - I can take 10 pieces.
- 10 out of 30. - That is right.
- Let's... - If I win, give me three pieces.
- Haha, let's play. - All right.
Light up the Fire.
How do we play it?
Like that, you light it up. You know it, Ji Yeon.
(The player chooses 1 lighter out of 5.)
(If the player turns the lighter on in one go, he or she wins.)
Jae Seok, you are barely...
hanging off the cliff, aren't you?
I feel like I should give it to you.
I have to win this game.
(The woman who holds Jae Seok's fate in her hands)
Ji Yeon, you have to win this for me.
Okay? Good.
Please choose one each.
- You cannot touch it first. - Would you like to go first?
- Yes, I will choose first. - Okay.
He's being nice.
- You can choose. - Don't touch it.
Next person.
Don't shake it. Why are you shaking it?
Wait a minute, why are you shaking it?
(She is very motivated to win.)
Choose one.
- You can't choose it again. - Okay, that is fine.
On three, both of you face forward and go.
You thought you were doing it with the same one, right?
One.
Remember, it's in one go.
(Concentrated)
On the count of three...
Can you please be careful with your breath.
Don't let out a sigh.
- It's at the same time? - Yes, it is.
Ji Yeon, make sure you keep it pressed.
One.
(We're ready.)
- One. - Let's end it here.
(One)
Two.
(Two)
Three.
(Three)
If it doesn't work this time,
it definitely will in the next round.
- If that's what you say... - It will end in the next round.
One.
Two.
Three.
(What?)
(Ji Yeon lost.)
(Haha succeeded.)
(I am done for.)
(What should I do?)
Haha. Haha.
(Jae Seok lost. Haha won.)
Congratulations, Sir.
Let's see if I can get a butler as well now.
(Poor Ji Yeon)
- Which one was it? - Was it this one?
It works.
This one.
They all work.
Ji Yeon has no skills with her hands.
I thought she'd be good.
She can do it well.
- She's good. - She is good now.
What's the point of being good now?
- She was nervous. - What is the point of doing it now?
It's okay. It happens when you get nervous.
Right, Jae Seok. Take this and follow me.
- Let me follow you too. - Let's go.
(By winning this game, Haha acquires five more pieces.)
I get to have a very good tour.
Kwang Soo.
This is fun.
I am here to see some land.
- This is his territory. - There is not a lot.
(This is where it is.)
(Jae Seok's getting nervous.)
We will take it apart now.
You can open it, but it may not be here.
Gary really wanted to take this land here.
Let's just have a look for fun.
There is a piece I want to take.
- Where is it? - That's the one.
I kind of wanted this.
I like that land too.
This one and then...
The floor is very wrinkled here.
Is it wrinkled?
Look here, it's all wrinkly.
We will go with this.
Why is this so wrinkled?
- This must be it. - We found it.
This must be it.
(They chose the piece according to Jong Kook's advice.)
(But it failed.)
I'm all right for now.
It must have been this, not that.
I'm all good.
(Jae Seok was saved thanks to Jong Kook.)
Let's go for this one, next.
(This is the piece which made everyone suspicious.)
Let's go for this one, first.
Shall we?
Okay. I will take it off.
(Looking uneasy)
Here we go.
If I am right, it will be so unfair.
(Will there be Jae Seok's House Deed under here?)
Goodness, it is there.
(House Deed is found.)
Congratulations, Haha.
(They got me.)
(Haha the Rich Landowner)
Haha.
Goodness.
He could have been my butler.
I was the next in the queue.
It's all because of Kwang Soo.
Congratulations, Sir.
(Haha has overtaken Jae Seok's land.)
(Jae Seok's territory now belongs to Haha.)
(Episode 5: The Lucky Lady)
She's here again.
Can all the heirs step out to the front, please?
- Yes. - We have all been called out.
What is this?
(Which game is it this time?)
Step out here please.
It's like king of the hill.
I think it's a game similar to that sand castle thing.
If you weren't confident, you should have let me know in advance.
He holds grudges.
He does have grudges.
I thought Ji Yeon would...
- Sir, you are here. - Sir.
Yes.
He answered like a kid.
- He is a funny guy. - Sir.
(I am your master.)
- You make us laugh sometimes. - I wasn't answering you.
- I was talking to my butler. - Okay, Sir.
- Is everyone here? - Yes.
The game we are going to play now is called...
Wobbly Stick game.
- Wobbly Stick game. - Wobbly Stick game.
That sounds fun.
After you choose the the order of playing the game,
- you will pick the sticks in turn. - Okay.
When the stick is pulled out,
if the balls fall to the ground,
they will be your negative points.
You really sound like a machine.
After all the sticks have been pulled out,
the number of balls dropped by each person will be counted...
and you will be ranked in order of smallest points.
During this game, you can use your slave.
If you are not confident about playing this game,
you can make your slave work instead of you.
It sounds better than the Lim Ji Yeon Chance.
The Lim Ji Yeon Chance still exists in this game.
- Oh, really? - Yes.
- I can use the Lim Ji Yeon Chance. - How does the slave chance work?
If you let your slave play and if your slave wins,
10 R-Money will be given as winning prize.
It will be given to the slave.
Master, please.
Let me do it, please.
- Master, please send me. - Give me a chance, please.
Master, I will be your dog.
- Master, I will be your chicken. - Woof, woof.
See how loyal they are to me.
Will you be able to see me on Saturday?
Is that a threat?
- You can't do that. - That's not very nice.
Why did you bring up the Saturday show?
What did I say about Saturday?
No, I mean on Saturday...
I think you are mistaken.
- We planned to meet on Saturday. - I don't think that is right.
We have a family meal planned together, isn't that so?
- Right? - Yes, of course.
I will use the Lim Ji Yeon Chance.
Wait, is it not only because you like her?
That's another reason.
He really falls in love quite easily these days, right?
Yes.
Lim Ji Yeon, Go.
Go.
- I will use my slave, Seok Jin. - Thank you.
That's why you need to be nice to people all the time.
You really need to do well on this. Don't mess it up.
Yes, I understand.
(Order: Seok Jin, Ji Yeon, Ji Hyo, Haha)
The one on the top looks safe.
Aren't these...
the safer ones to go for?
But you should take the ones from the top...
If you take the bottom ones, the balls will start falling,
- That's when the problem starts. - I'm not too sure about this.
- It doesn't matter, next time... - Just do it.
- Do it quickly, come on. - There are so many.
It's okay, because there are a lot more at the bottom.
Do what you want. Don't feel pressured at all.
(Next up is Ji Yeon in Gary's place.)
You have to take the bottom ones first so the next person...
- will end up dropping the balls. - I will go next now.
Okay.
You have to take out a lot in the beginning.
Just do it with confidence.
- It made holes. - These will let the balls through.
I like the calm approach there.
Is it my turn?
Your turn comes back quite quickly.
- Oh no. - Oh no.
(A little movement)
Your turn comes back quite quickly.
(Dropping)
- One has dropped now. - One ball dropped.
You have to take that one out. You have no choice.
(The warm-up is over.)
(Careful)
She managed.
(The balls are gradually falling as the sticks are pulled out.)
Why don't you take it out?
Just keep out of it and be quiet.
Yes, Sir.
There. That's good.
- Like this. - Good job.
(That is perfect.)
- That was good. - It's empty here.
- There's more. - Ji Yeon,
you're doing great with Gary.
Hey, Ji Yeon.
- You are so focused. - Really.
It would have been great...
if you played like this before.
- Don't hold grudges. - Come on.
It's dangerous now.
I have to get this.
(It's Ji Hyo's turn again.)
There are a lot there.
- Oh, no. - That's good.
(Several balls fall.)
- That's great. - It's a party.
Congratulations.
It's a party.
- Was it 6? - 6 balls.
(Falling)
- Wow. - That's a lot.
- That's a lot. - Oh, no.
- Oh, no. - Oh, goodness.
I think you've chosen the wrong one,
- Ma'am. - That was wrong.
I picked this one on purpose.
- It's okay. - It's fine.
Let's pick these up.
Keep up the good work.
- Thank you, Sir. - There are two more.
- It's my pleasure. - Sure.
Here. Here.
Ouch.
(What was that?)
Give it to me. Where did that come from?
- What are you doing? - The ball just flew.
- How could you? - It wasn't me.
- You're mistaken. - Okay.
- It's stuck. - Shall I pick this?
- Will this fall? - Just lose that one.
I'll have to try this side.
That one is caught.
You never know what'll happen.
- Oh, no! - Oh, my goodness!
(Balls are falling.)
- It's a party! - Why did you pull that one?
- Congratulations - Congratulations
- Congratulations - It was the wrong one.
You will have to pick these up.
- Good job! - Nice.
- Great job. - That wasn't bad.
- Here. - Take these.
(There are plenty of balls.)
We have lots of balls now.
(She's being careful.)
- That was okay. - I was doing well.
- We're on the same boat. - It didn't feel right.
- Wow. - That's great.
- She is good. - She is good.
- Good job. - Okay.
- Ji Yeon's good. - Wow.
- Wow. - You're good.
She's good.
- She only dropped one ball. - That's great.
She's really good at it.
She's good.
She's really great.
- She's good. - I can't forget...
- about the lighter. - She's so good at this game.
(Jae Seok holds a grudge against Ji Yeon.)
It turns out she's really good at this game.
- Haha. - There's one right here.
- This one's a good one. - No, it's not!
- Oh, no. - That's not it.
(Haha makes balls fall again.)
- That was the wrong one! - Oh, no.
- That wasn't it. - More balls.
I'm sorry!
Oh, well...
(I was too excited.)
- I'm sorry. - I'm sorry, Sir.
Look carefully.
(It's Ji Yeon's turn again.)
Nothing is a safe bet.
Gary chose really well.
- I should've asked for Ji Yeon, - Pick carefully.
Excuse me, are you two shopping?
- Right? - I got it.
- This one. - Let's go.
One, two, three.
- Pull it out. - Okay.
- Pull it out. - Fall, fall!
(She is very careful.)
- What? - That's amazing.
- How? - Why aren't they falling?
Nice.
(She's ecstatic.)
(Nice!)
- That's nice. - Wow!
- Yes! - I can't believe it.
- Yes! - Wow!
I can't believe it.
- That was awesome. - What was that?
- What did she say? - That was so tacky.
- She said, "Nice". - She said it in a tacky way.
"Nice".
(Again, it's Ji Yeon's turn.)
They are so good.
They are too good.
(They are so good. They are too good.)
- Ji Yeon. - Yes?
- Take this. - You touched it.
- Are you a couple? - You're too close.
- They look good together. - It won't work.
- Oh, man. - Ji Hyo is...
watching you, Gary.
Isn't she all in the past?
(What?)
- I moved on. - Ji Hyo.
- Ji Hyo, it's okay. - Don't be upset.
- Ji Hyo. - It's all right.
He's not worth your time.
(Ji Yeon is focused on playing the game.)
- It's okay. - Just let that one fall.
- It's okay. It's just one ball. - Yes.
- Just three. - It's okay.
- They keep falling. - It's okay.
- Gary. - You shouldn't...
- pull it out slowly. - That's right.
- Just pull it. - Pull it out quickly.
- That's okay. - Don't worry.
- Great. - That's good.
You'll still win.
- It's okay. - You'll win anyway.
Now it all depends on the timing.
- Okay. - Next.
(Haha pulls one out swiftly.)
Don't do it like that.
I told you not to do that.
He doesn't know how to play.
I'll get sold again.
(I'll get sold again.)
- I'll get sold again. - Hey!
What did you just call me?
At this rate,
- I'll get sold again. - I can't do this.
- I'm so frustrated. - What?
- Calm down. - I'm not good at this game.
I can't stand playing a game like this.
- If Gary wins... - If Gary wins...
- The other team is in trouble. - Right.
You can consider me as a slave.
- You'll be a slave. - Yes.
- Right. - Poor you.
Nobody lives forever.
- You'll get sold again. - Really.
I don't want to be sold again.
I really don't.
- Let's tidy up. - I have three.
- I'll throw away six. - Okay.
Gary wins the game anyway.
- Great. - That's it.
- Next. - Who's next?
(Swiftly)
(It's finished.)
Come on.
I told you not to do that.
(The game is over.)
- I can't believe this. - Come on.
- I'm the last one. - I know.
- Gary. - Okay.
- It's 1, 2, 3, 4. - Tidy up.
- First one. - First place...
Ji Yeon, you were great.
Gary gets 10 pieces thanks to Ji Yeon.
- We're second. - Yes, we are second.
Here you go.
- Yes. - That's a lot.
- Congratulations. - Thank you.
Thank you.
Gary was lucky to have Ji Yeon.
- He was. - Really.
- Second place. - I'll take it.
- Thank you. - We don't need that.
- Take it. - Gary.
Where are you going? I'll carry it for you.
- I'll carry it. - I'm not the heir yet.
- Don't do this. - Come on.
- What are you doing? - Pardon?
- What are you doing? - Master.
- Let's go. - What are you doing?
Master Gary, Master Gary.
(Gary was lucky.)
Where are you going, Sir?
I'll carry that for you.
(Later)
(The game isn't not over yet.)
(There's an unexpected ending.)
(It starts now.)
Everyone, gather around.
(Last Episode: The Grand Finale)
Seriously, you know what?
(It's time for Gary to take over the land.)
Gary now has 10 chances.
And he has 11 pieces.
(Jong Kook has 11 pieces.)
- Am I right? - That's right.
- If Gary can't find it, - It wouldn't make sense.
it wouldn't make sense.
- I can. - If Gary takes...
Jong Kook's...
- Then Gary can win. - That's right.
- Gary's situation is better. - Jong Kook's in trouble.
- There's a possibility. - Yes.
It's up to Gary.
If Gary tries to...
take mine...
- What do you mean? - What?
If Gary...
finds my deed early,
he might find...
- other people's deeds too. - Right.
Wait a minute.
- Let's start. - Okay.
- Let's start. - All right.
- Okay. - Where should we go?
- That way. - All right.
Master Gary.
We're moving to Jong Kook's area.
- Okay. - Yes.
I'll take this side.
(Jong Kook settled next to the kitchen.)
It's great except for the open windows.
(He kept his spot even though cold wind blew in.)
- This way. - Yes.
- Let's check it out. - Okay.
- I'll move the chairs. - Let me check this out.
- Sir. - The red one.
This land looks good.
Yes, if I were him,
- I'd go with this too. - Yes.
- Where? - Here.
I have no regrets.
- I really don't. - This?
- Let's flip it. - Okay.
- Is it this one? - Yes.
Yes, I'll flip it.
- I choose this one first. - Okay.
- Look. - Let's do it.
- Here I go. - Here it is.
You guys are in danger too.
- One, two, three. - One, two, three.
(Will there be a House Deed?)
- One, two, three! - One, two, three!
(It's not there.)
- No. - Oh, no.
- He's a tough opponent. - Right.
He's not easy to beat.
Well. Okay, then.
How about this one?
This is amazing.
What if I can't find it in 10 tries?
One, two, three.
(Gary's second choice)
(What's underneath it?)
Look at this.
What did I tell you?
Let's keep going.
- I'll keep going. - Keep going.
- You must keep going. - You can do it.
- This is your third try. - You have no other choice.
One, two, three.
(Gary failed twice in a row. What about his third try?)
Oh, no!
(It's also nothing.)
- This is not it. - Wrong spot.
Sir, it's not in here.
- No? - This isn't it.
- Let's go upstairs. - Won't you try this?
I'll try it later.
You have to concentrate.
Where's the original spot?
Choose carefully. You can't afford any more mistakes.
- Gary. Here... - You can't try that.
- This isn't it. - No, it isn't.
- This isn't it. - I know.
I might...
(Everyone moves upstairs.)
- choose the wrong one again. - You might.
Master Gary, come this way.
Earlier, I definitely saw Jong Kook...
enter this room.
- I wrote his name here. - I can't...
- believe Kwang Soo. - I wrote it.
- He's something. - Look.
- It's my handwriting. - I can't believe him.
- This is it! - Yes.
- This! - This is my handwriting.
- Try this. - This is it.
This...
- was almost useless land. - I think...
it's about time.
- It's your fourth try. - Yes.
- Please. - Try it.
- Please, let this not be it. - I will rip it.
One, two, three!
(Kwang Soo recommended this spot.)
(Will there be a House Deed?)
I have 11 pieces.
You never know what will happen.
(Will there be Jong Kook's House Deed?)
- Yes! - Yes!
(They found Jong Kook's House Deed.)
(I did it!)
(He found it on his fourth try.)
Congratulations!
Hey, get in here.
Give me that.
- Master, I will go outside. - Master.
- Master, here. - Thank you!
- Master. - I knew it from the start.
- Now... - Master Gary.
- Master! - How dare you call my name?
- Then what should I call you? - He's amazing.
Now he owns a big land.
I was going to lose anyway,
so I'm really happy for him.
Now he's in the situation to help the others.
- That's right. - You have a very good insight.
Jong Kook!
You have a great insight.
- He's a good man. - You make me uncomfortable.
Look at everyone following him.
- Master Gary! - Master Gary!
- Unbelievable. - He's unbelievable.
(Gary took over Jong Kook.)
Where do you want to take next?
- I will hear your opinions. - Okay.
- My next target is Ji Hyo. - We need to take her down.
- I will go with Ji Hyo. - If he finds her House Deed...
- I will try to take her land. - It will be amazing if he finds it.
I am certain that it's on the second floor.
- Because... - I think...
She was...
lying down on this room for a long time.
- Was she? - Yes.
- That's strange. - Right?
You normally don't come inside this room.
This piece is very neat.
- Which one? - This one.
- This one is neatly attached. - That one?
(From the start, Ji Hyo focused on this room.)
I will put the House Deed...
(Is her House Deed in this room?)
- This is very nicely attached. - It is.
It's neat, but...
It's usually placed in a corner.
Or maybe it's this one?
- This is... - This room might be a trap.
It's dangerous. Those two are dangerous.
She must have put it under here earlier or she moved it.
- It's very neatly attached. - I will rip it.
- I've been through this, you know? - I will check this one.
It feels really bad.
(It's hard to beat Gary and his butlers.)
Please, please.
(Is the House Deed underneath that piece?)
Come on!
(Bingo)
(He finds the House Deed in one try!)
Master Gary! Master Gary!
(He's as sharp as a detective!)
(I can't believe it.)
- Master. - I told you.
You are unbelievably sharp.
- We now have a female butler. - Yes.
- My dear butlers... - He's taking over everything.
Now, there are...
(Gary even claimed Ji Hyo's land.)
- There are four House Deeds left. - Four House Deeds are left.
- Let's go to Haha's area. - Let's do it.
So this is going to be...
- This is going to be the last one. - It's the last match.
(It's the last one on one match.)
(Why did it have to be you again?)
This is Haha's.
(Haha won the first game,)
(claiming numerous pieces of land.)
Nice. I got all the toilets.
(Haha established his kingdom!)
This is my land.
(Haha's land is spread all over the House.)
(Where would his House Deed be located?)
Where should I put the House Deed?
If you were him, where would you hide it?
I would look for a safe place first.
And at the start,
you don't think about where to hide the House Deed.
He would've first thought about which areas to take over.
He would've first thought about which area would benefit him.
Then it shouldn't be here. Let's look for the most useless area.
Yes.
Let's get this done.
(Let's see.)
It should be somewhere.
(If I were him, where would I hide it?)
Yes.
(Yes!)
That one is suspicious.
He must have heard...
that you could go through the grass.
I will rip that one out.
This one is definitely suspicious.
It's suspicious.
(It's suspicious.)
(I feel it.)
See if the surface is loose.
It's not loose.
Is it well-attached to the floor?
Yes. It's not loose.
(He's nervous.)
I will rip this one out.
Yes, go ahead.
- Now I have three chances left. - Rip it out.
Please.
(Will the House Deed be...)
(in this useless piece of land?)
Please.
It's not here. I told you.
(Now Gary has only three chances.)
But that one is useless too.
Why did he claim that piece next to the table?
(Why did he put two pieces next to the table?)
(I wonder why.)
Not that one. The one in the front.
Why is that piece there?
(He checks it out throughly.)
- It's totally useless. - So...
(I can't watch it.)
I can't watch it.
- I'm really suspicious of this one. - I'm suspicious of this one.
Let's rip this one.
- This one? - Anyway...
It just depends on our luck.
- Right. - I will rip it now.
(This is the land nobody would want.)
(Is the House Deed underneath it?)
He has too many pieces.
(They found the House Deed!)
- Yes! - Yes!
- I told you! I told you! - Seriously?
(How is this possible?)
Really?
(Really?)
We did it.
(Gary and Jong Kook's plan worked!)
I told you.
My butlers are the best!
- We did it! - Look!
- I told you it looked suspicious. - Master! We did it!
We did it.
- I told you! - No!
- No way! - What did I tell you?
(I can't believe the squid beat me.)
I knew it.
That was useless piece of land.
- Master Gary! - Unbelievable.
- Master Gary! - Jong Kook helped me.
Master Gary!
(They finished the game in two more tries.)
- We did it! - Master Gary!
- Hey. - Hey.
Pick up your bag.
- Hey. - What?
- Move over. - Hurry up!
- Hey. - How can you find it so fast?
Master Gary is...
- a legend. - I had two chances left.
I can't believe how sharp I was.
This is why you need good men working for you.
- We did it. - Yes.
- Bravo. - Congratulations, Sir.
- You dominated the world. - He's really amazing.
(Gary wins the Game of the Heirs!)
(Gary claims the House!)
- I admire you. - All right.
Master Gary is amazing.
- He's the most successful squid. - He gets travel tickets.
Really? Take me with you!
Today,
- Ji Yeon played a vital role. - She was amazing.
- She was unbelievable. - She was.
- She played so well. - Really.
- She can't do the simplest thing. - Right.
- But she did the hardest thing. - That's right.
This is what happens when you meet good partners.
- Gary is lucky with girls. - Yes.
How was it, Ji Yeon?
It was really fun playing the game.
I think I brought all the good luck.
- She just complimented herself. - She brought the good luck.
- Ji Yeon... - Nobody even mentioned it.
- You weren't that lucky. - We should be the one to say it.
I brought all the good luck and played the game well.
Thank you!
(Free travel tickets to Jeju Island)
- Say "Nice" once. - Say "Nice".
Say "Nice" please.
Nice!
- Ji Yeon is the best. - She is.
We should invite her here again.
The End