(On an autumn day at Paju, Gyeonggi Province)
(Autumn is here.)
(They have a good feeling today.)
- Hello. - Hello.
- Are we going on a trip? - Hello.
It's still hot although it's fall now.
- North Chungcheong Province. - Backpacks would've been better.
Why are you in the same shirt for weeks?
- This isn't the same shirt. - Do you have only one shirt?
- Is this a different shirt? - It is!
He told me that he has 20 black shirts.
I've never seen...
anyone wearing the same shirt except Steve Jobs.
I thought you'll showcase a new cell phone today.
(They both love black shirts.)
Don't you think it's too early to wear that jacket?
Don't talk about my fashion.
It's such a hot autumn day.
You know I'm a fashionista.
You're in a summer look,
and you're in a winter look.
- Why do all of us have a suitcase? - What's all this?
- I thought we're going on a trip. - What is this?
It's like a uniform.
It looks like we all brought the same suitcase to not lose anyone.
We distributed suitcases to you because you'll go on a trip today.
Did you pack your bags?
We did.
I'm sorry, but will we really stay here?
(The place looks very empty.)
(Will they really stay here?)
I can't believe we'll stay here today.
No one would ever want to stay in a container.
For our special trip,
we invited special guests here.
(We'll introduce our guests to you.)
- There they are. - Really?
(They're coming.)
- That's Na Rae. - Se Chan and Na Rae are here.
Hi, Sol Bin.
(We're here to make your trip extraordinary!)
- Look at Na Rae. - She dressed up too much.
Isn't it a little excessive?
By the way, she and Soo Hong look good together.
Are they a couple?
It feels like they don't want to be with me.
- Hello. - Introduce them to us.
- Hello. - It is...
- She's Sol Bin. - It's like a movie from the 70s.
- Welcome! - Hello, Sol Bin.
- Hello. - It's good to see you.
His mother now allowed him to go clubbing.
- Right. - There's no one who saw...
her son go clubbing on television except your mother.
- Your mother is the first one. - She is.
(Soo Hong went clubbing in a television programme.)
My goodness.
I never mentioned about clubbing before, but Jae Seok brought it up.
- He blamed me a lot. - Of course.
Since I was young back then,
I was worried I couldn't get married because of what you said.
I resented you a lot.
Soo Hong, you were 44 at that time.
(You weren't young.)
- My goodness. - You can't say you were young.
(He was a young guy at the age of 44.)
You weren't young because you were 44.
He called me and told me he's in trouble.
He even said he was scolded by his nephews.
He blamed me a lot,
but now he's in the spotlight because of that club episode.
- My nephews are proud of me now. - Right.
His nephews told him during the holidays that they're proud of him.
- So Seok Jin goes clubbing, too. - He's right.
- That's a problem. - You can't go clubbing, Seok Jin.
- He called me and asked, - Please take me clubbing.
"Do clubs open on Sundays, too?"
- He really asked me. - Goodness.
- Gosh. - That's a problem.
- Hello, Na Rae. - Hello.
Gosh, Na Rae...
(Shy)
- Why do you put your hand there? - Please lower your hand.
What's wrong with you?
- Gosh. - I'm sorry.
- She's trying to look sexy. - No way.
Please wipe the lipstick off your teeth.
(You got lipstick on your teeth.)
- You shouldn't say that. - What is this?
- But... - You can wipe her teeth for her.
How can I wipe it with my fingers?
- I can't do that. - Why didn't you tell me earlier?
And we have Lee Kyu Han with us.
(A rising entertainer, Lee Kyu Han)
Kyu Han.
It's nice to see you here, Kyu Han.
But I never expected you here, though.
He's stuck between these comedians.
He's a rising entertainer.
- He appeared in "Knowing Bros". - "Knowing Bros"...
- Right, he did. - I saw it, too.
- He was funny there. - I saw him...
- He did a lot of funny things. - Kyu Han.
You don't have to try too hard to explain...
because I also have no idea why I'm here.
When I first saw Na Rae and Soo Hong,
I thought you were wearing blue screens.
(People in special effects)
They can change our clothes using special effects.
You've become a good entertainer.
How have you been doing, Kyu Han?
I prepared a lot...
- because it's a popular show. - Right.
I'll do my best...
Gosh, there's a wasp.
(She's making a fuss.)
- So this... - Gosh.
People have a misconception about wasps.
People stay still when they see wasps near them,
but an expert said we must not stay still.
- Really? - No way!
- That's dangerous. - You shouldn't stay still.
- It's good only for wasps. - He's so hilarious.
If we stay still, we'll give enough time...
- for wasps to sting us. - That's right.
I heard that we must not wear sweaters.
- Why not? - Wasps get stuck in the sweater...
- There's an insect... - and think we're attacking them.
Hold on.
What on earth are you doing?
- Are you out of your mind? - You can't do that!
- Jae Seok! Are you crazy? - What are you trying to do?
- But there was an insect... - You can't do that!
- There was an insect on her... - I'll do it for you.
My goodness.
- Let it go. - Good.
- Gosh. - Now I'm relieved.
Se Chan is here with us!
Hello.
Se Chan is Se Hyung's younger brother.
- Are you two really brothers? - Yes, we are.
Se Hyung and Se Chan have the same parents.
How is Se Hyung like at home?
Does he really behave like an older brother?
When people ask me who I respect and admire the most,
- I always say it's Se Hyung. - Why?
He's very honest and polite.
(What about that incident?)
The way he thinks...
But isn't he a troublemaker?
I won't make any excuses about that.
(He admits right away.)
A troublemaker...
- It wasn't like a big crime. - I'm good friends with them.
Let's not insult each other's family.
- Se Chan. - Yes?
That's all for your interview.
(His interview ends abruptly.)
- About my brother... - Se Chan is closed to tears.
Both Se Chan and Se Hyung are really busy these days.
Se Chan barely managed to spare his time for us.
- I'm glad you're here. - Thank you.
You're all sweaty.
Seriously,
I feel really hot here.
I think your skirt will melt.
That's why I told you not to wear that.
Seok Jin finally took his leather jacket off.
- It's really hot. - Isn't it?
- I'm going crazy. - It really drives me crazy.
- I feel like I'm on fire. - He finally took his jacket off.
Actually, I thought his jacket looks like a wrapper.
Seok Jin wants to know about this lady.
It's Sol Bin!
(A rising star, Sol Bin)
- A rising star. - I have a crush on you.
I have a crush on you.
Hello, I'm Sol Bin of Laboum.
(All guys can't help but smiling.)
- She's so pretty. - Well,
I have a crush on her, too. Who else will have a crush on her?
Kwang Soo already has a crush on her.
- Again? - Kwang Soo.
Look at him smiling.
He loves ladies who have "Bin" in their names.
You like Sun Bin and Soo Bin as well.
I think he's nickname should be Playboy.
What are you talking about?
- That's too much. - How can you ever say that to me?
All right. So we're on a trip today,
but I have no idea where we'll stay.
Before we start,
we have a box which has balls in four different colours.
We'll divide you into 4 teams with 3 members each.
- Gosh. - We don't know who'll be with us.
- Pick a ball first, Kwang Soo. - Okay.
There goes Playboy.
There's only one person I want to be with.
I have a green ball.
(Kwang Soo is in Green Team.)
I wonder what team I will be in.
Please!
It will be funny if you pick a green one.
- Right. - Yes.
My goodness.
(Jong Kook is in Orange Team.)
This is Soo Hong's turn.
- You... - You can't do that!
(He puts the ball back into the box.)
(Everyone complains.)
- You can't do that. - It's because of my sunglasses.
Just pick one quickly.
If you do that again, I'll cut your wrist.
(He picks a ball.)
(Soo Hong is in Red Team.)
It's Na Rae's turn now.
Who do you want to be with?
I want to be in the same team with Jae Seok.
A shaman told me you'll bring me luck.
- I mean it. - I wish I could meet that shaman.
(Na Rae takes out an orange ball.)
- It's Jong Kook's team. - We don't know if it's good yet.
- Okay. - You rule in your team.
It's Kyu Han's turn.
It's a blue ball.
- Why is there a blue ball? - Are there four teams?
- Now, Se Chan. - I don't...
- want to be in Na Rae's team. - It's okay.
- What a relief. - It's green.
- They are lucky. - Nice.
- Now, it's Sol Bin's turn. - Today...
- Ji Hyo, pick red. - Today's highlight.
(He's anticipating.)
Let Sol Bin pick last.
- That's not fair. - Why?
- The chances will decrease. - It's okay.
- This is not good. - What is it? Green.
(Seok Jin is in Green Team.)
Green Team is doomed.
I can't believe it.
(If I could turn the clock back.)
Green Team is done. They have all three.
How come I should be with Kwang Soo and Seok Jin?
(He's so frustrated about his team members.)
- One team is ready now. - Okay.
One team is complete.
(Green Team is organised like this.)
Why don't they pick together?
Now, Ji Hyo.
- Sol Bin and Ji Hyo. - I guess it'll be blue.
Pick blue.
- Good. - Great.
(Ji Hyo joins Orange Team.)
Let's go.
Jong Kook has been teamed up with girls these days.
- Gosh. - How lucky you are.
- You're lucky to be with girls. - What did you say?
- It's true. - You're lucky.
Is this something you should be upset about?
It is true that you're lucky to have us.
- They're all wearing hats. - They go well with each other.
- The team in hats look good. - Right.
I'm getting nervous.
You should have let her choose sooner.
- There is no big difference. - Right.
Go. Let's go.
Go. Pick blue.
(You should be with us.)
- Pick blue. - It's red.
(Sol Bin becomes a Red Team member.)
(The middle-aged clubber is thrilled.)
- I'm so lucky. - He is.
(Haha put Sol Bin's ball back in so that she can choose last.)
- Wait. He put the ball back in. - She should pick last.
Oh, that's right.
(Soo Hong shoots a red ball to Haha.)
Please calm down.
(He's angry at Haha.)
- Though it's a show, I can't... - Get back.
(The man is infuriated.)
- This is not fair. - Calm down.
She was supposed to pick last.
- This is so funny. - Please...
- Soo Hong is disappointed. - It's Gary, now.
(Gary goes first.)
- Ta-da. - Soo Hong's team.
(Gary is a Red Team member.)
You'll make me unlucky.
How could you say that?
- I'm sorry. - Just wait and see.
- You'll be glad to have me. - Sorry.
Kyu Han is secretly smiling.
(Kyu Hand is secretly smiling.)
- Let's wait and see. It's not over. - This is ridiculous.
This is thrilling.
- Haha's turn. - Let's make a great team.
He picked one.
Gosh.
(Haha joins Blue Team.)
(Red Team is so happy.)
(But he is disappointed.)
- The chances are 50-50. - It is.
- I can't be in her team, right? - You can't.
Why did you wait until the last moment?
- Gosh. - Jae Seok can't team up with her.
- Please. - Let's pay attention.
- Sol Bin, go ahead. - Please.
One team will have Sol Bin and the other will have me.
- I picked one. - She did.
- Blue Team versus... - Red Team.
One will have me and the other will have Sol Bin.
- Please. - Please.
One...
(It's either Jae Seok or Sol Bin.)
- Two... - Pick red.
(Please)
Three.
(Sol Bin is in Blue Team and Jae Seok is in Red Team.)
(They experience contrary feelings.)
- Goodness. - That was close.
Oh my gosh.
We win.
- Oh my. - We made it.
- He made it. - So we set the teams.
- They're so lucky. - Right.
- Kyu Han looks so happy. - Kyu Han does.
- He said he didn't want to come, - I know.
- but now, he's so smiley. - What a lucky team.
I bet time will fly today.
- Gosh. - He's funny.
- Why am I teamed up with him? - I don't know why.
They are unluckier than you.
(They're worse than you.)
- I feel miserable. - I feel bad for them.
I have Seok Jin and Kwang Soo.
- It's the worst combination. - That's too harsh.
How could you say that?
- Just admit it. It's true. - It's not that bad.
Please take care of me.
Now that you're all teamed up, you'll be now on a trip.
The place for your trip is...
a house that you don't want to get out of...
because it's full of fun.
Have a nice day playing various games.
You have to purchase all food, your necessities...
and lands with R money in the house.
- Do we have to purchase lands? - Yes.
You can get R money in the pawnshop.
It can be exchanged with the outfit and possessions you have.
The team that goes bankrupt after losing all R money and the lands...
is eliminated automatically and has to get penalty.
- Do we have to purchase things? - Yes.
The more R money and the more lands you have, the better it is.
So utilise the two assets to win the race.
- Do we have exceptions? - No.
We can exchange our outfits and possessions with R money?
You mean I have to take off my clothes?
(Breaking news. Na Rae didn't mind taking off her clothes for R money.)
Na Rae, what are you trying to get at?
How far can I go?
(Until you don't violate censorship)
I'll show you the pawnshop where you can exchange R money.
(What will the pawnshop for R money look like?)
(The Man's Pawnshop?)
(Is that the scary pawnshop from the movie?)
(Then is the owner...)
(He expects another Bin.)
- It's Gwang Rok. - Gwang Rok.
(It's not Won Bin but Gwang Rok.)
He's Gwang Rok from "People Looking for Laughter".
His famous line is "Just do it."
- "Sure. Sure. Just do it." - "Just do it."
- "Just do it." - "Just do it."
- That sketch is funny. - If you look in the front,
there will be a table for price.
- 50 R for the tops. - Cell phones?
- If I check my top, do I get 50 R? - The tops?
The clothes we're wearing?
- The clothes we're in? - I think that's right.
- You mean these? - What should we wear, then?
And do we turn in our own shoes?
- Even the shoes? - Yes.
- Then we'll be barefoot. - Without shoes?
- R money must be very important. - Girls will be uncomfortable.
I think I need to exchange both the top and the bottom.
- A top is worth... - 50 R.
- Here is 50 R. - I'll give you my bottom, too.
- You take bottoms, too, right? - Yes, they are 50 R.
(They got all dressed up without knowing this.)
I need to change my trousers.
Giving you my shoes means that I gave up on my height.
- Please give me 10 R more. - Let me take a look.
Don't they look new?
(Just go.)
(There is no deal because of the odour.)
- No. - Please.
I almost took five R back from you.
I'm not kidding.
Sir, these are very new.
The insoles are separate.
- These are related to pride. - Put them down first.
- This... - Go ahead.
- Is it a matching ring? - Yes, here you go.
- It fits your finger perfectly. - Please give her five R for it.
- Please give me a lot. - Here you go.
Could you give me that, too?
- Give her one more. - Here.
- This is it. - Thank you.
Thank you.
Here is my bottom.
- Is it your underwear? - No, they're short trousers.
- Did you wear it or not? - Gwang Rok.
I've worn them just once.
Just accept them.
- Here they are. - These are trousers.
This is good wine and this is an autographed ball.
These are first-aid medicine.
- You keep the medicine. - These are beauty products.
- This shop is crowded. - 230 R, please.
Give some more.
Don't force him. I wouldn't want to give you R money, either.
- Give me 10 R more, please. - Did you say 10 R?
- What? - You said...
- 10 R? - What did you say?
- You sound like you're swearing. - 20 R...
- 20 R? - I didn't swear.
How could you be so rude?
- I didn't... - Apologise to us.
- Apologise immediately. - I'm sorry.
- 20 R... - What? Did you swear again?
- I mean 20 R money. - You did.
This guy has no manners.
(We'll fix that problem next time.)
(R money each team acquired)
You have R money now, but there is something more important than that.
Who conquers the lands first matters...
- the most. - That's the most important.
It matters the most.
- We should try our best here. - Okay.
(The right to conquer the lands first gives you a huge advantage.)
No matter how much R money you have,
if other teams buy all the lands before you, you'll be in trouble.
I know.
In order to decide...
who buys the lands first, you'll have to...
have one-legged fights.
- Okay. - Okay.
(Let's buy the advantageous spot.)
- Let's go. - We can do it.
Choose the leader of each team and let me know.
(Choose the leader of each team to have a fight.)
I won't cut slacks even to girls. Even if it's Sol Bin.
Don't worry. He's just bluffing.
It feels like real Running Man now.
- Kwang Soo, write it down. - Okay, let's go.
I will tear all your pants today.
- Why would you tear pants? - You'd better be careful.
- Why would you tear pants? - Why would you?
I'll not give you a break.
- Age doesn't matter. - We'll be merciless...
even to Sol Bin.
(The players who will have a one-legged fight are...)
(Jong Kook, Soo Hong, Kyu Han and Se Chan.)
(The fight to conquer the lands first has started.)
(The king of a one-legged fight, Kim Jong Kook)
We should attack Jong Kook together.
(Park Soo Hong with strong legs due to dancing)
(A smart player, Lee Kyu Han)
(Yang Se Chan who is so eager to win)
(To get the right to purchase the lands first)
(The winner can occupy the crucial zones including the bathroom.)
One player from each team.
We should attack Jong Kook together. Otherwise, we don't have a chance.
That's right.
(The first target is Jong Kook.)
(Guys, let's make an alliance. Okay?)
(Okay. We stand a chance if it is 3 against 1.)
(His leg is already shaking.)
- Together. - That's right.
My left leg really hurts so bad.
(Already?)
We can't afford to lose, Se Chan.
- We can't even go to the toilet! - My knees are weak.
- Hang in there. - My knees hurt.
(He falls over.)
What was that?
(I'm sorry, everyone.)
- What are you doing? - What was that?
- Are you kidding me? - What was that?
That was fast.
What was that?
- You said you could do this. - Hold on.
One, two.
Kyu Han's been working out.
He's got stamina.
- Let's work together. - We should have done better.
- This is great. - Let's get the tiger.
Let's do this.
- On the count of three. - Let's go.
(Jong Kook, are you ready?)
- Come over here. - Let's go!
(Soo Hong distracts Jong Kook.)
Here I go!
(Kyu Han charges forward.)
(Can you please get rid of that monster?)
Here I go!
Here I come!
- What are you doing? - Why are you going for him?
(Why are you attacking me?)
Here I go!
Where are you going?
- What are you doing? - What was that?
You're supposed to be working together.
We came in third.
I'm in second place, right?
(Orange Team takes 1st place, Red Team 2nd and Blue Team 3rd.)
- Are you stupid or something? - Second place isn't that bad.
- Are you stupid? - What is this?
(What have you done?)
What is this?
(I don't know why I did that.)
You will now occupy the land of your choice.
Let's go buy some land.
Good work, everyone.
Basically, we need...
an area where we can cook.
- This area costs 30 R. - We have to get this one.
Let's get these two.
- These two? - Okay.
We need a way out.
We need to go to the washroom. Let's see here.
Let's go for the area near the kitchen and the washroom.
We can jump over here.
Okay.
(The door to the washroom)
(She barely makes it over.)
- We've got a problem. - What?
- My legs are too short to cross. - What?
- Let's just buy more, then. - Okay.
We need all three of them.
It only costs 30 R.
They won't be able to cross.
We have to purchase this as well.
- We have to buy this. - We won't make it across otherwise.
- We need to purchase this area. - Yes.
- That's right. - One, two.
This is looking good.
- Nice. - Good job, everyone.
(Red Team starts purchasing land.)
Let's see.
We have the most money.
We could eat here.
Gary, we need to purchase this land...
if we're going to eat sitting down.
Let's get this one and the one over there.
- Good idea. - Just get all of them.
- Gary, we're filthy rich. - Aren't we spending too much?
- Don't worry. - What are we saving up for?
You're spending too lavishly since you started clubbing.
- Isn't this too much? - Not at all.
- What now? - Let's get the 10 R ones.
- We should buy all of them. - Yes.
Can you cover up this area with the tiles?
Please cover them.
- We can charge them the toll fee. - This is good.
(Red Team has spent 230 R for the area near the washroom.)
Let's buy the land near the turntable.
- There's a turntable? - Look over there.
Na Rae will want to go over there.
Gary, let's buy the land near the turntable.
- We have 115 R left. - That's a lot.
That's a lot.
What are we supposed to do?
This is ridiculous.
Should we buy one over here?
They might be in a hurry to go to the washroom.
- Let's buy this one right here. - Should we?
We have no choice.
What should we do?
That's it for us.
How much is that?
(Blue Team has 200 R remaining.)
Is it our turn now?
Let's buy the entire area right here.
- Sounds good. - Okay.
We need to buy them all.
We'll purchase the entire vacant area.
How much is that?
It's 390 R.
Do you think we spent too much?
You guys are cheating.
(The dangerous game begins now.)
(You can easily go bankrupt.)
I know it's somewhere.
(Who will go bankrupt and receive the penalty?)
You've all purchased your lands.
Before you go inside, I'll tell you the rules of No Way Out Race.
The number one rule is that...
you can only stay on the area you've purchased.
If you step on someone else's land,
you have to pay the toll fee.
That's too harsh.
That's way too harsh.
- We'll be fine. - If you're hungry,
you can purchase food with your R money...
from the snack bar outside.
It's up to you how you spend your money.
How are we going to get out?
If you want to eat,
- you have to go over our land. - I got it.
Gosh, you little...
(What are you doing?)
(Let's see what happens when you tease me again.)
- Why'd you do that? - Good job.
We have ladies watching.
At least Sol Bin turned away. Why'd you two look?
Thanks for that.
(It was a great sight to see.)
Don't picture it in your head.
Don't.
(Please forget about what you just saw.)
You can now go inside.
Let's go inside.
Let's take the tolls first.
- Pay up. - Hold on.
They can make their way around our land.
- I see. - Go sideways.
- Let's go, Gary. - This is easy.
- We have to charge them. - You have to let us in at least.
Give me the money first.
I have a suggestion.
Why don't we intentionally step on Orange Team's land?
- That's a good idea. - I don't want to pay Red Team.
- Let's do that. - Who needs Red Team?
We'll give you a discount.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
- Orange Team! - Orange Team!
Their land and ours cost the same 10 R.
We're going to give them a discount.
You can't do that.
Isn't five R too expensive?
We can negotiate the price.
We'll let you go with two R.
- Two R? - Two R?
Did you say two R?
- We'll do one R. - What?
- Let's go with that. - Orange Team!
- Orange Team! - One R?
Just pick which one you want to step on.
Be careful or you might step on our land.
If you do,
we'll charge you the usual price.
- You heard him. - It'll be five R.
It's not too late to pay us.
This is your last chance.
- I see. - It's one R, right, Jong Kook?
- Yes. - Let's go.
Can you get on my back, Se Chan?
- Se Chan. - I can't.
- Just try. - Yes, I'm fine.
(Oh no)
That's 20 R in total.
- Can you start moving? - Hey!
(Kwang Soo's shoes got stuck on the carpet.)
That's 20 R.
Pay up.
- It's 20 R. - The floor was sticky.
- Give us the money. - You don't understand.
- The floor was sticky. - What was that?
- This is a foul. - That's too bad.
- We have to start over. - Is this...
Someone pushed us.
Isn't this for catching bugs?
Why is it so sticky?
This is not going to work.
- We picked the right area. - This is good.
Let's just give them the money.
- That'll be one R each. - Okay.
- Pay up. - That's better.
- That's one R. - Okay.
You can make it over with just three R.
Just step on the orange one.
Step on the orange one.
I'll help you jump over.
- Step on the red. - That's two R.
- That's three. - Good.
That's four.
- Make the jump. - That's five.
Just go slowly.
That's 6, 7...
and eight.
That's eight R in total.
Get down from there, Seok Jin.
- We'll let you all go with 10 R. - Okay.
- 10 R for all three of us? - Yes.
Let's go.
That'll do it.
Nice.
(He steps on Orange Team's land.)
Oh, no.
That'll be one R.
You stepped on it.
No, he didn't.
(Why is it so hard to come home?)
I'm going to jump.
- What? - I think I can do this.
You're really doing it?
(Here I go.)
(Fly like a butterfly, land like a bee.)
(Jae Seok interrupts him.)
You stepped on our land.
Pay up.
That'll be two R.
- Give us the money. - I'll go now.
We'll let you all go with 10 R.
- Okay. - Off you go.
Thanks.
- You can just step on our land. - You can go.
That'll be 10 R.
What now?
You'll have to jump all the way over there.
Here it goes.
You could get hurt.
(He hops over.)
- That was amazing. - How'd he do that?
Oh, my.
Jong Kook, move over.
- Okay. - I'm going to keep an eye on you.
He's not going to make it.
(He hops over.)
It's Sol Bin's turn.
- Be careful. - You dropped this.
Be careful, Sol Bin.
(She screams...)
(and falls over.)
(I tripped myself.)
- What are you doing? - That'll be five R.
Ours is five R, too.
- It's five R. - Congratulations.
Give us the money.
- It's five R. - We're not giving you a discount.
It's five R.
Give us the money.
This is nice.
- Take a seat. - We have chairs.
This is comfortable.
This was a good buy.
You don't have a couch.
This is so comfortable.
You guys are hilarious.
What are you doing on that couch with all this empty space?
What are you doing over there?
Kyu Han said this is the Green Belt.
There's nothing there for them.
- How much money did we make? - You don't know that.
- We made a lot. - I heard it's getting redeveloped.
How are you going to eat?
- What? - How are you going to eat?
We'll order delivery.
We'll have delivery food.
- Do you want some ramyeon? - Let's go outside...
- and get some ramyeon. - Let's go.
- Let's get some ramyeon. - Excuse me.
- Can you get some for us, too? - I'll go.
- Gary. - What?
Where are you going?
What kind of ramyeon do you want?
- Can you get some for us as well? - I don't really care.
This is really comfortable.
(Red Team bought all the land near the entrance.)
The house is quite big.
Things on the menu are quite expensive.
Can I have three cup noodles?
Yes. Three of them.
(They will cost 60 R.)
60 R please.
- 60 R? Why? - Yes.
- Cup noodles costs 20 R each. - 20 R each? Wait a minute.
How much are those packaged noodles?
I will buy three packaged noodles instead.
- Are you sure? - Yes.
We give a pair of chopsticks if you buy cup noodles.
But you don't get any if you buy packaged noodles.
(Do we have to buy chopsticks? That's so cruel.)
- You have to buy them separately. - How much are they?
- A pair of them costs 10 R. - 10 R for chopsticks?
Yes. Really.
10 R for a pair of chopsticks is crazy.
Then you should buy cup noodles.
Okay. I'll buy cup noodles.
(No matter what he buys, he has to spend 20 R.)
How can you sell a pair of chopsticks separately?
It's usually free if I buy noodles at the convenience store.
- I will deliver these for you. - Oh, will you?
- Yes. Just pay me 10 R and... - No, thank you.
You're really greedy.
- Come again. - Bye.
(The kitchen is ours. Let's cook some noodles. Shall we?)
(We don't have any money but we'd like some too.)
- Let's buy something together. - Shall we?
- Let's collect money. - Can we pass through their area?
All right. Let's see how much money we have. How much do you have?
- We only have 50 R. - Only 50 R?
Where can we earn more R money?
- We don't have any money left. - So we have 50 R.
We have to buy chopsticks separately.
- We will go out and buy them. - Let's just split the toll fee.
Hey. Orange Team.
How much is it for a round trip?
- Round trip? - Yes.
Pay us five R for it.
- How much is it? - Five R for a round trip.
Five R for a round trip sounds reasonable.
All right. Pass through.
- Hurry up. Go. - Check the prices before buying.
(They pay the Orange Team 5 R for a round trip.)
- It's tough. - We bought the wrong area.
We have to pay every time we want to go somewhere.
- Hello, Ms Do. - Hello.
- Hi, there. - Give us two packaged noodles.
- Would two be enough? - Packaged noodles sound okay.
How many do you want? Three? Four?
- Let's buy three. - Three will be enough.
Should we buy a dried filefish fillet? It costs only 10 R.
Shouldn't we buy something to drink, too?
We can drink the soup from the noodles.
(We can't afford water. It's too expensive.)
- Let's buy an egg. Shall we? - An egg?
(They keep buying.)
- Let's buy an egg. - We don't have any eggs.
- Oh, they do have eggs. - Thank you.
- Bye, Ms Do. - Bye.
What should we buy?
Hear me, Kwang Soo. We should lie about the prices.
Let's tell them that we paid 30 R for each and ask 15 R.
We can sell these noodles for 30 R and earn 10 R in total.
30 R sounds really expensive.
No, 30 R for two packages is fine. We'll tell them we paid 15 R each.
Let's tell them we paid 40 R for this dried filefish fillet.
- We must eat something first... - We can cook any time we want.
- to deal with other things later. - I'm sure we can.
- Gosh. - We shouldn't eat noodles...
- Gosh. It hurts. - My gosh.
(Jong Kook pretends to be gravely injured.)
What's wrong with you? How can you hurt him like that?
- Look at him. He's in pain. - Gosh, it really hurts.
- Where's the manager? - Call the manager.
Is this how you treat your customers? He's really weak.
- He gets hurt so easily. - The board hit me. It really hurts.
Please stop that nonsense. Would you?
- You must pay 10 R for that. - No. I'll pay five R.
- Come on. You know him. - I will only pay five R.
He's a good fighter.
(Really?)
- I won't pay 10 R. - All right, then.
Five R sounds okay.
Don't tell others. Please.
- Don't worry, we won't. - Okay. I'll pay five R.
- Are you all right, Jong Kook? - Gosh. It really hurts.
- That was your fault, wasn't it? - You should've put it properly.
- I'm sorry. - Here is your five R.
- Gosh, I'm too kind. - My goodness.
You must be an angel. I've never seen anyone like you.
- I'll forgive him for only five R. - You're so generous.
- Here is your five R. Take it. - Okay.
Thank you.
- Hope your business goes well. - Okay. Bye.
- I nearly got injured. - What's wrong with him?
(They finish their shopping.)
- These are all we could afford. - Haha.
- All right. How much were they? - We paid 20 R for each.
- 20 R? Really? - Yes. This was 30 R.
- So it cost 30 R each? - No, 20 R.
These noodles were 20 R each and this was...
Hold on a second. Didn't you tell us that you only had 50 R?
- They cost way more than 50 R... - Sol Bin,
- listen to him first. - so it doesn't make any sense.
- They cost 100 R altogether. - Sol Bin is really smart.
- You're trying to overcharge us. - No. That's not true.
In fact, we had more than 50 R.
Do you think it makes sense? No way.
I'm sorry. We're really short on money.
I'm so glad that we can stay out of their fight.
Really.
I'm so glad that I'm not the one who is arguing with you.
We will pay you 10 R.
- We... - Let's cook our noodles together.
We'll pay 10 R for using the kitchen.
- Okay. - Let's pay five R each.
I'll pay you four R.
Don't be so stingy.
- We're running out of money. - I know you can afford five R.
Should we eat one uncooked?
- Shall we? - Okay. Let's eat it that way.
- All right. Gather up here. - Sit in a circle.
Uncooked noodles is a good appetiser.
- We're a team. Don't betray us. - All right.
You can count on me.
It looks good.
It's really delicious.
- Wow. This is delicious. - It really is.
Your noodles are ready.
Okay.
Please come and take it.
- My goodness. - Amazing.
Seok Jin, here's your bowl.
- How is it? - I'm fine. You can have it.
- Those noodles look so delicious. - They really do.
(They paid almost everything for this.)
- It smells great, too. - Hey. How are your noodles?
- Are they cooking something? - We're cooking kimchi jjim soon.
- Are they cooking kimchi jjim? - We're boiling water already.
- They even have samgyeopsal. - How are your noodles?
- We have 1.5kg of samgyeopsal. - My goodness.
We also have ripened kimchi from two years ago.
- Here's the samgyeopsal. - How much is it?
I'll tell you later after we finish cooking.
(First, they put in the ripened kimchi.)
It smells really delicious.
- That's amazing. - I can smell it, too.
- Look at her. - That kimchi jjim must be awesome.
- My goodness. - Look at her.
- Look at Na Rae. - It smells awesome.
She is cooking, but she seems really relaxed and comfortable.
Look at Na Rae. She's amazing.
(Here comes the special ingredient,)
(MSG powder.)
(We should call it MSG jjim instead of kimchi jjim.)
(How would MSG jjim taste like?)
It's amazing.
This is really delicious.
(They are enjoying their noodles.)
It's amazing.
(Seok Jin must be thirsty.)
It's really delicious.
(Orange Team has enough water to quench their thirst.)
Excuse me.
- May I have a glass of water? - Do you want some water?
- Yes. I'm really thirsty. - It's two R.
I'm really thirsty.
Show us how much water we get for two R, first.
Here. You'll get a bowl of water.
- I will pay one R for that. - Yes. We'll pay one R.
- That's not one R. It's an egg. - We will give you this egg instead.
We will give you this egg instead of one R.
No way. Gary paid 10 R for this bottle of water.
- 10 R for a bottle of water? - We'll give you half the bottle...
- for two R. - It's really expensive.
- It's a good deal. - We shouldn't buy it, guys.
- Aren't you thirsty? - It's only two R.
- Two R sounds okay. - We should buy it.
- Are you sure? - Let's put this over there first.
(Blue Team decides to store their water for later use.)
- Do you mean this one? - Yes.
- Hey, Kwang Soo. - What?
(There's some water over there.)
- I wonder who it was. - We can't sit down and eat.
- No. We can sit here and eat. - You can sit here and eat.
(Really? Can we take it for free?)
- Blue Team members can eat it. - Yes, we can.
(Kwang Soo takes the bowl of water from Blue Team's shelf.)
(What is he doing?)
(Gulping)
(We want to drink, too.)
(Isn't that...)
(our water?)
What are you doing?
Hey.
You filthy thieves!
Who took the bowl filled with water from this shelf?
- It's not me. - Where's our water?
- It's gone. - It's right over there.
- Where? - Where is it? We didn't do it.
- Hey. How could you do that? - We didn't do it.
Do you mean this book? I can't drink this book.
We're done. I mean it.
You took our water.
(The alliance between Blue Team and Green Team is about to end.)
- How could you do this? - Look at that.
- I didn't even sip it. - You must pay four R for the water.
- Come on, Haha. - Take this and pay four R.
- You took our water. - That was our water.
(Na Rae's kimchi jjim is ready.)
Wow. It looks amazing.
Excuse me.
Hey. Hold on a minute.
Seok Jin, hold on a minute.
- Here. Take this. - There's some samgyeopsal, too.
- It's really delicious. - We should buy that kimchi jjim.
Hey. How much is that kimchi jjim?
- Do you want a dish of kimchi jjim? - Yes.
(I'd love to have a bite.)
All right, everyone.
- It's 15 R. - I'll buy it.
(I'll gladly pay 15 R for that kimchi jjim!)
- It's 15 R. - We'll eat it.
- We will pay 15 R. - Yes, we will.
- I'll gladly pay it. - You owe a great deal of money.
- Come on. We'll pay the money. - It must be really delicious.
(However, Green Team cannot afford the kimchi jjim.)
We should've saved up some money instead of buying so much land.
(I'll sell this area for kimchi jjim.)
- No. - What are you doing?
(Seok Jin, we mustn't sell our land.)
- Come on. Let's sell our land. - No, we shouldn't.
- Let's sell it and eat kimchi jjim. - No. Please don't.
Let's just sell our land and enjoy.
(Other teams are enjoying their lovely kimchi jjim.)
- I gave you some extra meat. - Really? Thank you.
- You're welcome. - Thank you so much.
It's really delicious.
She should open her own restaurant.
I think she can. It's so delicious.
- Come on. - I won't let you sell our land.
Let's sell the land and enjoy what we can.
(No. We won't sell our land.)
- Hey. - I'm sorry.
- Let's sell the land. - Wait.
What is that?
It's time for a move-in celebration.
You must be really happy to move into your new home.
Why don't you buy some food to celebrate each other?
(What do you mean by "move-in celebration"?)
"Each team must choose a team and buy two dishes of food for them."
You can buy food from the cafeteria.
You must eat all the food you've received.
- So we must assign a team... - We will get food from other teams.
Don't we have to buy the food?
Isn't this for some kind of attack?
Do we make others go to the bathroom?
- There comes the store owner. - There she is.
Do we sell the land if we don't have any R?
Yes, you must sell the land to buy two dishes for the assigned teams.
We have five R, but there's nothing we can buy.
Please attack my team with watermelon.
I'm so thirsty.
Let's attack each other with watermelon.
Let's do that.
Let's give each other watermelon.
(Do they agree to exchange watermelons?)
- Give us watermelon. - Give each team a watermelon.
That sounds good. Let's have one watermelon.
- Right now, Kyu Han is... - It's hard to hold it.
Okay, let's get one watermelon.
Get him one watermelon and some sports drink.
- He's trying so hard. - All right, please pay up.
(Until then, no one knew...)
(that the watermelon would cause such a disaster.)
- What? - We can attack now.
Sell our land so we can attack.
What's the use of that piece in the middle?
Let's sell two pieces of land in the middle.
No, sell the piece at the edge.
We don't need to get to that sofa. Let's sell it.
Does anyone want to buy it for cheap?
- No. - No one wants it.
- We'll sell it for seven R. - Pardon me?
- The bank would buy it for five R. - Seok Jin.
Its appraised value is five R.
- That's not what I mean. Listen. - You insist on a higher price.
- If you pay me seven R... - Don't say seven R.
(Be careful of the pronunciation.)
(How dare you call for seven R?)
What did you say?
Seven R?
Let's not price it seven R.
- Watch your words. - I said seven R.
(His words were misunderstood. He meant seven R.)
What's wrong with what I said? Don't ask for seven R.
- Goodness. - We don't have much money.
- We don't have much money. - Kwang Soo.
What's the point of having that piece of land? Sell it.
You never know if it'll come to use.
- What's the use if you lose? - Let's have a watermelon party.
If you don't, we won't give you watermelon, either.
(Let's just sell it.)
(Please don't sell the land.)
Let's sell them all.
Let me go.
Please stop, Seok Jin.
(His shorts are coming off.)
(Things are a mess for Green Team.)
He begged and said, "Please stop, Seok Jin."
Let me go.
Aren't you sad that...
- we have no money? - Please stop, Seok Jin.
No, you can't.
(Let's talk it out instead.)
- Please, Seok Jin. - We're too poor.
- Let it go. - He's like a cartoon character.
(If only the land wasn't part of the greenbelt,)
(they could sell it.)
He looks like that grandfather who appears in the cartoon "Dooly".
You look so pathetic.
- Here's the watermelon. - Gosh.
(Watermelon that will make you urinate appears.)
- Thank you. - Thank you for the watermelon.
Thank you for the watermelon.
This watermelon is delicious.
It's delicious.
It's sweet.
(Everyone sits around their own land and hydrates.)
It's tasty.
This is great.
There are no seeds at all.
Kyu Han, aren't you good at imitating others?
- I can mimic Lee Bum Soo. - Lee Bum Soo?
- Shall I do it? - Please do.
- It's been a long time. - I've never seen him do it.
(Bum Soo's spirit is possessing Kyu Han.)
He sounds just like him.
Do you know how much you've done wrong?
(He's quite good.)
Se Chan, is there anything you can do?
I can sing "Don't Worry" by Jeon In Kwon...
- with a shaky, nasal voice. - Okay.
(Will he be possessed by the spirit?)
(My dear)
(Don't worry about anything)
(Let's)
(Sing together)
He tried so hard to come up with this.
(Bury all the painful memories)
(This proves that he's a comedian.)
- He's good. - He's good.
He's definitely a comedian.
(He takes a big bite.)
(Everyone is hydrating.)
- It's an ointment. - It's a bug repellent.
Let's see.
Isn't watermelon interesting?
- Why? - I want to urinate right away.
I want to go to the bathroom.
It's because it has a lot of water.
I cross my legs without being conscious about it.
I'm not kidding. I can feel it right away.
Don't you need to use the restroom?
I bet you feel it by now.
- Just hold it. - Go through our land.
(Their bladders are slowly filling up.)
Can you donate the restroom?
(It's red almost everywhere.)
He drank the whole thing in one go.
Why did you drink it all by yourself instead of sharing it?
- Let's hold it. - Pay five R to use the restroom.
- We'll let you go for two R. - You should just go.
Just pay us two R.
- Two R? Okay. - Yes, two R.
- Let's go right away. - Two R is really cheap.
(Let's sell the land.)
Two R is cheap, isn't it?
Gosh, what are you doing?
(It's a mess in Green Team.)
What are you doing?
- We have to sell it. - We need money to attack.
We need to sell these so people can't leave.
No one's leaving. Why do you keep saying that?
- We don't need this piece of land. - No, it's this area.
(While holding their bladder, they're fighting over the land.)
(Are you ignoring my comment?)
That's what I mean.
(Kwang Soo pulls down their shorts.)
(Se Chan takes revenge.)
They're too precarious.
(Due to conflicting opinions, they become more violent.)
(Things are getting worse among Green Team members.)
(Who cares about having shorts when they have no R money?)
- What are you doing? - Goodness.
Let's get it over with.
Let's sell all our land and give up.
(Laughing)
What's the point?
Who sells their land to use the restroom?
Just urinate in your pants.
(We should have bought diapers.)
(When Green Team's argument settles...)
Everyone, this land will develop into a golf course soon.
- What's that sound? - What's that?
- You can eat it. - You eat it.
"Your land is my land."
(What is it this time?)
(Your land is my land.)
What?
Here comes our chance.
- Here it is. - It's finally here.
We'll start conquer lands competition.
(A set of three games chosen at random)
All of these games are difficult.
"Electric Roulette" looks fun.
(The team that gets an electric shock loses.)
- This is it. - I've never seen it before.
Shall we start?
Two members from Red Team and Blue Team, step forward.
- How about you two? - Do you want to play first?
Get ready, set, go.
(The winning team takes land that's worth 30 R from the losing team.)
You should turn.
(Dancing in excitement)
(The team with the last man standing wins.)
(Who will feel the electric shock?)
Wait a little longer.
- Avoid getting the shock. - Blow the whistle, please.
How strong is it?
How strong is the electric shock?
(Their hearts are pounding.)
- Everyone, be quiet. - Please.
- Please. - Who will it be?
Goodness.
(Waiting for the pain is scarier than losing all the land.)
Please, please.
I'll work hard. Please help me.
(Which one will get unlucky?)
I'll do my best. Please.
(Electric shock)
(Gary gets shocked.)
This isn't easy.
(It's more exhilarating to watch someone in pain.)
- We won. - We won!
Gosh, it really hurt.
Are you kidding?
You should endure the pain.
I felt it all the way to my heart.
- Goodness. - Gary got unlucky.
(The electric shock is terrifying.)
(Haha gets shocked.)
It hurts.
(Gosh, it's very painful.)
- The shock must be strong. - Goodness.
Keep calm.
(It's Jae Seok versus Kyu Han.)
- It started. - Endure the pain.
The shock will be very strong.
It's level four.
It's level four, the highest level.
Please, endure the pain, Kyu Han.
(Whoever avoids the shock can take three blocks of land.)
(Which of them will get the electric shock?)
(Kyu Han loses.)
(Blue Team wins three blocks of land.)
That was great.
It feels like I've been bitten by a snake.
This isn't the kind of pain you can endure.
(We'll take back our land no matter what.)
- Kwang Soo, you have long arms. - Is this "Draw a Mole"?
What is this game?
One of the markers doesn't write as it's out of ink.
Okay, do we draw a mole however we'd like?
- It's up to you. - Okay.
One.
- In 1, 2, 3. - In 1, 2, 3.
(Kwang Soo versus Jae Seok)
(It's an unfortunate fight they can't avoid.)
Draw it.
Let's go.
Draw one on this side.
(Which one is the unlucky one?)
Make it big.
(Oh, I'm the unlucky one.)
Jae Seok's marker is working.
(Shaking)
(No matter how much he shakes it, there's no ink in the marker.)
Kwang Soo, try blowing air on the marker.
(He blows hot air.)
Poor Kwang Soo.
(The marker doesn't write.)
Gosh, Red Team is so lucky.
(Kwang Soo, the unlucky one)
Hey.
Just back away.
Is Sol Bin next?
It's Sol Bin.
Gary will play next.
(Sol Bin versus Gary)
(A girl group member's face is on the line.)
- Let's start. - Goodness.
- In 1, 2, 3. - Turn around.
- Do it now. - Go.
(Which one is the unlucky one?)
(Screaming)
(Sol Bin is an unlucky idol.)
She's an idol.
Don't ruin her face.
Gary, make a unibrow.
- Make a unibrow. - She's an idol.
- That looks beautiful. - Oh, no.
- Look at my face. - That was great.
Red Team is so lucky.
We'll go next.
(We have to stop Red Team somehow.)
Let's play a different game.
Sounds good.
Who's going to play?
(It's Se Chan, Soo Hong, Na Rae and Sol Bin against each other.)
- You have to do it. - You're up, Se Chan.
There's no other choice.
- Do you want to go, Soo Hong? - Got it?
- You can do this. - You're up, Se Chan.
- Let's go! - I think she's quite unlucky.
(The person who pops up the pirate wins.)
No pressure.
- You can do this. - You're on fire right now.
You got this.
- You can do this. - Look at her dance.
I have a good feeling about this.
I hope it pops up.
Nice.
Good job.
You can do it, Na Rae.
No pressure.
(Na Rae and Sol Bin avoid the spot.)
You have to make it pop up.
(He makes a loud noise.)
- Why'd you do that? - You scared me.
Bring me the hammer.
It was a mistake.
We have a long way to go.
(She's concentrating.)
It will pop up this time.
You're doing good, Sol Bin. That's the right spot.
(The pirate isn't coming out the barrel any time soon.)
Mind your face.
Take it slow.
(He's taking it slow.)
- This is it. - No, it's not.
Which one do you think it is, Kwang Soo?
This game is always nerve-racking to play.
Is it this one?
I'm getting nervous.
(Se Chan wins.)
Did you see that?
Do you know what Kwang Soo said?
"It's the one below the green one."
(How did Kwang Soo know that?)
How'd you know that?
That was amazing.
There's still a long way to go.
It's this one.
(Kwang Soo says it's the one below the green knife.)
- It's that one. - Mind your face.
- That one? - Yes.
(Kwang Soo has a way of knowing these things.)
That was amazing.
How'd you know that?
He's got the instinct.
- That was amazing. - He was born unlucky.
No, I wasn't.
(Thanks, Mr Pirate.)
You should buy as much land as you can with the money you have.
You need as much land you can get for the last mission.
At the same time, you don't have to spend all your R money.
You will still need it later.
If you don't have enough R money, you'll have to sell your land.
How should we do this?
Should we spend all our money?
Let's not spend too much money.
Let's get this one.
Should we buy all of them except for the ones that cost 20 R?
- Sounds good. - Let's do that.
- What's this? - Are we playing another game?
What do we do now?
- Do you hear that? - What's that?
There's been a theft?
What's that supposed to mean?
Did someone steal something?
Is there a spy among us?
- What's going on? - There's been a theft.
"Your suitcases have been stolen."
"We've been informed that they're in Heyri. Please hurry."
Are we going to Heyri?
Let's go.
(What's waiting for them in Heyri?)
Here in this town of Heyri,
your suitcases are hidden somewhere.
If you successfully carry out the mission here,
you'll be able to get your suitcases back.
("Find Your Luggage")
(Carry out the team mission to receive R money and suitcases.)
What's the mission?
(Succeed the team mission and you'll be given R money and suitcases.)
(What missions will the teams have to carry out?)
"Act out accordingly to a given word together with a citizen."
"If all of you get it right, the mission is successful."
If you come back with a name tag after you finish the mission,
you'll get your suitcases back...
and receive some R money.
(Each team has a different mission.)
Take a look.
Tell me if you spot the place in the picture.
Are those stairs?
Tell me if you see a statue of a dog.
Where is this place in the picture? This is confusing.
There's someone over there.
Here she comes.
Hello.
Can you help us with a mission?
Ready, set, go!
(Jumping)
Gary.
(They look exactly the same.)
Jumping.
Okay.
Hopping.
Jumping.
Popping.
(They failed the first one.)
- Is that right? - No.
Gary.
(Coughing)
Coughing.
Hey.
Clock, clock.
Club, club.
Club.
- Club, club. - That's not it.
Club, club.
- Did you get it? - That's not it.
Did you get that?
(They're looking for a person wearing green.)
Isn't that green?
- She's wearing green. - Hey, little girl.
- She's wearing green. - Do you know who we are?
Don't you know Kwang Soo from Running Man?
- Hello. - You know him, right?
(I've been looking for you.)
(They're very close to succeeding the mission.)
- Hello. - You know him, right?
(She runs away.)
Where are you going?
- Let me give you an autograph. - He'll give you an autograph.
- I want to give you my autograph. - He'll give you his autograph.
Kwang Soo wants to give you his autograph.
Don't you want my autograph?
Oh, you don't want it?
Don't you want to get his autograph?
- You don't want it? - It might not be valuable now,
but it'll be of great value in the future.
I don't want it. I'm going.
(They get denied.)
(This is hilarious.)
Fine, then.
- Goodbye. - You really don't want it?
Are you sure?
We have to find someone else.
Why doesn't she want your autograph?
I thought you were better than this.
Why are kids these days so stubborn?
(Green Team fails their first attempt.)
I can hear them.
- They're over there. - Hold up, Na Rae.
Don't rush it.
Jumping.
Can someone help us with our mission?
- Can you help us? - Hanging.
Hanging.
- Can you help us out? - Help us.
- Hanging. - We have a mission.
What are you doing?
What do you think you're doing?
Thank you.
Let's go.
Baseball. One, two, three.
Three.
Mission success.
We did it.
That was easy.
You will be given...
your suitcases and 50 R.
(Orange Team claims their prize.)
Walking.
Hey.
Okay.
(Red Team succeeds their mission.)
Nice.
That was hard.
Can we take this off now?
I'm drooling all over the place.
This is harsh.
Two teams succeeded their missions already?
- Two teams? - We have to watch out for them.
- There she is again. - Hello.
Did you change your mind?
- Did you change your mind? - Do you want my autograph?
No?
Okay.
- We're not forcing you. - Don't you like Kwang Soo?
- Are you wearing green? - He's too tall, isn't he?
What are you doing?
She doesn't like you at all.
Let's get his autograph.
(I don't want it.)
We really want to give you an autograph.
Can you just let us sign something?
Anywhere you want.
She's not wearing green.
Please, I'm begging you.
- Ji Soo. - I don't want to.
Let's get an autograph on your trousers.
- Let's do it. - Don't you want it?
Do you want my autograph?
- No? Okay. - We're sorry.
- We'll go. - Thanks anyway.
I'm going to work harder from now on.
Kwang Soo, I thought kids loved you.
- How old are you, by the way? - Stop it.
I don't get it.
Get over it.
Kids her age are supposed to like me.
Am I supposed to take off their name tags like Running Man?
This is Running Man.
Oh, right.
The other team can't take our name tags off.
(Red Team needs a name tag to claim their prize.)
I wonder where they are.
- Who should we go for? - Make up your mind.
- Did you do your mission? - Not yet.
- Come here, Seok Jin. - Why?
(Is Green Team attacking?)
Get the name tag!
- Come here, Seok Jin. - Get the name tag!
Hold on.
(Green Team succeeded their mission before running into Red Team.)
I think they did their mission.
- No, we haven't. - Let's go after other teams.
- Sounds good. - Let's not waste our energy.
Did you see where the other teams went?
No.
(The truce is broken after 10 seconds.)
Run!
Take it off.
Take it off, Soo Hong.
I got it!
- I got it! - Nice.
- I got attacked. - Is this it?
- Good job. - What happened?
(Red Team got their suitcases back and were given 30 R.)
We have to go for Blue Team.
What's going on right now?
They're over there.
Why isn't anyone wearing green?
(Green Team decides to attack...)
(Sol Bin while her team is idle.)
Sol Bin, come here.
I got it.
(Green Team successfully tears off the name tag.)
- I tore it. - He did it.
(Green Team obtains their luggage and 10 R.)
We didn't have much time.
It was very difficult.
Since you came in last, take the luggage without any R money.
- Okay. - I won't take the luggage, either.
How disappointing.
(What awaits them in the house?)
(The second half of No Way Out Race begins.)
(Escape with your luggage.)
All of you found your luggage.
The second half of No Way Out Race is "Running Marble".
- The second half? - It's "Running Marble".
Wow.
The luggage lock combinations are hidden under the lands.
Your lock combinations are hidden under other teams' lands.
Therefore, the team with the most land has an advantage.
If you get someone else's combination, place an R mark.
If you find your lock combination, return the land as you found it.
The team to find two lock combinations first wins.
A terrible punishment awaits the team that comes in last.
We need to control our facial expressions.
You can't express your emotions too much.
Let's not control our facial expressions.
(A terrible punishment awaits the team that comes in last.)
The team to find first wins.
Okay.
(Kyu Han keeps a poker face.)
I'll roll it.
- Let's start. - Go.
(Orange Team goes first.)
It's two.
(I wish it were a bigger number.)
Which ones should we flip?
- Let's flip 20 and 27. - Okay.
(They choose Green Team's 27.)
Flip 20 and 27.
Why are you flipping ours?
- Flip Red Team's land. - Other teams can't watch.
(There's nothing under Green Team's 27.)
Let's see.
(There is nothing.)
(We're off to a bad start.)
(He's happy that they got nothing.)
I'll roll the die.
Please.
- Let it be six. - Six.
(It's exactly like Soo Hong called it.)
We're lucky today.
(Today is a lucky day for us.)
- How is this possible? - They're so lucky today.
Red Team is winning right now.
- Let's flip three here and there. - Okay.
(In the direction that Jae Seok is pointing,)
(Red Team's lock combinations are hidden in Green Team's land.)
(Red Team heads towards their lock combinations.)
(Will it be this easy on them?)
I'll be bold and choose one.
Be bold.
(He gets nothing.)
(Their lock combination is under the block right next to it.)
There was nothing.
(They keep getting unlucky.)
(They get nothing again.)
Why do you keep staring at us?
(It's interesting how you continue to miss where the combinations are.)
Where could it be?
(They look under Blue Team's land but still get nothing.)
Let's flip three blocks of Blue Team's land.
Okay.
(They get nothing again.)
- You scolded me for expressing... - Don't we have to put it back?
disappointment, but why are you doing it?
(Getting 6 on the die was useless.)
They didn't find anything.
I bet it's here.
I found something.
Here it is.
(They find Orange Team's lock combination.)
It's Orange Team's.
(Be quiet.)
(If you find other team's combination, leave an R mark.)
Why are they looking through our land?
(Orange Team has no idea.)
(We know your lock combination.)
- Let's go. - One.
- One. - That's good.
We got one.
(He can't do that.)
I didn't do anything wrong.
What's wrong with you?
Things come true when you say them out loud.
- What's wrong with you? - What you say out loud comes true.
- That was incredible. - What you say out loud comes true.
Are you going to flip our land again?
(Green Team looks through Orange Team's land.)
- Why ours? - I'm being very careful.
I think it's better to get it over with.
Why are you in such a hurry?
Trust me just this once.
Are you going to flip it?
(Of course, they find nothing.)
(You told us to trust you.)
(They take his pants off.)
(Smacking)
Come here.
(I'm sorry for being unlucky.)
- One, one. - Let me do it.
(It's Blue Team's turn.)
- One. - One.
- Six. - Six.
(Will it be one again as Soo Hong wished?)
- There it is. - Two.
It's two.
(Blue Team only gets 2.)
I shouldn't have said what I did.
We choose this.
- Number 10? - Number 2.
Why are you getting so emotional?
(Chance Card)
It doesn't matter if you flip it.
Gosh, Haha is getting too emotional.
We'll flip only one block of your land.
There must be something.
Did you find something?
Wow.
Can we tell everyone?
(What kind of Chance Card is it?)
We won the lottery!
"You can obtain information on other teams' land."
Whisper in my ear and ask...
which block you'd like to know about.
Pick one. What's your favourite number?
- I pick 27. - Okay.
Red Team's 27?
(Sol Bin picks Red Team's 27.)
Do you mean 27?
There's nothing.
You're so unlucky.
Goodness.
No, I'm not.
There's nothing there.
- I think you are. - No, I'm not.
(In that case, how unlucky is Seok Jin?)
(Blue Team picks Orange Team's 21.)
What's here?
(They find a lock combination.)
- See? I knew it. - Wow.
- I had a good feeling about it. - That was amazing.
We found it.
Na Rae, get six.
(Next up is Na Rae from Orange Team.)
- Na Rae. - Let's go, Na Rae.
(It's 2 again.)
(Oh no)
It's okay, Na Rae.
Let's flip one.
Let's go.
(They're next to where Red Team found Orange Team's combination.)
What's going on?
(Pick anything but Blue Team's 4.)
- This one? - Yes.
(No...)
(Orange Team finds a lock combination.)
We found it.
(Orange Team has one more to go.)
Let it be six.
(What he says really comes true.)
- It came true. - I can't believe it.
What I say comes true.
(It's unbelievable.)
This is amazing.
He's so good at playing games.
I'm scared of myself.
How did I know?
Flip all six of those.
We should find one here.
Don't look.
We're so lucky.
What's that?
There it is.
(It's some kind of Chance Card.)
Goodness.
(Pay 50 R to the bank for maintenance fee.)
- Oh, my goodness. - I'm sorry.
This makes me happy.
(The others are happy.)
What's this?
(It was only the beginning of their misfortune.)
(They keep getting nothing.)
Let's drop it and see where it points.
(They decide to choose where the stick points.)
It's this one.
(It's Green Team's 24.)
(It's a lock combination for Red Team.)
(All teams found one combination except for Green Team.)
Wow, we found one.
How did you find one?
(Green Team is the only team without any lock combinations.)
How will we ever find it?
(No one finds anything.)
It's impossible to find.
- You're unlucky, aren't you? - No, I'm not.
(It's Green Team's turn.)
Let it be six.
(Kicking)
It's four.
- We got four. - Seok Jin.
We found something.
(It's a Chance Card.)
"An angel has appeared."
(Provide a hint related to where the combination is to another team.)
We can't afford to do this.
We can't provide a hint to another team.
Our team is not in... Wait, time out.
Please listen to me.
How could you do this?
(It's over for us if we give out a hint.)
Red Team, step out of the group.
- Step out. - You're excluded.
We'll give a hint to either Orange Team or Blue Team.
We're desperate for a hint.
- A lot of things happened today. - If you find one more, you'll win.
(It's over for one of the two teams.)
(Which team will Green Team choose?)
We'll give a hint to Orange Team.
- Kwang Soo. - You don't want to give it to us?
It's because next is Blue Team's turn.
- Orange Team. - Where am I standing?
Do you mean this one?
Underneath this, you'll find your lock combination.
Okay, thank you.
Here we go.
(It's pretty much Orange Team's victory.)
Let's check the ones that were flipped.
We might find our lock combination under the blocks that were flipped.
Why do you want to flip this one?
(Eureka!)
- See? I was right. - How did you know?
I found it!
(Why did we find it so late?)
(Every team has found 1.)
I just had a good feeling.
- We have two more chances. - Right.
- We have two chances left. - Finish it this time.
Kwang Soo, we can reverse the score.
- Wow. - I told you to trust me.
It has to be 2 or 3.
I think we got it!
Get out. Let's finish it here.
(What are they thinking?)
There's Leg Spreading Card. What is this?
We found Leg Spreading Card.
(You can get hints as much as you spread your legs.)
- Okay! - We must spread our legs...
(They can get hints.)
- But they... - Lie down.
- How should we do? - Let's bend our legs.
- We can... - What is Kwang Soo doing?
(They act as if they don't care.)
(But in fact, they're focused.)
Okay?
(The mind game has begun.)
- That's intentional. - We're not interested at all.
- This isn't the right one. - It's not.
- 12, 13... - Wow, he's flexible.
(Which one would it be?)
- He's good. - You have to reach 19 and 20.
Kwang Soo, spread your legs wider.
- Good. - You should keep up.
- Just one more. - We'll get 12, 19 and 20.
(They reached 12, 19 and 20 red mats.)
We'll give you hints for 12, 19 and 20.
There's nothing...
under 19.
There's also nothing...
under 20.
And 12...
(If they get no hints here, they won't be able to win.)
There's Green Team's combination.
(They found it.)
- What are you doing? - Why are you opening the mat?
(Because there's our combination!)
(They surprisingly win the round.)
(This unlucky trio makes a miraculous victory.)
Let's get on our knees.
We must repent what we've done today.
- We were really poor... - It is...
When Se Chan became my teammate, I thought I'm super unlucky.
- I'm sorry. - I'm sorry, but I thought the same.
I was really disappointed when I picked the green ball.
(Still, they're the winners.)
As I said earlier, the other three teams will...
roll the die. And only one member of the team...
who gets the smallest number will get the penalty.
- We should roll a die? - But it is...
What is our prize?
There is no prize.
(You won't get any prizes today.)
My goodness.
- What is this? - There's no point in winning.
(The lucky guys win when there's no prize prepared.)
The penalty for a member of the team with the smallest number...
is to go home in the suit you're wearing now.
Record the video with your phone and send it to us.
That will be humiliating.
- That is... - This is the same as winning.
- You did a good job. - He's lucky.
(He rolled only 2 today.)
(Orange Team is less likely to lose.)
That was nice.
- Orange Team is safe. - Let's roll it together.
Blue Team is the unluckiest team.
In 1, 2, 3.
One!
(Will it go as Soo Hong said?)
Three!
It's one!
(It has once again obeyed Soo Hong.)
(I can't believe this.)
(Soo Hong is a prophet.)
- I'm scared now. - This is amazing.
(Am I really unlucky this year?)
- I can't believe this. - No way!
She's really unlucky this year.
We can just throw it freely. We already won!
(Really?)
We already won! We did!
(This is truly incredible!)
(They won't get the penalty by a slight margin.)
This is unbelievable!
(One of their members will get the penalty.)
I can't believe this.
It will be Sol Bin anyway.
So you go first.
Sol Bin, I think you're the unluckiest idol group member.
She's really unlucky.
No, I am not.
She's so unlucky.
If you lose this time again, you can join us.
- This is really unbelievable. - She's unlucky.
Get ready.
- It is... - Does it hurt badly?
- Go! - You don't have to win.
- Exactly. - Do it now!
- Go. - Good.
Who will be the unluckiest member?
I think it will be Kyu Han.
(Who will be the unluckiest member?)
(Screaming)
It's Kyu Han.
(He's super unlucky today.)
- Gosh. - Kyu Han.
- Gosh. - Wow.
How can this happen?
(Sol Bin laughs out loud.)
- He was the culprit. - It was him.
- Sol Bin, you're not lucky. - My goodness!
Kyu Han is the unluckiest.
(Kyu Han has to go home in the dress he's in now.)
- Sol Bin, goodbye. It's hot. - Thank you.
Don't ever show up in front of me.
Things didn't work as I wanted at all today.
It was really weird. I lost every time I tried something.
It was the same when I rolled the die.
Why don't we have a drink?
(He wants to drink on this unlucky day.)
Hello.
(He's in his suit.)
(He's going into a restaurant.)
Oh my goodness.
Here's yours.
- Can I have more bean sprouts? - Sure.
(It looks tasty.)
I worked really hard today, so I will eat a lot.
Let's go for it.
We'll have a field day today.
Hello!
Son Yeon Jae is here!
(Beautiful ladies are here!)
Yeon Jae!
- Did you all bring gimbap? - Yes.
(Yu Ra)
There's a secret agent in each team?
A secret agent?
It's pepper.
(Find the secret agent...)
(who betrayed us!)
You're suspicious.
(Let's enjoy this field day...)
(with these lovely ladies.)
(Secret Field Day)