(The Running Man members have all arrived.)
Good morning.
Govod morning, all.
Hello, good morning.
What are we going to do today?
What is this?
(What is today's mission?)
Today we will have a Running Man Intern Race.
Fuor the members that have been running hard,
interns with a 12 year age gap will be picking you up.
So we ask all members to wait at your assigned location.
Interns with a 12 year age gap?
If it's a 12 year age gap...
and I was born in 1979,
my intern was born in 1991?
A person born in 1991.
I found celebrities born in 1991.
There's Kim Go Eun...
and Park So Dam.
My goodness.
There's Park Bo Gum. Maybe he's my intern.
It's nice to meet you, Park Bo Gum.
(Grinning)
If the intern is only 20 years old,
he or she may not be a skilled driver.
Who could it be?
(There is a great deal of teaching to do.)
So my intern will pick me up?
If it's an internship,
I should teach them a few things.
(I should teach them a few things.)
(What are the interns doing?)
It's very nerve-racking.
I'm so nervous.
(He is full of excitement on his first day of work.)
I'm nervous.
I don't know if I'll do well.
I'm not sure what's going on yet.
(Please wait a little, we'll be there soon.)
My intern is here.
(Who will be Haha's intern that was born in 1991?)
(Will it be the person he has been imagining?)
(Park So Dam or Kim Go Eun?)
So Dam.
So Dam, I'll be waiting for you.
(Welcome, my intern.)
Oh, it's you.
(Oh, it's you.)
Hey.
Haha,
it's nice to meet you.
(Stumbling)
Haha,
I'll serve you well today.
(It's Korea's number one female show host, Park Mi Sun, born in 1967.)
- Sir, Haha.
- Wait a minute.
Wait.
You meant 12 years older than me?
(You meant 12 years older than me?)
- Bye, bye.
- Not younger but older?
Haha, we should get going now.
(Haha is uncomfortable with Mi Sun's formal behaviour.)
I'm sorry.
This is really uncomfortable.
Yes, okay.
- This way, Haha.
- Let me drive.
- I'll do it.
- Get in, Haha.
Please get in.
Oh, my.
(Interns should escort the senior members into the car.)
(Speed is a necessity for interns.)
My goodness.
What happened, Mi Sun?
I'm your...
intern today, Haha.
What's gotten into you?
What should I call you, Haha?
How long has it been since your debut?
It's been 29 years.
(She is a veteran intern.)
- Should I call you Sir Haha?
- Hold on.
Would you like to call me Miss Park?
Miss Park?
(This is very uncomfortable.)
Is that too much?
- Please.
- Yes, Haha.
It's okay when it's just the two of us,
I understand what today's concept is.
- No, it's all right.
- So when it's just the two of us,
- No, that wouldn't do.
- please just be yourself.
- I know that you have a temper.
- Don't be like that.
Stop it right there.
What are you talking about?
(She is an intern with two faces.)
Please let me do my work.
(Intern Park Mi Sun wants to be called Miss Park and has a temper.)
Please call me Miss Park.
I'd like to be called Miss Park.
I see a car coming this way.
There's a camera inside. I think that's it.
Could that be the one?
(What a surprise)
It's Hong Ryul.
Hong Ryul.
(Who will be Seok Jin's intern for today?)
It's Hong Ryul.
Hello, Hong Ryul.
Hong Ryul, it's nice to see you.
Hello.
- It's nice to see you.
- Hello.
- Are you...
- Yes.
the intern?
Yes, I will be working as your intern today.
So you will assist me today?
Yes, you're right.
- I'll drive.
- No, it's okay.
Please let me drive.
- The driver's seat...
- This is uncomfortable.
fits me perfectly.
I'm uncomfortable.
Please get in.
- Have a seat in the back.
- No, that's all right.
- Sit in the back seat.
- No, that's too uncomfortable.
- The back seat is all warmed up.
- No, it's okay.
- That will be too uncomfortable.
- I warmed it up.
- I don't know what is happening.
- What am I doing right now?
(Absolute discomfort)
Okay.
Please don't do a thing.
- I'm trying to have a fresh start.
- To be frank,
- Don't worry.
- please don't be surprised,
but I actually searched for people who...
are 12 and more years younger than me.
Did you really?
Seok Jin, you're now...
one of the seniors too.
I don't think that way though.
Once I begin to think about age, I can't interact with young people.
So I try to forget about my age.
- I tried to do that too.
- I've been thinking like that.
But that only works for a while.
That's what I'm concerned about too. I'm not...
- sure how long I can keep this up.
- You're right.
When you reach a certain point,
making an effort is useless.
- Yes, you're right.
- It happens.
- Yes.
- My goodness.
I forgot my duty.
- I wasn't scolding you.
- No, it's fine.
- I didn't mean to say that.
- No, it's okay.
- This is more comfortable for me.
- No, it's all right.
I've been reminded repeatedly,
but I forgot for a moment.
- I apologise.
- It's all right.
I understood you completely.
- No, I'm sorry.
- It was right of you to say that.
No, it wasn't.
We both have something in common.
We both have nicknames related to our nose.
Yes, I heard.
Right, because my nose is big.
Goodness, I forgot again.
No, it's all right.
I don't know what's gotten into me.
I keep speaking comfortably with you.
What should I do?
- I forgot about all these cameras.
- That's all right.
Please just be yourself.
I thought we were having a private conversation.
- Oh, it's fine.
- I forgot my duty.
(Intern Lee Hong Ryul is the oldest intern and often speaks freely.)
I see my intern coming.
Why turn on the emergency lights?
Wait, who is it?
(Who is it?)
Hello.
(Who will be Jae Seok's intern for today?)
Please don't get out.
It's Yoo Yeol.
(Yoo Yeol, who led the K-POP industry through the 80s and 90s.)
Yoo Yeol.
Oh my.
It's nice to meet you.
- Oh goodness.
- Yes, well.
I will assist you today as your intern.
- My name is Yoo Yeol.
- What is this?
Yoo Yeol.
What do you mean, you're my intern?
I've come here today...
- Yes?
- to learn from the best.
- What?
- I'll assist you today.
- Please, get in.
- No, wait.
- That's not it.
- Yes?
- I should drive.
- No, it's all right.
- Today, I will drive.
- I should be driving.
- That's not it.
- No.
- I'll drive safely.
- This is very uncomfortable.
My goodness.
You're making me uncomfortable.
I'm a good driver.
I see.
I should be driving, though.
No, let me serve you today.
Are we doing this right?
- I should be sitting next to you.
- No, it's fine.
There's no camera in the back seat.
- Is that so?
- Yes.
- Then I'll have you sit next to me.
- Okay.
- I'll sit next to you.
- Sure.
- Please stay there.
- Let me help you change seats.
- I'll sit next to you.
- Okay.
Please go unlock the door.
- I'm not used to this yet.
- I understand.
- There you go.
- You can go back to your seat.
Just get in.
(After a slight mix-up, the two set out again.)
- Shouldn't I be driving?
- No.
No, it's all right. I'm an intern today.
That's my role.
And this is my first time on a variety show.
- I see.
- I am an intern today.
Since you're an intern, I'll let you know that...
your voice doesn't really suit variety shows.
(Yeol's voice is too romantic for a variety show.)
It's too soft and sweet.
It's not fit for variety shows.
My goodness.
(Intern Yoo Yeol is advised to improve his voice for the show.)
(Running Man Headquarters, 9am)
What is this? It's driving me crazy.
This is so sudden. I don't know what to do with myself.
- Haha.
- I was expecting...
- Park So Dam or Kim Go Eun.
- Haha.
- Haha, please sit here.
- Mi Sun's 50 years old.
Please don't mention my age.
It's been 29 years since she debuted.
And she tells me to call her Miss Park.
- Please call me Miss Park.
- This is absurd.
(Haha can't stop complaining.)
- Haha.
- She's like a grandmother to me.
She's an ancestor.
She's a fossil.
(She's as old as a fossil.)
- If she's my intern,
- Haha.
what about Seok Jin?
Is his intern Song Hae?
(Is his intern Song Hae?)
- Come this way.
- This is so uncomfortable.
(Hong Ryul is here instead of Song Hae.)
Have a seat.
They're coming. Seok Jin is here.
What is this? Oh, my.
- Hello.
- Hong Ryul.
- How have you been?
- Hong Ryul is here.
- Oh, my.
- It's Hong Ryul.
(Bowing)
I should do that too.
Stop it, don't do that.
- What are you doing?
- Don't do this.
Why is it so uncomfortable today?
- This is so uncomfortable.
- Stop it.
Hong Ryul.
- Come this way.
- Okay.
(Seok Jin guides his intern, Hong Ryul.)
- Thank you.
- Here.
- Have a seat.
- I should be doing this for you.
- No, it's fine.
- Sit here.
Don't do this. You're making me uncomfortable.
- Hong Ryul.
- Have a seat.
- Please, have a seat.
- We're comfortable standing.
- Don't be like that.
- Please don't do that.
- We're doing as we were told.
- No, please.
- Please sit down.
- We have to be standing.
We're supposed to be standing.
This is ridiculous.
(This is ridiculous.)
What am I supposed to do?
Oh!
(Who is it?)
He has a beard.
Who is it?
Is it Raymon Kim? It's a man?
(It's not a 20-year-old intern?)
Wait.
(Who will be Kwang Soo's intern?)
Hello.
- Hello, it's nice to meet you.
- Hello.
Oh, I see.
Hello. I should have opened the door for you.
- No.
- I'm sorry.
- Don't do that.
- Let me open the door for you.
Stay in your seat. I'm really okay.
- It's okay.
- Hello.
- Nice to meet you.
- Yes, hello.
I'm the new intern, Kim Jo Han.
What are you talking about?
It's all right.
I came to escort you.
- You don't have to.
- Don't worry.
(Uncomfortable)
- Please, get in.
- I'll drive.
- No.
- This is so uncomfortable!
- Don't be like that.
- What?
I'm a great driver.
- I can drive the car.
- Don't feel uncomfortable.
Okay.
I should have introduced myself more properly.
That's absurd.
- Don't say that.
- I'm sorry.
This is crazy.
(This is crazy.)
- Should we go?
- Yes, sure.
I'm not sure what exactly we'll be doing today,
but given the situation...
- Yes.
- Can I speak casually to you?
Yes, of course. Please treat me comfortably.
- Given the situation.
- Sure, Kwang Soo.
Then I'll have to talk more casually.
- You can call me Intern Kim.
- Okay.
Please drive safely.
I heard you got lost on the way here.
The thing is...
(Kwang Soo starts to act like Jo Han's senior.)
The navigation system misguided me.
The people I hate the most are people who give excuses.
(I hate people who give excuses.)
Please drive within the speed limit.
You're right.
I won't make any excuses from now on.
I was freezing.
It was so cold that I think I'm getting a cold now.
- Should I find a pharmacy?
- No,
- What about a hospital?
- it's okay.
I can understand you...
because I'm a generous senior who can embrace others' mistakes.
Thank you.
This will never happen again.
I promise you.
(Laughing)
I'm not sure if I'm doing the right thing.
No, you were right. I was late.
(Innocent intern Kim Jo Han is quick to apologise.)
Oh, my.
(Ji Hyo is surprised.)
Is he my intern?
He's my intern?
Is he 12 years older than me?
Hello. Nice to meet you.
- You're here.
- Yes.
- I have the car ready.
- Okay.
(Intern Kim Won Hae)
(Won Hae debuted in 1991.)
Didn't I warn you all?
You!
I'm your supervisor!
(Won Hae, born in 1969, is a versatile actor.)
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
I don't know what to do. Thank you.
Who's the senior here?
(Breathing deeply)
- Buckle up.
- I already did.
(Rustling)
(Laughing)
Are you going to wear those gloves?
(He even prepared gloves.)
Are you...
- nervous?
- Yes, very much.
(Let's take off.)
(The car is filled with an awkward atmosphere.)
Plate number 6432, please go faster.
My senior is running late.
- It's okay.
- Plate number 6432!
- It's all right.
- Why are you driving so slowly?
(No one can get in my senior's way.)
I'm really okay.
I'm okay. I really am.
Take your time crossing. You have some time left.
(There's still some time.)
Take your time, you still have a few seconds left.
All right.
You're very attentive to your surroundings.
(Intern Kim Won Hae is a nosy and determined driver.)
(Who will be Gary's intern?)
Oh, goodness.
It's Kil Kang.
What a surprise, hello.
- Hello, I'm Intern Ahn Kil Kang.
- Yes, hello.
- I'm honoured.
- It's my pleasure.
- Let me drive.
- No.
- I should drive.
- You can't.
- No really.
- Please, get in.
Oh, my.
Wear your seatbelt. I'll drive carefully.
Goodness, Kil Kang.
(I'll escort you safely.)
What's going on?
- I should have come to you.
- No, it's all right.
I'm Intern Kil Kang.
- Are you an intern?
- Yes. It's nice to meet you.
(Nice to meet you, Gary.)
When we were...
shooting "Dachimawa Lee" together, you taught me how to act.
And you're my intern now? How did this happen?
It's because I like you so much.
- Goodness.
- I'll do my best.
- Okay.
- Please speak casually to me.
- Should I?
- Yes.
- How could I do that?
- Be comfortable.
You can be comfortable with me.
I'm not sure if I can do that.
Of course you can.
I brought some tangerines for you.
- Oh, my.
- You just have to sit and wait.
Is it really okay for me to let you do this?
Yes, you just wait.
- Open your mouth.
- Okay.
- This is delicious.
- I'll have some too.
Tangerines taste best when someone else peels them for you.
Is that so? I love you, Gary.
(I love you, Gary.)
I love you.
I know.
Thank you.
(Intern Ahn Kil Kang has great people skills.)
- Can't you sit down?
- Seriously.
- Please sit down.
- Please.
It'll make me feel comfortable if you sit down.
We were strictly instructed...
that we shouldn't sit down.
Oh, Hong Ryul.
- Oh, my.
- It's Yoo Yeol.
- Yoo Yeol.
- Yoo Yeol's here.
- It's Yoo Yeol.
- What's going on today?
- I've never seen him before.
This is too uncomfortable.
- What's happening?
- What do we do?
- What is this?
- What's going on?
- Why are you doing this to us?
- What is this?
- Oh, my.
- I can't believe this.
- I'm so uncomfortable.
- This is crazy.
- Hello.
- Nice to meet you.
- I don't know what to do.
- I can't believe this.
- This is so uncomfortable.
- It really is.
- It's nice to meet you.
- Yes, hello.
- Hello.
- Nice to meet you.
- What do I do?
- Are you an intern?
- Oh, my.
- This is so uncomfortable.
Please sit down.
- It's okay.
- Please have a seat.
- We can't sit down.
- I see.
Sit down first.
- Have a seat.
- We'll sit if there are seats left.
- Why are you doing this?
- Let me be.
- I'll sit if there's an empty seat.
- You're not usually like this.
- No, I'm okay.
- Please sit down.
- Please have a seat.
- I'm okay.
- Have a seat, Won Hae.
- Sit down first.
- This is so uncomfortable!
- Please be seated.
- Your mother is well, right?
- Yes, she is.
My mum is...
his friend!
(Hong Ryul is old enough to be Haha's eldest uncle.)
This is so uncomfortable.
Tell us anything you want us to do.
No, it's all right.
It's uncomfortable for us to be sitting down.
We're uncomfortable too.
Would you like some coffee?
- I'll get you coffee.
- No, it's okay.
No, no. Please remain seated.
- That's not it!
- No, it's all right.
- It's okay.
- Sit back down.
- I will do it.
- I'll get it.
- I'll get it myself.
- Come back!
- Just stay still.
- Please let us do it.
I was asking them if they wanted coffee.
- Please have a seat.
- Don't go out.
- I can get it.
- Please let us do it.
Please sit down.
- Oh, hello.
- Hello.
- Hello. What brings you here?
- Kil Kang is scary.
- Hello.
- Jo Han!
- Where did Mi Sun go?
I think she went to get coffee. Bring her back here.
Thank goodness. Won Hae only pretends to do things.
Won Hae is like that.
I'm not familiar with SBS, that's why.
Where is the reception area?
(If you teach me where it is, I will go make some coffee.)
Why are you looking for the reception area?
Stay seated, Won Hae. Don't do that.
(I need to earn bonus points too.)
Oh goodness, Won Hae.
(Here comes your coffee!)
Kil Kang and Mi Sun actually brought coffee for us.
- What?
- This is crazy.
You didn't have to do that.
Why are you doing this?
(Their coffee delivery makes everyone uncomfortable.)
- Please have a seat.
- I only asked if you wanted coffee.
- Here's your coffee, Sir.
- Sir?
- What's wrong with you, Mi Sun?
- There was no more coffee, so...
- I brought it from another office.
- Please sit down.
(I should do something too.)
No, it's okay.
(He helps Ji Hyo take off her jacket.)
- What are you doing?
- What is he doing?
- What are you doing, Won Hae?
- Why is he doing that?
I'm envious.
(He helps his senior colleague with love.)
Just take a rest, Won Hae.
Why are you fanning her?
She said she's hot.
It's all right.
- Won Hae.
- Have a seat.
- Have a seat. I'll do it.
(It's time for the interns to introduce themselves.)
Let's have the interns introduce themselves.
Kil Kang, can I please ask you to introduce yourself?
- Yes, Sir.
- Okay.
- Yes.
- We should stand up too.
(Everyone stands up.)
- Please sit down.
- Why did you have to do this?
Hello, everyone. My name is Kil Kang.
I am a new intern. It's very nice to meet you.
- Welcome.
My name is Won Hae. I am a new intern.
I will be working with Ji Hyo. It's nice to meet you.
- Welcome.
By the way, are you feeling well?
(I passed all the medical tests.)
- You look rather tired.
- I am all right.
Are you really all right?
- You should take the afternoon off.
- No, it's okay.
Are you really okay? All right, then.
(Next is Yoo Yeol's turn.)
This is my first time on a variety show.
(This is my first time on a variety show.)
(Yeol speaks in a delayed manner.)
This is my first time on a variety show.
Listen to his voice.
- He's like a radio show host.
- I will warn you all.
His voice tone doesn't match with variety shows.
His voice doesn't match well with variety shows.
His voice is perfect for a morning radio show.
His voice is too gentle.
You should bear that in mind.
And once you find out how humane he is, you'll fall in love.
Please continue.
(He rests for one beat and starts talking.)
Recently...
(His voice is way too gentle.)
It's so refreshing.
You saw that, right?
- Yes.
- It's morning.
I am Yoo Yeol. I will be an intern for Jae Seok.
(Welcome to Running Man!)
Is this really your first appearance on a variety show?
- Yes, it is.
- It's your first time ever?
It's so nice to meet you all.
I didn't expect this kind of atmosphere.
(In 20 minutes, Yoo Yeol fell deeply in love with variety shows.)
The next person, please introduce yourself.
(Bowing)
(She bows to all her seniors at once by swinging her head.)
Hello.
I am an intern for Haha.
- My name is Miss Park.
- Miss Park?
- It's nice to meet you.
- Okay.
(We look forward to Miss Park's active presence today.)
- Goodness.
- Yes.
I will give everything I have to serve Seok Jin well as his intern.
I hope he will torture me as much as he pleases.
My name is Hong Ryul.
(He's the godfather of comedy! Welcome, Hong Ryul.)
This is awesome.
Hello.
I am the youngest among all the interns today.
- He's right.
- That's true.
He's the youngest intern.
I can't believe it either,
but I will serve Kwang Soo well today.
My name is Jo Han.
- Welcome.
Brilliant.
Why is he so late?
An intern should be on time.
This is the problem with interns.
They don't know how society goes around.
I should give him a good teaching when he comes.
Goodness.
(I'm sorry, I am late, Sir.)
(Who is the intern that surprised Jong Kook?)
- Hello.
(It's Kim Do Kyoon, one of the three top guitarists in Korea.)
- Hello, Sir.
- Hello.
- Thank you for coming.
- No problem.
I knew this would happen.
I knew it.
Did you drink coffee yet?
No, it's all right.
- I'll get you coffee.
- No, it's okay.
It's all right, I don't drink coffee.
- What would you like to drink?
- I'll get you a cup of juice then.
No, I am all right.
- Please stay seated.
- Okay.
- I have to learn a lot today.
- Right.
This is so uncomfortable.
This is very uncomfortable.
One orange juice and...
one black coffee, please.
(Jong Kook acts very humble.)
- Will that be all?
- Yes, that's right.
(Intern Kim Do Kyoon has long hair that overwhelms Jong Kook.)
(Kim Jong Kook and Kim Do Kyoon are 30 minutes late.)
Where should we go? Should we go this way?
This way? Okay.
- Oh, wow!
- What?
Oh goodness.
- It's Kim Do Kyoon.
- It's Do Kyoon.
- Hello.
- Hello!
- Do Kyoon is here.
- Hello.
- Oh goodness.
Oh dear.
Please introduce yourself.
- Introduce yourself, please.
- I see.
Yes. I am... Well...
I came here...
as a new employee...
for Running Man.
Wait, I'm not an employee yet. I came here...
as an intern.
So...
I will learn a lot of things from Jong Kook...
and...
Speak up.
If you talk like that, you will be fired after the internship.
I see, okay.
(I'll work hard.)
- Please have a seat.
- Okay.
- Please sit down first.
- Goodness.
- All right.
(What sound is this?)
This is an announcement.
Now, the training for the interns will begin.
The first game is "Pull from the Front and Put in the Back".
- Pull from the front?
- All employees and interns...
should go to their places at this time.
"Pull from the Front and Put in the Back"?
(The interns first training test)
(Class 1, Pull from the Front and Put in the Back)
(The interns must move without their feet touching the floor...)
(and grab the trash bin with their feet.)
(Then their senior colleague will toss crumbled papers into the bin.)
(The team with the most number of paper balls will win.)
How do we move with this?
- Wow.
- This is crazy.
I think it's going to be tough to move this.
- It's not easy to come here.
- It's too difficult.
- You have to try hard.
- Haha.
Please teach us your know-hows.
Cheat.
- Okay.
- You're just like Song Ji Hyo!
- You got this, Miss Park!
- I got this!
- Actually...
- Miss Park!
- I am sorry, but...
can I grab other intern's chairs?
- Of course you can.
- Of course.
- It's strange not to grab them.
- Don't do it.
- No.
- Grab the two chairs...
beside you and push.
- Push the chairs beside you.
- Yeol.
- Yeol,
- You should be merciless.
- you can't be gentle.
- Of course.
- Mi Sun.
- Yes.
Good luck, Jo Han!
Good luck, Hong Ryul!
(The first training, Pull from the Front and Put in the Back)
- Go, team!
- Go!
(What is he doing?)
(He moves faster than anyone.)
Can he do that?
He can do that. His feet didn't touch the floor.
You should come this way.
- You should do that too!
- It's this way.
Go to the right!
- Come here.
- Just like that.
- All right.
- That's it.
That's ours.
- Come on.
- Be careful.
Just step on the floor and move faster.
- You can step on the floor.
- Do Kyoon.
- It's okay if you cheat.
- Come on.
- Hold on.
- Just step on the floor.
Just cheat, it's okay.
Put your feet on the floor and come here.
- Come here.
- Do Kyoon.
Hurry up!
Stay there, Do Kyoon.
Come. Just come here.
Just come.
- Wait. You have to tilt it forward.
- Grab the trash bin.
Just do it one by one.
(Focusing)
- Slowly.
- Wait, hold on.
You have to catch the ball.
When I throw the ball, you have to receive it.
(The ball goes inside.)
You have to receive it. That's it.
- That's great.
- Oh man.
- Good job.
- Okay now.
Okay, this is good.
- That's it.
- Tilt it towards me.
(It's not that easy.)
- How can you miss that?
- Goodness.
- This is good.
- It's not going in.
(Jae Seok and Yoo Yeol are also struggling.)
- Good job.
- Why isn't it going in?
(Kwang Soo...)
(scores.)
- Throw some more!
- That's it.
(Throwing)
- Move your legs.
- Keep going.
- Okay.
- Good.
- Let's go.
- That's good.
Just get it in.
- Throw it slowly.
- Hold on.
(It's not easy to get the ball in.)
- Go in!
- No.
- Oh no.
- My goodness.
It's really hard to get it in.
- Yes!
- Okay, it went in.
- He's really good at this.
- Oh no.
- Okay.
- That's great.
Mi Sun, it's this one.
- I saw that.
- It's not easy.
- What are you doing?
- Kil Kang and Gary...
has none.
I have one.
Seok Jin...
has two.
- It went in at the last minute.
- Exactly.
- It went in after.
- Then, it's just one.
Just one.
Ji Hyo has one.
- Goodness.
- How many are there?
Is it 3 or 4?
- Nice!
- Isn't it only two?
- Isn't it three?
- Let's be honest.
- It's two.
- Okay.
- She's honest.
- She's nice.
- Okay.
- It's only two.
Mi Sun is honest.
- This is touching.
- I'm sorry.
Kwang Soo has four.
We have four.
- Four?
- There are really four.
- Are you sure?
- Yes, we got four.
Really?
I swear. Look at it again.
Replay the video. Come on, go!
- Let's replay it.
- Why don't you believe us?
- Wait.
- He just swore.
- I think we should trust him.
- Okay.
- He swore.
- Goodness.
- There's only 1.
- There are 2.
No, there are two.
One bounced off, so I put it back in.
Then it's only one.
- Okay.
- You're too strict.
I'm not being strict.
- This is one.
- That's too short.
- He's too strict.
- He's right.
You guys are too honest.
Let's do it one more time.
- Let's go again.
- Shall we?
- Yes.
- I have a question.
Is it okay to go on the chair like Kil Kang?
- I think that's too fast.
- I agree.
- Yes.
- That's right.
- Wait a minute.
- Okay.
Kil Kang started it first.
- Right.
- No,
- wasn't it Yeol?
- I'll give you a warning.
- No one said I can't do that.
- I'll take one ball out.
- No one told me.
- Exactly.
- Jo Han did that as well.
- He pushed with his feet.
I'll take one out from Jo Han's bin too.
I just copied somebody else.
- I did it too.
- I only copied someone.
I did it too.
Take one out then.
- Take one out.
- Let's do it over again.
- Shall we?
- Let's do it one more time.
- Let's follow the rules.
- Does everyone agree?
Let's just do it here.
Let's play from here.
- Let's do that.
- Okay, let me...
ask everyone.
- Tell me your opinions.
- Okay.
- Do you want to do it here?
- Ask him if we can use our feet.
Let's use our feet.
(They must choose between starting where they are or going back.)
- Okay.
- Ask if we can use our feet.
Tell me your preference.
(Jae Seok listens carefully to what the interns have to say.)
I will start from here.
It's 2 to 2.
(It's Mi Sun's turn.)
Okay.
(Goodness)
(She whispered in his ears.)
What happened?
(Oh my goodness)
What did you just do?
- Goodness.
- I didn't do anything.
- Come on.
- Mi Sun.
- What is it?
- What happened?
- I didn't do anything.
- What is it?
- What was it?
- Did you...
- blow in his ears?
- No, I didn't.
- She sounded like Sharon Stone.
- Come on.
What do you mean, Jae Seok?
- What did she do?
- Did you blow in his ears?
- No, I didn't.
- What I mean is...
she was really...
Jae Seok, I'm sure it wasn't your first time.
Come on.
(No one has done that to me before.)
She whispered,
"Let's do it here."
That's what she said.
All right.
(He continues to listen.)
I got it.
(Whispering)
Come on.
- What?
- What is it?
- I can hear him.
- I asked him, "Here or there?"
- The start...
He said, "How about half-way?"
(Why not start from the middle?)
That's funny.
- That's a good idea.
- I like that.
- He has a good idea.
- Okay, then...
I'll tell you the result.
- That's cute.
- Do Kyoon wants a half-way start,
and four people want to start here.
So we'll start here.
- Okay.
- That's great.
Let's pick the balls up.
- Let's start.
- Throw one at a time.
- Don't throw multiples.
- Okay.
Let's do it.
- You have 30 seconds.
- Okay.
Okay, good.
- Ready.
- What are you doing?
Wait a minute.
Put your shoes on.
It's slippery because you have no shoes on.
What's the reason?
- Put your shoes on.
- I'll hold the bin like this.
I told you it's slippery.
Are you sure he's younger than me?
- I'm trying to get the right angle.
- Come on.
Why are you all so stubborn?
Just do it.
- Let's just do it.
- These interns don't listen.
- Oh goodness.
- Come on.
I feel like they are company CEOs.
- Put your shoes on!
Please put your shoes back on!
(I don't want to.)
- My goodness.
- He won't listen.
Am I supposed to wash your feet?
Come on, Yeol.
No, I can do it.
- Okay.
- He got it.
- I can hold it for 30 seconds.
- Okay.
- I got it.
- Ready.
Throw one at a time.
- Okay.
- Ready.
Go!
(Round two starts.)
(They only need to shoot.)
Do it slowly.
(They just need to get the balls in the bin.)
(Kwang Soo shoots well.)
It's not going in.
My goodness.
(Kwang Soo gets it in again.)
That was too short.
Try again.
- Quickly.
- Great.
- Okay.
- Goodness.
- Keep going.
- Okay.
Keep going.
Move your feet.
- Okay.
- That's great.
- Go ahead.
- We have to keep going.
- There's not much time left.
- Oh my.
(They all get the balls in the bin.)
- Go slowly.
- Keep it up.
(Let's do this, Do Kyoon.)
(Oh my gosh)
- Slowly.
- Keep going.
Keep shooting.
(He moves the bin.)
What are you doing?
- Good job.
- Keep going.
You got this!
(Do Kyoon turns the trash can.)
(Do Kyoon is blocking the balls.)
- Great job.
- Keep it up.
Keep going.
Keep trying.
We need to keep trying. There's not much time left.
(Round two is over.)
Let go of the bin.
We had two that bounced off.
- I think we got a lot in the bin.
- We got a lot in.
Yeol, why did you raise your hand?
I want to go on more variety shows.
(He declares his desire to enter the field of variety shows.)
Isn't it fun, Yeol?
We had two that bounced off.
- Kil Kang and Gary...
- Yes.
- has one.
- One.
- Don't be surprised, everyone.
- Okay.
There's 1, 2, 3, 4...
- and 5, 6 and 7.
- Really?
(They have seven!)
- Goodness.
- That's great.
- That's a lot.
- That's awesome.
- This team has 1, 2, 3, 4.
- I should take off my shoes.
- Oh wow.
- Two balls bounced off.
They got a lot of balls in.
This team also has a lot.
They have 1, 2, 3, 4, 5.
(Ji Hyo and Won Hae have five.)
They are getting better.
(Mi Sun previously had two.)
Okay, one!
(Why is only our team like this?)
This team has 1, 2, 3, 4, 5.
(Kwang Soo and Jo Han have five.)
(What is this?)
(The two...)
(look at each other...)
(and smile.)
I have never...
seen someone block everything.
It was about to go in and he moved the trash can.
He moved it like this.
(Laughing)
- He looks happy.
- Why did you do that?
We needed to have a connection.
But we didn't start out right.
I mean...
- it was my fault.
- I think...
you didn't catch the balls well.
That's true.
(Results: Kwang Soo 9, Jae Seok 8, Ji Hyo 6, Seok Jin 5,)
(Haha 3, Gary 1 and Jong Kook 1)
Let's hear what the interns...
- think about the first test.
- Okay.
How about Yeol?
Well, from the beginning...
Could you please speak faster?
Please talk faster.
I think Jae Seok and I are good partners.
(We have a good partnership.)
(Yeol is getting used to variety shows.)
How about Hong Ryul?
I want to try one more time.
Well then...
how about Jo Han?
I think our team is really great.
- Is that true?
- Wow.
I'm sorry, but you're sitting like a judge from "K-POP Star".
I'm sorry.
- I think our team is really great.
- Is that true?
(Jo Han will choose Running Man.)
I'm sorry.
- His posture was like this.
- It was the posture of a panel.
Don't forget...
that you're an intern.
- He's a rude intern.
- I'm sorry.
(I'm sorry.)
(Class 2: Partners Run Errands)
(While the senior member calls out the intern's name,)
(the intern has to bring five items requested by the senior member.)
(The interns will be ranked by the number of items that they bring.)
- Can I sit here?
- Of course.
- Of course, Sir.
- And by the way,
- Yes.
- I was watching and...
in the beginning, everyone...
was acting like a real intern.
But now they are beginning to act like themselves.
- Really?
- Look at how Hong Ryul is sitting.
(A veteran comedian)
Look at his posture.
I think I need to scold them.
- What do you mean?
- Well...
I should.
- What are you talking about?
- It's strange.
It doesn't feel good to be...
treated ill like this after being treated so well.
I'm sorry, but let me speak casually with you.
- Of course, Sir.
- I was kidding.
Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
Wouldn't it be better if the interns...
- play it?
- I think so too.
Let's have the young ones play.
- Wait.
- What?
- Aren't you an intern?
- He sounds like a boss.
- Yes.
Let's start from the top.
- What?
- I mean from the oldest.
(Start from the oldest!)
(The interns are outspoken.)
Shall we start from the oldest?
- We are all equals.
- Why don't we play a game?
Do you know the number game?
- Play the number game.
- Okay.
- Just the interns.
- Only the interns should play.
- One.
- Two.
- Three.
- Four.
- Five.
- Six.
Seven.
- It's seven.
- Why did you do that?
You're out when you say seven.
- Is that right?
- He aimed for seven.
He's so innocent.
You're very charming.
He is charming.
There's something going on between these two.
- I think you're right.
- Aren't you older than me?
No, I'm not.
- What year were you born in?
- I was born in 1969.
He's younger than me?
Yes, that's right.
(He is two years younger than Mi Sun.)
Won Hae will go first.
Then I'll go. The game is to number six.
- Get ready.
- Wait.
Why am I not allowed to say seven?
- It's the last number.
- That means you're out.
You're out if you say the last number.
- It's the last number.
- Play some games once in a while.
- It's up to number six.
- Right now...
- the game is to number 6.
- Number 6.
- Get ready.
- Am I out?
- Yes.
- Start!
- One.
- Two.
(They're both out of the game.)
They're out.
- Since two more people are out,
- We're doing it again?
the game is to number four.
- It's all right.
- What are we going to do?
- Four.
- It's okay.
(What is he doing?)
Four.
- Wait a minute.
- You're out if you say four.
- Why did you say four?
- What?
Kil Kang, you're out.
- Kil Kang, you're out.
- Why did you do that?
(Kil Kang is dazed.)
Kil Kang, why did you say four?
Why did you say it suddenly?
He was fiddling with his wrist and suddenly, he rose and said four.
I was surprised.
- He is so cute.
- Okay then.
- Now the game is to three.
- Right.
- Who's left?
- Get ready. I won't answer that.
Get ready. If you're still in, please participate.
- Start.
- One.
- Two.
- Three.
He's out.
- You're out when you say three.
- You're out.
(Kil Kang doesn't know what to do.)
- You're out since you said three.
- You said three.
- Why did you stand up?
- Why were you standing?
I thought I was still in the game.
He is really cute.
(Will the interns be reliable in the real game?)
(Running Man: The Interns)
Get ready.
(Partners Run Errands Game)
It's team Won Hae and Ji Hyo.
Get ready, go.
Tape, work gloves,
an eraser, correction tape and a snack.
Tape, work gloves, an eraser, correction tape and a snack.
- Tape and...
- Go.
work gloves.
- Kim Won Hae.
- Won Hae already forgot.
(The time is how long the intern's name is called in one breath.)
(Moving quickly)
Tape and work gloves...
(He already found something?)
(An intern should be fast.)
(He is like a flash of lightning.)
(Did he find another item already?)
(This intern is doing great.)
The A4 paper.
She has reached her limit.
- The A4 paper.
Grab the paper.
- The slippers.
- Grab the scarf.
(He found it.)
Hey.
Hey!
(I gave it my all.)
- Oh wow.
- Goodness.
(This is the right way to assist a senior colleague.)
- Wow.
- Oh wow.
This isn't it.
(Goodness)
(It's not?)
This isn't it.
(It was a useless effort.)
- You have to find the tape first.
- Ji Hyo must be really annoyed.
- She really must be.
- She probably is.
It's all right.
(Ji Hyo and Won Hae succeed in finding three items.)
Next up is team Jo Han and Kwang Soo.
I have to say the name, right?
(Whispering)
Kwang Soo is the intern in this team, right?
No. Why? Isn't it obvious?
It's obvious that Kwang Soo is the intern.
No, Kwang Soo is the senior...
- and I'm the intern.
- Good luck with that.
- You have 10 seconds to read it.
- Okay.
On your mark, get set, go.
A blank CD, an air freshener,
work gloves, a ruler and paperwork.
A blank CD, an air freshener, work gloves, a ruler and paperwork.
It's CD, air, work, ruler and paper.
- A blank CD, an air...
- He's making it more confusing.
- Because of that.
- You're right.
- Jo Han lived abroad for a while.
- Right.
Kwang Soo should have said it in English.
Hong Ryul, you shouldn't be standing over there.
(Jo Han found the ruler.)
Why did he find the ruler? That wasn't on the list.
Jo Han.
- Was it on the list?
- Was it really?
That was on the list.
- Kwang Soo is nearly done.
- The USB.
I don't remember.
Didn't Kwang Soo stop?
- That wasn't on the list.
- The scarf.
(Kwang Soo is frustrated.)
- Jo Han!
- This is funny.
- What are you doing?
- Kwang Soo is angry.
- What are you doing, Jo Han?
- Kwang Soo.
Wasn't this on the list?
- The ruler was on the list.
- I know.
I told you. It's CD, air, work, ruler and paper.
There was a pair of work gloves in there.
I couldn't find the blank CD.
What are you going to do with just a ruler?
(Kwang Soo and Jo Han found only one item.)
- We are next.
- It's a pity.
He looks like Robert De Niro from "The Intern".
- He does look like Robert De Niro.
- He really does.
- He looks exactly like him.
- You're right.
- He has a similar vibe.
- Hong Ryul looks like him.
- They're similar in age too.
- Right.
- Yes.
- He looks like Robert De Niro.
- Say one item per second.
- One item per second.
- Since we have 10 seconds.
- Okay, 1 item per second.
- One item per second.
- Let's see.
- Go.
- It's a bit different.
A calculator, coloured paper,
tea, paper cup and a book.
Calculator, colour, tea, cup and book.
- A calculator, coloured paper,
- Coloured paper.
- Tea.
- Tea, paper cup and book.
- A calculator.
- Go.
Lee Hong Ryul.
Paper, calculator and coloured paper.
(Goodness)
Hong Ryul.
(The game is over in five seconds.)
Hong Ryul, it's over.
Why?
Seok Jin!
(Gosh!)
And you call yourself a singer?
(I am a sinner.)
I got something in my throat.
(Seok Jin has weak lungs.)
- What is he doing?
- I lost my breath.
I didn't get why you were stopping him.
It was just too funny.
Seok Jin is really...
- Isn't he funny?
- Yes, he is.
Later,
you'll see how different Ryul can be pronounced.
(By this guy over here)
I'm sorry Hong Ryul.
You should consult me before saying something like that.
Okay.
- Next up is team Gary and Kil Kang.
- Right.
- Let's go.
- We can do it.
- Gary has a long breath.
- Let's go.
When looking solely at the physical aspect,
Kil Kang seems unbeatable.
But he's the worst of us here.
He also has the worst concentration.
A mechanical pencil, toothbrush set,
highlighter, staples and USB.
- Why does he stress the set?
- Toothbrush set.
- Why does he stress it?
- Highlighter, staples and USB.
I don't know what a USB is.
Ahn Kil Kang.
Mechanical pencil.
Grab the squid.
Kil Kang, it's the squid.
- Kil Kang, the squid.
- Was it really on the list?
(He passes the second cabinet.)
- You shouldn't leave the door open.
- He's in a rush.
If you leave the cabinet door open, we can all see what's inside.
(No matter how long I look...)
- I can't remember a thing.
- The eraser is over there.
(What is he saying?)
(Gary is out of breath.)
It's over.
He didn't have anything on his mind.
He was just looking around.
Do you know what a USB is?
- I don't know.
- He doesn't even know what it is.
What do you know from the list?
I memorised mechanical pencil and toothbrush set.
(Gary feels betrayed.)
Then why did you go?
You shouldn't have left then.
- Oh, Kil Kang.
- What is this?
He's hilarious.
- It's hilarious today.
- It really is.
- We're next.
- Wow.
(The fifth team is team Jae Seok and Yoo Yeol.)
Jae Seok, show us your lung capacity.
- Sure.
- Okay?
I didn't agree to that.
Yeol told us differently.
Spray glue, clips.
What's spray glue?
Green tea, chain ring and a note.
- I can't memorise a thing.
- Spray glue, clips,
- green tea, chain ring and a note.
- Start.
What's a chain ring?
Yoo Yeol.
I can't hear a thing.
We can't hear Jae Seok at all.
(Yeol is taking his time.)
I think he can do it.
(Searches thoroughly)
He looks like he's out for a stroll.
(Pronouncing Yeol is easy for me.)
(No, it isn't.)
Why?
- It's over?
- It was too funny.
(Jae Seok and Yoo Yeol found zero items.)
Next up is Do Kyoon and Jong Kook.
(The sixth team is Do Kyoon and Jong Kook.)
(How will the two work as a team?)
Look at his hair.
Batteries, strands of ribbon, a pen,
slippers and a ruler.
Batteries, strands of ribbon, a pen, slippers and a ruler.
Battery, ribbon, pen, slipper and ruler.
- Ribbon pen?
- No, strands of ribbon.
- Strands of ribbon.
- Slipper and ribbon.
- Okay.
Kim Do Kyoon.
Do Kyoon looks like an adorable housewife.
He looks like an adorable housewife.
(Do Kyoon quickly finds one item.)
- He's really fast.
- Close the door.
- You should close the door.
- There's the coloured paper.
(He cleared three cabinets already.)
(He is as fast as lightning.)
- Oh wow.
- He's nearly done.
Really?
- Already?
- He has three items.
(Do Kyoon has very quick hands.)
(Charming)
What are you doing?
Jong Kook is really doing well.
- He's still at it.
- He has the longest breath.
Should we go and punch him?
- He has more than five items.
- He has so many.
- How many items are you taking?
- Do Kyoon!
- Were there that many items?
- Why do you have so many items?
(He swept the cabinets.)
How many did you pick up?
What is this?
- How many are there?
- You picked up so many.
- I just picked up as many as I can.
- But...
gloves weren't included.
You said you have a good memory.
- He just picked up whatever.
- He said he has a good memory.
- I heard him talking before.
- Yes?
He said that he went on another show...
and was tested to have the best memory there.
So then he must have...
remembered all of the previous items as well.
He remembered everything else.
- That must be why.
- I remembered everything.
- We have a ruler here.
- Okay.
- We also have a pen.
- Slippers, too.
- Slippers are here.
- Slippers.
And then...
- Where's the ribbon?
- I forgot that one.
(I forgot that one.)
- He finally gets a scolding.
- Where are the batteries?
I told you about the batteries before we started.
I forgot the batteries and a ribbon.
- We have three.
- I forgot.
You should have remembered the batteries.
You're right.
Jong Kook is getting angry.
- Good job, Do Kyoon.
- At least...
- I got three.
- Right.
(Jong Kook and Do Kyoon found three items.)
(The results)
(Rank 1: Jong Kook and Do Kyoon, Ji Hyo and Won Hae)
(Class 3 begins.)
- Hurry up.
- Can we go first?
Interns!
(We prepared this for you.)
(Have a good time!)
- Oh, my.
- It's been a while.
- The acupressure mat.
- It's an acupressure mat.
- The interns...
- Interns need to experience this.
(Interns need to experience this.)
- Oh, my.
- Can I have my socks on?
- It hurts so much.
- It's awful.
It must hurt a lot.
- It'll hurt so much.
- Put your feet on it.
- It hurts a lot.
- It's terrible.
- Have you tried it?
- It really hurts.
- You must have tried it a lot.
- It's awful.
By the way,
- I'm getting nervous.
- I'm sorry to say this, but...
why don't you guys just quit being our interns?
You're all getting ruder.
"Hey, does it hurt a lot?"
- Was I like that?
- Yes, you were.
I was worried about you, Sir.
Why are you suddenly calling me "Sir"?
Sir.
(I should behave.)
I've never lost to anyone in this game.
Mi Sun, take your socks off.
- How will it go?
- You have only one chance.
And as you all know,
even though we can't touch the player, we can still interrupt...
- the player in other ways.
- Yes, of course.
- As long as you don't touch them.
- You can still...
interrupt them.
- But you can't touch them.
- You can't.
- You can't touch them.
- Okay.
You have only one chance.
Go, Haha!
- Go!
- It's over when you jump.
- It's been too long.
- It's over once you jump.
- He has bad posture.
- It's over when you jump.
- Okay.
- Stay away.
- Don't worry.
(One, two)
- Go, Haha!
- Let's go!
Oh, my goodness!
(Jae Seok distracts Haha.)
What? This is acceptable.
- Oh, my goodness.
- Goodness.
- You can't jump.
- My goodness.
- Don't do that.
- Hey!
If you can't jump, it's over.
(Jumping)
What a coward.
(Haha jumped 1m 40cm.)
- That's not bad.
- He jumped pretty far.
This is not easy.
I think Jae Seok will jump far.
(Jong Kook puts his foot near Jae Seok.)
- Jae Seok.
- Don't do it.
- Step back, everybody.
- We didn't do anything.
- Don't you dare.
- We didn't touch you.
I'm not going to forgive you.
Our interns...
are massaging their feet.
(The interns are massaging their feet on the mat.)
You can't do that here.
We're not in a spa right now.
My goodness.
- This is not a spa.
- People do this at the spa.
- Be nice to Jae Seok when he jumps.
- Sure.
- His voice is so soft.
- It drains all my energy.
- My energy is gone.
- It makes me tired.
- His voice has a strange impact.
- It drains all of your energy.
I feel like I'm bathing in warm water.
His voice...
makes your shoulders drop.
It feels like it's 2am.
(Jae Seok prepares to jump.)
- Don't do that.
- I didn't do anything.
He almost fell on his own.
- Here I go!
- Wow!
(Jumping)
(A flying grasshopper)
- Now you just have to stand up.
- Stand up.
- It hurts.
- He did well.
Oh goodness.
It hurts.
(The mat increases blood circulation.)
- He jumped far.
- It hurts.
Wow.
- It's Kwang Soo's turn.
- I think I can get second place.
I think Kwang Soo will jump well.
- Wow.
- Look at how big his feet are.
- He looks like a giraffe.
- Don't step on the line.
- They look like monster's feet.
- Please don't step on the line.
- Step away from the line.
- Okay.
- He's right.
- What are you doing?
What did you say?
Watch your toenails. You might trip over.
(Jong Kook is ready to interrupt him.)
Here I go.
- What are you doing?
- Nothing.
- It's nothing.
- Don't do that.
- Go.
- In 3, 2, 1.
- Jump!
- Don't do that!
(They pulled off Kwang Soo's microphone.)
- It was here.
- He landed over here.
- It was about here.
- Right here.
- It was over here.
- Is that acceptable?
This is acceptable?
- We didn't touch you.
- We only touched your microphone.
- Only the microphone.
- We didn't touch you.
- We didn't.
What if I pull someone's hair?
It was only the microphone.
- Next.
- It's Gary's turn.
- We won't do anything.
- I'm going to jump right away.
(The fourth player is Gary.)
(Twisting)
(Kwang Soo twisted Gary's arm.)
- Why? What happened?
- It was before he jumped.
Kwang Soo.
You didn't jump yet.
Jump as fast as you can.
(You have to jump far and fast.)
This is annoying.
Don't let them stop you.
(Here I go.)
- Hurry and jump.
- That hurts.
(Splashing)
(They splash water on Gary's face.)
- It's cold.
- He looks like a squid.
- Gary.
- This is too much.
Look, Gary's a squid under water.
It's a squid in the water.
(A squid in the water)
Gary looks like a squid.
This is hilarious.
(Will Gary be able to jump well after the distraction?)
Wait, hold on.
Here I go.
Go, Gary! Now!
- Jump now.
- Wow.
(Flying)
- He jumped far.
- He did well.
Oh wow.
(Gary jumped 2m 35cm.)
He jumped more than 2m.
- Good job.
- It's 2m 35cm.
Who's next? Ji Hyo?
It's my turn.
Amazing.
Please.
- Should we have a meeting?
- Sure.
(The members discuss how they will distract Jong Kook.)
We need to do something to Jong Kook.
- Of course.
- Let's discuss.
Guys,
let's not do this.
- I haven't done anything.
- Okay, just go.
- Everybody's waiting for you.
- Okay.
- The interns are waiting.
(Jong Kook hits Kwang Soo.)
Step back.
- Why?
- What happened?
What happened?
What just happened?
(We heard something break.)
- It must have hurt a lot.
- He hit Kwang Soo hard.
(Kwang Soo is in pain.)
- What should we do?
- Kwang Soo.
- Are you okay?
- Are you all right?
Kwang Soo, are you all right?
I didn't do anything.
I'm going now.
(Playing the xylophone)
- "National Singing Contest"!
- Singing Contest!
- Look.
- Look at this.
- He crossed the line.
- No, I didn't.
- Jong Kook crossed the line.
- I didn't jump yet.
- Did you see that?
- It doesn't count.
(Stirring of events)
- You crossed the line.
- I was just walking.
- Really now.
- I didn't jump.
(Jong Kook silenced everyone.)
- Here I go!
- I'll give you a countdown.
In 3, 2, 1.
- Let's go!
- Go!
(Jumping)
- Jump!
Wow!
That really hurts.
It must hurt a lot.
The red one.
- Wow.
- I can't jump.
- It's just half.
- Only half.
(Worrying)
I'll stop them from interrupting you.
Please stop.
- Ji Hyo.
- This is the only way to stop her.
(Wrapping her legs)
What are you doing? Stop it.
I'm not touching her.
Why?
Wait.
Aren't they supposed to be interns?
You're an intern.
- Isn't he an intern?
- Won Hae.
They're not interns.
(Hitting the xylophone)
Please stop.
(Won Hae protects Ji Hyo from distraction.)
Chen Bolin is watching you.
Really, come on.
- Don't do that.
- Who is that?
- Ji Hyo.
- Yes.
- Chen Bolin?
- Do you know what this is?
- It's "National Singing Contest".
- No.
Chen Bolin
- Do you like him more than Gary?
- Chen Bolin.
- Do you know what this is, then?
- He's handsome.
Ji Hyo.
- Chen Bolin, Ji Hyo
(Chen Bolin, Ji Hyo)
Ji Hyo, Chen Bolin
- I'm going to jump.
- Okay.
- I'm going.
- Excuse me.
You're supposed to be an intern.
- He's resting. – He looks like my dad.
This is not your own house.
- Look.
- Hold on.
We're not...
- at the beach.
- He's on vacation.
- What are you doing?
- This is so funny.
Oh goodness.
Here I go.
I think she'll do well.
Chen Bolin is watching you.
(Jumping)
She jumped farther than Haha.
No, she didn't.
It's 1m 50cm.
Seok Jin is the last player.
- Guys.
- Get ready, everybody.
- Don't do anything.
- It's Seok Jin's turn.
Seok Jin is the last player.
(Jae Seok brings a box.)
What are you doing?
(The members are preparing to distract Seok Jin.)
- Do it together.
- Throw them when he jumps.
(The members whip Seok Jin.)
(Throwing socks)
(Seok Jin was distracted by the towel and socks.)
Where did I land?
- Right here.
- No, it's here.
- Seok Jin walked.
- He landed over here.
Now,
- our interns will jump.
- Let's go.
The first player.
(The first player is Hong Ryul.)
I should aim for 2m, right?
- Of course.
- Sure.
- Then you'll win.
- Right.
You're stepping on the line.
- Look.
- Wait a minute.
- You're stepping on the line.
- Please step away from the line.
- Like this?
- Yes.
- Should I stand here?
- Right.
- Am I behind the line now?
- Yes.
(How far will the oldest intern jump?)
- Your stomach has come out a lot.
- It reminds me of mountains.
Mountains?
- You got this. You can do it.
- Be careful.
- Sir.
- He keeps...
- You keep moving forward.
- You can't do that.
- You can't.
- You can't step on the line.
- You can't move forward.
- Yes. Move back.
- You saw that?
Please don't step on the line.
- Please, don't.
- You saw that?
- Everyone can see you.
- But I think...
it's not going to affect the result too much.
(The 63-year-old Hong Ryul should be scared.)
- Go.
- Here we go.
(Here he goes.)
(Fly, Hong Ryul!)
(He lands perfectly.)
Bravo!
He's good.
He landed here too.
(His record is 1m 70cm.)
He jumped a lot.
I didn't reach 2m.
(He proves that he's still very healthy.)
I'm dizzy.
Next is Mi Sun.
- I've never done this before.
- You stepped on the line.
Miss Park! Miss Park!
Her body is so strange.
(It's her first time. What will be her record?)
It's 1m 50cm.
- Wow.
- She jumped a lot.
She's better than Haha.
She jumped 1.5m.
(Haha is ashamed.)
You are the best.
Lower.
(The third intern player is Kil Kang.)
(Power jump)
- That was awesome.
- Are you all right?
(Kil Kang's record is 2m.)
He jumped far.
- Here.
- It's 2m.
- It's 1.95m.
- It's 2 metres.
That hurts so much.
It hurts a lot, doesn't it?
- Who's next?
- Go, Won Hae!
- Just follow your gut feeling.
- A notch higher.
- Okay.
- It just hurts once.
Just once.
His feet are so pale.
(His feet are pale.)
But really,
his feet and hands are very pretty.
(He's got the whitest feet.)
He has soft and delicate feet.
- Really.
- How can they be so pale?
- His feet are like hands.
- Let me see.
- They are.
- He's got soft and delicate feet.
- He really does.
(He jumps.)
(He jumps far.)
(Won Hae's record is 2m 10cm.)
- He jumped a lot.
- Yes!
- He took off his socks.
It helps.
He jumped 2m 10cm.
He jumped really far.
(The nice-looking feet is good for walking too.)
What is he doing?
(The fifth intern player is Yoo Yeol.)
By looking at...
Yeol's feet, we can know...
that he has lived an easy life.
- Yes.
- He's got baby feet.
- He must've lived an easy life.
- The baby feet.
- He probably stayed indoors.
- Yes.
- Seriously.
- Look at his feet.
(He jumps with a loud scream.)
Express the pain!
Express the pain.
Yes.
(Yoo Yeol jumps 2m 15cm.)
He's amazing.
- Everyone jumped far.
- They are all very good.
They all did very well.
We shouldn't have played this indoor.
(Rank 1 is Gary and Ahn Kil Kang.)
We said we will add all the points.
We're done playing the games now.
The team with the most points...
is Kim Won Hae and Song Ji Hyo.
(Ji Hyo and Won Hae wins the training test.)
We won!
(Won Hae gets overwhelmed with joy...)
(and tumbles.)
(He rolls on the acupuncture pad.)
(He's thrilled.)
Rank 2 got 40 points. It's Jae Seok and Yoo Yeol.
- Come on.
- No ceremony?
(Yoo Yeol also celebrates this joyful moment...)
(by rolling on the acupuncture pad.)
(He plants himself on the acupuncture pad.)
- Sir...
- Son!
- Is your head okay?
- Are you all right?
Gosh.
The next ones must be pressured.
- They must be pressured.
- Now...
What will the next one do?
(He's not happy.)
Third is Gary and Kil Kang.
What will Kil Kang do?
(Rank 3 is Gary and Kil Kang.)
(Why do these things happen to me?)
Kil Kang.
- Oh dear.
- It's because of Won Hae.
(He throws himself.)
(And he rolls on the pad.)
(He flies and falls on the acupuncture pad.)
(And he suffers from the aftereffect.)
You fell.
Are you okay?
Kil Kang.
Why would you fly and fall on the pad?
I never imagined he would fall on the pad.
Everyone is so good.
(The training test is over.)
Now it's time for mentoring between the seniors and interns.
Each team can go inside a room...
and be comfortable.
We'll go to the mentoring room?
Let's go.
(What will happen in the mentoring room?)
(1 on 1 mentoring at Running Man Company)
- It's newly painted.
- Hong Ryul is here.
- Hello.
- It's here.
- Should we go in?
- I will see you later then.
- Okay.
- What's this place?
Wait. What's this place?
Wow, this is...
(Hong Ryul cracks up.)
There you are.
Oh dear.
These are your things from the past.
Oh gosh.
(This boy grew up to be Korea's best entertainer.)
I'm really surprised.
It's...
When was that, Hong Ryul?
I used to do a skit "Returned Ghost Wail Mountain Cabin".
- I remember that.
- I did that...
in 1993.
Right. You did it with Ha Ryong.
Two of you did it together, right?
- Yes. I did a play with Seong Beom.
- Right.
There are some pictures of me...
- that I don't even own.
- Look at these pictures.
They look like recent pictures.
This.
"Small House People".
- "Small House People".
You did it with Hwi Jae.
I did a lot of shows with Hwi Jae.
I remember you doing this with Hwi Jae.
(The skit he did with Lee Hwi Jae was a bit hit.)
Gosh, that was such a long time ago.
Hong Ryul's history is laid out here.
(And they bring back memories.)
Wow.
Right now
I love how you look right now
Wow.
(They are album covers of Yoo Yeol's albums.)
It's so new.
That's what I'm talking about.
- This was my first album.
- I know.
Which songs were from the first album?
"Since the Breakup" and "Autumn Rain".
"Since the Breakup".
("Since the Breakup" by Yoo Yeol)
Quiet you
Without words
Your appearance
Everything remains the same
That's how the song goes, right?
- That's correct.
- Right?
- The lyrics are slightly different.
- Right.
- It's 90 percent right.
- Why did they...
decorate the room like this?
I was very surprised as soon as I entered.
What's this?
(What is this place?)
There are many things here.
(Gary and Kil Kang are confused too.)
- What's this?
- What is this?
Your movie posters are here.
The movie we worked on together, "Dachimawa Lee" is missing.
- I know.
- It's too bad.
We used to be a team.
(The door opens.)
(Ji Hyo and Won Hae enter their mentoring room too.)
What's this?
No way.
(Plays, movies and posters that Won Hae appeared in)
These are all the movies your starred in, right?
Movies and plays.
You did so many.
You shot a movie with Kwang Soo?
Yes. We shot "My Little Hero" together.
It failed miserably.
Yes.
It was a great movie,
but it didn't do so well.
(The hero of the doomed movie enters the room.)
It's Solid!
(There's a guitar and a piano.)
It's been so long since I saw these pictures.
(Solid's pictures are on the wall.)
You were so young then.
Of course, you are still young.
It reminds me of the past.
- Look.
- Wow.
- This is...
- This is great.
- This is the house of rock.
Gosh.
You are right here.
(On the show, "Flaming Youth")
If they have a child, this is how the child will look like.
(The picture is photoshopped.)
This is your room.
(The room is filled with rock spirit.)
That's Larry Carlton.
It's a wall of all the famous guitarists.
This is so great.
What's this?
- Wow.
- What's this?
What is this?
What's this?
Wow.
What's this? Oh dear.
This is Mi Sun's room.
What are all these things?
This is crazy. So all of these are...
- What are all these?
- There are news articles too.
- There are locks too.
- What are those for?
- What's this?
- What is this room for?
What's this?
(The bell rings.)
(Suddenly,)
(they hear a mysterious bell.)
We must be doing something.
- It must be an announcement.
- Yes.
So there's really something.
This is an announcement.
Dear all employees and interns.
From this moment, the final mission for the day will begin.
The losing team has to pay for dinner.
Not this again.
What is it? What's the mission?
(Aren't we here to mentor them?)
(Oh my gosh!)
(They get locked inside!)
Wait.
What are you doing? What are you doing?
Loser has to buy dinner.
What are you doing?
Why are you locking the door all of a sudden?
Why are you locking the door?
Why is she locking the door?
- What are you doing?
- Why are you locking the door?
Hey.
They are trying to make us suspicious by locking the door.
The final mission begins now.
You will play roulette to decide who will treat everyone to dinner.
Starting now, you get 60 minutes.
You need to escape this room...
within 60 minutes.
You have to unlock the padlock as soon as possible...
and escape the room.
(The escape mission starts.)
Hello!
(Anyone there?)
Anyone there?
(Knocking)
(He knocks quietly.)
We are locked in. Aren't you too calm about it?
- Well...
- You have to panic.
- Really?
- Yes.
Are you...
just going to sleep here?
- Wait.
- Okay.
Hey! Anyone there?
What do I have to do?
Your voice is too soft.
(What will we do with him?)
"Hey!"
Oh my goodness.
You won the last game.
- Yes.
- We'll give you a hint.
- Great.
- What is it?
Do you call this a hint?
- Are you kidding me?
- Is this the letter "L"?
(What is it?)
- What?
- Tell me which letter it is.
(He's not happy.)
(They are stuck.)
Wait here. I'll go check the lock.
(What am I doing here?)
The lock is in alphabets.
(The lock is in alphabets.)
- What is it?
- Look at this.
- It's in English.
- It is.
It uses alphabets and a number at the end.
- It's a number.
- It is.
(They need four correct alphabets.)
We need a hint.
There must be a hint.
Okay.
Gosh. You shouldn't be so relaxed.
We'll get out of here somehow.
(He has a very positive outlook.)
Let me start from the first album.
(Let me start from the first album.)
This isn't it.
(Will he be able to escape?)
Do we have 60 minutes?
Some will...
(He's anxious.)
Some may escape before the time is up.
(They need to find a hint.)
There's a hint in here.
(60 minutes to escape)
The letters "S" and "N".
Wait.
I went to Samgwang Elementary School.
Look. It says Amgwang.
- Really?
- It's supposed to be Samgwang.
- The letter "S" is missing.
- "S"?
- Okay.
- What else is missing?
- It starts with S.
- Okay.
(They start looking for other hints.)
- There's a CD player.
- Let's listen to it.
- Play it.
- Let's try it.
Listen.
Listen to this.
What's the chord?
What is it? Try again.
Is there a metronome?
(Is there a metronome?)
(But that's for measuring tempo.)
Let me see.
- Do Kyoon.
- Wait.
I don't have perfect pitch.
Try it with the guitar.
- Try it.
- Wait.
It's not in tune.
Still, you should try.
- I found a way!
- Okay.
(There's not a lot of time.)
(Oh gosh!)
(What is that?)
(It's a recorder.)
- Why do you need that?
- Well...
- Try the guitar.
- It's a "G".
(He plays the recorder.)
It's a "G".
- "G"?
- Yes.
That's right.
- Are you sure?
- Yes.
Why did they put this here?
Why did they spell the names wrong?
That's not spelled right.
(They found spelling errors.)
Both have the same alphabet wrong.
Look at this. It is spelled incorrectly.
They have it backward.
This is wrong.
(What does this mean?)
The letters E, F, G.
H, I, J, K...
- It's "L"!
- "L"?
M, N, O.
(Is L the hint?)
P, Q...
- Wait. Won Hae.
- Yes.
- Won Hae.
- Yes?
Let's look at it from afar.
Look at it from here.
Look at it from afar.
(If you look at it from afar...)
There's something.
Look.
(Look!)
Wait a minute. It could be this.
- There's no P.
- Okay, zero.
- B.
- Blue?
It's not blue.
Let's see.
It doesn't have E.
(Is "Blue" the passcode?)
Green.
(Is it green?)
"G" for green?
- Don't you think so?
- Green!
Green. The letter "G".
Our clothes are green.
- We are the green team.
- Right.
There's a green line.
(Only some things have green lines.)
This one is green.
Which one?
This one's green too.
There's the letter "R"...
- on purple things.
- Yes.
- We should find purple things.
- Okay.
- Let's open this.
What's inside?
- Okay, here's a hint.
- What's the hint?
(First letter of the first prize)
- First letter of the first prize.
- First letter of the first prize?
Let's find the first prize.
(Let's find the first prize.)
Look.
It's 1970 University Song Festival's first prize.
(1970 University Song Festival's first prize)
(University Song Festival?)
(Year 1986 MBC University Song Festival)
(Yeol debuted in 1986 at the 10th University Song Festival.)
(Could it be?)
Who won the first prize?
It was Lee Jung Seok. He sang "First Snow Is Falling".
Lee starts with L.
- It was Lee Jung Seok.
- L.
We have L.
(It's L.)
We have L and then...
When is your birthday?
It's August 24th.
- Really?
- Yes.
Mine's on the 24th too. It's February 24th.
(Really?)
But 24 has nothing to do with this.
(They focus on what they have in common.)
What else? You're Kang Gary.
- I'm Ahn Kil Kang.
- We have Kang in common.
I'm Kang.
You're Kang Gary. I'm Ahn Kil Kang.
(Ahn Kil Kang and...)
(Kang Gary)
(If the hint has to do with what they have in common,)
(then could it be?)
I'll try Kang.
(I'll try Kang.)
I'll try one by one.
(It'd be nice if it was right.)
(It's unlocked.)
(He got it!)
Look.
We got it!
(They're excited!)
We must be stupid.
- It's not working.
- Why isn't it working?
We're so stupid.
(They pretend they didn't get it.)
Why isn't it working?
(They succeed in escaping!)
Congratulations. You've escaped.
You have to find the other team's...
name tags and...
put them on the intern's vest.
The name tags have each team's Chinese zodiac.
You have a greater chance of paying for the staff dinner...
if your name tags are on the roulette more.
Quickly find the Chinese zodiac name tags.
(The more name tags they find, the better.)
(He is very eager.)
I found one.
- Did you find one?
- Yes.
(Kil Kang finds one.)
It's Year of the Horse.
- That's ours.
- Put it on.
(They got Seok Jin and Hong Ryul's zodiac.)
Like this.
Gary and Kil Kang escaped.
(Already?)
- We can do it.
- What?
Can we?
- Where is it?
- This isn't it.
Gary and Kil Kang escaped.
I'm sorry. We should give up.
(I'm sorry. We should give up.)
- I'm sorry.
- It's okay. I got it.
- Did you bring your wallet?
- I have my company card.
Thank you.
Wait.
(They concentrate on purple things.)
- I got it!
- What is it?
- It's this.
It's 106.
The radio program I'm doing is on KBS.
Let's take the letters "K" and "L".
(They think it's K from KBS.)
K and L...
Do you think it's this? Look at the pictures.
These are the same pictures, but...
here you have your mouth closed.
(Pictures without yellow borders have closed mouths.)
But these ones have open mouths.
(The yellow borders have open mouths.)
Do you think it's...
the alphabet "E"?
(Could it be the letter "E"?)
Do you think so?
(Ji Hyo and Won Hae still look for hints.)
Why is there a protractor?
Do I have to look at it upside down?
- It's the letter "D".
- "D"?
(Upside down, it's D.)
- The one with red.
- Okay.
We have to look at the red things.
We should focus on the red things. That one's G.
- That's G.
- Okay.
- What's this?
- It's Black Sabbath.
- Is it Black Sabbath?
- Yes.
- It's Black Sabbath.
- Okay.
What about this?
It's Larry Carlton and Steve Lukather.
- He's wearing a red T-shirt.
- I see.
- What about him?
- He's Sammy Hagar.
- I see.
- They all have S.
- That's true.
Let's say it's S.
- Okay.
- Chord G and the posters are S.
Rock and roll.
The "And" symbol.
- That's in red.
- Right.
(Wait a minute.)
I got it.
Okay.
It's singer.
(They are both singers.)
- I think it's singer.
- Sing.
Singer? Song?
(Song?)
- Sing?
- Sing or song?
(The lock is cracked open.)
- What was it?
- I got it.
- It was sing.
- Sing?
Goodness.
I knew it.
Sing.
(Meanwhile, Kwang Soo and Jo Han are stuck.)
You're the original love seeker.
- Haha.
- What?
- Haha, are you out?
- Yes.
We need to find the name tags.
(Will they be able to escape?)
Let's try this.
This won't open.
(They are investigating the green video tape.)
Wait.
Maybe it's another one.
Zero.
(They found zero.)
It's the alphabet "O".
So, could it be "L"?
"L".
This is green too.
Which one?
(The "V" in Mi Sun's photo.)
(O, L, V...)
L. O. V. E.
(Rushing)
What's "L"?
- "L".
- "O".
- Zero.
- It worked!
Mi Sun.
Goodness.
My goodness.
- Let's get out of here.
- Let's go out and find it.
- Wait.
- My jacket.
(After their fast escape,)
(they are in search of the name tags.)
(They spot Year of the Rat name tag.)
Mi Sun.
- Mi Sun.
- Haha.
(Please stick the name tag on me.)
- Mi Sun.
- Haha.
(Please stick the name tag on me.)
(They are a great team.)
You should put it on.
You should put it.
(They are off to a great start.)
Let's go.
Yes!
Look.
It's there?
Again, Year of the Rat.
(They found another one.)
Where should we go?
(Is it a coincidence that they found Year of the Rat name tags?)
- Let's go.
- Goodness.
Oh, goodness.
CD, radio.
(Meanwhile the Year of the Rat team is oblivious of the situation.)
Oh!
It was there?
- It's on the hat again.
- Over here.
It's an ant.
- It's the letter "A".
- The letter "A".
"A" for ant.
Wait.
- Give it to me.
- It's L, A, K, right?
Oh, it's "Talk".
- What?
- Talk.
- Oh! T, A, L, K.
- Yes.
The best talk show hosts.
T, A, L, K.
(The lock opens.)
- Goodness.
- Let's go.
(Jae Seok and Yoo Yeol succeed in breaking out.)
(Seok Jin and Hong Ryul are still contemplating on their similarity.)
- Why?
- Wait.
- He's got it.
- N, O, S, E.
- Oh!
- N, O, S, E. Nose.
It's nose.
It should be this.
Nose.
(The lock opens.)
(Both are famous for their nose.)
We did it!
- I knew you could do it.
- You knew?
I knew it.
(Meanwhile, Ji Hyo and Won Hae are focusing on the film posters...)
(within the blue borderline.)
The blue borderline.
Yes.
The number of letters within the blue borderline is the same.
It's 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6 and 7.
Seven? Then it's A, B, C, D, E,
- F, G.
- The letter "G".
(The letter "G" is the seventh alphabet.)
The letters, G, L, D.
We found three letters already.
The letter "G".
G, O, L, D.
It's gold.
How did you find that? Where was the letter "O"?
- I just left it as a blank.
- You just put it in?
I just filled it in with a circle. And it spelled out as gold.
It was really gold.
(The answer was really gold.)
You should have done it earlier.
You could have got it sooner.
Goodness.
Gold.
Let's go.
Quickly.
(Now, shall we go search for some name tags?)
(Panting)
Haha.
(I'm so tired.)
This is what we usually do.
I've been up 63 flights of stairs before.
Haha, this is killing me.
(The number of name tags that have been found.)
(Haha and Mi Sun have Jae Seok and Yoo Yeol's name tag.)
(Here comes the team of the Year of the Rat.)
Come stand behind me.
Come this way.
(Mi Sun, run away.)
Mi Sun.
(Jae Seok and Yoo Yeol need their Year of the Rat name tags.)
Mi Sun, run away.
Go after her.
- Lock the door.
- Just get the name tags.
The Year of the Rat name tags.
(Give me the Year of the Rat name tags.)
- We just need our name tags.
- No.
(He is firm not to pay for the dinner bill.)
Mi Sun, hide it.
Just get our name tags.
(Yoo Yeol succeeds in taking the name tags.)
Did you get it?
- There was one more,
- Yes.
- but I couldn't do it.
- You did well.
See you again.
- Let's go find another.
- Just find the others.
All right. Let's go find another one.
(He is quite tough.)
(Jae Seok and Yoo Yeol are catching up with four name tags.)
(Meanwhile, Gary, who was the first one to break free,)
(finds Seok Jin and Hong Ryul's Year of the Horse name tag.)
Oh.
It's Year of the Sheep.
(The number of name tags that each team has currently.)
There's another Year of the Horse.
There's another Year of the Horse name tag.
- You are truly amazing.
- We got this.
(With seven name tags, Seok Jin and Hong Ryul are the first in line.)
I found it. It's here.
It's Year of the Chicken.
- Year of the Chicken.
- Yes.
Let's go.
Year of the Chicken.
Isn't this it?
It's Year of the Chicken.
It's Ji Hyo.
(Suddenly Ji Hyo and Won Hae become the first in line to pay up.)
- Are we allowed to come in here?
- It's all right.
Won't we get blamed if something goes missing in this room?
I'll go look somewhere else.
(He bangs his head.)
(Dizzy)
You should be more careful.
Really, you should be more careful.
(Meanwhile, Kwang Soo and Jo Han gave up and starts to sing.)
(Time over)
- There were none upstairs.
- The blue ones were close together.
- Goodness.
- None.
- Then.
- Yes.
- Jong Kook will spin the roulette.
Since I paid for the dinner last time,
- I will spin it this time.
- Okay.
I wouldn't be chosen again, will I?
I see that there are a few reds.
Yes, but that doesn't matter.
- You never know.
- Please spin it.
Okay. I'll spin it.
If it lands on a white, you need to spin it again.
All right.
I'll spin it now.
One. I'll spin it.
Oh, no.
(The wheel starts to spin.)
(Please, not us.)
The green one.
Please.
Wait.
No.
(It's getting closer to the red mark.)
(No, this can't be.)
(Stop right there.)
(Will Jong Kook and Do Kyoon pay for dinner?)
(It passed the red mark.)
(Thank goodness.)
(Though they had only three marks, it was a close one.)
Goodness.
That was close.
I'll spin it.
(The wheel will spin until a team is chosen.)
I hope it's Jong Kook.
It keeps on stopping near the red mark.
It should stop.
It's dangerous.
They should have stuck the marks closer together.
It's dangerous. Please just pass.
It's getting nearer to the red mark.
(The speed is slowing down.)
(Will it be Jong Kook and Do Kyoon?)
(Or will it be another team?)
(Who will pay for dinner?)
(The speed is slowing down.)
(Will it be Jong Kook and Do Kyoon?)
(Or will it be another team?)
(Who will pay for dinner?)
- No!
- Yes!
(Haha and Mi Sun have been chosen.)
(Unbelievable!)
(We only had three marks on the board.)
(He who laughs last is the winner.)
- Goodness!
- We did it.
(The fate of the dinner bill has been decided.)
(The employees and interns enjoy their time together.)
Let's give a round of applause for Miss Park.
(Eat up, everyone.)
I will hand out the employee ID cards.
- Here you go.
- Good job.
Mi Sun. Congratulations.
(A golden employee ID card is given as a token of gratitude.)
- Won Hae.
- Thank you.
- Yeol.
Good job. Jo Han.
- Thank you.
- Kil Kang.
Thank you.
Hong Ryul.
And Do Kyoon.
(Every intern has received a golden employee ID card.)
One more round.
- One more round.
- Yes, please.
Thank you, Mi Sun.
I love you, Mi Sun.
I love you, Haha.
("Experience never gets old", from the movie, "The Intern")
You have to try seven restaurants...
within 12 hours to complete the mission.
Everyone?
- We have to hurry up.
- We don't have much time.
(Visiting restaurants all over the country)
- Thank you.
- This is delicious.
This is my favourite restaurant.
It's Kwang Soo's house!
Someone is lying under the bed sheets.
Please be careful.
(Will they succeed in trying all seven restaurants?)
("12-hour Food Challenge" to be aired next week) !@\