(300th Episode Special)
(7 vs 300 Part 2)
(The 300th Episode Special is continued.)
(Special tests in celebration of the 300th episode are awaiting.)
It's the 300th Episode Special,
7 vs 300.
- 7 vs 300?
-  What?
(The grand match has already begun.)
What is it?
("Running Man Quiz")
("300m Essay")
("300 Bowls")
"300 Boxes"!
(The 7 members must become one.)
It's so painful.
(It's them against the number "300".)
(When they reach their limit,)
(they must face even greater opponents.)
(Y University in Seoul)
(What kind of "300" is waiting for them?)
Which university is it?
Let's go up.
(What is...)
(inside...)
(this building?)
(They can't help but exclaim as soon as they step into the gym.)
- Seok Jin.
-  What is that?
(What did they see?)
(Wow!)
(The sight gives them the chills.)
What is that?
(300 people are waiting for the Running Man members.)
Look at this.
(Overwhelmed)
There are really 300 of them.
(There are 300 young men and women.)
(Wow!)
Look at this.
(Amidst the young spirits,)
(the game begins.)
Look at this.
(7 vs 300: The Fourth Mission)
Nice to see you all.
(Bowing)
It's astounding.
- Since when were they here?
-  I don't know.
We lost.
We can't win this.
- But really,
-  Look at this spirit.
how can we beat this energy?
(It's hopeless.)
- The name of this mission is...
-  What is it?
"300 People".
(Do they want us to fight and beat 300 people?)
How can 7 beat 300?
- There's no way we can win this.
-  What do you mean?
- What is this?
-  How can we win this match?
We're older. We can beat them with our age.
We're just older.
The first person...
to go up against 300 people is...
(Please, not me)
Jae Seok.
Me?
(Jae Seok is the first player.)
Am I?
Am I the first?
- Yu Jae Seok!
-  Yu Jae Seok!
(What kind of match will he have against 300 people?)
The game Jae Seok will play will be revealed.
- What is it?
-  The game will be...
(The game is...)
The game will be...
- Slap-Match.
-  I should play that instead.
(Slap-Match is the first game.)
I should play this game.
(Slap-Match)
- Slap-Match against 300?
-  Is that possible?
How many times do I need to play it?
The student's ddakji will be put on the ground first,
and Jae Seok will slap his ddakji first.
If the student's ddakji is flipped over, then Jae Seok wins.
You have to flip it at once.
If I fail to flip it at once, will I not have another chance?
(Jae Seok is really good at this, but can he beat 300 people?)
(Who is the first opponent to play against Jae Seok?)
(It's a strong and handsome guy.)
(The first opponent looks tough to beat already.)
- Number One!
-  Jae Seok!
- Jae Seok!
-  Number One!
-  Jae Seok!
(This is how you do a pre-game chant.)
Akaraka
- Akaraka!
-  Akaraka!
(Akaraka!)
(Can you feel the energy?)
Us, too. We should do something.
(They are surely overwhelmed.)
(We can't step back like this.)
We should do something.
(How will the members cheer against this grand cheering?)
I'm testing the microphone.
- Running Man
-  You're lovely
From top to bottom
(What are you doing?)
(They are so funny.)
Please focus, Jae Seok.
I'm telling you.
- Jae Seok will play until he loses.
-  You can do this.
You can do it. You're good at this.
- He is.
-  You know you're good at this.
You will flip it at once. You will.
- You're the dominator of this game.
-  Go.
(After a deep breath, he throws his ddakji.)
(The ddakji flies high in the air.)
(What's the result?)
(Jae Seok failed.)
That was so close.
- Don't worry.
-  Jae Seok is at a disadvantage.
(Jae Seok failed. It's Team 300's turn.)
Jae Seok is at a disadvantage. It's Number One's turn.
Let's go.
(He gets ready.)
It would be a nightmare if he beat Jae Seok now.
(Hit it if you can.)
It's your turn, now.
(He slaps it hard right on Jae Seok's ddakji.)
(Will it end like this?)
It's your turn, now.
Oh, no.
(It's not so easy.)
- Try not to slap too hard.
-  It's Jae Seok's turn.
- I shouldn't slap it too hard.
-  He should...
- take aim precisely this time.
-  Hit it softly, not too hard.
(With caution, Jae Seok slaps his ddakji again.)
(I must end this here.)
(Precise targeting)
Okay!
(Jae Seok has won.)
- Okay.
-  Okay.
(It was a match that showed Jae Seok's skills.)
Number two, please come out.
(The second opponent appears with great aura.)
He's handsome.
I think...
I feel that...
I must flip it at once. I don't think I'll have another chance.
I think he'll be good at everything.
(Number Two seems to be good at Slap-Match.)
- Have you played this before?
-  You must be good at sports.
- I major in sports.
-  Wow.
(He's a sports major.)
(A sports major is here to beat Jae Seok.)
Here comes the challenger. Against this athletic student,
Jae Seok goes first!
- At once. At once.
-  Flip it at once.
(This is only his second opponent.)
(There might be no second chance.)
(Jae Seok strikes.)
Don't hit too hard.
(Jae Seok fails.)
(No way.)
- What's your name?
-  Number Two.
- Number Two!
-  Number Two!
- He's Ji Seok.
-  Oh Ji Seok?
It should flip that way.
- Please don't flip it.
-  Your names are...
- Ji Seok.
-  No, Ji Seok.
Go easy, Ji Seok.
(Please)
(I'll show everyone how athletic I am.)
(Fly like a butterfly...)
(and sting like a...)
Good job, Ji Seok.
Go easy, Ji Seok. Good job.
(Number Two fails.)
He's so bad.
(It's really hilarious.)
(Kwang Soo's exaggerated laughter makes everyone laugh.)
He missed.
- He missed his turn.
-  You can do it.
Okay.
(Jae Seok slaps hard without notice.)
(It flips!)
Jae Seok wins again.
(Jae Seok wins.)
That was good. Keep it up. Don't get relaxed yet.
Jae Seok is amazing.
He beat two opponents already. Number Three, please come out.
Oh, my. He's in good shape.
- Jae Seok is in trouble now.
-  Please introduce yourself.
I'm Lee Won Jae from the Department of Physical Education.
Oh my goodness. Another athletic guy.
You're also a sports major?
What kind of sports are you good at?
I'm good at swimming.
Swimming? He must be good at this game.
You have broad shoulders.
(Due to extensive swimming, he can slap the ddakji hard.)
Jae Seok versus Number Three.
Jae Seok, you must defeat at least 50 students.
His shoulders are wider than yours.
- Jae Seok, you can do this.
-  Jae Seok.
You must flip it at once.
Flip it at once. Do it while you still have the stamina.
(Perfect posture)
There you go.
(Jae Seok fails.)
Your friend mentioned something about a Mosquito Dance.
- Mosquito Dance?
-  Can you show us the dance?
Can you show it to us?
- In 1, 2.
-  In 1, 2, 3, 4.
A huge mosquito bit my foot
(A shocking transformation)
It was itchy
(Kwang Soo's counterattack)
So I started to scratch my foot without thinking
It was itchy
(He is the descendant of the Mosquito Dance.)
- You're good at the dance.
-  He is.
- He was good.
-  Good job.
Goodness.
This is the dance that Kwang Soo did in a sitcom.
- He danced this in a sitcom.
-  Right.
- All right.
-  He's a bit exhausted.
He's nervous.
- Go! Okay.
-  Good.
(Number Three fails.)
You failed to flip it.
(You failed, too.)
(Jae Seok makes a quick attack.)
Great!
(Jae Seok flips it.)
Jae Seok wins.
- Good job.
-  We have to keep the pace going.
- Number Four.
-  We shouldn't let our guard down.
Please come out.
He seems like a cheerleader.
You're like a cheerleader. Please introduce yourself.
Hello, I'm Kim Joon Hyuk, majoring in Church Music.
- What's your major again?
-  Church Music.
Church Music.
Are you good at this game?
When I was in high school, I was the best player in my town.
- Really?
-  Yes.
- I think he played this a lot.
-  Okay.
- He must be good.
-  Knock him down at once.
- You can do it.
-  Go!
- I failed.
-  You slapped too hard.
Now, the best player in Sinwol-dong will go.
- I think he'll be really good.
-  Be gentle.
(The best player in Sinwol-dong)
(He gives it a shot.)
(He also slaps it too hard and fails to flip the ddakji.)
- Jae Seok.
-  Come here.
I can see that he's a good player.
(He is really good at this game.)
He's really good.
His being the best player is proven!
- He's so good.
-  Get a hold of yourself.
- He has good power.
-  He's good.
- Wow.
-  He is superb.
He is a great player.
That's right. Jae Seok should beat at least 50 players for us.
But that won't be easy.
Okay. Go.
(Jae Seok's ddakji has left his hand.)
(Will he succeed in flipping the ddakji or not?)
(The ddakji turns but isn't flipped.)
Gosh.
I'll make sure to win this time.
Okay. I hope you don't.
- Do you have a girlfriend?
-  Yes, I do.
- Is she pretty?
-  Do you have a girlfriend?
- She's here.
-  What's her name?
- She's there.
-  Where?
- There she is.
-  Wow.
- Wow.
-  You two look alike.
- They look alike.
-  You really do.
Please say something to your boyfriend.
You can do it, Joon Hyuk.
(What a sweet couple.)
I don't think he can do it.
(Boo!)
- Jae Seok! Jae Seok!
-  Jae Seok! Jae Seok!
- We made it!
-  Great!
- You will miss it this time.
-  Oh, please.
- Your girlfriend is watching you.
-  Look at your girlfriend.
(He throws the ddakji.)
(How will the fate of Jae Seok's crisis turn out?)
(He flips Jae Seok's ddakji.)
(This is unbelievable!)
(The best player of Sinwol-dong succeeds.)
(Jae Seok fails to beat the fourth player out of 300.)
- He's really good.
-  He is.
- You did a good job.
-  You're good.
- Okay.
-  He's great.
(Now only 6 members are left.)
(Will they be able...)
(to beat the remaining 297 players?)
- Since I beat three players,
-  Yes.
now we have...
- 297 players left.
-  297 players.
There are 297 players left.
And we have six members on our team.
Those in the back rows might not be able to play games with us.
- Right.
-  Because the game will finish.
Let's find out who the next player is.
- Let's take a look.
-  I want to play at the end.
(Who will be the next player to overcome the crisis?)
It's Jong Kook.
(Shouldn't the ace go last?)
- Isn't it too early?
-  They're already scared.
- I think they are.
-  Isn't it too early?
- Already?
-  Please show us the game.
(What game will Jong Kook play with the students?)
(Arm-Wrestling)
- Yes!
-  This is great!
But there are too many players.
- Jong Kook, you can beat them.
-  There are girls, too.
- But there are too many players.
-  Okay.
Jong Kook, just beat 230 of them.
- He can do it.
-  Please beat just 230 players.
I'm sure he can do it.
(His power is beyond our imagination.)
(His power is second to none.)
(Jong Kook is a legendary, talented guy.)
(He is unbeaten in arm-wrestling.)
(How many players will he be able to beat today?)
You're seriously amazing.
- Go fast and don't waste energy.
-  He's right.
- But there are ladies as well.
-  Although...
Jong Kook is good at arm-wrestling, there are too many people to win.
- He has to save his energy.
-  Right.
- Come out.
-  Joon Hyuk will go first then.
(The best player of Sinwol-dong goes first.)
- What if he wins?
-  Now, Joon Hyuk...
will start arm-wrestling with Jong Kook.
- Beat him fast.
-  I think...
All right.
(Jong Kook starts the first round.)
- Do I have to touch the pad?
-  Yes, you do.
Get ready.
(If Jong Kook loses, Running Man will miss the chance to win.)
(A battle with the dark horse of Yonsei University)
(Who will become the winner in this first round?)
Start.
(It was a fast round.)
(Jong Kook's formidable power)
(Stunned)
Joon Hyuk's girlfriend is in great pain.
- It can't be helped.
-  You feel...
(Joon Hyuk's girlfriend is having a hard time.)
You feel the same pain as him, don't you?
- See? We're very strong.
-  Joon Hyuk disappeared so quickly.
(The dark horse loses.)
Then, it's Number Five's turn.
- She's a girl.
-  It's a female student.
(Bewildered)
You know what we're playing now.
- You have to arm-wrestle.
-  Right.
- It's just a game.
-  You still have to do it.
The women can just think that it's a chance to hold Jong Kook's hand.
(She raises her hand.)
- Gary.
-  Sorry?
- I want to hold Gary's hand.
-  Do you want to hold Gary's hand?
But you'll arm-wrestle with Jong Kook.
(You want to hold Gary's hand?)
- You have to hold mine.
-  Gosh.
I'm sorry, but...
You can do it!
Let's go!
- Now, I feel much better to play.
-  Okay.
Jong Kook just said he feels much better about beating you now.
Goodbye.
(Bye.)
(Jae Seok says goodbye in advance.)
- You did a good job.
-  You can do it.
Do you want to say anything to Jong Kook?
(What will she say to Jong Kook?)
- No.
-  Okay.
(I don't.)
(I don't have anything to say.)
- Why did you ask that to her?
-  She said no.
- She tried to bewilder Jong Kook.
-  I don't either.
Let's just start!
It's good that both of you don't have anything to say to each other.
As the main host, it's good that you said nothing.
All right. Why are you grabbing her hand so tightly already?
- No, I'm not.
-  Look at the veins in your arm.
- No, that's not true.
-  Okay.
Ready.
Start.
(Jong Kook, be gentle to the female students.)
Finish it quickly.
(No mercy!)
(I'm sorry for not being cool.)
(All the students jeer and boo.)
All right.
Chae Ryung.
(This is for choosing Gary over me.)
- He's really mad.
-  Do you have anything to say?
- This is funny.
-  I don't.
You don't?
She doesn't have anything to say.
(You know I was just kidding.)
Thank you. Let's have the next player come out.
(It's Number 7's turn now.)
- He's cute.
-  Can I...
- Sorry?
-  Can I shake hands with Ji Hyo?
- Are you Ji Hyo's fan?
-  Go ahead.
Do you have anything to say to Jong Kook?
No, I don't.
(Jong Kook is left out in the cold.)
Will you be okay?
- Let's start.
-  He wants to hold Ji Hyo's hand.
(His wish comes true.)
All right.
- Now, are you ready?
-  Yes.
(He wrings Jong Kook's hand tightly.)
We've tried that already to beat him.
- Right.
-  How does his hand feel?
- It's as hard as bricks.
-  Exactly.
- Don't expect to win.
-  How many seconds will it take?
I'll end it in one second.
- One second?
-  Are you sure?
- Of course.
-  Okay.
Get ready.
Start.
(Jong Kook wins.)
Goodness.
- You're stronger than I thought.
-  Really?
We're not weak. They're just strong.
- They're strong.
-  We've beaten seven players so far.
Jong Kook should beat as many people as he can...
- for us to win.
-  Right.
The next player, please come out.
I'm sure Jong Kook can beat a lot for us.
If you think about it,
arm-wrestling isn't an easy game for women.
I'm Kwang Soo's fan. Can I shake his hand?
Do you want to shake his hand? Kwang Soo.
(Kwang Soo gladly shakes hands with his fan.)
Why doesn't Jong Kook have any fans?
(Kwang Soo suddenly twists his fan's arm.)
(Ultimately ill-mannered)
Kwang Soo.
- What was that?
-  What is he doing?
- I twisted her arm.
-  Gosh.
- Why did you twist her arm?
-  He's not what you'd expected.
- Okay.
-  I'm sorry.
(He pretends to apologise and twists her arm again.)
(I can't believe I'm a fan of a guy like him.)
Goodness.
- You're a scum.
-  Gosh.
You're a piece of trash.
(Thumbs down)
This is how he is.
(He turns down his fan.)
(I still like you.)
- Do you still like him?
-  That's incredible.
This is not a joke.
He twisted your arm twice and you still like him?
Get ready.
(Thank you for liking me still.)
Start.
(The game starts.)
Ga Yeon.
- Bye.
-  I'm sorry.
(Jong Kook wins again.)
- Bye, Ga Yeon.
-  Bye.
He looks pretty built.
(The next player is well-built.)
- Well, then.
-  Nice to meet you.
Get ready.
- Let's move fast.
-  Sure.
Ready.
Start.
(He tries to resist.)
(Jong Kook wins.)
- What's the matter?
-  It's hard to stay still.
(He's on a different level.)
He's an incredible person.
He is, right?
Now do you see the troubles we must go through?
- It's been 6 years.
-  It's 6 years.
We've been ripped apart for six years.
(They've stuck by each other for 6 years.)
Next is Number 10.
Look at him.
(Number 10 makes his entrance.)
(He's robust.)
(He doesn't look ordinary.)
- I'll hold this.
-  You're wearing...
a very short bottom.
You look like...
somebody...
who works out a lot.
Jong Kook finally met someone on his level.
- It's Number 10.
-  Right.
- By the way,
-  Yes?
- I'm a big fan of his.
-  Is that so?
(Oh, my brother!)
(Jong Kook is deeply moved by his fan.)
I'm thankful.
I've been his fan since his Turbo days.
- Really?
-  Are you an older student?
- Are you a returning student?
-  Yes, I am.
I'm a returning student.
- I see.
-  You're older than the rest.
I can tell you're a returning student.
- You look different.
-  Don't say that.
- You have a different vibe.
-  What do you mean?
Are you on the table tennis team by any chance?
Leave him alone.
- He wore it because it's hot.
-  All right.
- Get ready.
-  You should pull your shorts down.
- After facing...
-  He looks strong.
seven people, Jong Kook met his match.
Set.
(It's a nerve-wracking moment. How will it turn out?)
Isn't that short enough to be underwear?
(Kwang Soo's dirty comment breaks the silence.)
(What's wrong with my shorts?)
- That's a warning.
-  Are those shorts?
- No, I was just curious.
-  That's a warning.
- You need to leave for a minute.
-  I'm sorry.
(He is timed-out for 1 minute.)
(We have freedom of speech in Korea.)
Do you want to wipe off your sweat?
Ready.
- Set.
-  He's good.
(This match could go either way.)
(Jong Kook vs Returning Student)
(What will be the result?)
Start.
(The game begins.)
(Jong Kook wins.)
You can't beat him.
- How's your shoulder?
-  Good job, Jong Kook.
It's too bad but goodbye.
Thank you.
- Thank you.
-  Next.
- Ready.
-  She's so cute.
Set.
(Will Jong Kook be a gentleman or pour his energy into winning?)
- You're handsome.
-  Gosh.
- Thank you.
-  Don't do that.
Set.
Start.
I'm sorry.
He finished her.
(He flashes a smile.)
(While playing against ladies,)
(he shows good manners.)
(However, when he competes against guys,)
(he turns from a nice guy...)
(to a Spartan in a split second.)
(Jong Kook continues to win consecutive matches.)
(He beats 33 people in a row!)
Next.
(Number 38 is next.)
This guy is different.
He has broad shoulders.
(He tries to intimidate Jong Kook by being restless.)
Look at him. He's fast.
- He's swift.
-  His arms are solid.
You have good pecs.
Your pecs are solid.
(He's muscular.)
I know. You look strong.
Set.
- They're getting physical.
-  You never know what will happen.
- He's glaring at him.
-  For Jong Kook,
this is Number 38.
So he has beaten around 35 people.
- Jong Kook must be tired.
-  Set.
(Jong Kook must be tired after playing 34 rounds.)
(His opponent doesn't look easy.)
(This is a moment of crisis.)
(Will Jong Kook be able to overcome this moment?)
Start.
(Shrieking)
(He goes down with a yell.)
(What was that for?)
Sorry. It's too bad.
You know...
(You would have thought he's the winner.)
I thought...
Jong Kook lost.
(Shrieking)
Thank you. Good job.
That was definitely comedy.
- He's funny.
-  That was excellent.
He's the scene stealer.
- That's right.
-  He tried to tire Jong Kook out.
Look at him.
(Number 42 is good-looking.)
(He's tall and built.)
He's handsome.
What's your major?
You look quite strong.
I'm in the Department of Physical Education.
We finally have somebody from physical education.
What do you major in?
- I'm a Track-and-Field Major.
-  They're all handsome.
- Do you do track-and-field?
-  Yes.
Track-and-field is the basic.
(His arms are muscular.)
Jong Kook lost a lot of energy.
- Since Jong Kook...
-  He arm-wrestled too many times.
arm-wrestled a lot, he's quite exhausted.
- He's exhausted.
-  This one's unpredictable.
- I'm not sure about this one.
-  Wow.
He's very handsome.
Get ready.
You never know how this will turn out.
- You can't stop here.
-  You can do it.
Set.
(Jong Kook's faced with a crisis again.)
(If he loses now, there are 258 students left to compete.)
(Will he overcome this crisis?)
Start.
Look at this. He's strong.
(Jong Kook comes out strong from the start.)
(His opponent is a fair match.)
(What will be the result?)
Look at this. He's sturdy.
Look at that. He's strong.
(It's a match of unparalleled strengths.)
(They start swaying towards Jong Kook's side.)
(Jong Kook wins.)
Oh, gosh.
(That was a close game.)
You're amazing.
- My goodness.
-  You did well.
(Jong Kook beats 38 people so far.)
Jong Kook is great but so are the students.
(There are 258 people left.)
This round could be Jong Kook's last.
Start.
(Number 43)
This one's hard. He lost a lot of energy.
Jong Kook is exhausted now.
(Jong Kook is not as fierce as he was in previous rounds.)
It's becoming too much for Jong Kook.
(Jong Kook feels pressured as the strongest member of Running Man.)
Jong Kook, you are starting...
- to get tired.
-  My arms are sore.
- It's sore.
-  Shall we continue?
There are four guys in a row.
- This person...
-  There are four in a row.
- This one looks strong.
-  He does.
You should watch out for this player.
Set.
(They grasp each other's hands.)
Get ready, Jong Kook.
Give it all you've got.
Set.
(What will be the result?)
- Start.
-  Good.
(The game starts.)
(It's a close one.)
(He clenches his teeth and pours every ounce of energy he has.)
At last,
will Jong Kook...
(At the 52nd game, he faces his biggest challenge.)
(How will this game turn out?)
After the 52nd game...
(At that moment,)
(Jong Kook's arm begins to sway.)
He's lost all of his energy.
(He lost his energy after 52 matches.)
(His opponent starts to take over.)
(Running Man still has 244 people to beat.)
(Will Jong Kook be able to flip the table?)
Jong Kook has lost all of his energy.
He's lost all of his energy.
(Jong Kook loses!)
(He lost on his 53rd match.)
(He's still incredible.)
(He must have been tired from previous missions as well.)
He's good.
(He beat 52 people in arm-wrestling.)
Good job.
Jong Kook...
was defeated by his 53rd opponent.
- That was a lot.
-  The students here...
- were great.
-  That's incredible.
Jong Kook was also incredible.
Please give them a round of applause.
(There are 244 people left.)
This one's unpredictable.
You never know what will happen.
Except for three of them up there,
Jong Kook has sent everyone else up there.
- I'm sorry.
-  Next.
That was incredible to watch.
All right, let's continue.
- Following Jong Kook,
-  Who is it?
let's see who the next person is.
I'm nervous.
(Who will it be?)
I hope it's not me. Gary?
It's Gary and Ji Hyo.
Are they playing together?
- They'll be playing...
-  It must be 2 on 2.
the Couple Game. You were right.
What game is it exactly?
Gary and Ji Hyo will form an airplane as a team.
One person will lie down and hold their partner up with their feet.
At the sound of the whistle, you must...
- bend your legs up and down.
-  I know this game.
- This one's a hard one.
-  This game?
Then we might have a bunch of people dropping out.
The person next to you is your partner.
You have to do well.
You can decide who will hold the other person up.
There are too many majoring in sports.
- You're right.
-  You can look at it this way.
There might be a lot of people dropping out in this game.
- This is good.
-  Gary has a strong will. He's good.
For the Couple Game, let's bring out Ji Hyo and Gary!
(It's Ji Hyo and Gary's turn.)
(If we were to talk about these two...)
This is the power of love.
(Having worked together for years, they have the best harmony.)
(They have mastered all couple games.)
(Ji Hyo and Gary are the best couple of Running Man.)
- We will begin now.
-  This is a conquest.
- According to my whistle,
-  Let's do this!
- stretch and fold your legs.
-  You stop when you're tired.
- It's going to be quite tough.
-  Are you all ready?
- Let's do this!
-  Here we begin.
- Cheers, everybody!
-  Let's go!
Start.
(The game begins.)
(Everyone starts flying.)
(From the start, people are screaming here and there.)
(Struggling)
- Many people are dropping out.
-  Wow.
(Go slowly.)
(10 teams are already out.)
(Lifting)
It's easier to hold them without having to move.
(They encourage each other with their eyes.)
(The screams become louder.)
A bunch of teams got eliminated again.
(He's tired, too.)
- Many teams failed.
-  Many teams are dropping out.
(After about 10 times, many couples begin to drop out.)
Slowly.
(This is my limit.)
Will they all drop out like this?
- It seems like they'll all fail.
-  I'm too tired!
(Female couple are panicking, too.)
(All of the couples except for 30 of them are down.)
- Doesn't your stomach hurt?
-  It's okay.
Gary is too strong.
- He's too good.
-  It's one of Gary's strengths.
About 50 people are remaining.
To get the result faster,
I will speed up the whistling.
(25 couples remain. The speed is increased.)
(More than 75 teams have already been eliminated.)
Gary is amazing.
Good job.
(We can do well, right?)
- A lot of couples failed.
-  This is crazy.
(The young couples are as good as Gary and Ji Hyo.)
(The whistling gets faster.)
They are a male couple and they are still going.
His legs are really strong.
If you're about to give up, let us know.
Gary is struggling, too.
Gary is struggling a lot, too. Ji Hyo is struggling as well.
- Your stomach hurts, doesn't it?
-  Yes.
What do we do?
- I'm okay.
-  Please cheer for the participants!
(The gym is filled with burning passion.)
(Cries of desperation)
We are almost there.
I hate you, Gary!
Gary!
- Stop, Gary!
-  Give up!
(Gary is everyone's enemy.)
The ones on top and the ones supporting...
- on the bottom are...
-  Number 120 is almost out.
- Number 120 is finally out.
-  Number 120 is out!
(They're like falling leaves.)
I can't believe it.
(Many couples are getting eliminated.)
- Their stomachs must hurt.
-  It's difficult.
(Throwing)
(Only 15 couples remain!)
- They are both men.
-  Seok Jin!
- They're unbelievable.
-  A male couple is still going.
- They are truly amazing.
-  Tighten your stomach.
(This is the definition of "bromance".)
Those girls are still going, too!
- Now...
-  Where?
There is a female couple that is still going.
They are both girls.
Only the tough ones are left.
The ones still surviving are unbelievable.
(Their passion is touching.)
It's hard to be on the top, too.
- Is that so?
-  Really.
It's also hard to be on top.
(Many couples reach their limit and get eliminated.)
I can't do it any more.
(He can't take it any more.)
Stop, Gary!
(They urge Gary to stop.)
Please give them a big hand!
(Yonsei University students' passion and spirit are praise-worthy!)
- They're all amazing.
-  They really are.
(Gary just looks ugly.)
Gary is about to lose it. He's almost done.
(Hold on just a little more.)
The male couple is still going.
The female couple is also still going.
Let's go!
Come on, guys!
- Come on!
-  They are amazing.
It's even tiring for me to keep blowing the whistle.
The ones who still remain are truly amazing.
- All right! This is the last part.
-  They're amazing.
Let's do just 20 more reps.
(The game will end after 20 reps.)
All the couples that manage to survive will be considered winners.
One!
(The 8 couples start the countdown!)
Two!
(Two)
- Three!
-  Three!
(Three)
- Four!
-  Four!
- Five!
-  Five!
- Six!
-  Six!
- Seven!
-  Seven!
- Eight!
-  Eight!
- Nine!
-  Nine!
- 10!
-  10! Just give up!
This is crazy.
What's this for? Stop it!
(It's strangely emotional.)
- 14!
-  They are too good.
- 15!
-  15!
- 16!
-  16!
- 17!
-  17!
- 18!
-  18!
- 19!
-  19!
(One more and it's all over.)
(Meeting for the first time, they were awkward at first.)
(But after playing the games together, they became friends.)
- 19!
-  19!
(They've completed 19 reps.)
Success!
(No teams dropped out.)
(All 8 teams succeeded.)
(We did it!)
You did it! You really did it!
- Put them down.
-  You can put them down now.
- They are exhausted.
-  They are truly amazing.
(They are proud of themselves and thankful to each other.)
They are truly amazing.
Good job. Good job.
- You can come down now.
-  Put them down.
(With their youth and fighting spirit,)
(they finished a mission that they had never done before.)
Good job.
You're done.
(At first, they came to beat each other.)
- You can come down now.
-  Good job.
- It was the best.
-  They are really amazing.
- Ji Hyo.
-  Good job.
- That was amazing.
- It was touching.
-  It really was.
All right. Gary and Ji Hyo couple...
and the last eight couples did their best.
Please give it up for them!
(182 people got eliminated and 63 people survived.)
Now,
(The competition is in the middle stage.)
Seven Running Man members...
are competing against 300 Yonsei University students.
Three Running Man members are still remaining.
Who will be the next contender? Please reveal it.
(Who is the next contender?)
It's Seok Jin.
- You can do it.
-  Be serious.
You have to do this one.
- It's nothing.
-  You're good at this.
- All right.
-  Let's go!
- Come on!
-  Let's see what the game is.
- What is it?
-  Is it rock-paper-scissors?
(What will Seok Jin play against 63 people?)
(Their hearts are beating.)
(What will Seok Jin have to play against 63 students?)
It's rock-paper-scissors.
(Tricky Rock-Paper-Scissors)
- What's Tricky Rock-Paper-Scissors?
-  You say what you'll put out.
I will say what I will give first and then play the game.
I will first say what I will give.
Whether I stick to it or not is up to me.
Seok Jin is the member who is the best at this game.
That's true.
(Seok Jin has proved to be the king of rock-paper-scissors.)
(He stood out for his brilliant ability. How will he do today?)
Number 71, please come on out.
All right.
(Number 71 takes the mound.)
Please stand here.
Can you ask him what his major is? I think it will help me.
- Industrial Engineering.
-  Industrial Engineering?
- You must be good at math.
-  We will begin now.
- Let's start it. Seok Jin?
-  Yes.
I will give scissors.
I've been playing rock-paper-scissors for a long time,
and 98 percent of the time, I give scissors.
- He's telling the truth.
-  Ready. We will start now.
You can play the game when I give the sign.
Will Seok Jin fail from the start?
Or will he continue his legacy?
Seok Jin is really good at this.
Seok Jin said he will...
- give scissors.
-  Yes.
- Okay. Here we go.
-  I will really stick to it.
What did the opponent say he'll give?
(Seok Jin's weapons are his one hand and his words.)
(Are they enough to beat 63 people?)
Rock-paper-scissors!
(What?)
(Seok Jin loses.)
(Number 71 wins on the first round.)
(No...)
(Seok Jin, this isn't right.)
He lost.
(Bye, Seok Jin.)
(Seok Jin is undeniably an unlucky man.)
- It's his first loss of the year.
-  Seok Jin.
Seok Jin, you are out.
I can't believe you lost.
- How did...
-  It's your first loss.
He said he will put out scissors. Why did you go with scissors?
If he puts out scissors, at least we could play once more.
- That's why you went with scissors.
-  Right.
Seok Jin, please go back to your place.
It's okay. We still have players.
- We still have two players.
-  Okay.
Kwang Soo and...
Haha still remain.
- Gosh.
-  We still...
don't know what will happen.
- Who's playing next?
-  Next!
- I think you'll play basketball.
-  No.
Please reveal the next player.
(Who will play next?)
- Haha.
-  It's Haha.
(It's Haha, the most mischievous player.)
He said there's something at the end.
Let's check what game they will be playing.
Please show it to us.
(Everyone is focused.)
(What's Haha's game?)
Towel Snatch.
(It's Towel Snatch.)
- Towel Snatch.
-  What's that?
(This is my game.)
You never expected this, did you?
(Haha is the king of tricks.)
(He's talented at snatching things.)
- He will be good at it.
-  We never know.
(It's 2 versus 63 now. Yonsei University is leading.)
Please cheer for the two players!
Bravo!
(Who will snatch and who will get snatched?)
If Haha loses on the first round again,
Team Running Man will be in trouble.
Seok Jin, the king of rock-paper-scissors,
lost on the first round.
He said he had a 98 percent chance of winning.
(His crushing defeat is unbelievable.)
(Will Haha be able to make up for Seok Jin's loss?)
(There is tension between them.)
(Haha wins as soon as the game begins.)
(He was helpless.)
I knew it.
(Hey, this is me.)
He's fast.
- His legs are short.
-  He's really fast.
Next.
Number 72.
- He is...
-  You did well.
Look behind you.
Let's go.
Haha has to...
(Did he just hit me?)
Haha has to win several rounds.
(Grabbing)
Okay.
(After the impressive greeting, they are ready to play.)
You two are going down too far.
- You were...
-  He did it, too!
What's the purpose of playing the game if they do that?
(He is a cheater just like Haha.)
Get ready.
(They will play a fair game.)
(Nervous)
(Number 72 wins as soon as the game starts.)
(Even Haha has failed.)
He lost.
Now...
It's too bad.
Even Haha lost.
Now,
it's too tricky.
Kwang Soo is the only one surviving.
(Kwang Soo must fight 62 people alone.)
The game Kwang Soo will play is...
(What game will Kwang Soo play against 62 people?)
Quail Egg Hit-and-Miss.
(Quail Egg Hit-and-Miss)
I know that.
(That one?)
All right. Great.
Everyone will be given an option of two eggs.
And you will only choose one.
The same goes for Kwang Soo.
On the count of three,
you will smash the egg on your forehead.
If you get the raw egg, you pass.
If you get the boiled egg, you fail.
Understood?
Yes, but I'm very pressured.
- All right!
-  I'm the last one.
Kwang Soo and everyone,
please choose a quail egg.
Oh my goodness.
(Quail Egg Hit-and-Miss begins.)
Please choose one.
Choose only one.
I'm scared.
(This game can eliminate many people at once.)
- I think I know what it is.
-  It's raw.
Please choose one.
On our forehead?
- On our forehead.
-  Okay.
(They are extremely focused.)
Take some tissues.
Now!
(It could be the last round.)
This could be the last round.
- Kwang Soo...
-  Yes.
will play Quail Egg Hit-and-Miss...
- with the remaining students.
-  Please!
He's known to be the member who doesn't have any luck.
He's the unluckiest man ever.
(He's the unluckiest member.)
Kwang Soo will now choose a quail egg.
Please choose one.
(Will there be a miracle?)
(Previously, Kwang Soo beat the odds and failed miserably.)
(Every choice he made was bad during the Unluckiest Man Special.)
- What's wrong with you?
-  Gosh.
(He's the man who is loved by raw eggs and Mr Barrel.)
(Here comes Mr Unlucky.)
- If he chooses a boiled egg.
-  If he chooses the wrong one.
- Our fate depends on...
-  Don't think too much.
That makes you unlucky.
- Just trust your instinct.
-  Just be yourself.
- Of course.
-  It will be funny either way.
Regardless of how many people pick raw eggs,
the moment Kwang Soo chooses the boiled egg,
- the game will end.
-  Yes.
Today, 7 vs 300 will end with...
Team Running Man's defeat.
- Kwang Soo.
-  Yes.
Please choose one.
Ready.
Close your eyes and choose one.
- Feel it.
-  Today...
- That's it.
-  No, you already touched it.
- You only get one chance to choose.
-  You touched it.
- He chose one.
-  It ends when he picks one.
It finally begins.
- Everyone.
-  I'm curious.
Some of you are going to smash it on each other's foreheads.
- Okay.
-  Let's go.
Don't hesitate.
You shouldn't hesitate.
One!
(One)
(Please...)
Two!
(Two)
(He is the icon of misfortune. Did he choose the raw egg?)
Please cheer for him.
(Jae Seok interrupts.)
(How dare you, Jae Seok!)
Let's do this!
(Everyone's heart is racing.)
- All right, Kwang Soo.
-  Ready.
One!
(One)
(Please let it be like how it always has been.)
Two!
(Two)
(Will he be able to beat 62 people with his misfortune?)
One, two, three!
(Here we go.)
Three!
(It breaks.)
(He got the raw quail egg.)
(It's party time!)
So we won.
- We won.
-  Kwang Soo won.
-  You won.
If you got the raw egg, please stay seated.
If you got the boiled egg, please stand up.
- Thank you.
-  Many people got eliminated.
- I knew it.
-  Kwang Soo...
- is amazing.
-  I did it!
Kwang Soo did it.
- Kwang Soo did it.
-  Just once more!
This is amazing.
There were...
two eggs, so there was a 50 percent chance.
Kwang Soo did it!
- You're amazing!
-  Bravo!
He did something really difficult.
- He did something really difficult.
-  Yes.
Now,
- the ones remaining here...
-  They are also amazing.
also chose the raw eggs.
- They are amazing people.
-  All right.
- Kwang Soo.
-  Yes.
Did you have the gut feeling?
I thought of the first round as a warm-up exercise.
Now, not too many people are surviving.
We will play the game one more time.
Please choose your quail eggs!
- They are very serious.
-  They are.
How many people are remaining?
25 people are remaining.
(If Kwang Soo chooses the boiled one, Running Man loses.)
- Don't think too much, Kwang Soo.
-  Maybe he'll choose the boiled egg.
- You may choose when they're done.
-  Okay.
Will there be...
another miracle?
- Please choose an egg.
-  Follow your gut feeling.
Don't try to do well. Please.
(Just be yourself.)
- Wow.
-  He looks cool.
He chose his.
He did it.
He chose his second quail egg.
(What will happen this time?)
One!
(One)
(Will 7 vs 300 end here?)
- Please.
-  Two!
(Two)
Please.
(The result of this game depends on Kwang Soo.)
Three!
(The egg breaks.)
(He chose the raw egg once again.)
(They won't lose to him.)
(Yes!)
He's amazing.
Kwang Soo is amazing.
Those who survived are also amazing.
(Many people failed.)
- Now...
-  The egg flew to the back.
- Go, Kwang Soo!
-  I can't do this.
- It flew to the back.
-  You did it.
(He's proud.)
Half of you got eliminated.
14 people remain.
Kwang Soo,
you did it again. Was it expected?
Well, I just did it...
like I always do.
- Yes.
-  Okay.
You thought it was no big deal.
Actually, the ones surviving here...
are very unlucky. It's not easy to choose raw eggs twice in a row.
That's really unlucky.
We will begin the third round.
The students have all picked their eggs.
Now, it's the third round.
All right, Kwang Soo.
If you do it again, I will acknowledge you.
If he succeeds again...
He's already done great so far.
- Even two in a row is hard.
-  It's hard to get.
It's really difficult for Kwang Soo...
- even though he's really unlucky.
-  That's right.
- I'll do this comfortably.
-  Okay.
Five, four, three, two, one.
- That's it.
-  He made a different choice.
- He went from left to right.
-  That one looks good.
One!
(What will be the result of his choice?)
Two!
Kwang Soo.
Go, Kwang Soo.
Please be quiet.
- Look.
-  He's really sensitive.
- I'm trying to focus.
-  He's really sensitive right now.
I'm sorry. I feel really nervous right now.
(Please keep quiet during the match.)
(This is the turning point of the game.)
(There's a 1 out of 8 chance. Can Kwang Soo make it?)
Two!
(There were 300 opponents, but now only 14 remain.)
Three!
(Crushing)
(The raw quail egg returns.)
(It's not easy to pick the raw egg 3 times in a row.)
(But it's nothing special to unlucky Kwang Soo.)
(Kwang Soo is unlucky, and unlucky is the word to describe Kwang Soo.)
- That's amazing.
-  It's unbelievable.
(Everyone, cheer for Kwang Soo!)
- This is...
-  Wow.
(He beat the small chance of 1 out of 8.)
No way.
This is amazing.
(His skills give you goosebumps.)
There are only a few people left.
We have been close friends for several years now.
But I'm really surprised.
Kwang Soo is amazing. But at the same time, all the survivors...
out here are amazing, too.
Now, there are only seven survivors left.
- Number 72 is really great.
-  He really is.
He survived since he played against Gary and Ji Hyo.
- He is really amazing.
-  He's the real survivor.
- He's incredible.
-  All right.
- Let's continue.
-  What are the odds now?
All right.
Please choose your eggs.
I think about two people will survive this time.
If Kwang Soo is the only one to break the raw egg...
- and survive, it'll be amazing.
-  Kwang Soo will choose his egg.
(It's more like an occult show now.)
Please choose your egg for this round.
- My goodness.
-  Do it, Kwang Soo.
- You're amazing.
-  We can win this.
Don't think for too long. Your initial choice must be right.
(Kwang Soo chooses the egg on the left this time.)
- Now...
-  He's really serious about this.
I'll count to three. Is everyone ready?
One!
(One!)
- Two!
-  It must be the raw egg.
(There are only 7 survivors and the chance is 1 out of 16.)
You'll make it.
You're amazing already.
Three!
(Please...)
(Coming soon)
(It isn't over until it's over.)
Is it up there?
(Mysterious hunters have come with the darkness.)
What's going on? Oh, gosh.
What is that?
(The final mission of the 300th episode special will begin shortly.)
Three!
(Please...)
(Hitting)
(He got the boiled egg this time.)
This must be the raw egg.
Wait. Among all of you,
did anyone get the raw egg?
(Is there anyone who got the raw egg?)
(If there's none, Kwang Soo will have a rematch against them.)
- Is there one?
-  Two?
(2 students survived.)
So it turns out that...
the Team 300 from Yonsei University has won!
(The final result: Team 300 from Yonsei University wins)
- Only two survivors were left.
-  It was really close.
- It was really amazing.
-  It was so close.
- Yes, it was close.
-  If we had more luck...
- If Kwang Soo picked the raw egg...
-  If Kwang Soo had passed,
- then he could play...
-  For the last time.
- once more against two students.
-  It was so close.
Please applaud for everyone who participated and did their best!
(We thank the 300 students who did their best.)
You did well. Good job.
- Well done.
-  It was a good game.
- Thank you.
-  It was a nice game.
Today, we'd like to show our gratitude for your warm welcome...
and for spending time with us until this late.
We're really grateful. Thank you, everyone!
(Thank you once again.)
Akaraka!
(But no one was aware of what awaited them.)
(After the long mission, they are headed somewhere.)
- I'm starving.
-  I feel hungry, too.
(It's too late even for a night-time supper. Where are they heading now?)
(They're somewhere in Gyeonggi-do, far away from Seoul.)
- Where are we?
-  It's scary.
Goodness. How far are we travelling?
We're deep in the heart of the mountains. What will we do here?
(Only the Running Man members' car is moving in the mountains.)
(They drive through rough and narrow roads to get there.)
How far are we going? I guess we just arrived.
(V Pension in Yangpyeong.)
This pension seems...
eerie.
That's for pillow fights.
We'll be pillow fighting here.
(Will they pillow fight in the heart of the mountains?)
(What will happen here?)
- You've played well so far.
-  Hello.
Behind you,
- we've prepared some ramyeon.
-  Oh, yes!
(You worked hard, so eat harder.)
Ramyeon is a perfect snack right now.
- Right now.
-  While we boil the water,
you will play a simple pillow fight.
We will rank you according to the result of this game.
And you will receive a bonus for the final mission...
according to your ranks.
- There's something.
-  There must be something.
You'll find out after watching the introduction video.
(Pillow Fight Tournament Table)
You must do your best for this.
- Ji Hyo can't win this match.
-  I think she'll lose immediately.
Ji Hyo, don't think you can't make this fight.
He probably can't use his right arm because of arm wrestling.
- Ji Hyo, you can do this.
-  Ready,
set, go.
(Ji Hyo versus Jong Kook)
- Go.
-  Ji Hyo, smash him.
(Okay, I'll give it a try.)
(Take this.)
(Smashing)
- He's serious.
-  That was harsh.
- My gosh.
-  Jong Kook is merciless.
- Jong Kook.
-  That was really harsh.
- Calm down, Ji Hyo.
-  Jong Kook is a man.
Jong Kook.
- He changed his concept.
-  Did that hurt?
- He's a better guy now.
-  He's nice.
- I'm sorry, Ji Hyo.
-  It's a match between Haha and me.
Viewer discretion is advised for the children and elderly.
- You're fine with this, aren't you?
-  Of course, I am.
You're both dirty fighters.
Why don't you hit each other once, first?
- Hit each other once.
-  Let's go.
- Go ahead.
-  I don't have any hard feelings.
- Of course.
-  Hit each other.
- I'll hit first.
-  Okay.
(Whacking)
Your face got stiff, Jae Seok.
- Don't get mad.
-  I'm totally fine.
- My turn?
-  Yes.
(What? Did you dodge?)
(Didn't we agree to hit each other once?)
(Look at the mess they're in.)
He's always a betrayer.
- That's right.
-  I saw that coming.
(You're so deceitful.)
(Jae Seok unleashes his fury.)
(Heavy smashing)
(Goodness. What are they doing?)
Hey, you shouldn't...
I can't defend it. I can't.
Isn't there a player protection policy?
Why are you two hitting that spot?
Protect the players.
The second...
(Jackpot)
- Why are they...
-  He fell down.
Why are you two so serious?
- He hit the exact spot.
-  Haha won.
That nasty Haha.
(The 3rd match: Jong Kook versus Haha)
- My left arm hurts, too.
-  I'm lucky. I will be in fourth.
- I secured the fourth spot.
-  That sounds nice.
Ready, set, go.
You arm-wrestled against 50 people. You can't use your arm.
(He makes a full swing.)
Was it that arm?
(Don't cheat when you play, little kid.)
(Haha gets thrown onto the ground.)
(You deserve it, Haha.)
- It's over.
-  Gosh.
(Jong Kook wins.)
This is the grand final between Jong Kook and Kwang Soo.
(The final round: Jong Kook vs Kwang Soo)
Where are my glasses?
Hey, Jong Kook. He's really strong.
- Yes and he has long arms.
-  He hits really well with his arms.
It's the final round.
I'm looking forward to this.
I can't guess the result.
Ready, start.
- Come on, don't give me that look.
-  What's the problem?
Kwang Soo...
has long arms, so he can reach further.
(Kwang Soo boldly hits first, and they exchange hits right after.)
(Kwang Soo fights head-on against Jong Kook.)
(I'm different now.)
(Smashing)
(He's stunned.)
(Jackpot)
(He's shocked and horrified.)
Wait. Wait. Please wait, I was really shocked.
Hold on. Did you put something in your pillow?
I was hit so hard. I'm really shocked.
- His pillow must be different.
-  Give me a second.
This is funny.
(Focus, Kwang Soo.)
(He fails to hit and fails to defend.)
Hey, Kwang Soo. Did your neck shrink?
You look like a mole right now.
You can't block anything.
(He was so full of confidence just a while back.)
He's helpless.
(He tries to hold on but fails.)
- Gosh!
-  What was that?
What just happened?
Can you blur this part out?
Does this even make sense?
- Kwang Soo.
-  My legs are shaking.
You should have stopped him earlier.
- This is impossible.
-  Gosh.
-  I saw it.
Jong Kook is the winner.
This isn't fun at all.
- It was as expected.
-  My goodness.
- Let's eat.
-  Go on and eat.
I love ramyeon.
Thank you for the food.
Thank you for the food. Enjoy your meal.
Enjoy your meal.
(Slurping)
(Gulping down)
(Ramyeon and kimchi are perfect together.)
- Thank you.
-  There's a lot.
(It tastes even better after doing physical activities.)
(By the way, are we allowed to be this happy?)
This is so tasty.
(After having dinner,)
(they are assigned rooms according to the results of the pillow fight.)
(They're all alone.)
(What's here?)
There are name tags.
(They weren't given any explanations about this.)
(Haha)
(They head to bed feeling anxious.)
I'm exhausted.
(The night has come.)
(Everything...)
(is hushed...)
(in darkness.)
(A siren breaks the silence.)
What's this?
What is that?
Hello?
What's this?
(What's going on?)
Here's your last mission.
(This is your last mission.)
The last 7 vs 300 mission...
(Here's the ultimate 7 vs 300 mission.)
Is "300kg".
"300kg"?
(This is the mission that will conclude the 300th episode.)
You must find a scale with your name on it...
- and escape the cabin.
-  Who is it?
The escape van can carry up to 300kg,
and those who cannot get on the van...
must walk to Yangpyeong Station on foot.
(Who will be left behind?)
(The game has started.)
I have to find the scale and weigh myself first?
Where could it be?
(They must first find the scale with their names on it.)
Where's the scale?
Do I just go around?
No hints?
It's so eerie here.
Oh, gosh.
Where could it be?
(He's scared and clueless.)
(He spots something!)
What's that?
Who is it?
(Who is it?)
What's that?
Run!
(Somebody is after us.)
(He runs for his life.)
What was that?
What's with the bell?
- What's that? What's after him?
-  My goodness!
- What is it?
-  Oh, dear!
(A stranger with a bell is chasing them.)
Why here?
Why are you coming this way?
Leave me alone.
(Jae Seok gets caught but he has no idea why.)
Please, let me go.
(Ripping)
(The stranger rips his name tag off!)
(What?)
(Is this a sand bag?)
The escape van can carry up to 300kg.
(This is a huge penalty for him.)
- Seok Jin.
-  Yes?
- 58?
-  Who was chasing you?
There were these two guys in black.
- That's no joke.
-  They had bells on them.
- They went that way.
-  Did you see them?
I was tying my shoelaces then ran away because I was scared.
Why are they hunting us down?
Only about four of us can escape here.
How much do you weigh?
- Why do you ask?
-  Is it 53kg?
It's important that we know.
300kg is the maximum it can hold.
How much do you weigh?
- I weight 76kg.
-  76kg?
- What about you?
-  I weight 67kg or 68kg.
I weigh 70kg. We're 70kg on average.
She probably weighs 50kg.
- I weight a little more than that.
-  Do you?
- What are we supposed to do?
-  This doesn't work out.
Hey, are we supposed to go about...
- without any hints?
-  No, actually.
Seok Jin, remember it said the "finish line"?
(There was something that referred to the "finish line".)
- Are these puzzle pieces?
-  There are writings on it.
This is the most important hint for the ultimate mission.
- It's a map.
-  It's a puzzle.
- It says "finish" something.
-  A finish line?
- All right.
-  Where is this?
- It's working out.
-  It's complete.
We can see all the important spots.
It must be spread out. There are many houses.
We have to go near the houses.
What if we can't...
find the scales by dawn?
We have to check how much we weigh.
What's this?
Haha, whose name is on it?
Look.
(They find a scale!)
It's wrapped.
Whose is it?
(It's useless if it's someone else's scale.)
This is how it looks like.
I hope it's yours.
Yours or mine, right?
It's Jong Kook's.
(This scale belongs to Jong Kook.)
I had a feeling.
(They can't take someone else's scale.)
(Where's my scale?)
This is hard.
- Gosh.
-  Goodness.
We have to be thorough.
I don't know what I'm supposed to do.
Jae Seok, how many times did you get caught?
(How many times did he get caught?)
- Hey.
-  Three times?
- Three times.
-  Do you get one sand bag each time?
- Do you want one?
-  Where's the scale?
(Jae Seok, come on now.)
(They wish they had all the puzzle pieces.)
It's not there. I already checked.
- It's not here, right?
-  No.
(Peeking)
(Goodness!)
(He finds a scale!)
It's not here.
(He hides it behind the curtain.)
I have a feeling it's somewhere here.
I have a hunch, too.
Let's head out.
(Let's go out.)
It's not here. Let's head out.
Why?
Why are you telling me to leave?
- You saw something, right?
-  You did.
(They suspect him.)
No, I don't think there's anything here.
- Tell me the truth. What was it?
-  Tell us the truth.
- What?
-  You saw it, right?
(He acts very awkward.)
- Hold on.
-  Look at this guy.
- Kwang Soo.
-  Come on.
- You saw something, right?
-  I am wondering.
I am asking this only because I don't get it.
How did you know?
I only said, "Let's go out."
- You said it all of a sudden.
-  He saw it.
- He saw it.
-  You did.
Whose was it? Was it one of ours?
It's mine, right?
If it's his, I'll leave.
(Should I tell them where it is?)
Let's just leave.
(He won't tell them.)
Where did you see it?
(Goodness!)
Here it is.
I didn't see it.
- I didn't open it yet.
-  Whose is it?
I only saw the box but I didn't see whose it is.
(Whom does this scale belong to?)
- It's you.
-  It's really Jae Seok's.
Why?
Kwang Soo, you can't do anything about it.
Why were you being so obvious?
I was going to look for it, anyway.
(Jae Seok locates his scale thanks to Kwang Soo!)
(Meanwhile, Gary is looking on his own.)
(He spots something!)
(He finds it!)
All right.
(Please, let it be mine!)
(Is it really...)
(It's Gary's.)
(Gary finds his scale.)
(He has to take it to the finish line and weigh himself.)
Isn't it suspicious that a lot of people are gathered down there?
(They try to remember the puzzle.)
Which way do I go down?
(They sprint down the mountain.)
(The maximum weight it can hold is 300kg.)
There it is.
Nobody's here yet.
There's the van.
I get to escape.
(Only a total of 300kg can ride the van.)
I'm good.
(Jae Seok is the first one to weigh himself.)
(He's 72.9kg in total with the bag and the sand bags.)
Hurry up!
(Gary follows shortly.)
Hey, Gary.
(Are you here now?)
You have three bags on you.
You don't have time for a break.
I went up by 10kg.
79.3kg.
(He's 79.3kg with the bag, camera and sand bags.)
Do I get on?
Gary, come in.
(Jae Seok and Gary are 152.2kg in total.)
This is scary. What's here?
Oh, hey!
(The remaining members start to catch up.)
It's mine.
(There's only 147.8kg of room left.)
Is it yours? Are you serious?
I found it!
(Who will be able to escape?)
- Who is it?
-  Somebody's here.
I feel so light.
Is it 152.2kg so far?
Are you carrying anything?
No, I'm carrying nothing.
Then we can probably squeeze in four people.
How did you not get caught?
- Then...
-  Should I take this off?
If I put this bag on, there's only enough room for Ji Hyo.
(Kwang Soo tries to unload himself and help the next person.)
Should I take this off?
Then why won't you take your pants off as well?
- Why would I do that?
-  You'll be lighter.
- That's too much.
-  You wanted to help the next one.
It's not like I want to help them. I'm just opening up possibilities.
He's tall.
(He passes with 78.6kg.)
- How much?
-  I'm 78.6kg.
That's close.
- How much is it in total?
-  It's 230kg.
- What?
-  It's a little over 230kg.
It's 230kg? Who's that?
- It's Haha.
-  What's going on?
You might make it.
You have to be at most 69.2kg.
- Hurry up and weigh yourself.
-  69.2kg?
- Yes.
-  Goodness.
Can you make it?
(He starts to take his clothes off.)
(Every gram counts.)
Take your microphone off.
Oh my goodness.
You won't be able to do it if Ji Hyo arrives here. Hurry up.
(He takes his bag, microphone and even pants off.)
It's 70.4kg. 70.4kg.
Then it exceeds 300kg, right?
(He exceeds the limit by 0.6kg.)
- It's 70.4kg.
-  Don't film me!
How many kilogrammes does he have to take off?
Ji Hyo is here!
(Ji Hyo shows up.)
- It's 69 point...
-  69 and what?
It's 69...
- Stay still. The number will stop.
-  Make it exact.
It was 63kg.
- It's 70kg.
-  Good. It's 69kg.
(Will Haha be able to lose 0.6kg?)
- What's wrong with your feet?
-  It's 70.4kg.
- It's 70.4kg.
-  Hold on a second.
- Should I?
-  What are you going to do?
It was really close.
It's because of this sand bag.
- It doesn't go down below 70.4kg.
-  This is the problem.
- It's Ji Hyo's turn.
-  Okay.
- Did you find it?
-  You won't pass, Jong Kook.
- Jong Kook has four sand bags.
-  Gosh.
Why do you not have many sand bags like me?
Do you still need more chances? Did you take your necklace off?
I already regret that I took all my clothes off.
It wasn't going to work anyways.
- Get away from me.
-  I think Ji Hyo won't make it.
- Jong Kook, get ready.
-  Why?
- Ji Hyo is too heavy.
-  Really?
Then...
(Ji Hyo weighs 53.4kg.)
She weighs 53.4kg. You've definitely passed.
All right. Everyone, let's get going.
Haha, you were so close.
Jae Seok should've taken his bag off.
I also carried my bag.
- We didn't know it'd go like this.
-  Right.
You are so selfish.
- We'll leave then.
-  We'll be leaving now!
- Goodbye.
-  Be careful, it will rain.
What should we do now?
We have no more chances left.
It was a long day.
- It was a long day.
-  I am exhausted.
(It was a long journey.)
(Way to Seoul)
As always, the finale is up to us.
- Let's go.
-  Let's think we're exercising.
- Okay. Let's walk for our health.
-  Let's go.
I can walk for now, but...
- it's 8km, right?
-  It's not bad. It won't take long.
That means I have to walk a 100m-road 80 times.
Seok Jin, it won't take that long.
But it's good that we're together. It would've been scary to be alone.
Gosh, it's too dark.
(Thank you for loving Running Man. We'll keep doing our best.)
(You've been racing hard so far. You may rest!)
- I've been on vacation.
-  Me, too.
What does Dangerous Meal mean?
- There's a lot. Hey!
-  Gosh!
- Watch out.
-  Let's catch them.
Stop there!
(Dangerous Meal and some dangerous individuals threaten Running Man.)
- Jae Seok!
-  I think I got a big one.
(The most dangerous trip in Running Man's history)
Why are you crying?
(A special guest, Yeo Jin Goo)
(TWICE)
I think I was set up...
- by them.
-  This is scary.
What should I do?
- This is no joke.
-  I'm sorry.
Be careful!
(Dangerous Meal)