The election campaigns began.
The election campaigns have begun.
I will make a vote.
(In the history of election,)
(this rule was widely accepted.)
(Majority rule)
(Unanimity)
(Is the majority's decision always right?)
("Unanimity is dangerous.")
("Death penalty consented unanimously is invalid" by Talmud)
("Minority's opinions impact the future" by Douglas)
(A timely project during the election)
(Election rules are reversed.)
(Avoid unanimity!)
I save you all!
(Or the winner takes it all.)
(Majority Rule, Dangerous Unanimity Race)
(And)
(Amazing supporters who will determine the result)
(Park Bo Gum)
(Seolhyun)
(Yoo Yun Seok)
(Seohyun)
(Who will they support?)
(The day before the shooting, Mapo-gu)
(Ding-dong)
(Beep)
(What is it?)
(Are they giving me a mission this early in the morning?)
(Goodness.)
"Majority Rule,"
"Dangerous Unanimity Race".
(Meanwhile, in Anyang, Gyeonggi-do)
(The door opens.)
(Jong Kook looks casual.)
Why... Why are you here? Hold on.
(It's not even the shooting day. Why are they here?)
What is this?
"Majority Rule, Dangerous Unanimity Race".
Hello.
How could you give me a mission so early in the morning?
(What?)
What is this? "Majority Rule,"
"Dangerous Unanimity Race".
What is this?
(They all received the mission.)
"Please vote for the time to shoot Running Man."
"We will shoot at the time with the most votes."
"If the result is unanimous, we'll start shooting at 7am."
If the result is unanimous, we'll start at 7am?
Let me think.
(An inner conflict)
Starting at 7am is too harsh.
This is really making me think.
I'll vote for 9am.
(9am)
No, I'll vote for 1pm.
(9am versus 1pm)
Why is it so hard to decide?
(Their decisions will affect the whole staff.)
If it's decided by the majority, it'll definitely be 1pm.
(He knows exactly what everyone's thinking.)
(The members would prefer 1pm.)
I actually prefer 1pm.
I really do.
(She wants to take enough rest.)
I'd like to work out in the morning and take my time to go to work.
So I'll vote for 1pm.
(I'll vote for 1pm.)
(Voting)
(Jong Kook voted for 1pm.)
I'll...
(Gary voted for 1pm.)
I'll vote for 1pm.
(Kwang Soo and Haha are done voting as well.)
They won't all choose 1pm, will they?
Right? They won't all choose 1pm, right?
No way. Can I change my decision?
I think they all voted for 1pm.
I didn't think about it before.
(Unanimous vote means they'll start at 7am.)
I have a feeling that they all voted for 1pm.
(9am versus 1pm versus 7am When will they start shooting?)
(The day of shooting)
Hi.
- What?
-  It was only one person.
- Gosh.
-  I knew it.
Hello.
- Hello.
-  Hello.
(It's hard to tell what time it is.)
Good morning.
I love starting work at 9am.
- I love start shooting at 9am.
-  I love start shooting at 9am.
We managed to start at 9am.
(Is it 9am?)
(Although he wanted to start work at 1pm,)
(he was afraid everyone else would vote for 1pm, too.)
(In order to avoid unanimity, he chose 9am.)
I voted for 9am.
(Jae Seok voted for 9am to avoid unanimity.)
Everyone will vote for 1pm.
(He was certain.)
(Voting)
Okay. I voted for 9am.
I should prevent unanimity.
I'll vote for 9am.
(Kwang Soo voted for 9am.)
I actually prefer 1pm.
I'll vote for 9am.
(Ji Hyo also voted for 9am to prevent unanimity.)
It's not for me, but for the other members.
Gary, Seok Jin and Jong Kook voted for 1pm.
I thought Ji Hyo would be one of them.
- So did I.
-  If it's decided by majority,
- I thought it would be 1pm.
-  So did I.
Jong Kook scolded me for voting for 9am.
I was scolded, too.
Isn't voting supposed to be anonymous?
- It should've been anonymous.
-  How could you do that?
People living outside of Seoul...
- want to avoid rush hour.
-  Excuse me.
- Right.
-  You go to Gangnam to exercise.
- That's right.
-  That's true.
He shouldn't scold us.
Today's race is called...
"Majority Rule, Dangerous Unanimity Race".
"Dangerous Unanimity"?
- Is unanimity a bad thing?
-  Yes.
When you're unanimous,
- there will be consequences.
-  Oh, no.
In case of threats or collusion...
There's only one person you should warn.
Don't do that.
You can whisper it to him.
Yesterday, he called...
Kwang Soo and Haha.
He scolded them.
They shouldn't have been scolded.
They were scolded for voting for 9am.
He said such harsh things to me.
- He did that to me, too.
-  By the way,
I'm sorry to change the subject, but...
why did you go to the "Descendants of the Sun" team dinner?
- Did he?
-  Really?
- Were you that jealous?
-  I was invited.
Were you that jealous?
- I appeared in that drama!
-  Why did you go there?
- Kwang Soo, why did you go there?
-  I appeared in that drama.
- You're obsessed.
-  Didn't you see me in that drama?
Kwang Soo, don't do that again.
- Don't do that.
-  You shouldn't be there.
What did I do so wrong?
Let go of Joong Ki now.
Song Joong Ki!
(He is in rage.)
(A downside of having a celebrity friend)
First of all, you'll select your outfits by voting.
Go into the booth and change into an outfit you like.
The outfit with the most votes will be your outfit today.
- Really?
-  I see.
- You're not playing tricks, right?
-  No, we're not.
Keep an eye on Jong Kook.
He'll say, "Why did you choose that outfit?"
Stop it.
(Jong Kook's upset.)
We just have to choose what we like.
- Don't send each other signs.
-  Seriously.
- Wait.
-  What is this?
(Wait.)
What is this?
- It smells!
-  Are you kidding us?
(Complaining)
- This is not okay!
-  You can't do this!
Hey, come here!
What is this?
See what you have done to me.
This is what you have done to me.
Do we have to wear that if we're unanimous?
(Why are they so furious?)
This is crazy.
(What are the two outfits they have to choose between?)
These outfits make me think.
Choose the outfit you'd like to wear.
If you're unanimous, you'll have to wear the outfit to your right.
- I see!
-  Okay!
This is so complicated.
(Hesitating)
Goodness.
(They don't want to be unanimous.)
- Are you ready?
-  Yes.
This is insane.
One, two, three.
(The result)
(Haha chose the normal outfit.)
(Gary chose the normal outfit.)
(Jong Kook chose the normal outfit.)
(Jae Seok chose the embarrassing outfit.)
Are we unanimous?
(What's the result?)
(4 chose the embarrassing outfits and 3 chose the normal ones.)
If I had chosen that one, we'd be wearing them.
- I almost chose that one.
-  So did I.
-  I wanted to prevent unanimity.
- That's what I thought.
-  That's what I thought, too.
Why doesn't mine have letters on it?
- Does it have a picture?
-  How does it look?
(Jong Kook's doesn't have any letters on it?)
I'm going to kill you all!
How about you, Gary?
- How does it look?
-  I'm going to kill you all.
-  Why?
- It's worse than mine.
-  Don't do that.
- Don't come in.
-  That's worse than mine.
"I'm a friend of Song Joong Ki."
Song Joong Ki!
Look at mine.
(I'm uglier than Gary.)
This is not true.
(Jong Kook has changed into his embarrassing outfit.)
Goodness.
- My goodness.
-  That's gross.
It was during a concert.
Why does mine have a picture?
You do awful things at your concert.
What is that?
- Why did you do this?
-  Look at that arm.
(We all wish we didn't have to see this.)
- You look like Park Se Ri.
-  What is this?
What is this?
(A t-shirt that says, "I am ugly.")
I'm sad.
Gary.
- You look great.
-  It stinks.
It's stressing me out.
This is too much.
Do you like your outfits?
I love Seok Jin's.
- You're the only one who likes it.
-  This is true.
(They're embarrassed by their outfits.)
(They chose the embarrassing outfits by majority.)
Today, you'll select your leader by majority.
The leader will have power over...
the other members for an hour.
There will be three elections and you can serve consecutive terms.
The leader will also be given two Go-Home Badges.
You can...
have one for yourself...
and give the other to a member you want to take with you.
As we'll have 3 elections, 6 badges will be given in total.
That means one of you won't receive a badge.
We found an abandoned amusement park next to a cemetery.
(An abandoned amusement park next to a cemetery)
(An abandoned amusement park?)
The one without a badge will go there as a penalty...
and will have to succeed in a mission in order to go home.
What?
(The loser will be penalised.)
However, that person can...
choose one member to bring along to the amusement park.
(The loser can bring along 1 of the 6 members who went home.)
I'm curious about one thing.
- So one of us has to go there?
-  Yes.
- It's 2 people.
-  It's 2.
- The person can take another.
-  Another person is taken along.
Can't I refuse? Do I need to go if I'm chosen?
You must go.
(The chosen has to go.)
(The night was filled with screams last summer.)
(The abandoned school has only given them traumatising memories.)
(Are you telling us to go through that again?)
(Welcome to a place filled with dreams and hopes.)
The first mission to elect the leader will be called...
Find Your Supporter.
What did you say?
Please pick a mission each.
After you complete the mission with the person written on your paper,
the two people that arrive first at the next location...
will be given the chance to run for election.
(The first mission is Find Your Supporter.)
(The members each get a mission that they need to complete.)
(The first 2 to complete their missions will become candidates.)
(Find Your Supporter)
I need to get a stamp...
from a celebrity that has a 12-year age gap from me.
(Grant a wish made by a celebrity in that age gap.)
Please don't get me wrong. Last time I was paired with...
Kim Won Hae who is 12 years older than me.
But today, I will meet someone...
who is 12 years younger than me.
Am I going to meet Park Bo Gum today?
Oh, my. What if Bo Gum comes?
Oh, my goodness.
(Bo Gum, I hope we meet today.)
(She needs to get his number.)
I'm leaving.
(Grant a wish made by a beautiful ambassador for general election.)
Are you going to see Seolhyun?
Yes!
(He quickly got a hold of Seolhyun's manager.)
I got her manager's number.
I couldn't get Seolhyun's.
- Hello?
-  Hello?
Yes?
- Are you Seolhyun's manager?
-  Yes.
- Hello.
-  Hello.
I need to meet Seolhyun because of a mission.
Are you with her at the moment?
Yes, please wait a minute.
I think she's fetching her.
(Will he be able to talk to her?)
(Gary was in love with Seolhyun the moment he met her.)
Stop filming me. Don't do that.
My heart is racing.
(Will he be able to meet Seolhyun once again?)
Hello?
- Is this Seolhyun?
-  Yes.
(His heart is racing.)
- Is this Seolhyun?
-  Yes.
(It's Seolhyun!)
Hello, Seolhyun.
Hello, Gary.
- I know you're busy.
-  Yes?
But I need to meet you because of a mission.
Could you please spare some time for me?
Sure, of course.
Wait just a little.
How long will it take you to arrive?
- I'll be there in 30 minutes.
-  Okay.
I'll drive at the speed of 200km per hour.
(I'll race against time for you.)
No, please drive safely.
All right.
- Okay.
-  Bye.
Oh, no. I really don't know anyone who was born in 1997.
(Grant a wish of a celebrity who's voting for the first time.)
Let's see who was born in 1997.
There's Kwak Dong Yeon.
Kwak Dong Yeon, who performed...
in a drama with me recently, was born in 1997.
I didn't know that he was born in 1997.
(He calls him immediately to carry out the mission.)
- Hello?
-  Hello, Dong Yeon.
- Hello, Kwang Soo.
-  Where are you?
I'm on my way to Everland Amusement Park.
- Ever... Oh, really?
-  Yes.
Why are you going there?
To... To hang out.
- I see. You're hanging out there.
-  Yes.
All right.
(Sighing)
He's going to the amusement park.
(He went to the amusement park.)
I used to go to the amusement park often when I was in my 20s.
(He reminisces.)
How are you?
(We'll say that he was just saying hello to the tigers at the zoo.)
I just searched right now and found Jaekyung.
Jaekyung of Rainbow was...
a student representative back in high school.
Look.
She was a student representative at Deungchon High School.
BoA was also a representative at Yangjeong Elementary School.
How can I meet Jaekyung?
- Kwang Soo.
-  Yes, Haha?
Do you have Jaekyung's phone number?
- Jaekyung?
-  Yes.
- Of Rainbow.
-  I don't have her number.
Do you know Yoo Yun Seok?
- I know Yun Seok.
-  Do you?
- Yes.
-  Give me his number now.
I know Yu Seung Woo's number. That works, right?
- Here you go. 010...
-  Okay.
And 7148.
You need to tell me his number, too.
- I'll call him.
-  What?
- To see if it's the right number.
-  It's the right number!
- Quickly. I don't have the time.
-  Wait.
- I'm calling the number.
-  You can do that later.
- Call him later.
-  He's not picking up.
It's because you're calling from an unknown number.
Trust me.
He's not picking up. You look like you're lying.
Text him first. Introduce yourself.
- You're driving me crazy.
-  You're lying.
- This isn't his, right? Hello?
-  Yes?
- Seung Woo?
(Yes?)
- Hello, I'm Lee Kwang Soo.
-  I told you.
He picked up.
Talk to him later.
Hang up first.
It's the right number. Hey!
(Kwang Soo runs away at full speed.)
- Seung Woo!
-  Are you a scammer?
Hello, I'm Lee Kwang Soo.
- Hello.
-  Hello.
Excuse me, but where are you at the moment?
(Only 2 can become the candidates.)
- You're at home?
-  Yes.
- By any chance,
-  Yes?
if you're free today, could you spare 10 minutes to complete...
a mission? Do you have time?
Yes, I do.
Thank you.
- You're welcome.
-  Where do you live?
- I live in Seocho-gu.
-  Seocho-gu, I see.
I'll call you when I arrive.
- Okay.
-  Thank you.
Isn't the mission too difficult?
(Jae Seok is near Ewha Women's University.)
I need to find a person who is very flexible.
If we go too much forward...
(Find a student who can wrap their arm around their waist.)
She's on her way to school.
Watch out.
(He found a university student.)
Excuse me, are you on your way to school?
Are you...
(Jae Seok is in front of me.)
Excuse me. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for disturbing your morning.
I'm sorry, you must be tired.
Could I ask you for a favour?
Do you know that pose where you wrap your arm around your waist?
- Sorry?
-  It's popular these days.
Wrap your arm around your waist and touch your belly button. I can't.
I don't think I can.
- Right? Wait, can you?
-  Maybe if I reach under my clothes.
(She slides her arm behind her.)
Didn't you succeed?
She did it.
(She succeeded in no time.)
You succeeded in one go.
(She looks calm for someone who has won a mission.)
Oh, my. How could you do that?
(She does it again as if it's nothing.)
(Even her "Wow!" sounds dull.)
This is really amazing.
Were you on your way to class?
- I'm going to buy coffee.
-  Coffee?
Oh, my.
- You should buy her coffee.
-  I was about to do just that.
Shall we go buy a cup of coffee?
It's all right.
(She immediately refuses.)
She says it's fine.
Gosh.
Thank you.
Please take care.
- Goodbye.
-  Goodbye.
- Good luck.
What should I do now?
You should go to the next location.
- Congratulations.
-  That was fast.
Is it possible to complete the mission that fast?
(It didn't work when I tried it. What will I do to fill up the time?)
(Tongin Market)
Oh, my.
I'm at Tongin Market.
What should I eat? Should I eat soondubu?
(Go to a traditional market and make them say, "Wow, you eat well!")
Look at those dumplings. Wow.
(Diverse dishes are lined up in this traditional market.)
They look delicious.
There's an old lady.
An old lady will probably say those words easily.
Hello.
- Soy sauce and oil tteokbokki.
-  Yes.
I heard that they're really tasty here.
This must be oil tteokbokki. I'll have a serving.
(Oil tteokbokki is a specialty at this market.)
It looks delicious.
(Was the mission too easy?)
- Here you go.
-  Thank you.
Please watch me eat.
- Should I watch how well you eat?
-  Yes.
I'll eat this much at once.
- Eat like this.
-  Please watch me eat.
(Munching)
(Savouring)
I should take a big bite.
Then the owner will compliment on how well I eat.
(Will he hit a home run at his first bat?)
It tastes best if you chew well like that.
(He is disappointed.)
- Don't I eat better than others?
-  Yes.
I'm gulping this down.
No, they all eat like that.
(What do you know?)
Is that so?
Ma'am, I would like some water, please.
Enjoy it. The water is tasty, too.
(I'll end the mission with this water.)
Maybe I should eat in a hurry.
The water should be tasty. Enjoy as much as you want.
(He's acting tough.)
(Please compliment on how well I eat.)
- Did you watch me drink that water?
-  Yes.
(I have a feeling becoming a candidate will be difficult.)
I'll call Park Bo Gum's manager.
Hello. Is this Park Bo Gum's manager?
(Is she on the phone with his manager?)
Jun Yeol, this is Ji Hyo.
Are you guys that close?
- Do you know...
-  You were born in 1981, right?
- Park Bo Gum's number?
-  1981...
- Bo Gum's number?
-  Yes.
Hold on. Bo Gum's number...
Can I ask him for his permission before I give it to you?
(Ryu Jun Yeol is protective of his friend.)
(What a humiliation!)
- Actually... Hey.
-  Right, you should ask!
I got his number! I got it!
(She has forgotten all humiliation.)
Jun Yeol sent me.
(Jun Yeol sent her Bo Gum's number.)
- Hello, Bo Gum.
-  Hello.
Do you have time now? I'm 12 years older than you.
I'm shooting something right now. Can I call you back in 30 minutes?
Yes, sure.
Then I'll call you back in 30 minutes.
- Okay.
-  Okay.
All right. I'll be waiting.
What should I do for 30 minutes?
(I'm probably at the very bottom right now.)
30 minutes are not a big deal if I can see Bo Gum.
Spring wind blows
(Bring Bo Gum to me along with the spring wind!)
(Gary is on his way to meet Seolhyun.)
I'm here.
- Good luck.
-  Thank you!
Thank you, Sir.
(Gary came to see Seolhyun at a hair salon.)
Gosh, my back hurts.
This outfit is really embarrassing.
(Gary's ugly top embarrasses him.)
(Let me at least cover the ugly letters.)
Hello.
- Is Seolhyun here?
-  Hello. Yes.
(Hey, Seolhyun.)
Thanks.
(I'm here for you.)
Is she here?
- Here you are.
-  Hello.
(Pretty Seolhyun is here.)
- You look even prettier today.
-  You're too kind.
(Gary successfully meets Seolhyun who is well sought-after.)
(Seolhyun has become famous...)
(in commercials...)
(and music shows.)
Look at your shirt.
I had no choice but to wear this.
- Really?
-  I might smell like squid.
Okay.
Gary, she watched the show last night.
Really? Oh, gosh.
Can you tell us how he reacted when he saw Seolhyun's photo?
He showed some kind of...
- Desire?
-  sexual...
- You piece of trash!
-  Gosh.
- What's wrong with you?
-  Hey!
It was against my will!
It was my brain, not me!
Seolhyun, you know that...
it is overstated to make the show more fun.
- I believe you understand that.
-  Yes, I do.
- You said it was against your will.
-  I'm so embarrassed!
What? My mission today...
is to meet an ambassador for general election...
and make her wish come true to get a stamp.
I see.
You were the only one I could think of.
- Okay.
-  So...
So do I need to tell you my wish?
Seolhyun, tell me something easy, okay?
Then,
I have to go to the set for shooting now.
Can you take me there?
Sure. Where is it? Is it in Busan?
No. It's nearby.
- Really?
-  Yes.
- Then, I'll take you there.
-  Okay, thanks.
Hello.
- Hey.
-  Yes?
- Are you shooting now?
-  Yes, I am.
Haha called you, didn't he?
- He did.
-  You don't have to meet him.
(Kwang Soo is planning something.)
I... I already agreed to go.
Are you going to meet him?
Yes. Actually, I just woke up.
Then give him a difficult mission.
It will be meaningless if you give him an easy one.
I'll clear my mission quickly and come see you.
- Oh, okay.
-  Thanks, bye.
Bye.
(Will Kwang Soo's plot work?)
Hello, Seung Woo.
- Haha.
-  Yes.
So should I not meet him at all?
- No. You should meet him.
-  Okay.
Meet him but take your time.
Say, "I'm sorry to make you wait. But I should get changed first."
- Okay.
-  Where are you now?
- I'm home.
-  Sorry?
I just woke up.
Okay. Just buy as much time as possible.
- Okay.
-  Good.
And keep reporting me what is going on there.
- Okay.
-  Great.
(What will happen to these two?)
If it were nearer, we could've walked there instead.
- The weather's nice.
-  Right. The weather is so nice.
The weather is just right to take a walk. There's a park, too.
Did you see when they compared me to a squid?
Yes, I did.
What do you think about it?
I couldn't understand why they said you looked like a squid at first.
But hearing what the doctor said,
I became easily convinced.
(She thinks he looks like a squid.)
So when you saw the photo of me next to a squid,
did you think that we looked similar?
(Did we look similar?)
Yes.
(Yes.)
Even I was shocked to see how similar we were.
Do you like guys with round faces...
or those who look a bit ambiguous?
I like guys with round faces.
- I see.
-  My ideal type is Song Joong Ki.
Really? You like him, too?
Kwang Soo will get more upset when he hears this.
I've been liking him for a long time.
- Really?
-  Yes.
I can see how much you like him.
What? It's Kwang Soo.
(Speak of the devil.)
Hi, Kwang Soo.
- Gary.
-  Yes.
Are you on your way?
I already met Seolhyun.
You did?
Yes, she is with me now.
But she just said something quite cruel about you.
What do you mean? What did she say?
She said her ideal type is Song Joong Ki.
(It's painful.)
- Kwang Soo.
-  Yes?
You'd better give up on her.
I'll tell her all of Joong Ki's secrets to make her hate him.
Although she doesn't know his secrets,
I'm sure she'll even love them.
- That's true.
-  Right?
Yes, that is so true.
Excuse me, Sir. Please drop her off now.
Just get off here and walk.
- I'm sorry.
-  Kwang Soo.
- Yes?
-  We should drink tonight.
Thank you, Seolhyun.
Thank you for making time.
(Seolhyun is about to stamp.)
Joong Ki, Joong Ki.
- Sorry?
-  Think about Joong Ki.
Kwang Soo and Joong Ki are close, so you may meet Joong Ki soon.
- Then should I stamp this?
-  Of course.
(She stamps it.)
(Gary successfully completes the mission and gets a stamp.)
Thank you, Seolhyun.
- You're welcome.
-  I even used Joong Ki for this.
- Hope you do well today.
-  Okay.
- You can do it.
-  Thanks.
- Make a lot of money.
-  Okay.
- You can do it.
-  You, too.
- Goodbye.
-  Take care.
- Goodbye, my lady.
-  Goodbye.
Yes, Seung Woo.
- Haha.
-  Yes?
He said he will be here in 5 to 10 minutes.
Really?
Then tell him to wait a little more. Say, "My manger just called me..."
"and said my stylist wants me..."
"to get changed..."
"and put makeup on". Just buy some time.
Okay.
Good. Do that for 15 minutes.
(Kwang Soo also calls Yun Seok with the same motive.)
- Hello.
-  Yun Seok.
- Yes.
-  Please take your time.
- What?
-  When Haha arrives,
don't go out right away. Go out after some time.
(I want you to buy some time.)
Why?
I think I should...
teach him some lesson this time.
- You should do that.
-  Okay, I will.
Thanks, Yun Seok.
- Okay.
-  Bye.
(Seung Woo and Yun Seok are both asked to buy some time.)
Now, I got Haha.
(But you have 5 more to win.)
What should I do to be the first or second?
(Kwang Soo arrives at the place to meet Seung Woo.)
(He hastily tries to contact Seung Woo.)
- Hello.
-  Seung Woo.
- Yes.
-  I just arrived.
- Oh, you did?
-  Yes.
- Where should I wait?
-  Well,
- Yes.
-  you can see McDonald's near there.
Oh, that's where I am now.
- Really?
-  Yes.
I'm sorry, but I have to go to the restroom first.
Oh, you need to go to the restroom.
- Okay.
-  I'll see you soon.
Okay, I'll be waiting for you here at the McDonald's.
- Okay.
-  Bye.
(Kwang Soo waits with a cup of coffee to give him.)
I guess he has a stomach problem.
I don't want a lot
(Haha also arrives at Yun Seok's place.)
- Hello.
-  Yun Seok.
- Yes.
-  I'm sorry, but I'm already here.
- Really?
-  Yes, I just arrived.
Oh... Okay, I'll be there shortly.
Okay. When we meet each other, please welcome me with a hug.
- Okay.
-  Thank you.
Bye.
Yun Seok...
sounds so nice.
I can feel how nice he is. He's different from you, Kwang Soo.
Okay? He's different from you.
I think I'm going to catch a cold.
(He has reached his limit.)
(He feels that something is wrong.)
This must be Haha's doing.
(Upset)
(Answer it now.)
- Hello?
-  Haha.
- Why are you doing this to me?
-  What are you talking about?
(What's wrong, Kwang Soo?)
You called Seung Woo, didn't you?
- Me?
-  Yes.
He is not coming out.
I am waiting for Yun Seok.
Just tell me. Have you talked to Seung Woo?
No. I swear, I haven't.
- You haven't?
-  No.
(Is he really having stomach problems?)
I've been waiting outside for 30 minutes.
I've been waiting for 20 minutes, too. Did you call him?
(Did you set me up?)
- No. I didn't
-  Okay, I'll talk to you later.
- Okay. See you.
-  All right.
(Hey!)
(Who is it?)
(He is here!)
(Yoo Yun Seok became really famous after appearing in "Reply 1994".)
What if I am correct?
(His role as Chil Bong made him famous.)
(Yoo Yun Seok is here!)
(Give that to me.)
(He is caught talking to Kwang Soo on the phone.)
Give me a second.
Oh, Yun Seok. Nice to see you.
I'm so happy.
Yun Seok,
what took you so long?
I had to get dressed, but someone kept calling me.
I almost got tired of waiting.
It's so nice to see you.
I heard you were a student representative.
Yes, I was.
You are loved by so many viewers lately.
All right. Let me prepare the microphone first.
You know, Kwang Soo is...
- full of mischief.
-  Yes.
Okay, Yun Seok.
(He was so eager to see Yun Seok.)
Please tell me...
one of your wishes.
Then I will grant that wish.
- A wish?
-  Yes.
What should I request?
Think of a simple one. I could give you a piggyback ride.
- So you want a simple wish?
-  Yes, something I can do right now.
(How about this?)
What? What is this?
(What is this thing?)
Hold on. Give me a second. I think he was prepared.
(Did Yun Seok know that Haha was coming?)
(Oh, my goodness!)
I think shaving will make a good mission.
- What?
-  Shaving sounds good.
You can ask him to shave in 10 seconds.
- What?
-  Make him shave in 10 seconds.
- Shaving in 10 seconds?
-  This needs to work.
- Isn't that too rude?
-  It's perfectly fine.
Calling you out this early in the morning is rude.
I do have an electric shaver...
Grab that.
Take that when you see him.
(He's in despair.)
My wish is...
You are asking me to shave my armpits, right?
No, not your armpits but here.
I can't stand this.
Hey, tell me the truth.
Tell me why you are doing this.
What is he?
(Even Haha seems so confused.)
Come on!
This is a penalty.
This is not a wish.
I'm sorry, but you're too rude.
Hold on. Yun Seok.
So...
you want me to shave, is that right?
(I'm sorry, but this is too hilarious.)
- So that is your wish?
-  Yes.
I will count to 10.
Gosh, I'm going crazy.
Can you pick just one place for me to shave?
Then...
- please shave your chin.
-  My chin?
(He suppresses his anger.)
All right.
How do I turn this on?
Okay. I'll turn it on for you.
(Yun Seok is so kind.)
- I'll count to 10.
-  Okay.
Ready, start. Ten, nine,
eight, seven...
(I don't care!)
Four, three...
(His laughing makes him slow down.)
Two, one.
(Haha has finished shaving.)
I think you missed here.
(Yun Seok won't let a single hair be unshaved.)
Right here. Slowly, slowly...
You shouldn't miss a spot.
It's all clean now.
I didn't know Yun Seok was this harsh.
Are you sure you were a student representative?
You know, I am meticulous.
Oh, no, you are bleeding!
- What should I do?
-  I was rushing.
It's okay. Bleeding this much for Running Man is normal.
- Oh, no, you are bleeding.
-  I'm fine.
- Oh, no.
-  It's okay, don't worry.
- It's done.
-  I'm done, right? Thanks.
(He is fuming with anger.)
All right.
Wow, Yun Seok.
Please join us on Running Man. Promise me.
- Am I still bleeding?
-  I am trying to stop it.
(I'm trying my best to stop it from bleeding.)
I was in a hurry because I had to shave in 10 seconds.
Just stamp on it already.
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry. I couldn't control myself.
- Am I supposed to vote?
-  Yes.
- Stamp it.
-  You know, on the election day,
my movie is coming out...
Just stamp it already!
Stamp it! Just stamp it!
(Haha successfully completes the mission and gets a stamp.)
Please join us on Running Man later.
- Okay.
-  If you do...
Hold on, you're still bleeding.
(If he does, Haha will be able to have a match with him.)
(Kwang Soo is wandering around Seocho-gu for Yu Seung Woo.)
It'd be too rude to hurry him on our first encounter.
(Is he really that sick?)
I don't have much time.
I called him 30 minutes ago. He should've been prepared.
(Irritated)
(Loss for words)
(He calls him again.)
Hello, Kwang Soo.
(What?)
(Seung Woo is here at last.)
(How would this young and adorable singer look like?)
Hello, Kwang Soo.
(Who are you?)
I am Seung Woo.
(Is he Seung Woo?)
(What happened to the young Seung Woo?)
(Seung Woo of SoulstaR)
(He is the lead vocalist.)
When was your first election?
It's been a while. I participated in the presidential election.
(He has voted for the presidential election.)
There is another election in April.
(He sounds very mature.)
(Was he born in 1997 or in 1977?)
I see.
Sorry, but how old are you?
I was born in 1981.
(He was born in 1981.)
I am so sorry.
(Sorry for bothering you.)
I received a call from Haha.
(Where is the 20-year-old Seung Woo that I was looking for?)
Were you surprised?
(Few hours ago)
Hello?
- Is this Seung Woo?
-  Yes.
Hang up first. It's the right number. Hey!
(Kwang Soo ran off after hearing that it was "Seung Woo".)
- Seung Woo!
-  Hey, are you a scammer?
Wow, that punk.
But I gave him a wrong number.
He's talking to Seung Woo, but it's not Yu Seung Woo.
(It's the wrong "Seung Woo".)
There was a group called SoulstaR.
He is Lee Seung Woo of SoulstaR.
Try calling. I knew he would run away like that.
I'm so sick of him.
(Haha won this time.)
(He is stunned.)
I see...
Sorry for bothering you.
(He finally understands.)
What should I do now?
(It feels so awkward.)
Are you busy today?
No, I'm fine.
(He is not busy.)
I see. Can I go now?
Yeah, sure.
I'm so sorry.
(He doesn't even tell Kwang Soo to leave.)
- I'm sorry, but I have to go.
-  That's okay. You are in a hurry.
I'll contact you later.
- Thank you.
-  Thank you.
Goodbye.
(Awkward)
Haha tricked me.
I'm sorry! I'm so sorry.
(Kwang Soo is on his journey once again.)
- Bye.
-  Thank you.
(Thank you, Seung Woo of SoulstaR for helping us.)
(He is so angry.)
(Kwang Soo has one word to say.)
Hey, Kwang Soo.
You.
(He said, "You".)
Hey, where are you?
(He wants to know where Haha is.)
Answer me!
(He is really angry.)
- Why?
-  Come here.
-  Come here. Where are you?
Where are you now?
(Kwang Soo has lost this match.)
- Where are you?
-  Why?
Why? What happened?
Who was that old man?
(He wants to know who that old man was.)
- Hey...
-  How could you do this to me?
- He's Seung Woo.
-  Why are you doing this?
He's Seung woo.
- Why are you doing this to me?
-  What do you mean?
You saw the name on my phone.
But why did he say, "Yes," when I asked, "Seung Woo?"
His name is Seung Woo. Lee Seung Woo.
- Okay. I get it.
-  What did you get?
No, it's nothing. I'll call you later.
(I'll see you in the next round.)
I'll call you later. I have to do my mission now.
This is a bit much.
(Grant a wish of a celebrity who has the same name as an area.)
I'll say this is photoshopped.
I think she is here now.
There she is.
(Who is he going to meet?)
I'm sorry, Seohyun.
I'm so sorry. I should cover this.
(It's Seohyun from Girls' Generation.)
(Her name is exactly the same as Seohyun-dong.)
I have to grant a wish of a celebrity to get a stamp.
- I see, a wish...
-  Yes, a simple one is fine.
- A simple one?
-  Yes.
- Simple enough for you to grant?
-  That's right.
You know, the weather is really nice these days.
I wish someone...
could carry me on his back...
or give me a ride on his shoulders.
I'd like to go on a walk like that.
- Well..
-  That sounds simple.
Don't worry, I can do that for you any time.
- Okay, I am ready.
-  Get on!
- One, two, three!
-  One, two, three!
- All right.
-  There you go.
(She hops on.)
- Am I heavy?
-  No, you are not.
You are not heavy at all.
(He indirectly brags about his strength.)
- This is so fun.
-  Really?
- You're not heavy at all.
-  I'm sorry, I'm heavy.
- I must be heavy.
-  No!
- I'm not?
-  You're as light as feather.
I never knew you were going to be this light.
- You are so funny.
-  Yes.
- It's unbelievable.
-  Wow!
- Should we get some coffee?
-  What?
- I will buy it for you.
-  Oh my gosh...
- Are you really okay?
-  Of course I am.
- I think I am a little embarrassed.
-  Right? Hello.
- What do you want?
-  Iced Americano.
Iced Americano, please.
- It's 9.80 dollars.
-  Okay.
Wait. No.
- Don't be sorry. Thank you.
-  This is so funny.
You can't put me down, can you?
- I can't.
-  Right?
- Here you go.
-  Oh dear.
Thank you.
I think it's too hard for you.
- No, I am okay.
-  But...
I am okay, Seohyun.
I am really okay.
- I'm okay.
-  This is so embarrassing.
It's embarrassing, right?
But you asked for it.
- This is crazy.
-  This is indeed crazy.
- Oh gosh...
-  Hello!
(They are enjoying the coffee while on a mission.)
I didn't know it was this hot today.
(The weather is so good today.)
It's such a lovely weather.
(Jong Kook successfully completes the mission and gets a stamp.)
- Where should I put it?
-  Just put it here.
- Do I put it on your palm?
-  Yes.
- R. In 1, 2, 3.
-  In 1, 2, 3.
Push.
Okay!
- Thank you.
-  Thank you.
(He will now go to the next mission place, Gimpo.)
(There you go.)
Yes.
Hello?
Hello.
Hello, Bo Gum!
Hello, Ji Hyo.
(She's thrilled.)
- I admire you.
-  Don't mention that.
I really wanted to meet you, Bo Gum.
Me too. I always watch Running Man.
And I heard you really like me.
- Yes. I know.
-  Yes. I'm sure you were joking.
- No, I did talk about you.
-  Right.
And I finally get to meet you.
- I know.
-  Gosh...
The power of talking is amazing.
Thank you so much. Thank you.
- Bo Gum.
-  No problem. Yes?
I have a mission today.
Yes. What's the mission?
I have to meet a celebrity who is 12 years younger than me...
- and grant his wish.
-  I see.
I have to grant you one wish and get a stamp.
If you have time now,
I will grant you a wish. Can you give me a stamp?
- Right now?
-  Yes.
If you are outside,
I can go there.
(Will the hottest celebrity Park Bo Gum...)
(respond to the spontaneous request?)
No, I will go there.
(He accepts the request.)
- Really?
-  Yes.
Where are you?
I am near the Independence Gate.
Where?
I'm near the Independence Gate.
We are fated to meet. I am near. I am in Jongno.
We are fated to meet, Bo Gum.
I have a photo shoot today in Jongno.
- Is that right?
-  Yes.
We are fated to meet today.
- Bo Gum.
-  Yes.
Have you already got to the Independence Gate?
Where are you now?
I'm near Korean Contemporary History Museum.
I will go to Sejong Centre Chamber Hall.
- You will?
-  Yes.
You are so sweet.
Okay. I will be waiting for you here then.
- Okay. I will hurry up.
-  Thank you.
- Thank you, too.
- See you soon. Okay.
-  See you soon. Okay.
Yes!
I have to go meet Bo Gum.
Let's go meet Bo Gum!
(She's meeting him at Korean Contemporary History Museum.)
(She arrives at the meeting place.)
(She puts down two cups of coffee on the bench.)
(And she fixes her makeup.)
(She fixes her makeup with delicate touches.)
(She hopes he will arrive before the coffee gets cold.)
(I am...)
(coming to meet you.)
- Hello.
-  Oh gosh!
(He surprised her.)
It's Bo Gum! It's you!
I can't believe it! I can't believe it!
Bo Gum is really here.
It's me, Taek.
(The hottest actor Park Bo Gum accidentally comes to Running Man.)
- Here's your coffee.
-  Oh, yes.
- I got hot coffee for you.
-  Thank you.
- Thank you.
-  Oh dear.
- Bo Gum.
-  Yes.
- Today, I will grant you a wish.
-  Okay.
- And you will give me a stamp.
Did you think about your wish?
- Yes.
-  You have one?
I am a little scared because he said yes so confidently.
(Is he naive or evil? What is his wish?)
I want to take a photo with you and get your autograph.
(He wants a picture with her and her autograph.)
No way!
It's okay. That's okay, right? I love it.
No way.
I'd love that of course.
I'd be happy.
(They take a photo together right away.)
I want to cover my face.
(Our smiles look alike.)
In 1, 2, 3.
(The couple with 12 years of age difference)
- Bo Gum.
-  Yes.
- Please write "Dear Ji Hyo".
-  Sure. Okay.
Doesn't it look like he's granting my wish?
(Careful)
(It seems like Ji Hyo gave up becoming a leader.)
- Oh gosh!
-  Thank you.
Please give me an autograph, too.
Oh my gosh.
I got Bo Gum's autograph.
- I...
-  I can't believe this.
- Thank you. Yes.
-  Bo Gum.
- I will grant your wish now.
-  Okay.
(She gives Bo Gum her autograph, too.)
- I wrote too much.
-  Do you...
Do you have to meet another person?
No, I just have to meet you.
- I'm done after I meet you.
-  Oh gosh.
- Thank you.
-  From the start,
- I only talked about you.
-  Really?
Thank you so much.
- Don't mention it.
-  No.
- Bo Gum, thanks for coming.
-  No problem.
- Thank you so much.
-  I never knew...
you'd come in the middle of your work.
(Hugging)
- You could've asked for more.
-  No.
Please invite me to Running Man later.
I hope you will get to...
- join us later.
-  Me, too.
I hope you will win today.
- Have a great day.
-  Thank you.
- Thank you.
-  I will be able to win today.
- Okay. I will watch the show.
-  Bye.
- Thank you.
-  Gosh...
- Thank you so much.
-  No problem.
- Thank you, Bo Gum.
-  Thanks for the coffee.
- Thank you.
-  No problem.
(Ji Hyo successfully completes her mission and gets the stamp.)
(6 members completed the mission.)
- Eun Ji.
-  Why?
What do you mean why?
I am shooting Running Man right now.
Oh, okay.
- Eun Ji. By any chance...
-  Yes.
Yes.
Ha Young didn't vote yet, right?
- She didn't do it yet.
-  Right?
Are you with her right now?
(Ha Young went...)
She went to do groceries?
She went to the jungle.
- Where?
-  A jungle.
Oh, a jungle! Right. She went to the jungle.
(He fails to meet Ha Young.)
He's taking a class in school.
- He's taking a class.
-  Yes.
(He fails again.)
It can't be someone born in 1987?
I can't meet someone who was born in 1987.
I know a lot of people who were born in 1987.
I am sorry.
(Fooled by Haha, Kwang Soo is still lost.)
(The other members are headed to the next destination.)
Sir.
Sir, can you drive a little faster?
I need to beat the car in front of us.
I can get there faster, right?
It wouldn't have been easy for them.
What's this?
(Who will become the candidates?)
(The Leader Election House in Gimpo, Gyeonggi Province)
(Who will leave the first footprints here?)
Congratulations.
(Look!)
(It's Gary!)
Am I the first?
- You are the first.
-  Oh my gosh!
You've earned the right to run for the election.
Thank you so much.
Where did everyone go?
(Who will take the last place?)
(Yu Jae Seok)
You are the second candidate.
Okay.
(Jae Seok is the No. 2 candidate of the Leader Election!)
(Candidate No. 2 Jae Seok)
I am the second one.
I'm the second, aren't I?
I'm not!
Gary got here first?
(Ji Hyo, Jong Kook and Haha shortly arrive.)
The situation is over.
The two candidates have already been decided.
Unfortunately, you don't have the right to run for the election.
(Sighing)
I don't have the right?
On the first election, you don't have the right.
(He becomes the voter.)
I can just give up and go there?
It's not giving up. You never had the chance.
(He never had the chance.)
(I went through all the humiliation...)
(because of Haha.)
Kwang Soo. Kwang Soo.
(I won't forgive you, Haha.)
(He walks angrily.)
- What is it?
-  What's wrong?
What? What?
What's wrong?
Why? What's wrong?
Wait. I am...
What's the matter?
- What wrong with him?
-  I'm just...
Let's talk later.
- Take off your glasses.
-  Calm down.
- Be careful.
-  Kwang Soo.
(Everyone including Kwang Soo is here.)
- I'm worried.
-  The two first-comers,
Jae Seok and Gary, will be the candidates.
I see.
Tell us what you're going to do.
- Tell us what you're going to do...
-  Tell us.
if you become the leader.
- As I said earlier,
-  Yes.
I'm not a mean person.
- That's right.
-  Gary is not mean.
- That's true.
-  I'm not mean.
- I won't bother you so much.
-  Of course not.
- Jae Seok can be very mean.
-  I know.
- He's so mischievous.
-  I might be mischievous...
- but I won't give you a hard time.
-  I don't believe you.
- It'll be fun.
-  You know him.
(I don't want to think about it.)
Don't you want to have fun for an hour?
- I can make it fun.
-  Even while having fun,
- he can give you a hard time.
-  That's right.
- Gary is persuasive.
-  He is.
- I lean towards Gary.
-  Gary would be better.
Even if we want Gary to win,
we shouldn't be unanimous.
- You're right.
-  We should never be unanimous.
You'll select your leader by majority.
The leader will have power over the other members...
- for one hour.
-  Really?
But if you're unanimous, there will be bad consequences.
If you're unanimous, the staff will be your leader.
(The producer's wish list)
We shouldn't talk to each other. Kwang Soo, go ahead.
- We shouldn't talk.
-  Haha, go ahead.
It's unpredictable.
Don't talk to each other.
It's hard to predict what will happen.
- As long as we're not unanimous...
-  It won't be unanimous.
- Let me count the votes.
-  Okay.
- Who will win?
-  Congratulations in advance.
- It'd be 3 to 2.
-  I'll be on his side.
I hope it'll be 3 to 2. We shouldn't be unanimous.
- It says Gary.
-  It's Haha's ballot.
It's Haha's ballot.
"I love you. Let's go home together."
(I love you, Gary.)
(Heart)
- He can be very sweet sometimes.
-  What do you like about him?
(What says the second ballot?)
- It's Gary.
-  Gary.
It's Ji Hyo's ballot.
- I voted for you, Gary.
-  Will the result be reversed?
- Ji Hyo.
-  Ji Hyo voted for Gary.
Ji Hyo, how can you do this?
We're in trouble.
- Yu Jae Seok.
-  It's Jae Seok.
(Jae Seok won one vote.)
- I voted for you.
-  He sided with him.
I saved you from the penalty.
That's right. You did well.
- Right?
-  We won't be penalised.
You shouldn't be in the minority.
(Who will be the leader and who will be in the minority?)
- Gary.
-  Whose ballot is it?
- It's Jong Kook's.
-  We could have been unanimous.
If it wasn't for Seok Jin, we would've been unanimous.
- Gary gained a majority.
-  We have only one ballot left.
You already gained a majority.
Gary.
- If it wasn't for me...
-  I can't believe this.
If it wasn't for me, you would have been penalised.
Thank you for supporting me.
- Congratulations.
-  By the way...
- Thank you, Seok Jin.
-  What would you have done...
- without me?
-  I know. Thank you.
- I'm disappointed in you, Seok Jin.
-  Thank you.
(What penalty will Seok Jin receive?)
You can style his hair with them.
What should we do?
Let me see.
- You should put it closer.
-  That's too much.
(Shocked)
Cover your forehead.
(Spraying)
The colour is quite vivid.
- Wait.
-  Cover your forehead.
(My goodness.)
It's too much.
- Is it the colour of grass?
-  Yes.
It makes me want to play golf on your head.
Don't spray on my ear!
(Jae Seok finishes it off by adding some pink.)
- Stop!
-  It seems done.
You look like a member of a motorcycle gang.
I like the colour combination.
- It's perfect.
-  Let me see.
You'll be surprised.
- Do you like it?
-  It doesn't look bad.
I look like a gangster.
Gosh, I hate it.
I want to look intelligent.
- You remind me...
-  What is this?
You remind me of the World Cup season.
I mean...
- It's a festival.
-  Go, Korea!
(Go, Korea!)
- Go, Korea!
-  Go, Korea!
Gosh.
You're very quiet.
Someone who turned on TV now will think...
- I intended to look like this.
-  That's right.
This is embarrassing.
I would like Seok Jin...
and Jae Seok to go grocery shopping.
He's good.
- He's so good.
-  He's great.
- Is this what power means?
-  He can do whatever he wants.
- That's not it.
-  This is embarrassing.
Leader, what would you like to eat?
- I'd like some braised chicken.
-  Braised chicken?
- See you in a while.
-  Anyone else?
- Does anyone want anything?
-  I'm so embarrassed.
I'd like some refreshments, too.
- Refreshments?
-  That sounds great.
- Yes.
-  We need them.
I'd like some chocolate for desserts.
- I want chocolate.
-  Chocolate.
I want ice cream.
My goodness.
Guys, we will try to prepare them. You can wait inside.
(Let's see what happens in the next election.)
(The first era, the Age of Gary)
- Kwang Soo.
-  Yes.
- Never mind.
-  What were you going to say?
To be honest...
Answer me.
If you're not given a badge,
you said you will choose Gary to be penalised with, right?
- I did.
-  Right?
If you don't give me the badge, I'm going to take you with me.
- What?
-  I'm serious.
-  If he doesn't give me the badge,
I'm going to take him with me when I'm penalised.
You know I can take one person, right?
Gosh. You should be careful who you trust.
Don't say that.
Think about it.
- I'm so tired.
-  You might sleep in the cemetery.
I'm going to take him if he doesn't give me the badge.
I mean it. I've made up my mind.
- Really?
-  Seriously?
He's so...
Get out.
- He wants you to get out.
-  Get out.
- You want me to get out?
-  Wait.
Meet me at the cemetery, then.
You'll meet him there.
- I'm so stressed.
-  Meet me there.
If you don't give me the badge, I have no chance.
You look so mean now.
I betray you all the time.
If you don't give me the badge, I'll take you to the cemetery.
(An evil threat to Gary's regime)
Seriously.
- He's unbelievable.
-  Really.
I don't think I'll be the leader.
- I have a lot of enemies.
-  I think I have a chance.
- You have a chance.
-  That's right.
In the next election, I'll help you.
- All right.
-  Give me a Go-Home Badge.
- I will.
-  All right.
- Okay?
-  Let's go home together.
Say "Yu".
- Yu...
-  And Ji, go!
Let's maintain our trust.
- Let's maintain our friendship.
-  Let's maintain our promise.
Kwang Soo, I'm afraid you might get me in trouble.
I think you should be beaten up first.
What?
Are you going to beat me up?
I saw boxing gloves.
- Is he going to beat me up?
-  Should I help?
I'd like to see Jong Kook...
- Jong Kook?
-  and Kwang Soo spar.
- That'll be interesting.
-  That'll be fun.
- I agree.
-  Look.
Who knows who will win?
- Don't worry too much.
-  Wait.
Did you take what I said seriously?
(He's shameless.)
Bring the gears.
- Leader.
-  I'll go get them.
- I was joking.
-  Be a man.
Bring the gears first.
- Bring the headgears.
-  Leader, I was joking.
- Don't be like that.
-  It'll be fun.
Why don't you make Kwang Soo write a note?
- A note?
-  What note?
- It depends on what he writes.
-  That you won't take me with you.
That you won't take me to the cemetery.
You have to write it yourself.
- We have cameras here, too.
-  What is this?
Guys.
You should be the witnesses.
- Write it.
-  Oh, they're ready.
- What are these?
-  Write the note first.
Why do we need a hammer? Are we in the movie, "The Chaser"?
I'll put them in front of Jong Kook for now.
- First...
-  I'll write it.
Write the note first.
(Jong Kook is getting ready to discipline Kwang Soo)
- Look at Jong Kook.
-  Wait.
- Write the note first.
-  Let him write it first.
- Okay.
-  I'll write it.
- Write the title.
-  Okay.
- Write your name.
-  I was joking.
- Write "Lee Kwang Soo".
-  Lee Kwang Soo.
- Even if...
-  "Even if..."
You're not given a badge...
"I am not given a badge..."
You won't choose me to be penalised with you.
- Okay. If I break this promise?
-  If you break this promise,
your ex-girlfriends...
What?
(What?)
Why?
Pick something else.
They will be revealed through Gary's social media account...
- one by one.
-  That sounds great.
- My ex-girlfriends?
-  Yes.
I'm really going to do that.
I have nothing to lose.
I've been working for 20 years.
- Kwang Soo looks really worried.
-  We need a set rule.
- Will that be strong enough?
-  It will be.
- It's strong enough.
-  It is strong.
I've made so many wrong moves today.
You're so smart.
(Kwang Soo's first revolt is now settled down.)
Be nice.
Okay.
They're taking a rest.
Those brats.
They should help us.
- You're back.
-  You're back.
- What are you doing?
-  Welcome back.
We've been sitting here.
- The weird thing is...
-  Set the table.
Set the table.
I don't even have to talk to them.
- You're not the leader.
-  Set the table.
I'm his right-hand man. Set the table.
- Set the table.
-  Why is it that...
you're acting like a leader?
It's my role.
- I gave him the right.
-  Come this way.
- Gary.
-  I'll do it.
Strawberries are my favourite. Who decided to buy them?
- I did.
-  It was me.
(Please remember me.)
He didn't want to but I insisted on buying them.
- I'll remember that.
-  It was me.
It's my favourite fruit.
Why don't you go wash the fruits?
All right.
(Kwang Soo volunteered to wash the fruits.)
They look great.
- That's right.
-  They look delicious.
I washed the strawberries.
You should have removed the stems as well.
(You should have removed the stems as well.)
- Kwang Soo.
-  Gosh.
He doesn't know a thing.
It's healthier this way.
It's hard to grab.
- There's a knife. Cut them off.
-  Use the knife.
We could use all of them.
You're right. We could have some more.
It's already boiling.
Leader, I removed the stems.
You did?
I did remove the stems.
- Is there another table?
-  That's driving me crazy.
Why?
- You must feel uncomfortable.
-  Is this how it usually is?
- Is it? To eat at the same table?
-  The king needs to eat first.
I saw another table inside.
I think it's a good idea to eat on the floor.
Excuse me. Kwang Soo and I...
- Me too?
-  Yes.
- Leader, me too?
-  Isn't that obvious?
I keep on being moved to the edge.
- Oh, my.
-  I will move.
I keep on sitting at the edge.
I think it'll be all right for everyone to sit down and eat.
Is that right? Since we're not eating at the same table?
- My legs.
-  This is annoying.
I'll fight for independence.
(It's sweet to be a king.)
I don't want to live as the subordinate.
(Gary's tenure comes to an end.)
- What is this?
-  Should we go outside?
- I think there's something outside.
-  Is it outside?
There must be something out there.
- Being a king is difficult.
-  You must know.
- How long did you last?
-  It's not easy.
- I had to write a note.
-  Do we need to take this off?
Being a leader is very burdening.
I received all kinds of threats and plots against me.
- I really can't stand it.
-  It's true.
If I had to do it again, I will forsake my rights.
- All kinds of threats.
-  What should we do now?
The next mission to elect the second leader will be fishing.
- Please.
-  What is it?
We will move to a fishing place in a moment.
- Yes.
-  A fishing place?
Each of you will begin fishing.
I'm really bad at fishing.
- Is this a test of luck?
-  But...
this is a good mission.
- What are you talking about?
-  Last time,
you caught a fish once.
Not with my bare hands but with a fishing rod.
- With a fishing rod.
-  A fishing rod?
- I can't.
-  It's difficult.
- Fishing is really difficult.
-  Isn't fishing a great idea?
I can see the fish moving in the water.
I have a good feeling about this.
- Kwang Soo.
-  Yes.
- You won't have the feeling.
-  Is that where Joong Ki comes in?
- Who's good at fishing?
-  Can we sit anywhere we want?
- Can we sit anywhere?
-  Gary.
Do you know how to fasten a float?
- It's over here.
-  I do.
Jae Seok, what are you doing?
Remember that you'll get tired if you sit next to a loud person.
- This is the place.
-  I'm going to catch one.
- Now.
-  Is this right?
A worm is the best.
- I'm sorry.
-  How much time are we given?
The time ends as soon as two people catch a fish.
Two fish?
Let's go for it.
- I don't know.
-  Did you catch one?
(Seven Anglers begin fishing.)
Please give me a chance to win.
I should wait laid back.
- Please.
-  Please.
-  Please send me one fish.
I think it's moving.
Have we ever caught anything? Weren't we the one being caught?
Goodness, he's so talkative.
You three, please be quiet.
- Us three?
-  What did you say?
What did you say?
- Goodness me.
-  Goodness me.
I would have taught you a lesson if you were next to me.
Shall I move?
No, stay there.
- Is it even possible to catch one?
-  Please, come to me.
It's coming.
It's better to get caught by me.
- Is he talking to the fish?
-  Or else your pride will be hurt.
If you're going to get caught, it's better to get caught by me.
My goodness. The float.
It's better to get caught by me.
(I had a feeling.)
- The float was moving.
-  What was that?
- I was surprised.
Were you exercising your arm?
Usually, fishing at fish farms...
(The float definitely moved.)
Oh, yes!
- My goodness.
-  Did you catch it?
- Really?
-  Yes!
What's that?
(He catches one as soon as they begin.)
- What is that?
-  He's got it.
- Look.
-  What is this? It's so big.
Why is it so big?
It's so big. How should I catch this?
- I'm in a hurry.
-  Excuse me.
- There's only one place left.
-  Help me out.
- Please let it go back in.
-  There's one place left.
- Please.
-  Please.
(If he loses grip of it now, it will all come to nothing.)
(Haha versus Big Fish, who will be the winner?)
Please.
- Haha can't win.
-  Really. Haha can't win.
(Haha wins.)
- You're all dead meat.
-  We're in trouble.
I'm in trouble, there's only one spot left.
- There's only one spot left.
-  Kwang Soo.
Haha, when did you pull it out?
The float went right under.
I got it out.
I did it by myself.
- He can't be the winner.
-  It's really big.
How did he do that?
(Everyone, follow me.)
Excuse me, do you need anything?
Haha is really awesome.
Haha has always been awesome.
(Everyone is already taking Haha's side.)
It ate my bait.
Do I just do this?
- Kwang Soo.
-  Yes, Jae Seok.
Where's your fish mask?
Can I catch you?
- Jae Seok.
-  Kwang Soo.
Please let me catch you once.
- I'll help you out.
-  I can't go in the water.
- Look there.
-  Kwang Soo, this is just too much.
Will I catch one?
(Barking)
Be quiet.
- Be quiet.
-  You little dog.
Hey, you.
- Go away.
-  Be quiet.
Stop pretending to be a big dog when you're so little.
Get out.
- Kwang Soo, there aren't any fish.
-  I don't think we can do it.
(At that moment, a fish jumped above water.)
- Did you see that fish jump?
-  Did it jump?
As if to make fun of us.
Can't I move to that side?
The owner of the fishing place gave us a tip.
The spots on the edges are the best.
- Pardon?
-  The spots on each side.
(Let's go to recommended spot.)
- Why did you tell us this late?
-  You should have told us earlier.
This is my spot.
You don't own this spot.
(Ji Hyo's spot becomes crammed with people.)
The one who catches a fish first is the owner.
What is this?
It's called fishing.
- Seok Jin is really weird today.
-  Shall we try some fishing?
Seok Jin is really weird today.
There's a pervert in the fishing area.
Take him away.
What if we all catch the same fish?
Why are they moving about?
This is my last spot.
This is my last spot for fishing.
Excuse me, are fish caught well here too?
Are there fish here too?
(Kwang Soo turned around.)
The fish keep on leaving after eating my bait.
(Who will win the second spot for candidacy?)
- I caught it.
-  What?
(I caught it.)
(At the same time, Jae Seok and Ji Hyo feel a nibble too.)
- Unbelievable.
-  I caught it.
I feel it.
- Unbelievable.
-  I caught it.
(Who will win the right for candidacy?)
- What is this?
-  I caught one.
I caught one.
- Jae Seok.
-  I caught one.
(It got away.)
(Meanwhile, what about Kwang Soo?)
- Unbelievable.
-  I caught it.
- I caught it.
-  I feel it.
(He caught a fish.)
I caught it.
- Does that qualify?
-  It's too small.
- Is that a fish too?
-  I've caught a big fish.
- I've caught a big fish.
-  I'm really jealous.
- I'm really jealous.
-  He caught a big fish.
Ji Hyo, you and me...
We both felt a nibble.
- We nearly caught it.
-  Jae Seok, we both felt it.
- I was this close.
-  What is he doing?
I never even felt a nibble.
How did you catch such a small fish?
I caught it. I have never caught a fish this big before.
- He's a professional entertainer.
-  You're my tuna.
- I was this close.
-  Really.
(Kwang Soo wins the second spot for candidacy.)
The two candidates have been decided.
- Really.
-  It's devil against lout.
(The candidates for the second king are Haha and Kwang Soo.)
- Who's who?
-  I don't know.
You're the devil and you're the lout.
You should be careful who you root for.
- Of course.
-  That's important.
I'll begin.
Will it be devil or lout?
- All right.
-  I have faith in you, Kwang Soo.
Please make a wise choice.
This is tough.
(Who will the voters choose?)
Gosh. I wish I could wear a hat.
- We can't be unanimous.
-  That's right.
- That's the worst scenario.
-  Yes, it is.
- It's the worst if we're unanimous.
-  You're right.
We will see the first ballot.
- Okay.
-  I hoped I voted with the majority.
Kwang Soo.
(Kwang Soo gets one vote.)
All right.
I should cut the root of that grass. Excuse me.
- Haha.
-  Haha.
My goodness, this fellow.
Are you taking sides already?
Well, you know.
Kwang Soo.
- Who is it?
-  Yu.
- Lee, cross.
-  Ji, cross.
I got it.
Yu Lee Ji.
- Yu Lee Ji.
-  It's over.
-  We only need one more vote.
- Only one more vote.
-  Yu Lee Ji.
- Okay, you three.
-  That's funny.
We need just one more person.
It's definitely shaving one's head.
- Yu Lee Ji.
-  Just one more.
(The result depends on this one vote.)
(Will it end with Kwang Soo's victory or a tie?)
- Just one more person.
-  Haha. Okay.
(2 votes for Kwang Soo, 2 votes for Haha)
- Hurrah!
-  What is this?
-  There's one last vote.
Go over to that side.
If it doesn't work out, we're all dead.
- Yu.
-  Lee.
-  Why are you "Yu"?
- Lee.
-  Yu.
- Ga.
-  My surname is Yu.
(What?)
- Yu.
-  Jee.
- Ga.
-  Gary.
(Gary, are you switching sides?)
(What has Gary chosen?)
- Yu.
-  Ji.
- Gary.
-  Ga.
Gary.
Hurrah!
(Go, Haha.)
(2 votes for Kwang Soo, 3 votes for Haha)
(He looks disappointed.)
Hurrah!
(Haha becomes the second king.)
I made a poem for you.
Haha is higher than the sky.
Haha is greater than the distance from Earth to the sky.
Stop it.
Let me do this.
- Let's choose colours.
-  That's great.
Green seems nice.
- How could this happen?
-  Wait.
(Grasshoppers are always green.)
Gosh.
- Should we draw red spots on him?
-  Wait.
- He looks like a ladybug.
-  He does look like a ladybug.
He is very skilled.
- Jae Seok looks natural.
-  Next customer!
Look at me.
I think pink colour suits Kwang Soo.
(Jae Seok sprays paint on Kwang Soo this time.)
It looks like your hair is on fire.
Doesn't Kwang Soo have to do that?
- You don't have to do this.
-  Really?
- Gosh!
-  You don't have to do this?
- Right. I don't have to!
-  That's right.
- I didn't have to.
-  No, you didn't.
What will happen if they have a blind date like that?
What if they go to a club like that?
- Why do we always lose?
-  Why is it always the three of us?
- I'm so fed up with it.
-  I can't understand.
(The second era, King Haha)
- We have three here...
-  Yes.
- and three here as well.
-  Okay.
- I am the umpire.
- We'll have table tennis today.
-  Okay.
And we have a great prize for the winner.
- What is that?
-  For the winner?
You may go home if you win.
- Yes!
-  You're so cool!
- Win and you can go home.
-  I'm really bad at table tennis.
That's why we're playing it.
(If I can go home early, I don't need to be a gentleman.)
- King Haha!
-  It's funny.
- I'm trying to be honest.
-  He's being honest.
He could make us laugh because he was honest.
- Right, he was funny.
-  Thank you.
- May I go first?
-  Okay.
Do we start now?
- Yes, it begins now.
-  I'll start.
Okay, sure.
Let's go!
- Good.
-  Great.
- Wow.
-  You're good.
- Good.
-  Great.
(Ji Hyo is out.)
It's okay.
- Way to go!
-  I want to change the players.
- Let's go home.
-  Okay.
(Players have been changed to Gary and Kwang Soo.)
(It starts.)
- Okay!
-  You're doing good.
- You did it!
-  You did it!
(The ball touches the net.)
- Okay!
-  He's good.
(Gary is out.)
It's okay.
You can beat others too.
- All you need is confidence.
-  Okay.
- I can make it!
-  You need confidence not skills.
(Kwang Soo is being sly.)
That's good. That's it.
- You did good.
-  Great!
All you need is confidence.
Kwang Soo.
Guys, stop it. Let's play.
- Let's play.
-  You can do it.
Be confident in yourself.
What you need is confidence not skills.
- Okay!
-  Good.
Gosh!
Why are you celebrating every time you win?
(They physically celebrate their victory.)
- Be confident.
-  Kwang Soo.
(Stop it now.)
My goodness.
- Come! Let's play.
-  Hurry up!
(Flustered)
(He was speedy but he missed the ball.)
(I'll break this table.)
(You humiliated me.)
- Good.
-  Calm down.
(Team Jae Seok needs one more score.)
You're good.
Right. Great.
Jae Seok is good at this.
You can beat him.
Great. Way to go!
(Who will win in this high-class rally?)
Jae Seok is good at this.
You can beat him.
Gosh!
- Wow!
-  Thank you!
- Thank you!
-  You got it!
I don't know if I can say this, but Jae Seok looks like a toad.
His colourful hair disturbs me.
Please, let us win.
You can beat him.
- You can decide Kwang Soo.
-  Okay.
- So, each has one cup. Right?
-  Yes.
My pick is Gary.
I'll choose Jong Kook.
Then, I'll pick Haha.
Please close your eyes, Seok Jin.
I thought we could open our eyes.
- Yes, you can open your eyes now.
-  Open your eyes.
- You can.
-  One, two...
Three!
(Water-slapping)
- Who is it? Is it me?
-  No, it's not you.
Yes!
He'll even survive in abyss.
(What an immortal guy he is!)
- He will.
-  It's amazing.
Yes!
(Kwang Soo may leave early. And Haha's tenure is over.)
(Gary has 2, Kwang Soo and Haha have 1 each and others have none.)
(They go to the polling booth to vote for the last king.)
It's a pirate roulette.
(They will play with a pirate roulette for the last candidacy.)
It never works when we want to be chosen.
Two of us will become candidates? Okay.
- It's time for the last candidacy.
-  Okay.
Two members who are chosen by the roulette will run for the election.
- Please go ahead, Leader Gary.
-  Okay.
Leader Gary.
All right.
(He puts a sword in.)
- Good.
-  It's only the beginning.
It's hard to get it in the beginning. Only one sword went in.
Ji Hyo is usually lucky with these.
- It'll pop up.
-  Can we choose colours?
- Of course.
-  Oh no.
- I like red.
-  I rarely succeed in such games.
Let me put it hard. Go!
- He failed too.
-  Gosh.
You can do it.
- My goodness.
-  It didn't work for me.
I knew it. I never succeed.
Oh, please. Please!
- Wow.
-  Yes!
(Seok Jin becomes the first candidate.)
Gosh, I don't want to do this any more.
- You're so lucky.
-  You're amazing, Sir.
Thank you, everyone.
This time, you should put it in the opposite side.
I haven't even given it a shot.
- So you don't play any more?
-  No, he doesn't.
- Then, let me try.
-  Okay.
Wow.
(Wow!)
I got goose bumps now.
I have goose bumps.
(His unluckiness reached the highest level.)
- This can't be manipulated.
-  Gosh.
- How can this happen?
-  We must air the unedited video.
- He didn't even think where to put.
-  Can this really happen?
(We'll show you the original video without any editing.)
Oh, please. Please.
Wow!
(After Seok Jin became the first candidate...)
Now I don't want to play this any more.
- You're so lucky.
-  You're amazing, Sir.
Thank you, everyone.
We have one more candidate to decide.
Did you feel something before put the sword in?
Yes, I did. I could even see it.
(They reset the roulette for the second candidate.)
Let's try from the opposite side this time.
I haven't even given it a shot.
- Let's try from the other side.
-  Okay.
- What a unlucky guy.
-  You start...
- Oh, you don't play it any more.
-  No, he doesn't.
- Then, I'll try.
-  Okay.
Wow!
I got goose bumps now.
I have goose bumps.
(He got it again at the chance of 1 out of 24.)
- He is really unlucky.
-  It's unbelievable.
Can this really happen?
- Gosh.
-  Amazing.
- You should see an exorcist.
-  What are you talking about?
- This is scary.
-  Gosh.
So, Kwang Soo and Seok Jin are the candidates.
If you want peace, please vote for me.
Actually, being in this group really hurts my pride.
If you earn a Go-Home Badge,
will you give it to one of them?
- Never.
-  Are you sure?
- Of course, because...
-  If you don't keep this promise,
and if I don't get any badge, I'll choose you as my partner.
Oh, really?
(Oh, really?)
Yes.
(Seok Jin's voice trembled.)
I really mean it.
- You do?
-  Yes.
You know he's reliable.
(He is always true to his words.)
It's the same as robbing the Badge.
That's too much.
(He feels something ominous.)
- Then, let's cast our ballots now.
-  Okay.
Please go in, Gary and Ji Hyo.
- Gosh.
-  It's hard to choose one.
(Who will become the last king?)
- This is the last election.
-  Please.
You chose him?
(Jae Seok voted for Kwang Soo.)
- It's Seok Jin.
-  Yes!
Good.
- Seok Jin.
-  Great!
What was that?
(Seok Jin released gas.)
(He got too excited and lost his contraction control.)
(Embarrassed)
Why do you do that?
You were too excited.
Were you that happy?
- How can you fart here?
-  Were you that happy?
- Because he's not young any more.
-  Right.
Did you fart because you're not so young?
- Seok Jin.
-  Yes, it's me.
- If I didn't vote for you...
-  It's over.
If I didn't vote for you...
It's over now.
- Seok Jin is amazing.
-  Yes!
- If I didn't vote for Kwang Soo...
-  He sent us telepathy.
- I'm sad.
-  It's a pity.
It's because you betrayed others a lot.
Do I get penalty again?
Right. That's right.
We almost forgot about the penalty.
(No one was thinking about the penalty.)
We almost forgot about it.
Right, we have the penalty.
I don't even know what we should do to penalise him.
(Unlucky Jae Seok got penalties three times in a row.)
(The third era is Seok Jin's rule. The rule of going home.)
- Dear me.
-  My goodness.
(Jae Seok wore stockings and short pants as a penalty.)
(Jae Seok is destined to get penalties.)
How can this happen?
I have some kind of feeling now.
- What do you mean?
-  You'd better call your wife now.
I feel that today's shooting will last even longer.
But if I give this Badge to Jae Seok,
I know Jong Kook will keep his words.
(My penalty partner is Seok Jin.)
I know Jong Kook will pick me as his partner for penalty.
But if I give it to Jong Kook,
then Jae Seok will choose me for his penalty partner.
The last king is the worst.
- This drives me crazy.
-  Seok Jin.
- What you have to decide...
-  Why did I become the king?
- What you have to decide is...
-  What?
who to stay with tonight.
Or you can be a cool guy if you give the badges to both of them.
Anyway, you'll receive penalty. So just be cool.
So call your wife.
You have nothing else to do here.
For an hour, think about who you'll stay with tonight.
- So I receive penalty anyway.
-  Right.
You know that Jong Kook is very true to his words.
I'm sure he'll pick me if I give the badge to Jae Seok.
Jae Seok will also do the same if I give it to Jong Kook.
I don't know why I have to worry about it although I have the badges.
(It's time for the final decision.)
- It's time for the final decision.
-  Okay.
(6 members with the badges may go home right away.)
We've prepared all your cars...
in the parking lot, so that you can go home...
- Oh, there they are.
-  if you receive the badge.
Whoever the last one becomes,
everyone can go home except the person who has to stay.
I see.
And the loser will make a phone call...
to call a partner.
(The loser can call a partner.)
- I should've turned off my phone.
-  Okay.
There are 2 people who have more than 2 Go-Home Badges.
You can choose a person each and give the Go-Home Badge.
Gary, you can choose first.
(Whoever is not chosen by Gary and Seok Jin will be the loser.)
- Okay.
-  Okay, I will.
(Gary chooses first.)
(Gary has one extra badge.)
(Jae Seok)
(Ji Hyo)
(Jong Kook)
(Only one of them will be saved.)
I will make it even harder for Seok Jin to choose.
(Who will be chosen by Gary?)
Really?
(It's unbelievable.)
I'll make it harder to choose.
(Gary chose Jong Kook.)
- Really?
-  I can't believe it.
(No one has expected that.)
(Now only Ji Hyo and Jae Seok are left.)
- Really?
-  You really chose Jong Kook?
I will make it so hard for Seok Jin to decide.
- You two are really close.
-  He really made it harder...
for Seok Jin to make a decision.
This is too difficult. You should've given it to Ji Hyo.
- Then it won't be fun!
-  I can't believe this.
You couldn't decide so I helped you out.
(Who will Seok Jin choose?)
- Seok Jin has two badges.
-  Why are you doing this?
This is too difficult.
You have two in your hand.
(Two badges...)
(and two people)
Should I just give away both and go with Kwang Soo?
(Do you want to go with me, Kwang Soo?)
Why are you choosing me? What have I done?
- You and me together.
-  Hey, stop it.
- That sounds like a good idea.
-  I think that sounds perfect.
- Please don't do this.
-  That's perfect.
You are a great judge.
Okay. You two, take this!
- That's amazing.
-  Are you really doing this?
- And you are going with me.
-  You don't have to do this.
- You never know.
-  I'll do as I want.
Please don't do this! Are you really giving the badges away?
- I'll handle this.
-  You went through a lot for this.
- You spent a whole day for badges.
-  I'll do as I want.
(Kwang Soo is about to cry.)
Okay.
(It's time for Seok Jin to decide.)
(Please choose me.)
(Not me)
Here.
(Whom did he choose?)
(Ji Hyo?)
(Jae Seok?)
(Kwang Soo?)
(Seok Jin chose Ji Hyo.)
Are you sure?
All right. Everyone, go home.
(Jae Seok is the loser.)
Please leave.
- This is even scarier.
-  I'm scared of Jae Seok's decision.
(It's time for Jae Seok to choose his partner for tonight.)
- You never know whom he'll choose.
-  I will count to three...
and I will pick the slowest.
(I will count to three and I will pick the slowest.)
(Time to go home.)
(Everyone runs away at full speed.)
Please don't call me.
(Please don't call me.)
I won't answer the phone.
- I won't answer.
-  I am getting tired now.
- You must leave before three.
-  Don't call me.
I don't want any phone call. Please don't.
I'll seat in the back.
Oh, please.
(Everyone is rushing home.)
Get in. Quickly.
Quickly.
- Are you leaving now?
-  Let's go.
Are you not?
He's so unpredictable.
I can pick the slowest car.
Let's go. Just go.
(The last car just left.)
It's time for me to decide.
(It is time for Jae Seok to make a phone call.)
(The member who receives the call must come back.)
(Hurry up and answer the phone)
(Who is the chosen one?)
(No!)
What is this?
(It is a call from Jae Seok.)
It's Jae Seok.
(No way)
No, no way.
(Just a while ago)
(He picked Jong Kook.)
Really?
I can't believe it.
(He may still remember the choice.)
(Is that the reason why he is calling Gary?)
Hey, Gary.
(Hey, Gary...)
Why did you choose Jong Kook?
(He did not forget.)
(Oh no.)
Jae Seok.
You can't do this!
Why not?
Then whom was I supposed to choose?
Hey, Gary.
You could give your badge to Ji Hyo.
You can't do this to me.
Oh, well.
Where are you about?
Let me see.
I guess I'm near Jamsil.
You are near Jamsil?
(It took three minutes to Jamsil.)
- Near Jamsil?
-  No!
It can't be!
(No! It can't be!)
Okay. See you later, Gary.
(Okay. See you later, Gary.)
(You just said "See you later.")
I see. Goodbye.
- Good night.
-  Good night.
(Yes)
(He had enough fun teasing Gary.)
(And he makes another phone call.)
(It's Ji Hyo this time.)
(Do you want me to go back?)
(Ji Hyo and Jae Seok were the last two members.)
Are you sure?
All right. Everyone, go home.
I will count to three.
And I will pick the slowest.
(After chosen by Seok Jin, she ran away as fast as she could.)
Please.
(Was I impudent to his eyes?)
- Hello.
-  Hi, Ji Hyo.
Yes.
I'm disappointed.
(Ji Hyo, I'm disappointed.)
You ran without a second thought.
Jae Seok, maybe you didn't see..
but I was the last among them. The feeling of guilt delayed me.
Really?
I wasn't... I wasn't happy leaving you behind alone.
Were you sorry?
Yes, I was.
(Please, Jae Seok.)
Okay, Ji Hyo.
You may leave.
All right. you may leave.
- Okay, Jae Seok.
-  Okay. Good night.
Okay. Good night.
Everyone seems happy.
(Jae Seok's phone calls are funny but scary.)
(I know your phone is ringing.)
(So answer it right now.)
(It's Jee Seok Jin.)
No!
No, it can't be!
(No.)
It's Jae Seok.
(Yu Jae Seok. His name seems so scary.)
Here.
(Seok Jin abandoned Jae Seok and chose Ji Hyo instead.)
All right.
Everyone, go home.
(It could be anyone but me.)
Please leave.
Hello?
Where are you going?
(Where are you going, Seok Jin?)
You called to say hi, didn't you?
- Didn't you, Jae Seok?
-  Where are you going?
- What?
-  Where are you going, Seok Jin?
I'm going home.
Where are you about?
- What?
-  Where are you about?
I am near the motorway, I guess.
(I am near the motorway, I guess.)
Okay, come! Come back.
(Seok Jin is the chose one.)
No!
Okay. Seok Jin is the person that I want.
My goodness.
Let's go back.
(Let's go back.)
(The tale of the first unluckiest man continues.)
(What is the penalty for tonight?)
It's name is Yong Ma Land.
What is this place?
So, do I have to go in?
Really?
In this abandoned amusement park,
- there is an abandoned piano.
-  Please, don't do this to me.
Do we really have to do this?
(They have to find an abandoned piano.)
Please go in and find the piano.
You have to sit...
and play "School Bell".
(They have to find an abandoned piano and play a song.)
This place is creepy.
(They get surprised very easily.)
- This is so scary.
-  I'm getting mad.
This place is driving me crazy.
(Where is the piano?)
- That was weird.
-  I have a chill.
- Where can we find the piano?
-  There.
Have you found it?
- There it is.
-  Is that the piano?
- What is it?
-  Here it is.
That is the piano.
(They have found the piano.)
- Oh my goodness.
-  What is this?
It's really scary.
- I'm going crazy.
-  It's cold out here.
(They have to sit together and play and sing "School Bell.")
- Here we go.
-  Here we go.
School bell's ringing, ding, ding, dong
Let's all gather now
(Jae Seok and Seok Jin have to sing "School Bell.")
The teacher is waiting for us
No. I don't like this song any more.
Lee Se Dol and AlphaGo played...
Lee was defeated again.
He was defeated twice in a row...
He resigned.
(But humans are not defeated yet.)
(The ultimate weapon, Hyeri)
(Song Min Ho and Nam Tae Hyun)
How can we beat that?
- Go!
-  Gosh!
It's thinking.
We can't cut him slack.
(Will artificial intelligence win or will human instinct win?)
Running Man has declared a war against machines.
(Next week at Running Man, Robot War)