(At a quiet beach on a foggy day)
(What will happen here today?)
I don't think there will be anyone to rescue today.
(Suspicious lifeguards are protecting this foggy beach.)
Look how foggy the sky is.
- Wow. - Yes, it's quite foggy.
Are we females or males?
(Mysterious gender identity)
(There's a blond lady with a moustache.)
- That's scary. - Oh, my.
(They need to change their hair styles first.)
Hello.
She looks very young today.
- You're right. - What do you eat?
You lost so much weight.
That's not true. I haven't.
(There they come!)
Oh, Jong Kook!
(Sexy masculine guys are riding through the foggy beach.)
- Hello. - Why are they...
- Hello. - Hi!
What's wrong with your shoulders?
(Team leader Jae Seok, an exotic-looking guy)
(Team leader Jong Kook, a muscular gangster)
Wow, you are here.
You guys look scary.
(Two charismatic team leaders show up.)
- My goodness. - You look scary.
- Hello. - They look scary.
Why are your shoulders so tense?
(Jong Kook versus Jae Seok)
Hi.
(Jong Kook powerfully takes his jacket off.)
Gosh, you scared me.
(Jae Seok feels unpleasant.)
He is really scary.
He looks like a character from a comic book.
I thought we're shooting an American animation film.
He looks just like that prince.
(They look perfectly the same.)
Good morning, everyone.
My goodness. Gosh.
- Anyway, - How are you guys?
- my team members surprised me. - Why?
Are you holding a concert today?
- We're the rescue team. - Are you sure?
What's your name?
- Sorry? - Don't you have an English name?
- Me? - Yes.
- I do have one. - What is it?
- It's Bruce. - Bruce?
It's Bruce.
- Bruce? - Yes.
- Are you Bruce Yu? - Yes.
- Oh, you're Bruce Yu. - What's your name?
I'm Cray.
- He's Crab. - Crab?
Oh, no.
- You like crabs. - He does.
- I'll catch you a crab later. - It's Cray.
So, he's Crab. What's yours?
- I'm Sophie. - You're Long.
(Jae Seok names Kwang Soo Long only because he's tall.)
- That is hilarious. - He's Long.
- Is he a guy or a girl? - His name is Long.
- He doesn't know that either. - That's not important.
- What's your name? - Me?
- I'm Mark. - Isn't it Bench?
What are you talking about?
- Bench? - He is Benchmarking.
(This American gangster is good at benchmarking.)
His name is Bench Mark.
What's your name?
I'm Red Song.
- Red Song? Isn't it Red Sun? - It's Red Song.
- I will hypnotise you. - In 1, 2, 3.
- Red Sun. - She's sleeping all the time.
- What's yours? - I'm Shark.
You're Jellyfish.
- You're Chakra. - No, I am not.
(Haha looks like Chakra members.)
Go, go, you look old
- Chakra. Good one. - Hello, Chun Bong.
No, I'm Gary Parker.
Gary Parker?
He's Pierrot.
- No. - Pierrot?
- His name is Chun Bong. - No, he's Pierrot.
Wait. We have four members...
- and they have three. - Right.
- I think it's because... - It means they have a guest member.
- That's right. - They'll have a guest member.
We'll have 2 guest members and you'll have 1 guest.
- What? - We have 2 guests and you have 1.
- Everyone knows that, you brat. - How can you say that to me?
- Did you say, "brat"? - You can't say that to him.
You know how close we are.
In the States, everyone is friends despite the age differences.
- This is not the States. - Do you want to die today?
Hey. My goodness.
- What are you doing? - Hey, come here.
- Gosh. - We are rivals.
What? Rivals?
- He's blocking him with his hands. - Step back.
- He's distancing himself. - He's scary.
- Wait. - Who is it?
(There is someone else on the beach other than them.)
(A tall trio shows up at Hanagae Beach.)
- Who is it? - He's Nichkhun.
- He's Nichkhun. - Oh no, he's on the Red Team?
- Lee Ki Woo is here, too. - She's Gyeong Ree.
- Oh, he's Lee Ki Woo. - Hello, Gyeong Ree.
- Welcome to Running Man. - Hello.
- Hello. - Gyeong Ree is here.
- Gyeong Ree, Nichkhun... - Hello.
- Hello, Nichkhun. - It's good to see you.
(Nichkhun, Gyeong Ree and Lee Ki Woo)
Wow, Gyeong Ree.
Hello, how are you?
- We're in the same team. - Right.
It's so nice to see you.
Kwang Soo, you are not so tall compared to Ki Woo.
- That's right. - He's really tall.
- He's so tall. - Kwang Soo, you're not that tall.
And Ki Woo is tall and handsome.
Although Ki Woo is handsome and tall,
- he's a bit sloppy. - Really?
No, he's not.
Ki Woo, please introduce yourself.
This is my first time to be on Running Man.
I'm an actor, Lee Ki Woo.
He's Chung Ah's man.
- He's adorable. - He's so cute.
- Is she his girlfriend? - He's Chung Ah's man.
Oh, really?
My goodness.
How can you not know that?
- I didn't know. - You're embarrassing him.
- I was just curious. - Dear me. Seriously.
(She's my girlfriend, Seok Jin.)
Nichkhun is here with us as well.
Hello, I'm almost a Running Man member. I'm Nichkhun.
(Nichkhun appeared on Running Man 11 times.)
It's been a long time.
- It's been so long. - He looks like an American guy.
Your hairstyle looks good.
- He really looks like an American. - Goodness.
We have Gyeong Ree in our team!
(Summer beauty, Gyeong Ree)
You're so beautiful.
Gyeong Ree from Nine Musics...
- is here with us. - It's Muses.
Right. Nine Muses.
I am sorry, but I'm sure...
you all saw how Seok Jin just corrected me with her group name.
But when Gyeong Ree was coming out, he said, "Who is she?"
- You're too mean. - You're unbelievable.
- Gosh. - She was just too far away.
- How can you not recognise her? - He's unbelievable.
- Really. - Everyone knows Gyeong Ree.
- Please come to the back. - His eyes are bad.
- They are. - Yes.
Why did you put on the sunglasses all of a sudden?
I wanted to look at Ki Woo.
He's cute.
- She's good. - She's acting like an old woman.
- Gosh... - What has gotten into you?
- Why did you change so much? - She adores him.
- I wanted to see Ki Woo. - She adores him.
You must be looking to buy some lands here.
- The red hair suits her well. - It does suit her well.
- New members have joined us. - Right.
Should we give them English names?
- You can call me Nick. - Nick.
- Nick is good. - Nicky.
How about you, Ki Woo?
- Panick? - "Panick" is a little...
- Just be Thomas. - Thomas?
Thomas the train is long.
- Great. - The Thomas train is long.
- You can be Thomas. - Thomas.
- How about you, Gyeong Ree? - I want to be Sandy.
- Sandy. Why? - Yes.
- There's sand here. - That's perfect.
The name Sandy and the sand go well together.
Sandy. It sounds tough.
Sandy, you are tougher than I thought.
The name has an impact.
- She's Sandy. - Isn't it nice?
- Sandy is tougher than I thought. - Is she?
Sandy is nice. We will call her Sandy from now on.
(The three new members are ready!)
Today, there will be a joint training, and one of...
the two team leaders will be promoted as the captain.
How about Chun Bong?
- You can be Sunset then. - Seok Jin is like a doctor.
We're rivals.
(They'll do unexpected missions. What will happen to them?)
(Suspicious R Rescue)
(The siren goes off.)
- It's an emergency. - What's going on?
(Why is the siren going off?)
They're bringing out a television.
- What's going on? - There's a television.
(They bring out a television on the middle of the beach!)
- Will they really play something? - What is that?
- Will a person come out of it? - What is that?
Maybe someone will open the screen and come out.
What was his name?
(Who is he?)
Maybe someone will open the screen and come out.
- Hello, everyone. - David Hasselhoff.
David Hasselhoff.
(He's the captain of "Baywatch", a popular TV series from the 90s.)
Hello, everyone.
(Why is David Hasselhoff here?)
Good job ensuring maritime safety in the honour of...
- Suspicious R Rescue. - I know him.
I've heard about Team Leader Kim Jong Kook's recent...
take-down of Jaws which appeared on the beach.
I've also heard about how Team Leader Yu Jae Seok...
caught the pervert on the beach.
I'm pleased because it reminds me of my heyday.
I see.
The two team leaders' promotion to the captain depends on this mission.
(One of them will be promoted as a captain?)
The result of the joint training...
will determine their promotion.
The leader of the team that wins on the joint training...
will be promoted as the captain.
Yes!
And his team members will also be rewarded.
- Reward is nice. - The losing team...
will pay for their defeat.
You'll be gaining points on every training mission.
The points will be important...
for the team leader evaluation. So the team members...
- should try your best. - Let's go for it!
Now, get changed into the training suits...
- and gather here again. - Okay. Let's go!
- Let's go! - Let's get trained!
The team members of the winning team...
will get a golden whistle as a reward.
I want that.
And the team member of the losing team will be flogged.
- We'll be flogged! - Stop it.
- That really hurts. - I know.
- The bruise lasted for a week. - Seriously.
Flogging is good.
Gary was flogged, but that part wasn't aired.
- It wasn't? - They flogged him hard...
and they didn't even show it on the television.
I'll count. In 1, 2, 3.
(Gary got flogged hard.)
(It was really fun and exciting, but we didn't have time for it.)
It hurts so much that he can't make any sound.
Why did you edit it out?
Today, one of you will become the captain.
Please do your best to win the mission.
- Please change into the suits. - Okay.
- And we will begin. - All right.
- Let's go! - Go!
- Can I talk to the team leaders? - We have to talk in English.
- Why are you calling us? - That's really lovely.
And the Red Team.
- Get some ice cream. - This is wrong.
- Why? - Why aren't we getting ice cream?
- What did you do wrong? - I don't know.
- Change into training suits. - Why aren't we getting ice cream?
Where's our ice cream?
- Why can't we eat ice cream? - I don't know.
- Is it because we didn't wait? - Only Red Team can eat it?
We must've done something wrong.
Why don't we get ice cream?
Why doesn't everyone get ice cream?
(We want to know the truth behind the ice cream discrimination.)
Isn't it strange?
Let's just eat first and see.
Perhaps we will get disadvantaged from eating this.
(He feels uncomfortable.)
Thank you.
Since you're giving them to us, we will eat them.
(They feel uncomfortable eating the ice cream.)
I think our team leader did something wrong.
(Is that what happened?)
Today,
every mission comes with a suspicious mission.
What is that?
There are special missions for the team leaders.
These missions will allow the captain to check...
if the team leaders are doing well in leading the team.
- Is that right? - The first mission was...
the team with a member who takes off the wig first loses.
Kwang Soo was the one.
(The problematic team member is Lee Kwang Soo.)
- That brat. - That's why the Red Team...
got ice cream as a reward.
Awesome.
(They were moving to another place several minutes ago.)
(And Kwang Soo took off the wig.)
(It's so cool!)
That's why the team leaders have to try harder.
Does that even make sense?
- This is... - Kwang Soo has to lose alone.
- Why do the team have to suffer? - Can we tell the team members?
We can't? All right.
On every game, the team leader will be evaluated.
- This is too much. - The moment you talk about it,
- you lose. - How can we not tell them?
- You can't tell them. - We have to blame him though!
- You... - I'm craving ice cream!
Just go to him and slap him for no reason.
(It's nice to feel the air.)
- So do not... - Let's go.
- talk about it. - All right.
Let's go! Don't you dare talk about it.
(The training starts with much secret and frustration.)
(The real competition begins.)
- Let's go! - Start!
- This is... - Why do we look so weak?
- This is unfair. - Why are we a team?
- Why did we become a team? - It's good enough.
- We have Gyeong Ree. - I can do well.
- I know. - We can do well.
At least the vibe is good.
- What is that? - What's that?
Is it another obstacle game?
- Hey. - It's an obstacle game.
(The obstacle road is stretched along the beach!)
- This is crazy. - What's this?
Gary, this is...
- What's up with the angle? - This is too much.
It's too much.
- The captain planned it. - It's going to be fun.
- The captain did? - He should've come himself.
Everyone, there are...
hidden missions everywhere.
- What did you say? - What?
We all...
- We... - We lived abroad for many years.
- Is that right? - That's why he can't pronounce.
- Is that right? - No, it's not that.
It's been a long time since Ki Woo's been on a variety show.
- He is so tall. - In the past,
- he was in a lot of variety shows. - Many years ago.
- He was on "X-Man"? - Yes.
(He appealed his charms with his stiff and long body.)
(He captured girls' hearts with his cute behaviour.)
He used to act like Kwang Soo.
- Right. - Is he sloppy like Kwang Soo?
The tall ones tend to be sloppy.
- But he's balanced unlike this guy. - That's right.
- No, we are similar. - They are very different.
- You have to be this big. - His head is so small.
His head is so small, and his shoulders are broad.
If you're not going to be like him, it's better to be short like me.
- What's wrong with me? - It's better to be me.
- It's better to be him. - I hate him.
He's fine.
- What's going on? - What's going on?
- The television is here again. - There it comes.
It's Mr Hasselhoff.
- Mr Hasselhoff. - Are you all ready?
- Yes. - Next competition is...
"Beach Relay", which will test your teamwork.
- It's going to be a relay. - The team members will stand...
in front of the four obstacles on the beach.
You will pass the rescue tube baton...
and the team that finishes first will win.
- You will play three rounds, - So this is it.
and the team that wins twice will win.
Plan a strategy and place the right person for each course.
- We will play three rounds. - All right.
Let's check your abilities.
- So we have to pass the tube. - Yes.
The first course is running.
- Please place one member there. - Gary can do that.
The second course is deflating the giant tube.
You have to deflate it and put it in a box.
- Kwang Soo can do that. - Kwang Soo can do that.
- We'll place two people there. - Two people.
- We have to deflate it. - Then pass the baton again...
and crawl through the tires.
- That's the most important one. - Then pass the baton...
to the last member in front of the slide.
When the last member climbs up and comes down the slide, you win.
- Let's gather our hands. - All right.
(They put their hands together with determination.)
- All right. - One, two.
- That was so funny. - Why?
- Gyeong Ree. - Gyeong Ree was...
We did this, and Gyeong Ree...
put her hand from the bottom.
Why? Is my hand filthy?
- That's not it. - What was that about?
- My palms are sweaty. - That was too obvious.
- She almost put it on top. - Let's put our hands together.
(They try it again.)
(Screaming)
What was that?
Do you think my hand is dirty, Gyeong Ree?
- We're on the same team. - It's okay, Gyeong Ree.
- What's wrong? - Gyeong Ree, that wasn't nice!
No, I have sweaty hands.
- You have sweaty hands? - What did she do?
- She seriously doesn't like him. - We have to be one at heart.
I think I offended somebody.
Let's do a cheer. We have to be one.
- Let's do a cheer! - We're falling apart already.
- Isn't this too much? - Let's go.
- One, two, three. Go! - Don't do that.
- Let's go. - You go first.
- One, two, three. Go! - One, two, three. Go!
(Blue Team finally does their cheer.)
Who's fast?
Then, Kwang Soo should...
Should Kwang Soo and I deflate the tube?
- You should do this one. - It's too hard.
- You can do it. - You should do it for the team.
- Today's your day. - You should do hard ones.
- You have to do it. - How do I go on my back?
Do this one.
- Who will run? - Ki Woo can run.
- He can do it. - Okay, he can run.
- You have to deflate the balloon. - Jong Kook should do it.
I'll do that, then.
- We should do it together. - Then I'll do that.
Okay, that sounds like a plan.
Beginning's the most important.
- Let's go. - Let's go!
- We're going to fight desperately. - It might take an hour to finish.
It's too far.
- What's this on the back? - It's a parachute.
Do we run with this?
It's a parachute.
(We're supposed to run with a parachute?)
I picked the wrong one.
- Is that how they should run? - I see.
- What's that? - I thought you just run.
- This is no joke. - What's that?
- Don't they just run? - What's that?
- Hey, Gary! - This is no joke.
- Isn't that a parachute? - This is no joke.
- I thought they just run. - They might fly away.
Let's go, Pierrot!
Let's go, Ki Woo!
- Let's go, Ki Woo! - Let's go!
- You have to move forward. - You can do it!
(Gary versus Ki Woo)
- Let's go! - Let's go!
- Sparta! - You have to win, Gary!
(The first members are ready to go.)
(The first runner is the most important in a relay.)
(Gary versus Ki Woo)
Ready!
(Round 1 starts.)
(Flapping)
(They both start strong.)
- They're flying away. - Come on.
- They'll fly away. - Gary's fast.
(It's difficult to move forward with the parachutes on their backs.)
Gary's fast.
(It's difficult even to walk.)
(They clench their teeth and run for their teams.)
Good. We're fast. Ki Woo's fast.
(Ki Woo's faster due to his height.)
Gary, Gary!
(But the competition is not over yet.)
(Gary chases Ki Woo.)
- He's good. - Good job, Gary!
- Hurry up! - This is it!
Why does Gary look so slow?
- Let's go! - Gary!
Gary is good, too.
Good job, Gary!
- You're not far too behind. - We got it.
- Why does Gary look so slow? - Good job, Gary!
- Gary! - Hurry.
- Good job, Gary. - Give me the baton.
- Good job, Gary. - Gary!
- Good job. It's okay. - Pass me the baton!
- Give me the baton! - Good job. We're pretty close.
I'm done.
(The second course starts.)
- Let's go! - Let's start.
I feel like my thighs are going to burst.
Sit on it.
Let's go, let's go!
We have to win this round.
(They have contrasting styles.)
Jump faster!
- I don't think it's working. - Jong Kook!
- This might not work, Kwang Soo. - Why?
You have to press on it.
- Press on it. - Hey, Jae Seok!
- You have to press on it. - Jae Seok, press on the sides.
- Press on it. - No, the air's coming out.
I think it's faster to press on it.
It is faster that way.
(They look like a bullfrog deflating a tube.)
- Can't you fold it now? - We're much faster, Jae Seok.
This is no joke.
(Are you faster?)
(If that's the case...)
It's working.
- Grab the wings. - Hey, hey!
(Jong Kook rips the flamingo open.)
(Deflating)
- What's that? You can't rip it! - He ripped it.
- You can't rip it. - That's not cheating.
- What did you say? - Ripping it is not cheating.
- What did you say? - He ripped it.
- My gosh! - You can't do that.
- He ripped it. - You can't do that.
How do you rip it?
Just rip it.
- How... - I can't rip it.
Power!
(Ripping)
(Jae Seok removes a wing.)
He's taking the head off.
- That looks odd. - Take the wing off.
- This is cruel! - Why are you so cruel?
One, two, three!
It came off.
(They take the head off, too.)
- How do you do this? - You can't use your teeth.
Hey!
(They're impressive.)
- Throw it. - Hurry, hurry.
(Red Team is about to close the lid.)
- Throw it. - You can do it!
- Go. - Hurry, hurry.
- Hey, hurry! - You're good.
- Switch. - You're good.
- Good. - Where's the baton?
- You have to pass the baton. - I did.
(Haha digs like a mole.)
- That looks hard. - Gyeong Ree!
- Let's go! - Gosh!
- Come on. - Gosh.
- Let's go, Seok Jin! - Go in.
(All eyes are on them.)
Seok Jin.
- Send the baton first. - Send it over.
- Send it over first. - Put it on your stomach.
- Hey. - Send it over.
- Put it on your stomach and crawl. - Send it over first.
Watch your cap.
- Good job. - Good. That's big enough.
- Let's go. - You have to put your head through.
- Good job. - Watch your head.
- Put your head through. - I think he's stuck.
Seok Jin! What are you doing?
- You have to dig in front of you. - Hurry, Haha.
(Seok Jin! Dig in front of you.)
(This is just too funny.)
Haha is about to finish.
(Haha is nearly at the finishing point.)
My goodness.
- There's only one hole. - Push me!
There's only one hole at the end!
That's good. You're almost done.
- You're done. - Push him harder.
(Haha reaches the exit.)
Seok Jin, hurry up and hold Haha's feet!
- I can't get through. - Do it the other way.
Hurry, hurry.
- Come on. - Go, go!
- Let's stop playing. - Go!
(Haha hands the baton to Nichkhun.)
- Should we give up? - You can't go.
- Hurry. - What's that?
What's that?
(He manages to escape.)
- Gyeong Ree! - Look at her.
Stand your ground, Gyeong Ree!
- Gyeong Ree! - Oh, gosh.
He's too fast.
(He's super fast.)
- I wish this is a test run. - You're not even close.
- What's this mess? - Try going through.
(Gasping)
(Sliding)
(He's relaxed.)
(Hopping)
(Red Team wins thanks to their best players.)
- I'm sorry, Gyeong Ree. - You didn't even get to play.
- I told you I can't do this. - That wasn't intense at all.
I'm sorry, Gyeong Ree!
- I was supposed to dig here. - I know why you got mad.
- You're supposed to dig near it. - You should have told me.
I told you like five times! I told you to dig near it.
- You should have told me. - That's what I was saying.
- We kept on telling you! - We said it like five times.
- You're supposed to dig here. - You need to dig here.
You're supposed to dig here.
I'll do this one.
- Try it. - Do it, Gyeong Ree.
- She was frustrated. - She's mad.
- We're sorry, Gyeong Ree. - It's okay.
- Gyeong Ree. - Let's go!
Okay!
You don't care because you have gloves on.
- I have gloves on. - One, two, three. Go!
Let's win this one.
- You're no match for us. - Just watch.
Let's just flog them.
- Just you wait. - Come on!
- You got lucky with your team. - This isn't fun at all.
- Watch where you put your foot. - What?
- Where are you putting it on? - There's nothing wrong with it.
- For goodness' sake. - What's there to complain?
Take your foot off.
(Staggering)
- See? He's losing balance. - You almost sprained your ankle.
- That hurt my pride. - I thought you were Shim Hyung Rae.
That hurt my pride. You try it.
- Hey, take your foot off. - Why?
Listen when I say it nicely.
- He won't budge. - Hey.
- He's driving me insane. - Just do this!
(Kwang Soo kicks him in the groin.)
That's how you're supposed to do it!
Why were you trying to do it like this?
- That's how you do it. - I was just showing an example.
- I'm just showing them an example. - This guy.
- Don't overreact. - Good job, Kwang Soo.
That's just another way.
Kwang Soo has anger management issues.
- I can't stand him. He angers me. - He's just like that.
Red Team takes the first mission.
- Let's overtake them. - We have three rounds.
- It's best 2 out of 3. - This is just 1 round.
- Do you understand how this works? - Yes.
- Only now? - We get it now.
Before you return to your positions, let me call out the team leaders.
- Sure. - Sure.
- Just them? - What is it?
- There's something going on. - There is.
Why do you give this to us in front of the other members?
- What's that? - They keep asking us about it.
- What is it? - You lose if you give it away.
(You lose if you give it away.)
- You can't say it. - This is ridiculous!
- What's this? - We lose if you tell us?
- Oh, my. - What is it?
Are you a spy? What was all that about?
- Are you a spy? - We thought we were a team.
- This guy! - Come on.
- What is it? - You're making me grab your collar.
- There's something going on. - There's something we don't know.
- There's something going on. - Look at them.
Our team members are bad in games but good at speculating.
- Let's just go. - Do we rip name tags?
Ki Woo and Nichkhun aren't asking any questions.
- Their team... - Look at them.
Shouldn't we take his shoes off?
- I know, there's something. - There's nothing!
- This is good for us, right? - Of course, it is.
We know how this goes so focus on the game.
- All right. - Don't doubt anything.
- Let's get ready. - Me?
What's going on?
- Kwang Soo! - Let's go!
(Let's go...)
(Blue Team fails the mission.)
What's wrong?
- Let's go! - What? Why are you giggling?
- Why are you giggling? - Is something going on?
- What is it? - This look fishy.
- I'm going to lose it. - What is it?
- What? - My goodness.
What is it?
All right. Let's start.
Let get started.
- What? - My gosh.
- There's something going on. - What's wrong with him?
(Thanks to Kwang Soo, Blue Team has lost the mission.)
("Beach Relay", Round 2)
Let's go!
(Kwang Soo versus Nichkhun)
(Running)
- Oh, my gosh. - Go, Kwang Soo!
Come on.
You're good. You're doing well.
(Who will win? Long with long limbs or athletic Nick?)
Kwang Soo is fast.
- Go, Kwang Soo! - Kwang Soo is good.
He's quite good.
- You're altering the wind's course. - Good. Kwang Soo is doing well.
Kwang Soo is good.
(Long is slightly ahead.)
- This way. - Kwang Soo is doing well.
(I'm pretty good at running.)
Kwang Soo doesn't look so attractive running.
(Good at running versus good looking)
(They arrive at the second spot about the same time.)
- Put it over your shoulder. - Take the air out of the tube.
We can do this!
- Take the air out. - Take the air out. Hurry.
- I'm exhausted. - Hey!
(Ripping)
- Wow, look. - You should rip it, too.
(It's like they are ripping the wings off a chicken.)
- How should I grab this? - Here. Grab here.
(They are all ripping the tube.)
Rip it off!
- Go! - Here. We can rip each parts off.
That's so great!
(He looks really brutal and manly.)
That's amazing.
- Show me a heart sign. - Don't take your eyes off. Focus.
All right, I'm done. I'm finished.
- Gyeong Ree says you are amazing. - Of course I am.
(Red Team is almost finished.)
We're done!
- Okay. - Let's put this in.
- Put this inside here. - Go, guys.
(Blue Team's tube still has plenty of air in it.)
Hey, come on.
(Packaging completed)
- You're doing great. - Hurry up.
Okay. It's done.
- No! - How can they do it so fast?
(Team Red is ready to start the third course.)
- Sorry, Gyeong Ree. - My goodness. What should I do?
Put the baton in first.
(We're almost there.)
- That's it. Dig around the tire. - Oh, gosh.
- Give me the baton for a second. - My gosh.
Yes, I think you can. You can crawl underneath now.
- Go, Gyeong Ree - The hole's big enough.
You can crawl underneath now.
- Good. - Go, Gyeong Ree.
- She got it. - Great.
Good. You're doing well.
- I can hold it for you. - Good. You can go in.
(She surely knows how to crawl.)
(G.I. Ji Hyo crawls and proceeds without hesitation.)
Wow. Good job.
- Awesome. - Go. Go and grab her.
(Gyeong Ree finally catches up and starts to chase Ji Hyo.)
- Hurry up, Ji Hyo. - Hurry.
- Grab her, Gyeong Ree. - Go, Gyeong Ree.
- Grab her ankle. - Let go of me!
(Ji Hyo kicks Gyeong Ree fiercely.)
Go away!
- Gyeong Ree, grab her from behind. - Catch her.
I'm sorry, Ji Hyo!
- Come on. - Grab her tightly.
- Just push her away. - I'm sorry, Ji Hyo!
I'm sorry.
- Come out. Hurry. - Gyeong Ree, crawl out.
Ji Hyo, hurry up. Come on out.
- Go. Hurry. - Come on, Gyeong Ree.
- His microphone! - Look at the microphone.
- You're nearly there. - Which way?
Hey, Ki Woo.
(Blue Team just has passed the second tire.)
Hurry up, Ki Woo!
(Will Red Team take their victory like this?)
(If we lose again, the first round goes to them.)
(I won't let that happen.)
- Hey, Ki Woo. - Easy, Ki Woo. Go easy.
Ki Woo!
He's chasing you, Ki Woo!
- He's chasing you. - Give me that baton.
(Grabbing)
(Jae Seok grabs his ankle.)
(Sliding)
(Jae Seok is doing his best to stop him.)
- Can he do that? - Is that possible?
Jae Seok. Here!
Go, Jae Seok. Just go.
(Blue Team's baton has arrived just in time.)
(The game isn't over yet. It has just begun.)
- I'm exhausted. - Let's do this.
No, we can't lose this!
- That's right. - We have to win this.
(Ki Woo is tired already. Jae Seok easily dominates him.)
- Hurry up. - Oh, no.
(Jae Seok is really fast.)
Wow. Jae Seok is really good.
(What's going on?)
- What's going on? - Wow. Look at Jae Seok.
(Jae Seok gets to the top at once.)
He's almost there.
He's nearly there. We got this.
(Slipping)
Okay!
(Experienced Jae Seok overwhelmed Ki Woo with his skills.)
(Blue Team has won the second round.)
Well done, Jae Seok.
Good job.
(Our leader is the best.)
Well done.
Anyway, Jae Seok...
which one is more important? This game or the secret mission?
- Stop asking. - I'm really curious.
- I really want to know. - We won the game anyway.
Look. They are not curious about it at all.
Is it because the mission was not important at all?
(Only the Blue Team is full of doubts.)
Just tell us.
- That's not important. - Then just tell me.
Which is more important? Game or the secret mission?
The game is more important, of course.
Why do you keep giving us the mission in front of them?
- He just said, "the mission". - So is that really a mission?
- Mission? - You said "the mission".
It's not that mission.
- What are you talking about? - Was it really a mission?
There is definitely a mission. We ate the ice cream earlier.
We're just afraid of him and can ask what it is about.
- We're aware of it, though. - Let me tell you one thing.
You ruined everything. Everything.
- What was it about? - Our team members are doing well.
I mean, really well.
Can't you tell us?
(I want to ask him, but he looks so scary.)
Blue Team has won the second round.
That was a worthless victory and you know it.
That mission thing is a complete nonsense, anyway.
What? What about the mission?
- I get it. Today, it's all about... - Close your eyes for a second.
It's not a team game. Today's game is an individual one.
- Seok Jin... - No, it's not.
- It is. I know it. - No, it's a team game.
It's not what you think.
(Suspicious lifeguards are becoming more suspicious.)
- Choose your players for a run-off. - Okay.
What is our plan?
Let's not rip the tube this time. Okay?
- Let's just deflate it. - Yes, let's do that.
- So we'll take the air out only. - Yes. Don't rip it this time.
Okay, I got it.
It's good to win this game, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
But I think...
maybe this game is meaningless after all.
(They have no idea what's going on.)
(Kwang Soo, please!)
(Kwang Soo, my man.)
- Let's go! - Ready!
(The Final Round)
Gosh.
(Kwang Soo versus Ki Woo)
He's really good at running.
(Tall men's race begins.)
- Both are really good. - Ki Woo runs quite fast, too.
- Both are good. - Both of them are strong.
(Who will win this match? Will Kwang Soo win?)
(Or will the guest, Ki Woo, win?)
Both of them are strong.
Kwang Soo is faster. He's faster.
(Marching of the Titans)
Kwang Soo is faster.
(It's really a close match.)
It must be really hard to run like that.
Good job.
(They begin to deflate the dolphin tubes.)
Well done, Kwang Soo.
(Gosh. I'm so tired.)
I'm so exhausted.
- Press the tube with your knees. - Keep pressing it.
- Just keep pressing it. - I need your heart cheering.
- You need to keep pressing it. - Really?
(Seok Jin's hopping actually delayed Blue Team.)
They're already doing that way.
(Red Team is pressing the tube already.)
We lost already.
- It's really slow. - Come on. Please.
(Then I'll...)
- I'm really tired. - You must be.
(I'm so tired. I want to lean on the dolphin.)
(Kwang Soo joined the cheating.)
I'm so tired.
(I'll join, too.)
(Both teams are trying to deflate the tube as quickly as possible.)
- Press it. - I'm so tired.
- Is the air coming out now? - I'm so tired.
- Kwang Soo, you're leaning on me. - Seok Jin.
(What is he doing?)
(Kwang Soo is scratching the tube to make a hole.)
(Tearing)
- Hey, that was strangely quick. - No, that was all right.
(That was strangely fast, wasn't it?)
- Come on. Move up. - It's done.
(With Kwang Soo cheating,)
(Blue Team's tube is fully deflated.)
- No way. I'll do the same. - Let's go. Hurry.
- Let's go. - What are you doing?
- Gosh. - We're already late.
- Hurry up. - Grab it.
Good. We're on the right track.
(Both teams end up ripping the tubes.)
- It's done. - Go. Hurry.
- Hurry up. - Go, Gyeong Ree.
- Hurry up. - We must win this, Gyeong Ree.
Take your time.
- You can do it, Gyeong Ree. - Gyeong Ree, come on!
Please, Gyeong Ree!
(We'll win this time.)
- Go, Gyeong Ree. - Hurry!
- Come on, Gyeong Ree. - Crawl in.
- That's it. - Good job!
(Ji Hyo the Red Song follows her fiercely.)
(Gyeong Ree crawls in.)
- Good. - You're fast.
You're really fast.
- You're doing well, Gyeong Ree. - Come on. You can crawl in now.
- Good. - You're fast.
(Gyeong Ree raises her pace.)
- You are doing well. - We got this.
- You must come out. - She's not out yet.
(Gyeong Ree hasn't come out yet, but Gary tries to run with baton.)
- You must wait for her to come out. - You must wait.
- Not yet. - Wait for Gyeong Ree.
(Gyeong Ree crawls out.)
- Gosh. - Hold on, Gyeong Ree.
(But it's no use. Gary is in the air now.)
- Gosh. - Hurry up, Ji Hyo.
- My ribs! - Hurry, Ji Hyo.
(Ji Hyo crawls out.)
- We must stop him. - My ribs hurt.
- Hey. - All right. It's time.
(Gary versus Jong Kook)
What are you doing? Where is the baton?
Here. This way.
- Go for it! - Go, Gary!
Gary. Oh, No!
(Gary slips all of a sudden.)
(Because of Gary's mistake, Red Team is ahead now.)
Hey, no!
(My gosh...)
- Grab the rope. - Come on, Gary.
(This will the turning point of this race.)
(Who will be able to climb up the Suspicious Hill first?)
(Will it be Gary or Jong Kook?)
(Flinching)
(Jong Kook is in danger!)
(Jong Kook flinches.)
(Will Gary be able to turn the game around, again?)
Run for it, Gary!
(They're quite close.)
(Slipping)
No. Gary!
(Gary, no!)
- No. Gary! - Please!
(Jong Kook manages to run down the hill first...)
(because of Gary's mistake.)
(No!)
- No! - We got this!
We'll be flogged today.
(I think I'll be flogged today.)
I'll be flogged.
(The relay is over!)
Gary.
Did you lose?
(He shakes his head.)
Did you win?
- Really? - Did we win?
- Really? - What?
- Did he win? - How did you lose?
Gary!
- Really? - What happened?
- Is it true, Gary? - Yes.
- Come here. - In 1, 2, 3. Yes!
Really?
- Kang Gary! - How did you win, anyway?
(What happened?)
(Jong Kook was ahead of the race when he jumped down the slide.)
(Running)
(Oh no, my baton!)
(Jong Kook drops the baton at a crucial moment.)
(In an instant,)
(Gary scores first.)
I lost.
Didn't we win?
Did we not win?
(Gary of Blue Team gets lucky and wins.)
How could you drop it?
I dropped it.
- That was great. - I made a mistake.
Gary, good job.
My heart is about to burst.
Blue Team wins.
(Blue Team wins the "Beach Relay" with a score of 2 to 1.)
- We got lucky in the end. - That was great.
I can't believe this.
Team leaders, please step forward.
- Again? - We'll get another mission.
Don't call us out in public.
- They'll give us a mission. - Goodness.
- It's the third mission. - I'll tell you quietly.
- How could Jong Kook lose? - He could have lost on purpose.
- What is it? - I'm also curious.
I'm very curious.
- Okay. - Is this the mission?
How could you give us such a mission?
- It must be a mission. - Well...
You said, "How is this a mission?"
Are we just pawns in a competition between you two?
- Definitely not. - What are we?
- Aren't we also participating? - Are we pawns?
- What are we? - What does that make us?
Ki Woo, that's a misunderstanding.
- It's a misunderstanding. - It's not like we don't know.
Just answer this.
Is what they're doing more important than what the rest of us are doing?
- Which one? - I wish we were more important.
- This hurts my feelings. - Come on.
- I... - Which one is more fun?
Are we on Running Man or The Two Men?
- No. - Goodness.
The main actor has been Kwang Soo all this time.
What about me?
Kwang Soo has played a crucial part so far.
- Do you remember that? - I haven't done anything.
He said you've been the main actor.
I haven't done anything.
(What is the reason?)
(Blue Team: 20, Red Team: 10)
(Special training to become the best rescuing team continues.)
- Let's go. - We're ready.
Let's go and finish it quickly!
The camera is on now.
- Look at all the people. - One, two, three.
- Yes! - That was amazing.
Was that a mission?
- That looked like a mission. - It wasn't.
It seems like Jae Seok finished a mission successfully.
- No. - Pardon me, but when I'm resting,
please stop looking at me in a weird way.
- We didn't. - Don't poke me either.
- We have to find it. - It's about this size.
We won't betray our team members,
- so relax. - In your team,
- Relax. - Ki Woo and Nichkhun...
- don't care about that at all. - It's because they're afraid.
- No, they trust me. - I can't even be suspicious of him.
- In my opinion, - They trust the team leader.
Haha keeps being suspicious of you, but those two look scared.
I'm trying to stimulate them, but no one is following me.
- Why aren't you two suspicious? - They just trust me.
Ki Woo, why aren't you suspicious of him?
- It's frustrating. - I saw it already.
- What did you see? - I saw your stomach.
What are you doing?
- He's hiding it somewhere there. - We don't have anything.
It's in his shoes.
Ki Woo gave up everything...
and only wants to be paid.
He wants to be paid.
We don't have to worry about not getting paid.
- Don't worry about that. - He asked me very seriously.
I'd like to say something but I can't.
Ki Woo has changed a lot compared to before.
I like how he's become more realistic.
This training is to test one's strength.
It's called "Wear the Socks".
- I love strength tests. - I can't believe this.
It's a one-to-one competition.
Both players pull the rope while being inside tubes.
The player who puts on all the wet socks...
in the bowl wins.
The first team to score three points wins.
I'd like to know...
if this game is more important than the team leaders' mission.
- The game is more important. - What does that make us?
- Goodness. - Which is more important?
Which is more important?
- Which is more important? - Is it the game or the leaders?
- What's more important? - This is driving me crazy.
- Gary, that's not right. - Stop it.
- Kwang Soo, you can do it! - Okay.
The next player is Ki Woo!
Yes.
Ji Hyo, step forward.
Players of similar height should contend.
- Be like him to be tall. - Come on.
We want to be tall like Ki Woo, but not like Kwang Soo.
That looks like some kind of sign.
Did you do something to me?
- Did you do something? - It's a slapping mission.
Did you do something?
- He missed the last slap. - What's wrong with you?
- I dodged the last one. - Why don't you try it?
- He only slapped me twice. - No!
- You're driving me crazy! - Don't be easy on him.
Do I need to slap you back?
No, that wasn't a mission.
- Was that a mission? - This is driving me nuts.
Gosh, I want to know.
- Gary, that's not it. - What are you doing?
Protect your cheeks.
- Wait a minute. - I'm already infected.
Be suspicious of Jong Kook, too, guys!
Just relax.
Let's be suspicious!
You're the only one being suspicious.
- Let him be suspicious. - I think he did something to me!
Stop it.
Even Gyeong Ree is suspicious of me.
- Don't slap me. - Let's start the competition.
- Please win. - Do it without your shoes on.
(Sighing)
Ki Woo seems very worried.
I haven't talked for too long.
Ki Woo said,
"It's really hard for me."
- We're only starting. - Take off your shoes.
His role in "The Classic" was a boy who collapsed all the time.
That's right.
He's collapsing.
- He's collapsing. - What's wrong with you?
Why did you collapse so fast?
- What's wrong? - In the movie "The Classic"?
("The Classic", 2003)
(He collapsed...)
(and collapsed.)
(He collapsed whenever he got the chance.)
- What's wrong? - In the movie "The Classic"?
You kept collapsing.
I feel dizzy whenever that movie is mentioned.
He always collapsed in the movie.
To me, you are
Like the sunset
- Like the sunset - He collapsed again.
Please step forward.
All right.
Don't do that.
You can do it!
(The first round of a game is always important.)
(Who will wear the three socks first?)
- You can do it! - Get ready.
Kwang Soo!
(He pulls him all the way.)
What's going on today?
He's doing well.
- What's going on today? - He's doing well.
Kwang Soo, you should pull too.
(Thanks to Gyeong Ree's cheer, Kwang Soo regains energy.)
- Come on. - Grab one sock.
(Ki Woo easily grabs his first sock.)
- Good. - Follow him to get tall.
You're doing well, Kwang Soo.
- Bend your body. - You're doing well, Kwang Soo.
- Lay your body down. - Good.
(Kwang Soo also gets his sock.)
- Good! - Go, Kwang Soo!
- Sit down. - You're doing well.
Get closer.
Good.
- Use your strength. - Good.
(He throws water at him instead since he's not as strong.)
Hurry and put the sock on.
Kwang Soo, you're doing well.
- Kwang Soo. - It's over here.
- Good job, Kwang Soo. - The water is dripping.
- Come on. - Kwang Soo.
- Put one on. - I'll put it on.
- Kwang Soo. - Keep the shoes on.
- Kwang Soo, move! - You can win.
Kwang Soo, hurry and put in on.
Kwang Soo.
(Kwang Soo puts on his second stockings.)
- No. - He hasn't put it on yet.
He hasn't put it on yet.
(Ki Woo only has one more to go.)
(Kwang Soo also grabs for his last one.)
- No! - He hasn't put all of them on yet.
He did it!
Kwang Soo.
(He celebrates his victory by showing off his leg.)
He looks like a synchronised swimmer.
- My leg is cramping. - His leg is cramping!
(He went overboard with his celebration.)
Like the sunset
It becomes a beautiful memory
- Good job. - He's...
He's really funny.
He's an entertaining actor.
I've told you about Ki Woo.
He used to play the role of Kwang Soo before.
- I'm the old giraffe. - Kwang Soo is the new giraffe.
All right, next up is Gyeong Ree!
- Ji Hyo. - Let's go.
Do we play with water on the mat?
- Why did you splash so much water? - The beginning is important.
- Do we play with water on the mat? - Why did you splash so much water?
The beginning is important.
(What is that?)
- What is that? - It's really hot.
- Why did you splash so much water? - Are they for us to drink?
Will you play with shoes on?
(What's the truth behind these mysterious water bottles?)
We'll give you water in the middle of the competition.
- Okay. - If you drink it first, you lose.
- Okay. - Is that the mission?
Are you kidding? I haven't seen you in a while but...
- Goodness. - That's good.
(This is the team leaders' mission.)
- What is this? - It's really hot.
(Jae Seok is cleaning the mat.)
- Why did you splash so much water? - Are they for us to drink?
(He hands the water to someone.)
Can you bring it?
(He takes a shot of cool water.)
I'll wipe off the sand.
- I'll do it. - It's okay.
(In 5 seconds, Blue Team fails.)
- I'm hot. - You can stay off the mat.
Stay off the mat.
- Jae Seok, stop it. - I'm wiping off the sand.
- Don't do anything. - Stop him.
- Stop him. - Don't do anything.
Break his arms.
Goodness, this is frustrating.
I'm too stressed to do this any more.
- I'm too stressed. - Jae Seok.
- Are you playing solo? - Gosh, I'm going crazy.
He's the only one busy.
Team leaders, please step forward...
- Okay. - before the competition starts.
- You should be at an advantage. - What is it?
What is it again?
- Are you receiving orders again? - It's the main competition.
It's different from the competition.
We'll let you know about the losing team.
I can't do it any more due to stress.
My team's giving me too much stress.
Too many of them are suspicious.
We brought water,
- and Seok Jin drank it first. - Goodness.
Please tell him about that.
Okay.
- Please decide who's next. - What is it?
- Gosh. - Okay.
Why do you always lose?
Our team members are impatient.
Although they're so nice,
they're impatient.
- Gosh, Jae Seok. - You can't say that to us.
You'll see.
- This is driving me crazy. - What's wrong with you?
I can't stand it any more.
- This is driving me crazy. - Why?
Who is it?
- What did he say? - Gosh.
- Why do you keep dropping down? - This is so hard.
There must be something wrong.
He's doing fine, but what's the matter with you?
Why do you keep dropping down?
- Please calm down. - Gosh.
Why do you think it's unfavourable for us when we won the last round?
Just trust us.
- Jae Seok, - Gosh.
- Are you looking down on us? - It was fine.
- He's weird today. - Just trust us.
He talked about the next runner.
That's not related.
- I think... - There's no point in winning now.
- It's... - Now,
let's root for Gyeong Ree.
- Isn't there no point? - If you do that, you'll lose.
What's the point in doing it?
I won't do it. Don't do as he says.
- Why do we have to... - Don't do it.
- I won't root for our team. - That's meaningless.
- We've done it a lot. - This is crazy.
- Gosh, I want to suspect him. - I will do it when camera is off.
- I really want to suspect him. - They don't suspect anything.
We're doing just fine without any suspicions.
Why do you not suspect anything?
I really want to. But there's nothing suspicious.
Haha, you have poop on your face.
It's just my hair.
I even touched it.
- It's my hair. - He touched it to check.
- Gosh. - He touched it.
He even touched it.
He touched it.
He really thought it's real.
(The second round is between Gyeong Ree and Ji Hyo.)
(One who puts a pair of socks on first wins.)
- Get ready. - Do it quickly.
- Go, Gyeong Ree! - Look at her.
Gyeong Ree, you can do it.
You can make it. Gyeong Ree!
- Goodness. - Gyeong Ree.
- You can do it, Gyeong Ree. - If you lose here, we all lose!
Gyeong Ree, pull it harder.
- She's too strong. - Good.
- She is strong. - You're doing good.
- Go. - Gyeong Ree, that's good.
- That's it. You're doing well. - Cheer for your team.
- You can do it! - That's great.
- Gyeong Ree. - Ji Hyo.
No, no way!
(Gyeong Ree obtains a pair of socks.)
You can do it!
- Gyeong Ree. - Just put it on.
- Go! - Just wear the socks.
- Gyeong Ree. - Put it on!
- Put the socks on! - Gyeong Ree.
Put them on!
- Gyeong Ree. - Good!
- Gyeong Ree. - Gosh.
- Put them on. - That's it.
- Put them on. - Goodness.
- Put it on now. - Do it quickly.
- Gyeong Ree! - Put them on!
- Do it now! - Gosh!
- Do it quickly. - Make it quick.
Gyeong Ree!
(Speedy Ji Hyo clears the mission.)
(Red Team earns a score.)
Our team is doing so great.
- Gosh! - We lost.
I love it when Ji Hyo's on my team.
- She's so strong. - I love it.
Did you see Gyeong Ree rolling just back then?
(Thanks to the powerful Ji Hyo, Gyeong Ree rolled on the mat.)
- I thought it was a tornado. - I thought she's shooting a film.
Let's have one more round.
I recommend Nichkhun and Seok Jin.
- It won't overturn the score. - That's right.
- You brat. - Flip Seok Jin over.
How about we bet three points?
- That's good. - Okay.
- We might win. - Right.
Seok Jin, they're like meerkats.
Seok Jin, you'll never determine...
- your team's fate like now. - That's right.
Actually, the viewers criticised me when I did "Dig and Crawl".
- I'm sure. - How do you know that?
- Did you read the comments? - That's nonsense.
- Is it live? - Yes, I received 300 comments.
- Come here. - Seok Jin, that part wasn't aired.
- Really? - Yes.
- It wasn't aired? - No, it was edited out.
- It was edited out. - I see.
- Gosh. - What's wrong with you?
I'm sure it wasn't aired.
- It was aired. - If you give up here...
It doesn't matter if it was aired or not.
- I'm sure the viewers blamed me. - This is crazy.
- You didn't do your best. - Don't you guys suspect anything?
- No. It's so peaceful. - Get ready!
(This time, I'll do my best.)
(Nichkhun must win in order to move on to the third round.)
(This round will determine each team's fate.)
- We'll get three points if we win. - You can do it.
Go for it!
- Seok Jin. - He might win.
(Surprisingly, Seok Jin is doing well.)
- That's a good strategy. - Seok Jin!
(But it goes as everyone expected.)
Gosh.
I got a cramp.
(Are cramps contagious?)
Hey, pass me the towel.
- Seok Jin! - What?
The viewers are getting angry now.
Just lie down on the mat.
(I'll improve my image today.)
Pull it harder.
Wow, that was a good move.
- He might win this time. - Good. Good.
(Seok Jin counterattacks.)
(I won't let you win.)
(A bit more!)
My goodness.
(He falls forward.)
This isn't a tug of war.
It looks like you're trying to put the socks on him.
Go put the socks on.
(He flops on the mat again.)
(He bumps his forehead.)
- I can't watch this any more. - Gosh.
Why does the mat always roll up...
- on our side? - Wear the sock.
- What's wrong with the mat? - Wear it.
You can do it.
(Do you think it's over?)
Fight it.
- Go for it! - Good.
- You're almost there! - He's lying still.
- That's good. - You're almost there.
(Seok Jin boosts his power.)
(He obtains a pair of socks.)
He can win this time.
That's nonsense.
- Seok Jin, put them on! - I don't agree with you!
- No way! - Gosh.
- That's it. - No way!
(I can't lose like this.)
He even struggles to lift his leg.
He's so stiff.
Why is his feet so large?
He can't fold his knees. He can't.
(It's not over until it's over!)
(The round is over.)
Red Team wins this round.
- Wow. - It's good.
(They have a tie.)
The game itself was so difficult.
- It was hard. - Gosh.
Before we go to the last round, team leaders, please come up.
- Please stop. - Why?
- Why does he want us to come out? - Why?
- It'll be a moment. - Did you clear the mission?
Come here.
- Okay. - Gosh, it's driving me crazy.
- This is crazy. - Please come here.
- This is so stressful. - I really want to know.
What is it?
What will be the last mission?
This is the first time they've given a mission so overtly.
- I'm offended. - Just be quiet.
How can they give you the mission like that?
- Gosh. - We're not fools.
We are already done for, so just keep quiet!
What is it?
What do you mean? It's a tie.
(Jae Seok is angry.)
Should I just tell them everything and finish this?
Should I just...
Fine. Put an end to this!
- Calm down. - Tell us and end it here!
I don't think it's a one on one match.
- What they do is more important. - Right?
- You guys are so loud. - That is...
Never tell them about your mission.
- What do you mean? - Come tell us.
- Tell us. - Tell us. We can cooperate.
- Tell us everything and finish it. - Please tell us.
- Tell me secretly. - What is it?
- Just tell me. - Gosh, it's driving me crazy.
- Come on. - My goodness.
What's most important...
- is that we must do our best. - Jae Seok...
Why is Jae Seok frustrated, but Jong Kook happy?
We must win the games.
- Gosh. - But Jae Seok,
we didn't mess up yet. It's a tie.
- That's right. - It has just begun.
- We can win here. - We didn't mess up yet.
- We must do our best. - It's a tie. We can win this round.
Isn't the water sweet?
(What is their third suspicious mission?)
(Blue Team: 20, Red Team: 40)
We must win the last round.
The last one is the most important.
- Kwang Soo, the last round... - Jae Seok.
(Kwang Soo is more suspicious than ever.)
I'm not going to say any more.
I'm so distracted now.
The most important part is that we need to win this.
- Okay? - I'm not sure if I should win...
- I mean... - or just suspect you.
Or do I need to remove your name tag?
Kwang Soo, you can trust me.
- Kwang Soo... - It's so confusing.
Why are there many tubes? Do we need to hang them?
This is really difficult.
(There are four poles on each corner and tubes are scattered.)
- We should hang the tubes. - What?
We've done this before.
When we went to Gangwon-do...
(It was for episode 146.)
- We did this with Uhm Jung Hwa. - Oh, I got it.
- No, we didn't. - Gosh, it's really hard.
- Really? - Goodness.
(The last mission will be fierce.)
Gosh, it's really hard.
- Oh, is this that game? - There's a DJ.
They even invited a DJ.
- Hello. - Hello.
Please put your hands up.
- Good. - Put your hands up.
This game is unfavourable for us.
- No. - That's not true.
What do you mean? Of course, we are.
- Jae Seok, move to the side. - Why do I have to?
Move. That's not the centre.
- This is the centre. - No, it's not.
- This is the centre. - The producer is over there.
(What's wrong with them?)
- Is this a mission? - No.
Gyeong Ree, come here.
Their mission is to stand in the centre.
- Goodness. - Let's begin.
- Gosh, it's not. - Come back here.
It's not your turn. Just stay there.
I already feel exhausted.
- Is this their mission? - Do they need to be in the centre?
(What's their suspicious mission?)
- Just stay put. - Please look at the screen.
It's David Hasselhoff again.
I'm sure you're having a long and tough day.
That is so true.
In this round, I'd like to see how sharp your judgment is.
This round is called "Hang the Tubes".
- What? - What did he say?
What did he say?
(They have to hang the tubes as they expected.)
When the music is on, you must dance.
And you can't touch the tubes while you're dancing.
When the music stops, whichever team hangs...
the most tubes on their team's pole wins.
But first, let's check out your dance skills.
Let's have a party!
(They do a dance competition first.)
The first one to dance is Ki Woo!
(Ki Woo is the perfect example of a tall person.)
Let's go, Ki Woo!
(Show us!)
What?
What's that?
(He looks like he's rubbing something.)
Wait.
(He passionately does the rubbing dance.)
(And next,)
(he flounders in the air.)
(And he falls.)
(He rotates 180 degrees and falls on the ground.)
- Are you okay? - It's fun.
- It's fun. - Didn't you fall hard?
He has a good sense of...
Didn't you fall hard?
- He has good motor nerves. - It's a technique.
(Ki Woo tries it again.)
What's wrong with him?
- Try harder, Ki Woo. - What's wrong with him?
You're excited, right?
- This is... - Isn't that really old?
(He falls to the ground.)
(He does an anaemia dance.)
Great.
Next is Gyeong Ree.
(Gyeong Ree goes next.)
(She shows off her sexiness.)
Oh dear.
Oh dear. Let's go!
(I'm so thankful that I get to watch this.)
Yes! Let's go!
We're winning!
We are totally winning the dance competition.
Let's go, Gyeong Ree!
What's that?
(I am Gyeong Ree from Nine Muses.)
Next is Nichkhun!
- Here we go! - Nichkhun!
(Nichkhun is the handsome prince.)
(He shows the old school dance.)
Go, Nichkhun!
(He looks good whatever he does.)
Nichkhun is good.
Here we go.
(Jae Seok and Haha dance next.)
(They heat up the atmosphere.)
(Kwang Soo the Dance Machine dances next.)
(His passion for dance never ceases.)
- You're sexy. - You're sexy.
- Ji Hyo. - Come on, Ji Hyo.
(Ji Hyo from Red Team comes in.)
She's good. It's a battle.
Gyeong Ree.
- It's a battle. - Here she comes.
(I heard you dance well.)
(Watch it for yourself!)
Come on!
(Kwang Soo annoys Ji Hyo.)
(And Ji Hyo slaps him.)
(Would you please move?)
(He gets beaten up while dancing.)
- How can she do this? - Good job.
- Good job. - Was that part of the dance?
- Good job. - Okay!
(Next is the couple dance competition.)
That's nice.
(It's a couple gorilla dance.)
That's good.
I don't want to lose. I don't want to lose.
(The two teams' prides are on stake.)
(The warm-up dance finishes with the couple dance battle.)
All right, everyone.
This is the mission given by the captain.
When the music plays, you have to dance.
- Okay. - Okay.
The team that has the most tubes on the poles wins.
When I blow the whistle, the competition ends.
- Okay. - We can't take them out, right?
Try every possible means to win.
(Anything goes.)
- He's really fast. - That's it! That's it!
(Will Blue Team win with a miraculous one win?)
Come on!
(Or will Red Team that got two wins...)
(with persistence and power win?)
He's really different.
He's really good.
(The current score is 1 to 1.)
(Which team will win in the end?)
(DJ, drop the beat!)
(The final mission starts.)
(They keep sticking together.)
(They dance and keep each other in check at the same time.)
(Everyone dances around the tubes.)
(They look for a chance every minute.)
(The whistle blows.)
(They start putting the tubes.)
(The team that has more tubes on their poles wins.)
No, no!
(Everyone is busy inserting tubes into their poles.)
Take this!
Do that later.
(Then, Kwang Soo approaches the other team's pole.)
- I'm here. - Jong Kook.
Look at Kwang Soo.
(Kwang Soo is determined to take the other team's tubes.)
No. No.
(But Ji Hyo guards the pole.)
(Red Team is winning.)
(Jae Seok can't let it happen.)
Take them out.
(They take all the tubes out.)
(Blue Team successfully ambushes them.)
Let's go.
What are you doing?
(We can't lose.)
(All the tubes are taken out.)
Hey!
That's it!
(You have to say something nice to hear something nice back.)
Good job, Ki Woo. Ki Woo is good.
(Ki Woo goes from a weak one to an ace!)
No!
(Kwang Soo chooses a target.)
- Hey, you! - What's going on?
(But Nichkhun's defence was fast.)
(Kwang Soo gets blocked by Nichkhun.)
We have to stop them!
- Take Ji Hyo out! - We need to steal them!
- Take Ji Hyo out! - Gyeong Ree!
(Haha runs and takes out all the tubes.)
(Haha attacks surprisingly.)
No way!
(Haha does a surprise attacks.)
Gosh.
- What was that? - Look at Haha!
- I'm not doing anything. - Look at that.
I'm not doing anything.
(The DJ drops the beat again.)
- Dance! - Dance!
Dance!
Come on.
- Come on. - What's this?
What are we doing?
- What are we doing? - It looks strange.
- Is this a club? - It looks strange.
It looks strange.
Hey, move.
(Jae Seok and Seok Jin dance dirty.)
(And Kwang Soo joins.)
(Let's dance.)
This is not dancing!
(Haha gets bounced on the floor.)
(This is the real bounce.)
(We will revitalise you, Sir.)
- Here we go! - Let's dance!
(Jong Kook heads towards Haha's pole as well.)
(It's so crowded around Red Team's pole.)
Come on, everyone.
Guard that area, Gyeong Ree!
Kwang Soo, Kwang Soo.
(Jae Seok runs fast.)
Kwang Soo.
(His target is Ji Hyo.)
(She's about to get in trouble.)
(She's goes into a defensive mode.)
Hey.
(I am Ji Hyo.)
Hey. Hey.
Come on down, Ji Hyo. Hurry up.
Come down!
- What's wrong with her? - What's up with this girl?
- What's wrong with her? - What's wrong with her?
She's...
- She's... - She's unbelievable.
What's wrong with her these days?
(It's empty on this side.)
(Some try to take out the tubes while others try to stop them.)
(Seok Jin tries to take out the tubes.)
(This game will determine the two teams' fates.)
- Move Ji Hyo. - Take him away!
Do it!
Let go of your hands!
Hold on.
(I can't let the tubes go.)
(He raises his leg.)
(He defends the tubes by twisting his legs around them.)
Jae Seok, you have to take them out.
(Screaming)
He bit me.
(Jae Seok bites Ki Woo.)
Wait.
He's weird. He bites people.
Kwang Soo is coming.
(Among all the chaos, Red Team gathers more tubes.)
That's enough.
We have too many tubes.
(Both teams have two poles each.)
(Red Team has 25 tubes, and Blue Team has 14 tubes.)
Please stop.
- Team leaders, come on up. - Why again?
(Why are you calling again?)
We are in the middle of the game!
People will have doubts if you do this in the middle of the game!
The captain sent us a message.
- We... - Wait.
Please stop for a while.
(They are all very suspicious.)
I told you about another mission.
Here's your mission.
You are playing "Hang the Tubes".
You have to make sure that your pole doesn't have any donut tubes.
Do you understand?
(They have to remove the donut tubes without the team knowing.)
(This is the donut tube.)
- What is it? - We will resume the game.
What is it?
(They are very suspicious.)
- Gary. - I am so curious.
- All right. - What is it?
- What is it? - It's...
Isn't he...
- What is it? - being too obvious?
- I just had... - Isn't it too obvious?
- I had something to tell my team. - Don't cheat.
What is it? Tell us. It's okay.
- I think it's about you. - This is frustrating.
I'm going to develop a stomach disease.
(He can't tell anyone about it.)
(It's more like a Sad Mission than a Suspicious Mission.)
It's okay.
Should we guard the tubes?
(Blue Team has 4 donut tubes, and Red Team has none.)
(The donut tube is the cause of his stomach disease.)
(The music starts.)
(They warm up before the game resumes.)
(Why are they coming towards me?)
(Jae Seok slyly takes the donut tube.)
Wait.
Why are you moving?
(What's wrong with them?)
(Gyeong Ree is happy that her song is on.)
- Bring it here. - Hey!
(Kicking)
What was that about?
(They're confused.)
That must be the mission.
- Come down, Ji Hyo. - Come down.
Come down first. Listen to me. Come down, Ji Hyo.
- You have to steal it! - Come down, Ji Hyo.
- Hold this. - Steal it!
- Hey! - You can't.
Hey.
- Come down, Ji Hyo. Trust me. - Jong Kook!
- Take them out. - Why are you doing this?
- Look at them. - Hurry.
Why?
- Take them out. - Why are you doing this?
- What's this? - Take this...
and hang it on the other team's pole.
(Haha catches on.)
- What? - I think that's what you do.
- What? - Take it out. Hurry!
Take it out!
(The doughnut tube is on the Blue Team's pole.)
What's this about?
What is he doing?
(Kwang Soo is quick to act.)
What's this about?
Why are you taking it out?
- You have to stop him. - It's the doughnut!
(He donates it to the opposing team.)
(How dare you disturb Ji Hyo's fortress?)
(Biting)
Just let go.
(Ji Hyo's teeth are strong.)
- Hold on! - I took it out.
What's going on?
(You need to put the doughnut tube on the opposing team's pole.)
- Why are you taking it out? - I don't know. He's losing it.
- What are you doing? - What is it?
- What do we do? - Where are my glasses?
What is it, Jae Seok?
Take the doughnut tube out!
Must I put it or take it out?
(Must I put it or take it out?)
What should I do?
I have no idea what's going on.
(Red Team has 14 tubes and no doughnut tube.)
(Blue Team has 14 tubes and 2 doughnut tubes.)
(Pass me...)
Give it me.
(the doughnut tube.)
(No way!)
Take the doughnut, Nichkhun!
(Run towards the doughnut tube!)
Block them!
(Falling)
(Blocking)
- What is it? - Wait.
Take the doughnut!
(What's with the doughnut tube?)
(Seok Jin grabs Haha's dreadlocks.)
(Give us the tube if you want to keep your dreadlocks.)
- Put it over. - Move over.
(They try to avoid the doughnut tube.)
What's going on, anyway?
I have no idea what's going on.
Why are you all going for the doughnut tube?
Should we take our tubes out and hang it on theirs?
What's more important?
Hurry and put it over.
Where are we supposed to go?
Five,
- four, - You can't rip it!
- three, - You can't rip it.
- two, - Kwang Soo!
- one. - Put a tube in.
(Game over)
It's good.
What was this game about?
Tell us already!
I already told you it was "Hang the Tubes".
The team that hangs the most tubes wins.
- We could have won. - What?
No, we're close.
- It's a close game. - It is.
(Their fates are decided by this round.)
(The winners are crowned and the losers are flogged.)
(Who is the ultimate winner?)
Take one out at a time.
- One, - One,
- two, - two,
- three... - three...
- Seven, - Seven,
- Seven, - They have one more.
(It's a tie.)
- Eight! - Eight.
- They have many small tube. - Right.
(They start counting the tubes on the second pole.)
We're only 1 behind. They have 8.
(Red Team: 8, Blue Team: 7)
That's nine.
Nine,
That's 10.
- We have a lot of fat ones. - We do.
- 14, - 14,
- 15, - That's 15.
- 16, - We have a lot.
- There are more inside. - 17!
- We have more inside. - Hold on.
- That's 18. - 18.
- That's 18. - Wow!
(It's 18 to 18.)
- 19! - 19!
- We have more. - They have more.
- 20. - 20.
(It's 20 to 20.)
(This round is unpredictable.)
(Which team is the ultimate winner?)
- 21. - We have more, too.
- 21, - We won.
- 22, - Okay!
- There's more inside. - We have one less.
- 23! - Okay!
(Red Team wins 23 to 22.)
Good.
Okay!
- We should have stolen their tubes. - Good.
That was so close.
- Did we lose by one? - We should have stopped them.
What was this about? What was it with the doughnut tube?
I think that's a competition for these two.
- Are we supposed to hang it? - So everyone,
let me announce the result.
Tell them. I'm itching to tell them. This is too stressful.
What is this? What's this about?
You probably realised that something suspicious was going on.
- My goodness. - That was so obvious.
I don't know what to do with my team. Tell them.
Your team leaders have been receiving suspicious missions.
- That was hard for us. - It was really hard.
- It was a huge dilemma. - My team...
was full of mistrust and misunderstanding.
My team trusted each other.
Nichkhun and Ki Woo didn't say a word.
They just felt uncomfortable.
The mission for this last game...
was to remove the doughnut tube...
since it won't be counted towards the total.
Therefore,
- Red Team has 23... - It's 23.
and Blue Team has 22.
However, Red Team...
- had three doughnut tubes. - That's right.
- Blue Team had two. - That's right.
In conclusion, the doughnut tubes...
don't count towards the total,
- They don't? - it's 20 to 20.
- Is it a draw? - Wow.
That's good to hear.
As a result, the score ends up being...
a tie but when you count the doughnut tubes,
- Blue Team wins. - We win, right?
- We won? - Yes!
- Is this what it was about? - However,
do you remember the ice creams you had?
The mission behind the ice cream...
was that if you take off your wig first, your team loses.
I wasn't the first to take it off.
(You're the culprit!)
(Let me try to recollect my memory.)
(Let's rewind six hours back.)
(He takes it off.)
And the mission for the first round...
was the team that says, "Let's go" first...
We didn't say it.
- Did I say it? - You have to apologise.
You said it as soon as we heard the mission.
Focus on the game. Don't doubt anything.
- Let's go! - We can do it.
For the second game...
- called "Wear the Socks", - I'm going nuts.
the team member that drinks water first...
- We didn't drink first, right? - Was it me?
I don't remember drinking it.
- When did I drink it? - I gave it to you.
- When? - I opened the bottle for you.
- See? - Did you?
- Our team... - My goodness.
- Why did you give it to him? - I knew we were going to win...
because he likes being treated well.
- Oh, gosh. - He drank it right away.
There were three games in total,
- but Red Team won two missions... - They won.
- wins by 10 points. - They won.
(Red Team wins by 10 points.)
- Way to go. - We have to thank Seok Jin.
- You two... - I just drank water.
- How many points was that? - Was I not supposed to cheer?
Do you know how many points you lost?
The wig kept on getting in my mouth so I had to take it off.
So according to the Captain's guidelines,
Jong Kook will be promoted as the captain.
(Jong Kook is the captain!)
Go on your knees!
- Go on your knees. - My gosh.
- You're at the bottom. - This is what I wanted.
- You're at the bottom. - We're done.
- I'll make you the leader. - Thank you.
- You can be the leader. - I'm so upset.
- Thank you. - I'm at your service.
All members of the Red Team...
get a golden whistle.
- This is amazing. - The leader gets a badge.
- I didn't even do anything. - This is amazing.
- This is amazing. - It it real gold?
- It is. - I didn't even do anything.
It's not part of the game,
- but we decided... - I'm so frustrated.
that the losing team will get punished.
Let's start with Jae Seok.
- Excuse me. - He's the team leader...
so he's the most responsible.
Is it just once?
- Of course. Don't rub it. - It's just once.
- It's almost done. - It has to stick to his butt.
- Exactly. - My gosh.
Oh, gosh.
(He wets Jae Seok's bum.)
Don't do that.
I can't watch.
Stop rubbing it.
- Count 1! - In 1, 2, 3!
(It's better to go first.)
(My goodness!)
(That's loud.)
Hey, wait.
- Hold on a second. - I'm sorry!
I'm sorry.
I should have worn red.
I'm sorry I'm wearing blue.
- Ji Hyo. - Give me a red shirt.
- Can you do it instead, Ji Hyo? - Why?
- Come here. - Ji Hyo!
- Come here, both of you. - Let her do it.
- Let Ji Hyo do it. - Give it to her.
Let her do it.
- I'll do it for Kwang Soo. - Sure.
Let her flog me.
You have to flog it harder than you think, Ji Hyo.
- Okay. - You have to hit it hard.
- Right. - She's strong.
(She takes a mouthful of water.)
Did you drink?
Ji Hyo.
(Trickling)
This is gross.
- Don't do that, Ji Hyo. - Why are you doing this?
I didn't even bring an extra underwear. What's wrong with you?
You're quite something.
- Let's get started. - Yes.
One, two, three.
Three.
(Flogging)
(Hitting)
(Thank you Ki Woo, Nichkhun and Gyeong Ree...)
(for joining us and participating in the games.)
(The following segment is based on the discussion from our meeting.)
We don't have anything filmed for next week's episode.
Should we reveal the mission in the trailer?
It'll be a way to check if the members watch the episodes.
(Sniggering)
(Therefore)
Running Man members, this is your first mission.
Once you see this, call the main producer right away.
(The first three to call will have an advantage for the final mission.)