(A diamond has disappeared...)
(from a mysterious mountain cabin.)
(Traces have been left on the scene.)
(What is the truth behind the disappearance of the diamond?)
(The day of the incident, January 26, 10pm)
(He's the detective.)
(And she's the suspect.)
- I am innocent.
- Yes.
I'm someone who has spent the most time...
with the other members.
The only time I was alone today...
was when I went in my room...
and tried to fall asleep.
Other than that, I never went outside alone.
If you check the visitor's history, you'll be able to see...
that I've never been here before.
That's all you need to check.
(Who's telling the truth?)
Why did you come here today?
Kwang Soo invited me.
Kwang Soo said...
- Go on.
- that he won an event...
and asked me to join him. That's why I came here.
(The day before the incident, January 25, 4pm)
(A mysterious letter was delivered to Kwang Soo.)
What's this?
Kwang Soo asked me to join him on a trip.
So I agreed. He said he won some kind of an event.
"Invitation to the mountain cabin. Congratulations."
"You have won free lodging at the mountain cabin."
It's free?
I get to stay at the mountain cabin for free.
It expires tomorrow.
It's my first time to win such an event.
(Kwang Soo, the symbol of misfortune, gets lucky?)
To be honest, I never entered the event.
I received an invitation.
- Okay.
- And many people have been...
asking me to treat them.
So since I got a free stay at the cabin, I thought...
I would invite the members to join me on the trip.
I won free lodging at a mountain cabin.
You don't need to bring anything.
I will prepare everything.
(The Case of Burglary of the Tears of the Sun)
(The day of the incident, January 26, 2pm)
Where are we going?
- Kwang Soo.
- You won an event?
It's an invitation. You will know when you get there.
- It's an invitation to...
- I'm nervous if its an invitation.
A mountain cabin?
- A mountain cabin?
- A free lodging event.
- Yes.
- I'm scared for some reason.
- We're staying the night there.
- But...
- Hey.
- Why all of a sudden?
- Don't be suspicious.
- Maybe it's a haunted house.
Come on.
What if it's a blind dating event at the mountain cabin?
- I'd love that!
- Seok Jin.
It's nice just thinking about it.
Anything is possible.
(The day of the incident, 2:40pm, Gapyeong tourist site)
- It's...
- We're here.
Can you see the mountain cabin over there?
There's the mountain cabin.
What is this place?
- What's this?
- Okay.
Kwang Soo, it's very nice.
Look at this place. This place is amazing.
Why are you amazed too? You invited us here.
There are people partying inside.
- Is this a tourist spot?
- What's this place?
- Look at that.
- What is it?
Is it some sort of a party?
It's a party.
Look, they are all wearing our name tags.
What's going on?
(It's a dance party in the middle of the cabin.)
Let me leave my bag here.
Maybe it's a race with the community.
Finally,
- What's going on?
- things are changing.
What are we doing here?
What is this?
It's a dance party!
What's going on?
What's happening?
Kwang Soo, are we having a party today?
- This is great!
- Is it going to be...
- an outdoor party?
- This is awesome.
(Welcome! Is it your first time at a mountain cabin party?)
There's a barbecue too.
- It's a party!
- What's this?
There's a barbecue here.
What's going on?
(Everyone is getting excited.)
It's really a party!
Are we having a party today, Kwang Soo?
(Security guard: Choi Bo An)
I never expected something like this.
- Hello.
- Who received the invitation?
- It's me.
- It's you.
- What's this?
- I'm glad he invited us.
- Okay.
- This is great.
I will take care of everything today.
But isn't it too early for a dance party?
Just trust me!
I think it's too early.
There's food, too.
Is this an after-club party?
- An after-club party?
- Thank you.
- Oh wow.
- Let's go in.
- What is this place?
- Great job, Kwang Soo!
Thanks to Kwang Soo, we were able to come here.
What did I tell you?
- They are partying well.
- Oh wow.
- I know.
- They really are.
She's doing the rabbit dance.
It's a real party.
- Hello!
- We're from "Running Man".
(Let's party together!)
Let's party.
(They leave their worries behind and immerse themselves in the fun.)
This is great.
Since you're eating and dancing, you can digest food immediately.
(While the party is heating up...)
He grills meat well.
(A mysterious woman...)
(is heading somewhere.)
(Who is this woman...)
(that is approaching the party?)
- Look at her.
- Hello.
- Goodness.
- Oh my.
- Hello.
Go on, everyone.
(Kim Ga Yeon, the owner of the cabin)
- Hello.
- Hello, everyone.
- What are you doing here?
- Hello.
- What's going on today?
- I am the owner of this cabin.
- I see.
- Oh.
- It's your party.
- I...
- You're the owner?
Wait, let me talk first.
Be careful with your fur.
- Oh, my fur!
- Behind you.
It didn't touch the fire.
When you were walking towards us, I thought you were a dog.
Be careful.
- Hey!
- I just saw...
- This is from abroad!
- I see.
Of course.
I am the hottest...
heiress of Korea.
The only thing I have is beauty and money.
- You are my ideal type of a girl!
- She's perfect.
You are my ideal type.
- By the way,
- Yes?
what should we do now?
You should enjoy the party. Please enjoy the party...
with the many guests that are here today.
- We just have to enjoy the party?
- Of course.
Last time,
your husband was on our show.
- Right.
- My husband?
He's not very good at playing arcade games.
- He played tetris.
- He wasn't very good.
- He lost in tetris.
- He did.
It's such an honour...
to have you guys here at the mountain cabin.
(Laughing)
(I'm hot.)
What is that?
(Will you look at my necklace?)
- It's heavy.
- I know.
Look at my necklace.
Oh, the necklace!
That's a nice necklace.
- It's gorgeous.
- Is it authentic?
- Have you seen this?
- It's gorgeous.
Aren't they droplet diamonds?
These diamonds are known as Tears of the Sun.
They're worth 20 million dollars.
- 20 million dollars?
- What is?
(They're worth 20 million dollars?)
(Also known as Tears of the Sun, they are worth 20 million dollars.)
Take a look. You can touch them.
I saw them at a street market the other day.
At a street market.
These are not the same.
- I'm sorry.
- Look at her.
I apologise.
They look similar, but the ones I saw were fake.
- Kwang Soo.
- Yes.
- You can touch it.
- Really?
- Be careful.
- Sure.
Wow.
Thank you.
Diamonds that are worth 20 million dollars.
There wasn't anything special about them,
but it was an interesting sight.
(I want those diamonds.)
I'm being honest.
Diamonds...
are vulnerable to moisture.
- I see.
- So...
- I'll go put them in my room.
- Okay.
Please excuse me for a moment.
- Of course.
- Sure.
- Thank you.
- See you.
- See you later.
- Bye.
- Let's go.
- This is a real party.
Partying with you guys is fun.
I didn't expect this.
This tastes great.
We should eat before doing anything else.
(Ga Yeon's room is in this building.)
Good afternoon.
Wait.
(The day of the incident, 3:20pm, Ga Yeon enters her room.)
It's cold.
My lovely necklace.
(Entering the password)
(Her safe requires a password to access it.)
There you go.
(Ga Yeon's safe can be open with a password.)
My precious baby.
(Kissing)
(Ga Yeon keeps the Tears of the Sun in her personal safe.)
(I'll see you later.)
(The day of the incident, 3:25pm,)
(Ga Yeon stores the Tears of the Sun.)
Hello, everybody!
Enjoy!
This is a high-class party.
What did I tell you?
- I'm impressed.
- Kwang Soo.
- I'm very impressed.
- It was a good idea.
- See?
- It's all thanks to you.
This is a rare opportunity.
You surprised me, Ga Yeon.
The fire is too weak.
- Let me see.
- The meat won't cook.
I'll cut the meat since I'm the owner.
It's not cooked yet.
- It's raw.
- It's hard to cut right now.
- We should wait a bit.
- This is annoying. I give up.
- The scissors are dull. Jong Kook.
- Yes?
Do you see the big building over there?
- The one over there?
- Right, the one on top.
- That's where my room is.
- Okay.
My room is the first one in the corridor.
- In my room,
I have sharper scissors.
- I bought them when I was abroad.
- Okay.
- Can you go get them?
- It's the first room, right?
- Yes, don't touch anything else.
- Okay.
- Scissors.
- I understand.
- As in "rock, paper, scissors".
- All right.
Okay. I'll be right back.
Scissors.
Hi.
(The day of the incident, 3:45pm, Jong Kook greets Guest 99.)
(Looking around)
(This room must be hers.)
(The day of the incident, 3:47pm, Jong Kook enters Ga Yeon's room...)
(in search of the scissors.)
She wanted scissors. Here they are.
(Looking around the room)
(The items in her room look rather ordinary.)
Let's see.
There's a safe.
(There's a safe.)
(This is where the Tears of the Sun is kept.)
It's a safe.
All right.
(The day of the incident, 4:00pm, Jong Kook exits Ga Yeon's room.)
I have scissors.
Hello.
Why isn't Jong Kook coming?
- What is he doing?
- Is he doing a mission?
Ga Yeon.
- Here are your scissors.
- Jong Kook.
Jong Kook, they're telling us to wait.
- What?
- But look,
we're running out of salads.
- Haha, we're running out of salads.
- Okay.
I have some vegetables in my room.
- You should wash them too.
- Ga Yeon, I'm sorry but...
- Yes.
- we have a lot of vegetables here.
No, we need some more.
- Ji Hyo.
- Yes.
I have some drinks in my room.
- Drinks?
- Yes, can you get them?
Ga Yeon, can't you leave us alone?
No, I can't.
- Isn't the customer the king?
- I'm getting upset.
(Isn't the customer the king?)
Ga Yeon was a bit strange.
Customers should be the king, but she kept bothering us...
and ordering us around.
Where is Ga Yeon's room?
(Haha also runs into Guest 99.)
She told me to bring some vegetables.
(The day of the incident, 4:18pm, Haha enters Ga Yeon's room.)
(Haha discovers something as soon as he enters.)
(Ga Yeon's safe where the Tears of the Sun is kept)
Hi.
(The day of the incident, 4:30pm, Ji Hyo arrives at the building.)
Ga Yeon has a nice place.
(Ji Hyo found the safe, too.)
(The day of the incident, 4:36pm, Ji Hyo leaves Ga Yeon's room.)
Where's the meat?
(The day of the incident, 4:44pm, Kwang Soo enters Ga Yeon's room...)
(for some meat)
Why does she have a safe?
She must keep her necklace there.
(She must keep her necklace there.)
(Sneaking in)
- Kwang Soo.
- I brought the meat.
Did they make you do something there?
No, no one was there.
- No one?
- No.
- It tastes great.
- It's delicious.
Here you go.
- Get some rest.
- Already?
- See you tomorrow.
- Gary and Haha are here.
- Good night.
We're going to bed already?
(Room 3: Haha)
This is nice.
Who is it?
It's me, Ga Yeon.
- You surprised me.
- You surprised me, too.
What's the matter?
There was something suspicious about her.
She told us to get all kinds of things from vegetables and...
drinks to blankets.
She makes me uncomfortable.
I feel very uncomfortable.
(Please take her away.)
You'll find room 209 two doors away from my room.
- Okay.
- There are some blankets there.
Can you get them?
- Goodness.
- Bye.
(What's wrong with her?)
- I have some wine in my room.
- Okay.
- Wine?
- Please go get it.
She wants four bottles of wine.
(The day of the incident, 6:55pm, Seok Jin heads to Ga Yeon's room.)
Go to my room...
- I'll bring the remote control.
- and bring only the remote control.
It's freezing.
I don't even watch TV. Why do I need a remote control?
She said it's two doors away.
What's going on?
(Only Jae Seok was sent to another room.)
My goodness.
It's freezing.
I don't watch TV. I don't need a remote control.
I should look carefully.
(Gary notices the safe, too.)
This might be a mission.
Here's the wine.
(He approaches the safe.)
(And tries to open it.)
Gosh.
She said she's an heiress. This safe must be full of valuable things.
This mountain cabin...
has a nice vibe.
I'm sure something grand will happen.
(I'm sure something grand will happen.)
This has never happened before.
I'm so bored.
We had no idea of what was about to happen.
We didn't know something like that would happen there.
(We didn't know something like that would happen there.)
My goodness!
My diamonds!
My goodness! My diamonds!
My diamonds are gone! My Tears of the Sun!
- What?
- Excuse me.
Have you seen my diamonds?
My diamonds are gone!
Is she in danger?
Jae Seok, what do I do?
The Tears of the Sun disappeared! What do I do?
(The 20-million-dollar Tears of the Sun has been stolen.)
Have you seen it?
I haven't seen it.
You saw it a while ago.
Yes, I did see it then.
- But you haven't seen it after?
- No, I haven't.
- I knew this would happen.
- Quick, come here.
- Jong Kook.
- Yes.
Come here quick.
(Knocking)
Seok Jin.
Come out, quick.
- Why?
- My necklace is missing.
- Come out quickly.
- What?
- The necklace is fake, I tell you.
- Come out, quick.
Don't tell us. Report to the police.
Where did you leave it?
I took it with me and put it in the safe.
Then I closed the safe and enjoyed the party.
- That's right.
- Yes.
After the party, I went around to make sure you were all comfortable.
Then I went into my room...
to take it out and polish it, but the necklace was missing!
I couldn't find it anywhere. It's worth 20 million dollars.
Why are you telling us this?
Just call the police.
- I called the police.
- Okay.
- But it snowed today.
- Right.
So they said it will take them four hours to get here.
- What kind of police is that?
- So I was hoping that you could...
- find the necklace in four hours.
- All right.
If you find it,
I will let you leave this place.
- Excuse me.
- Yes?
I'm in fact Detective Yu.
Shut your mouth.
No one ever called you that.
- Are you the thief?
- You're probably the thief.
- He's the thief.
- Since when were you a detective?
They call me Sherlock Yu.
That's enough.
Don't act on your own from now on.
Because these people...
have been in my room at least once.
- So they are all suspects.
- One of us may be the thief.
- You're right.
- Who's the thief?
- Confess this instant.
- Wait.
- Give it back so we can go home.
- Don't leave anyone behind.
Let's all go to the crime scene together.
It may be a coincidence,
but all the members have been near Ga Yeon's room at least once.
Therefore, we can all be suspected.
(Previously on Running Man)
(The members were invited to the mountain cabin.)
Hello everyone.
- Kwang Soo.
- Yes?
- Go get some more meat.
- Why are there so many errands?
The necklace disappeared. What do I do?
- The thief is among us!
(Gary, Yu Jae Seok)
(Ji Seok Jin, Haha)
(Kim Jong Kook, Song Ji Hyo, Lee Kwang Soo)
(The Burglary of the Tears of the Sun)
I'll ask some direct questions.
Jae Seok,
who do you think is the thief?
From the beginning,
- I thought the thief was among us.
- Okay.
But among our members, there is only one suspect.
Where were you at the time?
I went to see Ga Yeon.
Criminals always leave behind clues at the crime scene.
That's right.
We'll start by looking around the crime scene.
(Jae Seok and Seok Jin have come to investigate the crime scene.)
See!
This wasn't open before.
- Goodness.
- This was closed before.
- What?
- I had locked it.
(There was a 20-million-dollar necklace inside the safe.)
(She saw that the necklace was put in safely with her own two eyes.)
(Who could have possibly opened the high-tech safe?)
To be honest, I did try to open it. I was curious.
- But I couldn't open it.
- Why would you touch that?
But how did the thief open this?
You need to know the password to open it.
- Wait a minute.
- Of course.
What is the password?
- What is it?
- Actually,
I always set my password to four zeros.
- Do you really?
- My goodness.
That way, I don't forget.
- What? Four zeros?
- Why did you make it like that?
It's way too simple.
Who could have possibly taken the necklace?
This is frustrating.
Quickly, find out who took it.
- We need to investigate this room.
- All seven members have been here.
- Wait,
- Right?
did you leave this window open?
Yes, to ventilate the room.
It's important to ventilate the room in the winter.
Even so, don't you think you left it open for too long?
It's because it's not automatic.
There must be a clue here.
The thief must have left a clue.
- Well...
- We should look for fingerprints.
Who has been in this room?
- Everyone.
I haven't been in this room before.
- I came here to...
- To bring the wine. And Gary?
He came to bring the remote control.
- From this room?
- Yes.
But you told me to go to the room next door.
- I didn't come in here.
- You didn't come here?
- It was the room next to this one.
- Why was he sent elsewhere?
Because the blankets were over there.
- There are blankets here, too.
- They were washed recently.
- This is my blanket.
- Oh, I see.
The guest blankets were in the other room.
I think you're the culprit.
(I think you're the culprit.)
(What?)
(Jae Seok suddenly suspects Ga Yeon to be the thief.)
What did you say?
Do you think this is a joke?
I think you're after the insurance money.
- Aren't I right?
- That might be true.
(She planned this to get the insurance money?)
(Jae Seok suspects that Ga Yeon has planned the theft.)
Why did Kwang Soo bring us here?
He just wanted to hang out with us.
I'll take care of everything today!
You'll find out when you get there.
- An invitation?
- Mountain cabin?
- That's where we're going?
- Yes.
I think the person who rented this place,
Kwang Soo, is the most suspicious.
It's something Kwang Soo would do.
He's the only person who would do this kind of thing.
He's always up to no good.
I suspect Kwang Soo.
This might be...
related to Guest 99 and Kwang Soo.
Maybe it's related to a number of people.
- Do you think so?
- Don't you agree?
Or why else would he have brought us here?
- There's no other reason.
- But here...
Guest 99.
Guest 99 is definitely related to this case.
I'm sure of it. We have to find Guest 99 first.
Excuse me,
have you ever seen Guest 99?
(Shaking their heads)
I remember his face.
(Although it was a short moment, Gary remembers his face.)
I clearly remember what he looks like.
(Haha and Gary believe Guest 99 is the key to solving this crime.)
Guest 99.
Who should we ask?
Excuse me,
- did you see it?
- Did you see anyone...
- going in the cabin owner's room?
- The cabin owner's room.
We just got back from the grocery store.
- So you didn't see anyone?
- No, we didn't.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
- Excuse me.
- It was too cold.
- Okay.
So we didn't go out.
- It was too cold to go outside?
- Yes.
They didn't go out of the room because it was cold?
That's strange.
Jong Kook,
there are two men here.
There are women, too. Let's go and ask them.
- Hello.
- You should have knocked.
- Look, there's a couple here.
- Look, number 93.
Hello.
- By chance have you seen...
- In the cabin owner's room.
- someone going in the owner's room?
- Anyone suspicious?
(Did you see anyone suspicious near the owner's room?)
- I saw some people.
- Suspicious people?
(Someone was there?)
I saw the employees.
I think I saw the cleaning ladies go up to the cabin.
The employees of this mountain cabin went up to the owner's room.
Oh, the employees?
- Is that right?
- Thank you.
All right. Thank you.
- Cleaning ladies?
- Let's go find them.
There are a lot of people here.
There was also the guard.
- Yes, the first person we saw.
- We saw the guard this morning.
There's an employee over there.
- Hello.
- An employee.
- An employee?
- Yes, he is an employee.
- Is he really?
We were wondering if you happened to see...
anyone suspicious go near the cabin owner's room?
Have you seen anyone suspicious?
We're in charge of the food supplies so we weren't able to see anyone.
- You're in charge of food supplies?
- Right.
- So you were only in this place?
- Yes.
- You've never went up this way?
- I was in this area.
The cleaning lady has the master key.
That's what I was saying.
- There's a master key.
- She's probably over there.
- This way?
- All right.
- The cleaning lady.
- Thank you.
Thank you very much.
The cleaning lady?
It's the the cleaners' room.
- It's here.
- The cleaners' room.
(They found the cleaners' room nearby.)
Hello.
Nice to meet you.
(Who is it?)
- Hello. Jong Kook, over here.
- Look, she's in here.
- Hello.
Have you been in the cabin owner's room earlier today?
Did you clean the room?
The cabin owner's room?
- Yes, I did.
- You cleaned the room?
Did you clean the room when we were with the owner...
or after we parted with the owner?
In the morning.
- In the morning.
- I see.
Then did you...
Did you happen to lend or lose the master key today?
No, I didn't.
- Have you ever stolen...
- We need to ask the others.
other people's things?
- She might have experience.
- What are you saying?
- Kwang Soo.
- Maybe when she was young.
- All right.
- It's not that we suspect you.
But we have to think of every possibility.
- Yes, we're sorry.
- We apologise for...
- a number of things.
- I'm sorry.
- We're sorry to have bothered you.
- Rest well.
If we have further questions, we'll come back to ask you.
- Yes.
- I think we should hold...
- onto her passport just in case.
- You're right.
There's no reason to come here from another room since it's so cold.
- Meaning the thief's room is here.
- Exactly.
So the thief came out of the room...
- Yes, to drink a cup of coffee.
- and came over here.
- He was drinking coffee here.
- You're right.
Gary, you are amazing.
(He looks in the room.)
(Goodness)
Excuse me.
What is it?
(The witness, Park Kwan Chal, Guest 99)
subtitles ripped and synced by riri13
Are you meeting him for the first time?
You were over here?
- Is it your first time seeing him?
- Yes, it's the first time.
Have a seat.
- Do you know the owner's room?
- Yes.
How many people went in the room?
How many went in?
(Guest 99 witnessed everything...)
(from the beginning to the end.)
(All the members had been in the room, except Jae Seok.)
(His testimony might change the entire course of the investigation.)
- Right.
- Honestly, did you...
try to open the safe or not?
- I didn't.
- Did you try?
- No, I didn't.
- To be honest, I tried.
- Why?
- I was just curious.
- That's weird.
- I tried...
- What are you saying?
- I tried pressing the buttons.
- I tried to press the buttons.
- You're saying this...
- so we don't suspect you.
- No.
I only tried. But I just found out that the password...
- is 0000.
- How do you know?
Ga Yeon told me.
The cabin owner told me.
- I didn't try 0000.
- Are you close with Ga Yeon?
- I know her personally.
- Wait a minute.
- I met her before Running Man.
- Wait.
Give me a break.
Whatever.
He said he tried to open the safe.
He was trying to...
make us think that he had nothing to do with the case.
That was very strange. I'm suspicious of him.
Did Jae Seok go in or not?
He said he didn't go in.
He didn't.
- He didn't go in?
- He went to...
- the room next to Ga Yeon's room.
- Did he...
- go to the next room?
- Yes.
- Was he getting blankets?
- Right.
- The blankets were there.
- Yes, you're right.
- Did he bring out blankets?
- Yes.
I remember clearly.
- Hold on.
- Wait, listen to me.
It was the room next to Ga Yeon's?
Yes, it was.
- Are the rooms connected?
- If it's the room next door,
he could've entered her room through the terrace.
He didn't see Jae Seok go in though.
No, that's not it.
It's Jae Seok.
Why isn't Jae Seok one of the suspects?
(Why isn't Jae Seok one of the suspects?)
That confused me.
He was the only one that didn't go into the owner's room.
The witness, Guest 99, said...
Jae Seok didn't go into that room.
He did not go in.
It's possible that since the rooms were right next to each other,
Jae Suk went into Ga Yeon's room through the terrace,
instead of getting the blankets.
He stole the necklace, came back to the room...
for the blankets and left.
He has a perfect alibi because...
there's a witness.
(Jae Seok has a perfect alibi.)
He didn't go in through the door.
He went in through...
- the terrace.
- Wait.
- Is that possible?
- Usually...
in mystery movies,
- whoever doesn't go inside...
- That's the suspect.
Right. In order to prove that he didn't enter the room,
- he went in the room next to it.
- You're smart.
He went in through the terrace and came back.
- That's great.
- Wow.
That's amazing. Is it okay to catch the suspect this quickly?
What about this?
Someone opened the safe and...
What was that?
(What was that noise?)
Wait a minute.
- What was that?
- At this important moment,
I think a bomb just exploded.
Why did you have to fart at such a critical moment?
- My goodness.
- Oh no.
But why am I covering my mouth?
- Seok Jin.
- Go to the bathroom.
Come on.
- You see.
- Seok Jin,
- you should've restrained yourself.
- Well...
Well, you see...
- it's hard.
- I see.
- I'm sorry.
- Don't be nervous.
- Wait, are you the thief?
- No, I'm not.
- You seem nervous.
- I can't smile if I'm nervous.
You seem to be nervous.
(They continue to argue.)
My diamonds.
Let's check this room.
- Let's ask the guard.
- Okay.
Let's go meet the guard.
- Let's ask the guard.
- The cleaning lady...
and the guard...
have master keys.
What did the cleaning lady say?
She said she only cleaned the room and left.
Excuse me.
Could you please come out for a minute?
- Okay.
- Do you...
have a master key...
that opens the cabin owner's room?
I only keep a record of...
people who stay in the cabin.
If there is a problem, the manager...
So you didn't go to her room today?
I didn't leave this room today.
- Not at all?
- Correct.
Can I check your pockets?
You never know, he might have the necklace.
- You never know.
- That's not how you do it.
- Come on.
- Do you have the master key?
- I don't have it.
- You don't have it?
- I see.
- Where's the manager's room?
- It's over there.
- Okay.
- It's room 14.
- I see.
- Let's go.
- Can we see the guestbook?
- Maybe there's something in there.
- You're right.
There might be something in there.
(It has a record of all the visitors.)
- Why didn't we think of this?
- It's here.
This is an actual list...
of the people who stayed here.
(There might be a clue.)
- Okay, I got it.
- Great.
- Thank you.
- Let's go to room 14 first.
- Shall we?
Let's go to the manager's room.
Oh goodness.
And so we headed for the manager's room.
It's so cold today.
The manager, who has the master key,
is an important person.
It's here.
- This is it.
- It's here, room 14.
It's the manager's room.
We're here.
This is room 14.
It's the manager's room.
Hello?
- Can we ask you something?
- We'd like to...
- ask you something.
- The door is locked.
(The door is locked.)
- Sir?
- It's locked?
- What?
- The door is locked.
Look, it's "Running Milk".
- What is this?
- What is it?
- Leave it alone.
- It might be a clue.
- Wait.
- The milk...
- is still outside.
- Check the date.
- A newspaper is here, too.
- Don't touch it.
The manager wasn't here.
- He must've stolen the necklace.
- No.
- He's dead.
- What?
- What do you mean?
- What are you talking about?
His shoes are here. What is the date on the newspaper?
- His shoes are really here.
- That's why he's the thief.
(That means there's someone inside.)
- This says January 26th.
- What's the date on the newspaper?
- It's the same.
- It's a murder case.
What's today's date?
Isn't it the 26th?
- Where's the manager?
- If it's really a murder case,
we need to call the police.
- Hurry!
- Someone's on the floor.
- What?
- Really?
- Are you sure?
- The manager is on the floor.
- Really?
- I told you.
- The manager didn't drink the milk.
- Are you crazy?
- He's on the floor.
- This is a murder case.
- How could this be?
- It's a murder case.
- Wait a minute.
- His name tag is on the floor.
- The murder happened inside.
- The door is locked on the outside.
- And it's locked on the inside.
- I'm a pro at this.
I was at Johns Hopkins...
Be quiet!
- Where is that?
- Where is Johns Hopkins?
- Tell me where it is.
- Johns Hopkins...
- Wait.
- Why are you stuttering?
- Who am I?
I'm Johns Hopkins.
Look. The door is locked from inside and someone's dead.
This means that the murder took place inside.
- Hey!
- This is how you make it exciting.
- Jong Kook!
- This is thrilling.
Come here, the door is open.
- What?
- The door is open.
The door is open?
This door is open.
- Give me a hand.
- Okay, get on top of me.
- Help her.
- Okay.
The door is open?
It's open over here.
- I'm sorry, Jong Kook.
- It's okay.
- Step on me.
- Shouldn't Jae Seok go in?
- Will you be okay?
- I'll go in first.
- Be careful.
- Don't touch anything.
- Hey, Ji Hyo!
- Goodness.
- Be careful.
- Oh no.
Ji Hyo!
- Ji Hyo!
- Come in.
This is a crime scene.
Ji Hyo don't touch anything.
Don't touch anything.
Don't touch anything!
(The manager's death)
(Who did it?)
(When?)
(Why?)
(Gary, Jae Seok, Seok Jin, Haha)
(Jong Kook, Ji Hyo, Kwang Soo)
(The secrets are getting bigger.)
I saw someone who was brutally eliminated.
It was inhumane.
(The members investigate the crime scene.)
- Goodness.
- It smells.
First, let's take a look.
(They will investigate in three teams.)
First, let's take a look at the manager.
He's right-handed.
(He has ketchup on his right hand. He must be right-handed.)
We have to figure out...
what he was trying to write on the floor.
What letter is it?
He wrote it twice.
He started from here...
and stopped here.
Then he went straight.
Aren't I right? He stopped here.
He went like this.
I don't think it was just...
any letter.
It might not be someone's name.
It could be a symbol.
Or it could be something else.
What do you think happened?
Don't we have to find out...
what these letters are? What can they be?
Wait, look.
Does it say Kwang Soo?
Isn't it written backwards?
Kwang Soo.
(Kwang Soo)
Did you see the dying message?
(Did you see the dying message?)
What is that?
(What is that?)
Is it the title of a movie?
(Is it the title of a movie?)
What is a dying message?
(Is it a new form of SNS?)
(Seok Jin, Gary and Haha investigate.)
This is creepy.
I've seen numerous crime scenes, but this one is really bad.
I found hair.
I see hair.
Isn't it a woman's hair?
Long strands of hair were stuck to the name tag.
There's a big chance...
that the suspect is a woman.
I have a few scenarios in my mind.
One is that Ga Yeon...
could've staged it.
(Ga Yeon could have staged the whole thing.)
I think...
that's the most plausible scenario.
The manager wrote two letters before he died.
It could be...
K for Kim and G for Ga.
I think she staged it herself.
That's...
what I think for now.
Wait a minute.
- It's either Ji Hyo and Ga Yeon.
- Ji Hyo.
But it's hard for a woman to eliminate a man.
(It's hard for a woman to eliminate a man.)
How can a woman knock down this big man?
(Seok Jin predicts that the suspect must have an accomplice.)
Wow.
- Seok Jin is really...
- Don't you agree?
(Seok Jin is on a roll today.)
He's a great detective today.
The crime wasn't committed alone.
I think that...
two women were in it together.
And that is because...
women love diamonds.
(Ji Hyo and Kwang Soo thoroughly investigate the scene.)
What's this?
What Is this?
Turbo!
Seok Jin's CD is here as well.
There's Leessang's CD, too.
Why is Haha's CD missing?
Right?
- Kwang Soo, look.
- Yes?
Hold on.
What is this?
Look, Kwang Soo.
- Giraffe, grasshopper.
- It's not me.
("Run, Grasshopper", "Giraffe That Cries Cock-a-Doodle-Doo")
Kwang Soo... Kwang Soo...
("The Story of Kwang Soo and Hwa Ni")
- There's a book with Haha, too.
- Haha.
Kwang Soo and Hwa Ni...
(Is he the suspect?)
I have goose bumps right now.
(I have goose bumps right now.)
I can't believe I was in the same room as the suspect.
(I can't believe I was in the same room as the suspect.)
I think the suspect would've...
gotten rid of all the evidence...
that leads to him.
Inside the room, there was Turbo's CD, Seok Jin's CD...
and Leessang's CD. Those were the three CDs in the room.
And on the books,
were the names of Haha, me and...
Jae Seok. There were three names.
But there was absolutely no evidence...
relating to Ji Hyo.
(There was no evidence relating to Ji Hyo.)
When you take the long strand of hair into account.
When you think of the long strand of hair on the name tag,
I am certain that it's Ji Hyo.
(He's certain that it's Ji Hyo.)
- Isn't it right?
- Oh no!
- What is it?
- What's wrong?
- This is crazy. I got the chills.
- Why?
What happened?
(They enter the manager's master bedroom.)
Oh my!
- No way.
- Oh my goodness.
(Goodness!)
Look at the pictures!
(What is the password for the safe with the diamond necklace inside?)
- So the manager...
- Is he the thief?
was very interested in the necklace.
- Right?
- From the very beginning.
Hold on.
"What's the password?"
Baekriyang Unit 10?
Master key, okay.
(Baekriyang Unit 10, master key okay)
Baekriyang is the name of the cabin owner's room.
- Is that right?
- Yes.
I see.
(Is the manager the thief?)
Then why did he get eliminated?
Oh my goodness!
The 26th!
- That's today.
- Today was D-day.
He planned it. He planned to rob the diamond necklace.
The date of the newspaper is the 26th,
and he didn't pick it up.
That means he didn't get to come out of the house.
He never got out of the house in the morning.
The fact that he didn't pick up today's newspaper this morning,
but he has all the newspapers from the previous dates.
That means something happened between last night and this morning.
The person who stayed all night with him is the suspect.
Someone who stayed all night with him.
Then that makes a strange situation. Our members...
(Meanwhile, Ga Yeon's situation)
Oh dear.
What?
(Huffing)
I can't believe this.
(Hurrying outside)
- This is a crime scene.
- He has the master key for...
Baekriyang Unit 10?
Look!
It's a reminder.
(Reminder)
- It's a reminder of his debts.
- Oh wow.
- He owes 500,000 dollars.
- He was...
- in severe debt.
- It's 500,000 dollars of debt.
After seeing the manager's room,
I got the chills.
What did you see there?
The manager was in huge debt,
and he was eyeing...
the cabin owner's diamond necklace.
D-day for robbery was the 26th.
Which is today.
However, before he was able to act,
he was eliminated.
(Seok Jin predicts that the manager was eliminated yesterday.)
That's why I'm confused.
- I'm so scared.
- The manager is...
(It gives them chills to think about it.)
The manager...
- The manager...
- Goodness.
What's wrong with you? He's Mister Fart.
Mister Fart...
exploded again!
(Moving)
Seok Jin farted again!
(He returned from death thanks to Seok Jin's fart.)
Wait a minute.
The master key is missing.
- You're right.
- The master key is missing.
Someone has the master key.
I need to check the members' rooms first.
I might find the necklace.
(He might find the necklace in the members' rooms.)
I need to check my room as well.
Where are you going?
- I'm going to check the rooms.
- There are three suspicious people.
I'm going to search their rooms.
(They go in a group to search the members' rooms.)
- What is this?
- Behind you.
Wait, hold on.
The CD on the bed was...
Leessang's second album.
Turbo's second album was there, too.
- Is that Seok Jin's second album?
- Are they all our second albums?
- It's my second album.
- So they are all second albums.
- Really?
- They are all second albums.
- Really? The second album?
- I got goose bumps.
- The second album.
- They are all the second album.
(Whose room should I search first?)
Goodness, this is mind-blowing.
- There's nothing.
- You are Unit Two!
(Kwang Soo's room is Unit Two.)
Wait a minute.
(Jae Seok guesses that the suspect is related to the number two.)
- Kwang Soo is in Unit Two!
- That's not it!
- Kwang Soo is the suspect.
And his last name is Lee too.
- That's right.
- His last name is Lee.
It's not me.
There's only one member with the last name, Lee.
(The members begin to investigate Kwang Soo's room)
Something is strange.
Look!
Look at this!
There is a long strand of hair. Don't touch it.
Bring the camera and film this.
There's a long strand of hair.
(They continue to investigate Kwang Soo's room.)
He wouldn't have put the diamond here.
There has to be something.
Look!
(What's that?)
What's that?
(That key is...)
It's the master key!
(It's the master key.)
(Why is the master key...)
(in Kwang Soo's room?)
- It's the master key.
- Let me see.
- It was hanging here.
- Really?
(Is Kwang Soo the suspect?)
(Previously on Running Man)
It's a real party.
- My necklace disappeared.
- The necklace?
Let's investigate the area.
Have you seen anyone near the cabin owner's room?
The manager collapsed on the floor!
- What's this?
- It's the master key!
(Who is the suspect of the mountain cabin crime?)
(Gary, Yu Jae Seok)
(Jee Seok Jin, Haha)
(Kim Jong Kook, Song Ji Hyo, Lee Kwang Soo)
(Evidence or Tricks)
So...
people suspected me all day.
All the alibis and evidence...
pointed at me.
The master key was hanging in my room.
(All the evidence pointed to him.)
So many things happened. However,
it's the suspect who set this whole thing up.
- It's a setup?
- Yes.
- Really?
- The master key was hanging here.
Really? Come here.
- How dare you!
- Come here.
Confess.
- Confess already.
- How does he have the master key?
- I can't believe it.
- I didn't see that.
And like this, we have now caught the suspect.
- Jae Seok, call the police.
- Yes?
Let's listen to what he has to say.
- Jong Kook.
- Leave the key and tell us.
Why is the key here?
- This?
- Right.
I don't know either.
(Punching)
What is this? He really punched me.
- Jong Kook, don't hurt him.
- I really got hit!
Think again.
- Kwang Soo, think again.
- The police will come soon.
- Why is this here?
- What happened?
- What?
- What did you say?
- He really hit me.
- I didn't see it.
What? How could he do this?
- Wait a minute.
- Is this a scene from a movie?
- Hold on.
- What is it?
- Continue the investigation.
- Okay.
Calm down, everyone.
- Tell us the truth.
- That hurts!
- Kwang Soo.
- Why are you hitting me?
- Why is this here?
- Who hit you?
Why are you all so immersed in this situation?
So tell us why the master key is here.
Tell us quickly.
- Why is it here?
- I really don't know.
- All right.
- That hurts.
(Then we will wait until you figure it out.)
- I know.
- He's really hitting me!
- What's wrong, Sir?
The camera is filming you. Watch what you say.
- He's really hitting me!
- Hold on.
- Kwang Soo.
- Let's just talk like this.
- Producer Lim!
- Don't worry.
- No one's hitting anyone.
- Producer Lim!
- Why do you have the key?
- Why is the key here?
- Why do you have this key?
- Tell us.
- Wait, listen to me.
At least give us an idea.
- An idea.
- If I am the suspect,
do you think I will put the key in a place that is so easily visible?
What does that matter?
- That's it.
- You're right.
- He's got a point.
- Jong Kook, he has a point.
- Let's think carefully.
- He's got a point.
- If I am the suspect,
- He has a point.
- That's true.
- I wouldn't put the keys in a...
- place where you can see them.
- You're right.
You make sense.
- Right.
- This feels like a setup.
But why is this key here?
- Isn't it so strange?
- If I were you,
- It seems like a setup.
- I would look at the key...
- and know that I'm not the suspect.
- It does seem like a setup.
This key was missing from the janitor's key box.
- This key is important.
Who was Ga Yeon most interested in today?
- Jong Kook.
- Exactly.
They like each other.
If we were in a movie,
- Jong Kook must be the culprit.
- It's possible.
That makes sense.
- Then am I done now?
- Wait.
- I just remembered something.
- What is it?
- Seok Jin.
- Yes.
(Jae Seok asks Seok Jin a question.)
The prices of the stocks you invested in...
are dropping, aren't they?
- Really?
- Wait.
The prices were going down.
- Look.
What's going on?
He's suspicious.
- I'm innocent.
- Let me repeat.
- The prices are dropping.
- Hold him.
- What happened to your stocks?
- He's...
- He's the most...
- Tell us about your stocks
- Tell us.
- Listen.
- It wasn't...
- Speak towards the camera.
I took a peep...
(Beating)
Are you okay?
Oh, my.
I looked at the stock prices.
I looked at the prices of his stocks.
They're really not doing well.
They were all dropping.
- Do you remember anything?
- Seok Jin.
- Do you recall anything?
I'm innocent.
My situation is not so bad that I have to steal a necklace.
Doesn't your wife love jewellery?
- You two got new rings.
- She does.
- She does, right?
- Yes.
See?
Everything points to him.
- It's over now.
- It's over.
I have another critical clue.
- We had a conversation earlier.
- Stop it.
He told me,
"To be honest, I tried to open the safe."
He said that...
- Really?
- to make us believe...
- that he's not the culprit.
- Right.
It was his trick.
One more thing.
There was a reason...
why he farted so much today.
It was because he was nervous.
It might be because he ate so much meat.
(Is it the meat or is it because he was nervous?)
He ate too much meat.
Do you know what that means?
- It means...
- He's a greedy pig!
- Hey.
- I'm serious!
- I wasn't going to say that.
- You're being too harsh.
I didn't mean it.
I'm sorry.
- It does seem...
- Somebody set him up.
like somebody set Kwang Soo up.
Our prime suspects...
are...
- Is it Kwang Soo?
- these three.
Jae Seok found the key.
It was found in Kwang Soo's room.
And Gary was the last one to be here.
- You're spot on.
- You're perceptive.
Then we're not suspected.
I'm just speaking my opinion.
And there's someone that's the most suspicious.
Why do you talk so much?
- Why do you suspect everyone?
- He talks too much!
- Wait.
- You're being suspicious.
This is crazy.
It's strange.
He doesn't usually talk this much.
- He's talking too much.
- He's being strange.
Does he think he's Sherlock Holmes?
He's talking way too much.
- What did he say?
- He said he's innocent.
Wait.
You were talking a lot, too. He talked more than me.
You made us suspect him.
It was strange.
He talked too much.
It was too obvious.
(At 8:00pm, Ji Hyo is investigating.)
This hair was found on the name tag.
This must belong to a woman.
There must be an accomplice.
Let me pull out just one. Done.
(Will it help find the culprit?)
- Why did she pull out her hair?
- It takes long to grow one.
(Ji Hyo obtained the cleaning lady's hair.)
(She's going to compare it with the one in the janitor's room.)
Let's see.
The length is not right.
They're different lengths.
(They're different lengths.)
The length is not right.
(Then who does this hair belong to?)
It's not the same.
(Meanwhile, Gary...)
Lee Kwang Soo.
Kwang Soo was suspected once.
So was Jae Seok.
This car wasn't here before.
(Gary found a suspicious car...)
(with initials "GY" on it.)
Let's see.
(Gary examines the car.)
(What is this?)
Wait.
(Gary found a picture in the car.)
(Will this give Gary a hint?)
(At 8:20pm, Jae Seok is pondering.)
Who would have left the key in Kwang Soo's room?
(Jae Seok visits the information office...)
(to find out the secret about the key.)
Let me ask you a question.
Who are you suspecting?
- I had been unsure...
- Okay.
until I found...
(Until I found...)
a critical...
(a critical...)
- clue.
- Okay.
Tell me about it.
I looked at the guestbook...
that the janitor had kept.
- In the guestbook...
- Okay.
for the day before the incident,
there was a critical clue.
(There was a critical clue.)
(He visited the janitor's office before the police arrived.)
Excuse me.
- Could I see the guestbook?
- Sure.
Thank you.
(Looking carefully)
25th.
"Sibling" visited on 25th.
(He found a name "Sibling" among the visitors on the 25th.)
Everyone else wrote his or her real name.
But this one says "Sibling".
"Sibling"?
(Her sibling was here yesterday?)
What would that mean?
Why didn't I realise it before?
(Why didn't I realise it before?)
What would "Sibling" mean?
(What would "Sibling" mean?)
It means he's younger than her.
(It means he's younger than her.)
That excludes Seok Jin and me.
Jong Kook, Kwang Soo, Gary, Haha and Ji Hyo...
(The culprit must be younger than Ga Yeon.)
are younger than Ga Yeon.
That's why he wrote "Sibling".
(One of the younger ones was here yesterday.)
I'm not really sure.
We don't have enough clues. If it's one of us,
it must be Ji Hyo.
Or it could be Ga Yeon...
or the cleaning lady who stole the key.
(Judging from the hair found in the room, it must be a woman.)
(Ji Hyo came to Kwang Soo's room.)
- Seok Jin.
- Yes.
Have you found anything?
The key was found here.
- Really?
- Yes.
(Ji Hyo realised the key was in Kwang Soo's room.)
But it didn't feel right.
- Seok Jin.
- He must not have done that.
- Look.
- Okay.
I'm the only one...
whose name was not in the book.
And there was a woman's hair.
- Do you understand?
- The circumstances point to you.
They do. But I'm innocent.
I think it's neither you nor Kwang Soo.
I think this whole thing was staged by Ga Yeon.
I thought so too.
- I do think so.
- She's after the insurance money.
Seok Jin.
Seok Jin!
- Yes.
- Are we to point out the culprit?
Yes, we are.
- When the police are here?
- Yes.
But we don't have much clues.
Everything points to Ji Hyo.
Wait.
(They're having a discussion.)
- What if...
- Yes.
the janitor's actually not dead?
- I hear a scream.
- Gosh.
- Help!
- This is scary.
Someone's dead!
(They heard a scream.)
- What?
- Someone's dead.
- Who is it?
- Hurry!
- Someone's dead.
Someone's dead.
Who is it?
What happened?
- Where is it?
- It's here!
- Is someone dead?
- Yes!
- Hurry!
- Preserve the scene!
Preserve the scene!
- Oh.
- What happened?
Preserve the scene!
It's the cleaning lady.
(Shocking)
(In the laundry room,)
(with her name tag ripped off,)
(a lady is lying on the floor.)
(Cleaning Lady)
(Signs of struggle)
Preserve the scene!
(This lady...)
We found a woman's hair.
Are you saying you think that hair belongs to me?
(Why did this happen to her?)
Preserve the scene!
It's the cleaning lady.
- Gosh.
- Preserve the scene.
- Don't make a fuss.
- Who found her?
- When was she found?
Who found her?
- I just got here...
- Okay.
- and found her.
- I see.
- I came here to get some blankets.
- Okay.
- Look for evidence.
- Wait.
(They're busy investigating.)
- Examine the scene.
- Wait.
Before she died,
she might have left a message.
We shouldn't touch her.
Is there anything?
- Can we touch her?
- Do you see anything?
- We shouldn't touch her.
- Is there anything?
Can we touch her?
- Do you see anything?
- She had the key.
What is that?
- Oh.
- She has some pictures.
(Will they find any evidence in her phone?)
Let's look at the pictures.
- Hey!
- It was taken here.
It was taken here.
She's wearing the necklace.
Let me see.
- My goodness.
- Show me.
She's wearing the necklace.
It's the necklace.
(A picture of her wearing the necklace was taken at 8:57pm.)
Was the janitor here?
Were they in a relationship?
No.
The person tried the necklace on the lady.
(The necklace is missing at the moment.)
The person tried it on her.
The person let her try it on and she took a photo.
To falsely lay the blame on her.
Because after she tried it on...
- So she just tried it on?
- That's right.
- Then she took a selfie.
- It's a trick.
- This is a trick.
- She's not the thief.
- It's to pin the blame on her.
To make her look like the thief.
- Look,
- Because it's not us.
first it was Kwang Soo, then now it's the cleaning lady.
Who's the one person that didn't appear?
It's the owner.
So all we need to do is go to her.
- Let's go.
- Yes, let's go.
(Wait a minute.)
Is this the office?
Look!
- In the list of the calls she made,
- Yes?
there's Ga Yeon.
- You're right.
- Did she make the call or take it?
- When was it?
- At 9:03pm.
It was 30 minutes ago.
So this lady was alive 30 minutes ago.
This is scary.
This is really breathtaking.
It really is.
But it's strange that the lady tried the necklace on...
and took a selfie...
just because she was asked to.
- Would you have tried it on?
- Let me see the photo again.
She might have liked how it looked on her.
- This is all set up to make it...
- Exactly.
look like she's the thief.
It's possible to have taken the photo.
All we need to do is confront the owner.
- Let's go.
- Yes, let's go.
- Wait.
- Look.
Why?
- There was a missed call?
- Yes.
- Let me see.
- Who was it?
Don't hide it.
Look at the missed calls.
- Let us see.
- Show it to us.
- Show us.
- Hurry.
Why are you trying to hide it?
It's not that.
- You should be careful, Kwang Soo.
- Show it to us.
- You should be careful.
- Hey.
- Come here.
- Come over here.
- It's not that.
- You're really strange.
You saw that I was surprised.
I was surprised.
- It's from the owner.
- Ga Yeon?
- Look at this.
- Wait a minute.
I was surprised, too.
- Hey.
- I was surprised like everyone.
- What's your deal?
- I was surprised.
What is your relationship with her?
I think this is a setup too.
- This is a setup.
- Don't you think so?
I'm being set up.
But how on earth did...
- Why?
- There's a hairpin.
We saw that already.
You did?
- You saw it already?
- It doesn't really...
mean anything.
There's another hairpin here too.
(What is the meaning of the hairpins lying around the scene?)
Do the hairpins have any significant meaning?
- At 8:57pm...
- There's another hairpin here.
(The clue of the selfie that was taken at 8:57pm.)
The first photo...
was taken at 8:57pm.
(Six minutes later, she gets a call from Ga Yeon.)
The lady didn't steal it.
It wasn't her.
I think we need to meet the owner first.
I have to meet her first.
(He walks over to Ga Yeon's room in an instant.)
- Excuse me.
- Yes.
(At this instant,)
(we would like to hear an explanation from you.)
(What is he doing here?)
(He realises instantly that something fishy is going on.)
Did you cook ramyun?
(Did you cook ramyun?)
(She laughs.)
Did you?
Excuse me.
- Yes?
- You had the time...
to cook ramyun?
Do you feel better now?
I'm still knocked out.
(How could she eat something?)
(Losing the necklace is already done and over.)
I haven't had ramyun in a long time.
(A person needs to eat.)
Ga Yeon.
(This is embarrassing.)
- Excuse me.
- Yes?
- Ga Yeon.
- Please answer this question.
- Okay.
The cleaning lady...
has been found dead.
When did she die?
The presumed time of her death is between 9:10pm and 9:33pm.
But it seems that...
you talked to the cleaning lady over the phone.
- We did have a talk.
- Yes?
(Let's have a look.)
Anyways, wasn't it...
- at 9:06pm?
- Yes, that's right.
She called me at that time and we had a talk.
- What did she say?
- Since there were a lot of...
barbecue parties today, she had worked overtime.
She asked how much more pay she would receive.
The lady took a photo...
of herself wearing the necklace.
(Goodness!)
- Really?
- Yes.
Didn't you talk for a minute on the phone?
- No, that's not true.
- Was that all she said?
- Yes.
- I have another question.
Do you have a sibling?
No, I don't.
- You don't?
- I don't.
Someone checked in as your sibling on the guestbook.
No, I'm the only child.
If someone checked in as your sibling,
on the 25th, the person must be very close to you.
I think it must be someone you know.
I don't remember. There's simply too many people.
No, there was only one person.
- Who was it?
- The person that came on the 25th.
- Someone close enough.
- But it might be that...
- What?
- Close friends...
know that if they check in as a sibling,
- they can receive a discount.
- Wait a minute.
Yes?
Why did you call Kwang Soo?
(Blinking)
That is what confuses me.
I think Ga Yeon did that...
to make an alibi.
She called Kwang Soo,
in order to make others...
look more suspicious.
She's a very bad person.
(Is Ga Yeon really...)
(a bad person?)
My goodness.
- Hey.
- Yes?
Didn't you stage this?
- You should call me madam.
- I'm sorry.
- All right, Madam.
- Yes?
(Seok Jin suspects Ga Yeon.)
- Aren't you tricking us?
- If I had the necklace insured...
then it's possible, but I don't.
- So there's no reason.
- Tell me who knows...
- Yes?
- the password.
- You're the only one that knows it.
- I don't know.
You're the only one that knows the password.
What's this?
(What's this?)
What is it?
(Seok Jin hides it behind his back.)
Yes?
What is it?
- Explain this.
- Wait.
A theft insurance policy.
This insurance policy...
- Wait a minute.
- Ji Hyo,
- you and I...
- Goodness.
- Wait, what is this?
- What's this? Explain this.
My father got this insurance without me knowing.
Your father? Let me see.
It's an insurance policy worth 10 million dollars.
Really?
- Yes, 10 million dollars.
- My goodness.
Did you really not know?
I didn't know. I didn't sign it.
Are you sure?
I told you to look around before.
But you told me there was nothing.
Seok Jin, she's pretending to have the necklace stolen.
- Then...
- But...
it might be true that Ga Yeon didn't know about the insurance.
I really didn't know.
You didn't know you were insured?
No, I didn't.
(Is she telling the truth?)
- I think...
- Yes?
she plotted the whole thing.
- You're right.
- She's fooling us.
- Either that...
- There's the insurance.
- or...
- Yes?
her father...
Her father?
- got someone to do it.
- Hired someone.
- Yes, hired someone to steal it.
- I think you're right.
He must have hired one of the members.
He hired someone...
to steal the necklace.
He told the person the password...
- and let the person steal it.
- And...
the guard and the cleaning lady are also...
in on this. Losing the master key...
was also staged.
- That's right.
- Seok Jin.
But who was hired to do it?
- I think it's Jae Seok.
- It's Jae Seok, right?
Yes.
Do you have the phone number under the name "Sibling"?
No, I don't have a sibling.
I told you before that I don't have a sibling.
- Are you sure?
- Yes.
Well then.
All right.
- Is that all?
- Yes.
Come visit often.
- All right.
- I'm bored.
(She must be hiding something on her phone.)
To be frank, you can't trust anyone in Running Man.
Even if we say that we trust each other,
we have doubts about the other person.
Why is there a car out there?
This is really baffling me.
Gosh.
Don't tell me it's in here.
Please don't.
Don't you dare come out.
Since I received the invitation...
(Since I received the invitation...)
I'm the most suspicious person?
(Then let's see that invitation letter again.)
This is an invitation to the mountain cabin.
You have won a free voucher to lodge at our mountain cabin.
The mountain cabin is located in Gyeonggi-do, Gapyeong.
(Jae Seok is in search of the cell phone.)
(He has arrived at the guard's room.)
Excuse me.
(The police are about to arrive.)
(Everyone is trying to come to conclusions.)
This isn't easy.
(Whose bag is this?)
(Invitation to our mountain cabin. Congratulations.)
(He is carefully looking over the invitation letter.)
(The letter is addressed to Kwang Soo from Running mountain cabin.)
Wait a minute.
It was stamped in Mapo-gu?
(The letter was sent from Mapo-gu, not Gapyeong.)
It was here.
It was over here.
There was a cell phone here.
Oh.
(Look!)
(Something is in here.)
Oh gosh.
That was unexpected.
(That was unexpected.)
I found something crucial.
I saw the insurance policy that the other members...
didn't see.
It could've been staged by the owner.
(Did anyone find the real suspect?)
This is how it was found out.
This was it.
(What is Jae Seok looking at?)
(Gary is thinking hard.)
This is crazy.
(What did Gary see?)
(The police is here.)
(In order to solve this case,)
(the police finally came...)
(after four hours.)
(They are here.)
(Who is this?)
No way!
Sir!
(Detective Yeom of Violent Crimes Department)
It's the police. Wait a minute!
How have you been, Doctor?
(He played the doctor in the zombie episode.)
Doctor! Salute!
(Nice to see you again.)
- How have you been?
- It's nice to see you again.
- I switched jobs.
- I see.
- I'm Detective Yeom.
- Hello, Sir.
- Sir.
- Did you take the zombie medicine?
- Doctor.
- You're alive.
- Sir.
- You are alive, doctor.
- Hi.
- I have a secret.
- Hello.
- I'm a triplet.
(The Yeom triplets)
That was funny.
Police! Police!
You're here. Why did you come...
- so late?
- Wait.
- Everyone listen.
- Okay.
Do not share information with each other.
You should only tell me what you know.
You are all suspects and witnesses of the stolen...
Tears of the Sun case.
- Okay.
- We'll...
- go to the inquisition room.
- Yes.
- I'll start interrogating.
- Okay.
- Let's go.
(Who is the real suspect?)
Congratulations, you won a free lodging event.
My necklace disappeared! What am I going to do?
Someone is unconscious!
- The master key is missing.
- The master key?
What's going on?
It's a fake. He's not the culprit.
- What does it say?
- Wait a minute.
- They're toying with us.
- This is too much.
This is how he knew.
(Gary, Jae Seok, Seok Jin, Haha)
(Jong Kook, Ji Hyo, Kwang Soo)
How did you come here?
I'm Kwang Soo's close friend.
Kwang Soo asked me to come.
As you know, a lot of things...
- happened at the mountain cabin.
- Yes.
Who do you think...
the culprit is?
Well, there are many suspects.
(There are many suspects.)
- If I had to choose someone,
- Yes.
I'd choose Jae Seok and Kwang Soo.
(Haha suspects Jae Seok and Kwang Soo.)
What is your reasoning?
When we were trying to solve the case together...
and couldn't find an answer,
we heard a scream.
(There was a scream.)
Everyone was there...
Help!
Everyone was there except Jae Seok and Kwang Soo.
The "Out" incident happened then.
(The "Out" incident happened then.)
They weren't there.
When the cleaning lady was tagged out,
only Jae Seok and Kwang Soo...
weren't at the scene.
So do you suspect Jae Seok?
Since we found out "Tears of the Sun"...
was stolen,
Jae Seok was on his own.
Kwang Soo also...
was on his own most of the times.
(Kwang Soo was by himself a lot.)
I suspect...
Jae Seok and Kwang Soo.
(Ji Hyo suspects Jae Seok and Kwang Soo.)
- The manager was also tagged out.
- Yes.
According to the witness, there was an argument the day before...
and the milk and newspaper dated January 26th...
was left outside. That means...
the manager was tagged out on the 25th...
before the milk and the newspapers...
were delivered.
- The newspapers and the milk...
- Right.
And inside the room there were...
a lot of books that pointed to...
Jae Seok and Kwang Soo.
Haha, Kwang Soo, Jae Seok,
Jong Kook, Turbo, Haha, Kwang Soo.
What do you think is the truth?
I don't know. But I saw...
an insurance policy.
- An insurance policy?
- Yes.
But the owner didn't know...
about the insurance policy.
I'm not sure if that's true or not.
The manager could've...
wanted Ga Yeon's necklace very badly.
There were a lot of pictures...
of Ga Yeon. I'm not sure if he...
was obsessed over her or the necklace. Anyway,
I think he had a plan.
He seemed to be in debt.
The manager was tagged out yesterday.
There were strands of hair on his name tag.
(There were strands of hair on his name tag.)
They were long. That means it was a woman.
The cleaning lady was tagged out too.
I checked her cell phone.
She had talked to Ga Yeon over the phone.
I think Ga Yeon...
staged everything.
(Ga Yeon is the criminal.)
I think Ga Yeon was having a financial crisis.
- The necklace was insured.
- Okay.
I think she staged everything in order to...
receive the insurance money.
Are you saying Ga Yeon also staged the invitation...
- that was sent to Kwang Soo?
- Yes.
- People find Kwang Soo suspicious.
- I see.
I think Ga Yeon knew this and...
- tried to frame him.
- She framed him.
- I think Ga Yeon planted the...
- Hey!
- master key in Kwang Soo's room.
- Where's the master key?
I think Ga Yeon did all that...
in order to frame Kwang Soo for the crimes.
- Okay.
- I believe...
Kim Ga Yeon is the criminal who staged everything.
(Jong Kook suspects Ga Yeon.)
Actually,
people easily suspect me every week.
So I think it's one of the members...
who used that...
against me.
(He suspects the members.)
It has to be one of them.
When we...
went into the manager's room,
I saw four CDs...
on the bed.
(Four members released albums.)
Haha's CD was missing.
(Haha's album wasn't there.)
- Haha's CD wasn't there.
- Right.
- And here's the crucial clue.
- Okay.
(It's the crucial clue.)
I will show you.
(To Kwang Soo)
It's this stamp.
(Mapo-gu)
It says "Mapo-gu".
Out of the members, the only person who lives in mapo-gu...
is Haha.
(Kwang Soo suspects Haha.)
Let's start from the beginning.
What's your name?
My name is Kang Hee Geon.
- What?
- It's Gary.
Okay, Gary.
(I thought I was really being interrogated.)
I'm sorry.
I thought I had to tell you my real name.
Who do you think is the...
real criminal?
I think it's...
Ga Yeon's siblings. They...
- are after the insurance money.
- Insurance money?
Why do you think that?
There was a car...
parked in front of Ga Yeon's room. It seemed like her car.
There was a picture.
- Is that so?
- Yes.
Who else do you think is the criminal?
(Who else is the criminal?)
Stop pondering and just spit it out.
(What does Gary think?)
- It's been confusing.
- Okay.
- I suspected Kwang Soo at first.
- I see.
- Okay.
- I think...
(The criminal is...)
I think it's Haha.
(It's Haha.)
Why do you think so?
I saw the guestbook.
(He looked at the guard's guestbook.)
- One of the visitors...
- Yes.
on the 25th...
wrote "sibling" instead of a name.
It must be someone...
who is close enough to Ga Yeon...
that he or she can just write "sibling" instead of a name.
Also...
- the dying message...
- Yes.
- I think...
it means...
(Did Jae Seok solve the mystery sign?)
"Little Brat".
(Does the dying message read "Little Brat"?)
Little brat.
- Little brat?
- Yes.
Little brat is Haha's nickname.
- I see.
- So it must be Haha.
(That's why it's Haha.)
(Who is the real criminal?)
After investigating...
the crime scenes and listening to your testimonies,
I was able to find the real criminal.
- Really?
- Did you figure it out?
It must be one of us.
- Did you catch the person?
- Yes, we caught him.
- That's great.
- Did you find the necklace too?
- Yes, we found it.
- Really?
- The suspect is...
- Who is it?
(Is it Seok Jin who was anxious all day long?)
(Is it Kwang Soo who got suspected?)
(Is it Jae Seok who was alone the whole time?)
(Is it Ga Yeon, the mysterious owner of the mountain cabin?)
(Or is it Haha who was unusually active in the search?)
(Who is the culprit?)
- The suspect is...
- Who is it?
(Is it Seok Jin who was anxious all day long?)
(Is it Kwang Soo who got suspected?)
(Is it Jae Seok who was alone the whole time?)
(Is it Ga Yeon, the mysterious owner of the mountain cabin?)
(Or is it Haha who was unusually active in the search?)
(Who is the culprit?)
Kim Ga Yeon and Haha.
- Really?
- I guessed it right!
(Oh my gosh)
Kim Ga Yeon and Haha.
- Really?
- I guessed it right!
(Ga Yeon and Haha were behind everything.)
- It's not me!
- I knew it!
I knew it!
- Really?
- I knew it!
They were the culprits!
- What?
- It wasn't me.
- I was innocent.
- There were two people...
who figured out the criminals.
It's Jae Seok and Gary.
(Jae Seok and Gary guessed it right.)
- Yes!
- How did you find out?
Who do you think...
is the suspect of this incident?
(Gary suggested that Kim Ga Yeon had an accomplice.)
I think it's Haha.
(He picked Haha as the other suspect.)
I think Haha and...
Ga Yeon are siblings.
(He suspects Haha and Ga Yeon to be siblings.)
What's the reason for that?
I saw...
(How are they siblings when they have different last names?)
I saw Haha's wallet in his bag.
And there was...
Haha's family picture.
It was Haha and his older sister.
In front of Ga Yeon's room, there was a car parked.
And she had the same picture.
- You found the picture in the car.
- Yes.
So my guess is that...
they were separated when they were young.
(He suspects that they are siblings separated in the past.)
This incident was done by Haha and Kim Ga Yeon.
(Gary's conclusion is that Haha and Ga Yeon did it together.)
They did it to get the insurance money.
- The insurance money?
- Yes.
- Little brat.
It has to be Haha.
Also, I...
(Jae Seok pointed Haha as the suspect.)
I found a crucial evidence.
- Another one?
- Yes.
You will know what it is when you see it.
This is the guard's cell phone.
The suspects are...
Kim Ga Yeon and Haha.
- They are accomplices.
- Yes.
Everything is here.
This was found on the guard's cell phone.
(There is a written oath in the guard's cell phone.)
That's Kim Ga Yeon.
(Little brother)
See that?
Yes. Therefore,
the guard was pressed because of the debts and...
he accidentally found out about Haha and Ga Yeon's plan.
So he took a picture of them planning the crime...
and using that picture,
he continued to threaten them, especially the owner.
That's why she conspired with Haha and...
got rid of the guard.
(Afraid that their plan will be revealed, they removed the guard.)
(What is the truth?)
Yes, this is what happened.
(This is the whole story of the incident.)
Oh gosh.
It's been a while, Sister.
Yes, it's been a while.
(They are siblings from different mothers.)
Several days ago, I was cleaning Father's room and...
Haha and Kim Ga Yeon are siblings from different mothers.
And they discover that their father is about to donate all his wealth.
Does it make sense?
How could he do that?
- How can he?
- Come on.
Ga Yeon decides to...
steal the Tears of the Sun necklace, which is worth 20 million dollars.
On top of that, she also plots a self-fabricated incident...
with Haha to earn 10-million-dollar insurance money.
You know how much this is worth, right?
- 10 million dollars!
- 10 million dollars.
(10 million dollars)
The Tears of the Sun is mine forever.
10 million dollars!
They chose to put the blame on Kwang Soo,
and they sent a fake invitation to bring in the Running Man members.
You know.
Invitation to the mountain cabin. Congratulations.
You have won free lodging at the mountain cabin.
I get to stay at the mountain cabin for free.
However,
the security guard of the cabin accidentally found out the scheme.
(The guard accidentally finds out about their scheme.)
And the guard, who was pressed to pay his debts,
asked them for five million dollars for keeping their secrets.
- What's wrong?
- What are you doing here?
I'm not smart, but I think you're scheming an insurance scam.
(No way!)
Stamp it. Hurry up.
Stamp it right now.
Let's get this over with.
(They write a promise note that they will pay him five million dollars.)
- I will go now then.
- Okay.
This is so upsetting.
We've lost five million dollars.
(I am upset.)
However, the siblings didn't want to give him the money.
Why am I so anxious?
On the day before D-day, which is on the 25th,
they went to the guard.
(On the 25th, they went to meet the guard.)
- Come in.
- Open up.
- It's us.
- We're here.
- What are you doing here?
- Hello.
A while ago...
- We have something to tell you.
- Come in.
- Okay.
- Come on in.
They brutally murdered the guard.
What's up?
What are you doing?
(We can't give you the money!)
(One day before D-day, the guard got eliminated.)
- Let's go.
(The guard's room)
(The guard leaves his last message.)
The guard's last message was a smiley face.
It meant Haha.
(With a smiley face, he pointed Haha.)
The guard is eliminated.
Ga Yeon took the guard's master key...
and put it in Kwang Soo's room.
- She did it!
- See?
- And then she placed him there.
- I told you it wasn't me!
The housekeeper accidentally found the hidden necklace.
And Ga Yeon eliminated her.
- So the housekeeper found it.
- No!
Darn it!
(She brutally eliminated the housekeeper.)
(Last night, she went inside Kwang Soo's room.)
(She naturally placed the master key in his room.)
(And Haha who came to get the vegetables this afternoon...)
(stole the Tears of the Sun necklace as planned.)
(And he hid it in the corner of the laundry room.)
(It's done!)
They prepared everything,
but unexpected events happened.
The housekeeper accidentally found the necklace.
(The housekeeper accidentally found the necklace this evening.)
And Kim Ga Yeon who figured this out...
eliminated the housekeeper in the laundry room.
(The housekeeper contacts Ga Yeon to return the necklace.)
Hello.
Hello, Madam.
You are here.
Where did you find that?
I saw it...
inside a cup.
There is...
Oh gosh! What are you doing?
Oh no!
Gosh.
(Because of Haha, she unexpectedly eliminated the housekeeper.)
My back hurts.
My hair is a mess.
(She left traces of evidence at the site.)
Ga Yeon's hairpin and hair were found...
on the spot.
(Guard)
Haha who visited the day before also left traces of evidence.
Family pictures were found in Ga Yeon's car and Haha's wallet.
Also, Haha's book was upside-down alone.
Haha was the only one with no album.
All these traces of evidence...
pointed to...
- Haha and Ga Yeon.
- Show us the evidence.
(It pointed to Haha and Ga Yeon.)
- All right.
- I was innocent.
Only two people figured out that...
- there were two suspects.
- There's one more person?
- However,
- He was precise.
the person who guessed more precisely is...
- Gary.
- I got it!
I guessed that they were siblings from different mothers!
I think they are siblings separated when they were young.
I think they are siblings from different mothers.
(Gary guessed precisely that they would be siblings.)
Haha and Ga Yeon...
- plotted together.
- They are accomplices.
I think they were involved...
in a romantic relationship.
(He guessed they were involved in a romantic relationship.)
I couldn't possibly say it on TV.
Something like that.
I thought...
you were a person with innocent thoughts.
What does that have to do...
with being innocent? I'm trying to solve a case.
(He guessed they were involved in an inappropriate relationship.)
- I won't forgive you.
- That thought never occurred to me.
He told me.
- How did you know?
- He said he wrote a novel.
What did he say?
- How could you guess that right?
- He's amazing.
Watching a lot of TV series really helped.
- The messed-up TV series helped.
- They helped.
I am a big fan of "My Daughter, Geum Sa Wol".
Hey.
Do you think you can get married in May?
- You'll be in jail.
- You'll have to eat jail food.
You'll be in jail for quite a while.
Go away.
See you next week.
Go to jail.
No!
- It serves you right!
- No!
You're not getting the insurance money.
They deserve to rot.
My goodness.
- Goodbye!
- Be a better person!
Bye!
- Save me.
- Don't blame others!
I've never been in a police car.
(The mountain cabin case is finally settled.)
Gary wins a prize.
- Really?
- What is that?
What is it?
- Is it a travel voucher?
- Do you remember the last prize?
It was a travel voucher.
- Again?
- Where's the destination?
- "Sherlock Tour"?
- What's that?
- What is it?
- Are you going to the UK too?
- He's going to the UK.
- You'll go with Haha.
(Haha won a trip to London last week.)
It serves him right.
Good for him.
Why do I have to go with him?
The squid and the octopus are going to the UK together.
- Wow.
- Why does it have to be him?
- This is great.
- That was fun.
Thank you, everyone.
Thank you.
Should I be happy or not?
Look forward to Sherlock Yu's next adventure.
What did you say?
- You didn't do anything.
- How did you know?
(The End)
Senior interns?
I'm a new intern. My name is Kim Do Kyun.
- Hello.
- Nice to meet you.
It's Yoo Yeol.
- Hello.
- Wait.
- I'll drive for you.
- I'll drive.
- You don't have to.
- No way.
- Just get in.
- Would you like some coffee?
- Coffee?
- No, stay seated.
- I'll do it!
Why are you so bad?
Give us another chance.
(Age is just a number.)
(Competition for a team dinner)
- Let's see.
- No!
(Who will win?)
(Next week, "Senior Interns")