(Last Sunday night)
(Last week's episode of Running Man is almost over.)
(Running Man Producer)
(Why is he holding his cell phone so anxiously?)
(The Running Man is on.)
(The trailer for the next episode is on.)
(The following segment is based on the discussion from our meeting.)
We don't have anything filmed for next week's episode.
Should we reveal the mission in the trailer?
It'll be a way to check if the members watch the episodes.
(Therefore)
Running Man members, this is your first mission.
Once you see this, call the main producer right away.
(The first three to call will have an advantage for the final mission.)
(What will happen in the next week's episode of Running Man?)
(Although he decided to give a mission through the trailer, )
(he's not sure if the members would watch the show.)
(What if no one calls?)
(His phone doesn't seem to be ringing.)
(Then, )
(his phone starts ringing.)
(Who is this, calling a minute into the trailer?)
You are the first to call.
Oh, thank you.
(And he gets the second call.)
Another member is calling me right now.
(Who will be the next member to get the advantage?)
Someone just sent me a message to call you now.
Other members are calling me now.
I see.
- Okay. Thank you.
-  Okay.
Phone calls are flooding in now.
Don't lie to me. Are you serious?
I'm serious. I was surprised too.
Really?
I never thought I'd get this many phone calls.
I already have three missed calls.
(Which three members would get the merits?)
(Two days later, on the day of the shooting)
Chuncheon!
(Are the members heading to Chuncheon?)
- Are we taking the subway?
-  Hello.
- Good morning.
Are we taking the subway to get to Chuncheon?
Today, we will go on a trip with guests.
- With guest?
-  A trip?
-  With guest?
- Really?
-  This is exciting.
Today's race is called...
"The Best Couple's Race".
- "The Best Couple's Race"?
-  The best couple?
We'll take the subway here in Yongsan and get off at Chuncheon.
At the next stop, both female and male guests will join us.
(Both female and male guests?)
- Both male and female?
-  Right.
Is Cool our guest today?
(Jong Kook is so old-fashioned.)
There are no mixed groups nowadays.
Right.
- It's coming. ITX is coming.
-  It's here.
That's ITX. I've never taken it before.
Let's get on.
- Wow, it's good.
-  It's big.
- We can bring bicycles, too.
-  It's neat.
I'm sure couples will enjoy this subway trip.
- Wow. It's nice.
-  It's called ITX.
- Can we sit?
-  Take your seats.
- Please sit by the window.
-  By the window?
- I wonder what will happen.
-  This is amazing.
Years back, we had to go...
to Cheongnyangni Station to take a train.
I never missed school trips even when I skipped classes.
- You're incredible.
-  I know.
- School trips are the best.
-  That's right.
- Did you go with Jeon Do Yeon?
-  Of course, I did.
Oh, really?
Wait, was she there? I think she was with us.
If Jae Seok was handsome, he would have been very popular.
This is so sad.
- But I...
-  Don't call her name so friendly.
- It's weird.
-  Why don't you call her...
- and invite her to our show?
-  You mean, Do Yeon?
We haven't been in touch for more than 20 years.
- Then, she's a stranger to you.
-  Right.
Who else did you go on the trip with?
- Ye Ji Won?
-  Right. Ji Won.
- Yes, Ji Won!
-  I see.
Her real name is Yu Jeong.
- That name is prettier.
-  Her name is Yu Jeong.
There was Ha Soo Bin and Kim Won Jun as well.
Won Jun majored in film.
- Wasn't he popular?
-  Yes.
- He was handsome, right?
-  So we male students were jealous.
- I remember.
-  You didn't like him, did you?
I didn't.
- Why did you have to hate him?
-  I mean, male students did.
- You two are in different leagues.
-  Why you...
- Jae Seok is so funny...
-  You're so mean.
That everyone finds him very hilarious.
- But girls don't fall for him.
-  That's true.
- What do you mean?
-  As he said,
other students loved to be with me during trips because I was funny.
- But in the end...
-  They never think of you as a man.
That's right.
"Jae Seok, you're so funny. That was so hilarious!"
But at late nights...
when they gather in small groups and drink,
I was left alone.
(I always found myself alone in the end.)
- It's because...
-  They didn't like you.
It's because the students who majored in film joined us.
- All right, everyone.
-  Yes?
We gave you a mission through the trailer...
to check if you really watch our show.
I missed it.
- I'm sorry.
-  Anyway...
-  I apologise.
- I am so sorry.
-  I'm sorry.
(48 hours ago)
(Exactly a minute after the show was over)
(Who called the producer first?)
It's Kwang Soo.
(Kwang Soo called first.)
- Kwang Soo.
-  Yes?
- You are the first to call.
-  Thank you.
How did you call me?
I was watching the programme and...
Did your mother tell you?
That's right.
- Anyway...
-  You sound so cold.
(Kwang Soo, we're shooting now.)
Anyway, another member is calling me now.
Okay.
You called me first.
Thank you so much.
(The phone rings.)
(Which member would take the second place?)
Hello.
Jae Seok.
(Jae Seok takes the second place.)
Hello. Someone just sent me a message to call you now.
Jae Seok, you're the second member to call me.
Really? So I got the second place.
- That's right.
-  Okay.
Others are calling me right now.
I see. Okay.
Okay. Thank you.
Hello, Seok Jin.
(Seok Jin takes the third place.)
Hi, Ju Hyeong.
(Seok Jin drops honourifics as he's in a hurry.)
I got one of the three places, right?
- Seok Jin.
-  Yes?
Phone calls are flooding in now.
Don't lie to me. Are you serious?
I'm serious. I was surprised too.
Really?
- Seok Jin, you are...
-  What is this about?
The third person to call.
Yes!
(Running Man Mission Call Centre closes in just three minutes.)
In just one minute after the end of the show,
Kwang Soo called me.
You're just going to tell everyone that?
- Kwang Soo called first,
-  I enjoyed the show.
- so he gets three points.
-  Yes!
- He gained three points.
-  That's amazing.
- What's that?
-  I was...
- the very first one.
-  Kwang Soo watches the show...
when he's with his girlfriend.
- What are you talking about?
-  Really.
-  It's true.
- He watches it when he's with...
-  That's not true.
I watched it with my mum.
He saved his girlfriend's name as "mum" on his phone.
- That's not true.
-  Hey!
Kwang Soo, who's your mum?
It was my mum.
- It was your girlfriend, wasn't it?
-  No. No.
- All right.
-  I am sorry.
Then, Jae Seok called second.
And Jae Seok gets two points.
(Jae Seok gets one point less than Kwang Soo.)
- You take two points.
-  I'm jealous.
And Seok Jin almost called me at the same time.
Nice, Seok Jin.
Seok Jin gets one point.
All the unlucky ones got lucky this time.
That's right.
It's our day today.
- We're at Cheongnyangni.
-  We're here.
(Which guests are waiting at Cheongnyangni Station?)
(Who are they?)
(Sistar shines brighter during summer.)
- Who is it?
-  It's Sistar!
Look at them!
There are four of them.
- What are their names?
-  There's only Sistar.
I saw him!
- I saw Jong Kook.
-  I only saw Jong Kook.
I pick Jong Kook.
Honestly, give Jong Kook to me.
It's because...
he can lift heavy things, and I am the heaviest.
I think you fit well with Kwang Soo.
Me? I was actually thinking about Kwang Soo.
- I am going to take him from you.
-  Try.
(Will the girls be able to decide on their partners without a problem?)
(Welcome to the outing of Running Man.)
(They will go shake the hearts of Running Man boys.)
(She stealthily enters.)
(It's Da Som.)
- Oh dear!
-  Oh my!
- Da Som!
-  Welcome, Da Som!
- Oh dear!
-  Da Som!
- Welcome.
-  Long time no see!
(Kwang Soo claps to appeal to her.)
(The boys passionately appeal to her.)
- Da Som!
-  Oh my.
- Hello.
-  Da Som!
- She's so beautiful.
I heard you have an important key.
- I have two points.
-  Yes!
- I have three.
-  I have one.
They are the ones without any points.
- They have no points.
-  We don't have any.
Da Som, that's not important.
- We each have 1, 2, 3 points.
-  That's right.
- One is the best.
-  We are 1, 2, 3.
- I have three points.
-  One is the best.
- That's not important.
-  They are all very unlucky.
Yes. Kwang Soo is famous for being unlucky.
- Why would you tell her that?
-  They'll give you bad luck.
- Hey.
-  I have two points.
- And...
-  Why are you hesitating?
- I'm offended that you have doubts.
-  Da Som.
Please close your eyes.
- Gosh...
-  Gosh...
- What's that?
-  Why close our eyes?
- That's too much.
-  What's that?
- Gosh...
-  This is not good.
- Please close your eyes.
-  Okay.
I can't see well even with my eyes open.
Whether I open or close my eyes, I look the same.
Please close your eyes. I'm really coming.
(It looks like Da Som has made up her mind.)
(Will she be realistic and choose a man with points?)
(Who will Da Som choose?)
- You already won three games.
-  They'll give out a lot of points.
- Da Som.
-  No, Da Som.
All right. Please open your eyes.
(She came to me!)
Gosh...
- I knew this would happen.
-  Yes.
I knew it.
- You're so cruel.
-  Hey.
- Why do you like Kwang Soo?
-  Gosh...
It's not decided yet.
- It's not?
-  Other guests can come...
- and like Kwang Soo too.
-  Right.
- Da Som.
-  Yes?
From my understanding,
you are not Kwang Soo's type.
What's wrong with you?
- She is my type.
-  Da Som, you're out.
- I like girls like Da Som.
-  I am serious.
You're ruined.
When I was here several years ago,
Kwang Soo told me that I was pretty.
- He says that to everyone.
-  No. No.
I've never said it to Ji Hyo.
(Don't bring me up.)
(It's my turn.)
I had a feeling that Da Som won't be my partner.
- Same here.
-  Same here.
(Hyo Lyn enters!)
- You made all the fuss for...
-  Oh dear!
- Welcome!
-  It's Hyo Lyn!
- Hyo Lyn!
-  Welcome, Hyo Lyn!
-  Hyo Lyn!
Welcome!
Hyo Lyn is the best!
Hyo Lyn is the best in Sistar.
She is the best.
(Were they like this a while ago?)
- She can sing, and she can rap.
-  I don't want Da Som.
- She's good at everything.
-  She is.
- I will tell you one thing.
-  Okay.
I have one point already.
- One point?
-  That means...
- I'm number one.
-  Hyo Lyn.
Mr One Point, please take a seat.
I have two points.
You sit down too, Mr Two Points.
I have three points.
- Hey, what's wrong with you?
-  You're with Da Som!
- You're so mean.
-  What does that make Da Som?
- I'm just telling her...
-  Why would you do that?
- for the sake of her knowing.
-  You're unbelievable.
- Did you see Da Som's face?
-  You're a bad person.
- I feel so bad for Da Som!
-  This is who he is.
If Hyo Lyn chooses Kwang Soo, she can tell Da Som, "Get out".
- I feel so sorry for Da Som.
-  I know.
Nothing happened yet.
- I know.
-  Oh, no.
- I won't do that.
-  I feel bad for Da Som.
(It's time for Hyo Lyn to make a decision.)
Please make a choice now.
- With her, I can...
-  Bo Ra...
- loves Song Joong Ki.
-  Right.
Bo Ra loves Song Joong Ki.
She's crazy about him.
- You two would look good together.
-  I know.
Yes!
No!
This can't be happening.
- They can't be partners.
-  When we were little,
- cool students used to go out.
-  By the way,
- they look good together.
-  The two bosses met.
- They are both very tanned.
-  Honestly,
I would've been pressured if Hyo Lyn chose me.
- Same here.
-  Same here.
- I'm being honest.
-  Why would you say that?
- Honestly.
-  Really.
- So this is how it goes.
-  Yes.
Isn't Bo Ra the most popular member of Sistar?
(Sistar equals Bo Ra!)
There's another guest approaching.
- It's a man.
-  Oh dear.
No way.
(A hot male guest will complete the teams.)
- He's Monsta X!
-  Hello.
- Hello.
(He's Shownu from Monsta X.)
(He's got the hot body and dance moves.)
- It's Shownu.
-  Shownu.
He was on "The Law of Jungle" recently.
And his nice body became a huge hit.
Gosh, do you have to put it that way?
His nice body became a huge hit?
Shownu is...
Shownu, you can choose a partner too.
- Shownu, make a pick.
-  Okay.
- Your life depends on it.
-  His life depends on it.
I will stay beside Ji Hyo.
- Go ahead.
-  Okay.
- Awesome.
-  Congratulations.
- There was Ji Hyo.
-  Yes.
Yes! Yes!
Bravo.
When is Bo Ra coming?
(He's already waiting for Bo Ra.)
(Finally, that girl enters.)
- I didn't force him.
-  Bo Ra is here!
(Bo Ra is here!)
- Song Joong Ki!
-  Bo Ra.
I have Joong Ki's number.
- She got a haircut.
-  Bo Ra.
- She's beautiful with short hair.
-  She's Sistar's face.
It's been a year, boys.
- Yes.
-  It's been a long time.
Bo Ra tries so hard.
I can't imagine Sistar without Bo Ra.
I will go with my first choice.
- Please sit next to that person.
-  Maybe she will go to Gary.
- She looked at Gary.
-  Come on.
Oh, who did she say she wants?
(She acts cute.)
(Bo Ra, why are you doing that to me?)
- Oh, my. Bo Ra!
-  Hey.
- Don't do that.
-  Are you choosing him?
Bo Ra, is it Gary?
It's been a long time since I saw Gary like that.
- Bo Ra.
-  I was so surprised.
(Will she choose Gary?)
(Or will she choose Seok Jin who has Joong Ki's number?)
- Bo Ra. Bo Ra.
-  I will choose...
- Bo Ra.
-  You, get out.
Oh dear!
(Bo Ra chooses Kwang Soo!)
- I can't believe this.
-  This is unbelievable.
- Gary...
-  What's up with you?
You shouldn't have given me hope.
(Why would you tempt him?)
Bo Ra chose Kwang So too.
- So it's up to Kwang Soo now.
-  Look at that.
- He will decide now?
-  I knew this would happen.
- Get out!
-  He will make the decision now?
I came first.
Get out.
- Make your choice.
-  Say it on the count of three.
- Okay.
-  You can shout the name.
One, two, three.
(You know love never changes, right?)
(Love changes.)
(Who will Kwang Soo choose?)
Da Som, please move.
(So love moves.)
- Poor Da Som.
-  Love changes, Da Som.
- I knew this would happen.
-  Why would you...
I knew this would happen.
- I knew this would happen.
-  I thought he chose her.
- I was sure this would happen.
-  That's who he is, Da Som.
- Is she leaving like that?
-  Is she?
- Where are you going, Da Som?
-  Please wait outside.
- Really.
-  Must I stay out?
- Poor Da Som.
-  Some guests are not here.
- You became a couple now.
-  Okay.
(Kwang Soo and Bo Ra become a couple.)
Now, it's time for Su You... I mean So You.
- It's So You!
-  I see her!
(So You appears.)
So You is the best.
- How have you been, So You?
-  How have you been?
(He tries to become her partner.)
- What are you doing?
-  You can't do that.
-  Come on.
(That's cheating!)
(Everyone claims to own So You.)
What are you doing?
- It's not decided, yet.
-  She sat here.
- Tell me what's going on.
-  So You sat here.
- The guest gets to choose.
-  Exactly.
- You should stay still.
-  She sat here, right?
Hey, you know what Jae Seok said, right?
- He called you Su You.
-  Hold on.
- Jae Seok!
-  He called you Su You.
Do you think I would have called you Su You?
He called you Su You.
- Come on, Seok Jin.
-  That's what he said.
- They both said it.
-  You're crazy, Seok Jin.
- That's because I lived in Suyu.
-  You're bad!
- Why?
-  You betrayed Da Som.
(Don't put it that way.)
- So You.
-  Don't put it that way.
(I'll take my revenge.)
I'll give Da Som my spot.
What becomes of me, then?
Don't do that. Kwang Soo can get off at the next station.
- Go ahead.
-  Why are you saying that?
- Kwang Soo.
-  I don't know where we are.
(The player should get off!)
He can't do that.
- Send him off.
-  So You, take your pick.
- Let So You take her pick.
-  By the way, it's raining heavily.
- You see...
-  You, get out.
(You, get out!)
- She can do that.
-  That's right.
She can do that.
Jong Kook, you need to decide.
- One, two, three.
-  My goodness.
(Would he choose the passionate Hyo Lyn...)
(or So You who always picks him?)
- Look at Hyo Lyn.
-  This is difficult.
You can move to the back for a moment.
(Hyo Lyn is the second one to get betrayed.)
- Look at So You.
-  Poor Hyo Lyn.
There's no room for friendship here.
- I'm sorry, Hyo Lyn.
-  Yes!
It's not that So You likes you. She just wanted to make it funny.
(My goodness!)
- Go out for now.
-  I have to go.
Why are you guys doing this to each other?
Da Som is here.
- I see.
-  Don't get me wrong.
("Love and War" is not over yet!)
I know for sure she'll go to you again.
(Who will Da Som choose?)
- Don't go to him.
-  Think about it carefully, Da Som.
- Good choice.
-  That's right.
He already betrayed me.
- That's right.
-  I didn't betray you.
Good job!
- Good choice.
-  Kwang Soo, were you being hopeful?
- No, I wasn't...
-  You were.
What am I supposed to do?
You were being hopeful.
He's too much to handle.
(My gosh!)
He does that.
(Hyo Lyn is back after getting betrayed by Jong Kook.)
We're going to go like this.
- Welcome back.
-  This is what happened.
(Did you think you'd be fine after betraying me?)
(Swallowing)
I feel bad to sit next to someone else now.
No, don't feel bad. We're not like that.
If you've made up your mind, please take your pick.
Five.
(Hyo Lyn has to make up her mind.)
(Which one of these guys will she save?)
(Would it be another "Love and War"?)
One.
(Hyo Lyn chooses Gary.)
(These are the couples headed to Chuncheon.)
I feel like I have everything I need to win.
(Seok Jin and Haha are the male couple.)
(Gary and Hyo Lyn are loveable.)
(Jae Seok and Da Som talk over their pain.)
(Jong Kook and So You look strong.)
(Shownu and Ji Hyo only have eyes for each other.)
(Kwang Soo and Bo Ra won't betray each other again.)
(The Best Couple's Trip starts now!)
Each couple will play different games...
- on the trip and earn points.
-  Really?
You'll use the points to buy items...
that'll be useful in the last mission.
- That's why you need points.
-  We'll win in the games.
(The winning couple will earn diamond rings.)
(They are headed to Chuncheon with their spirits high.)
Heavy rain continues to pour in the capital and the Gangwon area.
Heavy rain in the central districts will continue into the night.
It continues to pour in the central districts.
It's pouring outside...
so we're going to have to change our plan.
(We'll make sure Kwang Soo receives his prize for calling first.)
(Maybe it's raining a lot because Kwang Soo won.)
We're going to play our first game.
We're going to play the "How Many People?" game...
- to test your teamwork.
-  That's a good one.
- Good one.
-  It's simple, too.
- You'll get one point if you win.
-  Is that so?
You have to open the magazine to a random page...
and the couple that gets the page with the most number of people wins.
It only counts if their eyes, nose and lips show.
- All right. One, two, three.
-  She shouldn't have picked him.
I know.
There are four people!
You got four people. Kwang Soo's team has four.
That's a lot.
- All right. One, two, three.
-  One, two, three.
There's three people!
- There's three.
-  Look at that.
- I've seen this before.
-  He flipped to the same page as me.
- It's by chance.
-  Pass it over behind you.
- I hope you fail!
-  Because...
- One, two, three.
-  One, two, three.
Come on!
- That's two people!
-  That's two!
That's the page you flipped to.
We have three. Look.
Yes, there are three.
Look here, it's four!
- That's amazing.
-  You can see the face.
- Look at these people.
-  That's amazing.
- No, that doesn't count.
-  These are people.
- You can't see it clearly.
-  Those are people.
You have to accept this.
- You have to.
-  You can't see the facial features.
You think they don't have eyes, nose and mouth?
- You think they don't?
-  You can't see them.
You don't know about that.
- What are you talking about?
-  You never know.
How many is it, then?
- Use the same magazine.
-  It's 4, 4, and 3 people.
- We had so many.
-  When I count down...
- I hope you fail!
-  I hope you get one person.
- I hope you get one in total.
-  Wish me good luck.
It's the same page.
- That's 2, then!
-  There's 1 and 2.
- It's the same page as Gary.
-  I told you to let it go.
- No way.
-  Serves you right!
- Da Som did so well.
-  It's three for all of us.
- It's 3, 3, and 3.
-  I feel bad.
All right. One, two, three.
(What about Ji Hyo and Shownu?)
- That's three people.
-  That's three!
- It's three again.
-  My goodness.
- Four people is the highest.
-  This is pretty difficult.
Haha and Seok Jin will go last.
- Don't do that!
-  One, two, three.
(Wow!)
How many is this?
(It's filled with people.)
Move away!
Move!
(This is who I am!)
(He summons a crowd with his lucky hands.)
- We're the best!
-  How did that happen?
- That's me!
-  Thumbs up!
- That's jackpot.
-  Give me my point.
It's the jackpot.
It's 20 at least.
- I knew it.
-  It's over a dozen.
(Here comes the second game!)
- Let's play the second game.
-  Let's go.
One of the couples will come out to the isle.
One of them will sit at the front and try not to laugh.
The other couples will try to make them laugh.
The couple that lasts the longest will get two points.
(In the "Don't Laugh" game, you must not laugh for one minute.)
This is not a funny situation.
- Everybody's upset.
-  They won't laugh.
- You should go first.
-  I'm good at this.
- You can go first.
-  Go ahead.
(The others will try to make them laugh after five seconds.)
Get set. Go.
Get lost.
Get out of my sight.
Why do you hate me?
You're old and useless.
(Old and useless?)
(You're old and useless.)
(Chuckling)
- My gosh.
-  He laughed.
- He laughed.
-  It's done.
(Haha made Seok Jin laugh.)
(Seok Jin couldn't help but chuckle at the insult.)
- You're done.
-  Move over.
- Time's over.
-  Hey!
I didn't laugh.
- Move over.
-  Come on.
(Seok Jin and Haha made themselves lose.)
I'll give you five seconds right away.
- One.
-  You start in five seconds.
Get set. Go.
How are you doing, Ji Hyo?
- Five,
-  Ji Hyo doesn't care.
- four, three...
-  I hope you're happy.
(Ji Hyo turns serious as soon as the timer starts.)
One.
Do you think those glasses suit you?
(Do you think those glasses suit you?)
- How do I make her laugh?
-  Ji Hyo.
- Ji Hyo.
-  Yes?
Seok Jin actually likes you.
(Seok Jin actually likes you.)
(Chuckling)
(Seok Jin loves all the members.)
(She can't stand it.)
- Good one.
-  That came out of nowhere.
(Ji Hyo laughs in eight seconds.)
- What am I going to do?
-  Have a seat.
- You can do it.
-  Get set. Go.
Get yourself into it.
I chose you to make Da Som jealous.
(I chose you to make Da Som jealous.)
(What is he saying?)
(That was unexpected.)
I knew that was right.
(She's about to burst.)
I can see her smiling.
- Why are you laughing?
-  They're done.
Hey, that's not supposed to be funny!
- Doesn't that make you mad?
-  That was too much.
- That was too funny.
-  Hey!
- They're done.
-  Doesn't that make you mad?
- You're done.
-  Kwang Soo!
- What? You were supposed to focus.
-  That was too funny.
Let's break up. Don't call me ever again.
Seok Jin really likes you.
- You're not lady-like.
-  Kwang Soo betrayed you.
Will you marry me?
- Your hair smells like poop.
-  Really?
Hyo Lyn and Da Som's team both win.
- Yes!
-  Yes!
(Both teams earn two points.)
- I knew it!
-  We finally have some points.
We're getting off. We're already at Chuncheon Station.
(The rain picks up.)
(Chuncheon is covered in rain.)
My gosh.
The rain...
(Would they be able to finish their trip?)
It would have been good if it didn't rain. It's pouring.
- Is Chuncheon having the most rain?
-  That's right.
It's raining so much right now.
It's raining a lot.
- This is no joke.
-  I know.
It's quite scary.
It would have been a great trip if it didn't rain.
(This is how a trip to Chuncheon looks like.)
(It sure makes you excited.)
(You're supposed to go on a date on bicycles.)
We can't go on a trip in this rain.
How were we supposed to play a game in the pool?
(We don't even know.)
(We have a lot prepared but you can't have them.)
(We'll save this for another time.)
(When is Running Man coming?)
(There's a sudden change of plans.)
(It's been relocated to an indoor gym.)
(Supplies have been gathered last minute.)
(Have you heard of this before?)
(It's an indoor couple's trip.)
- What's this?
-  What's this?
- What's going on?
-  Wow!
- This is so nice.
-  This is what it's about.
- This is exciting.
-  Sit here.
You're supposed to sit in a circle on a couple's trip.
We're the only team without any points.
- Let me see...
-  You have zero point.
- We're first place.
-  We have two points.
Sit next to your partner.
- Sure.
-  Next to your partner?
It's a joint couple's trip.
Some of you know each other...
- but let's introduce ourselves.
-  Sure.
- Let's start from the right.
-  Go ahead.
We've been going out for 7 years. Is it 6 years?
It's been six years and it was love at first sight.
We're in platonic relationship.
- You look good together.
-  Sorry to interrupt you two,
but you're not on a honeymoon.
- What?
-  That was kind of too much.
- It's just a trip.
-  No, it was too much.
- Isn't this a couple's trip?
-  It doesn't mean we're all married.
(This is a couple's trip, but not for married couples.)
- Anyway, hi.
-  Good to see you all.
- Hello.
-  All right. Next couple please.
You two didn't want to become a couple at first.
- I like my partner.
-  Me too.
Hi. I'm Gary Kang, the dancing king of Jamsil.
- The dancing king.
-  The dancing king of Jamsil?
Hey. My partner is the dancing king of Uijeongbu.
- Who are you talking about?
-  This guy. His name is Shownu.
- Really?
-  The dancing king of Uijeongbu.
- You can't lose to him.
-  How about a dancing competition?
- Let's see.
-  You can't lose to him.
- He's the dancing king of Jamsil.
-  Okay. That's enough I think.
- Okay, I am...
-  Everybody knows this guy.
As you already know, I am the faculty representative.
Why are you the representative?
- Why are you the representative?
-  I just am.
- Let him take the title.
-  This time, I will...
- The title suits him.
-  But everybody ignores him.
- Anyway...
-  Are you good at dancing?
My partner, Da Som falls in love really easily.
- Does she?
-  Yes, very easily.
If someone likes her,
she is attracted to the person without knowing.
- So please be cautious.
-  No flirting, please.
- Be cautious.
(I mean, you!)
- No way.
-  You shouldn't.
- No, I mean...
-  You stay away from her.
I may fall in love unconsciously.
(I'll make you my man, Kwang Soo.)
That was really nice.
- You look excited.
-  No, I'm not.
- He's excited.
-  I'm not.
You guys are tall.
They look scary.
I'm Jong Kook from Anyang.
I love to exercise.
- What?
-  Yes, you heard me.
I bet you love to fight, not to exercise.
I'm So You from Cheongdamdong.
Hey, you are from Jeju Island.
Jeju Island sounds weird.
Where she lives now is the important thing.
- Where she was born is not.
-  I live in Cheongdamdong now.
I love to exercise, too.
You guys make a good couple.
So...
we'll make your life difficult if you get in our way.
(We'll make your life difficult if you get in our way.)
(Gosh!)
(I'm not joking.)
- She's bold.
-  I was really surprised.
She really surprised me. I must be careful.
We'll collect many points...
and secure the diamond ring.
- No way.
-  You...
- Here come the player.
-  Hi, everyone.
They are both players.
My name is Kwang Soo. I'm from Namyangju.
He's keep looking at Da Som.
- What are you saying?
-  Stop looking at her.
But Da Som is also looking at him.
Hey!
- Hey.
-  I told you not to do that.
What are they doing?
A nonsense love story, I guess.
I'm afraid that they might fight sometime today.
- No way.
-  Am I watching "Love and War" now?
- That guy is handsome.
-  He really is.
- He's new to this show.
-  It's good...
- to see someone handsome here.
-  He has many charms.
I envy you.
I am Ji Hyo, and I'm from Hongdae.
And my partner is extremely quiet.
- Talk to us. Would you?
-  I am... Hi.
I think I'm talking a lot today,
but everyone is asking me to talk.
- Do you think you're talking a lot?
-  You will talk more before you go.
I wish to become a more entertaining person today.
- Do you know what's really funny?
-  What?
If someone is quite like him, people tend to look at him more.
- You're right.
-  It's interesting how that happens.
- I'm sure.
-  It's really strange.
- I get curious if someone is quiet.
-  That's what happens.
- No matter how the guy looks?
-  That doesn't matter.
Of course, there are some exceptions.
Why are you pointing at me while saying that?
(Because you are one of the exceptions.)
- All right. We'll play you a music.
-  Okay.
Since we have our representative with us,
- he will give you chances.
-  Okay.
One of our staff members will choose the best dancing couple.
- Really?
-  We'll give them one point.
- Wow.
-  Da som.
(The competition will start off with Sistar's dance.)
(Swaying)
(They are so nice...)
(and sexy, too.)
That's amazing.
(Sistar rules the summer.)
(Sistar rules today's trip, too.)
Nice.
- You're the best.
-  That was really nice.
- They have something different.
-  They do. Really.
Okay. Please start the music.
(The music starts.)
This is the song for Shownu.
(The couples are warming up.)
(He's all excited.)
(Jae Seok is absorbed in dancing.)
(Even his partner doesn't like him dancing.)
Stop moving around.
(They are really shocked.)
(I am your representative!)
He is completely out of rhythm.
I'm just warming up. Warm yourselves up, everyone.
You're doing good.
All right. Haha and Seok Jin, it's your turn.
(Haha and Seok Jin are the first.)
- I'll give you three seconds.
-  My gosh.
(That's disgusting.)
- My gosh.
-  What are you doing?
I guess you guys were too excited. You get a warning.
- No, I mean...
-  This is your first warning.
- My partner is tough.
-  Next time, you're out.
All right. Please start the music.
(Gary and Hyo Lyn are the second.)
- It's your turn, Gary.
-  He loves this kind of music.
Go, Gary.
(Join me, Hyo Lyn.)
Go for it, Gary.
(Goodness!)
(How can she dance like that?)
- Wow.
-  How is she doing that?
- How could she do that?
-  How can she dance like that?
- What's this?
-  What are you doing?
- Gosh.
-  What are they doing?
Wait. Stop.
- Why?
-  What are you doing?
- What are you doing right now?
-  Why did you stop us?
- Why?
-  Please stop for a minute.
-  What's wrong with you?
We were enjoying it. Why did you stop us?
- What were you thinking?
-  What's wrong?
- You two get a warning, too.
-  A warning?
- Why? What's wrong?
-  You get a warning.
- You get a warning.
-  We didn't do anything wrong.
- We're just college students.
-  I think that was acceptable.
- All right.
-  That was really something.
All right. Please start the music again.
Please start the music.
Kwang Soo and Bo Ra. It's your turn now.
What should we do? What should we do?
- What is she doing?
-  What are they doing now?
- What is this?
-  Hey, what are you doing? Stop.
What happened?
- Hey!
-  What's wrong with you?
- No, we were trying to...
-  You saw others getting a warning.
- You must be crazy.
-  What are you thinking?
- Are you crazy?
-  We planned to do something.
-  What's wrong with you?
We were trying to do that spinning thing...
- Take him out.
-  You are mad.
- What's your problem?
-  Get out. Get out.
- No, I mean...
-  What's wrong with you?
(This is unfair.)
All right, everyone. Let's try that again.
- That was so funny.
-  Something's wrong with the music.
- The music is provocative.
-  The music is the problem.
- That music inspired me.
-  Please play something different.
Can you play a more cheerful music instead?
(Jae Seok and Da Som are the fourth.)
(Da Som is cute...)
(and Jae Seok is frivolous.)
- Look at him.
-  Hey, this isn't a nightclub.
He's enjoying it. Really.
- What's wrong with you?
-  When will you stop dancing?
- Look at him. What is he doing?
-  What's wrong with him?
- You're blocking the camera.
-  What is that?
- Here comes Shownu.
-  Go, Shownu. Go, Shownu.
- Show us your moves, Shownu.
-  Go for it.
(Splendid dance moves)
(The dancing king of Uijeongbu)
(It's your turn, Ji Hyo.)
She's so cute.
- That's nice, Ji Hyo.
-  Wow.
(Jong Kook and So You are the last.)
- They look scary.
-  Just by looking at them...
- I feel scared.
-  Are they dancing or sparring?
(She stops.)
- What are they doing?
-  They are waiting for something.
Let's interrupt them during the highlight.
- It's the highlight.
-  They're waiting.
- No, don't.
-  While they are waiting,
- get ready to join them.
-  Be ready.
(They're all waiting for the beat like hyenas.)
(Join in.)
(They are all dancing like crazy.)
Are you okay, Hyo Lyn?
Look at Da Som. She's good.
- This is fun.
-  Look at that camera.
(So You doesn't care about winning any more.)
- We must win this time.
-  Well done, Da Som.
Well done.
You danced really well in front of the camera.
We would've won if we showed our trick.
- Teamwork must come first.
-  Yes. Teamwork.
Teamwork must come first.
How you felt is the most important.
Which is the best dancing couple for today?
- The best couple is...
-  Yes?
They are on a roll. Literally.
(This is what we were trying to do.)
- That looks tough.
-  It hurts if you do it that way.
- Their heights are way different.
-  That won't work.
Which couple is the best?
It's Seok Jin and Haha couple.
(Seok Jin and Haha make the best couple.)
- Really?
-  Are you serious?
- Why couldn't we dance then?
-  No way.
- How could they be?
How could you choose these two?
- I knew I could count on her.
-  I knew it.
- Well done.
-  What did I do wrong to her?
- Then we could've won instead.
-  No way.
She's really good. She is.
That's unfair. Don't you think so?
- Oh well. Anyway,
-  All right. Let's move on.
For Gary and Hyo Lyn, their managers must make sure...
they get back home. Make sure they don't dance on their way.
- Seriously.
-  I mean it.
They were so excited.
- You're too open-minded.
-  It's raining really hard.
I never knew that Hyo Lyn will get close with Gary like this.
(Point Board: Kwang Soo and Bo Ra are the first with four points.)
All right, everyone. This time, you will play "Leg Wrestling".
- What is it about?
-  "Leg Wrestling"?
- Couples will play against others.
-  Okay.
- Jong Kook will win.
-  We have won already.
- Do we have to hang on there?
-  There's no hope.
- Good luck, Da Som.
-  Go, Hyo Lyn.
- You can win.
-  Let's go.
- Are you ready?
-  Yes.
Ready...
(The game starts.)
(Climbing)
(Da Som has got the upper hand.)
(However, Jae Seok and Gary are...)
(Gary begins to kick his back.)
(Gary attacks Jae Seok fiercely with his toes.)
Gary is really serious.
(Tickling)
(Gary tickles Jae Seok under his arm.)
(Jae Seok begins to kick Gary's weak point.)
(Jae Seok pays back for what Gary did.)
Stop it.
I'm not in a good shape down there.
- What's going on?
-  I'm sorry.
(He drills even harder.)
It really hurts.
What are you doing here?
(We have censored it for your sakes.)
Are you all right, Gary?
- No!
-  I'm sorry, Gary.
Gary.
(He's getting completely humiliated.)
Do we have to hang onto the bar like this?
(Jae Seok and Gary are both out.)
- It's a fight between you two.
-  It's between you two.
You humiliated me.
Goodness.
What does Gary make everything rated R?
It's because he's rated R.
(Gary is a man who's rated R.)
You must be aggressive.
Stop it!
- She turned.
-  She turned.
(She's determined to stay hanging.)
So You, that looks dangerous.
- Look at Da Som.
-  Wait, Da Som.
(She won't let her win easily.)
- Da Som is quite good.
-  Wow, Da Som.
What's going on?
(A gravity-defying fight between two warriors)
Da Som, you can do it.
(Even at the Shaolin Temple, )
(at a circus...)
(or in the jungle, this anti-gravity show would surprise everyone.)
Which legs belong to whom?
(Da Som is out.)
Are you okay?
Good job, Hyo Lyn.
- Hyo Lyn, are you all right?
-  Are you okay?
That was amazing.
- Gary's team wins.
-  Good job.
- Hyo Lyn.
-  Gosh, I lost.
Bo Ra, you should play without shoes.
- Ji Hyo is really strong.
-  She is.
Bo Ra, you also exercise.
Get ready.
Hang onto the bar.
Start.
(Everyone puts their legs up.)
She's really strong.
- Bo Ra is in trouble.
-  She's in trouble.
Are you all right?
(Ji Hyo and Bo Ra are out simultaneously.)
Look at them.
What are they doing?
He got him.
(The tables are turned.)
He's starting to tickle him.
(Tickling)
(But it doesn't work.)
(He immediately tries to suffocate him.)
Stop.
How will he endure it?
(He swings his body.)
- That's impressive.
-  Wow.
Look at them.
He's acting like a monkey.
- You can do it.
-  Wait.
Kwang Soo, you can do it.
(He lets go of his mentality.)
(Poor Kwang Soo.)
No, Kwang Soo.
- No, Kwang Soo.
-  Kwang Soo.
(But then)
(His feet land on the floor.)
They touched the floor!
(Shownu is out.)
- Please help me.
-  Goodness.
Seriously, this is...
Next team, please.
Get ready.
I can't even grab the bar.
I might lose as soon as I start.
She's exhausted.
(Bo Ra swings her leg.)
(With a sudden high kick, Hyo Lyn is out.)
- He spun around.
-  Are you all right?
(Kwang Soo spins around.)
(Kwang Soo spins like a roasted chicken.)
No, stop!
(He hits.)
What is he doing?
What are you doing?
What did he do?
He has a weak back.
(He strives to get on top.)
Kwang Soo is very determined.
Kwang Soo, you must win.
(He tries to put pressure on the ribs.)
(Then, he swings punches.)
(He gives a rough massage to his bottom.)
(It's a scary sight.)
You must win.
You can also do it.
(Screaming)
(The shorts are getting tight.)
(His wailing keeps getting louder.)
- You have to endure it, Kwang Soo.
-  I'm being serious.
You might fall off.
I'm being serious.
- Get off of me.
-  Twist his leg.
Hold on to his leg tightly.
I want to go down!
Come down.
Gary.
"I want to go down."
(It's not a proud victory.)
Who's the winner then?
Kwang Soo's team wins.
What is this?
Why is there something on my shorts?
No, Kwang Soo. Don't misunderstand.
- It's water.
-  It's just water.
Good job, Gary.
- Go back up to the bar.
-  Okay.
You'll start...
- the final round. Get ready.
-  Kwang Soo.
(It's Kwang Soo versus Jong Kook, a cheater versus a strong man.)
(Bo Ra versus So You)
(Which couple will be the strongest?)
- I'm too short.
-  Get ready.
That startled me.
He can't even attack Jong Kook.
(It's a brutal attack.)
- It doesn't work on Jong Kook.
-  You have to climb on top.
- It doesn't work.
-  Goodness.
(So You attacks first.)
It's okay for you to lose!
You did it, So You.
(She's flung onto the floor.)
(I'm the strongest woman in the neighbourhood.)
(Kwang Soo struggles with all his might against Jong Kook.)
(Getting a point doesn't matter at this moment.)
(His pride is the only thing that matters.)
(Kwang Soo, stay strong.)
(What can he do now?)
(He punches.)
(The cheater strikes violently.)
It's okay for you to lose!
(He's merciless.)
He's releasing all of his anger.
(He delivers uppercuts containing sorrows from the past.)
Jong Kook has wrestled on the bar many times,
but this must be something new.
(Punching)
That's amazing.
(He flops on the floor.)
- Go, So You!
-  Jong Kook.
So You is still on the bar.
- So You is still on the bar.
-  So You.
- So You.
-  Don't do it, So You.
(I'll win that diamond ring.)
(She attacks him violently.)
(He flops down.)
(Kwang Soo is out.)
He did a great job.
That was impressive.
You should've done this.
Jong Gook's couple earns two points.
Kwang Soo's couple earns one point.
(It's not over. It's round two.)
(Youth Race)
Next up is "Couple Badminton".
That's right.
- What is that?
-  It looks good.
- Wow.
-  I'll explain.
(A big and thick racket appears.)
One person from each couple must use this racket.
The other person will have to use one of the various rackets...
that aren't normal.
It will be randomly picked.
This is what the game will be.
The first team to make the first five points wins.
- That sounds good.
-  Five points?
It sounds simple.
You win when you earn five points.
Please start the game. The team to earn five points wins.
(Kwang Soo's team vs Gary's team)
(Round one of Couple Badminton starts.)
(Will she be able to serve with a flipper?)
(She serves the ball.)
He's good.
(The type of racket isn't important.)
(She looks comfortable playing with a table tennis racket.)
(They continue to hit back and forth.)
(It hits the floor.)
(Kwang Soo's team earns 1 point.)
They play well.
Gary, go closer to the net.
This racket works well.
Goodness.
Why? What's wrong?
I'm just saying this is upsetting.
Gary seems to be getting upset.
You need to lift the ball high.
- I'll serve.
-  Okay.
(The game resumes.)
That's good.
- That's right.
-  That's right.
(An unexpected hit)
(He's satisfied.)
- Wow.
-  That's right.
It's fun to watch the shuttlecock move across the net.
Hyo Lyn plays well.
- Have you played it before?
-  You're doing well.
No, I just have a good racket.
- She plays well.
-  That's great.
- They're coming up with a plan.
-  This game is fun.
- How do I serve?
-  You can do it.
(What's Gary and Hyo Lyn's plan?)
That's right.
(Their plan is to target the back corner.)
(Will she score easily?)
That's right.
(She hits.)
(She makes a strong counterattack.)
(The ball hits the net.)
(Gary gets flustered by Bo Ra's play.)
- This team is fun to watch.
-  Bo Ra also plays well.
Did you study physical education?
Da Som also plays badminton well.
(Kwang Soo's team has 2 points total.)
- This game is fun.
-  It's fun to watch.
(He throws the birdie.)
(There you go.)
It's Bo Ra's serve anyway.
It's a psychological warfare.
(Fine, let's do it, Bo Ra.)
(He's nervous.)
I can't see Bo Ra because of Kwang Soo.
Kwang Soo is too tall. I can't see either.
(That's right. This is...)
(the flipper-hiding tactic.)
I can't...
Okay!
(It was a blinding attack.)
- That was awesome!
-  The birdie was too fast.
(Rest in my shade.)
- They're good.
-  Bo Ra also plays well.
- Awesome.
-  The flipper is powerful.
The serve was quick.
Give us a good serve.
- Serving requires technique.
-  I see.
- The racket can't go over the net.
-  Okay.
(Only the racket shouldn't go over the net, right?)
That's so...
(What is he doing?)
That's a foul, Kwang Soo.
- Was it over the net? Sorry.
-  Yes, it was.
- All right.
-  That's so funny.
Then I'll serve.
It'd be funny if the birdie was blocked by Kwang Soo.
- Flipper will be better.
-  Right.
- Good.
-  We need a bigger one.
That's it.
(Kwang Soo makes a powerful smash.)
(Here goes my powerful shot.)
(It's 4 to 1 so far. It can be his last chance to attack.)
- Nice!
-  Hit it!
(This shot ends the match.)
He's good.
He's so tall.
- We won!
-  He's so tall...
- That was powerful.
-  that he strikes from a high point.
Did we lose again?
Gary.
We'll finish the match very fast.
The sound will be very light.
(Jong Kook's team vs Jae Seok's team)
Let's end the match fast.
- We can do it!
-  Let's go for it.
(How will this match turn out?)
(That's good.)
(That is a full swing.)
(Jong Kook's dreadful swing)
(They counterattack.)
We made it!
(But it is too weak.)
- Gosh.
-  Goodness.
- They're good.
-  Why are they so good?
He doesn't even need that big racket.
He's too strong.
It's like a fly swatter.
(Listen to that sound!)
(Jae Seok slides and hits the birdie.)
That was so cool.
(Da Som attacks.)
(It's a piece of cake for me.)
(Jong Kook's team earns another point.)
Good job.
(Jae Seok's team has no point so far.)
(Is he a singer or an athlete?)
(Here it goes.)
- Gosh.
-  Wow.
Let's do it again.
(It is a sudden attack.)
(But Jong Kook successfully defends.)
(You're so good.)
- That's unbelievable.
-  It's okay.
Gosh, that was amazing.
- He got another point.
-  He's strong.
(Jong Kook's team has 3 points.)
It's over.
- Da Som, concentrate.
-  Let's resume.
(We have no choice but this in order to defeat Jong Kook.)
(What is that over there?)
Let's go.
(Jae Seok distracts Jong Kook and serves all of a sudden.)
(And Jae Seok smashes wisely.)
Gosh, that was so sly.
(Jae Seok's team earns a point.)
- Here it goes!
-  Okay.
(They hit it back.)
(The two pans come together and hit the birdie back.)
That was a spike.
Do we get to serve this time?
What a close match.
(Jae Seok tries to close the gap.)
(Jong Kook tries to widen the gap.)
Good!
It's deuce.
(They go to deuce.)
This match is very interesting.
- You can serve.
-  Gosh, this is crazy.
(He's anxious.)
(Jae Seok is very close to the net.)
- That won't work though.
-  He's too upfront.
You can never make it.
- That's right.
-  Okay. Fine.
(No wonder I felt anxious.)
You should step back.
- I'll keep my manners.
-  You are so crafty.
- That was so ridiculous.
-  Okay, okay.
Okay.
(The team who gets 2 points first wins.)
- Let's resume the match.
-  Okay.
Let's go!
Go for it.
Good.
(He blocks it with all his might.)
Okay!
(This is a good chance to smash.)
(Take that!)
Nice!
(We made it!)
- Good.
-  Well done.
(Jae Seok's team is leading by one point.)
You just need one more point.
Shall I throw my racket and hit him?
Then I'll dodge like this.
(Jae Seok irritates Jong Kook.)
Fine. Come on.
(Jong Kook serves with a grunt.)
(It's a fierce rally.)
- Gosh.
-  Are you okay?
(This can be the last match. I must win!)
- Are you okay?
-  I'm okay.
It's okay.
(It's just a game but they're so fierce.)
- Are you okay?
-  I'm okay.
(Jae Seok counterattacks.)
(Will she be able to counterattack?)
(She hits it back!)
That's it!
(We won!)
(Jae Seok's team wins.)
(They move on to the next round.)
- Get five points first.
-  Let's do it!
(Ji Hyo's team vs Seok Jin's team)
(They show slapstick humours.)
(Seok Jin and Haha win.)
- Good.
-  Seok Jin and Haha won.
It's hard.
(Kwang Soo's team vs Seok Jin's team)
You can do it!
Good.
- Strike it!
-  Go for it!
Bo Ra is good at this.
(Bo Ra is the MVP.)
(Kwang Soo and Bo Ra move to the final round.)
Kwang Soo's team wins.
(Kwang Soo's team vs Jae Seok's team)
(Final round)
(Will Jae Seok's team win with their speed?)
(Or will Kwang Soo's team overcome them with their power?)
You must get back at them.
- That's right.
-  Yes.
- Bo Ra, let's go for it.
-  Okay.
- We'll win.
-  You can't beat us.
- This is...
-  You'll never beat us.
(This is time for revenge.)
Let's do our best.
Let's go, Bo Ra.
Goodness.
(It's another fierce rally.)
(All four of them are very concentrated.)
You have to hit it back.
Wow!
(It's like a Wimbledon match.)
Strike it.
- Wow.
-  Good!
(He blocks it.)
- We're so good.
-  They're really...
- good.
-  It's like a tennis match.
There are so many points.
(Nice attack!)
Okay!
(He blocks again.)
- This is...
-  My goodness!
He uses the racket skilfully.
I've mastered this.
This is like a tennis match.
(Kwang Soo's team is leading by 2 points.)
(Now, Kwang Soo's team is leading by 3 points.)
(Spectacular)
(This match seems like a preliminary round for the Olympics.)
(You can't beat us.)
(Kwang Soo's third block.)
Yes!
That was amazing.
(It's like the Wailing Wall.)
- My goodness.
-  Gosh.
You're so good. What was that?
- My goodness.
-  Gosh.
- That was awesome.
-  He's so good.
Just get one more point!
- That was awesome.
-  He's so good.
(They just need to win once more.)
(Will they be able to?)
- Get one more point!
-  We can do it!
(Or will Jae Seok's team be able to turn the tables?)
We can turn the match around.
(Let's do our best.)
You can't beat us.
(Da Som strikes the birdie.)
(The birdie flies high.)
It's over.
(Da Som strikes the birdie high.)
(How will this turn out?)
(Kwang Soo smashes.)
(Catch it if you can.)
(But Jae Seok makes it.)
Nice!
(They lose pathetically.)
We won!
- It's over.
-  This is so annoying.
Please come out of the court.
But you received one point, too.
Kwang Soo's couple gets two points,
- This was close.
-  and Jae Seok's gets one point.
- Great.
-  Kwang Soo did a good job.
(The couples get 2 and 1 points respectively.)
(Kwang Soo's team has a total of 9 points.)
(It's still pouring out.)
(But their trip continues.)
My goodness.
- That looks so tasty.
-  It smells so good.
- It smells good.
-  Let's eat!
I love this smell.
Here comes my partner.
- Hello.
-  His wig changed!
- Seok Jin?
-  It's my partner.
I went to a hair salon.
Go to the end.
Where is Da Som?
Where's she?
Thank you.
- Thank you.
-  Please help yourselves.
Thank you.
- It looks so tasty.
-  I've never had dakgalbi here.
- Me, too.
-  Really?
- This is so good.
-  Gosh.
- We eat a lot today.
-  Please eat a lot.
It's good.
(She's shy.)
(Their chemistry is good.)
I love dakgalbi. Which one should I eat first?
(They make another good memory in Chuncheon.)
I really wanted dakgalbi.
Anyway, do Ji Hyo and Shownu get along well?
We talked a lot.
What do you think about Ji Hyo?
She takes good care of me.
Ji Hyo is nice to younger boys.
I'm kind to girls, too.
Hyo Lyn fell asleep back then, and Ji Hyo covered her with a towel.
- She covered me with a towel.
-  She covered her.
Then why is she so mean to me?
Because you ask for it.
You're so annoying.
The way Ji Hyo treats you is more than you deserve.
Gary and Hyo Lyn, please eat a lot.
Okay. We're very tired.
I never thought you two would look this good together.
- It's unexpected.
-  You look good together.
Your chemistry is good.
- They look great together.
-  Right.
Eat slowly if you want to twerk later.
(Hyo Lyn is happy.)
That's the only thing we're good at.
We didn't get any points.
(But they're good dancers.)
- Did you enjoy the dakgalbi?
-  Yes.
Then, now it's time...
- to make fried rice.
-  Right.
We gave dakgalbi for free.
But unfortunately, the team who gets first place will get two bowls.
And the second team will get one bowl of fried rice.
- I see.
-  I want fried rice.
If you eat dakgalbi but not the fried rice,
you're left with much regret.
We ate only meat.
- We need some rice.
-  Right.
- I want rice so badly.
-  Me, too.
I really want fried rice.
(How does this delicious fried rice look?)
- Thank you.
-  Here it comes.
- I want to eat it.
-  Gosh, I want it so bad.
(Dakgalbi and fried rice must always go together.)
(The two winning teams were Gary's and Ji Hyo's, respectively.)
It's fried rice.
- That looks delicious.
-  It looks delicious.
There are too many delicious foods in this world.
I agree.
(Please let me have some.)
Thank you.
(The perfect fried rice is ready.)
- Thank you for the food.
-  I will try it.
I will taste it.
Enjoy your meals.
Gary's team got two points.
Ji Hyo's team got one point.
After eating the fried rice, you have to eat makguksu.
Chuncheon is known for their makguksu.
- We have to eat it.
-  We have to have makguksu.
- Right.
-  We must.
- We're going to play a game.
-  Okay.
The team that wins will get two points and two bowls of makguksu.
The team that comes in second will get one point and one bowl.
Let's do this.
We are going to play...
"Biscuit Dancing Time".
- What's that?
-  Dancing?
While holding a biscuit in your mouths,
you have to dance for a minute.
You will be wearing pace counters.
The couple with the highest number will win.
The couple that has the second highest number comes second.
Gary's team are going to have a blast.
Please put the counter on her hips.
We are at a disadvantage.
- Our heights...
-  Your heights don't match.
(They face a difficulty from the start.)
The three couples will go first.
- We are?
-  Yes.
Hyo Lyn and Gary are here.
- Wow!
-  They're the sexy couple.
I am excited to see Hyo Lyn dance.
Gosh...
Ready.
- They are the best.
-  They're the sexy couple.
Bite on the biscuit. Music, cue.
Look at them.
I don't want to do that.
(Everyone just shakes their legs.)
(They look shy, )
(but their ankles move as if they have motors!)
Look at Hyo Lyn.
Look at her.
(But there's one couple that looks unique.)
(Feel the passion of South America!)
Look at them.
They are something.
(We approve of you.)
They are the best.
Bravo!
Go, Hyo Lyn!
(They're in love with the couple!)
(Their dance is of different class!)
Hyo Lyn and Gary...
give me the chills.
(We are in Brazil!)
(Shaking)
(Dancers nationwide, )
(join us in Chuncheon!)
Hyo Lyn and Gary...
(Everyone's attention is fixed at the couple.)
give me the chills.
- They are...
-  This is crazy.
Look at them. I feel so embarrassed.
(They say they're embarrassed, but they keep watching them.)
(Jae Seok's excited, too.)
They are really good.
(They have 5 seconds left.)
I can't watch them.
(Shake it until the end!)
They are unbelievable.
Please check the counter.
Don't you think you were too close?
We were just doing our best.
The other couples were out of our sights.
Bo Ra, please show us your count.
Bo Ra's count is 144.
(Bo Ra's count is 144.)
Kwang Soo has 138.
(The total count is 282.)
Shownu got 140.
What did he do to get that number?
Ji Hyo got 126.
(The total score is 266.)
- I got 124.
-  Hyo Lyn got 124.
(Hyo Lyn got 124.)
- Gary got...
-  I thought she got more.
(What did Gary get?)
How could you get only 39?
(He's embarrassed.)
I was busy supporting her.
But you were playing a game.
What's that?
- I was busy holding her.
-  Gosh...
- That much for the hips is a lot.
-  It really is.
- You did get a lot.
-  Perhaps mine is broken.
This was all that you did.
I had to sync with her. That's why.
- I...
-  You should've focused.
The count was all that mattered, not the dance.
- You did well.
-  The next teams can come out.
- Ready.
-  Where do I put it?
- Come on.
-  Jae Seok can put it on his waist.
- Waist?
-  Your waist is unbelievable.
Ready and bite the biscuit.
- It might snap.
-  Music, cue.
(It has begun.)
(They all shake their legs.)
Jong Kook is so funny.
Look at them.
(At that time, )
(something drops.)
(A pace counter drops.)
The counter flew away.
You can't do anything about it.
(Oh dear)
You can't do anything.
And this is a couple dance.
But you guys aren't dancing.
I think Jae Seok's count will be high.
I think Jong Kook will get a high count as well.
Your feet hurt at some point.
Aren't they too close?
They are about to kiss.
Why are your eyes closed?
- From the back...
-  Open your eyes, So You!
Haha is cheating!
This is really funny.
- Look at Jong Kook.
-  It's...
(The game is over.)
- I am so tired.
-  Everyone stop.
- Gosh...
-  I'm tired.
Da Som, really...
I got 102.
- Da Som is unbelievable.
-  She's good.
(Jae Seok got 102 counts.)
She got 162 counts.
- Really?
-  How did you do this?
That's amazing.
I got 138.
(Jong Kook got 138.)
And she got 123.
I got 108.
I got 94.
(Their total is 202.)
- It's tough.
-  It's tougher than you think.
Kwang Soo's team wins.
(Kwang Soo and Bora win.)
Did we win again?
(Ji Hyo and Shownu come 2nd.)
Kwang Soo's couple has won too many times.
- They have.
-  They shouldn't be included.
- Kwang Soo's team...
-  We're good. We can't help it.
- Thank you.
-  Thank you.
Thank you.
- Do you want more?
-  Let's put some sugar.
Eat.
It's good.
(They love it.)
- It's good.
-  Let's beat Kwang Soo.
- Right.
-  Let's do that.
- That's a good idea.
-  We have nine total, too.
Gosh.
(Until when will Kwang Soo continue to win?)
(The last location is A Museum.)
(They managed to come in this rain.)
What's this?
How...
How are we supposed to wear this?
What's that?
How can we wear that?
- What's this?
-  This is...
(They are couple outfits.)
We have to wear them?
I can't believe you're making us do this.
- But...
-  What's this?
- What is this?
-  what will Kwang Soo and I do?
- Bo Ra can't see.
-  That's your fate.
All right. It's the last game.
So far, Kwang Soo's team is winning.
- Oh dear.
-  We will take you down.
Why?
Don't you know that you are our enemy today?
What are you talking about?
All right. You will wear the couple outfit...
in the back...
and play Name Tag Elimination.
- It ends when one person wears out.
-  Where is the name tag?
The name tags are on the outfit.
- It's here.
-  Two outfits are connected.
- Do we have to rip this whole?
-  Oh dear.
- It's tough.
-  We have to rip this?
If this gets ripped, we're out.
Can you please put on the outfits?
- Okay.
-  Okay.
- Let's do that.
-  Can we choose any colour?
It's pink.
- Seriously.
-  I think you should wear it first.
- This is...
-  This is too tight.
- I will put my head in.
-  This is really tight.
It's small.
(Everyone somehow puts it on.)
(But Bo Ra goes missing.)
Bo Ra can't get out!
What?
- Bo Ra.
-  She's stuck.
- She can't come out.
-  Poor girl.
Wait.
Bo Ra is here.
There's no other way.
- What are you doing?
-  What are you doing? Help her.
- Bo Ra is here.
-  Treat her nicely.
Kwang Soo, you should lower your body a bit.
- How?
-  Kwang Soo's team will lose.
You want me to crawl around?
- There you go.
-  You want me to crawl?
- You're done for.
-  You're done for.
How can I play the game like this?
(He no longer is a winner.)
You're done for, Kwang Soo.
- What are you doing?
-  They became weak.
- Help us.
-  We're in trouble.
- They're in trouble.
-  They look easy now.
- They were our target anyway.
-  Good.
- With the points,
-  What do we do with them?
You can purchase items that will give you advantage.
- I see.
-  Items.
(Thank goodness we earned those points.)
(Points)
(List of Items)
(Five points equal one chance of revival.)
You will shop for items.
I will explain how it works.
You can only buy one item per category. Think wisely.
Take your outfits and go to the item store.
(List of Items)
This is good.
There's nothing else to buy.
(Kwang Soo's team buys the two best items.)
- How many are there?
-  Four.
- Thank you.
-  Revival Card?
Revival Card.
- There you go.
-  Thank you.
Let's choose the middle one. We got the middle one.
Should we go with this?
Let's go with this.
If we had one more, we could've gotten the Revival Card.
Can we pay you? How much is it?
(The teams are finish purchasing their items.)
We will now begin the race.
I want to start now.
- I'm scared.
-  Let's do this.
- Three,
-  Three.
Two, one.
The race starts.
I'm in trouble.
- Can you see?
-  I can.
I am sorry.
(They bought the chance to remove the wings.)
I'm not sure if going outside is a good thing.
It's probably a good thing, right?
Can we walk sideways?
I can see better this way.
- Like this?
-  I am sorry.
(That's not an armpit, but a facepit.)
- Hi, friends.
-  Hi.
It's the sexy couple.
(Ji Hyo's team purchased a smaller name tag.)
(Gary's team removed their wings.)
I'm your fan.
(Haha's team also removed their wings.)
- Hello.
-  Right now,
- You know, right?
-  it looks like they can revive.
- I'm sure.
-  I saw them taking scissors.
- Scissors?
-  Yes.
- That means they cut the wings.
-  We did that as well.
You know who we're eliminating after Kwang Soo, right?
- Jong Kook?
-  Yes.
- Really?
-  Then it's Jae Seok.
And then us three can remain.
- Then...
-  All right.
- You know, right?
-  High-five.
- One, two, three.
-  We can do it!
- You understand, right?
-  We'll expose our back.
(3 couples with no points plot together.)
(It's still quiet on the 2nd floor.)
Hey, friend!
(Jong Kook's team removed their wings, too.)
Hey, friends!
- Hey.
-  We are friends.
- For now.
-  Yes, for now.
About Kwang Soo's team...
(Jae Seok's team switched to a smaller name tag.)
- Let's get rid of Kwang Soo.
-  Let's do it.
- Even if we're at risk,
-  Of course.
- let's not attack each other.
- Seriously.
-  I'm being serious.
I think Kwang Soo is upstairs.
(They still can't trust each other so they walk backwards.)
I think this is a better idea.
Let's face each other.
- Let's do that.
-  Right?
- You never know.
-  Your instincts may crawl up.
Kwang Soo, the elevator is moving.
- Let's go to the third floor.
-  Let's go.
(With the facepit's guidance, they flee the scene.)
What now? I'm scared.
Should we hide here?
We're dead if we get caught.
- This is the third floor.
-  No, no.
- It's the third floor.
-  Is it?
Does "PH" stand for "penthouse"?
(The two teams get off on the 3rd floor.)
Wait, this floor...
You have to watch your back.
I'll look.
- We should defend each other.
-  Of course.
- I don't think they're here.
-  I'm sure Kwang Soo's here.
They're hiding.
Where is Kwang Soo?
- Hey, look here.
-  Hey, hey.
There...
- Was there something outside?
-  Where could they be?
- Hold on.
-  Are they outside?
Are they out in the rain?
I think they went out in the rain to hide themselves.
I know Kwang Soo would do that.
- I don't care if I get wet.
-  Jae Seok.
- I'll go check if they're outside.
-  Yell if you see them.
- Okay.
-  Okay.
- Right away, okay?
- They have to be here.
-  Where else would they go?
(Jae Seok's team set off in the rain.)
It's 100 percent.
- They're here!
-  Hey! They're here!
Kwang Soo's team is here!
(They find Kwang Soo's team soaked in the rain.)
(Go get Kwang Soo!)
I can't see what's in front of me!
Let's go get Kwang Soo.
(The facepit is drenched.)
I feel so bad for myself.
Did you have to come this far?
- Hurry up!
-  Hurry!
- Hurry!
-  Let's go.
(The other three teams join as well.)
- There they are.
-  Hurry up!
- Let's do this fairly.
-  Save me.
- We're in the rain!
-  Come here!
- I can't use my right hand.
-  My back hurts.
(Jong Kook grabs the name tag.)
No! Bo Ra!
- Bo Ra! Bo Ra!
-  Rip it.
(They managed to come this far despite the height difference.)
I ripped it.
Good job. Yes!
- We got Kwang Soo.
-  We did.
- I did it.
-  Bo Ra looks tortured.
- I almost threw up.
-  Leave me alone.
(She's guilty for meeting a partner who's 190cm tall.)
- I can't do this any more.
-  I'm sorry, Bo Ra.
I'm sorry, Bo Ra.
(Everybody's enemy team is removed.)
Kwang Soo and Bo Ra are out.
How could this happen?
What are we supposed to do? Should we crawl?
(They get ready to use the Revival Card.)
You can go now.
- I feel like they are outside.
-  Let me take a look.
I'm pretty sure.
They're waiting to hunt us down.
(Who are the people outside, waiting to hunt us down?)
(Everybody's assembled.)
(Oh, hi there.)
What are we... Hold on.
- Come here, please.
-  Let's talk.
We're going to revive.
- We're going to come out.
-  Give us one chance.
Why are we your target?
- Come out first.
-  We will come out.
Dress yourselves first.
We're going to do that but why are you doing this?
- Come out.
-  We already lost five points!
We have nothing!
Why are you even hiding?
We're not hiding. We're just waiting.
- Oh, is that true?
-  We're just waiting.
- What did I do so wrong?
-  It must be my fault.
It's fun when things don't go his way.
Can I not use the Revival Card?
Then, it ends here.
- It's the end?
-  Yes.
What am I supposed to do then?
(They're done for either way.)
We need the slightest hope.
(You'll receive your prize later for calling back first.)
I don't think they plan on coming out.
(The 5 couples watch for an opportunity to attack.)
- They're out.
-  They're back.
Come this way.
- Look at them.
-  We have to get out of here.
(Stumbling)
(They take themselves down.)
(Ripping)
(Ji Hyo's team spots an opportunity.)
- My gosh.
-  You're done.
Give us a chance.
- Look at Bo Ra.
-  Poor Bo Ra.
- Shownu's got it.
-  Shownu!
I'll let you go.
(Ripping)
(What's the point of coming in 1st place?)
(They're the 1st to get eliminated.)
(Kwang Soo and Bo Ra are out.)
Let's have a truce until we eliminate Jong Kook.
- Can the books come in first?
-  Come in.
Are you an encyclopedia or something?
Where are they?
They must be hiding.
(They hide themselves in a blind spot.)
I hope they don't jump out of nowhere.
- I know where they are.
-  They're behind a wall.
- They were hiding there before.
-  The corner, right?
- It's by the corner.
-  That's the only hiding spot.
Let's have one team go towards the elevator.
- You can go ahead.
-  Let's do this.
Yell as soon as you see them.
(Welcome to the tiger's den.)
- They're not here.
-  Go that way.
Go towards the robot experience hall.
(Roaring)
(Their target is Jae Seok's team, who's the furthest from the group.)
(Shrieking)
Producer.
(Thanks to Jae Seok's quick reflexes, Jong Kook fails.)
We made a truce with the other teams.
- Be careful.
-  No wonder...
it didn't feel right.
- Thank goodness we're in a group.
-  We came too far.
- My goodness.
-  My gosh.
- I was shocked.
-  This is shocking.
- Attack him.
-  What are you waiting for?
(This is the only time they become generous.)
We'll go here, then.
- Come here.
-  Let's switch.
- Hold on tight.
-  Should we go to the open space?
No, we'll go where we were before.
- Here?
-  They were waiting there?
We said we'll do this, so let's go.
Let's yell while we attack.
- One, two...
-  You are ready, right?
- One, two, three.
-  One, two, three.
(Yelling)
(It's all or nothing.)
(Let's have a real match!)
- Ouch, So You!
-  Pull us back!
She's so strong. I'm not even lying.
- Let go.
-  Ouch.
(Heavy-ho!)
- It's not working.
-  Rip it!
(They manage to pull them out of the corner.)
One, two.
(3 couples hold onto them while Seok Jin attacks.)
(Ripping)
(Jong Kook and So You are finally out.)
Look what happened.
We can't do this alone.
- We can't.
-  I agree.
So You is so strong.
She is.
- I think she's stronger than me.
-  She's a man.
Jong Kook and So You are out.
- Jong Kook is out.
-  What happened? They teamed up.
- It serves him right.
-  Exactly.
- That's good to hear.
-  I'm so happy.
I can finally sleep in ease.
I feel so much better now.
Jae Seok is next.
He has the second most points.
How lame.
- Think about this.
-  Is he next?
Hold on. Come on.
This is what's meant to happen.
(As planned, they go for Jae Seok this time.)
(Yelling once again, they pull Jae Seok's team out.)
(Ripping)
(I can't let them eliminate us.)
(However)
(Ripping)
I ripped it!
Did you rip it?
- My gosh.
-  Where?
(The alliance betrays them.)
(Jong Kook and Jae Seok's teams are out.)
What did I tell you, Jae Seok?
I told you that you're next!
- Listen.
-  Oh, dear.
I hope you're not mistaken.
Did you think you would last forever?
Look at these people.
The diamond rings are out of reach.
(What? Why is Seok Jin out?)
(1 minute after Jae Seok's elimination)
(Ji Hyo and Gary's teams team up and eliminated Seok Jin's team.)
- I'm so mad.
-  Me, too.
(What goes around comes around.)
I should have teamed up with Jae Seok.
Why would you... You always do this.
He always does this.
(It's too late now.)
It's a food chain.
That's true. There's no alliance.
- He's strong.
-  Shownu?
- He is.
-  He's so strong.
- Shownu...
-  He works out a lot.
We couldn't drag Jong Kook out,
but with Shownu's help, we could do it.
He's incredible.
I guess it's not over yet.
- That's Gary's voice.
-  It is.
- I guess Gary is being cornered.
-  I want to see it.
- Oh, dear.
-  Hey!
(Shownu power is seen once again.)
(Gary's team is in danger!)
- No way!
-  No!
(They try their best to resist.)
(Ripping)
(Ji Hyo and Shownu are the winners.)
- What is it?
-  How did it go?
Is it Gary and Hyo Lyn?
Ji Hyo won again.
(Ji Hyo is good in big games.)
- They're too strong.
-  They're unbeatable.
(Shownu's power is invincible.)
We should applaud for Gary and Hyo Lyn.
Hyo Lyn, can you please go out with Gary?
- Even if it's for one month.
-  Please.
- Just for a month.
-  You look great together.
So the winners for today...
Shownu pulled through.
The winners are Shownu and Ji Hyo!
(Shownu and Ji Hyo are today's winners.)
- He's strong.
-  He's different.
- They're sweating.
-  Shownu is so good.
(Shownu is the MVP.)
- Look.
-  My goodness!
- Ji Hyo has some already.
-  Goodness.
She always wins when there are prizes.
- She must be lucky.
-  You know what?
Today, I received a bigger diamond than that.
(The name of the diamond is Hyo Lyn.)
It's "Hyo Ring".
- "Hyo Ring".
-  "Hyo Ring".
(Hyo Lyn is more precious to Gary than a diamond ring is.)
Can you show us your dance again before we finish?
- Dance!
-  Dance!
- Dance! Dance!
-  It's embarrassing.
One, two, three, four!
(Dancing)
(Have a good Sunday night and see you next week.)
Hello.
(Don't forget me.)
Good to see you, Hee Ae.
(The unforgettable queen, Kim Hee Ae)
Yes, Hee Ae showed up. So what?
"Hee Ae"? Am I a friend of yours?
That's funny.
(We get to see the unexpected sides to her.)
(She leaves everything behind and joins Running Man.)
So what if something happens?
(So a man full of doubts has joined.)
(The queen's man, Ji Jin Hee)
- Why is he acting strange?
-  That's so odd.
(Everything is suspicious. Everything is strange.)
(With all the doubts and suspicions, they face the truth in the end.)
(Special Agent H)