What's all this?
(We've invited beautiful actresses for this summer special.)
(Beautiful Queen Park Shin Hye)
Oh, my. Look at her.
(Lovely Queen Lee Sung Kyoung)
(Soon, these three queens will compete fiercely.)
Previously on Running Man.
(Last Week)
(Running Man vs Hunters)
(The 7 members became Preys last week.)
I need to get out of here.
(Mysterious Hunters...)
(and the Preys who failed to resist temptation...)
(A vault is hidden somewhere in Seoul.)
(Become the owner of 7,000 dollars!)
(The Hunters are after the Preys.)
(Experienced Running Man members vs the Special 4 Hunters)
Start the car now!
(Hunters' only goal is to catch the members.)
(Will the members obtain 7,000 dollars or will they be caught?)
No way.
(Four are arrested and the survivors haven't earned full hints yet.)
(There are only three Preys left.)
(Clever Haha, Speedy Kwang Soo and Talented Ji Hyo)
(Who will be the one to come out on top?)
Please get ready to be caught.
(6 hours since the run)
(Kwang Soo is on his way to meet Haha.)
(He hurriedly grabs a taxi.)
Hello. Please take me to the War Memorial.
(What?)
(Jin Woong is right next to Kwang Soo, looking for him.)
Look! It's Uncle Jin Woong!
(Goodness.)
Right, I'm old enough to be your uncle.
Kwang Soo, you're making this old man run after you like this.
He's right there.
(I can't get caught like this.)
Please.
He's right next to us.
- Kwang Soo.
- Yes?
There's someone here...
who wants to talk to you. He has something to say.
- Who?
- Talk to him.
Kwang Soo, this is Sung Ki.
Hello, Sir.
Kwang Soo.
(What will be the head Hunter's ultimatum to Kwang Soo?)
(Will he say that he'll catch Kwang Soo or save his life?)
- Hello, Sir.
- Aren't you thirsty?
- I'm okay.
- You must be hungry, too.
(Aren't you thirsty and hungry?)
(Is this an ultimatum?)
Yes, Sir.
Let's meet and have some cold beer together.
Well, Sir...
(Sung Ki's sweet-talking.)
Actually, I'm being chased at the moment.
I think...
you should prepare to get caught nicely.
- So let's call it a day quickly...
- Okay.
and have some drinks together.
Sir, Haha is in Samgakji right now.
(Kwang Soo betrays Haha.)
He's having lunch in Samgakji.
Then, get ready to be caught heroically soon.
- Yes, Sir.
- I'll count on you.
That was really nice.
- I think it will make him hesitate.
- Right.
I'm sure he will hesitate.
(His eyes tremble in hesitation.)
(He starts running with contemplation.)
I'm in front of Changdeokgung.
Okay.
Good. I'm right next to Doldam-gil.
(Kwang Soo decides to meet Haha.)
I'm on my way to Haha now.
(He's on his way to meet Haha.)
He says he's nearby.
(Haha is on his way to Kwang Soo by taxi.)
- Hello.
- Kwang Soo, I think...
Oh, there you are. I can see you.
Get in. Get in.
(He sees Kwang Soo and stops the taxi.)
Okay.
- Hey.
- What should we do?
- Gosh.
- This is driving me crazy.
It's so nice to see you again. I'm so exhausted right now.
If we go this way, we can catch him.
- Who?
- Haha.
- Do you mean this way?
- Yes.
- This building must be there.
- There are cameras.
- Hold on, is it this way?
- That way.
Let's go.
(Haha and Kwang Soo head to Daehangno for hints.)
We must watch out here.
We should go that way.
- Where?
- Down that way.
(Ji Hyo arrives at Daehangno after obtaining hints at Ant Village.)
- Do you know where Art Council is?
- It's not this way.
- Really?
- You have to turn left.
Left?
- So are we not alone?
- We're in trouble.
Ji Hyo, hurry up!
You called me, right?
Then one of us must be on the lookout.
Why don't you two go? I'll look out for you.
- Then I'll go with Kwang Soo.
- Okay. Stand guard.
All right. Let's go find them.
I don't know where we're heading. But let's give it a shot.
Haha's at Marronnier Park now.
- So it's near Dongseong street.
- Now...
I think we should go that way.
- We should...
- We must hurry now.
Wow. They have surveillance cameras everywhere.
(Haha uses surveillance monitors for a perfect lookout.)
I think they found something. They're coming up.
Will they share the hints?
- They look the same.
- Kwang Soo,
we have to find the differences in these pictures.
"Press the button next to the window."
Window? Where is it?
- Now, Haha is...
- He's trying to survive.
not with them.
I think he's staking out.
- Do you mean Haha?
- Yes, in Daehangno.
And Kwang Soo is with Ji Hyo.
Where are you, Haha?
Why are you two not coming up?
Haha, you have to open the door in the basement for us.
- Do I have to open the door?
- Yes.
Ji Hyo, I have a bad feeling.
(I don't feel good about this.)
Oh, I found it.
One, two, three, four, five.
I need to find two more.
- This is driving me crazy.
- There are so many people here.
The atmosphere's very strange here.
Haha.
Calm down, Ji Hyo. Take your time. You can do it.
Haha,
- switch positions with Kwang Soo.
- I think they're coming in.
What?
They're here?
Find it now, Ji Hyo!
I can't!
Find it!
I found it!
(Ji Hyo finally finds all the passwords.)
(Haha discovers something.)
(They're here.)
Gosh, they're here!
They are here!
They're here!
(Ji Hyo starts running away, leaving Kwang Soo behind.)
(Tall Kwang Soo tries to climb over the wall.)
(Will they be able to successfully escape from the Hunters?)
Go get them! Catch them!
Where are they? Where?
(They're running in the middle of Daehangno.)
(Haha, don't make this chase more complicated.)
(Jae Seok is running after Haha.)
- Jae Seok!
- Come here.
(Jae Seok sucessfully corners Haha.)
(There's no way to escape.)
Gary, go catch Kwang Soo.
Kwang Soo, run!
Come here.
- There you are, Jin Woong.
- Jin Woong, rip his name tag.
My goodness.
- There you are.
- Hello, Jin Woong.
You're here, Jin Woong.
(Nice to meet you, Prey.)
(I got you, Haha.)
Rip his name tag off.
(Ripping)
Come over here, Haha.
Come here.
- Let's go catch Kwang Soo.
- No way!
Haha, where's Kwang Soo?
(The Hunters are now after Kwang Soo and Ji Hyo.)
(Hunters arrest Haha.)
(Ji Hyo barely escapes the building with the password for the vault.)
Sit down. Let's talk first.
Let's sit down here.
We should...
(Ji Hyo obtained all the hints and the password.)
There's information here.
Yeonhui Hill was a battlefield of the Korean War.
There was a battle here. I found the information.
Ji Hyo!
(No one answers back in the silence.)
Ji Hyo.
(Quiet)
(He's nothing but a rat in a trap without others' help from outside.)
Haha.
(There's no one here, either.)
(Haha... Ji Hyo... Please, anyone...)
Let's be together until the end.
(Us three must survive and find the vault together.)
- Kwang Soo!
- Ji Hyo!
(You're on your way to save me, right?)
(We're here for you.)
- Why did you do that?
- Hello.
- Kwang Soo.
- How do we open the door?
My goodness.
- How could you...
- Hold on.
No way! Why are you here?
- You...
- Wait.
- Sit down. Sit down.
(Yul removes Kwang Soo's name tag.)
- Sit down.
- No!
How could you do that to me?
Did you get Haha, too?
- We finally caught Kwang Soo.
- Gosh, I was almost done!
- It was a long day, right?
- Right.
You're so inconsiderate.
- You shouldn't do that.
- Wait...
You shouldn't have done that to the taxi driver.
How could you?
I am sorry.
(We'd like to thank the taxi driver for driving him around.)
- Let's go catch Ji Hyo!
- Did you not see her?
- Ji Hyo just went up!
- Let's go.
- Let's get going.
- Goodness.
(Let's go get Ji Hyo. She has all the hints.)
(Kwang soo is out, too. Ji Hyo is the only one left.)
(Ji Hyo heads to the vault.)
Sir, please go to Yeonhui Hill.
(Meanwhile, the Hunters are chasing after Ji Hyo.)
Ji Hyo is the only one who got the hint at Miari Ridge.
(They must catch Ji Hyo before she gets to the vault.)
- Ji Hyo is the most dangerous one.
- It's her.
Look at this.
I just looked it up on the internet.
It says there's a Memorial monument of Hill 104 there.
Is this the right place?
(She arrives at Yeonhui Hill after almost 8 hours of running.)
Oh, I'm finally here.
This is the right place.
It says "Memorial monument of Hill 104".
(I should hurry.)
I found it.
(She finds the right place with the hints she obtained.)
What?
(She's about to garner 7,000 dollars.)
(The vault is right before her.)
(She has been running all day for this.)
(Will Ji Hyo be able to grab 7,000 dollars?)
- My goodness.
- Well done so far.
(Hello. Nicely done, Ji Hyo.)
- Poor Ji Hyo.
- How?
We waited for you for a long time.
- We waited the whole day.
- I knew you'd be waiting here.
- What's that building? A hospital?
- This man is on crutches.
Isn't it Marronnier Park?
- It's near Daehangno, isn't it?
- Yes.
Somewhere related to the Korean War.
Isn't it Yeonhui Hill?
- It looks like it.
- It really does.
This must be the place. Yeonhui Hill.
- Hello.
- Have you found the place?
I just arrived at Miari Ridge. Oh, goodness.
They said we should go underneath Hangang Bridge.
All right. I saw it.
- It's 53.
- The answer is 53.
- This is the building. Right there.
- I think they're there.
We're at the right spot.
- My goodness! Jin Woong!
- Where are you going?
Where are you going?
You're right! It's Hongje-dong.
Sorry, do you know Mr Kim Jae Pyung living in the village?
I found it. Memorial monument of Hill 104.
I found it.
- Isn't it referring to year 1953?
- Isn't it 1907?
Did something special happen in 1907?
Look.
- It must have been in the 1950s.
- Right.
- So it's 1953, in July.
- In July.
- It's the Korean Armistice Day.
- Yes. It's the Armistice Day.
- In 1953.
- It's the Armistice Day.
(They successfully open the vault.)
It's my father's birthday, too.
What's inside?
- Look.
- There's something inside.
- Are these for us? One each?
- Yes.
- They're the Golden Badges.
- Thank you.
- Congratulations.
The R mark in the centre is made of real gold.
- So the exterior is fake.
- Yes. You can detach it, too.
I'll cut off the parts when I get back home.
At home?
You should keep it as a token of remembrance.
Anyway, thank you everyone for joining us today.
(We'd like to thank all of the guests for joining us.)
- It was tough.
- Good job everyone.
Well done.
(There are 48 days left until the Rio 2016 Olympics.)
(Korea National Training Center)
- Well done.
- It's summer already.
It's summer already. It's so hot.
- Did you see the preview for today?
- Yes, I did.
- Shin Hye will join us today.
- It came out in the preview.
- Call her by her full name.
- You should do that, not me.
- I'll keep calling her comfortably.
- Does everyone want to know...
- today's guest?
- No, we've watched the preview.
He tried to court Sung Kyoung last time,
- but it didn't go well.
- No, I didn't!
- He tried to.
- We're like family now.
He approached Hyun Jin and Sung Kyoung last time.
- Yes. That's right.
- You approached Hyun Jin as well.
- That's not true.
- It's really strange though.
All the women who was approached by Kwang Soo and turned him down...
- become really famous.
- That's right.
- That's so true.
- It's not true!
- That's true.
- Think of Hyun Jin.
- Sung Kyoung and I are friends!
- That sounds reasonable.
- No way.
- They all became stars.
- That's right.
- Do you agree with me?
You should never go out with Kwang Soo.
Why is everyone doing this?
(Just have fun, but don't go out with him.)
I know everyone is curious to know about today's guests.
- We already know.
- You revealed them all already.
So I'll introduce them now.
They are actually standing over there right now.
Who are they?
(Two handsome men approach them.)
- It's Gyun Sang.
- From "Descendants of the Sun".
- Good to see you, Gyun Sang!
- Welcome.
(Yoon Gyun Sang and Kim Min Seok)
(Yoon Gyun Sang acted in the drama "Six Flying Dragons".)
I'm Moo Hyul, a warrior!
(Kim Min Seok acted in the drama "Descendants of the Sun".)
Hello. My name is Gyun Sang...
and I'll be acting in the drama "Doctors". Good to see you.
Last time, he acted as a warrior named "Moo Hyul".
- In the drama "Six Flying Dragons".
- Will you be a doctor this time?
Hello. I'm Min Seok. I'll be acting in "Doctors" as well.
Min Seok will play the role of Kwang Soo.
I'll introduce the queens who are joining us today.
(Finally, the queens are here.)
(Ji Hyo looks beautiful in a white dress today.)
(He's stunned.)
- Ji Hyo.
- Ji Hyo looks...
really pretty in a dress like this.
She often dresses up properly like this.
Ji Hyo is dressed up today.
- My gosh. You're pretty.
- You look Vietnamese.
- You look pretty today.
- You're dressed up today.
- You look really pretty today.
- Hello.
- Hi.
- You look so pretty.
(They are surprised.)
Who's next?
(Who is the second queen?)
(She's so charming that you may fall in love with her at first sight.)
- Welcome.
- She's Sung Kyoung.
(Lee Sung Kyoung)
She hasn't changed at all.
- She's the daughter of Running Man.
- Right.
Everything went well for her after joining us last time.
Here comes the next queen.
(Wow. They can't help but exclaim.)
(Her smile is as bright as the sun.)
- Wow.
- It's Shin Hye this time.
(Park Shin Hye)
- Hello.
- The dancing machine is here.
Nice to see you, Shin Hye.
- Good to see you.
- They are both here.
(He can't hide his smile.)
- They are pretty.
- Wow. They are all..
- beautiful today.
- Today, these women...
These queens will join us today. Park Shin Hye and Lee Sung Kyoung!
(They're today's two beautiful queens.)
Also,
Min Seok and Gyun Sang has also joined us!
(The queens' bodyguards, Min Seok and Gyun Sang)
- Wow, he's tall.
- He really is.
Both of you look so handsome.
The title for today's race is "Oh, My Queen!".
A few minutes ago, the three queens...
picked one rose each...
to see which one of them is the real queen.
Only one of them is the real queen,
and the other two are fake queens.
Really?
The queen who wins the game in the end will receive a diamond tiara.
This is what the male members have to do today.
You need to find the real queen and make her victorious today.
I see.
A hint about the real queen will be revealed after each mission,
so you must gather the hints and decide in the end.
But if a fake queen wins the race,
you will be flogged.
- Goodness.
- Flogged?
This is crazy.
You will receive a hint...
about who the real queen is at the end of each mission from now on.
- So watch them closely.
- We got it.
First, we'll make three teams.
We must choose which queen we think is the real one.
- Can we change our decision later?
- Let's begin.
- All right.
- Let's go.
(They may find hints while the queens dance.)
How should I do this?
(The dance battle among the queens)
I'm not sure who it is yet.
(Let's begin, Queens!)
- Look.
- I don't have any ideas yet.
I think Ji Hyo is the real queen.
- Do you think it's Ji Hyo? Really?
- Yes, I think it's her.
- Ji Hyo? Is it really you?
- We can change our decisions later.
- Really?
- I feel like it's Ji Hyo.
- Can we really change our choices?
- She's dancing really hard.
(They dance hard to attract more members to their team.)
(And this man seems so happy as well.)
Sung Kyoung dances well.
Look at Jae Seok's face. What's wrong with him?
- Hey, look.
- He's really scary.
(Jae Seok is really excited.)
- He's so annoying.
- He is.
(What was that dance move?)
We can't have too many people in a team.
- I feel like it's Ji Hyo.
- I think so, too.
Ji Hyo is dancing really hard.
I really think it's her.
You must keep moving.
All right. In 5, 4, 3, 2...
How will it turn out?
One!
I really think it's Sung Kyoung.
All right.
(Ji Hyo)
One, two...
(Sung Kyoung, Shin Hye)
Three.
(Who did the men choose as the real queen?)
- Park Shin Hye!
- Lee Sung Kyoung!
- Song Ji Hyo!
- Park Shin Hye!
- Lee Sung Kyoung!
All right. You chose your teams.
Now, we will give you a hint about who the real queen is.
It's related to the dance battle we just had.
- A hint?
- What does he mean?
- About their dances?
- There must be a hint...
- about their dancing.
- Among their dances.
The real queen was...
the last person who stopped dancing.
She was the last.
- Really?
- No. Shin Hye was the last.
- I'm not so sure.
- I didn't see them in the end.
- Wasn't Shin Hye the last?
- You're right!
(You shouldn't let your guard down. Make good use of the given hints.)
(Ji Hyo, Sung Kyoung and Shin Hye. Who is the real queen?)
(Team Shin Hye, Team Sung Kyoung and Team Ji Hyo)
Queens, please get on a palanquin.
- Two members will carry it.
- And one will fan her.
More importantly, there is a big difference in their height.
Have a sip, Your Highness.
- Don't hold me back.
- Isn't that too much?
Doesn't it feel nice to be treated like this, Shin Hye?
- It feels nice.
- It's nice.
- Can I have some strong wind?
- Of course, you can.
(I can make it a lot stronger if you want.)
Is this how things will go today?
- Shall we go?
- The tag says "Queen Sung Kyoung".
- She's "Queen Shin Hye".
- If you take a letter out of here,
it will change the meaning completely.
- Hey, Shin Hye!
- Shin Hye.
Go, Haha. I should've lost some weight before I came.
- How did people do all of this?
- Do you feel cool, My Queen?
- Actually, it feels nice.
- Please fan me, too.
It's nice to be able to fan Shin Hye.
- Anyway...
- We're almost there.
(They arrive at an outdoor pool near the Training Center.)
- My goodness.
- Should we run there?
- What is that?
- I guess we need to run over that.
(The queens give sunscreen to the members.)
You're so kind.
You're kind. No wonder.
Put it on your ears.
You should put sunscreen on your nose and cheeks. Like this.
Put it behind your neck.
- You must put on sunscreen.
- Your neck, too.
(Seok Jin rides a buoy to get to the centre of the pool.)
- Don't do it. Just don't.
- Wait.
You must jump over to that side.
Don't! I'll just jump!
(Lifting)
(He falls into the water.)
(Seok Jin starts off by getting soaked.)
- Why did you do that?
- Why?
This game is called "Carry Your Queen".
The guys from each team will piggyback the opponents' queens.
The opponent?
You'll piggyback the opponents' queens...
and run on the track. Then, you'll pass the queen to the next player.
It'll be a relay...
and you must finish the race before the other team to win.
(You must come in before the other team to win.)
And as you can see,
there are toy hammers and other tools on the side.
The queens can pick one and use it to disturb the other team members.
- I see.
- That's what they were for.
(Team Ji Hyo moves on since they've already won a game.)
What's the white one?
(Running Man members are known for cheating.)
You can hit their faces.
This one's good, too.
This one is good, too.
The sprayer is the best.
You can spray it in their eyes.
Can I spray it in their noses?
- This is enough.
- No, she needs something more.
Which team would be better for us?
(These rookies are scared.)
Ready!
- Let's get started.
- Ready!
She's giving me an arm bar!
- What's this? She's already aiming.
- Ready.
(The 2nd runners fight amongst themselves.)
(They have started their own game.)
Let's get ready, everybody.
(The 1st runners get ready.)
(We can't lose.)
(We must let our queen take the win.)
(This looks interesting.)
(These women are intense!)
(The game starts!)
(Spraying)
(Pouring)
(They start attacking as soon as the match starts.)
(Struggling)
(They fall into the water.)
(Queen Shin Hye's tactic works!)
(Nice one, Queen Shin Hye.)
(She shoots water into his nose...)
(and wriggles her feet.)
(Seok Jin collapses.)
(Kwang Soo is proud of her.)
(These queens are no joke.)
- Stand up.
- Stand up!
(Shaking)
Why aren't you coming?
(He crawls instead of walking.)
(She draws on his face with a lipstick.)
(Is this a rodeo?)
Hey, hey. She's no joke.
- It must be difficult for them.
- That's right.
(Seok Jin finally gets back up.)
That's cold. That's cold!
Lean back, Sung Kyoung.
Fall down, Sung Kyoung!
Hey!
- Hello.
- Hey!
(They fall in.)
(She's driving him crazy.)
(Struggling)
- Gosh!
- I'm so tired.
I'm so tired.
(He looks mad.)
Come back!
- Come back, Shin Hye.
- Stop it!
- Come back.
(I'm 50 and I miss my mum.)
- I know I look ugly right now.
- Let's go!
(Shin Hye is slightly behind,)
(so she uses a wrestling move.)
She's too strong. She's fierce.
That's the par terre position.
- Isn't that too much?
- Let's go.
You can't do that.
It's wrestling.
She's hanging onto him.
(The two queens make this a close match.)
(Seok Jin comes in first.)
- She's tired.
- Let's go, Sung Kyoung.
What happened to your face, Haha?
(He can't stand being criticised about his face.)
This is too much.
(Gagging)
(The guys are exhausted.)
(I can't watch this.)
Hurry up, Sung Kyoung. Come closer.
(Seok Jin passes the baton to Jae Seok.)
I'll go fast.
(She starts attacking him nonetheless.)
(He goes fast into the water.)
She's no joke.
(Cheering)
This is not a party!
- Get on first.
- I'm going to disturb you.
One, two, three.
(Queen Shin Hye has a new weapon.)
(He tries to hurry.)
(He's actually balancing well.)
(The secret is in his skinny and long legs.)
I won't be responsible if you fall, okay?
(Kwang Soo's piggyback makes her dizzy.)
(She still rubs the glove against his face.)
(Shocked)
I'm sorry, Kwang Soo.
(It's just a rubber glove but it's powerful.)
- I can't see anything!
- This stings.
Wow, Sung Kyoung is fierce.
(The two teams are quite close.)
(Queen Shin Hye dangles from his back.)
(He doesn't budge.)
Good job, Kwang Soo!
(He shows no mercy.)
(Open your mouth, Jae Seok.)
(I'll clean your teeth for you.)
They're both fierce.
(They're worried about who they'll get.)
You're almost done. Hurry up.
She's no joke.
Just go in the water!
(The rubber glove is the first attack.)
Are you trying to peel the squid?
(She prepares the squid...)
(and rinses it.)
- Hurry up.
- My goodness.
(It's Jong Kook's turn.)
(He charges on.)
No!
(He's shocked.)
No! Fall in the water!
(She sways from side to side but he doesn't budge.)
(He overtakes the other team.)
Oh, wow. We're good.
You can do it!
(Are you sure?)
(She's fast.)
(He's done.)
Oh, dear.
My eyebrows are gone.
Gary, you're almost there! Hang in there!
(Queen Shin Hye and Jong Kook are too strong.)
(Now, it's all up to Sung Kyoung.)
No! No way!
I'm scared!
(They fall in.)
(He's more scared of her.)
(Sung Kyoung's splashing performance starts now.)
(Splashing to the left)
(Splashing to the right)
(She's incredible.)
(This is it!)
(Thanks to Sung Kyoung, the gap narrows.)
Hurry up. Hurry!
- Good job.
- Stop it!
(Gary surpasses Jong Kook.)
Shin Hye!
(Queen Shin Hye's attack doesn't make him flinch.)
(Meanwhile, Queen Sung Kyoung attacks Jong Kook.)
(And she succeeds.)
(Thanks to Queen Sung Kyoung,)
(Gary crosses the finish line.)
(Team Sung Kyoung wins the first round.)
(They owe it to Sung Kyoung.)
I don't know what you're talking about.
I lost but I feel good about it.
Wait, we have to do another round.
We have to do another round.
They have another round to go.
It's our turn now.
What's more tragic is that we'll be facing Ji Hyo.
Try your best.
Try piggybacking Ji Hyo.
(She's the real deal.)
She's very fierce.
(Wait for me, guys.)
Team Ji Hyo has only 2 guys so you have to pick 2 as well.
- Okay!
- Let's do rock, paper, scissors.
- All right, brothers.
(They're too tired to be nice.)
- Rock, paper, scissors!
(Haha wins.)
Okay!
(He's angry and resentful.)
(Haha always gets lucky.)
(Team Sung Kyoung advances to the final round!)
Let's go, Ji Hyo!
(Team Sung Kyoung vs Team Ji Hyo)
- Let's go!
Look at her. Look.
(Ji Hyo loads herself with clothespins.)
(She plans to clip them all over their faces.)
Look how cruel she is.
Is she trying to exfoliate me with the scrubber?
(Sung Kyoung takes a scrubber.)
(Gary and Min Seok are good to go.)
Get on their backs.
Why has Ji Hyo gotten so light?
She's so light now.
This reminds me of the old days.
("Carry Your Queen")
(The final round begins!)
(Queen Sung Kyoung pours ice as soon as they start.)
(Squeezing)
(Queen Ji Hyo represses Gary by putting her legs around him.)
Wait!
(Ji Hyo is unbelievable.)
Ji Hyo is unbelievable. He can't even start.
(Queen Sung Kyoung takes out her scrubber.)
She's exfoliating me!
(Scrubbing)
That must hurt.
That's too much.
- He didn't even soak his skin.
- Look at Sung Kyoung.
(He can't stand the pain...)
(and enters the water.)
(Meanwhile, Queen Ji Hyo...)
(clips Gary with clothespins and gives him a makeover.)
This hurts so much!
Come on, Ji Hyo!
This is so annoying! Ouch, my legs!
(His legs are about to give out.)
I'm going to cry!
I'm so tired!
(It's been a while, right?)
(I'm just happy to see you again, that's all.)
(This is a couple's synchronised swimming.)
(Title: Mermaid and the Ugly E.T.)
- She's strangling him.
- She's no joke.
- She's unbelievable.
- Ji Hyo is unbelievable.
Take these off now! Take these off!
(It wakes him up.)
I feel so lucky we didn't move onto the finals.
- I'm so thankful.
- It's a relief.
Ji Hyo is too strong.
Come here.
Gary, they're far ahead of you!
Hey, Kwang Soo.
(All right, I'm on my way.)
(Where do you think you're going?)
Hey, stop!
(Her lethal move is wrapping her legs around him.)
Come on!
You won't know unless you experience it.
(But this was just the beginning.)
(She hits his throat at full speed.)
(She wrings him tightly with her legs.)
- Come on!
- My legs!
Think of something else!
What's that?
Bear it, Gary! You can do it!
This is too cruel! I can't watch it any more!
- She is cruel. She really is.
- This is crazy.
Ji Hyo, you never disappoint us.
Ji Hyo is impossible. She's impossible.
No...
(They go from a couple to this. What is your limit, Ji Hyo?)
(Thanks to Ji Hyo's interception, Gary arrives late.)
You're here! You're here! Okay!
Kwang Soo, you're in trouble now!
She lost a lot of her energy. She's weaker now.
Her entire body is a weapon.
(Ji Hyo holds him tightly.)
(Kwang Soo falters.)
I wasn't trying to be funny! I wasn't!
It's impossible to move!
(While Kwang Soo kneels down,)
What's this?
(Gyun Sang sprints.)
(But not for long.)
- That's good! You went far.
- I don't know how I did it.
(His plan is to go as far as he can since he will fall anyway.)
Good job, Gyun Sang! You went far!
(Kwang Soo tries again.)
Here we go.
(But he kneels once again.)
He is seriously not exaggerating.
- I was so shocked.
- Ji Hyo is unbelievable.
Ji Hyo is unbelievable.
Stop her from wringing you!
(He collapses.)
(Power off)
How bad is she?
(How powerful is she?)
- That's great.
- This is really crazy.
(Meanwhile, Gyun Sang...)
(throws himself in the water as planned.)
(Team Ji Hyo has the lead.)
Kwang Soo, you can stop her from tightening her legs!
(Kwang Soo, aims for her legs.)
(He attempts to stop her legs using his two hands.)
(Ji Hyo, forgive me...)
(for everything I've done wrong. I was wrong.)
(Flapping)
(It's no longer about competition, but about survival.)
Good job. She's doing well.
(With Ji Hyo's power and Gyun Sang's strategy,)
(Gyun Sang scores a goal.)
(They got both power and tactic. They show perfect team work.)
Goal!
Team Ji Hyo wins this round.
(Team Ji Hyo wins.)
I want everyone to experience this so that...
- you know I am not lying.
- You can't walk.
You really can't walk.
Here we go.
- You collapse automatically.
- I am not lying.
- You just collapse.
- My back problem got fixed.
- Come here.
- She corrected my spine!
- My cold is cured.
- Come here. Come on.
Min Seok, come here.
But why do I have to do this to my own team member?
- Why do I have to feel this?
- Just experience it.
(He gasps in pain.)
Congratulations! You will instantly feel better!
I was right, wasn't I?
That's how it is.
- Why am I doing this to my team?
- After I got it,
my eye sight improved.
I see better now.
(Is this how variety shows works?)
- Here's the hint.
- Okay.
In the "Carry Your Queen"...
We have to get this one.
On average, the person who dived...
into the water the most is the real queen.
- The name is...
- Ji Hyo didn't dive much.
(Is it Ji Hyo?)
(A while ago, Ji Hyo showed an unbelievable skill.)
(It looks like she fell into the water many times.)
(They cannot remember.)
- Didn't she stay in the water?
- Isn't it Sung Kyoung?
Sung Kyoung fell in the water a lot.
- Yes. I am the real queen.
- It's not Ji Hyo.
I fell on my face so many times that it hurts.
(Who is the real queen?)
(The members get into their queens' cars.)
Something happened at home.
I was on the 007 special the other time, right?
At the time, I won a Golden Badge, right?
But a thief broke into my place.
- Really.
- Really?
- Did he take the badge?
- He took it.
He only took the gold that was attached to it.
How did he know about it? He must be a fan of Running Man.
He must've watched the episode.
- You have to be careful.
- So today,
- I have to make sure to get one.
- You have to get one.
You should win the gold today.
- There's a reason why I'm the one.
- That's why you are the real one.
By the way, that team must be very quiet.
- Which one?
- The one in the front.
- Oh, goodness.
- What will they do?
- They will just stay quiet.
- They'll only be breathing.
(Silent)
(Nobody is speaking.)
We have to use our brains and win today.
Otherwise, you will be flogged.
(Why would you break their spirits?)
Getting flogged on your first variety show...
is too sad.
- They only hit men, right?
- Yes.
But when you get flogged, it will become a memory.
Good or not, you will have a memory of what a variety show is about.
(It becomes quiet again.)
(We are worried about these rookies.)
When I drive, I have to put on some music.
Let's sing. What song should we sing?
A rap song.
You go first.
- All eyes on me, my soul is free
- She's actually doing it.
Other girls feel insecure because of me
They won't talk until I apologise
- Gosh.
- Aren't I good?
- That's not it.
- Wait.
- It's not that we didn't like it.
- It's not that.
Concentrate! Listen! Look at me and listen!
- It gave me goosebumps.
- You were too serious.
- Kwang Soo...
- He interrupts my groove.
We don't get along well.
You always make me like that.
- What is this?
- It's a track.
Get off, get off.
- What is it?
- One, two, three.
Look at that.
(There is a huge structure.)
(What kind of mission will they carry out here?)
The second mission is "Queen Olympics".
We invited one more special queen.
There's another?
- Taekwon Girl.
- It's her.
She's athlete Kim So Hee.
It's Kim So Hee.
(She will be joining the Rio 2016 Olympics.)
(She's got a small physique, but she has sharp kicks.)
She succeeds to hit the head!
(She is the gold medalist of the 2014 Asian Games.)
- She appeared like a comet.
- Awesome.
(The Taekwondo queen visits Running Man!)
- Taekwon!
- She must be busy.
- It's an honour.
- Taekwon!
- Kim So Hee.
I love Taekwondo, too.
She's black belt.
Preparing for Rio 2016 Summer Olympics,
she must be very busy right now.
The mission rule is simple.
So Hee will kick and smash...
- This?
- styrofoam boards.
Shin Hye is really good at kicking.
One queen and one representative male member from each team...
- Gosh...
- must beat So Hee's record.
The winning team will get the hint.
- Jong Kook.
- Go, Jong Kook.
- But...
- He has a third degree black belt.
- But that's...
- Gary has eight degrees in total.
- But a tall person...
- He's the master of fighting.
Short people can't do this.
Have you ever done Taekwondo?
- Never.
- His nickname is Eiffel Tower.
- Why?
- He can't split his legs far.
Is that true?
(His legs make a perfect A-shape.)
- Is that right?
- But he's Moo Hyul.
- His nickname is Eiffel Tower?
- But Moo Hyul doesn't kick.
- It's advantageous for us.
Moo Hyul doesn't kick!
- Moo Hyul doesn't kick.
- He only uses a sword.
But Shin Hye is very flexible.
- Being flexible beats everything.
- She's the best.
Anyway, the male representatives will play against the queens.
So Hee will first show us how it is done.
- Yes.
- Please welcome So Hee.
- It's an honour to see your kicks.
- Don't hurt yourself.
- She can kick high.
- She can.
(She can kick at a 180-degree angle.)
- Do I have to just kick?
- You know what will be...
more honourable? You have to get hit by her kick.
Do you want to try it?
- Seok Jin will try.
- I will do it.
You have to put something on his head.
- Like that.
- Oh, gosh.
It's scary.
- You're good at aiming, right?
- Yes.
- Please do well.
- Please.
Maybe she will kick his nose and his nose will fly off.
(That was a perfect kick.)
(This glorious high-kick overwhelms Seok Jin.)
- She makes it look easy.
- It's really scary.
Like this.
- She's truly amazing.
- It's really scary.
- So Hee.
- You can use any form you want.
- Just relax and do it.
- Come on!
You can do it!
(Her glorious kick will lead Rio 2016 Olympics.)
(She has charisma.)
The boards got ripped.
19.
- 19.
- She kicked 19 of them.
19.
She's not a tall person, yet...
- Her kick was almost straight.
- I know.
- Kwang Soo can...
- Now, the team that breaks...
more than 20 boards will win.
Which team will go first? Queen Sung Kyoung!
She's very tall, so we have an advantage.
Because she's tall, she can kick more boards.
(Shall I give it a go?)
Cheer her on, please.
Sung Kyoung has fair skin, too.
- It's the same when I'm tanned.
- She doesn't get a tan easily.
- How do you know that?
- This is me being tanned.
- Is that right?
- We're close friends.
How do you know so well?
- How do you know so well?
- It doesn't make sense.
- How would he know that?
- How do you know that?
I've known her for a long time.
Sung Kyoung is ignoring us.
(She doesn't mind them.)
(Oh my goodness!)
- Sung Kyoung, that's great!
- That...
was really high! You reached 20.
She has really long legs.
(At this rate, they'll be able to succeed.)
- You can do it!
- Can I get the tiara?
- You can get the tiara.
- Lee Sung Kyoung!
(Go for it, Sung Kyoung!)
- Get ready.
- Go for it!
Try to stretch your leg as high as possible.
- Raise your leg high!
- You can do it.
(Queen Sung Kyoung breaks 18 boards.)
You broke 18 of them.
- I was so close.
- You did a good job.
- You're strong.
- You did great.
- She broke 18 boards.
- Okay.
- Queen Ji Hyo!
I think she'll break a lot.
(Why am I worried about this?)
Just think that's Kwang Soo.
Get ready.
(Let's do this as usual.)
(Ji Hyo often kicked Kwang Soo very well.)
(Here goes Queen Ji Hyo!)
(She kicks the boards.)
(Many boards are broken.)
- She broke 13 of them.
- She is...
- No, she broke 11 boards.
- It's 11.
Finally, it's Queen Shin Hye's turn!
(It's Queen Shin Hye's turn.)
Queen Shin Hye!
- I think she'll succeed.
- Really.
- She's competitive.
- Then...
- She's good at this.
- Director!
Gosh, I feel so pressured.
- I feel like I must win.
- You must.
- Since you're flexible.
- Of course.
She has a flexible body.
But she also has a dogged determination.
(She has a dogged determination.)
And...
No, please stop. It's my first time here in two years.
(We'll see how dogged she is.)
- Don't be nervous, Shin Hye.
- Show us how strong you are.
(She looks determined.)
(She has a firm stance.)
(She breaks the boards.)
Wow!
(She breaks 19 boards.)
She also made a scratch on the 20th board.
- She really did.
- That's amazing.
Gosh, you were so close to it.
- I was so close.
- Right.
All right.
The queens have competed fiercely.
- It's the guys' turn now.
- Okay.
We have many tall members.
- You can do it!
- Go for it!
(Gary goes first.)
Go, Gary.
(What a powerful kick!)
(Gary breaks 22 boards!)
(That's unbelievable!)
(Thanks to Gary, Team Sung Kyoung completes the mission.)
That was amazing.
It's Jong Kook's turn!
(Jong Kook gives it a try.)
(He breaks 21 boards and his team also succeeds.)
(It's all up to Gyun Sang now.)
It's Gyun Sang's turn now.
His nickname is Eiffel Tower. Gyun Sang!
(It's Gyun Sang's turn.)
- He's really tall.
- But...
his body is a bit stiff.
He can do it because he's tall.
(Will this stiff guy be able to break the boards?)
Warrior Moo Hyul!
Break more than 23 boards!
- What was that?
- 23?
- What did she say?
- Surpass 23.
- I'll carry out the mission...
- What is she doing?
without any mistakes.
I'll start.
(Start)
Warrior Moo Hyul!
I'll carry out the mission without any mistakes.
(I'll do my best...)
(with all my heart.)
(Breaking)
It's broken!
(His performance is a bit disappointing.)
(Laughing)
- He made it!
- He reached the 20th board.
- It's 20!
- It's 20.
- He cleared the mission!
- Good job.
(Gyun Sang, Gary and Jong Kook broke 20, 22 and 21 boards respectively.)
All three teams...
cleared the mission.
So we'll tell all of you what the real queen did as a hint.
(They get closer to finding out who the real queen is.)
(Who is the real queen?)
(The real queen held hands with one of her team members.)
The real queen held hands with her team member?
When did she do that?
I can't remember.
No. Didn't she hold...
someone's hand when she lifted her leg?
Does it have to be a hand exactly?
- Isn't it Shin Hye?
- Hands and arms are different.
Please tell us exactly. Can it be an arm instead of a hand?
- This counts, too.
- The shoulder?
Please tell us exactly.
- But...
- We need to make this clear.
It was great to have So Hee with us.
But we'll be even more happy to see you again on television.
We'll root for you, So Hee.
Please take care and do your best in the Olympics.
(The Rio 2016 Olympics will be held this summer.)
(The Korean players will do their best and we'll root for you all.)
Please don't get hurt.
- It's okay if you don't get medals.
- Right.
But please do your best there.
- We'll root for you.
- He's right.
Don't forget that we'll be rooting for you in Korea.
- Did you hold a guy's hand?
- I did.
- I think...
- Shin Hye held a guy's hand.
- Right.
I might be the real queen.
- But they said she held hands.
- Right.
I remember that I grabbed your arm like this.
Min Seok hopes that I'm the real queen.
So he asked if this part can be regarded as a hand.
Didn't you?
I think it's not you, Sung Kyoung.
Do you think so? Then leave me. You won't get the diamond.
I'm confident that I'm the real queen.
If you are, I think you would've tried to persuade me more.
Why should I? Don't you think I was born to be the queen?
Can't you feel how confident I am?
Can't you?
Are you smart or dumb?
I'm telling you the truth.
(Sung Kyoung is too confident.)
It's okay. Leave us, then.
- You're good.
- Of course, I am.
- She is.
- Great.
You should show me some reaction.
(They head to the next mission.)
(S University in Gongreung-dong, Seoul)
Gosh, it's really confusing. Who's the real queen?
Just believe me. Trust me.
- Okay.
- Shin Hye.
- You're our queen.
- We'll believe you.
See you.
(The three queens head somewhere.)
Are you going to separate us?
(The three queens are isolated in different rooms.)
What's going on?
It's time to make a final choice.
(A final choice?)
Here is The Decision Room.
Find your team's queen and go into the room.
Change into the team uniform of the one...
who you think is the real queen...
and join her team.
It's so confusing.
I just need one more hint.
What should we do?
(Their choice might change their destiny.)
(There were three hints about the real queen.)
(Hint 1: The real queen danced until the end.)
She danced until the end.
(Is Sung Kyoung the real queen?)
(Hint 2: The real queen fell into the water the most.)
I fell face down into the water so many times that it hurts.
(Is Shin Hye the real queen?)
(Hint 3: The real queen held a guy's hand.)
(Is Ji Hyo the real queen?)
(Which one of them is the real queen?)
I seriously don't know.
(The male members enter the rooms.)
(Will they stay loyal to their original queens?)
Gosh, this is not easy.
(Whom will they choose?)
Park Soo Kwang!
(Kwang Soo acted as Soo Kwang, Sung Kyoung's partner, in a drama.)
If you're not the real queen, everything will become meaningless.
It's you, right?
(Kwang Soo chooses Sung Kyoung.)
No. I'm almost done.
(5 minutes ago, Kwang Soo thought about going to Shin Hye.)
(But then he contemplated.)
Yes, I'm done now.
(He chose Sung Kyoung in the end.)
(Kwang Soo didn't betray her.)
I am the real one.
- Are you?
- I am.
I thought so.
- I'm the real one.
- Good.
(Who will come to Shin Hye's room?)
(Jong Kook enters.)
- Jong Kook.
- Hi.
I am so happy.
What are you so happy about?
Actually,
- I'm the real queen.
- I hesitated a bit.
- But for now,
- I'm the real queen.
I chose you.
- Jong Kook.
- Yes?
Wow, great.
(Min Seok betrays Ji Hyo and joins Shin Hye's team.)
(He betrayed Ji Hyo without hesitation.)
Welcome.
I really hope you're the real one.
Of course, I am. Don't worry.
I think Jae Seok will come here, too.
Really?
See? I told you.
(Jae Seok also joins Shin Hye's team.)
I told you.
Oh, it's Gary.
There's someone outside.
Is everyone here?
(Even Seok Jin joins.)
Wow, Haha.
Really?
- Welcome to my room.
- You danced until the end.
She's a bit weird.
She dances automatically when she hears music. She really does.
(They said the real queen danced until the end.)
- See?
- It's true.
That's plausible.
She really does.
(Haha believes that Sung Kyoung is the real queen.)
- You're right.
- She's the real one.
(While Team Sung Kyoung is having a fun time,)
(Ji Hyo's room is quiet.)
(Sighing)
What if no one comes?
(But there's a gleam of hope for Ji Hyo.)
(Oh, my Gyun Sang!)
Gosh, you're the best.
- I'll protect you.
- Gosh, you're so reliable.
Did you just hear that? He said he'll be with me.
(Gyun Sang is Ji Hyo's only team member.)
You're so reliable.
(New teams have been formed.)
(What will be the final mission?)
The final mission is "Protect the Queen".
"Protect the Queen"?
(Protect your queen's name tag.)
You must protect your queen's name tag...
to become the final winner.
Only queens are allowed to remove other queens' name tags.
If your queen's name tag is removed,
all the members in her team will be out as well.
However, if the winning queen isn't the real one,
all the male members will be flogged as a penalty.
But if the queen turns out to be the real one...
Gosh, it's driving me crazy.
The male members of the other two teams...
will be flogged as the penalty.
You'll find Betrayal Rooms within the building.
(Betrayal Room?)
(It's their last chance to change their minds.)
Inside the room,
there is the conclusive hint about the real queen.
If, during the race,
you start harbouring doubts about your queen,
you can go to the Betrayal Room and change your mind.
That's a possibility.
However, once you enter the room,
you must change your mind.
If your choice is wrong,
you'll be flogged double the original amount.
It's double?
(If their choice is not correct, they'll be flogged twice as much.)
(There are three Betrayal Rooms and each can be used once only.)
Why would you hit us?
(The race starts in 5 seconds.)
What do I do?
Five, four,
three, two, one. The race has begun.
- Let's go!
(Who is the real queen?)
Let's be cool and stay here.
- Let's make them betray each other.
- That's a good idea.
- You can stay here.
- I'll...
- hide here.
- I'll stay here.
Can I open this somehow?
(Let's look for the real queen!)
(The race starts now!)
Gyun Sang, I feel so safe around you.
Of course.
I'll guard you using my entire body.
(I will protect my queen!)
Shin Hye, you'll win for sure with us around.
There's five of us.
We'll be fine as long as you don't betray us.
I won't. I swear.
- Let's eliminate the guys.
- We should.
We're going to outnumber them and attack them at once, right?
Let's use our number to our advantage.
Where could they be?
- They must be hiding.
- I'm definitely sure about that.
(Eating)
(Team Sung Kyoung replenishes their energy while in hiding.)
Let's take a selfie.
(She's not ordinary for sure!)
(Let's not betray each other and remember this moment.)
- Are they not there?
- Shall we split in half?
Let's do that.
Jong Kook, go this way.
(They split in half for a more effective search.)
- The three of us, then?
- We can do that.
This is a perfect combination.
- If they...
- I'm sorry for saying this.
Would the three of you betray the rest of us?
- Oh, come on.
- Why would you say that?
Look at this guy.
- The three of you could do that.
- No way.
The three of you could each enter a Betrayal Room.
You can do that as soon as you find the rooms.
- That's nonsense.
- That'll put us at a disadvantage.
What are you talking about?
- Don't say that.
- Wait a minute.
Let's see what happens if you betray us.
- I won't.
- I'll rip the skin off your backs.
Watch me.
Jong Kook, let's put these two in separate groups.
Min Seok can go to this group. Stay with him.
- That's a good idea.
- I saw Seok Jin's face.
- I can't trust them.
- I know what you mean.
Wait. I have a bad feeling about this.
- Let's go, Jong Kook.
- All right.
- Hey.
- Get rid of the guys.
- Eliminate Gyun Sang immediately.
- Okay.
Ji Hyo is calling.
- Yes, Ji Hyo.
- Where are you?
I'm by the Gifted Education Centre.
I'll be there as soon as I can.
You have to stay alive.
It's this way. Come this way, Gary.
(They're nervous.)
- Can we do it on our own?
- We better bring the others.
- Can we do it?
- Let's bring them.
Hold on.
Seok Jin, come here. Come in.
- Come inside.
- Hurry up.
- Why?
- Don't go in.
There's only room for three. Betray your team and join us.
- She's the real one.
- I swear.
- I'm the queen.
- She is. Come inside.
- Are you the real queen?
- I told you I was the real one.
- She's being honest.
- Are you sure?
- You caught me.
- She's being serious.
There's room for three, so betray them.
(Is it Shin Hye or Sung Kyoung? That is the question.)
(What will Seok Jin do?)
- Team...
- Betrayers. Cross!
Isn't this too early in the game?
I can tell that she's real.
I'm being serious!
I think I was dancing until the end.
I was dancing until the music ended.
- She'll start moving once you clap.
- She's the real queen.
(Is this strong enough of an evidence?)
- I'm the real one.
- This is driving me nuts.
This is strange, but...
I feel better after looking at Sung Kyoung.
- Right?
- I don't know why.
- Go to the room.
- You won't regret it.
- There are only three rooms.
- This is the third floor, right?
- Text us.
- There are only three.
(Is Team Shin Hye swayed?)
Oh, gosh.
The real queen danced until the end.
(Is Sung Kyoung the last one to stop dancing?)
She fell into the water the most.
(Did she fall in the most?)
- She held hands with a male member?
- She did?
When did she do that?
(Is Sung Kyoung the one who held a male member's hand?)
(This moment of choice will change their destiny.)
(Will they decide to betray their team?)
I think we can talk them into entering the Betrayal Room.
They'll go in for sure.
- But we're done for if they see us.
- I agree.
(Is this the end for us?)
Gyun Sang, you should...
(Ji Hyo hesitates to speak.)
I should what?
(What's wrong, Ji Hyo?)
Move to...
another team...
before the Rooms get used up.
(Ji Hyo is being thoughtful because Gyun Sang is on his own.)
To tell you the truth,
I'm very happy that you came to me.
But I don't want you to die on your own.
(Ji Hyo plans to get a hint through Gyun Sang.)
She said she's the queen inside my heart.
(You're the only queen for me.)
Thank you. Thank you, Gyun Sang.
Don't say that.
I hope, like in the movies, she turns out to be the real one.
(Is Ji Hyo the real queen like Gyun Sang wished for?)
Let me turn this on.
(6 hours ago)
I knew it.
Ji Hyo, you're not the real queen.
(Ji Hyo is not the real queen!)
This is the Gifted Education Centre.
I thought it was this way.
Ji Hyo!
Ji Hyo is here. She's here.
- Hurry up.
- Is it just the two of you?
Ji Hyo, tell me this. Are you the real queen?
I'm not. I'm trying to help you.
(She tells the truth so that they can form an ally.)
- It's not me.
- That sounds so convincing.
- I'm trying to help you.
- She won't betray us.
Then let's have Gyun Sang visit the Betrayal Room.
(Gyun Sang heads to the Betrayal Room for the hint.)
You're my queen. Right, Ji Hyo?
(You're my queen.)
- Of course.
- I'll be back.
(Oh, goodness.)
Stop talking rubbish. Hurry up.
- Where is it, anyway?
- Hurry up.
- Where was it?
- Look for it.
(Will Gyun Sang earn the hint and return safely?)
(Striding)
I feel so bad.
(I'll do this for Ji Hyo.)
I feel like I'm betraying Ji Hyo.
(They search intently.)
(If he gets caught by Team Shin Hye, their plan will be over.)
They're not here either?
(Finally,)
(he finds the Betrayal Room!)
(There's a decisive hint in this room about the queen's identity.)
(Gyun Sang has no choice but to betray Ji Hyo now.)
I'm sorry, Ji Hyo.
(He changes his mind after Ji Hyo convinces him to do so.)
(My goodness!)
(What is the hint?)
Where are they?
There are so many of us, so they must be hiding.
They can't do anything by hiding.
- What's that?
- Somebody betrayed their team.
No way.
The Betrayal Room on the fourth floor is closed.
- The Betrayal Room on...
- I think it was the tall guy.
Let's go to the fourth floor.
Let's check it out.
(What is Gyun Sang's new guess?)
Let's go.
We have to eliminate them fast.
(The allies also head to the 4th floor.)
Gyun Sang.
(Oh, my! Is he wearing yellow?)
(He decides to be loyal to Queen Sung Kyoung.)
I saw the hint.
- Be quiet.
- I saw the decisive hint.
- I changed my shirt.
- You probably changed it before.
I saw the hint before I changed my shirt.
You change afterwards.
(He knows the hint?)
- I'm telling the truth.
- No way.
There are two rooms left. I'm telling the truth.
(He warns everybody else...)
(and runs for his life.)
(They feel conflicted again.)
Should we switch?
- Let's eliminate him first.
- That's the first step.
- Come on.
- I can't run because of my back.
I want to be able to help.
(Gyun Sang runs to find Queen Sung Kyoung.)
Where did he go?
- Come here!
- Where?
Ji Hyo.
Gary, Gyun Sang changed his shirt.
- Did you make him?
- Yes, I did.
- It doesn't matter if I die.
- I know.
- Let's eliminate her.
- It doesn't matter.
- You can kill me.
- The three of us?
- But be careful.
But I want to see what colour Gyun Sang is wearing.
- It's yellow.
- He's wearing yellow.
It's yellow, right? See?
(Ripping)
- That's fine.
- She's not it.
- Okay.
- You're all going to be flogged.
You'll all be flogged. You better run to the Betrayal Room.
(They're suddenly panicking.)
- Did you...
- We'll be flogged?
I told you already.
It's not Shin Hye. It's Sung Kyoung.
That's not true.
- This is...
- I don't care.
- It's not Ji Hyo, right?
- Gyun Sang...
- had the hint for sure.
- Right?
- Is that right?
- He chose based on the hint.
What hint?
- Does he still have it?
- There was a hint...
- in the Betrayal Room.
- Of course, there is.
Let's go.
- Shin Hye, say something.
- No, it's not.
It's not that. That's not it.
Did you see that? I told you. I told you things will become chaotic.
Gyun Sang holds an important key.
(What does she mean?)
(Strolling)
Are you not well? Why are you walking so slowly?
My back hurts, so I will walk slowly.
Please guard Shin Hye well.
- My gosh.
- My back really hurts.
- Really?
- I kept shouting a while ago.
(She's nervous.)
There are only two rooms left.
(The crack in the team is getting bigger and bigger.)
(Jae Seok, who trusts Shin Hye, searches the 5th floor.)
They are here. They're here.
(Team Sung Kyoung appears!)
(They finally get the chance to make a roundup.)
Come down. Everyone, hurry up and come down.
We have to go down.
Go down?
My back hurts.
Good, good. The vibe is good now.
All right. Let's just make one more person our team.
(Team Shin Hye starts the arrest operation.)
We can meet them.
- We can meet them.
- It's Shin Hye.
- You left. Min Seok, look.
- Shin Hye, wait.
- The hint is "Crazy".
- No.
(Was that the hint Gyun Sang read?)
Go to the Betrayal Room.
There are two rooms left.
Why do you think he didn't go to the team with more people?
- It's because...
- There are two left.
- The hint is "Crazy".
- Ji Hyo sent them to us on purpose.
If we win, you will live.
- Living is more important.
- Think about it.
(If the hint is really "Crazy",)
(Sung Kyoung is certainly the queen.)
Hey.
Gyun Sang, you betrayer.
- That's not it.
- Jong Kook.
- Jong Kook, join us.
- Hurry up.
(It's your choice to receive the flogging or not.)
- Hurry. You don't have time.
- Just join us.
- Jong Kook!
What floor was it, Gyun Sang?
- What floor was it? The 4th floor?
- The 4th floor.
- Then...
- But it took us three seconds.
come down to the second floor. Hurry.
- Hey!
- Okay.
(Yes!)
What? What's going on? What is he doing?
- Run! Ride the elevator!
- What's this?
What's wrong?
(They rush to the Betrayal Room.)
- Hurry up.
- Go to the second floor.
- Catch Jong Kook.
- Where was it? There it is.
(But they are too late.)
- Hey!
- I'm in.
I'm good.
(He's ready to betray!)
When we come together, we can catch him.
As soon as he comes out, we must eliminate him.
Someone could've gone to the third floor.
(And that would be Gary.)
What's this?
(Seok Jin already entered the room on the 3rd floor.)
(When it comes to betrayal, Seok Jin is better.)
Whoever comes first gets to take the room.
(The last Betrayal Room goes to Seok Jin.)
I'm done.
(Seok Jin takes the last Room.)
(Gary is sad.)
(Gyun Sang, Jong Kook and Seok Jin betray their teams.)
(The Betrayal Rooms are sold out!)
- What is it?
- You go first.
You're alone. Wait. What's this?
- Come here.
- This is the time.
Catch Min Seok!
- Hey!
- Catch Min Seok!
- Shin Hye!
(The lone chick becomes a good target.)
(His name tag is ripped.)
- We did it. Catch Jae Seok!
- We did it.
Catch Jae Seok!
(It's chaos.)
Min Seok is out. Min Seok is out.
He's our team.
(He can't believe it.)
We got tricked by Jong Kook.
In any case, betray me and...
Trust us.
I will rip the skin off your backs.
Watch me.
I am so angry!
Kim Jong Kook.
(He gets betrayed by the one he trusted.)
(I've been waiting for you to come out of this room.)
Gary, this isn't right.
I can't help it either. I have to survive.
Wait a minute!
(While Gary can't run, Seok Jin sprints.)
Seok Jin! Seok Jin! Come down!
- Come on.
- Come on down.
Hurry up and come down!
(Jong Kook joins Team Sung Kyoung, too!)
High-five!
(Welcome to the team!)
(Jong Kook is the VIP member!)
Kim Jong Kook! Kim Jong Kook!
You've been waiting to change teams.
- You've been waiting.
- That's right.
- You've waited.
- We did it.
(What was the hint that Jong Kook and Seok Jin saw?)
"Crazy".
(Gyun Sang was telling the truth.)
It's right.
(If the hint is "Crazy",)
(the queen is Sung Kyoung for sure.)
(In the preliminary meeting, she picked a rose.)
Sung Kyoung, you are the real queen.
(All right!)
(Sung Kyoung is the real queen!)
They have more people. Why take more people?
Jong Kook ran down.
I am sorry, Jae Seok.
I am sorry, Jae Seok. I am not the real queen.
- You're not?
(You are not the real queen?)
I wanted to win the game.
Honestly, when I went to the Room, Seok Jin was already there.
I was a little late.
When I saw your face, you didn't look so confident.
Honestly, Shin Hye,
- I've been looking for loopholes.
- I know it.
- Jae Seok, we can...
- I wanted to win fast.
(They have only one option.)
We have to rip Sung Kyoung's name tag.
That's better even if we get flogged.
- Let's go.
- You have to rip her name tag.
- I will.
- We will wrap it up.
- Okay.
I can hear something.
The only thing that team can do is eliminate Sung Kyoung.
So we have to guard her well.
(They will guard Sung Kyoung with all their strength.)
(Only the queens are allowed to rip each other's name tags.)
- There!
- Where?
Hey, be careful!
Where?
(The final battle begins.)
(They're surprised by the army of members.)
Why are they so bold?
- What gave you the courage?
- They're out of their wits.
That's right.
You must've thought very easily of me.
No. No.
I'm so scared.
Come on.
- She's strong. She's strong.
- Shin Hye.
(We just have to protect Sung Kyoung.)
- She's strong.
(Team Sung Kyoung is confident.)
- You...
- You can't rip her name tag anyway.
Grab her!
(They grab Sung Kyoung!)
(They wait for the right timing and launch an attack!)
(What will happen?)
(Ripping)
(Has someone's name tag been ripped?)
You have to rip it!
(Sung Kyoung is on the floor. Is she out?)
(Queen Sung Kyoung is alive!)
- We got it. Jae Seok is out.
- That was close.
I'm out.
(Jae Seok is out.)
Grab her!
- No! No!
- Come on!
(Ripping)
(Even Jae Seok's last attempt was in vain.)
(Queen Shin Hye is in trouble.)
Be careful. You have to survive.
(She launches another attack!)
(It's Shin Hye versus Sung Kyoung.)
(Only the queens can rip each other's name tags.)
Shin Hye, please.
(Gary can't fight any longer.)
- Time to go.
- He's ripped.
No. Come on.
- Sung Kyoung.
- We have no choice.
- We have to do this, Shin Hye.
- You can do it.
(Jong Kook and Seok Jin join.)
Shin Hye, I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
(Shin Hye is out.)
Sorry, Shin Hye!
(Team Sung Kyoung wins.)
("Protect the Queen" is over.)
Sung Kyoung managed to survive until the end. Please go up to the podium.
(Sung Kyoung was the real queen.)
She was the real queen!
It was her!
How is it, Min Seok? Ready to be flogged?
- There it is!
- What's that?
Inside her shoe, it says "Real Queen".
(The identity of the real queen was written inside the shoe.)
The true queen, Sung Kyoung, will receive this diamond tiara.
(She receives a diamond tiara.)
- It's beautiful.
- Wear it over your hat.
(The ones who chose Sung Kyoung will be exempt from the penalty.)
Now, it's time to get flogged.
It's time.
(The time has come.)
(It's flogging time!)
- I love you.
- He turned it sideways.
You have to hit lower.
Oh, here?
(Ouch!)
(What a strong swing!)
My goodness.
- That looked painful.
- You held on. Good job.
That really hurt.
- I'll start.
- Okay.
Poor you.
Stop rubbing it.
You've made a wrong decision.
Poor you.
I'm sorry, Jae Seok.
- You've made a wrong decision.
- I'm fine, Shin Hye.
Poor you.
(Slap)
(The power from the hit makes him stand up.)
- That was strong.
- It really hurts.
(He can feel the pain rising from his bottom.)
Don't rub with your hands.
I suddenly feel competitive about this.
What?
I just don't want to lose.
I just don't want to feel defeated.
(He swings far.)
- My goodness.
- I just don't...
- want to lose.
- All right. How about...
after saying goodbye, you flog him immediately?
All right. Let Kwang Soo's swing be the finisher.
(What?)
Does that mean I can't say goodbye?
(Everyone agrees to end the day with Kwang Soo's swing.)
All right, queens.
How was it today? Your drama will be aired soon, too.
Yes, our new drama "Doctors" will air tomorrow evening.
We hope you love our new drama.
(While the queens say goodbye,)
(Kwang Soo warms up.)
(Gary can only laugh.)
I became the real queen today...
and also won the race.
(He practises swinging.)
I'd like to come on this show again.
(Now's the time!)
He's...
(Jae Seok flogs him.)
Okay. We're done for today.
(A flogging for a flogging.)
(We'd like to thank all our guests for joining us today.)
- Well done!
- Thank you!
(The strongest enemies have appeared in front of Running Man.)
(Lee Kyung Kyu and the Avengers)
(They compete for the throne.)
(This will be a completely different type of variety show.)
("Running Rumble", a survival game, is coming soon.)
(Name Tag Elimination with never-ending twists)
(Who will be the last one standing?)
It was really fun. I'll be going now.
(Running Man vs Avengers)