(At a cafe near Hongik University)
(A cup of warm coffee is waiting...)
(for today's guest.)
Hello.
(Who is this mysterious woman?)
- Hello.
-  Hello.
(She still looks so young and beautiful just like before.)
(Kim Hee Ae)
- Nice to meet you.
-  Hello.
It's an honour. Please sit.
(Why are they meeting up in secret?)
There's a reason why we called you before the filming starts.
- Please, don't get nervous.
-  I'm nervous already.
This week's special is...
Invigorating Foods for this hot summer.
You will be doing a race as a team.
But...
we will assign a special mission just for you.
I'm getting nervous now.
We will assign you as a special agent for today.
You'll be doing a hidden mission alone in secret.
(Special agent? Hidden mission?)
If you complete the hidden mission as the special agent,
you will get not only invigorating foods from today's race,
but you will also get the winning prize.
Oh. What is the prize?
(She's glad to hear that.)
The prize is a golden badge...
which is specially designed for the agent.
(A handmade golden badge just for the special agent)
(She wouldn't want to miss it.)
I see. It must be quite expensive.
Yes. You can win that badge along with other prizes.
- I'll tell you what the mission is.
-  Okay.
The mission is called "Second to Last".
(The hidden mission is "Second to Last")
- "Second to Last"?
-  That's right.
Let me explain.
(The name is similar to her upcoming drama.)
Let me explain the details.
Every member will draw a number each.
There are nine members in total today.
The 2nd to last number is number 8, right?
You need to make a person with number 8, the 2nd place.
You don't want to give me the gold, do you?
Can't it be easier?
- I'll continue.
-  Okay.
There will be one more special agent.
(Another special agent?)
There are two special agents including you.
Who is that?
(The other special agent will be her supporter. Who will that be?)
There are two special agents including you.
Your mission is to make the 2nd to last number be in 2nd.
You need to make a person with number 8 take the 2nd place.
(Help 2nd to last person come in 2nd place.)
(Who will hunt for the golden badge with her today?)
(The members come to have doubts toward the special agents.)
(If the agent fails a mission, a hint will be given...)
(to reveal the agent's identity.)
(Will the second to last person...)
(be able to take the second place?)
(30 minutes later, the members are gathering.)
(Kwang Soo is the first one to arrive.)
Hello. Good morning.
- Hello.
-  Please pick a number.
(Kwang Soo does it without realising what it's for.)
Oh, no.
I'm usually the unluckiest one.
It's six.
(Kwang Soo drew number six.)
Please go inside.
Okay.
What is this about?
(Kwang Soo enters the cafe with the number card.)
Hello, everyone.
I must be the first one to arrive.
- What number is it?
-  I drew number six.
- I see.
-  So it's about making a team.
(Next member to draw a number is Jae Seok.)
What's all this?
(What number would it be?)
Hello.
(Jae Seok picked number one.)
Please go inside through the entrance over there.
- Hello, Jae Seok.
-  Kwang Soo.
Hello.
- Hello.
-  What's your number?
- Number one.
-  Really?
Yes, number one.
I get nervous without Jae Seok on my team.
Finally, the two unlucky members are in different teams.
I know. I'm number six.
Seriously.
I feel like this is really important.
(What number would it be?)
It's number eight.
(Haha drew number eight.)
(If so, would Haha be the person?)
The 2nd to the last number is number 8.
You should make number 8's team take the 2nd place.
It's eight.
I have a bad feeling about this.
Why are you in the centre?
There's nothing I can do about it.
You dressed like a gang member at a vacation spot.
(It looks like he's about to provoke a fight with a couple at beach.)
Stop making fun of me with my style.
Look how big your pupils are.
My goodness.
- You don't understand fashion.
-  Your pupils...
Your pupils are too big.
- This is the trend right now.
-  Your pupils...
Look how black your pupils are. Are you wearing contacts?
- Hello.
-  Oh, it's Jong Kook.
- Your number.
-  What's your number?
- Is it okay to open this?
-  Sure.
- Of course you can.
-  Jong Kook.
My number is five.
(Kwang Soo and Jong Kook are both in Yellow Team.)
Yes! I knew it.
- Each team has different colours.
-  What?
- Yes.
-  Right?
- Seok Jin is here.
-  Welcome.
- What's your number?
-  It's four.
It's four.
- Why?
-  What a team!
-  What's wrong with it today?
- We are a team.
-  What's wrong?
- Numbers 4, 5 and 6 are a team.
-  We never had this combination.
So numbers 4, 5 and 6 are a team.
- Welcome, Gary.
-  You are here.
- My number is two.
-  Yes.
(Come and greet the lady.)
- Gosh.
-  He's destined to serve.
He was trying to put it in a nice way.
Gary is there to serve his lady.
- Oh, Gary.
-  Gary is there to serve his lady.
- Gary.
-  Behave like a butler today.
(And the lady enters.)
- It's Ji Hyo.
-  She's here.
- You must be 7 or 9.
-  I'm 6.
- Did you say 6?
-  No, you must be 9.
- You are nine.
-  What are you talking about?
- What? It's 6.
-  It's 6.
- I told you it's six.
-  You were the one who got it wrong.
- Seriously.
-  My goodness.
Goodness, Kwang Soo.
What were you doing?
- Now, we have the best butler.
-  So this is my role today.
The best butler in the world.
All of a sudden, I feel so uncomfortable.
- I don't want this number.
-  Are we a team?
Suddenly, Jong Kook is on pins and needles.
Now, we have a strong butler.
- He's also a butler now.
-  Gosh, I don't like that.
(Jong Kook, welcome. You are now another butler.)
He has to serve his lady, too.
(All the members have arrived. Who will fill the remaining spots?)
(It's been a while since we invited this handsome middle-aged man.)
Long time no see.
(Ji Jin Hee)
Your jacket is torn apart.
(He ran spraying duck feathers to win the game four years ago.)
Look at this. He's the best.
(An actor with full of passion, Ji Jin Hee)
Can I open this?
(What number would he pick?)
It's lucky seven.
(Jin Hee drew number seven.)
- It's Ji Jin Hee.
-  Welcome.
(Welcome back, Jin Hee.)
- Welcome!
-  We have Jin Hee today.
- What's your number?
-  It's seven.
- Good.
-  I'm scared.
Jin Hee, you are more than welcome to shove them around.
(He has two butlers to shove around.)
- Oh, my.
-  The best butlers.
I saw him at the parking lot a while ago.
So what?
(He's going competitive already.)
- He was very nice to me then.
-  I see.
And he went, "So what?"
Someone's here.
- It's a nice car.
-  We want a lady.
(The last spot is for the lady.)
(She had the secret meeting with the producer beforehand.)
Hello.
(The special actress is here as the special agent for today.)
(Special Agent H, Kim Hee Ae)
- She's here.
-  Hee Ae.
- She's the queen.
-  Oh, my.
(Please fall for my lies.)
She's the queen from Hyehwadong.
- Welcome.
-  Your number must be three.
- Yes.
-  Come this way.
- Number three.
-  This way.
- Oh, my.
-  It's an honour.
- It's an honour.
-  Please stand here.
She's the queen of Hyehwa High School.
I know about it very well.
Hello.
You went to Hyewha and Jeon In Hwa went to Soongeui High School, right?
(He's bringing up the old times.)
My sister graduated Hyehwa High School.
All right.
(She forces to end the topic.)
- Okay, I'll stop talking now.
-  Let's just shoot the show.
She doesn't like it when you try to buddy up with her.
(We need some time to get familiar.)
Today, Kim Hee Ae and Ji Jin Hee are here as guests.
- They're shooting a drama together.
-  Yes.
The drama "Second to Last Love" will be broadcast soon.
- I see.
-  So we prepared a special race.
You'll be able to obtain various kinds of invigorating food...
to help you get through the hot summer.
It's a race called Invigorating Foods.
Invigorating Foods.
- Invigorating Foods.
-  That's right.
Now, you have a team according to the number you drew.
You are going to play various games we prepared.
We have prepared various invigorating food here.
You'll be able to get them through completing missions.
- What are the prizes?
-  Can we see it now?
(Collection of invigorating food from everywhere)
(From red ginseng to fresh fruits and beef)
- Oh, it's fresh ginseng.
-  Look at the fruits.
- It's Korean beef gift set.
-  We don't usually buy them,
but I just want to take it when I see them here.
- Really.
-  It's true.
- Look at the beef gift set.
-  It's like I can't live without it.
Who brought Chinese bush-clover?
I'm the one who needs it.
- Chinese bush-clover.
-  Chinese bush-clover.
- This is great.
-  Look at that yellow corvinas set.
- Yellow corvinas are the best.
-  I want the Korean beef gift set.
(While everyone is focusing on the prizes...)
The 2nd to last number is number 8, right?
You need to make a person with number 8, the 2nd place.
(She needs to make Blue Team be in second.)
(Is the other special agent ready?)
(Possible candidates)
(One of them is her supporter.)
(I'm ready.)
(Jae Seok or Gary may be the other special agent.)
(Who would be the one to help Hee Ae?)
It's good to be outside.
How old is Seok Jin?
He's 51 years old.
(He's quite old.)
Why are you surprised?
I told the staff that I'd be so embarrassed...
if I don't understand the rules quickly.
They said Seok Jin still doesn't get it after doing it for seven years.
- Is that right?
-  That's right.
(Hee Ae is relieved to have Seok Jin.)
Seok Jin doesn't understand the rules.
I'll be the same.
(Hee Ae feels so familiar to Seok Jin.)
- By the way...
-  I was so glad to hear that.
What are we doing today?
I have no idea.
(He has no clue like always.)
We are here. Is this the right place?
(What would be the first mission to win invigorating food?)
(Microphones are placed in the middle.)
- No one's here yet.
-  What's all this?
- Why aren't they here?
-  Something's strange.
You look young all of a sudden.
Don't say that. She lives young.
(She didn't change a bit from the old days.)
This is her favourite pose.
She speaks very elegantly. Okay.
(Gary transforms into an armrest for her.)
I'd be happy to support your arm.
She's the elegant lady.
She speaks very elegantly.
(The elegant lady)
Jin Hee, I'm begging you.
Would you please stop looking at us with suspicion?
- I was so surprised.
-  He always does that.
- No, he doesn't.
-  He does that every time.
He does not have desire to win.
- Are you serious?
-  Yes.
Don't you remember? He didn't even notice his torn jacket last time.
I hope everything would go fine today.
- He's continuously looking around.
-  He's a pacifist.
It's time for the first mission.
- Jin Hee, please read this.
-  Okay.
(Jin Hee will read the rules for them.)
(What? You don't have to go through there.)
- Goodness.
-  You can come this way.
- There's enough space here.
-  Why did you have to...
I hesitated for a second.
That was weird.
There's nothing to hesitate about.
You get suspicious on everything.
He really doubts about every single thing.
I worried that I'd be off the angle.
He was worried he'd be off the angle.
He did it in order to stay in the camera angle.
This mission is "Guess the Song."
Members must tie their legs to each other.
- And...
-  Gosh.
After listening to a prelude of a song,
you'd come out and guess its title after naming your team.
You get one point if you guess the singer and the title right.
If you guess it wrong, you will receive punishment.
(Hee Ae has to make Blue Team take the second place.)
Put your legs in there.
- All right.
-  We got it.
You'll play three rounds of this game.
- Let's go!
-  Let's do this!
- Go!
-  We can do this!
The first round is about songs from the 2000s.
- From the 2000s.
-  Good.
It's when "Cyber Lover" by Turbo was released.
(What's Agent Hee Ae's special plan to make Haha place second?)
(What's the first song that was popular in 2000?)
Let's go.
(He senses something.)
(Already?)
(Blue Team gets to the answer zone first.)
In 3, 2 and 1.
It's by Davichi.
- "Love and War".
-  "8282".
("Love and War", "8282")
What was it?
- Please move out of the zone.
-  Move.
(They fail as two different answers were given and one didn't answer.)
Why didn't he say anything?
In 3, 2 and 1.
- It's "Love and War" by Davichi.
-  It's "Love and War" by Davichi.
It's wrong.
Move out.
- Hurry and move out.
-  Move out.
Here comes a Korean pop encyclopaedia.
- In 3, 2 and 1.
-  It's "8282" by Davichi.
(He mumbles.)
He didn't say it.
- Only two of them answered.
-  No way.
- Didn't you see it?
-  It's not "8282".
- Hurry up.
-  Isn't it "8282"?
(Be quiet.)
(Many of them complain at the same time.)
- "8282" is correct.
-  Just a second.
Gosh, it's so noisy.
It's "8282".
They didn't succeed because...
- Gary doesn't know this song.
-  Of course I do.
- See? You don't know.
-  Baby, baby.
Let's play together today.
(When did Davichi sing that song?)
- What on earth?
-  He doesn't know the song.
- Come on.
-  They didn't get it right.
(These are the original lyrics to the song.)
- Do you know the song, Jin Hee?
-  He does.
Try singing it, Jin Hee.
(He gets flustered.)
(He tries to sing it.)
What are you singing?
- This is nonsense.
-  I can sing it.
- Does Hee Ae know the song?
-  Of course she does.
- Do you know this song?
-  You don't have to know it exactly.
- Baby, baby
-  Baby, baby.
(She sings it most elegantly.)
- That's the easiest part.
-  Come on.
It's not a round.
- Hee Ae always sings that way.
-  She's always beautiful.
Since there's too much arguing...
- Why?
-  Come on.
- Their answer is invalid.
-  It's invalid.
Their answer doesn't count.
- Let's move on to next question.
-  Why doesn't it count?
(Pink Team's answer doesn't count.)
- Good job.
-  You're the fair judge.
Now,
I'll give you the next song during the 2000s for the round 1.
(Here's the second song from the 2000s.)
- What is it?
-  Let's go.
- 1, 2, 1, 2.
-  1, 2, 1, 2.
(Blue Team runs to the microphones.)
- What's the answer?
-  Get ready to answer.
In 3, 2 and 1.
- It's by Ivy.
-  It's by Ivy.
Goodness.
(Why did they look so sure when they didn't know?)
- What was that?
-  Did they even know the answer?
- It's a song by Ivy.
-  Go slowly.
Let's listen to the song more.
Play the song a little more.
The song stops when a team comes forward.
- Of course.
-  It should stop.
That's right.
All right. In 3, 2 and 1.
Do we just have to get the title right?
- In 3, 2 and 1.
-  In 3, 2 and 1.
- "Sonata of Temptation" by Ivy.
-  "Sonata of Temptation" by Ivy.
- Hee Ae didn't move her lips.
-  Yes, she did.
- She didn't.
-  She did.
(The answer is "Sonata of Temptation" by Ivy.)
- It was Ivy's song.
-  Somebody do it.
- Didn't she dance like this?
-  That's right.
This was the dance.
(The song is from her 2nd album released in 2007.)
(It became popular due to its unique dance choreography.)
Did the dance go like this?
(Hee Ae makes Ivy's song popular again in 2016.)
She knows how to have fun.
Why are you dancing like a robot?
There she goes.
Isn't this someone else's dance?
(Let's go.)
(Sonata of an excited robot)
She's full of fun.
We did it.
- Here's the next song.
-  Okay.
(Here's another song from the 2000s.)
I've never heard of it before.
(Which song starts with a cyber-like sound?)
(Are they planning to just go for it again?)
- I know the answer.
-  "Two of Us" by Chae Yeon.
(Does "Two of Us" by Chae Yeon really start like this?)
- I know the answer.
-  "Two of Us" by Chae Yeon.
(The answer is "Two of Us" by Chae Yeon.)
(Blue Team is correct.)
I knew this song.
("Two of Us" by Chae Yeon is from her 2nd album in 2004.)
- Stop it.
-  I knew this song.
(He does a happy ceremony with the dance.)
You don't know this song, Jin Hee.
(He strongly protests.)
- Dance to the song.
-  Jin Hee doesn't know.
(He suddenly becomes a dancing machine.)
Come on, Jin Hee.
- See?
-  He doesn't know it.
- You don't know the song.
-  Yes, I do.
- This isn't the dance.
-  The dance goes like this.
What you did is something else.
This is what you did.
- Wasn't this the dance?
-  No.
You did well.
I watched this music video over 3000 times while serving the army.
I only heard of Honey Family's songs while serving the army.
That's cool.
Over there.
From afar.
- Don't do it.
-  I believe.
We can... Stop it.
- Is the next song from the 2000s?
-  Yes.
(The next song is another one from the 2000s.)
- Hee Ae.
-  Hurry.
(They sense what it is.)
How do you know from the sound of a bomb?
- In 3, 2 and 1.
-  "Turn Back" by Kim Hyun Jung.
(The answer is "Turn Back" by Kim Hyun Jung.)
It's not correct.
(She gets a blow of air.)
- That was incorrect.
-  I'm sorry.
Hey, you.
Move.
Goodness.
Did you hear what Hee Ae said?
She said, "Hey, you."
How could you make it blow out air?
- Let's go.
-  "Bruise" by Kim Hyun Jung.
Right. It was "Bruise".
(Is the song "Bruise" by Kim Hyun Jung?)
- Yes.
-  It's "Bruise".
That was the title.
I got confused about the song title.
Does the dance go like this?
("Bruise" by Kim Hyun Jung is from her 3rd album released in 2000.)
(It's the most famous hit song by Kim Hyun Jung.)
- Turn everything back
-  Turn everything back.
- To the way things were before
-  They're trying to spin.
Turn it back.
(Turn things back to the way things were.)
(Hey, hey!)
You seem excited.
I went clubbing a lot when this song came out.
In 1, 2, 3 and 4.
(Let's go, kids.)
Turn everything back.
(The song stops.)
- I'll stop it now.
-  Please do.
Here comes the next song.
- I said the wrong title.
-  That was good.
- Let's go.
-  Come on.
- Hurry up.
-  It's one of my favourite songs.
In 3, 2 and 1.
Will I be able to see you again.
All right.
(He whispers.)
- Let's listen to the song first.
-  In 3, 2 and 1.
- "Poisoned Love" by Cho Jang Hyuck.
-  "Poisoned Love" by Cho Jang Hyuck.
("Poisoned Love" by Cho Jang Hyuck is correct.)
Jin Hee doesn't know this song.
Yes, I do.
The other teams also knew what it was.
I forgot the title of the song.
- I didn't know the exact title.
-  It's Kwang Soo's favourite song.
- Kwang Soo likes the song.
-  It's my favourite song.
(He gets emotionally into it.)
Will I be able to see you again.
Why did you stop the song already?
- Don't sing.
-  Why did you stop it already?
- Move away.
-  I was just getting into it.
How can I release my emotions otherwise?
Did you forget?
It seems like...
it's a competition between me and Kwang Soo.
- Is the score 1 to 1 to 2?
-  Yes.
Here's the next song.
- I know this.
-  Do you know the song?
Please get ready.
- I know the answer.
-  I know the answer.
(Do they already know the answer?)
- Move over, please.
-  I know the answer.
- Just say anything.
-  In 3, 2 and 1.
- "Have a Drink" by Zia.
-  "Have a Drink" by Zia.
(It's incorrect.)
I was so certain.
- I'm sorry about that.
-  I can't believe it.
- Please go back to your seats.
-  I can't remember song titles.
- Isn't that it?
-  Go back to your seats.
Goodness.
- Let's go.
-  What's the title?
Isn't it by Baek Z Young?
- They wouldn't know the answer.
-  In 3, 2 and 1.
- "I Won't Love" by Baek Z Young.
-  "I Won't Love" by Baek Z Young.
(The answer is "I Won't Love" by Baek Z Young.)
- Wow, we got it right.
-  Yes!
- That was the song.
-  We got it.
Wow, it's a miracle.
I won't love any more.
- Ji Hyo.
-  The person like you.
Don't lie.
(She's lying about not loving again.)
You shouldn't say that, Ji Hyo.
- She's full of love.
-  She really is.
Here's the next song.
- Let's go.
-  Let's go.
-  It's by Rain.
(It's definitely a song by Rain.)
It's by Rain.
- Say it together after the count.
-  In 3, 2 and 1.
- It's by Rain.
-  "I Am Rain".
("I Am Rain" by Rain)
(It's completely wrong.)
In 3, 2 and 1.
- "It's Raining" by Rain.
-  "It's Raining" by Rain.
(The answer is "It's Raining" by Rain.)
That's right.
- What's wrong with you?
-  You're good.
Jung Ji Hoon, Jung Ji Hoon!
("It's Raining" by Rain is from his 3rd album released in 2004.)
(It's popular for his dance with a slurping sound.)
(Let's do the slurp.)
That's right.
Seok Jin, be careful not to break your ribs.
(He warns him out of concern.)
That was good.
- Seok Jin's so funny.
-  The current score...
is 3 to 1 to 2.
Is that the score?
The team to score five points first wins.
Let's go.
- Here's a hint as I'm Hee Ae's fan.
-  Gosh, it's going crazy.
- This is...
-  Hurry up and go.
- Hurry up and go.
-  Go.
(What makes Gary get up to answer?)
Doesn't Gary know this song?
- This is Gary's specialty.
-  Really?
(Will Pink Team answer it right?)
In 3, 2 and 1.
- Brown Eyes' "Don't Go, Don't Go".
-  That's right.
- What did you just say?
-  That's right?
("That's Right, That's Right" by Brown Eyes?)
- What was that?
-  Wait.
- No. Wait.
-  We don't have to say all together.
- It's okay if one of us answers.
-  What was that?
- He just agreed on my answer.
-  Yes, I did.
In 3, 2 and 1.
- Brown Eyes' "Don't Go, Don't Go".
-  Brown Eyes' "Don't Go, Don't Go".
- It's not fair.
-  Stop it.
- She just pretended to say it.
(Why does Gary know about this song?)
I listened to it more than 10,000 times to write its lyrics.
(Gary wrote the lyrics for the song, "Don't Go, Don't Go".)
- It's hard to sing the high note.
-  Yet, I.
(Gary is an emotional songwriter to write the sentimental lyrics.)
(Kwang Soo is into the song, too.)
(Thanks to Gary's hard work, Pink Team gets one point.)
Now, the score is 3 to 2 to 2.
- It's 3 to 2 to 2.
-  It's really hard.
Here comes the next question.
Ballad songs usually start like this.
- I know this song.
-  Hurry.
(She knows this song.)
What? What is the answer?
All right. Tell us the answer.
You need to tell us the answer now.
- In one...
-  You can speak out the answer.
- You should.
-  In 1, 2 and 3.
(I know the answer and I won't miss it.)
- It's "Sad Fate" by Nami.
-  It's "Sad Fate" by Nami.
(The answer is "Sad Fate" by Nami.)
(The answer isn't "Sad Fate" by Nami.)
(It's the air again.)
- It can be the remake version.
-  Yes, It can be.
- It's from 80s, isn't it?
-  It's okay.
I thought it was the answer.
That song is really old.
It could've been remade in the 2000s.
(It could've been remade in the 2000s.)
(What is this mysterious song with piano?)
- I think I heard this before.
-  What is this?
There are many songs which begin like this.
(They are all waiting to hear the first lyrics.)
- What are you doing?
-  I only need the first part.
(You fill my heart.)
(They all noticed the song right after hearing the first lyrics.)
Please tell us the answer. All right.
In 3, 2 and 1.
- It's "One Love" by Park Sang Min.
-  It's "One Love" by...
- That's wrong.
-  They got it wrong.
- It's "One Love".
-  That's right.
(The answer is "One Love" by Park Sang Min.)
I almost forgot the title.
("One Love" is from his 5th album released in 2000.)
(It was popular especially to boys at that time.)
(Seok Jin is confused with the lyrics.)
(The score is 4 to 2 to 2.)
This song is a masterpiece.
Let's move on to the next song.
(This can be the last song of the first round.)
- Wait.
-  This kind of intro is common.
- Hurry.
-  Let's go.
(They all sensed the rhythm.)
- In 3, 2 and 1.
-  They have to guess right away.
- Wait a second.
-  It's by Baby V.O.X.
- That's wrong.
-  They got it wrong.
(They guessed it wrong.)
(It's not by Baby V.O.X.)
- What was that?
-  Move over.
- Wait. What is it?
-  All right. In 3, 2 and 1.
- "Baby, One More Time" by Jewelry.
-  "Baby, One More Time" by Jewelry.
(It's wrong.)
- "One More Time" by Jewelry.
-  "One More Time" by Jewelry.
("One More Time" by Jewelry is the correct answer.)
What was that? "Baby, One More Time"?
It's "One More Time".
(Oh my baby)
This is their dance, right?
("One More Time" is from their 5th album released in 2008.)
(It's popular for the rhythmic and unique dance.)
- Very good.
-  For the first round,
- Yellow Team wins.
-  Yes!
(Yellow Team gets three points.)
Let's start the second round right away.
The 2nd round is about songs from 1990s.
- Good.
-  Songs from 1990s?
Turbo was playing in the scene during 1990s.
(The second round of "Guess the Song" begins.)
(They sense it right away.)
(Dragged)
We were faster. I grabbed it first.
(They're trying so hard not to lose the microphones.)
- It's so obvious.
-  You should know it.
(Whispering)
All right. In 3, 2 and 1.
It's "You Do Not Answer" by Kim Jong Seo.
- That's right.
-  To whom should I lean on.
(Their answer is correct.)
("You Do Not Answer" is from his 1st album released in 1992.)
(To whom should I share my hurt feelings now?)
(Being highly emotional)
(She's also into the song.)
Do you know this song?
(Thumbs up!)
I want to say.
That I am so hurt.
(This is the feeling that I've been waiting for!)
That's right!
We all memorise its lyrics.
- It's from early 90s.
-  It's so much easier.
- It's going to be easy.
-  The music is on.
(What would be the second song?)
(A siren is wailing.)
- Come out.
-  Let's go.
(They hurry to the microphones after hearing the mysterious siren.)
- Let's go.
-  I know this.
- In 3, 2 and 1.
-  Wait. Give us a few seconds.
What?
- In 3, 2 and 1.
-  Gosh.
Wait.
- Give us another chance.
-  No, please go back.
Move over.
- Just give us another chance.
-  Hurry. Move over.
- Move.
-  That's so cruel of you.
Move.
- You invited me here.
-  I mean...
- I'm trying my best here.
-  Look at her hair.
We didn't mean that.
- Are you ready?
-  All right.
In 3, 2 and 1.
It's "Change" by Lee Jung Hyun.
(The answer is "Change" by Lee Jung Hyun.)
(Is it "Change" by Lee Jung Hyun?)
- "Change"?
-  Yes.
(Blue Team got it right.)
(He imitates the famous moves of the song.)
("Change" is from her 1st album released in 1999.)
(The country became crazy about techno because of her song.)
(Blue Team dances to celebrate.)
(Hesitating)
(Do I need to dance again?)
Jin Hee doesn't know this song.
- What are you doing?
-  Come on.
Just do it.
Just once.
(He's starting to dance.)
Why do you keep your hands like that?
That's not right. Make it like this.
- Pretend the microphone is here.
-  Does he want something else?
Does he think it's boring?
- Blue Team got one point.
-  It's crazy.
(The score is 0 to 1 to 1.)
(What is this song?)
- I heard this before.
-  Me, too.
- Go.
-  Let's go.
Hurry.
(Two teams head towards the microphones.)
- Hurry.
-  Let's go.
(Yellow Team arrives earlier.)
- You're not in the line.
-  You went out of the line.
It's "Love is a Cold Temptation", but was the singer Bang Mi?
(Was the singer Bang Mi?)
(That's wrong.)
- Don't count that one.
-  I didn't answer it.
- I talked to myself.
-  He was just talking to himself.
- Why? What's wrong?
-  It's our turn. Move.
- All right.
-  Please guess the answer.
(It's Pink Team's turn now.)
In 1, 2 and 3.
It's "Love is a Cold Temptation" by Yang Soo Kyung.
It's not right.
(They got it right.)
- Really?
-  Wasn't the singer Min Hye Kyung?
It's Yang Soo Kyung.
("Love is a Cold Temptation" is from her 4th album released in 1991.)
- Good job.
-  We were so close.
- Well done.
-  Love is a cold temptation.
(The score is 0 to 2 to 1.)
Still, it's inevitable.
That was a tough question.
- I thought is was Min Hye Kyung.
-  You're so foolish.
It's tough.
All right. Here's the next song.
(What's the next song?)
Let's go.
(Let's go!)
Gosh. Slow down!
(Pink Team is quick to take over the microphones.)
Lee Ja Yeon.
- Tell us the answer. In 3, 2 and 1.
-  The singer is Lee Ja Yeon.
- Please tell us now.
-  No, it is Kim Ji Ae.
- Yes. That's right.
-  In 3, 2 and 1.
It's "Spiteful Person" by Kim Ji Ae.
Gosh.
- Yes.
-  You gave them too much time.
- You're spiteful
-  That's unfair.
("Spiteful Person" is from her 4th album released in 1990.)
I knew it.
I knew it right when I heard the intro.
(They all remember its catchy lyrics.)
- Let's move back a little.
-  Isn't this song from 1980s?
The score is 1 to 3 to 2.
Here comes the next song.
I know this song.
- I know this song.
-  I forgot the title.
(Where did I hear this melody before?)
(They're getting close to the answer.)
(It's 3 seconds before the first phrase.)
- Let's go!
-  Go.
(Everyone hurries to the microphones.)
Be careful.
(Falling down)
- Watch out.
-  I got it!
(They do whatever it takes to get the microphones.)
- My gosh.
-  Are we fighting here?
- I'm just kidding.
-  Wait a second.
- I know the answer.
-  What is it?
- It's by Lee Sang Woo...
-  Let just one person answer it.
Jin Hee, you say it.
- It's Lee Sang Woo's...
-  He got it wrong.
- No.
-  It's...
"Met Her 100m Before"
(The answer is "Met Her 100m Before" by Lee Sang Woo.)
Is it 10m then?
No, it's definitely not 10m.
Move over.
(Move over so we can answer.)
- Isn't that the answer?
-  It should end with away.
- No, that's wrong.
-  All right.
- Just follow him this time.
-  Answer now.
In 3, 2 and 1.
It's "Met Her 100m Away" by Lee Sang Woo.
("Met Her 100m Away" by Lee Sang Woo is correct.)
- Yes.
-  Really?
- Wasn't that our answer?
-  No, it's different.
Singing the song leads us to the title.
I met her 100m away.
("Met Her 100m Away" is from his 2nd album released in 1991.)
Should I give her a bucket of roses?
- A bucket of roses?
-  What was that?
(He changes the lyrics into very weird ones.)
(He is an astonishing songwriter.)
We were so close.
(The score is 2 to 4 to 2.)
- Let's get this one right.
-  Here comes the next song.
Let's do this.
I got it.
(Okay. Let's go!)
Let's go.
Hurry up.
(Jae Seok reacts as soon as he hears the first part.)
- Kim Won Jun is the singer.
-  Okay. In 3, 2 and 1.
It's "After All Asleep" by Kim Won Jun.
(Is it really "After All Asleep" by Kim Won Jun?)
- They got it right.
-  That's right!
- They were correct.
-  All right!
I knew the lyrics.
I also knew the answer.
("After All Asleep" by Kim Won Jun was his debut song in 1992.)
After all asleep.
It's all right to remember a lot of things
I sigh at the moments I've lost.
As Pink Team earned...
five points, you move up to round two.
We're tied.
For the other two teams,
- I'll give you one more song.
-  Okay.
(The last question will determine which team places second.)
(For Haha to win second place, he needs to get this right.)
(If you answer correctly this time, I'll give you a special compliment.)
(The final round to determine second place starts.)
(They're very focused.)
(They run forward first.)
- Do you know the song?
-  No.
Don't be too impatient.
- I thought you knew.
-  Don't be so impatient.
- Go on.
-  Go back to your seat.
- Let's listen to it longer.
-  Shall we do that?
- Let's go back to our seat.
-  Why don't you go back?
(The song plays for the second time.)
Pass.
Don't pass it.
I have no idea.
(The first verse starts to play.)
(On a melancholy day)
(They run toward the microphones as soon as the first verse plays.)
- Stop it.
-  Let go.
- What's the answer?
-  That's not the original song.
Is this a remix?
- Isn't it?
-  It's not the original.
This isn't the original song.
- One, two, three.
-  Marronnier Park.
- Marronnier.
She said Marronnier Park.
(Yellow Team is wrong.)
- Isn't it Marronnier Park?
-  Marronnier Park?
(She created a new song, "Daehakro Love" by Marronnier Park.)
- "Cocktail Love" by Marronnier.
-  "Cocktail Love" by Marronnier.
That's correct.
("Cocktail Love" by Marronnier is correct.)
- Goodness.
-  It's Marronnier's song.
("Cocktail Love" by Marronnier is from their first album in 1994.)
I thought it was Marronnier Park.
- I love this song.
-  I thought it was correct.
Now, take your shoes off.
Anyone from the team who knows the answer can come up.
- Is that so?
-  Okay.
The current total score is...
We're all tied.
- That's amazing.
-  Is it true?
- This is the current total score.
-  Let's win our special victory.
- Let's go.
-  Let's go.
We're the original victory.
- Special victory.
-  Special victory.
- Special victory. Hurrah.
-  Hurrah.
- Original victory
-  Original victory.
Our team will win anyway.
Why are you embarrassed?
(Everyone is embarrassed.)
Why do you feel embarrassed?
What kind of cheer was that?
Goodness.
- Here's the next song.
-  Okay!
(Round three that will determine the winning team starts.)
(She stumbles.)
(She pauses and goes forward again.)
I think I know the answer.
- One, two, three.
-  Move away.
It's a song by Girl's Day. This is the dance.
- I'll answer it.
-  "Something" by Girl's Day!
(Blue Team dominates at the beginning of round three.)
- Original victory
-  Original victory.
Original victory.
Gosh, I knew the song.
- That was impressive.
-  Good job.
Wow, that was great.
You're impressive.
Gosh, I was so close.
He knows so much about girl groups.
(He's a girl group specialist.)
- It was so close.
-  About girl groups?
- All right.
-  Seok Jin.
(Does he already know the answer by listening to such a short opening?)
(Viewers, can you guess which song it is?)
- What's the answer?
-  It's Jong Kook's favourite song.
- "Last Love" by Kim Bum Soo.
-  That's correct.
("Last Love" by Kim Bum Soo is correct.)
My last love
I've heard Jong Kook sing it a lot.
Really?
He even sings it in his sleep!
He sings this song a lot.
He always sings this song instead of his own.
I know it right away by listening to the opening.
- You knew it right away.
-  I know it.
I don't know who it is, but please come back.
(What are you talking about?)
What?
Seriously.
I don't know who you are, but please come back.
- Please.
-  What's wrong with you?
- You sing this a lot.
-  I only like the song.
I don't know who it is.
- He answered it correctly.
-  Goodness.
The score is 1 to 0 to 1.
Here's your next song.
I need to recognise the opening.
- Let's go.
-  Let's go.
(While everyone runs forward, )
(she stays behind alone.)
- It's my turn to answer.
-  Wait.
- He was so fast.
-  It's okay.
- One, two, three.
-  "Growl" by EXO.
That's right!
That's right.
- That's right.
-  Pardon me.
- Please play something I know.
-  I'm sorry, but...
- let's stand in a circle.
-  Seriously.
He's too close.
- His seat is the closest.
-  If not,
let's switch seats.
- All seats are the same.
-  I know.
Don't let them discuss.
- This is the shortest distance.
-  To make it fair,
we'll take out two microphones.
Three points are given in the last round.
Don't say that.
You won't be able to get out of your seat.
No one can get out of here.
- Gary, don't stay still.
-  Let's go.
All right, here's the next song.
(I'll do it too.)
- Look at Ji Hyo.
-  Hey.
(He recognises the song.)
One, two, three.
"Penniless Youth" by Buck.
("Penniless Youth" by Buck is correct.)
I was so close.
("Penniless Youth" by Buck is from the first album released in 1997.)
Why did you do that?
My ribs are broken.
- Why did you do that?
-  My ribs are broken.
What happened?
Didn't you hit me as you went out?
- It really hurts.
-  I didn't hit you.
Here's the next song.
(Currently, the score is 1 to 1 to 1.)
- All right.
-  Ji Hyo.
- Ji Hyo is also holding him down.
-  He should lay him down.
Ji Hyo, I didn't think clearly.
Wait a minute.
- This is going to be hard.
-  Block Blue Team.
Hey, stop it.
I'll go instead.
- Don't do it.
-  Wait a minute.
- Go now.
-  Wait.
(Jong Kook grabs the microphone.)
- Jong Kook was the fastest.
-  He grabbed it.
One, two, three.
- Is it "Speed" by Kim Gun Mo?
-  That's it.
("Speed" by Kim Gun Mo is correct.)
Why did you hold me back?
I know this song too.
("Speed by Kim Gun Mo is from his fourth album released in 1996.)
- Yellow Team...
-  Did they place first?
Is the winner of this game.
You earned two coupons.
We'll determine the second place that will win one coupon.
Your current score is 1 to 1.
(My team has to lose for Haha to place second.)
(If he doesn't win, a hint on the agent's identity is given.)
(What will happen to Agent H?)
- Don't hold me too tightly.
-  Jae Seok.
He can't get out.
- Jae Seok knows.
-  Stop it.
(Let's slowly take action to make Blue Team place second.)
(Where are you going?)
He doesn't know the song.
Hurry up.
(I can't let you go no matter what.)
(They're struggling.)
(He falls down.)
Jae Seok doesn't know either.
(There's no such thing as fair play in Running Man.)
Put your foot there.
(He throws a shoe.)
(Kwang Soo throws his large shoe toward the microphone.)
(Jae Seok stretches Haha's legs.)
(He screams in pain.)
- It hurts.
-  Stop it.
You don't even know the song.
What's wrong with you people?
Do you even know the song?
(Blue Team must get up.)
(This is their chance.)
- Do you know it?
-  I know the answer.
- One, two, three.
-  "No. 1" by BOA.
"No. 1" by BOA.
(The agent's mission would succeed at the same time.)
Really?
(Blue Team answers correctly.)
He got it right.
Wow.
- That was good.
-  Blue Team places second.
(Blue Team wins second place.)
(Since she accomplished her mission, her identity won't be revealed.)
Yellow Team earned two coupons.
- Congratulations.
-  Blue Team earned one coupon.
(Agent H Kim Hee Ae succeeds in making Haha win second place.)
(Round 1 of the agent's mission is a success.)
I haven't lost in a long time.
They're like machines. How could they guess...
- I know.
-  by listening to the opening?
Thanks to you, our team kept our reputation.
- I know.
-  Goodness.
Gary knows all the hip hop songs.
Why didn't they play any hip hop?
They should have played hip hop.
- It's popular these days.
-  My children love hip hop too.
I know. Hip hop is popular now.
Does Announcer Na have a lot of complaints?
Because you're too busy?
She doesn't complain, but...
- she gets a little disappointed...
-  Does she?
When I can't join the family on vacation.
Does your child like you?
Of course.
- You must do your best.
-  I try.
I don't go out or anything.
After work, I go straight home.
That's what I do.
It's hard because there's only one year difference between my sons.
They're going through puberty.
- Is that so?
-  Whether it's puberty or not,
it's really tough these days.
I didn't know raising children would be this difficult.
I have so much respect for all the mothers out there.
I was really surprised.
(He can sympathise.)
I never thought babies needed that many diapers a day.
I really didn't know.
(While they're talking about mothers...)
We're here. It's a market.
We're at a market.
- They sell tasty foods.
-  They do have a lot of foods.
I love traditional markets.
Me too.
(They'll have their second race in a traditional market.)
It's been a very long time since I visited a market.
I love this place.
(This traditional market sells a lot of tasty foods.)
(What mission will they do there?)
- Oh yes.
-  Food!
Really?
(Is that tteokbokki?)
Why is there tteokbokki at a barbecue restaurant?
Tteokbokki at a barbecue restaurant?
Please find the dish of your colour and enjoy the food.
- Really?
-  Can we eat this?
- Yes, please.
-  Thank you.
- Do we eat now?
-  Yes.
Don't we have to count the number of rice cakes?
We're eating tteokbokki at a barbecue restaurant.
- Do we eat now?
-  They sell beef here.
Find the right dish that has your team's colour.
- Don't count out loud.
-  Please help yourself.
This is for free, right?
(They never give things for free.)
- It's good.
-  I feel uncomfortable.
Jin Hee.
- It's so good.
-  It is.
Please enjoy it.
- Did you enjoy it?
-  Yes.
All right. We prepared a mission...
- to carry out in this market.
-  Okay.
We named the mission...
"Mrs Market".
You named it after the drama Hee Ae appeared, right?
"Mrs Market"?
"We'll give you an Exchange Card if you earn the most points."
"The first game is Jang Geum's Tteokbokki."
"Please buy the tteokbokki ingredients."
We used 14 ingredients for the tteokbokki you just had.
But we'll tell you what seven ingredients are.
"The basic ingredients we used are rice cake, water, chilli paste,"
"sugar, seasoning, fish cake and cabbage."
"Please buy the rest seven ingredients."
"But if one of the three members' feet touch the ground,"
"you fail."
Aren't you good at cooking?
There's taco sauce in it.
- That's why it tasted like this.
-  Wow.
Gosh, you're amazing.
- This tastes like...
-  He knows many good restaurants.
- Who knows?
-  Jin Hee.
I think they put ingredients we'd never think of.
Gosh, this is hard.
- I don't know what's in it.
-  Let's go.
(What are the 7 ingredients?)
Sir, please give us onion and garlic.
(Pink Team buys onion and garlic.)
- We don't need many.
-  We need just a few.
We'll buy the same ingredients.
You can't do that.
Gary, go inside and buy there.
Go inside the store.
(Confrontation)
Goodness.
(Do you want some special spanking?)
- Hey.
-  Come over here.
Hee Ae's used to our show now.
I'll hit you with Hee Ae's foot.
Goodness.
What would it be? Eggplant?
No, I don't think so.
- There were vegetables.
-  Shepherd's purse?
-  Bracken.
(What? Bracken?)
(Was bracken in this tteokbokki?)
- Let's buy bracken.
-  Okay. Let's buy it.
Please give us bracken.
We want bracken.
Let's buy kelp.
- Let's buy a bit of kelp.
-  Kelp?
The sauce can be sticky because of rice cake.
We'll count on your judgment.
- Do we buy kelp then?
-  My judgment?
(This special housewife chooses kelp.)
Let's buy kelp, then.
(Meanwhile, Jin Hee is...)
We need walnuts.
Please give us walnuts.
(Walnuts?)
(At the restaurant a while ago)
- This is...
-  It's not peanut but walnut.
It's walnut.
Let me see.
(They find walnut.)
(Jin Hee is a gourmet.)
- Jin Hee is very...
-  He's like Jang Geum.
Sir. Excuse me.
Excuse me.
Hello?
Sir!
(He's in a hurry.)
Jin Hee, we have to go now.
Sir. Hurry.
What is it?
What was it again?
- Licorice?
-  Please give us licorice.
- A herb?
-  Jang Geum is in its title.
I'm sure they used healthy herbs.
Licorice?
How many seconds left?
- 10 seconds.
-  10 seconds?
Sir, see you later!
Goodbye. Come here.
(Blue Team buys licorice.)
Everyone, we'll open all 14 ingredients we used...
in "Jang Geum's Tteokbokki".
- Okay.
-  Take out the ingredients...
you bought if you got them right.
Gosh, I'm not sure if we bought the right ingredients.
But we have no choice now.
(What are the 7 ingredients?)
Then, the first ingredient is...
red pepper powder.
(Red pepper powder)
(Goodness.)
You forgot red pepper powder?
Great!
(It's a basic ingredient.)
- Red pepper powder is...
-  Gosh.
I thought you're a good cook. Are you not?
It happens.
- There are still six left.
-  Okay.
- The second one is...
-  Gosh.
Onion.
(Onion)
- Onion.
-  Onion!
They forgot onion, too.
- No. We have onion.
-  Onion.
- No, this is garlic.
-  That's garlic.
- Oh, I found it.
-  They have it.
- Gosh, I was worried.
-  Good.
- I'm nervous.
-  The third one is...
Please.
Green onion.
(They didn't buy it.)
You didn't buy green onion?
That's unbelievable.
- You need green onion.
-  It's so important.
Have you seen tteokbokki without green onion?
You forgot it.
- The fourth one is...
-  Gosh.
- Kelp?
-  starch syrup.
(He had it ready.)
- Yes!
-  Yes!
There's always starch syrup in tteokbokki.
Now, we have three left to go.
- This is hard.
-  Gosh.
We told you that the tteokbokki was very special.
Good. We made it.
- Angelica root?
-  No way.
- Ginseng?
-  It's curry powder.
That's right. It was curry not taco sauce.
You only added a tiny bit.
- I didn't know there was curry.
-  I couldn't taste curry at all.
- You fooled me. You're amazing.
-  The next one is...
pear juice.
- Pear juice?
-  I was going to buy it. Gosh.
I never thought of it.
- The last one is...
-  I think we got it.
A kind of nuts.
- That's right.
-  Good.
- We must have the right one.
-  Great.
(Blue Team seems confident.)
- It's walnut.
-  Yes!
- Yes!
-  I told you.
(They all get it right.)
It's me who bought walnut.
- Blue Team got five right items.
-  Yes.
And the other two teams got three correct.
Please show me what you bought.
We bought kelp. Hee Ae said we must buy this.
I told her we needed starch syrup. But she insisted on kelp.
(Special housewife's mistake)
And we also bought Cheongyang chilli.
We found it very spicy.
- Right.
-  We have garlic, too.
We bought peanuts. Because we weren't sure...
- if it was peanut or walnut.
-  Right.
This team bought more than seven items.
- But they bought eight.
-  No, they said we can buy more.
- Do you have more than seven?
-  Yes.
- Take items away from them.
-  This is nonsense.
- This is ridiculous.
-  Gosh.
- This is total nonsense!
-  We asked them.
We asked you before we left.
- You could buy only seven items.
-  Right.
Anyway, these are the main items.
We bought this for Jin Hee's wife.
I bought this ginseng for myself.
They even bought ginseng and angelica.
- That's a foul.
-  Gosh.
Hee Ae, please say something. Does that make sense?
- That's nonsense.
-  See?
That means you failed.
Let me announce the result of the first game.
Although Blue Team has five right items, they failed.
Isn't it amazing that we bought this many items in a limited time?
Don't you think you should compliment us?
Good job.
- Every team gets one point.
-  Nice!
But there are more missions left.
We'll decide a winning team in the two missions left.
- That's chicken.
-  Chicken.
It's dakgangjung.
- Gosh, I like it.
-  It's chicken.
Is it Jang Geum's chicken as well?
(Jin Hee starts inspecting it.)
This game is very objective.
(What mission will they do with this dakgangjung?)
- Please help yourself.
-  This is strange.
(They're very distrustful.)
Please enjoy. It's very tasty.
- That's very famous here.
-  It's good.
(Gary finds something.)
Grain powder?
(Hee Ae bursts into laughter.)
What is he talking about?
(Did they put grain powder because it's summer?)
Gary is dissecting the dakgangjung.
(Dakgangjung Detective Gary)
Please enjoy it.
(She bites into the dakgangjung elegantly.)
It's good.
- Hee Ae.
-  What?
Although you're hungry, don't just eat up.
(She's caught.)
I have no idea.
(She seems to have given up on everything.)
Please guess the total weight...
of the dakgangjung you just had...
- What?
-  What?
And the plate.
Then, you should go to...
a fruit store and buy fruits that weigh the same.
How can you make such an annoying game?
(That's why we handed it right into your hands.)
- Guess the weight.
-  He's measuring with his hands.
Don't forget to add the weight of your plates.
(What fruit will weigh the same as the dakgangjung and the plate?)
(Pink Team chooses an oriental melon.)
Oh, this isn't that heavy. Hold it with your left hand.
- And Jin Hee...
-  It's not so heavy.
Keeps trying to hold us in check. It's pretty stressful.
This is it. I think this weighs the same.
- Theirs is heavier.
-  Really?
- Isn't ours more heavy?
-  It's very confusing.
Can we have a bite of our fruit?
As long as it's not a quiz to guess the fruit,
we'll allow you that until we start measuring its weight.
Let's just have one bite.
Do you want it?
(Biting)
Stop there. Give it to me.
But don't we have to wash it before we eat?
(Pink Team cuts it with a knife.)
- Time is ticking. Please hurry.
-  We should hurry up.
Take two-thirds of it.
- Two-thirds?
-  Maybe one-third?
- Okay. One-third.
-  We'll take one-third.
Okay. That's good.
I think it's too light.
It's too light.
This is...
This won't be enough.
- Stop eating, Kwang Soo.
-  Stop eating!
Stop. It's too light now.
(It's significantly smaller.)
The total weight of the plate and dakgangjung is...
820g.
- Wow.
-  I think ours is about that heavy.
- Is it 820g?
-  The total is 820g.
- It doesn't look that heavy.
-  We didn't have to do that earlier.
Blue Team first.
Please put your fruit on the scale.
Stay still. Leave it as is.
(It starts with 4.)
Gosh.
Take it back.
(Kwang Soo is to blame.)
(It starts with 4 for Pink Team too.)
(What a shame.)
(It's 4 again for Yellow Team.)
(All of their numbers start with 4.)
Let me announce the results. Blue Team's pear...
weighs 472g.
(Dakgangjung on a plate: 820g, Blue Team's pear: 472g)
Why did you eat so much?
I don't know.
- Why would you even ask?
-  Yellow Team's...
Gosh.
The melon weighs 488g.
(Dakgangjung on a plate: 820g, Yellow Teams' pear: 488g)
Pink Team's melon...
weighs 498g.
(Dakgangjung on a plate: 820g, Pink Team's melon: 498g)
- Are we first?
-  Yes, we are.
- Are we really?
-  Be quiet.
- This is heavier.
-  Does this make sense to you?
- Why did you eat so much?
-  This is amazing.
- Why on earth did you eat so much?
-  You kept telling me to eat.
- We did well.
-  Currently,
the scores are 3 points for Yellow, 4 for Pink and 2 for Blue.
The last mission...
- at the market...
-  Let's make it up this time.
- will determine the winner.
-  Okay.
(At this pace, )
(they might fail the special agent mission...)
(and end up revealing Agent Hee Ae's hint.)
(Mrs Market Final Round)
- I don't think we should eat.
-  Here.
(The food for the final round is mandu.)
- Have a piece, Hee Ae.
-  Thanks.
- What could it be?
-  I need some soy sauce.
- What could we be doing?
-  What are we supposed to do?
- Enjoy.
-  Give me some soy sauce.
- We can't be weighing this.
-  Should we guess what's inside?
- I don't think it's about that.
-  Is it something about soy sauce?
- Usually, what goes inside is...
-  This is just plain soy sauce.
What we have to guess.
Mostly, when you get mandu, you have to guess what's inside.
(Can I really go on and eat?)
Let's savour the taste.
This is good.
- It's salty.
-  I don't think we have to guess...
- the ingredients.
-  I don't think so.
It wouldn't be the weight.
(Blue Team finished eating first.)
It's really good.
It tastes really good.
I think the soy sauce tastes good.
First place goes to...
Blue Team.
(Blue Team is the winner.)
(We won?)
- Second place goes to Pink Team.
-  The first to finish.
And third place goes to Yellow Team.
It's about finishing first.
- What was it?
-  The first to finish.
You won because you finished eating first.
(I knew it.)
(It's a relief they were lucky.)
Seok Jin left some on purpose.
(Nothing works for Seok Jin.)
This was unexpected.
The overall winner of "Mrs Market" is...
- Pink Team.
-  Yes!
(Pink Team is the winner of Mrs Market.)
- We won?
-  We did well.
It's because the scores accumulate.
That makes Blue Team come second.
- Yes!
-  Yes!
(Haha's team comes second.)
Thank you.
(Fortunately, the hint about the agent remains unrevealed.)
(5pm, SBS)
Now, it's time for the final mission.
(What is the final mission?)
We'll win no matter what.
The final mission is...
(Whatever it may be, I won't miss the chance.)
It's "Name Tag Elimination for Exchange Cards".
(The final mission is name tag elimination for exchange cards.)
You all turned out to have equal number of cards.
- Two each.
-  Right?
You'll be rewarded with three cards for this game.
Look at Jin Hee's eyes.
- Only the winner will be rewarded.
-  I'm just tired.
- They will have five in total.
-  Oh, really?
The winner will also get to choose the invigorating foods first.
(The winner will have extra cards and choose the food first.)
- What are you talking about?
-  Why are you doubting things?
Why are you speculating?
- Why?
-  You trust nothing.
- Jin Hee doubts everything.
-  He just guessed something amazing.
- It gave us the chills.
-  What is it?
The title is...
"Second to Last", right?
Is it about getting the second place?
Check it when it airs.
Seriously. I think he may be right.
We have one condition.
- What is it?
-  Only those who pass...
the extra mission will be able to participate in the final game.
What?
All of you will go into separate rooms.
You'll be given the same mission.
I have no hope if it's about being clever.
Is it about luck or brain?
If you can't complete it within 30 minutes,
you'll be disqualified completely.
- Oh, I see.
-  Really?
- That sounds like fun.
-  You can't even participate.
I'm not good with these things.
"Gary is disqualified."
(This doesn't look easy.)
- I understand.
-  Cover your eyes.
- Okay.
-  You shouldn't see where you are.
- I see.
-  We have to be blindfolded.
I'm worried.
(They move to their designated rooms.)
Can I take it off now?
(The mysterious mission is revealed.)
What is this?
Oh no. Do I have to put them in the cups?
Do I have to put them in?
How do I do this?
I won't be going out then.
Be ready.
(The extra mission starts.)
Okay.
(It goes in.)
(Jae Seok succeeds on first try.)
(Bouncing)
It's in!
(Gary succeeds.)
I get it now.
Everyone would get out.
Oh no.
No. I can't do it.
Gosh.
(Whatever)
Oh no.
(It's not so easy to handle.)
This is frustrating.
(Jae Seok is laid-back.)
I should try to read the atmosphere.
(It's in).
I don't think getting out quickly is a good thing.
(She aims for the cup in the middle.)
(It goes in anyway.)
What just happened?
How did that end up there?
(Jae Seok only needs to get one more in.)
(It goes in.)
Gosh.
(He finishes first.)
What do I do?
Since you completed the mission, here is the rule.
(Here is the rule.)
I thought I could just leave.
"Different mission"?
(Be aware of the two people with a different mission.)
They have a different mission?
(Hints on those two have been revealed.)
What?
When were they revealed?
You know them.
They have a different mission?
(He receives a pass to go into the building.)
(Jae Seok escapes the room first.)
What is going on?
What other mission?
Yu Jae Seok escapes the room.
He escaped already?
Wow, Jae Seok is unbelievable.
(The news got them nervous.)
This is nerve-racking.
(Kwang Soo of Blue Team...)
Okay!
(also succeeds.)
Thank you.
(He also gets the rule card and the pass.)
"The two people with a different mission."
(What does this mean?)
Gosh.
"Be aware of the two people that have been acting suspiciously."
(Two people who have been acting suspiciously)
It must be Jin Hee.
For Kwang Soo.
(Jin Hee is oblivious to everything.)
Korean beef for Kwang Soo.
Korean beef.
That's it!
(Haha of Blue Team...)
(also completes the mission.)
"The two people with a different mission."
I knew it. This wasn't what's important.
There are suspicious people.
There are.
(The two who have been deceiving everyone)
(Who could they be?)
What is this again?
(Who could the two people be?)
Oh gosh.
(Startled)
You scared me. Jae Seok.
- You read the hint, right?
-  Kwang Soo,
there are two people with a different mission.
Don't just rip anyone's name tag.
Jin Hee is suspicious.
Should I share this with you?
What is it?
(Tell me, what is it?)
Today...
While we were on missions...
(While we were on missions today...)
I noticed that the game titles...
were related to Hee Ae's filmography.
- Hee Ae's?
-  Yes.
- And?
-  "Dae Jang Geum" is Jin Hee's work.
You're right.
Right? So I think it must be the two.
(Is everything related to Hee Ae and Jin Hee today?)
Kim Jong Kook escapes the room.
None of my team has escaped. Where are Seok Jin and Ji Hyo?
(Jong Kook has escaped, )
(but others are still struggling.)
Gosh.
(Other team members are struggling.)
Shoot.
(Agent Hee Ae is still at it.)
(It goes in.)
Oh my gosh.
(Hee Ae escapes the room.)
Where should I head to?
(Looking around)
I can't find anything.
Where do I go? You know, right?
(Is she acting or what?)
Tell me, please.
Is no one out yet?
Ji Jin Hee, Song Ji Hyo and Jee Seok Jin has escaped the room.
(Everyone is out.)
I just want to meet anyone.
(I'm bored.)
From what I see,
setting up a different mission for the two...
- must mean Hee Ae is one of them.
-  Be careful.
- Oh gosh.
-  She scared me.
I was just tying my shoe laces. Aren't you scared?
Oh, you guys are on the same team.
Did you just get that?
Be careful. Don't wander around on your own.
Please don't walk about by yourself.
- Please.
-  I'm serious.
I don't know.
- I was just happy to see you guys.
-  You're out if we rip you.
Hee Ae!
Do I have to go over there?
Gary!
They're here. Jae Seok is here.
(Team Yellow vs 2 members of Team Pink)
- You two are here.
-  Jae Seok.
- Someone has different intentions.
-  I know.
Hee Ae,
do you have a different motive?
Me? I just came down here...
because no one was up there.
I was happy to see them, but they're running away for some reason.
Is that so?
I have no idea what the mission is.
Is this a team game or an individual game?
Right. Can you at least tell us the goal of the game?
Is our goal to simply eliminate everyone?
How am I supposed to know?
Hee Ae, what's the spy's purpose?
What are you talking about?
What do we have to do?
(My goal is for Haha to be the second from last to be eliminated.)
- Hee Ae...
-  It's not that difficult.
Is just astonished to have...
- Right?
-  something like this take place.
- That team is too strong.
-  Excuse me.
Jae Seok, don't you think that Blue Team is too strong?
- I think they're very strong.
-  We should eliminate at least one.
- At least one of them.
-  Right.
- Look at him.
-  Kwang Soo is running away.
Can't you hand Kwang Soo over to us?
Let's hand him over. We'll be eliminated if we don't.
Okay. Okay. Kwang Soo is the most suspicious right now.
- Before, Kwang Soo was...
-  He was strange.
- acting strange.
-  I thought the same thing.
He kept eating.
(Sorry, Kwang Soo. Goodbye.)
Are they going to eliminate me?
You're going to eliminate me?
(Running away)
Wait, hold on. You guys must be crazy.
- Why are you running away?
-  You guys should be protecting me!
- What are you doing?
-  Why are you fleeing?
- What are you guys doing?
-  It's because you're running away.
Aren't you guys going to help me?
(They pretend not to notice.)
What's my team doing?
I got it.
I ripped him.
(I won't leave them alone.)
- Why did you run away?
-  Why would you flee?
- Why'd you run away?
-  You should've helped me!
- Let me see your back.
-  Why should you run? You have us.
You shouldn't run away when you have us on your team.
(There's nothing there.)
(Kwang Soo is out.)
Kwang Soo is out.
You're not anything?
I can't believe this. I'm bewildered, really.
(I can't believe I was abandoned because I ate a pear.)
(Among the three teams, )
(Kwang Soo has been eliminated from Blue Team.)
- Is that so?
-  Why'd he run away so suddenly?
I have no idea.
Maybe he ran away and acted strangely on purpose.
- Do you know why I'm spooked?
-  Why?
Because I think you might be the agent.
- I'm so scared, really.
-  Haha.
- I feel like it might be him.
-  I see what you mean.
(If so, Haha easily gave Kwang Soo away.)
I hope Blue Team loses!
Jin Hee's a spy!
- It might be Jin Hee.
-  It's a possibility.
Hold on.
- Why are you touching my name tag?
-  Be careful.
- Why are you grabbing my name tag?
-  She grabbed your shirt.
- What's wrong with you?
-  Gosh, I got scared.
(The battle officially begins.)
I'm scared. Guys, my arm hurts!
(Stay away, my arm hurts!)
I apologise.
- I'm sorry.
-  Be careful, Hee Ae.
(Hee Ae lies down on the floor.)
- Wait a minute.
-  Hee Ae. Hee Ae.
- Stop. Stop.
-  Hee Ae's lying down.
- She lied down.
-  You have to get up now.
- Would you like to stay down there?
-  Hee Ae...
- She lied down on purpose.
-  Maybe she did.
- Then stay there, Hee Ae.
-  Go away.
Hee Ae.
- Hold on, Hee Ae.
-  Are you shooting a movie?
- You shouldn't stay there, Hee Ae.
-  Are you?
I'm scared.
(Pink Team has become the new target.)
(Jin Hee makes a sudden attack.)
- Jin Hee has quick hands.
-  Are we battling now?
Gary, Jae Seok's grabbing your name tag right now.
Jae Seok, why are you doing this?
- We have to eliminate one of them.
-  Go over there.
That's right. Keep going straight.
- Go straight. Good.
-  That's good.
- Great. We cornered them.
-  That's great.
- We made it.
-  Stay still.
Someone rip their name tags.
It's okay. It's okay.
- Hold on.
-  We got it.
Come inside. What are you guys doing?
(Ripping)
(As soon as Gary's eliminated, Jae Seok and Jin Hee battle.)
- My goodness.
-  They're battling.
- Go for it.
- Spread out.
-  Oh, gosh.
(Goodness, I'm scared.)
(Who ripped my tag?)
Who is it?
(Jae Seok is very competitive.)
He's determined.
- He has a strong will.
-  Jae Seok is very determined.
There's something going on. They might both be spies.
(Hee Ae, I will protect you.)
(Is Jae Seok Hee Ae's supporting agent?)
Jae Seok, I think you're the one who ripped my name tag.
What are you talking about?
(Is Gary blowing his team's cover?)
You're right. You're right.
(Jae Seok and Jin Hee...)
(were both holding Gary's name tag.)
(Did Jae Seok remove Gary's name tag amidst the chaos?)
- You're right.
-  Gary!
I was trying to save you!
Are you sure?
(Jae Seok seems suspicious.)
There's something strange. They might both be spies.
There's something going on.
(Gary is out from Pink Team.)
(Who is the other special agent?)
Gary, are you out?
I think it's either Jin Hee or Hee Ae.
Jae Seok was a bit strange toward the end.
Is there a hint in the visitor's card?
No way.
It says it can't be handed over to Tiger.
(Tiger?)
(Tiger and special compliment?)
(If there is a tiger among us, )
(wouldn't it be Jong Kook?)
(Hee Ae was given a secret mission this morning.)
It's going to be hard.
(Special agent Hee Ae felt great pressure with the secret mission.)
That's why we designated...
another secret agent.
Who could that be?
(Who will be the agent to help Hee Ae?)
(A wide chest and bulky arms)
Wow, it's Jong Kook!
- Goodness.
-  Hello.
(Agent Jong Kook)
(Goosebumps)
I just got the chills.
Who's the other one? Are both hints here?
- It's "special compliment".
-  Who's that?
Do you not watch television?
It's Hee Ae.
Why is she "special compliment"?
"Special compliment".
(Don't you know this catchphrase?)
This hint wouldn't have been helpful to me anyway.
I can't believe I'm out with someone like him. It's stifling.
It's depressing, really.
(I guess Hee Ae was a special woman.)
(Will these two agents complete their mission without being caught?)
(The three teams are once again face to face.)
- Are they here?
-  Okay.
- Hee Ae stay out, you can get hurt.
-  I'm hiding over here.
I'm here.
Is today's show going along properly?
- I'm getting so suspicious.
-  I agree.
I'm questioning my own actions.
- Hee Ae, get ready.
-  Hee Ae...
- Get ready, Hee Ae.
-  hasn't been doing anything.
- Be prepared.
-  It's a great strategy.
(Hee Ae hides behind a cameraman.)
I'm dizzy. Let's turn in the opposite direction.
(The official battle begins.)
- Let's finish this quickly.
-  All right.
(Hee Ae grabs Ji Hyo.)
(Hee Ae makes a surprise attack.)
(Slipping)
- Oh, gosh.
-  My goodness.
(Hee Ae attacks and runs away.)
She attacks while being scared.
It was a good try.
- She's scary.
-  She made a good effort.
Seriously.
(Gosh, it was close.)
You guys are amazing.
I'm so scared.
(Jong Kook makes the first attack.)
(Jin Hee's target is Ji Hyo.)
(Jong Kook protects Haha while attacking Jae Seok.)
(It's Ji Hyo vs Jin Hee.)
Hey, watch out.
(Seok Jin and Hee Ae join them.)
- Hee Ae, you have to come now.
-  Come in now.
- Come here.
-  Hurry.
Wait a minute!
- Come here now.
-  Hurry.
Wait a minute!
- I got him.
-  He's out.
(Seok Jin of Yellow Team is out.)
Okay. Okay. Get her now.
(Jin Hee and Hee Ae go for Ji Hyo.)
What do I do?
I'm sorry, Ji Hyo.
(Jong Kook, we have to eliminate everyone but Haha.)
(Okay, Hee Ae.)
Hey, Haha!
Haha, rip him!
Rip his tag.
Did you get ripped?
(Haha grabs Jong Kook's name tag.)
- Rip it.
-  Did you get ripped?
There we go!
Good job.
(Special agent Jong Kook is out.)
(On the other hand, Jin Hee and Hee Ae...)
(easily eliminate Ji Hyo.)
Are you okay?
What's going on?
(Now, they just need to eliminate Jae Seok and Jin Hee.)
(But at that moment, )
(Jae Seok makes a surprise attack.)
(Ripping)
(Haha is out, thanks to Jae Seok.)
Hey.
(The final secret mission to make Haha come second has failed.)
(Haha, why did you eliminate me?)
Hee Ae.
- Hee Ae.
-  Are they all eliminated?
- It's okay.
-  Gosh, then I'm going to lose.
What are you?
It was you.
(Let's just get as many invigorating foods as possible.)
- Goodness.
-  Hold on.
- Hee Ae, go away.
-  Come here!
Stop it. Hee Ae, what are you doing?
Please stop!
You can't do this!
Come on!
Gosh!
(Jin Hee's name tag is removed.)
(They succeed in getting the invigorating foods.)
Pink Team won. We'll give you three Exchange Cards.
Great.
It's all thanks to Hee Ae.
Pink Team earned five invigorating foods.
You can pick first.
But...
while you were playing the race for invigorating foods,
you also had a special race for two golden badges...
at the same time.
Based on a specific drama,
- we named it "Second to Last".
-  Right!
Jin Hee talked about it in the car.
The eighth person who showed up...
- It's you.
-  was Haha.
So the mission was to make Haha's team come second to last.
(It was to make Blue Team come second to last.)
Haha's team takes the second place.
(Haha's team came second after the first mission.)
Blue Team came second.
Thank you.
(Haha's team also came 2nd during the 2nd mission.)
We got two Exchange Cards.
As Haha's team came second again, so we didn't give you any hints.
They were going to give you hints about us.
But you succeeded the mission.
- That's why they didn't give us...
-  Did you intentionally do that?
And in the final mission,
Haha, who was the second to last,
had to become the second last one to be out.
That's why you didn't rip my name tag.
So, you failed to complete your secret mission.
- They failed.
-  The winning team is Pink Team.
- Yes!
-  We made it!
(Pink Team is the final winner.)
Thank you very much for joining us today.
Let's have a round of applause...
for Hee Ae and Jin Hee.
- Thank you!
-  And we'll watch...
your new drama.
- We'll definitely watch it.
-  It's a weekend drama.
Thank you.
- Thank you.
-  Thank you.
- Goodbye.
(Thank you, Hee Ae and Jin Hee, for joining us on such a hot day.)
They've been treating me quite awfully these days.
I was going to get therapy.
We're here to save you.
(They have come to his rescue.)
(Hong Jin Kyung, Seo Jang Hoon and Lee Ki Woo)
I'll take revenge!
Today's the day.
We used to work together.
(Let the tall ones prepare for battle.)
Get out!
(Their average height is 192cm. This will be immense.)
(Will they be able to stop these giants?)
(Kwang Soo's Revenge)