(Beautiful Icheon where excellent quality rice grows)
Our special guests today are waiting behind that door.
Are they inside?
(Today's special guests are waiting for Running Man members.)
Enter the door and meet them.
There they are.
- There they are. - I can see them.
(They walk towards the door.)
(Five members of Sechs Kies return.)
(Jang Su Won, half human, half robot)
(Kim Jae Duck, an idol singer with accents)
(Kang Sung Hoon, a handsome vocalist)
(Eun Ji Won, the leader)
(Lee Jae Jin, positive yet strange)
They're all here.
- Why are they posing? - Goodness.
- Hello. - Some dyed their hair.
(They're trembling.)
(That pose is so outdated.)
Long time no see.
I haven't seen you in a while.
You're such an old idol group.
You haven't changed at all.
You look the same.
Today, Running Man and Sechs Kies...
will compete against each other.
We're competing with them.
There are two ladies...
who will lead each of the team.
- Ladies? - Ladies?
Please come out.
(It's the first lady everyone waited for.)
(Is it who we think she is?)
(Who's the second lady who looks good under the garment?)
Please come out.
Is the lady whom I think it is?
(They can't wait to see who they are.)
(Two ladies are as beautiful as the sunny weather.)
(They're loyal to their ladies.)
(They look shy and embarrassed.)
Why is Ji Hyo covering herself?
(She laughs shyly.)
Gosh, that's Hwangwoo Seul Hye.
What's the point of this?
They can see our faces anyway.
(He looks happy.)
Hello.
(Today's special lady is Hwangwoo Seul Hye.)
(With her unique loveliness, she acts in movies, TV and commercials.)
(Now, she even appears in variety shows.)
- You're on our team. - Hello.
- Seul Hye. - Hello.
By the way,
you curled your bangs too much. What's wrong with you?
That was a popular hairstyle when I was in college.
She wanted to look younger.
(Her hairstyle is perfect for her character.)
(He's full of smiles.)
Among the other team members, Sung Hoon is the prettiest.
- You look colorful. - Ji Hyo is the second prettiest.
When I said I'm an idol singer,
they dyed my hair like this at a beauty parlor.
(A beauty parlor?)
(It's a place for haircuts and perms.)
Seok Jin also went to a barbershop this morning.
I certainly did. I washed my hair like this, too.
At barbershops, you wash your hair while leaning forward.
You know what I mean? That's how you wash your hair.
Today is...
ladies and servants'...
Food Thief Race.
Food Thief Race?
Food thief?
Among 10 servants,
one of you is a food thief.
(1 of the 10 servants is a food thief.)
(There is a food thief...)
(among the servants?)
- There's a food thief? - You punk.
(We caught the thief.)
Whenever this happens...
We haven't selected the thief yet.
They haven't selected the thief yet!
They haven't selected the thief yet.
- They haven't selected one yet. - Isn't it you?
- They haven't selected him yet. - He doesn't look like he's lying.
He doesn't look like he's lying.
The food thief...
will be on a hidden mission in secret.
(The food thief will be given a hidden mission.)
I see.
The 2 teams will compete 3 rounds.
If the food thief remains on your team after the final round,
your team loses.
(Stay away from the food thief.)
At the end of each round,
the lady of the winning team...
will be given a hint about the food thief...
and a chance to exchange a servant with the other team.
(It's advantageous to win each round.)
She can exchange a servant.
Do you see a pavilion back there?
When you get to the pavilion,
you'll find a row of rice in stone pots.
When you open the stone pot, you'll find out if you're a food thief.
(The one with soy sauce gejang in the stone pot is the food thief.)
(Accomplish your hidden mission and win 100 bags of rice.)
(If you succeed, you can donate rice under your name.)
(If not, you're punished.)
I'll be caught if I'm the thief.
(Suspicious Kwang Soo starts first.)
(He's worried of getting caught if he's the food thief.)
I...
choose this one.
(He makes a random choice.)
(Is Kwang Soo the food thief?)
If it's Kwang Soo, it'd be obvious.
Kwang Soo seems very flustered now.
I think he received the hidden mission.
He's coming.
- What's going on? - Why is he running?
Next up is Jae Jin.
(He's nervous.)
I'm not good at hidden missions.
(He wants to avoid finding soy sauce gejang in his pot.)
Okay.
(It's hard to tell.)
- He's already coming back. - He was quick.
- I'm next, right? - You're up, Haha.
Why did you take so long, Kwang Soo?
I had to wait for them to set up the cameras.
The cameras were already set up.
No, they really weren't.
Kwang Soo is the food thief.
Show them the camera.
The one that was in front of me.
He looks too calm to be the food thief.
Jae Jin, why are you smiling?
- Excuse me? - He looks flustered.
Are you quite flustered?
(Why is he smiling?)
(Haha hurries up to a pot.)
(He looks suspicious.)
Kwang Soo is the thief because he took too long.
It was because of the cameras.
The staff didn't even talk to me.
- The cameras weren't set up. - All you do is open the pot.
- Really? - Tell them I'm innocent.
- The cameras weren't set up. - Come on.
- It didn't take that long for me. - I'm being honest.
The cameras weren't set up.
(Nine servants)
(One food thief)
(Today's race depends on the food thief.)
(The hidden mission is only given to the food thief.)
(Who will be the food thief that will lead his team to victory?)
I think it's Haha.
- Why? I don't think so. - Me?
- I think it's Haha. - Why?
(She has a hunch that it's Haha.)
You're not very sharp, are you?
I've worked with Seul Hye a few times.
She's...
- She isn't sharp, is she? - very innocent but isn't sharp.
She's quite dull.
(He stares at others.)
Ji Won, what did you find in your stone pot?
What did you find in your pot?
(He hesitates.)
- It's him. - It must be him.
The problem is that...
Ji Won is good at...
- looking suspicious. - That's right.
- Why would I do that? - He likes to act suspicious.
(Is that so?)
What was inside your pot?
Seul Hye, stop pretending to be sharp.
Come on.
She wants to find out who the food thief is.
(Food Thief Race, Round 1)
This is the first round.
The food thief is already given the hidden mission.
When did that happen?
(When? To whom? I didn't see anyone.)
It's the person who took a long time to get ready.
It's Kwang Soo because he took the longest time.
I'm telling you. The cameras weren't set up.
Now, Seul Hye will show one of Sechs Kies' dances.
(All eyes are on her.)
Gosh, do I dance now?
- Right now? - Now?
Dancing when it's awkward is the best.
(Sechs Kies' dance is the best to break the ice.)
Show us the dance now.
- She's taking her jacket off. - Goodness.
Our dances aren't usually for women.
Show us the dance now.
("Road Fighter" by Sechs Kies)
- This is it. - Gosh.
(I'm not here as an actress right now.)
(I'm here as a fan of Sechs Kies.)
There she goes.
- Look at her. - She is pretty good.
- Look at her dancing. - She is nice.
(Her footwork is good enough to surprise Sechs Kies members.)
(Sechs Kies fans will be surprised if they see her dancing.)
- What's the next move? - Just follow her lead.
(Flipping)
(She is doing her best at dancing.)
- She is really good. - Yes, she is.
- She is so good. - That's it.
Go, Seul Hye.
- She's so good. - She remembers all the moves.
- She's so good. - Can you dance like her, Ji Won?
(I remember this melody, too!)
("Couple" by Sechs Kies)
- Oh love - Oh love
(Everyone naturally dances to this song.)
- She's good. - Yes, she is.
She's not a good dancer. She just remembers the moves well.
- Why did you come so late - Why did you come so late
(Now, everyone dances together to the music with her.)
Oh love
(Forget the mission. Let's dance for now.)
- I love you - I love you
(She remembers all the fine details. She must be their huge fan.)
(She acts flashy.)
(Ta-da)
(She even finishes her dancing with their signature gesture.)
- Can I ask you a favor? - Really.
- She's really good. - I want to ask you only one favor.
- Can you do this again, Seul Hye? - Please show us the footwork again.
- Seul Hye. - My gosh.
- You're really good. - It's really embarrassing.
- That was amazing. - Seul Hye is an amazing dancer.
- Thank you. - You're welcome.
- You danced really well. - She's talented.
- She even made up a few new moves. - I am really surprised.
How did she make those moves?
For the first round,
please choose one crystal ball.
We've prepared games according to the song titles attached to them.
(For the 1st round, the teams should play 3 games with the song titles.)
Never pick "Road Fighter". Jong Kook will crush us.
(Is Jong Kook really a road fighter?)
- "Road Fighter"? - We must choose it.
- Haven't you decided yet? - It must be a game for couples.
Shall we choose "Couple"?
- Let's choose "Couple". - Okay. We'll choose "Couple".
- Gosh. - "Limbo with My Lady"?
For this game,
each team must play the limbo game in turn.
The team which passes the lower bar without touching it will win.
- All right, Jong Kook. Let's go. - Good luck.
(Jong Kook and Seul Hye will play as a pair this time.)
- You will play first. - Here it is.
- Stop pushing others to play first. - Lower the bar.
(Jae Jin seems as fit as Jong Kook.)
- Is it okay now? - Yes. Lower it.
Go, Jong Kook.
- That looks great. - Just once, please.
- We finally miss Gary now. - Yes, we really do.
You're right. Gary's really good at this kind of games.
(We miss you. How are you doing, Gary?)
Stretch your legs. That's it.
- There you go. - Get lower, Jong Kook.
You need to stick together for a good result.
Let Seul Hye to pass under the bar first.
- That looks good. - There you go.
- Nice. - Watch out for your microphone.
- He's really steady. - They are amazing.
- Mind your head. - You're doing great.
(What a great pair they are!)
- They succeeded. - Just a little more.
- They passed. - Yes.
(They succeed flawlessly.)
- Success. - Yes!
- Jong Kook, that was great. - Did you see that?
Did you see Seul Hye slipping her head under the bar?
- It looked like a movie. - It really did.
That was like a scene from a romance movie.
(It's Jae Jin and Ji Hyo's turn.)
Please excuse me.
Look how gentle Jae Jin is.
- Yes, He's really gentle. - All right.
It seems really tough.
(The height of the bar is 70 cm.)
- He let her head slip under first. - Jae Jin, tuck your head down.
You must tuck your head down to pass.
Wait.
Excuse me. Just a moment.
- Well, that's a fail. - What was that?
- What are you doing? - Did he just dump her?
- You dumped her! - You threw her on the ground.
- That's a fail, indeed. - That must be a fail.
- What did you just do? - You dumped her.
Are you all right?
Nobody will excuse you if you do this.
- Gosh. - What was that?
That was rude.
- Wasn't it? - That was so rude.
(Jae Jin and Ji Hyo give the second try.)
Saying "excuse me" won't make people feel better.
Step back if you think you wouldn't make it.
Wait. Isn't that too far from the bar?
Step a bit closer.
You can't hold her forever. Hurry up.
Now, I see why you argue often.
(They just can't agree on anything.)
(Slipping)
- Wow. That was good. - No. Mind your head.
(It seems they can pass without a problem.)
(Jae Jin advances cautiously.)
- Mind your head. Good. - Nice.
All right. Just a few steps more.
- Be careful. - Be steady. Nice.
- You did it. - Yes.
(Jae Jin and Ji Hyo succeed.)
Gosh. I have a cramp.
(Did I play to get this muscle cramp?)
- Gosh. - Are you all right?
Gosh. I have a cramp.
- Good work. - It hurts.
Jong Kook. How about this?
- Lift Seul Hye like this... - Don't worry. I'll handle it.
and shove her in like this.
- Come on, Jong Kook. - How about this?
- Get out. - Jong Kook.
You can throw her to the other side first.
(You too get out.)
Jong Kook. It'd be much easier if you dig a hole underneath.
Everyone should get back to your seat.
- That's really low. - He can do it.
Are you taking off your shoes for this?
(Jong Kook will do anything to pass under the bar.)
Jong Kook is serious about this.
I'm sure he can do it.
(Even just crawling under the bar seems difficult.)
- Can he do it? - That is really low.
What's the height of the bar? Is it 65cm?
- I'm not sure. - Jong Kook. Just a bit more.
Tuck your head down. Just a bit.
- They are amazing. - How can they do that?
You're good. Just keep going.
- Good. - Just a little more to go.
- Keep your posture. - You're really close.
- That's amazing. - You're almost done.
- Yes. We did it. - Slip her to the other side.
- We did it. - Yes.
(Jong Kook and Seul Hye succeed.)
- That was amazing. - You're really good.
(Did you see them? That's how you play the limbo.)
- Good job. - Jong Kook is still amazing.
- Good job. - I'd never be able to do it myself.
(Jae Jin did his best, but...)
- Did you see that? - Only you can do that, Jong Kook.
- Only Jong Kook can do it. - That was amazing.
I can't even do it by myself.
It's over.
Shall I rip your name tag off?
It may touch the bar.
(What is he doing? Is he the food thief?)
That's your mission, isn't it?
- Are you the food thief? - No, I'm not.
- Isn't this your hidden mission? - I just wanted to help you.
- I thought... - Why would you try to take it off?
- Are you on your mission? - No, I really want to help him.
- I know you are the food thief. - Hey.
- I'm not the food thief! - You're doing your mission, right?
Since when did you care about our team?
- The name tag may touch the bar. - Does it matter?
It does. I really wanted to help you.
- Are you on a mission? - No, I'm not. Really.
They can't succeed.
- The height of the bar is 65cm. - No one can do it.
(I don't think I can do this.)
Can we swap?
(What did you just say?)
Do you want me to switch the side?
- Like this? - No, I mean...
can you lift me up instead?
(Please. My cramped muscle still hurts.)
- He... - Just kidding.
He wants me to lift him up and do the limbo.
Are you serious, Jae Jin?
Let's do this.
(Jae Jin lifts Ji Hyo in his arms.)
- Jae Jin is good. - Can they make it?
- No. That's not good. - Be careful with your name tag.
Mind your head. Your head will hit the bar.
- He did it. - They are almost done.
(If he fails to pass under the bar, they will lose the game.)
(Can he really make it?)
- Slow down, Jae Jin. - Don't rush. Walk slowly.
- Just move your feet. - Slowly, Jae Jin.
- He will knock the bar over. - No.
- No. - Yes!
That's why I wanted to take your name tag off. Can you see it now?
(How did Jong Kook and Seul Hye do this?)
- That was really close. - We won.
- I thought he would succeed. - I thought so, too.
- They almost succeeded. - Where are you?
Come out, Jae Duck.
- In my opinion... - Jae Duck, come out.
Let's play "The Way This Guy Lives" this time.
That's right. You must understand...
- "Speed Quiz with a Mouth Gag". - What is a mouth gag?
All right. For this mission,
one of your team members must wear a mouth gag fashionably...
and explain the word in the card to the team mates.
Other team members must guess the answer in turn.
All right. The topic is "Classic Folktales from Around the World."
All right, let's begin. Who will wear the mouth gag?
(Everybody picks Su Won.)
Goodness.
All right. Let's sit.
- Don't look back. - Yes. We mustn't look back.
Ready, set...
("Thumbelina")
- This. - Number one?
- No. What is this? - It's a thumb.
- It's a thumb. - You know...
"Thumbelina".
Hurry up. Speak faster.
- One's nose grows like this. - "Pinocchio".
- "Pinocchio". - That's right.
This person is naked. Completely naked.
- This person wears nothing. - "The Little Mermaid"?
- "The Emperor's New Clothes". - "The Emperor's New Clothes".
Okay.
Pass.
This one wears a scarf.
- A scarf? - "Rapunzel"?
- Isn't it "Rapunzel"? - Frilled lizard?
- A wolf in the story... - I get it.
"Little Red Riding Hood Cha Cha".
No, it's not.
(His action doesn't make any sense.)
- Pass. Just pass. - All right. Pass.
This character works really hard.
- A hardworking one? - Yes.
- Is it "Kongji and Patji"? - No.
- Do you mean "Shim Chung"? - They are really tiny.
- "Jack and the Beanstalk". - No. I mean...
- Is it over already? - What's the answer?
It's "The Ant and the Grasshopper".
(My goodness.)
- "The Ant and the Grasshopper"? - You said the character works hard.
- What's wrong with you? - It didn't make any sense.
Why didn't you tell us that the characters are insects?
- You should've have said that. - What's his problem?
We thought the character was human.
He's really bad at explaining things.
- My goodness. - He's a terrible at this.
I thought the answer was "Cinderella".
- Take it easy. - Kwang Soo. Will you explain?
Explain well, Kwang Soo.
It's more fun if he's bad at this, though.
(Here comes Kwang Soo, the mouth gag expert.)
Don't worry. He'll do it badly. Kwang Soo is the food thief.
- No. We're not sure yet. - Why not?
Su Won was terrible, too.
No way. He did his best.
(I tried my best. I'm not the food thief.)
I never thought that you'd be that bad.
- Ready, set... - Tell what animal it is first.
(Kwang Soo is ready with his opened mouth.)
("The Good Brothers")
(What is that?)
Hurry up, Kwang Soo.
- What are you doing? - Is it "Scarecrow"?
(What on earth are you doing?)
There he goes again.
I'm sure that he's the food thief.
- He must be the food thief. - What is that?
- "Alice in Wonderland"? - Pass.
- That was really strange. - The topic is fairly tales.
(With a mouth gag, everyone's a food thief.)
(My gosh.)
("The Magpie Who Returned the Favor")
- It's a magpie something. - There's a thing like that?
- What are you doing? - What is it?
My leg is broken. Wait, that's not how it goes.
- "Heungbu and Nolbu"? - What is this?
That's not the correct title.
You can't pass this one.
Who's the woman that goes, "Of course"?
- What? - You know what I mean.
- Eun Hye? - It returned the favor.
"The Magpie Who Returned the Favor".
You're so dumb.
A naked person taking a bath and a lumberjack.
"A Fairy and a Woodcutter".
- "A Fairy and a Woodcutter". - "A Fairy and a Woodcutter".
- Time's up. - What are you doing?
- What's this? - "Puss in Boots".
- What is that? - Gosh.
How do you not know "The Magpie Who Returned the Favor"?
Do you know what "The Good Brothers" is then?
Of course, I do.
- Is it a real thing? - Have you not heard of it?
How do you not know this story?
I've heard of the Wright brothers, but not "The Good Brothers".
How can you not know this?
Was this how he described "The Good Brothers"?
I figured good brothers put their arms around each other's shoulders.
It's the story about a magpie ringing a bell with its head.
- Oh, is that the story? - That's the one.
What's the story about a gourd seed?
That's "Heungbu and Nolbu".
Oh, that was a swallow.
Get it together.
I thought Su Won was bad, but you're on a whole new level.
I'm sorry, Su Won.
I really didn't know.
- Su Won got three right. - He did?
- It was really hard. - What on earth was that?
Get the next game started already.
Let's get on with "Road Fighter".
("Road Fighter")
("Pillow Fight")
We'll be able to tell who the food thief is from this game.
(The person to knock the opponent off first with a pillow wins.)
- You should go. - You want me to do an all-kill?
- You should go up. - If you lose this one...
- We have our eyes on you. - I can do good.
- Only the food thief would lose. - Let's go.
Prove us wrong, Kwang Soo.
- Let's go. - I can do this.
- Let's go. - I'm watching you.
- I can do well. - This is your last chance.
- I can do good. - Hold onto the zipper.
They say Kwang Soo is stronger than he looks.
- He is strong. - You should go first.
I think you should go first.
(The leader of Sechs Kies, Ji Won, goes up against Kwang Soo.)
Watch Kwang Soo carefully.
- He's acting like he's not. - He's trying to be smart with us.
(Kwang Soo versus Ji Won)
They get one pillow each.
- Ready, - Wait.
- set... - Hold on.
(He steps down before the game even starts.)
- We didn't start yet, right? - Are you forfeiting?
- We didn't start yet. - Why can't he keep his balance?
He's acting so strange.
Wait! Is he allowed to do that?
My legs are just weak.
- Ready... - Why would a right-handed person...
stand that way, Stupid?
(Did you call me stupid?)
Please don't verbally harass him.
- Isn't that a bit harsh? - It was.
They're supposed to cheer for me.
I was just...
trying to maximize my reach.
I had a plan.
- Do as you wish. - Ready,
set, go.
(They're already weak from the start.)
Let's see how he does.
(Why you little...)
(Kwang Soo flinches.)
- Hit him. - Just hit him.
(He throws a swing.)
Duck.
(He throws a big swing after faking his flinch.)
(Ji Won swings.)
(How dare you hit me first?)
(I'm counting on you, my servant.)
Duck!
(I took a step back to take two steps further.)
subtitles ripped and synced by riri13
(Ji Won hits himself.)
(He loses balance and hits himself in the face.)
(Thanks to Ji Won's self-destruction, Kwang Soo wins.)
I told you, I'm not a food thief.
See that?
(My body's not like how it used to be.)
I was meaning to do a counter attack.
(Thanks for that.)
Ji Won looked so cool when he dodged.
- I thought I lost for a second. - That was a good dodge.
- Why did he suddenly fall down? - He's must be the food thief.
He must be.
- If not, why did he fall? - Because I was strong.
- He's acting strange. - I don't understand.
Su Won is up next.
- Ready, set, go! - Looking good.
(Input command: Move forward and attack.)
- Just swing it. - He's looking at me funny.
- Hit him. - He's tall, too.
He sure is tall.
Nice.
(Su Won is in attack mode.)
What was that?
(Replay)
(Where are you going?)
- How many times did he hit you? - Can we go again?
Let me go against him one more time.
I want to get him back.
I didn't win this one.
- It's not done yet. - That's enough.
(He got slapped by a robot with a pillow.)
You did good.
- Kwang Soo's good. - It feels like...
Jae Jin is always the one cleaning up their mess.
Oh, my back.
If you lose this one, consider our friendship over.
- Ready... - You can beat them all.
What are you doing?
Why would you...
Why would you do that? It's just a game.
That's why your back hurts.
You don't have to do that.
- You'll hurt yourself. - Just play the game.
Take it easy, Jae Jin.
- Don't hurt yourself. - Who made you like this?
Don't get yourself hurt.
- He used to be quick. - Right.
Don't say that.
Ready, set, go!
Swing the pillow.
Make him lose his balance.
What are you doing?
- That hurts. - Be careful.
(He hits him numerous times.)
- What are you doing? - What's he trying to do?
(He gets hit again.)
(Jae Jin is about to lose his balance.)
What are you doing?
- What was that? - Come on.
- Are you the food thief? - No.
- No, no. - I didn't even do anything.
He's not very enthusiastic.
- He's the food thief. - Are you?
- No, I'm not. - He's definitely the food thief.
Did you take your jacket off for that?
(Jae Jin makes Ji Won curse at him.)
Calm down.
This doesn't make sense unless he's the food thief.
But still, that was a bit harsh.
Team Seul Hye wins!
(Team Seul Hye wins.)
Lady Seul Hye will be awarded with a hint...
- and a Member Swapping Card. - Can we look at the hint as well?
- It's for her only. - Okay.
Does it say who the food thief is?
(The food thief was born in summer.)
Did you see it?
- We won. - When's your birthday, Kwang Soo?
- I was born in July. - When's your birthday?
- When's your birthday? - The birthday is the hint.
July, August, August,
- April. - April, and July.
- When's your birthday? - June.
- When's your birthday? - It's in July.
- When's your birthday? - July.
- August. - August?
Am I allowed not to use the Swapping Card?
- Of course. - You don't have to.
I won't use it, then.
Good thinking.
- You should save it for later. - That's right.
Keep it until the very last moment.
- Are you all hungry? - Yes.
We're in Icheon, home of delicious rice.
We prepared a table full of food with delicious Icheon rice.
Look at all that.
- It's waiting for us. - This is really nice.
The second round of Food Thief Race is called...
"The Servants' Drawings".
- What? - Do you see the rooms behind you?
The five servants will go in each of the rooms...
and when a door opens, the servant has to guess...
what the shown drawing is about and redraw it...
to show to the following person.
The winning team will get to enjoy the food we prepared.
The losing team will be given rice only.
With that rice,
you'll go over to the neighboring villages...
and will have to ask the villagers for six kinds of side dishes.
- We have to win. - I don't want to do that.
You will have to ask the villagers for six kinds of side dishes.
I don't eat side dishes.
- I never eat side dishes. - I dip my rice in water.
I don't want side dishes.
Please decide on the order of the servants.
Jae Jin is really good at drawing. But even then,
- there's a time limit. - That's right.
It's not easy to emphasize the characteristics under a time limit.
That's right. You have to draw it quickly and concisely.
It should be in this order.
The start is the most important.
I'll go first, then.
(The order of the servants)
The theme of the given words will be about landmarks.
- Ready... - Landmarks?
(The game has started.)
(The first servant has a critical responsibility.)
- One. - Two, three.
- I'm not good at drawing. - Four.
Five.
(Jong Kook shows it to Jae Seok.)
It's a landmark.
(Welcome to my artistic world.)
Do you get it?
(What is this drawing?)
It's not in Korea, is it? What is that?
Wait, I didn't get a good look.
I made a mistake.
- I didn't get a good look at it. - Take a look at his drawing.
- Take a look at his drawing. - What is this supposed to be?
One, two, three, four,
- This is a Korean landmark? - Five.
(Take a look at his drawing.)
(There's a tower in the middle of the mountains.)
- Okay. - You have to start drawing now.
- What do you think that is? - I thought it was N Seoul Tower.
It's a tower in the mountains.
(He's feeling artistic.)
Is that a finger?
Oh, gosh.
Is he giving me the middle finger?
Gosh.
I'm really sorry about this.
One, two, three.
It looks like there's a ring on a finger.
Three, four, five. Time's up.
(Take a look, Lady Seul Hye.)
What on earth is that?
- An alien? - It's a landmark.
- I think I got it. - Really?
This is the hint.
That's the hint?
(It's all up to Seul Hye's imagination now.)
It could be a Korean landmark.
Two, three, four, five. Please say the answer.
Is it N Seoul Tower?
(Is it?)
N Seoul Tower.
Is it correct?
Are you sure?
(Our lady did it.)
- Is she correct? - What?
How can she get it right?
- How did she know? - How did she?
How did she get it right?
It is N Seoul Tower.
- Is this N Seoul Tower? - Yes.
(Great job, Seul Hye.)
- This is ridiculous! - This is!
- I thought you were wrong. - It's unbelievable.
How did you get it correct?
I drew it like this and she got the correct answer.
(How did she think of N Seoul Tower with this drawing?)
I thought it was Kkumdori, the mascot of Daejeon.
I thought it was the statue...
in Brazil.
- She got it correct. - I can't believe it.
Seul Hye, you're incredible.
I don't think you're doing your duty properly.
I'm not the food thief.
How could you help her guess?
She got the other ones correct, too.
(Who could be the food thief?)
It's the second question. Ready,
set.
One, two...
(Though Jong Kook described some critical points of Colosseum...)
- What on earth did you draw? - It's a landmark.
(Jae Seok, Seok Jin and Kwang Soo ruins the drawings.)
- Remember it's a landmark. - A landmark?
What could it be?
(The drawing is no longer that of Colosseum.)
What is this? Wait.
Sorry. This is exactly what Seok Jin drew.
Is it Gwangan Bridge?
(She fails the second question.)
- What is it? - What's that?
- Draw them well. - Look at Seok Jin.
(They're narrowing down the suspects.)
Seok Jin, concentrate.
- We need to get at least two. - Okay.
This is the last question.
We must get the correct answer this time.
- Ready. - It's a famous landmark.
It's a landmark.
Oh, this one.
This is the one.
I'll start drawing this one. Wait for a moment.
He thinks we can get the correct answer.
- It must be easy. - It must be famous.
Seok Jin, concentrate.
(The first drawing is important.)
Ready,
(He gets ready.)
Start!
Two, three, four...
(What does his drawing look like?)
(Haha is the second runner to get Jong Kook's drawing.)
- What is this? - I see.
- You can figure it out, right? - Wait.
- Think it over. - It's a landmark.
I figured it out. You wanted to draw the buildings but they look weird.
You should draw it in the limited time.
- Let's describe it well. - Describe?
(After seeing the buildings and the statue, what will Haha draw?)
Five.
Jae Seok, you know what it is, don't you?
I see.
I have to describe it well.
Describe it well. Emphasize the special points.
Do it well.
I should draw it well.
(I trust you, Jae Seok.)
- One, two... - All right.
(He starts to draw.)
Wait a minute.
(Sung Hoon laughs.)
(What is Jae Seok's drawing like?)
- Wait. - Jae Seok.
- Seok Jin. - It's a squid.
It's a squid.
- What on earth is that? - It's a landmark.
You should look at this part. This is the key point.
(It's the Statue of Liberty.)
(But it looks like the statue of a baby octopus.)
Look carefully before you start to draw.
You should not explain it, Jae Seok.
(Observation time is over.)
(The next person is no other than Seok Jin, the terrible artist.)
(We're done for once again.)
Five.
(They laugh.)
Now, show it.
Look at this carefully.
What is this?
(What should I look at carefully?)
- What's this? - Look carefully.
This person is...
- Look carefully. - You're not supposed to explain it.
- I know it but I can't explain it. - Look carefully.
I...
Pick out the key point!
(We're doomed!)
My goodness.
(Where did we go wrong?)
This looks like a dumpling.
- What should I do? - One,
two...
(You can do it, Kwang Soo.)
Five. Stop. Drop the pen.
(It's a disaster.)
Is this a landmark?
Seul Hye, take it easy and think about it.
Be quiet.
(The only thing you can guess is that someone is holding something.)
(Will Seul Hye be able to work her magic again?)
The Statue of Liberty?
(Okay)
Is the answer the Statue of Liberty?
(It's the correct answer.)
(Seul Hye is the legend of interpreting drawings.)
This is unbelievable.
(It's chaos.)
- It's correct. - There you go.
(They are shocked at her imagination.)
How did she get the correct answer?
- She did it. - Awesome.
It's the correct answer.
(How could she think of the Statue of Liberty out of this?)
- This is ridiculous. - Incredible.
(I'm this kind of a girl.)
(Ji Hyo is puzzled.)
How did you figure it out with this?
(Escaping the hazard of Seok Jin,)
(Seul Hye worked it out with her imagination.)
The first drawing is the most important.
It's for sure. Don't try to draw it well.
Just describe the key points.
(This is Team Ji Hyo's plan.)
The key word for Sechs Kies is...
"occupation".
This must be difficult.
Leave people out of the drawings.
Ready,
- Don't draw people. - set...
Draw something they use.
- It can be easier. - You're right.
It can be easy.
- This can be easier. - You can...
Jae Jin is so good at drawing pictures.
I'm doomed.
I can think of something I would draw.
(Maybe my brain is broken.)
Something like this?
- Well... - How can I describe it?
- Start drawing. - Draw it simple.
- Ready... - Wait, wait.
I have no idea.
- Just point out what's important. - I want to draw it but...
- Three. - No, wait. What are you doing?
Wait a moment, please.
It takes too long.
(His brain stops temporarily.)
What are you doing, Jae Jin?
Let's do it quickly.
It's not good to draw too much.
(I have to remain calm to survive.)
- Okay. - One. Start!
- Okay. - This is terrible.
(What does Jae Jin think a model's key points are?)
(Jong Kook laughs.)
Five.
(What should I do?)
You ruined it, didn't you? What is it?
This is it.
(It's just a person.)
(What is this unidentified creature?)
- It's an occupation. - Gosh.
- It's an occupation. - Wait.
You have to make up this occupation.
I know.
(It's just a naked body. How can he find it out?)
Does he have to make up that occupation?
How could he draw only a person?
We should've not placed Jae Jin first.
(The first runner ruined everything.)
I'll draw it the same anyway.
I'll start.
(He hesitates.)
One, two...
(Haha bursts into laughter.)
What is this?
(Now, it is tossed to Sung Hoon.)
Let me see.
- What is it? - What is this?
Gosh, what did you do?
- Well... - What does it mean?
- Jae Jin drew it like this. - Two, three...
- Ji Won has to guess it. - What could it be?
- Goodness, what can it be? - This is impossible.
It's not my fault. I copied what he drew.
Is this an occupation?
What is it?
Poor you.
(How did a model become this skinny?)
- How can you figure it out? - Four,
five.
He's poor at drawing, too.
(It'll be tossed to the last runner, Ji Won.)
I exactly copied it.
(What does his exact copy look like?)
My goodness. It's hard to figure it out.
- Did you say you copied it? - Yes.
Is he a scarecrow or what?
(This is the butterfly effect caused by Jae Jin.)
(Ji Won is creating its job with his imagination.)
Four, five. Stop.
Ji Won can't draw.
It has changed completely.
(He added something near the left hand.)
Ji Won made this up just now.
This is totally different.
(Can Ji Hyo also work a miracle with her imagination?)
An athlete.
(It's not correct.)
What did you think it was?
I thought it was a shot putter.
(This is my fault.)
Was it a model? It was difficult.
- Jae Jin, let me see yours. - You should draw a runway.
Su Won, look at that.
Gosh, that is an alien.
(It sure looks like an alien.)
(I was a fool to believe you're the ace.)
(It doesn't look like a model at all.)
- Was it a model? - I think it looks like an alien.
(We learn that the first step is crucial.)
- Did you see what Jae Jin drew? - We have to imagine it.
(I didn't become the first runner to be treated like this.)
(They change the order.)
I think Ji Won should go first.
(Ji Won and Jae Jin switch places.)
Jae Jin is flustered.
It was funny.
(Did he plan everything as the food thief?)
Ready, set...
(They get ready for the second question.)
(If they fail this time, they should give up this abundant meal.)
Start.
(The answer to this critical question is a flight attendant.)
This is easy. This is too easy.
It must be easy.
I'll start drawing.
(You can just draw a plane for this job.)
Three,
four...
(The drawing is about to take off.)
- I'm done. - Wasn't it too long?
(He described it with a plane and a person in a nice skirt.)
What does the person mean?
How can they guess it correctly?
One...
(Did Jae Jin get the hang of it this time?)
Four, five.
Oh my.
- Show us first. Just show us. - We need to figure it out.
- Right. Right. That's spot on. - What is that?
- In 3, 4, 5. - Is it a plane? What is that?
Show them.
(Is this correct?)
You won't figure it out.
(Can it be a stingray?)
- What on earth is this? - I don't have any clue.
They started questioning what it is.
It doesn't even look like a shark.
(Su Won is agonized.)
- Hey, I think we won. - Seriously?
- I have a feeling that we won. - Didn't they say it was easy?
Su Won, you should at least start.
It doesn't matter even if he starts.
(He starts to draw.)
Two, three, four...
(Laughing)
(His magical drawing brings smiles to people who see it.)
- You guys are last. - Hold on.
What is this? Is this a fish?
Somehow there was something that looked like this.
(Plane became sujebi.)
(A person with a skirt became a naked person dancing.)
You can't figure it out, can you?
How can you possibly know what it is from this drawing?
(His drawing is absurd to understand.)
When you look at the drawing, think about occupations.
(There's a cloud over their heads.)
(What they need is a miracle from Jae Duck.)
(The way he uses his pen makes Kwang Soo think...)
I'll bet my everything...
that we will win.
(Finally the drawing is revealed.)
I don't think I can look at it. I'm scared.
It scares me.
- Don't you feel nervous? - I'm too scared to show her.
(What kind of drawing did Jae Duck come up with?)
He drew something similar to a wine opener.
(He presents it.)
We won.
(Is it the drawing without any embellishment?)
Did you draw as it is?
- Almost. It's very close. - Almost?
It's almost an exact copy.
(This is the exact copy?)
- I mean he drew well... - This is challenging. Seriously.
- You can figure it out, though. - Sure. Sure.
(An alien invades the Earth with a spacecraft.)
My gosh. What on earth is this?
(I'm speechless.)
The drawing shows a job?
I'm sure the drawing describes a job.
Think carefully.
Think who would have that sort of job around us.
It's a job?
I'm sure the job exists.
(Something weird floats in the air, and there's a strange person.)
(Can she figure out it's stewardess?)
In 1, 2, 3.
A hunter.
- My gosh. - Goodness.
(Team Ji Hyo will face the penalty.)
Come here.
(Team Seul Hye wins.)
- Okay. - Let's eat.
- Let's eat. - Let's have the meal.
- We won. - Let's eat.
- What was that? - Get over here.
Who was it?
- The answer was a flight attendant. - Stewardess. It's stewardess.
That's what it was supposed to be?
- You drew a stewardess? - It's a stewardess.
This was supposed to be a flight attendant.
(Was it you?)
I see. It was a flight attendant.
(You know what you did wrong.)
I thought... I thought it was a shark.
This doesn't make sense?
(Is Su Won the food thief?)
(A hearty meal is served.)
- Thank you. - He did really well.
(It's a meal with rice from Icheon given to the winning team.)
- Thank you for the food. - Thank you.
- Thank you. - This is all because of you.
(It's good to be winners.)
- Seriously. - I didn't know we would win.
You did really well.
The rice is amazing.
- The texture is very different. - Rice from Icheon is so tasty.
This is indeed delicious.
(They enjoy their lunch in Icheon. It is known for good quality rice.)
- I can taste the difference. - Rice from Icheon is very good.
(They enjoy their meal with side dishes. How about the losing team?)
- We need to hold it? - Do we need to carry it around?
(We only get a bowl of rice?)
(They'll have to enjoy the rice without side dishes on the street.)
The rice smells so good.
We can eat this, right?
Take your chopsticks.
(It's as if he's eating his sadness away.)
Why don't we start over there?
(They must get 6 side dishes, but they can get 2 from each house.)
What a coincidence. There are people outside.
- They are making kimchi. - They must be making kimchi.
- Hello. - Hi.
- What are you doing? - Is it soy sauce?
Sikhye. They are making sikhye.
- Sikhye. - Could we get some?
Sikhye isn't a side dish. It's a dessert.
I eat my rice with sikhye.
(He's already trying to cheat his way out.)
- They are making a lot of sikhye. - That's a lot.
- Hello. - Hi.
- Hello. - You are all celebrities.
- We have a mission to complete. - Yes?
If we find the most generous person in this town,
- SBS will give you a cash prize. - Really?
(SBS will give you a cash prize.)
- Stop cheating. You are cheating. - It's not true?
Hello.
We need to...
have a meal. We didn't eat at all today.
I can give you rice. Follow me.
- Side dishes, please. - Can we have some side dishes?
- Please give us side dishes. - We need to...
- Look at that. - You have the best kimchi in town.
I can eat the whole bowl with just kkakdugi.
- This is her house. - We'll wait here.
The people in this town are so generous.
They are known for their generosity.
(Cheering)
We only need two.
(Side dishes descend upon them.)
(Start your praise. Here comes the side dishes.)
- Just give us two of them. - My gosh.
- We'll use chopsticks. - I want dried seaweed.
Thank you so much.
(They can only choose two side dishes from each house.)
Okay. Hold on. Let me put it here.
Thank you so much.
We love you.
Thank you for the food.
- I chose two. - I did, too.
- What is this? - I chose deodeok and kimchi.
It's balloon flower root salad.
- How about the dried seaweed? - It's not allowed.
It's not allowed? I see.
(They successfully eat two side dishes.)
Thank you so much.
- Thank you so much. - Thank you for the food.
(We appreciate helping them despite their sudden begging.)
Take care.
- Let's go now. - She is so nice.
- We can just eat it now. - Yes.
Here?
How can you let us eat on the street?
- We are already begging for food. - Come on.
We are already paupers.
(They are a group of attractive beggars.)
Because the rice is good, it's still tasty just with kimchi.
I think she grilled the balloon flower roots.
- Let's get going. - Let's go.
It's so delicious.
I might need more rice.
- We need more rice. - We don't have enough rice.
I can eat and digest while I'm walking.
Hello.
You are about to make kimchi.
Look at all the Chinese cabbages in the front garden.
We have a bowl of rice from Icheon,
but we don't have side dishes. Could you give us two side dishes?
It's kimchi.
(Of course. She brings out gimjang kimchi.)
- I like gimjang kimchi. - I'm fine with it.
Is it spring onion kimchi?
- Didn't you eat kimchi just now? - That was geotjeori.
You can't eat the same side dish.
That's not geotjeori. It's gimjang kimchi.
Excuse me, isn't it gimjang kimchi?
- Yes, right. It's gimjang kimchi. - This is fully fermented.
- This one is fermented. - That's right.
- Geotjeori is not the same kimchi. - Exactly.
Thank you so much.
Thank you for the food.
That looks delicious.
- Are you only eating kimchi? - This is really good.
This is so tasty.
We can also get one of the cabbages over there...
- and if we only have ssamjang... - We can eat it with ssamjang.
That will give us another side dish.
- That's right. - I think that counts.
- Of course. - Right.
How did you think of this?
- Eating it by itself is also good. - Yes, that's right.
(They are eating three dishes out of cabbages. It's a cabbage trip.)
This cabbage is priceless.
The cabbage itself is sweet.
- The cabbage is amazing. - There're even garlics in ssamjang.
This is delicious.
It's indeed tasty.
This cabbage leaf is crunchy.
(Why don't you let the cameramen to taste some?)
- What? - Give some for the cameramen.
You need to work for it.
You can each get two.
You're mean.
Did you say I'm mean?
Did you just find that out?
He's known to be mean.
Excuse me.
By any chance, do you have different types of kimchi?
- I have gat kimchi. - You have gat kimchi?
- I have gat kimchi. - Really?
Let's go and eat some gat kimchi.
We need to taste gat kimchi.
Look at that gat kimchi.
(Divine gat kimchi is on the move.)
- That looks delicious. - I bet gat kimchi is amazing.
I can even smell it from here.
Do you have disposable plates?
(Ji Hyo comes to escort gat kimchi outside.)
This looks savory.
(How wonderful.)
Look at this gat kimchi.
- This looks really delicious. - It does, indeed.
I can even smell it from here.
(He takes a bite.)
It's tasty.
(It even impresses Su Won as it is the taste of rich kimchi.)
This is incredible.
(It is completely delicious.)
- It's absolutely savory. - It is, isn't it?
(It's absolutely tasty.)
- Really. - This is totally different.
I happened to have this, too.
My gosh. Thank you so much.
- What is it? - It's pickled garlic.
- That's it. - This ends our penalty.
Your kimchi is top notch.
This kimchi is the best.
Here's gat kimchi. She said she can give us more if we any rice left.
(Gat kimchi and pickled garlic are the perfect combination.)
Gat kimchi is amazing.
- This is really tasty gat kimchi. - You didn't get to eat, right?
There isn't much left.
Can I have a spoon of your rice?
(Mean Ji Won steals a spoon of rice.)
- Do you still have some rice left? - Yes.
- This is my second bowl. - You are eating another one?
With gat kimchi, I can finish a bowl of rice with no problem.
- This is amazing. Try it. - Right.
Really.
- It's not what I expected. - It's the tastiest kimchi ever.
- You, too? - Isn't it different?
The shape is the same.
It's not as thick as other ones.
(Ji Hyo shares gat kimchi with the cameramen.)
(And a man stares at her.)
(Is someone looking staring at me?)
Isn't it good?
Ji Hyo, can you give me a bite, too?
I want to taste the kimchi you give me.
(I want to taste the kimchi you give me.)
There isn't much food, so please help yourself.
Please give me a bite.
Here, take a bite. It's really delicious.
Should I also hold a camera to be fed?
(Is someone on a secret mission?)
She'll give you a bite if you close your eyes.
- May I get a bite? - Give Jae Jin a bite first.
I'll just eat it.
- We have to return them? - Yes, you finished the food.
(Something seems strange.)
(The two look very suspicious.)
- Thank you for the food. - Thank you.
Let's get sikhye for dessert.
- Sir? - Do we get one each?
(They get some sikhye for dessert.)
May I take it out?
- They're all the same, so take any. - Okay.
- We'll give you sikhye for free. - Thank you.
Thank you, Ma'am.
- You're very generous. - Cheers.
- Cheers. - Is this place famous for sikhye?
(He links arms with her and takes a sip.)
- Enjoy it. - Is it made with Icheon rice?
Yes, it is.
(He smiles.)
(Why is he smiling to the camera?)
(Su Won smiles because he's the food thief.)
"You're the food thief."
"Accomplish your hidden mission and win 100 bags of rice."
"If you succeed, you can donate rice under your name."
"If not, you're punished."
(The mission is to reveal Jae Jin's abdomen.)
Jae Jin.
- Really? - Let me see.
(He pretends to check Jae Jin's microphone.)
- Is it okay? - Yes.
You should put it under your shirt.
(The producer approaches him after the first game.)
(The hidden mission is to link arms with the lady and drink.)
Thank you, Ma'am.
(He looks for an opportunity.)
(He succeeds his mission.)
Thank you for giving us delicious sikhye.
- It's so delicious. - Really?
It's perfect to finish with sikhye after eating rice and gat kimchi.
I'm glad you enjoyed it.
- Thank you, Ma'am. - Thank you.
Thank you.
(Su Won of Team Sechs Kies is the food thief.)
- Did you get any food? - I had a bowl of rice.
Team Running Man won Round Two.
- Seul Hye gets a hint. - Is that so?
The hint will tell you who the food thief is.
- Okay. - Confirm that it's not me.
- Me, neither. - You'll narrow down the suspects.
Seul Hye, you'll find out that I'm definitely not the food thief.
(Whom will Seul Hye choose?)
(He's nervous that it might be him.)
- What is it? - You should apologize to me.
She suddenly looked up at Kwang Soo.
- What's the hint? - I'm so curious.
What is she trying to do?
(Let me think.)
What is she thinking? She's looking at us.
I'll exchange a servant.
- You'll exchange someone? - Yes.
(Did she find out about me?)
- Jae Seok. - Jae Seok?
- Kwang Soo. - Me, too?
(Both of you are out.)
- Seul Hye, I'm really not it. - I'm not it, either.
- My goodness. - I'm really not the thief.
- Seul Hye. - I didn't do anything suspicious.
Jae Seok and Kwang Soo, please move to the other team.
(There's a certain letter in the food thief's last name.)
This is so frustrating.
- You're the thief, aren't you? - No, it's you.
- Isn't it you? - I think the hint said it's you.
- My goodness. - Gosh.
Sung Hoon, come this way.
(The new servants are...)
(Sung Hoon?)
- Come this way. - See? I'm not the thief.
- You're definitely a suspect. - I told you that I wasn't.
Okay, we heard you.
- Ji Hyo. - What is it?
(Why were we selected?)
(Both of their last names contain the letter O.)
- Hey. - What?
I'm not the thief.
- What's wrong? - I made a mistake.
- You did? - I made a mistake.
Wait, may I exchange the members again?
She can't exchange again.
- It's not allowed. - I got confused.
She got confused.
- I got confused. - Thank you for taking Su Won.
(He looks nervous.)
Thank you so much for taking Su Won to your team.
(Team Running Man and Team Sechs Kies)
(Su Won, the food thief, is on Team Running Man.)
You'll play "Toy Hammer with My Lady" for the final round.
"Toy Hammer with My Lady".
("Toy Hammer with My Lady"?)
The two teams will alternate between attack and defense...
to catch the taggers.
The taggers of the attacking team are a servant and the lady.
Only the lady can eliminate the members by popping their balloon.
There's a time limit for each attack.
The taggers can attack the other team only while...
the remaining four servants are doing a mission.
The team that eliminates more members wins.
(Who will win the game?)
Let's spread out.
(Team Running Man attacks while Team Sechs Kies defends.)
What's going on?
What's the ice for?
I don't want ice in this weather.
(Cone Sitting)
(Hula Hoop)
(Barefoot on Ice)
(Leg Split)
(Endure these 4 activities.)
There you go.
- You should do this one. - He's good at it.
- Wait a minute. - He can last for two hours.
Does it feel good?
Gosh, this may damage my health.
I can do it, but it's probably unhealthy.
I'll sit on the cone. I think I can do it.
(Taggers)
(The defending team goes to hide.)
There's no place to hide.
(What is he doing with the basin?)
(He goes under the basin.)
(Ji Won disappears.)
Gosh, it's way too small.
(He hides himself under a bigger basin.)
(He hides himself completely.)
(While Ji Won is hiding under a basin,)
(Kwang Soo hurries up to the mountain.)
They won't be able to find me here. Please get closer.
(The balloon pops.)
(Kwang Soo is out.)
(The balloon pops and leaves flour on his helmet.)
Wait a minute.
Sir?
(Kwang Soo is very unlucky.)
This is unfair, don't you think?
(Now, he'll look even more suspicious.)
This is not what I meant.
(One member is already out.)
We'll start after 10 seconds.
In 10, 9, 8...
- Go, you can eliminate all. - Seven...
(How many of Team Sechs Kies will Team Running Man eliminate?)
Start.
We must catch them quickly.
The game started.
Can you help and hold me up?
- In one... - Be careful.
(Haha starts to sit on the cone.)
Three.
(I must endure it.)
(Gosh)
You must endure it, Haha.
(Why don't you try it?)
(He moans in pain.)
(For Haha who endures the pain of sitting on a cone,)
(Jong Kook is out to attack the other team.)
(Haha, hold it a little longer.)
- Does it hurt? - Haha, try to endure it.
(I can't do it.)
(The first endurance mission is over.)
We're in trouble.
(Sung Hoon starts the hula hoop.)
You're doing well.
(There's no time to waste.)
Where are they hiding?
They'll find us here easily.
All of you, sit down. Goodness.
- Why are you standing? - You were standing, too.
My goodness.
The color of your balloon is too bright.
It's too easy to notice it from afar.
What else can I do?
You're the one who followed me here.
- Goodness. - Do you know that?
(Fidgeting)
How long will this last?
There's no oxygen in here.
(He's the only one hiding in the forest.)
I'm getting sleepy.
(He's so bored of waiting that he gets sleepy.)
- It's falling down. - Be careful.
Gosh, the time is up again.
(There are only two activities left.)
This is all I have to do, right?
I'm exhausted.
(Hopefully, Seok Jin endures it.)
How can I stand here for a long time?
(Please hang in there a little longer.)
- Stay close. - I hear the bells.
Sit down.
(Did they spot us?)
(They're close to being spotted.)
Stay hiding.
(The tagger with a toy hammer is getting closer.)
(If she finds them, they're in big trouble.)
She found us.
(Here's Seul Hye.)
Don't do it, Seul Hye.
- No, Seul Hye. - I found you.
(Ji Hyo escapes.)
Seul Hye.
- Please, Seul Hye. - No.
(She's determined to eliminate him.)
Don't do it.
(Jae Seok is out.)
- Why did you do it, Seul Hye? - Gosh.
- Jong Kook! - Ji Hyo.
- Run away. - Jong Kook.
(Let's chase after Ji Hyo.)
(Meanwhile, Ji Hyo makes it out of the forest...)
(and goes to hide near the houses.)
(I should be safe here.)
Where did she go?
(Did I scare you?)
(5 minutes ago)
Run!
Oh, gosh!
Where are you?
(She called for Jong Kook's help.)
She's running over there.
(Jong Kook caught Ji Hyo running down.)
(I'm on...)
(my way...)
(to see you.)
She's over here!
Come quick!
Jong Kook! Wait for me!
Where are you?
I followed her...
all the way here.
- Gosh. - Jong Kook.
- I caught someone, too. - Really?
- Where? - There's more.
(Ji Hyo is finally out.)
(Only Jae Duck, Ji Won and Jae Jin remain.)
How long has it been?
(Servant Seok Jin goes barefoot in this cold weather.)
It's 8 minutes and 40 seconds. That's pretty good, isn't it?
It is.
I'll try to make it to the 10-minute mark.
- You're so brave. - I know, right?
You can do it, Seok Jin.
- It's starting to get to me. - You're almost there.
(I'm here, too.)
(Kwang Soo splashes water on his feet.)
(You got me.)
- That was mean. - I'm sorry.
- Hey! - I'm really sorry.
- That's not right. - Why'd you do that?
- My feet are freezing. - Do you want to quit?
(Barefeet on Ice is over.)
- You did good. - You lasted for so long.
(Only one mission remains.)
(He's as stiff as a robot.)
Oh, gosh.
(He looks like he's ready to give up already.)
Hold on for just a little longer.
I'm almost there.
(Jong Kook spots Jae Jin on a container.)
(He has nowhere to go.)
(I told you it's dangerous outside.)
(He doesn't know what to do.)
(He makes his last effort.)
(He jumps off the roof.)
(He runs away.)
It's so cold.
Oh, gosh.
(He's making a run.)
(He's trying to get as far away as possble from Jong Kook.)
(Jong Kook is after him.)
(Jong Kook knows where his prey is headed.)
(The second place of hiding is...)
(the sewer.)
Hide.
(Where did you go?)
(You won't be able to find me.)
(Lady Seul Hye is on a search as well.)
(He's determined not to get caught.)
His foot's coming off.
(Servant Su Won has reached his limit.)
Haha.
It's not off.
(If he fails this mission, they'll run out of time to attack.)
(Which servant will last longer?)
Oh, gosh.
(Her stamina is plummeting as the race continues.)
(I just need to hold on for just a little longer.)
(Jong Kook predicted Jae Jin's route.)
(He got spotted.)
Seul Hye!
(Over here, Lady.)
Over here! Seul Hye!
(This is a brutal sight.)
(I can't get caught like this.)
I got him.
Where is he?
(Thanks to Servant Jong Kook's hard work,)
(Jae Jin is out.)
We got him.
Are you okay?
(I guess this is the end.)
Let me get that.
You hid really well though.
Good job.
I almost couldn't find you.
Why did I get caught?
- How did you know? - I didn't.
(At the same moment, Su Won's mission came to an end.)
(The last mission is over.)
- Did Seok Jin win? - You did good.
- Seok Jin won, right? - You did good.
(Team Seul Hye's turn to attack is over.)
The attack is over.
(Knock, knock. Anyone there?)
(Is it over?)
(Servant Ji Won managed to survive until the end.)
I couldn't hear you in there.
(Only Jae Duck and Ji Won remain.)
(4 people are out with only 2 remaining.)
- We have to win this one. - I know.
It's all your fault.
You're out, too.
- Why is everything my fault? - You got me out.
(It's always your fault.)
Kwang Soo is the food thief for sure.
I understand why you might think that,
but I went all the way into the woods not to get caught.
It's time for Team Seul Hye's...
defence.
Where are you going to hide?
Where did they hide last time?
- They were gathered over there. - We should go into the woods.
We should hide somewhere where nobody can find us.
(If more than 2 people survive, Team Seul Hye wins.)
We have to catch more than five, Jae Jin.
Don't worry, Jae Seok.
Don't care about Jong Kook.
- Let's go! - You know what I mean, right?
I'll make a monkey sound if I spot someone.
How?
(He imitates a monkey.)
I see.
Can't you just call us over like a normal human being?
You could just say, "Over here!"
Just call her over.
Just a suggestion.
Doesn't the monkey sound just give away where you are?
(Let me do this my way.)
Just do as you like, Jae Jin.
If we don't manage to win,
- everything will come to nothing. - We can do this.
We can do this.
(Ji Hyo and Jae Jin have to catch them while others are on missions.)
("Toy Hammer with My Lady")
In 5, 4, 3, 2, 1.
Start!
(Jae Seok sits on a cone as they start.)
(He's in pain.)
Oh, goodness.
(The pain doubles and triples.)
(He can't stand it any more.)
What are you doing?
Already?
It almost went in.
I'm sorry about this.
- That was close. - This is too hard.
It almost came out of your neck.
I know.
This is difficult.
(Jae Duck is up next after Jae Seok.)
(Please hold on, my fellow servants.)
(He spots a prey.)
There's one over there.
(Who's the first person they found?)
(It's Seok Jin, of course.)
What?
(He runs after him.)
Who is that?
(A monkey is coming after me.)
Jae Duck. Wait, it's Jae Jin.
(Jae Jin will lure him towards Ji Hyo.)
You don't have the hammer.
(He tries to escape.)
(I'm too tired now.)
(Seok Jin gets caught.)
Sorry, Seok Jin.
- Don't be. - We got him.
(Seok Jin is out.)
(His work is done today.)
(While Ji Hyo and Jae Jin are working their strategy...)
You can do it, Jae Duck.
Jae Duck's in the zone.
He's about to break the world record.
This could go in the Guinness Book of Records.
Give them a call right now.
I'm sorry, but could I have some water?
You can drink water while doing that?
- Give me some water. - This is good.
Call the people of Guinness Book of Records.
- I wonder if I can do this. - Don't go too close.
(Thanks to Jae Duck's great work,)
(Sung Hoon gets caught.)
Why is he so good?
(Meanwhile, Sung Hoon is caught.)
There you go. Throw the bottle away.
(I've still got it.)
- Is this a talent show? - I can do this.
Way to go.
(While everyone is trying their best to achieve victory...)
(He's thinking.)
I don't need to win today, though.
I just need to do the mission, right?
(10 minutes ago, the food thief saw the staff members in secret.)
I can't do that.
(The last mission is hitting Jong Kook in the back of his head.)
(He will get 100 bags of Icheon rice if he succeeds this mission.)
(The person he has to do the mission on...)
(is the man who only lives on chicken breasts.)
Should I just get myself caught?
(Why aren't they after me?)
(There's a monkey wandering around to catch his prey.)
(This mountain monkey is after balloons filled with flour.)
(He's a monkey who wants to be...)
(the leopard of Icheon.)
(The monkey is lurking around.)
Did you catch any, Jae Jin?
(It smells like servants.)
There's no time.
(He hears something.)
(The monkey cries again.)
(I hear a monkey.)
I hear the monkey!
(The monkey finds a prey.)
(It's Haha.)
Hold on, Jae Jin.
- You were hiding in there? - Calm down.
- Haha. - How did you know I was in here?
- Let me hit you. - You're amazing.
(Ji Hyo and Jae Jin are perfect partners.)
- I'll come down. - You're stalling, aren't you?
(The balloon pops.)
(Haha is out.)
Is it over now?
How did they know I was in there?
(The monkey is on a rampage.)
There he is!
(Running)
(You can't outrun...)
(a monkey.)
(Energetic Jae Jin fiercely chases after Su Won.)
Great! You almost got him!
- You got him! - You made it!
- Who is it? - It's Su Won.
Great. Go, Ji Hyo!
Ji Hyo!
- Great job. - Isn't it over?
- Done! - It's Ji Hyo.
(Ji Hyo pops the balloon.)
(Su Won is out.)
Ji Hyo! Ji Hyo!
Ji Hyo! Great.
- We made it! - I have a cramp.
We have one more to go.
(If Team Ji Hyo catches one more, they win.)
(I have a bad feeling right now.)
(They are waiting in ambush.)
(A team running out of time versus a team wanted by a monkey)
(Ji Hyo is near the hole in which Seul Hye is hiding.)
(She hears the bells.)
(Will Seul Hye be caught by Ji Hyo?)
(Ji Hyo passes by.)
(Ji Hyo misses Seul Hye.)
(She's scared to death.)
(Jae Duck's hula hoop show is over.)
- It hurts. - You're doing just fine.
- It hurts. - It's all right.
- It's okay. You can do it. - With this...
I learned some magic from the internet.
- What is it? - Come here and take a look.
(Seok Jin is curious.)
- And? - Now, look inside.
(Drenched)
Jae Seok, good job!
Thank you so much, Jae Seok!
(I can't get mad here, right?)
- Jae Seok, that was so helpful. - Really?
You're right. This helps you endure longer.
Isn't it funny? I saw this on the internet.
I think I'll be frostbitten.
- You won't. That's not true. - No way.
(What do you mean it's not true?)
Really?
(The last runner Kwang Soo will try Leg Split.)
Kwang Soo, let me hold it.
(This is the best mission for the tall Kwang Soo.)
- Good luck. - Okay.
I'm sure he'll make it. Good.
Wow, Kwang Soo.
(If he gives up, the time is up.)
Did you find anything?
(Where on earth are they hiding?)
This is a dead end.
(I'm right here in front of you.)
(Will she be able to survive?)
(Or will they be able to find her?)
(Or will they hold out until the time runs out?)
(How much longer should I stay here?)
(Here comes the hunting duo.)
(I found her!)
(He makes monkey sounds.)
(That sound is creepier than the bell sound.)
Where is she? What's going on?
What happened? Where are you?
- Gosh! - Did you get her?
When does the time run out?
I thought time would be up if I stayed here like this.
Turn around.
I'm sorry, Seul Hye.
(Another balloon bursts.)
The flour is all over me.
(Seul Hye is out as well.)
(What a scary pair.)
Team Ji Hyo won...
the last round.
Ji Hyo!
- Ji Hyo and Jae Duck! - Jae Duck!
- No, it's Jae Jin. - Jae Jin.
- Kwang Soo. - Jae Duck.
You did a great job.
You were a perfect duo.
- It was terrific. - It was so...
(There's one person who's nervous.)
(It's the food thief, Su Won.)
I can't hit him.
(The last mission is to hit the back of Jong Kook's head.)
(I do not have much time left.)
(He's holding the toy hammer.)
Team Ji Hyo won this round.
(Now...)
(is...)
(the chance.)
- Ji Hyo! - Good job.
(Su Won hits Jong Kook.)
- They were so good. - Thank you.
(It's hard to read his face.)
- Good work. - He hit my head with this hammer.
He hit me and said, "Thank you".
What was that? Are you out of your mind?
I'm the food thief!
(What? What on earth is going on here?)
What?
It's not the time yet. Why did you make it public?
- It's Su Won. - Su Won!
(Poor Su Won, it's your mistake.)
- All right. - I think he confessed because...
he made a mistake earlier.
- That's not right. - Are you sure?
I think it's his mistake.
(He pretends to be a robot when things are unfavorable.)
- I think it's his mistake... - Look at Su Won.
He seems to feel bad now.
- That's not true. - He just sighed.
- Was it your mistake? - No, it wasn't.
The final winner...
It will be so funny if it's Su Won.
The winner of the Food Thief Race is Team Ji Hyo.
(Team Ji Hyo is the final winner.)
- And... - We did it.
I'm sure you were all curious about who the food thief was.
That thief was...
Su Won.
(Su Won was the food thief.)
What's wrong?
What is this?
- I won, right? - This is so funny.
Isn't he a spy sent by another broadcasting station?
"I'm the food thief!"
Why did you do that?
(What an innocent and child-like spy he is.)
Anyway,
the food thief, Su Won, succeeded his mission.
(He cleared his mission anyway.)
Here's a golden rice bowl for you.
And we'll donate the 100 sacks of rice in your name.
- Great. - He's so charitable!
And we'll give you the premium rice grown in Icheon...
for the final winner, Team Ji Hyo.
I'm sorry, Kwang Soo.
I didn't know it'd turn out this way.
I said it wasn't me!
I'm really sorry. It must've been a long day for you.
Goodness.
- I'm sorry that I misunderstood. - Me, too.
You can't just make such excuses this late!
- Did we stress you out? - Come on, Jae Seok.
Thank you, everyone, for joining us today.
(Thank you, Seul Hye and Sechs Kies, for being with us on this cold day.)
(Bromance: a close relationship between two men)
(A secretive friendship between two men)
(This is the epitome of bromance.)
(Of course not!)
(They struggle to maintain their twisted bromance.)
(Guys fiercely compete to show their charms to win other guys' hearts.)
(Do not miss the amazing chemistry among these men.)
(War of Bromance)