(It's morning in Jeonju, an artsy town that cultivated many artists.)
(Here, a trial awaits for the members of Running Man.)
(There's a throne for a king.)
(There is a straw mat.)
(And is that a wooden table for flogging?)
(What are these items for?)
- Hello. - Hi.
- Hi. - What a nice day.
Why are these men here? We just started.
- What are these? - They are getting ready to...
- give us a stick from the start. - Goodness.
- What is this chair for? - At least try to hide.
- You're here. - Gosh.
We have started our filming for an episode in Jeonju.
- First, I'll ask you a question. - What is it?
You can choose your answer as a collective group.
Will you be together or apart?
(Will you be together or apart?)
(Will they stay as a group or split? What will their choice be?)
If you decide to be together, you'll either live or die together.
If you decide to be apart, someone may be happy,
but someone will certainly be ruined.
(If they split, someone may be happy, but someone will be ruined.)
- Let's be together. - Yes, let's stay together.
- Yes, it's been a while. - Let's be together.
- We ought to be together. - We've been apart for some time.
It's so lonely when we split.
To be honest, I'll be jealous if someone does better than me.
- Some people will be ruined? - That's what he said.
- It's always been like this. - Let's be apart.
- Let's split. - Let's be apart.
I don't think it's such a bad idea after all.
It's nice that everyone will be responsible for the outcome.
You only live once.
- Yes, we only have a shot at life. - Then...
can you uncover the sheet on the right?
- Unlucky ones will be ruined. - What's wrong with being together?
- What is it? A straw mat, - A wooden table?
- a wooden table, and a throne? - A throne?
Isn't being rolled in the straw mat only for serious crimes?
Wouldn't it hurt to be smacked on the wooden table?
You'll do your opening sitting in this comfortable chair,
sitting on this cold straw mat,
or getting smacked on this wooden table.
What have we done wrong to deserve the wooden table?
- We didn't do anything wrong. - Seriously.
Isn't this too much?
Will you be together or apart?
- Ji Hyo? - I want to be apart.
- Ji Hyo wants to be apart. - She's strong.
- I want to be on my own. - What do you want?
- She's an individualist. - What do you want?
I want to stay together.
- Really? - It's better to be ruined together.
- If someone's bound to be ruined, - Someone will be.
- I'll be the only one to succeed. - What did you say?
This is why. Because of your attitude, you're always picked on.
It would be fun to watch someone get ruined.
What do you think, Seok Jin?
Victory tastes sweeter when you're the only victor.
- It's better that way. - We'll follow the majority.
- We'll be apart. - How about you, Jae Seok?
I want to be apart, too.
(They decided to be apart.)
- Let's split. - You'll regret it.
It's so hard to stay together.
In that case, please uncover the sheet on the left.
You chose to be apart.
It's better. See? Splitting could be better.
- Splitting could be better. - Right.
- It's the ghost leg. - This will be fun.
- This is much better. - I'm confident.
- I'm good at this game. - Look at this.
Please choose a number.
- Ji Hyo, choose one. - I'll choose the first one.
- She took the first one. Jong Kook? - I'll take the second one.
- Why don't we just go in order? - Let's do that.
- Fine, we'll do that. - Let's just do it.
- So it's 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, and 6. - That's right.
- I'm have the sixth one. - Ji Hyo will go first.
(The first one starts to make its way down.)
(Will she get the throne, the straw mat, or the wooden table?)
(What will she get?)
- She got the straw mat. - Okay.
(Even her nickname rhymes with the straw mat.)
Ji Hyo will take the straw mat.
Start the second one.
- I don't want the wooden table. - It's Jong Kook's turn.
(The throne)
(He takes the throne.)
He's so lucky.
(I am the king.)
He's going to be an annoying king.
Let's start the third one.
- I should've picked that one. - What's the third one?
(Unlucky Jae Seok's leg starts.)
- It's Jae Seok's turn. - It has to go up, Ji Hyo.
- It has to go up. - And it'll come down again.
(What will Jae Seok get?)
- What is it? - Whose leg was this?
- It's mine. - It's Jae Seok's.
- Whose leg was this? - It's Jae Seok's.
(He gets the wooden table.)
- He got the wooden table? - Please hit him hard.
- I knew it. - I won't get the wooden table now.
Sprinkle water on him beforehand.
- I can't believe this. - Sprinkle water on him.
- Let's move to the 4th one. - Didn't you choose the 3rd one?
- Move aside. - It's mine.
- You're truly unlucky. - It's Seok Jin's turn.
(As long as I'm safe, it's all good.)
- Please be the throne. - It's the wooden table.
It's amazing.
(Congratulations, Seok Jin.)
How can he be so unlucky?
(Now it's almost becoming a curse.)
Ji Hyo, you are lucky.
- The straw mat's better. - Seriously, it's much better.
- Who's next? - Do the next one.
- Kwang Soo's next. - That's right. I'm next.
(A throne and a straw mat remain.)
(This outcome will tell the fates of the two men.)
(What will Unlucky Kwang Soo get?)
He got the throne.
(The throne)
- Then Haha gets... - My life has just begun!
My goodness.
- The wooden table's the worst. - It's coming in.
- Why do we need to get flogged? - It's a real one.
- All I did was select a number. - This is so much fun.
- We'll show you how it's done. - I can't believe this.
- This is the perfect size for him. - It's made for you.
- Jae Seok is ruined. - It's perfect for him.
If we were together, we would've spun the wheel.
- We would've gotten the same thing. - That's right.
Do you want to spin it just to see what it could've been?
- Spin it. - Should I?
- Yes. - I wonder what would've happened...
if we stayed together.
- Seriously? - What if I spun it?
(What would've happened if everyone's fate depended on him?)
- We passed the wooden table. - It's the throne.
- No way. - It's the throne.
Wait, it passed it.
- Is it the wooden table? - It's the throne.
- The arrow is backing up. - It's the straw mat.
- We could've gotten the straw mat. - It could've been the straw mat.
- Hold on, it's not the mat. - It's moving.
- It's the wooden table. - We would've had the wooden table.
- It's the wooden table. - I'm glad we split.
- Everyone could've gotten it. - It was the right call to be apart.
If only we stayed together...
Do you see how unlucky I am?
I don't even want to go near you.
Do you see now?
(I will never leave my fate to you.)
Please take a seat in your choice of chairs.
I didn't choose mine.
Go take a seat, Kwang Soo.
Do I even have the right to sit in a chair like this?
- This is nice. - This chair is really comfortable.
(Ones who got the straw mat will have to sit on the cold ground.)
(The six who chose to be apart ended up with different fates.)
I didn't do anything wrong.
- What did I do? - What did we do wrong?
Please spank them when I raise my left hand.
I'll explain it to you now.
This is fun.
Hold on. Shouldn't they be rolled up in straw mats?
(Spanked)
(Why are you so talkative?)
- That was powerful. - What was that?
- What was that? - That really hurt.
What was that?
Are they professionals?
They're spanking you by certain rules.
- I see. - Don't talk, Jae Seok.
I should stay still.
I think you get spanked if you open your mouth.
Today's race is Probability Race: Together or Apart.
You may live together or die apart.
Let's just die.
- That'd be the cleanest way. - Yes.
You are to travel around Jeonju...
doing the Probability Race.
Probability Race, Jeonju Travel Guide.
From Deokjin Park to Hanok Village.
- They have food there. - I've been to Hanok Village often.
- We'll have a Korean course meal. - Nice.
- After that, we go to Nambu Market. - There's good food there, too.
Finally, we go to a guesthouse.
- This is looking good. - When are you going to hit us?
"When"?
(I told you to watch your mouth.)
That really hurt.
It's "when".
Can you spank each cheek evenly?
He keeps hurting the right side.
It hurts so much.
There is one condition.
You will be asked to be together or apart...
like how you just decided on your chairs.
- We have to decide every round. - I see.
This is the result of our being apart.
Let's stick together next time.
If you succeed your mission, you will be given R coins.
- R coins? - R coins.
A plane ticket to Europe is on the prize list.
Why do we have to buy you a meal?
- It's a 29-dollar meal. - Because that's the legal limit.
- I see. - That's clever.
(We are law-abiding citizens.)
We will tell you the reason why you got spanked.
- What was it? - It was for asking questions.
(The smallest decision will change your fate.)
- Because we asked questions? - Yes.
(What will be their fates?)
(Probability Race: Together or Apart)
(Deokjin Park)
- Is this where we're doing it? - Yes.
You'll be unlucky whether we are together or apart.
Don't come to me asking for my help.
I have a really bad feeling about today.
You saw me back there, right? Everything I touch turns bad.
The power of your unlucky aura is stronger than ever.
- What's this? - There it is again.
- What's this? - "Fly swatter", "flippers",
- "normal paddles". - Are we rowing?
- Oh, gosh. - Let's just roll it.
We should be together this time.
Here are the rules.
- Jeonju is the hometown of pansori. - Right.
For the first course of Jeonju Tour,
you'll get to enjoy our traditional sounds.
The name of the first mission is "Come Take a Quiz".
Two people will go on the same boat.
You will have to guess the title of the song...
by listening to the traditional singers sing.
Are the people on the same boat teams?
- This is an individual mission. - Okay.
The winner will get 40R with the prize getting smaller gradually.
Will you be together or apart?
Let's be apart.
- Let's be apart. - Why do you always want that?
- What? Let's be apart. - Why are you like that?
- I'd like that, too. - What about you, Ji Hyo?
I think it's better to be together this time.
I think so, too.
Let's be together this time.
Sounds good.
Please spin the roulette.
- Please spin the roulette. - Okay.
- Why is it you two again? - Get away from there.
- Stop it. - Get your hands off of that.
(The members refuse to leave their fate to the unlucky.)
- Don't do it. - You do it, Ji Hyo.
- Do it, then. - Ji Hyo is the better choice.
She's not that lucky.
What are you doing?
- Why did you do that? - What are you doing?
- I want to spin it. - Stop it.
- Let Ji Hyo do it. - Let go.
- Let go. - Do it, Ji Hyo.
Gosh. You guys are so mean.
Flippers would work, but fly swatters will be hard.
Are we in this together?
We are.
What did you do, Ji Hyo?
- Flippers aren't that bad. - We're getting flippers.
(Flippers)
(Jae Seok is cranky.)
I want to be apart.
Everyone will get flippers.
(Flippers, it is.)
- I knew this would happen. - Let's get on the boats now.
Let's show them how fast we can row with flippers.
I'm going to try seriously.
(Everyone is ready to go with flippers.)
- This is better than fly swatters. - Of course.
It'll take at least eight hours with fly swatters.
I'm sure of it.
(That is true.)
(The singer with the quiz...)
(is all the way out there.)
- Let's go. - Let's go.
(She's in the middle of Deokjin Park.)
I know Seok Jin isn't going to try hard.
(Come row towards me.)
(They get ready.)
Isn't it important who sits at the front?
It's much better this way.
(Jae Seok and Seok Jin get on the same boat.)
You could row like this.
(Jong Kook and Kwang Soo get on the same boat.)
- This is easier. - It's better this way.
I'll start rowing first.
(Haha and Ji Hyo get on the same boat.)
You row that way and I'll row the opposite way.
- Let's turn around. - We're good to go.
(Will they be able to row with flippers?)
- Ready... - Let's go.
This actually works.
- This works. - Set, go!
(The first round gets started.)
(Charge towards the singer.)
- This is so slow. - It's working.
- Jong Kook. - Can you row harder?
Harder. Put your hands deep in the water.
(The nagging starts.)
- Why are we going backwards? - I don't know.
- Why are we going backwards? - What's going on?
We have to row like this.
That way, Jong Kook.
We have to get there first.
- Where are we supposed to go? - Over there.
(That's where they're headed.)
Right.
(Welcome.)
Row harder.
Maybe you should row less.
(It's the battle between the two boats.)
- One, two. - One, two.
- Stop copying me. - What are you talking about?
(It's a close race.)
- Can you row less? - Row harder.
- This is the wrong direction. - Keep rowing.
- Can you row harder? Gosh. - There you go.
You have to row harder.
Row that way. The boat won't turn otherwise.
(They're rowing against each other's direction.)
(Where are you going?)
I'll go this way.
(They landed on a swamp.)
We're stuck.
Are you a crocodile?
(While Haha and Ji Hyo are looking for crocodiles...)
- One, two. - There you go.
(The other two boats have almost arrived.)
- We're almost there. - One, two.
- Kwang Soo. - Can you row harder?
(Jong Kook and Kwang Soo drift away.)
- We're almost there. - Stop rowing.
(Jae Seok and Seok Jin arrive first.)
- Can you do me a favor? - We're here.
- This is the first question. - We're here.
(I don't know)
What?
(Your eyes pretend to be innocent)
(You put me up)
Hold on. What is she singing?
(Then I feel)
(Loco)
(What on earth...)
(is she...)
(saying?)
What are you saying?
(Hey, baby boy)
What did you say?
(Stop spinning me around and around)
(Hey, baby boy)
- Hold on. - I know this song.
- Do you get it? - Yes.
Why are we getting farther and farther away?
(The song echoes throughout Deokjin Lake.)
(Up and down)
(This song is...)
("Up and Down" by EXID)
(This cheerful melody...)
(is transformed into a sorrowful tune.)
(It's a deplorable song.)
(It's a classical version of "Up and Down".)
This song sounds familiar.
I don't get it.
Jae Seok will get to guess it first.
Okay. Hold on.
You have five seconds.
- I didn't hear anything. - Five, four,
- Hold on. - Three, two,
(What did Jae Seok write down?)
"Like Ooh-Ahh".
("Like Ooh-Ahh" by Twice)
- What? - By Twice.
(That is incorrect.)
(What kind of answer is that?)
"Round and Round" by Nami.
(Seok Jin thinks it's a song from the 1980s.)
(It's Jong Kook and Kwang Soo's turn to guess.)
- "Up and Down" by EXID. - "Up and Down".
(Jong Kook and Kwang Soo both guess "Up and Down".)
Really?
Kwang Soo and Jong Kook guessed it correctly.
(Jong Kook and Kwang Soo both receive 40R.)
- I didn't know the lyrics. - Stop spinning me around
Up and down, up, up and down
(Good job.)
This is the second question.
What is it?
(Drop the question.)
(Every day it rings)
It's over there.
(Where is this sound coming from?)
(I'm over here.)
- What a mess. - Gosh.
(She's at the dock where they took off in the beginning.)
Can you push our boat?
- Hold on. - We're coming.
Row faster.
(They have to go back the way they came from.)
I don't know, I don't know
This is really hard.
- Can you row harder? - I am trying.
Why are you so bad at this?
This is so hard.
- Come on. - Goodness.
- You're rowing too carelessly. - No, I'm not.
(Ji Hyo and Haha arrive.)
The phone keeps ringing so much
That it might explode
I don't know, but he says he can't breathe
I break his heart because I give him a hard time
It's a song by Twice.
(It's a song by Twice.)
("Cheer Up" by Twice)
(It's the biggest hit song in 2016 that made "Shy, shy, shy" popular.)
(Will Ji Hyo guess the correct answer?)
I'm not bragging
I'm sorry for not answering the phone
I have no idea what it is.
(Finally, "Shy, shy, shy" is coming up.)
Don't you know "Shy, shy, shy"?
(If the lyrics include "Shy, shy, shy" and it's a song by Twice...)
- "Shy, Shy, Shy". - "Shy, Shy, Shy".
("Shy, Shy, Shy" by Twice?)
Goodness.
- That's incorrect. - Don't you know the title?
Don't you know this dance?
- Don't you know the song? - "Shy, Shy, Shy".
- Did you write "Shy, Shy, Shy"? - Yes.
What's the title of the song?
(Isn't "Shy, Shy, Shy" the title?)
- "Shy, Shy, Shy". - What's the chorus?
I'll show you more, cheer up, baby
(They must recognize it by now.)
"Shut It, Baby".
(What?)
("Shut It, Baby"?)
What kind of title is that?
- The chorus is "Cheer up, Baby". - "Shut It, Baby".
"Shut It, Baby"?
"Shut It, Baby".
Isn't this correct?
(Everyone is speechless.)
Didn't you hear the chorus?
Wait a minute.
Would the beautiful girls say, "Shut it"?
Look over here.
"Cheer Up" by Twice.
- Is it "Cheer Up"? - Of course it is.
Seok Jin's answer is correct.
(Seok Jin answers correctly.)
It's "Cheer Up".
Right, it's "Cheer Up".
The boat is docked properly.
Now,
Jong Kook and Kwang Soo earned 40R each.
- We're on the lead. - I know.
- Seok Jin earned 10R. - I only earned 10R?
Good job, Ms. Shy, Shy, Shy.
You did a good job, too.
- Ms. Shy, Shy, Shy. - Mr. Shut It, Baby.
How could they think it was "Shy, Shy, Shy"?
(Current status of how many R coins each member has earned)
- What's this? - What's over here?
There are makeup tools.
- What are these? - What are they?
The second part of Probability Race...
is in Hanok Village.
You'll play "Secret Mission at Hanok Village".
"Secret Mission"?
("Secret Mission at Hanok Village")
Without letting the public find out who you are,
you must clear the mission.
(If someone says hello or calls out their name, they fail.)
How can we remain discreet with a blonde wig?
- I can wear anything. - The makeup will make us stand out.
The worst is putting on your name tag.
- It's like a Halloween party. - Will you be together or apart?
(What will they choose to do this time?)
I can't be together with Kwang Soo. Let's be apart.
We decide to be apart.
We should be apart this time.
- It's because of Kwang Soo. - Wait.
Kwang Soo stands out too much.
- It'd be impossible with him. - He can't be discreet at all.
People would recognize him even if he crawls.
Crawling wouldn't be any better.
It's too stressful to be with him in public.
Will you be apart?
- Yes. - We'll be apart.
- We have to be apart. - Then,
please choose the number of the ladder.
Let's do the opposite this time. I'll take one.
The hat and jacket are the best.
- I choose two. - Let's start with Haha.
- Please. - It's Haha's turn.
In 1, 2, 3, 4.
(Will he get to cover himself or put on his name tag?)
- He gets Professional Makeup Card. - Go over there.
That's a good thing.
Okay, this is great.
- Aren't hat and jacket the best? - Okay.
- It's my turn. - It's Ji Hyo's turn.
(Next up is Ji Hyo.)
(Will it be confirmed that Ji Hyo is truly lucky?)
- Hat and jacket. - Hat and jacket.
- These are the best. - These are great.
- They are. - Thank goodness.
Isn't Professional Makeup Card the best?
- Who's next? - Is it Jong Kook?
No, my turn is before Kwang Soo's.
- Next up is Kwang Soo. - No.
- In 2, 3, 4, 5. - Isn't it Seok Jin's turn?
Okay, this is my turn.
(Why did Seok Jin take Kwang Soo's turn instead?)
It's Seok Jin.
Put on your name tag.
(Put on your name tag)
He's so unlucky.
It wasn't his turn originally.
How unlucky am I?
I shouldn't have changed my turn.
- Who's next? - It's Jae Seok.
That's the worst.
- Let's see. - It's Jae Seok.
(Next up is Jae Seok.)
You'll get the name tag, too.
- Hat and jacket. - That's not bad.
That's much better.
- It's impossible to hide yourself. - I can cover up myself.
Only the name tag and Professional Makeup Card remain.
Who's next?
(It's between the name tag and Professional Makeup Card.)
I wanted this ladder.
(Kwang Soo's fate depends on Jong Kook's choice.)
(He wants to meet the professional makeup artist.)
(He doesn't want the name tag.)
It's Professional Makeup Card.
That's crazy.
(That means...)
Put on your name tag.
I didn't even get to choose.
Why did everyone else get to choose?
So 2 out of 3 were destined to put on the name tag.
- It's strange. - It's impossible.
- It's very strange. - I can't put on my name tag.
- It'd be impossible. - It's strange how it turned out.
- I've been on the show for 7 years. - This isn't all.
(The three unlucky members are still unlucky.)
(Professional Makeup Card, hat and jacket, name tag)
There are three locations for the mission.
Two members will be dropped off in each location.
Which one is the worst location?
Please pair up.
Pairing up with someone with the name tag won't be good.
- Is it random? - Let's find out.
(If your partner is found, you might be found.)
Please take one.
- Jeondong Cathedral? - Awesome.
- You and I have the same. - That's incredible.
Who has "Pick a Fortune"?
(Who is Jae Seok's partner?)
- I have "Pick a Fortune". - Is it him again?
(Jae Seok is forever bound to Seok Jin.)
- Am I paired up with you? - Come on.
- Are you my partner? - How is this possible?
- We have our old partners. - We have the same partners.
- My goodness. - I can't do anything.
- We might be at an advantage. - I gave out the paper.
- You're so unlucky. - Did you notice that?
My partner is with his name tag.
(They're both unlucky.)
I can't hide my name tag.
This team has the most advantage.
(Locations for Probability Race)
You can put on the makeup any way you want.
What's the point? I'm with Kwang Soo.
- My goodness. - Wait.
- Goodness. - Gosh.
- It's Jong Kook. - There's Jong Kook.
- Anyone would notice that it's him. - It's so obvious.
What's the point of putting on a costume?
(How does Jong Kook look?)
(It's obviously Jong Kook.)
Why is your skirt so wide?
(He's in a big costume.)
- You're obviously Jong Kook. - Everyone will recognize you.
I'm scared.
Is that a sideburn?
(He ignores his question.)
Your big arms...
don't fit in the hanbok.
The hanbok is too tight on you. It should be loose.
This is funny.
- Let's go. - All we have to do is...
- buy some rice cake skewers, right? - Yes.
- Stay calm. - All we have to do is buy them?
- How many should we buy? - You must remain discreet.
- This isn't possible. - We need to buy rice cake skewers.
Five rice cake skewers, please.
You stand out more than I do.
- Hide your voice like this. - How?
Excuse me.
- It's Jae Seok. - What are you doing?
- Is that it? - It sounds like a voice mimicry.
- My voice doesn't stand out. - It sounds like you.
- Is it obvious. - Sir?
Kwang Soo, say something in a different voice.
Five rice cake skewers, please.
Was it unrecognizable? I was surprised myself.
- It's definitely Kwang Soo. - Five rice cake skewers, please.
(Will he successfully remain discreet?)
Here we are.
It's Hanok Village.
(Hanok Village in Jeonju contains the beauty of Korea.)
- You walk here in hanbok. - There's another Eo Woo Dong.
She's wearing the same costume as Jong Kook.
- Is there another Eo Woo Dong? - Yes.
Look.
- There they are. - They're wearing costumes, too.
- There are many in costumes. - You're right.
It's trendy these days.
They put on costumes together and go on a date.
There are many in costumes.
(Hanok Village is full of people in hanbok.)
This is risky here.
- There are many. - Many are in costumes.
Next up are Jong Kook and Kwang Soo.
Unfortunately, rice cake skewers shop is closed.
- Instead, - They should change the item.
you must buy shrimp dumplings from Joeun Dumplings.
Buy six portions.
I don't care how much we need to buy.
I can buy 12 portions.
If you get caught, buy all 6. I'll buy only 3 portions.
Here's the money for the dumplings.
Kwang Soo, bring back a lot of delicious food.
I'll clear the mission first.
Bring back the dumplings.
Do we get 3 or 4 portions?
(He tries to hide himself with his hoodie.)
- Which dumpling shop is it? - Joeun Dumplings.
This is the way to the shop.
- Go this way. - Will we see it on the street?
Yes, go out this way.
(Hanok Village gets more crowded because it's lunch time.)
- We start after the corner. - What?
- We start after the corner. - Just go.
(After a few steps is a street crowded with people.)
Go on.
(He's too scared to go.)
What is he doing?
(He squats down when there's nobody watching him.)
(He's close to the wall.)
(Jong Kook moves ahead with his face hidden.)
(He looks suspicious with his face covered.)
(Kwang Soo rises.)
(He starts walking fast.)
Where did Jong Kook go?
There are too many people here.
(What is that young man doing?)
(Glancing)
(He must be in a hurry.)
(Please)
(Why is he walking like that?)
(He passes a crowded street with people staring at him.)
(Jong Kook strides ahead easily with his costume.)
(That's a good looking costume.)
(Peeking)
(Scrambling)
I might make it.
(There are people at the end of the street.)
Where is it?
(Jong Kook is closely behind him.)
(He passes easily.)
They didn't recognize me.
(The dumpling restaurant is right around the corner.)
(Spinning)
There are people here.
(He pretends like he's a statue.)
(He finally arrives at the dumpling restaurant.)
(A group of young students approach him.)
(It should be okay as long as they don't see my back.)
(He's only a few steps away.)
(Is Kwang Soo already there?)
(Would Kwang Soo make it?)
May I have six servings of dumplings?
(He changes his voice.)
(But the dumpling restaurant is the place on the right.)
(We sell rice cakes.)
(This is not it.)
Hello, Kwang Soo.
- Sorry? - Are you filming?
Would you like me to get you some?
Would you like some dumplings?
- What is he doing? - Sure.
(Jong Kook approaches the dumpling restaurant.)
(Kwang Soo, that's a fail.)
(Hold on.)
May I have three servings of dumplings?
Three servings, please.
- Three servings? - Yes.
Oh, my goodness.
- My goodness. - Do you want me to take it?
(People are focused on Kwang Soo.)
(All Jong Kook has to do is leave with the dumplings.)
Do you mind taking a picture for us?
(Do you mind taking a picture for us?)
(How dare you, Kwang Soo?)
Are you Kim Jong Kook?
It's him.
(It is me.)
Thank you.
(We need to talk, Kwang Soo.)
What are you doing?
(He gets slapped.)
- Who is this guy? - Hey.
- Hey. I did all this for nothing. - What?
Who is this guy?
- It's not my fault. - It's your fault.
Hold on. It wasn't...
Hold on. It wasn't because of me, right?
You didn't notice him because of me, right?
I did.
You punk.
(Jong Kook is mad.)
I'm mad. I'm so mad.
(What was the mission?)
I was supposed to come unnoticed and buy something.
- We can see your name tag. - How could you not be noticed?
I don't know. I got unlucky.
(How could you be unnoticed with this on your back?)
- What happened? - He failed. He took his hat off.
- What happened? - Why didn't you get something?
- What happened? - I was...
ordering quietly,
and Kwang Soo was taking pictures with people.
He approached me and told me to take pictures for him.
- Kwang Soo did? - You were close.
- Were you almost finished? - He has a lot of problems.
I agree. He has problems.
Thanks to you, I failed. I failed the mission.
(You're handsome.)
Thank you.
(Me? I know I look quite good.)
(All right, then.)
(You can take your time.)
(People gather around the dumpling restaurant to look at him.)
(I may not have won, but it's fine as long as my fans smile.)
I'm mad. I'm so mad.
Thanks to you, I failed. I failed the mission.
(I didn't get any dumplings but I am a lucky guy.)
Thank you. Thank you for the food.
Thank you.
- I'm back. - Kwang Soo, you're back.
Jong Kook. Hold on, you're mistaken.
I merely asked you to take a picture for me.
- Have a seat, Kwang Soo. - You went too far.
No, that's not it.
- Let's try these first. - Is it good?
(They decide to taste the dumplings first.)
- It has an entire shrimp in it. - These are shrimp dumplings.
- It's mine. - Give me some.
They have shrimps in them.
This is so good.
(They decide to eat first.)
This is good.
- They're the same. - This is tasty. The sauce is good.
Anyhow, both of them have failed, right?
Okay!
I should stick with Jae Seok.
- That's a good idea. - Right?
Watch me.
I'll show you how a professional does it.
What kind of a professional is that?
- What is that? - How is that useful?
- Didn't you know? - You must be a thief.
I have two jobs.
- What are they? - I'm a celebrity and an agent.
(He's a celebrity and a secret agent.)
You had no idea, right? I collect your information...
I collect your information...
- That was so random. - I was hiding my identity.
I was shocked when I watched "Jason Bourne".
I thought they were talking about me.
(Forget about the celebrity Jae Seok. He's Jae Seok Bourne.)
- Did you have no idea? - I had no idea.
- You didn't? - What kind of things did you do?
You might not know...
Tell me something that made headlines on the news.
This didn't make headlines...
but I passed on Seok Jin's personal information once.
(That's a big deal.)
My wife knew what I was doing.
- Plus... - I told her.
- You almost had me. - I knew.
- Is it me next? - Get ready.
- Yes. - Agent Yu.
- Give us some information. - Don't you worry.
- Jae Seok is too noticeable. - I agree.
- You're too noticeable. - You are.
He can't be a secret agent.
(Jae Seok is easily noticeable and Seok Jin has a name tag on him.)
- Where are we supposed to go? - Where is it?
Look.
People can see you like that.
People can see you.
(You must pick your fortune and return without being noticed.)
I usually don't avoid people.
(Jae Seok Bourne is out on the street.)
Where is it?
(There are a lot of people on the streets.)
Where's my destination?
(He'll make eye contact with people as soon as he turns his head.)
(He turns away.)
(He turns away and avoids making eye contact.)
(Here's a map.)
(He uses it to cover his face.)
Is that it? There are quite a few people.
(A person in a costume looks in his direction.)
(But he's a secret agent and he escapes suspicion.)
We're not noticeable.
(He walks fearlessly.)
(He's almost at his destination.)
Where is it? Where's the place?
(Meanwhile, Seok Jin is lost.)
This is the biggest challenge.
This is the biggest challenge. There's a lot of people.
I'm going to run.
(Sprinting)
(He sprints when there's nobody around.)
(He conceals his name tag.)
(People don't even pay attention to him.)
(Are they pretending not to recognize me?)
(Jae Seok arrives at his destination.)
My gosh.
What's wrong?
(It's getting more crowded.)
Jae Seok, I think I can make it.
Seok Jin.
(People are gathered.)
How does this work?
(He puts in a coin.)
(He receives his fortune.)
(Jae Seok clears the mission.)
I don't have a good feeling about this.
How much is it?
(Seok Jin tries to get Jae Seok to talk.)
(Here's somebody from Running Man.)
(Jae Seok runs away after exposing Seok Jin.)
(It's Running Man.)
Hello.
(He's so popular today.)
I'm so mad. I almost had it.
I tried so hard.
Really? Hello.
(He comes back with a fan club.)
Thank you.
(He gathers his fans.)
(That annoying Jae Seok cost me my failure.)
People recognized him, right?
(It's so fun to betray Seok Jin.)
I'll succeed if I make it back to the car without being recognized.
Where is the bus?
(His weakness is his poor sense of direction.)
(He looks around.)
(Their eyes meet.)
Goodness.
(Please, pretend to not recognize me.)
(You are Jae Seok, aren't you?)
I mean I can't find the bus.
- Anyway, - Can we take a photo together?
This shouldn't...
This shouldn't have happened.
I was looking for the bus and our eyes met.
- Hold on. - It's Jae Seok.
I was merely looking for the bus and our eyes met.
- My name tag got pulled out. - But...
- I was searching for the bus. - Hey.
Why did you do that for?
- You betrayed me. - I mean,
this should count as a success.
- I was so close. - I couldn't find the bus.
That's the only reason our eyes met.
- Over there. - This is driving me crazy.
It's making me angry.
(It's all your fault, Jae Seok.)
- So both of them failed. - They failed.
Yes, they did.
- Did you picked your fortune? - Yes.
- What does it say? - How's your fortune?
"You'll have good fortunes."
"You'll have a comfortable life."
"You will have an abundance of food and wealth."
"Mostly, you'll spend the upcoming year without any difficulties."
"If you head north, it'll bring you riches."
"Instead of keeping old things, it's better if you move to a new house."
"You'll receive a lot of support in the midst of good fortunes."
What a nice fortune.
There's not a single misfortune mentioned.
- You have a good fortune. - Yes, he does.
Of course, they wouldn't write something bad in it.
- They won't write a misfortune. - "Your grandchild will be unlucky."
- "Be careful at night." - That makes sense.
I apologize.
(It won't feel great reading a bad fortune.)
(Current score of collecting R coins)
(A highlight of a trip to Jeonju is having a Korean traditional meal.)
- Look at this. - What is all this?
- This looks amazing. - I have to eat this.
Goodness!
(Jeonju brings the best authentic Korean food to the table.)
I have to eat this. I wouldn't have it any other way.
- What is this? - Hold on.
This has gotten me all worked up.
- This time, it'll be a food tour. - I must eat it.
- This looks so delicious. - I have to try this.
We prepared three kinds of meals to keep up with Jeonju's reputation.
- It looks very tasty. - I'm going to eat this.
- This is driving me crazy. - The first one will have...
- tteokgalbi, seasoned raw beef... - This is amazing.
- All these are included? - This is incredible.
Look at how fat the octopus is.
The next one will only get you one spoonful of food.
You can put as much food as you want in one spoon.
The last one is a special rice ball made by the staff.
We put healthy herbs like thistle bitter gourd and motherwort.
This is a punishment.
- They're all healthy for you. - This is a punishment.
(We can take care of our own wellbeing.)
- But it must be healthy. - If we eat that...
I think we might become immortal.
- The second one gets me a spoon. - You want to be together or apart?
- Let's stay together. - Let's be together.
- Do you want to be together. - Let's stay together.
Let's start the game right away.
- Let's split this time. - I want us to be together.
If we do, some people are bound to have this meal.
- Anyone can. - Then how about this?
- I think Jong Kook makes sense. - Yes, some people ought to eat it.
- It's better if some of us eat. - Exactly.
- Ji Hyo, which one? - This is strange.
- Will we choose it beforehand? - Yes.
Ji Hyo, which number do you want?
- I'll choose number 5. - Okay, 5th one it is.
- This is nerve-wrecking. - I'm so nervous.
- This is driving me crazy. - I didn't eat the meal in Icheon.
(It's the meal of Jeonju that no one can refuse.)
Please.
- Please. - I hope she gets the second course.
- I beg you, please. - Get the second course.
- I hope she gets the rice ball. - Please.
Please, I beg you!
(Which food has Ji Hyo picked?)
(It's the special rice ball made by the staff.)
- Please. - Please be the second course.
(She gets the healthy rice ball filled with medicinal herbs.)
(Her misery is happiness for everyone else.)
- Great. - It's fine as long as it's not me.
- This is great. - I'm glad it's not me.
I'm sorry for you, Ji Hyo.
- You can't be lucky all the time. - Right.
- Have the rice ball. - You know it's a punishment, right?
How about you, Jong Kook?
- I choose the 2nd one. - He chose the 2nd one.
- I think it's a lucky number. - I hope he gets the rice ball.
- Please get the rice ball. - Get the rice ball.
- Get the rice ball. - Get the rice ball.
- Get the rice ball. - No way.
(There are still two vacancies left for the meal. Will he get one?)
(Get the rice ball for your health.)
(What is the result of the second leg?)
(He gets one spoonful of food.)
(Everyone has united for the same purpose.)
This is too harsh.
- How many people are left? - Please.
Two of us will have the meal and the other won't.
Yes, two of you will get the meal.
- Please. - I can't believe my luck.
Who's next? I really want this meal.
Two of us will be lucky and the other two will be unlucky.
- I need to eat this meal. - All I want is this meal.
- I deserve this meal. - You saw what happened to me today.
- Which number? - Get the rice ball.
- I'll choose lucky number... - Four!
- five. - That one's already done.
- We did? - Ji Hyo picked it.
(He again picks the wrong number.)
I almost got the rice ball..
(Join me for a rice ball.)
You saw that, right? If she didn't go before me, I would've gotten it.
- Which will it be, Jae Seok? - I'll pick lucky number...
- Choose 4. - Pick 4.
- I'll choose four! - Don't tell him what to pick.
- No. - Don't influence him.
(Stop it.)
I pick number six!
- You want the 6th one? - I'll choose the 4th one, then.
(He changed his number. Will it be a great move for him?)
(I have a good feeling about this.)
- Okay. - Here you go.
- Please be the rice ball. - Get the rice ball.
Get the rice ball. What is it?
Jae Seok.
- What is it? - Is it the first meal?
- Did he get lucky or not? - Really?
- Let me see. - Is it the first meal?
In 1, 2, 3.
(Will this unlucky man's fate take a turn?)
(He gets the meal of Jeonju.)
(An extraordinary event occurred.)
I'm so annoyed.
- We shouldn't have let him change. - What's wrong with him?
(I got the meal of Jeonju!)
- Now there's only one seat left. - I'm sorry.
(He's embarrassed.)
(He yelled loudly at such a peaceful place.)
What's the matter with you?
(Is this your first time having a proper meal?)
Don't rub it.
(He's feeling embarrassed.)
- He picked the 6th one, right? - I'll choose the 3rd one.
- I should've picked that one. - Did you pick the third one?
- Yes, I'll go with that one. - Please.
Kwang Soo, choose the first one.
(They are curious about the outcome.)
Please, there's still one more seat left.
There's one more left.
I still have a shot at it.
- He might get it. - Please get the rice ball.
- Please. - It can't be the meal.
Please be the meal.
- It's long. - Peel it.
The writing is really long, Seok Jin.
- He might get lucky. - In 1, 2, 3.
(She said the writing was long. Could it be that he got the meal?)
(Will he get the meal of Jeonju?)
(Or will he get the special rice ball made by the staff?)
(They shout for joy.)
(He gets the special rice ball.)
(He breaks his own record of being the unlucky one out of them.)
- How can I be this unlucky? - I will have the last number.
How is this possible?
- Again, two of us are unlucky. - That's right.
Please.
- Should I go with the 1st one? - Yes, get the 1st one.
(Trust me.)
- I'll get the 1st one. - Kwang Soo, you want the 1st one?
I'm sure it's the right number.
(When he's not sure, it's better to listen to Jong Kook.)
(The busybodies of the town gather around him.)
- Here it is. - It ends up in the first slot.
Please let me have the meal.
Kwang Soo.
- This was Kwang Soo's. - It is?
(I can't wait to try tteokgalbi and seasoned raw beef.)
(For the last 7 years, he was teased for being so unlucky.)
(Starting today, I will escape this curse alongside Jae Seok.)
(He is so close to having the meal. Will he get the meal or the spoon?)
Congratulations, Kwang Soo.
(There were no surprises.)
I guess only one of us will be lucky.
I really wanted the meal.
- Ji Hyo got the rice ball. - This is amazing.
(Jae Sook and Haha get the meal.)
(Ji Hyo and Seok Jin get the rice ball.)
I can put as much food as I want.
(They can't stop laughing and cheering.)
This looks amazing. You can just leave us two pieces of that.
(It's a shame to only have this special meal of Jeonju once.)
This is delicious.
(They seem as if they're promoting the meal.)
- This is incredible. - Bulgogi in the pot is awesome.
Look at the color of the rice ball.
- We put red ginseng extract in it. - I can smell it.
Look at the color of rice inside.
What is this? How can you call this rice?
Kwang Soo, have tteokgalbi and seasoned raw beef.
- Why is the rice so bitter? - Isn't the squid good, too?
(Life of immortality tastes bitter.)
I'll try bibimbap.
Should I have it like that? I think I should.
Jong Kook, are you sure that's a spoonful?
(He concentrates on having a big spoonful of food.)
I can eat it like this, right?
- Can you eat it at once? - That's almost 600g.
- That's 600g. - You're eating a whole cow.
(He opens his mouth wide.)
- Can he eat it all? - Seriously?
You just devoured a whole cow.
Are you bleeding?
That was a lot.
But it's really delicious.
Gosh, it's so bitter.
Goodness, this is amazing.
My eyes hurt from eating this.
The smell's getting into my eyes.
(We only put healthy ingredients in it just for you.)
(It's Kwang Soo's turn to have his spoonful.)
(He's careful.)
I'm already full after a spoonful.
How is that a spoonful?
(He's trying hard to get everything in one spoonful.)
It's so bitter.
How did he do that?
Do you think you can fit all that in your mouth?
Why did you put that on top?
You don't need that.
(The nagging starts again.)
Get your hands off.
(Kwang Soo is mad.)
- I almost dropped it. - Fine, Kwang Soo.
You shouldn't have done that to me in Hanok Village.
- Kwang Soo. - I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry,
but can you go play somewhere else? We're eating here.
What?
There you go.
(He tries a spoonful.)
(The entire Korean course meal is in one spoonful.)
- It's going to work. - It's looking good.
- It's working. - There you go.
There you go.
(He holds grudges.)
Are you going to allow that?
- You can't do that. - What?
- You'll be able to do it this time. - Right.
(You can't stop me from eating.)
(He's shoving it in there.)
It hurt my Adam's apple when I tried to swallow.
(Be aware of the attack on your Adam's apple.)
(It's a tteokgalbi battle in the Adam's apple.)
You're not supposed to use your hands.
(It's a battle between tteokgalbi on the battlefield of Adam's apple.)
It'll keep hurting your Adam's apple.
You might throw up.
It's a fish. Look he's a fish.
(Kwang Soo's fish acting is top of the class.)
This is delicious.
Seok Jin isn't eating...
because he thinks he'll get food after the game ends.
(Seok Jin thinks he's getting food after the game ends.)
He doesn't want to fill up on rice balls.
Can you tell him that he's not getting anything else?
(The satisfying mealtime is over.)
While you're eating, the next decision awaits.
(What next decision?)
Do we have to pay for the food?
(Running Man's Bill, Free Food, The Entire Staff Members' Bill)
We have to pay for our food?
But I didn't even get to eat.
I'd be so mad if I had to pay for everything after eating rice balls.
- This isn't fair. - We should be apart for this one.
- We should be. - Okay.
In total, the bill is 578 dollars.
(Staff members' bill is 392 dollars. Running Man's bill is 186 dollars.)
Will you be together or apart?
(Will you split the bill?)
(Or make one person pay for the whole thing?)
How should we do this, Kwang Soo?
I don't want to pay 100 dollars...
for a spoonful. Why should I?
That's what I think, too.
- What about you, Seok Jin? - We should be apart.
There's no other way. This is war.
- All right. Then, Seok Jin. - Yes?
- Pick a number first. - Me?
(Everyone is on their own.)
Six was the lucky number, right?
I think 3 was the unlucky number. I pick number 3.
- Okay. - It'll be a lucky number this time.
Seok Jin picked number three.
Let's go.
(Only two people will be able to avoid paying.)
Please give me a zero.
(He prays that he won't pay.)
(Some of them will have to pay for the staff members' food.)
(How much will Seok Jin have to pay?)
(He gets 100 dollars.)
(He has to pay 100 dollars for some rice balls.)
- That's not that bad. - That's the second best option.
Who's going next?
- Ji Hyo? - Why am I so unlucky?
- I'll go with number four. - Okay.
(Ji Hyo also ate rice balls.)
(I was unlucky to get rice balls.)
(I won't be unlucky this time.)
(She gets to pay 200 dollars for the staff members.)
(It's a shocking result.)
- How much is that? - Ji Hyo.
(Exhilarated)
- What's going on with you today? - Today's not your day.
Today is not my day.
I'll go next.
- Okay, Jong Kook. - I'll go with number two.
(Jong Kook ate 20 dollars' worth of raw beef from a spoonful.)
Nobody got a zero so far.
(How much will he have to pay?)
(He doesn't need to pay.)
Haha?
- I'll go with number one. - Okay.
(Haha ate a lot today.)
(How much will he have to pay?)
(He got 100 dollars.)
It's not that bad.
(It's not that bad compared to what he ate.)
We meet again, Kwang Soo.
Let the best man win.
One of us will die.
We'll see who gets the last dance.
One of us three always gets to be the lucky one.
- That's right. - The other two are unlucky.
One of us will live.
Only one will get to live.
One of you won't have to pay and the other one will pay 200 dollars.
Please.
(One of them won't have to pay and the other one will pay 200 dollars.)
He got lucky because he switched from number 4 to 6.
- I choose number 6. - You shouldn't go for number 6.
That was the lucky number before.
It won't be the lucky number again.
(The two meet again in front of a large bill.)
It's a difficult path to number six.
I can't see.
- I must've gotten the good one. - I'll reveal both at once.
This one is mine and this is Kwang Soo's.
One...
(Left is Kwang Soo, right is Jae Seok.)
Two...
(It's a battle of pride between the two unlucky men.)
Three.
(How will this battle end?)
One, two, three.
(Kwang Soo gets 200 dollars.)
(Jae Seok gets the better of Kwang Soo.)
Oh, my.
(Let's split the bill, Kwang Soo.)
I told you not to pick number six.
(Jae Seok is today's lucky man.)
Everything's working out for me.
This is amazing.
Why are you and I so unlucky today?
We'll be paying for Running Man.
We're splitting the bill.
We'll each pay 94 dollars each.
That's right.
I only had a spoonful.
Thank you.
Thank you for the meal.
(Probability Race: Together or Apart)
(The fourth course is Nambu Market.)
(This place has a long history and tradition.)
Is this the famous market?
- I think we've been here before. - Really?
(This market is full of all kinds of food and necessities.)
There's choouhtang.
It says, "Mall of Youth".
(Different generations coexist in this hot spot of Jeonju.)
(Today's last mission will be held out at Nambu Market.)
I've seen this place on "VJ's on the Scene".
- Really? - Yes.
(There are chairs and an R sign.)
- What's this? - What's this?
- Why are there so many chairs? - What are these chairs?
There are 10 chairs.
This course of Probability Race has 50R at stake.
- 50R? - We're at Nambu Market.
50R?
Using the initial consonants of the word, "Nambu Market",
you have to bring back five things...
that have at least two of the initial consonants in the name.
What's this?
You have to wear these before you go.
The clothes will unravel the longer you travel.
So that's the distance we're allowed to travel?
(You're only allowed to travel as far as the clothes allow you to.)
- We won't be able to go far. - This is fun.
(Their fates will be decided by random.)
Before you go,
you'll need money to purchase the five things.
- Right. - You will have to earn money...
by auctioning the name tags with your autographs on them.
- Why are you doing this? - That's embarrassing.
(Who would buy our name tags?)
The bidders will be the staff members.
- The staff members? - Why would they...
want to have our autographs?
(Win over the staff members to earn money for the mission.)
- Can I get some hand cream? - I know.
(These people won't be persuaded easily.)
Thank you for coming out.
- She's the heart of Running Man. - Nothing gets done without her.
- She works 4 to 5 jobs. - She does.
- She's a director. - She's also an actress.
(Oh Yi Seul, Editorial Director)
She's a hard-working person.
She makes many small mistakes.
- She's famous for that. - But nothing serious.
It's hard to tell whether we should tell her off or not.
- She makes petty mistakes. - Right.
He's the zimizib director from the field day.
(Yoon Hong Min, Camera Director)
He lost to Kwang Soo while arm wrestling.
(He looks like the Terminator, but he's actually weak.)
Dong Geun...
(This staff member is...)
He had double eyelid surgery done recently.
- He did? - Don't bring it up.
- The surgery was successful. - It looks so natural.
- They look so natural. - They do.
I almost didn't recognize it.
Why are you looking at me like that? Don't glare at me.
- There's nothing to be ashamed of. - Are you not glaring at me?
(Is it just your eyes?)
(Enough bashing for now.)
- Let's go by the order. - Okay.
Let's start with Kwang Soo.
This is the order?
We're allowed to appeal to them, right?
- We'll give you 10 seconds. - We need to appeal.
- That's too short. - It can't be longer than that.
You can appeal to them if you want.
No matter how much you pay for my name tag...
(What are you going to offer us?)
I'll pay you back...
in double.
I'll pay you back in double.
(It's a good opportunity to make money.)
- What? - What are you doing?
- What are you doing? - You can't do that.
- This is my campaign. - You can't do that.
- What are you doing? - I'll pay you in double.
- He's clever. - As long as it's below 100 dollars.
I pledge to you.
You can't do that.
The people after you will pay back in triple.
(The name tags are very common to the staff.)
This is Kwang Soo's name tag.
- "I love you." - This is the name tag.
This is Kwang Soo's name tag with his autograph on it.
Starting with one dollar.
Is there one dollar?
- Nobody. - It's only a dollar.
- One dollar and 20 cents. - Okay.
- One dollar and 60 cents. - Okay.
- Two dollars. - We have two dollars.
Hold on. Are you an expert auctioneer?
- Do you even want this name tag? - He's not.
(Are you trying to raise the asking price?)
You're trying to raise the asking price.
What are you trying to do here?
(Why would you bid if you don't even want it?)
- He seriously wants my name tag. - Are you sure?
He called two dollars.
- In 5... - Two dollars and 10 cents.
- Okay. - Two dollars and 10 cents.
- We're on a roll. - Five...
- I call 2 dollars and 40 cents. - She called 2 dollars and 40 cents.
- In 5, 4... - 2 dollars and 50 cents.
Two dollars and 50 cents? Thank you.
- In 5... - Three dollars.
Are you also participating?
- That was out of the blue. - Are you also bidding?
All the staff can bid.
Really?
Some of the staff members are there...
only to lure people.
- Don't you think? - You're right.
- Some are acting as auctioneers. - They're auctioneers.
There are people who set standards.
We have three dollars.
- If there's no higher bid... - There's one.
- Three dollars and 30 cents. - Three dollars and 30 cents?
- We have 3 dollars and 30 cents. - In 5, 4...
- There should be one more. - three...
- 10 dollars. - 10 dollars!
(10 dollars?)
(Kwang Soo walks up to her.)
- How about 20 dollars? - You'll end up spending more.
Did you see what she did?
She made a hand gesture saying 20 dollars.
- Did you see what she did? - I can't believe it.
She asked him for 20 dollars.
She's being tricky.
- She wants my name tag that much. - 10 dollars.
In 5, 4, 3...
- 10 dollars and 10 cents. - All right.
- In 5, 4... - He has to pay 20 dollars.
- 10 dollars and 20 cents. - That sounds great.
- In 5, 4... - It's 10 dollars and 20 cents.
- 10 dollars and 30 cents. - 10 dollars and 30 cents?
It only increases by 10 cents.
This is what I think.
Kwang Soo's name tag price increases only by 10 cents.
Everyone, please spend more money.
- The price is reaching its limit. - Only 10 cents?
- It's at its limit. - Everyone.
- 10 cents can be worth a lot. - It's at its limit.
I think the price has reached the limit.
- It's at 10 dollars and 30 cents. - Some may increase by 1 cent.
In five...
- 11 dollars. - 11 dollars?
- It increased by a lot. - In 5, 4...
- 13 dollars. - That sounds good.
- She's good at bidding. - In 5, 4, 3, 2, 1.
Wait a minute.
- He raised his hand. - It's sold at 13 dollars.
It's sold at 13 dollars.
She buys it at 13 dollars.
- She earned 26 dollars in return. - She made a lot.
- Wait for me. - She gained 13 dollars in profit.
That was a good strategy.
Next auction is...
for Seok Jin's name tag.
You may convince the audience for the next 10 seconds.
- Please go on. - I have...
six beautiful sisters-in-law.
I'll set you up on a blind date with them.
(Is a blind date on the line?)
I'll pay all the expenses for your first blind date.
(He offers to pay the expenses.)
(That's a good strategy.)
You should go to a jewelry shop on the first date.
- Wait a minute. - They need couple rings.
You need to get couple rings first.
I'll pay for the meal and the movie.
Get your couple rings first.
You'll get a blind date with the beautiful, youngest sister-in-law.
Do you have her permission?
Not yet, but I'll take care of that.
What about...
the female staff members?
- What would they get? - Do you have any men?
I also have a brother-in-law.
I have a brother-in-law.
How old is he?
He's 48 years old.
(He's not too old.)
My brother-in-law...
isn't married yet.
- He's 48? - He's still single.
- I also have young brothers-in-law. - Let's get started.
I have young brothers-in-law who are great.
- It's for Seok Jin's autograph. - I really do.
As you saw, he signed it with a pen. Let's start with one dollar.
- One dollar. - Please.
- In five... - Don't avoid my eyes.
- In 3, 2... - Don't do this.
My sister-in-law is beautiful.
- We have 1 dollar and 20 cents. - Thank you.
- She studied chemistry. - 1 dollar and 50 cents.
We have 1 dollar and 50 cents.
In 5, 4,
- She's really beautiful. - three,
- She's like... - One dollar and 60 cents.
- We have 1 dollar and 60 cents. - You'd better show us...
- a proof of blind date. - In 5, 4...
- 3, 2... - No one is making a bid.
- We should confirm it. - Two dollars.
- We have two dollars. - Thank you.
I'm telling you. Se Mi is an auctioneer.
Didn't you hear that he's 48?
One of them is in his early 30s.
- Five dollars. - Five dollars!
In 5, 4, 3, 2...
- Come on, I need more. - One.
Come on, I need more.
She was startled.
Did you hear what she said? "My goodness, five dollars?"
She's spending her precious five dollars...
- on him. - What did you say?
- Goodness. - Take a photo of her blind date.
- All right. - He's 48 years old.
Yes, I have a brother-in-law who's younger.
- He looks like Kim Je Dong. - Here you go.
- He looks like Je Dong. - Congratulations.
Next up is Ji Hyo.
- Come this way. - Ji Hyo's autograph is nice.
- It's great. - Hers might be sold...
- She's the only female member. - at the highest price.
She has many fellow actress friends.
- Come up with a strategy. - Okay.
(They're dying to know what she's offering.)
This is my autograph.
My strategy is...
(What will be her strategy?)
Together...
- Together? - Together with you?
We'll take a selfie.
- Come on, that isn't good enough. - She's being arrogant.
- Also... - Show her that you disapprove.
- Come on. - Wait.
She's being too arrogant, don't you think?
- Let's show that we disapprove. - I am...
bad at taking selfies, but I'll try my best.
- I'm saying that I'll try my best. - Actually,
Ji Hyo doesn't like taking selfies.
- It's too embarrassing for me. - Here's your chance.
You never know how it will turn out.
It'd be embarrassing if hers is sold at a higher price.
Due to Kim Young Ran Act,
I'll give you 29 dollar 90 cent gift certificate.
- What kind of gift? - Whatever it is, I'll pay.
- That's the deal. - Why not just give them cash?
- Just give them cash. - It's to show my sincerity.
- Will you give them money? - Yes.
- You'll pay for whatever it is? - Yes.
- Will you come if they call you? - Yes.
- Really? - Yes.
This is not bad.
- She'll come in person. - Really?
- This is great. - It's a great prize.
Let's start the auction for Ji Hyo's autograph.
- We start with one dollar. - One dollar.
Five dollars.
- That's high. - First of all,
- She might come to Apgujeong. - the first bid is...
- as high as Seok Jin's final price. - I will.
It's the same as...
Seok Jin's final price.
- We have 5 dollars. - 10 dollars.
10 dollars?
The final price for...
Kwang Soo was 13 dollars. We have 10 dollars.
- In 5... - 15 dollars.
- We have 15 dollars. - Goodness.
He increased his bid by 10 cents for me.
Did he?
Did you have more money?
- Come back here. - I thought he didn't have money...
because he increased by 10 cents.
He's impressive.
How could he?
No matter the situation, he increases the price by 10 cents.
His lips were trembling when he called 10 more cents.
We have 15 dollars.
20 dollars.
- Really? - That's a big increase.
In 5, 4...
- 23 dollars. - My goodness.
Take turn one by one!
- You punks. - He called...
for 23 dollars.
We have 23 dollars.
- In 5, 4... - 30 dollars.
- 30 dollars. - Were you that generous?
Goodness.
- Four... - How high will it go?
- 35 dollars. - 35 dollars?
- People are getting competitive. - I think...
During our auction, they felt obligated to do it,
but now they're being honest.
- This is a real auction now. - Five.
- Four. - 40 dollars.
- 40 dollars? - Really?
- He has a lot of money. - He became handsome after surgery.
He's as handsome as a sculpture.
That's right.
Okay, in five,
- four... - 50 dollars.
50 dollars?
- 46 dollars and 50 cents. - 50 dollars.
- Come on. - It's 50 dollars.
- What's wrong with you? - It's 10 times more than mine.
He called 50 dollars.
Oh, my goodness.
It's not over yet, either.
It's so frustrating.
It's sold at 50 dollars.
(Ji Hyo's autograph is sold at 50 dollars.)
Thank you, Director.
- I'm doomed. - Women are dangerous beings.
After something is sold at a high price,
- It's unlucky to start after. - the next one isn't very high.
Is it my turn?
Next up is Haha.
He's in trouble.
(The auction for Haha's autograph starts.)
I'm getting competitive.
You can tell by the look in their eyes if they're working...
or if they're being honest.
Seriously.
Okay.
(Will he make a successful bid?)
- Okay. - What's your strategy?
Here's to the one who buys my autograph.
As it's the end of the year, there are many events.
- That's true. - If you bring this...
and come to my restaurant in Hongdae,
the whole party...
Never mind.
- No one said anything. - He hasn't decided yet.
No one said anything.
- What's going on? - He's estimating the cost.
- Be careful what you say. - For how many people?
- Make it clear. - For 10 people.
10 people? That's a lot.
I'll give you 10-person family discount...
Is it only a discount?
Come on.
(Is it only a discount?)
- Is it only a discount? - Come on.
Discount isn't good enough.
- It won't be a discount. - You should make it free.
- Gosh. - 10 people is a lot.
- Isn't it? - Make it four people.
- Make it four people. - Offer something you can.
- I'll give one table for free. - How about five people?
10 people can sit at one table.
People can squeeze in like this.
That's true.
(It's a new way to eat.)
- You can eat like this. - It's possible for four people.
- It's enough for 10. - It's possible.
Six people can sit like that.
Make your offer.
- Be generous. - What's your offer?
I'll give you 200-dollar coupon.
200 dollars?
Isn't that too much?
- That's not allowed. - You can take 200 dollars...
for a low price.
This isn't allowed.
Let's see what happens.
Get ready. We start at one dollar.
- It may be possible. - For 200-dollar gift certificate.
- That's too much. - We start at one dollar.
- 200 dollars? - 5 dollars.
- 5 dollars? - 10 dollars.
- We have 10 dollars. - He's quite generous.
- 15 dollars. - 15 dollars.
I offered a 200-dollar gift, after all.
- 20 dollars. - 20 dollars?
They don't care about the autograph.
They don't even care.
- Hey. - All right.
Haha wanted me to tell you this.
You can't take it home.
- You have to come... - That's obvious.
- and eat at the restaurant. - Right.
- It's for 200 dollars. - You can't take it home.
Sure.
- Cameraman? - 30 dollars.
Great.
33 dollars.
- 35 dollars. - 35?
The cameraman wants to use it with his family.
- He made up his mind. - He's serious.
- He's serious. - He made up his mind.
He plans to use as much as 100 dollars.
- He's serious. - Five, four...
(Is the cameraman the winner?)
- 100 dollars. - 100 dollars?
(She has everybody on their toes.)
Already?
Mi Yeon says 100 dollars.
You never did that for me, Mi Yeon.
- I didn't even know she was there. - Same.
- Me neither. - 100 dollars.
- Five, four, - That's great.
- three, two, one. - People won't go higher than that.
(That was the highest betting amount yet.)
That's pretty high.
Mi Yeon didn't want the autograph.
She wanted the coupon at a 50 percent discount.
(Is this what you're going to do?)
(Thank you, anyway.)
(Here's proof she ate at the restaurant.)
- Thank you for the food. - Thank you for the food.
Haha went too far.
You should do personal training for them.
- Personal training sounds good. - Consider it.
- They are starting to participate. - That's right.
They don't want the autograph.
You have to provide something on the side.
I should have done that.
That's not even it.
- The autograph doesn't matter. - It doesn't.
- It's not because they like me. - It's not.
I'm going to hold a concert for Turbo on Valentine's Day.
- Concert tickets? - If you bring this with you,
I'll give you two concert tickets.
- For two? - On top of that,
and... And.
During our last concert, we had Park Bo Gum and Song Joong Ki.
- What about me? - And me?
Yi Seul...
Yi Seul reacted for the first time.
- We're going to have guests. - Really?
You get a picture with the guest celebrity.
(A picture with the guest celebrity?)
- Really? - You'll get the opportunity.
- It'll be me. - No.
(That destroyed her heart.)
No, it's not him.
- It's me. - And...
there's more.
If you'd like to come as a couple...
and want to do something special on the stage,
we'll help you with it.
We'll plan it ahead of time in secret.
That's all included...
- in the package. - That's pretty good.
It'll be a special segment during the concert.
- Memories last. - All right.
Jong Kook's name tag...
We'll start betting on his name tag.
One dollar.
- 20 dollars. - 20 dollars?
- He has a girlfriend. - Really?
He wants to do something special.
- It'll be great for a proposal. - Four, three,
- two, one. - It's almost done.
(Hammering)
(Jong Kook's name tag is sold at 20 dollars.)
It's done.
- It's done. - That was too fast.
There are no couples here.
That was only 20 dollars.
- That was only 20 dollars. - My goodness.
We'll make it great.
He has a girlfriend.
Nobody here has girlfriends.
- We'll do something special. - Nobody here has girlfriends.
(Watch what I do.)
- I'll show you. - You were talking about couples.
Look at what Jae Seok is doing.
What if he invites them over to his house and nags at them?
What if he disciplines them?
Everybody.
- You've worked hard this year. - Come on.
Let's shake hands.
Jae Seok, you can't do that.
- You can't do that. - Stop it.
You can't shake hands with them.
- Why not? - You can't.
- Fine. - Get back.
- Let's get started in 10 seconds. - It must be...
a coincidence.
It's the strangest coincidence...
but I have a gift card on me.
You have it on you?
I'll planning to get it.
I was planning to get one.
- I was planning to get one. - What do you mean?
You were planning to get a gift card?
I mean, I was planning to get one and this happened.
- It's killing 2 birds with 1 stone. - How much is it worth?
- How much is it for? - I'll get one...
for 300 dollars.
- Really? - What are you doing?
- You must be insane. - You can't go this far.
That's not fair.
What are you doing?
- I have a gift card... - Let me go again.
- at home for 2,000 dollars. - I want to go again.
- Where's my name tag? - Fine.
- Bring it back. - I...
I have a bond at home.
I thought you might get the wrong idea.
That's why I was hesitant on saying it.
- Fine, then. - You can't get money involved.
- It has to be related to you. - Let's not get money involved.
- It has to be something memorable. - I was just joking...
but I'll do something memorable for you.
I recommend slapping your forehead.
- Slapping his forehead? - Slapping his forehead?
- Seriously? - He wants to slap his forehead.
- That's a great idea. - I'm in.
- Hold on. - I want to participate.
- Be quick. - Get out.
Hey.
- How could you? - What's the matter?
- 300 dollars. - What's wrong with you?
2,500 dollars.
57,000 dollars.
- That's a great idea. - Okay, then.
Everybody, along with my name tag,
you get to slap my forehead.
- Once is not fun... - Just once.
so you can slap his forehead whenever you want.
- You can do what you feel like. - You can't do that.
- What about five times? - You can't do that.
You can slap his forehead with this.
- This is part of the auction. - Hey.
- I'm not a lobster. - I'm sorry.
- It's part of the auction. - Hey.
- They're related. - I'll break my skull.
They're related.
You get a chance to hit a star's forehead.
(You get to hit a star's forehead.)
If you are stressed, take it out on me.
You can take your stress out on me.
I think their stress comes from you.
I think he'll bet the highest amount.
It's between Chul Min and Hwan Jin.
(It'll be a close match between those two.)
- What about Yong Woo? - It's between the producers.
Let's get started.
100 dollars and 10 cents.
You must be crazy. He's definitely insane.
- Hey. - 120 dollars.
- 120 dollars? - You're insane.
- 120 dollars? - 120 dollars and 10 cents.
- 120 dollars and 10 cents. - It's between them two.
Five, four...
(They're not stepping down from the competition.)
(Why are these two producers so eager?)
(They had to deal with Jae Seok all this time.)
(Jae Seok is like the nagging mother-in-law.)
- Five, four, three... - Go for it.
150 dollars.
(And there's Kwon Ryeol.)
(His forehead is mine.)
Kwon Ryeol.
You must be insane.
(Jae Seok's cameraman is the winner.)
All right. Five, four,
- three, two, one. - My goodness.
That was 150 dollars.
- I'm speechless. - Kwon Ryeol.
- Kwon Ryeol. - Hey.
- Come here. - I'll record this for you.
- Can I? - You have to leave it as memory.
- Record it. - Of course.
Take your glasses off.
(Running Man members are very enthusiastic.)
- I'm the cameraman. - What is he doing?
Kwon Ryeol.
(He even wets his hands while preparing.)
- Get started. - He only gets one chance...
so you can't do anything about it even if he doesn't do it properly.
- It'll be funny if he slaps hard. - Hold on.
I'll see how good you are. Slap my hand.
- That's not good enough. - It's not.
- You have to slap much harder. - Harder than how I slap Ji Hyo.
- What are you guys doing? - This is how hard I slap her.
This is how hard I slapped her forehead.
- I'm afraid he'll get hurt. - No, it's okay.
We get hurt from time to time.
- Hey. You're going to hurt me? - It's for 150 dollars.
- Why did you bet 150 dollars? - It's for 150 dollars.
If you're worried about hurting me, why did you pay 150 dollars?
- Hit him. Slap him hard. - Kwon Ryeol.
- No grudges, right? - Of course not.
Of course not.
- Of course not. Don't you know me? - Tell him.
I'm worried because it's you.
- That's why I'm worried. - Kwon Ryeol.
- You can slap me. - He made a fist. Don't punch him.
- You're not supposed to punch him. - Don't worry about it.
Don't worry. You can slap me hard.
I won't let it go if you don't slap me hard.
I won't let it go if you don't slap hard.
Slap him hard.
(Slapping)
(That was a 150-dollars slap.)
- Hey. - He hit the bottom of his forehead.
His neck jerked backward.
- He whacked him. - That wasn't funny.
It just hurt a lot.
- There was no sound. - My goodness.
- Kwon Ryeol. - Okay.
(Jae Seok sets a new record with 150 dollars.)
I recorded it all.
That was hilarious.
Actually, let's talk about it while we're on it.
It seems like our cameramen are stressed about their jobs.
- What are you implying? - That came out of nowhere.
What was that for?
- Look at Kwon Ryeol. - That came out of nowhere.
- Get back. - What are you saying?
- Who here... - That was just for you.
Who wants to give it a try?
- What are you saying? - It's okay if you don't want to.
- What about you? - Yoon Sang.
- I was the emcee for his wedding. - Is that right?
- What if you had the chance? - We text once in a while.
- I'm fine. - Okay.
(He's a loyal man.)
That's fine. You can whisper in my ear.
That's sweet.
Gary is gone.
Hey, hey.
- I'm getting sad. - Jae Seok.
(Gary's cameraman is lost without him.)
That's Gary's cameraman.
- His camera was pointing up. - Hold on.
I guess you're here just for the sake of it.
He's shooting the air.
I was wondering what he was shooting.
Didn't you get the call?
Who are you shooting?
Gary's not here anymore.
Accept the reality.
(Sung Oh is a man of loyalty.)
Fine. Just shoot those things.
(Jae Seok pities him.)
We'll put it to good use.
You should at least do something.
- Shoot those things over there. - You should.
(He was hard at work shooting those things.)
(The next target is Seok Jin's cameraman.)
I don't have any complaints.
Are you sure? You don't have any complaints?
Are you sure?
(Whispering)
- What is it? - What did that brat say?
(What did you say, Yoo Seok?)
What did he say?
He doesn't have any complaints...
other than the fact that Seok Jin isn't funny.
(He doesn't have any complaints except that Seok Jin isn't funny.)
(So that's how you've felt all this time.)
(He's guilty as charged.)
He's upset that Seok Jin doesn't get much air time despite his efforts.
He said Seok Jin isn't any fun to be around with.
(Seok Jin is at a bad spot after placing last at the auction.)
(What will happen next at Nambu Market?)
(Next week)
(Jeonju Tour Part 2)
(Following the name tag auction,)
(it's a grocery shopping mission.)
(And...)
(the super rookie of 2016, Blackpink)
(They're cheerful and charming.)
(Watch out for their playing with fire.)
- You're being used. - Which celebrities did you date?
(Three reasons why you like Infinite Challenge more than Running Man.)
(Jeonju Tour Part 2, featuring Blackpink)
(Running Man is looking for viewers to make memories with.)
(Visit our website for further information.)