("The Secret of the Frozen Village")
An ice witch cast an evil spell on the...
once warm and peaceful Running Village.
All the houses were destroyed by the strong wind.
The only people left in the frozen Running Village...
are the five brothers and sisters of the Orange House and...
the five brothers and sisters of the Blue House.
Only 10 children now live in the village.
Do you want to know who these children are?
(The children are inside the fairy tale book.)
The oldest of the brothers and sisters of the Orange House,
Seok Jin, had a habit of talking to himself.
(He acts like he's talking.)
He talked to himself.
This is so annoying...
The second oldest of the Orange House, Jae Seok,
always complained to his older brother...
- that he was being too loud. - You talk way too much.
- No, you talk too much. - You always talk too much.
When Jae Seok hit Seok Jin,
Seok Jin didn't try to stop him.
When Jae Seok hit Seok Jin again,
(Jae Seok hits Seok Jin.)
Seok Jin got very angry...
but didn't do anything about it.
There was only one person who could make them be quiet.
That person is Jong Kook, the oldest son...
of the Blue House,
which is the sworn enemy of the Orange House.
Seok Jin, who was older than Jong Kook,
always tried to fight him.
But he was no match for Jong Kook.
Even when Jae Seok and Seok Jin joined forces,
they were still no match for Jong Kook.
(Jong Kook is victorious.)
Jong Kook had...
two younger brothers, Haha and Kwang Soo.
Haha, who was short,
and Kwang Soo, who was tall,
got along very well. The two brothers were...
best buddies.
With their arms around each other's shoulders, they slept together.
- Catch! - They played basketball.
(They look very uncomfortable.)
And they danced together.
Quiet.
Running Village has...
another secret.
The youngest daughter of the Blue House, Ji Hyo,
and Gary, the third son of the Orange House,
were dating despite their brothers' strong disapproval.
- What are you doing? - What?
When their brothers were nearby, the couple pretended...
to hate each other and pulled each other's hair.
(They are fighting to the death.)
- Go. - Beat him up.
- I hate you. - Beat him up.
- I hate you. - That's right.
(Giggling)
- Where is she going? - Where are you headed?
- It's like a real fairy tale. - Where is she going?
(Which house will the next child belong to?)
The fourth son of the Blue House, Si Wan...
- What? - Si Wan is here?
- Is he here? - He was so handsome he had his...
- Is it Si Wan? - own fan club...
- Is it Yim Si Wan? - in the village.
(The fourth son of the Blue House is so handsome he has a fan club.)
- Yim Si Wan. - It's really Yim Si Wan.
(He is very handsome.)
(Running Village's most popular man, Si Wan)
(He is fiercely charismatic...)
(and has incredible acting skills.)
(Yim Si Wan has become a renowned actor in his own right.)
- Nice to see you. - Hello, Si Wan.
(Intelligent and determined, Si Wan always tries his best.)
- Wow. - Long time no see.
(But he was always the first one to be eliminated.)
- Hello. - Si Wan.
You're very good looking.
(Girls go crazy when he waves at them.)
- I'm your biggest fan. - I'm your biggest fan.
- I'm your biggest fan. - He is very good looking.
(She is going crazy over him.)
(She is a huge fan of Si Wan.)
He even danced with Yun Hwa, who was right next to him.
Is that really in the story?
(She doesn't care about the story. She wants to dance with him.)
- I'm your biggest fan. - Si Wan...
is the biggest star in Running Village.
Let's...
- go. - Where are you going?
- There's another one? - There must be another guest.
- Over there. - There must be someone else.
Is it one of my family members?
The fourth son of the Orange House...
- Our house? - is Hee Jun.
- Moon Hee Jun? - Moon Hee Jun?
That fat guy?
This is the original super star of the village.
(Is it a member of H.O.T?)
(The fourth son is...)
(the renowned actor, Lee Hee Jun.)
(The fourth son of the Orange House, Lee Hee Jun)
(Sometimes, he plays a charismatic, tough character.)
(Other times, he plays a romantic, charming character.)
- He's handsome. - He is handsome.
- Hello. - Nice to meet you.
It's so nice to meet you.
- Wow. - Each house needs a handsome son.
- Right. - That's right.
Although he's not that good looking, he's still...
- He's charming. - He is very charming.
- He's still very charming. - Right.
Hee Jun was great...
at singing.
(Hee Jun was great at singing...)
He was also good at dancing.
(and tap dancing.)
Hee Jun was the most talented man in Running Village.
- He's very talented. - My brother.
- Join us. - Right.
(He looks more charming by the minute.)
Next is...
We have to go over there now?
(They're going to meet the final child.)
- Slow down. - Where...
- are you going? - Where are we going?
In the Orange House, there lived...
a young girl named A Sung.
- A Sung? - Is she really here?
(A Sung? Can it be?)
(She's very young and cute.)
(The youngest daughter of the Orange House, A Sung)
(The cute girl from "The Host"...)
(has now taken Hollywood by storm.)
(Over the years she has become a much beloved Korean actress.)
- Wow. - This is great.
- Wow. - Amazing.
The last child was A Sung.
- A Sung... - Yes.
was an adorable girl who had a beautiful smile.
(She had a beautiful smile.)
- Wow. - Throw some flower petals.
(Now she looks even prettier.)
Mesmerised by her charms, the village's boys were left speechless.
(The boys are mesmerised by her beauty.)
(They are crazy about her.)
Her brothers of the Orange House...
- did everything she told them to. - Right.
- It's too cold outside. - You're cold?
- What? - Hold on, I'm coming.
Wait. Take this.
- Here you go. - But that's my...
- Here you go. - Take it off.
(What? Why does it have to be me?)
I knew he wasn't going to take off his own coat.
She only needs one coat.
You should take yours off too.
- I'm still cold. - Take it off.
- Take it off. - Take it off.
Hey!
- No, that's okay. - Take your clothes off.
- Are you cold? - You have a lot of clothes on.
- A Sung says she's cold. - No.
Let go.
Why does it have to be me?
What adventures will Ji Hyo's...
family and A Sung's family have now that...
the ice witch has transformed Running Village...
into the Frozen Village?
Ji Hyo's family and A Sung's family went to...
the place where their homes used to be.
However,
the witch's curse had already...
- destroyed their houses. - Where did my house go?
- Mum. - Where did it go?
Mother!
- What's going on? - Stop doing things like that.
- It's cliche. - Exactly.
- I'm sorry, I'll try harder. - The viewers don't find it funny.
Say that you're sorry.
- Right. - I apologise.
(He promises to make better jokes in the future.)
As they shivered in the cold, Ji Hyo and A Sung...
insisted that their brothers build them...
- a new house. - At least they're not asking...
- us to buy a new house. - Right.
- That's a relief. - Right.
- At least they're being reasonable. - Right.
They looked very cute as they whined...
- to their brothers. - That's right.
- All right. - Be cute.
- Be cute. - Yes, be cute.
- Try being cute. - Yes, let's see it.
Please build a house for me.
(Please build a house for me.)
She's very cute.
- Among the 10 people... - Ji Hyo, you should give it a shot.
- That's how it's done. - Please build me a nice house.
Please build me a nice house.
Hey.
(They are so violent to each other.)
- Have you gone insane? - What are you doing?
- What on earth was that? - What are you doing?
Family aren't supposed to kick each other.
The brothers gave their little sisters piggyback rides...
so that their feet didn't touch...
- the snow. - Hey, give me a piggyback ride.
(She demands a piggyback ride.)
- Hurry up. - One person should do that.
Now the brothers went to gather ice...
so that they could build their houses.
- What? - Where is the ice?
- Where is it? - It's over there.
- Do we go right now? - How do we carry the ice?
- There it is. - It's over here.
Where is it?
Here it is.
We have to bring as much as we can in one trip.
How do we carry the ice?
- Is that the ice? - Do we get it from here?
- Is this really the place? - How do we carry the ice?
- This is really... - There's no point in...
- trying to carry this. - It's too large.
You can't carry it...
There's no point in...
- trying to carry it. - Seok Jin.
- What? - There are sleds over there.
- Really? - There they are.
There are sleds over there.
You should have told us in private.
(The other team heard her.)
I didn't think that through.
- Where are they? - Go where Jae Seok is right now.
Jong Kook, we have sled. Why would you...
- They're over there. - Where?
- Over there. - Oh, over there?
- They're over here. - Because it's heavy...
Here they are.
Why are you so slow?
(Seok Jin is slowing things down.)
Put me down over there.
Just my feet shouldn't touch the ground.
- Put me down. - Okay.
I can put her down here, right?
Then hold on.
Here we go.
(She fell onto the snow.)
(Technically, only her bottom and back are on the snow.)
It's fine as long as your feet don't touch the snow?
So it's okay as long as her feet don't touch the ground?
(She's being dragged on the floor.)
- Hey! - Hey!
It's all right as long as the feet don't touch the ground.
- Good job. - Just don't put her feet down.
- Good job. - Wait.
- Hey! - Wait.
Hang in there, Kwang Soo.
You just have to keep your feet in the air.
(He lifts her.)
Hold on.
That's it.
Let's go.
There.
(Oh dear!)
Let me help you.
I can put my feet here.
It's cold.
It's cold!
(It turns out Hee Jun is such a sweet brother.)
It's so comfortable.
This is so comfortable.
(Run, Hee Jun!)
(While Hee Jun and A Sung are having a good time...)
Are you all set?
(Kwang Soo and Ji Hyo are carrying the ice.)
(Ji Hyo slides off from the sled.)
Hey!
- Kwang Soo! - Stay there.
It's so light now.
Stay there for a while.
Hee Jun.
- I'll be right back. - Hee Jun, please load the ice.
This one.
- Wait! - Hold on.
- That's our ice! - I'm sorry.
They are our enemies.
Ji Hyo, just crawl using your hands.
Just crawl.
Just make sure your feet don't touch the ground.
You used to be very good at crawling when you were young.
But this is an uphill.
- Yes. - Life is an uphill.
Take me!
(I hate you guys!)
When will we finish stacking all those ice cubes?
We have to stack everything here?
(It's been 20 minutes since they began building the igloo.)
This is crazy.
(Now the once desolate building site is...)
(getting filled with ice.)
Gosh...
Until when do we have to do this?
Is there another way to do this?
This is crazy.
(Team Ji Hyo and Team A Sung are trying hard to build the igloo.)
He's trying to steal it.
- He's trying to steal it. - Leave it.
Okay. I dropped it.
Gosh.
Why don't we play rock-paper-scissors...
- and bet ice? - Pardon?
How do you want to do it?
The winner gets the ice.
- We'll play rock-paper-scissors? - Let's just play it once.
- Let's play fair. - Gosh.
- Let's play fair and square. - Right.
- What will you give? - What?
What will you give?
I'm going to give scissors.
- Scissors? - Yes.
Rock, paper, scissors.
(They both gave rock.)
You said you'd give scissors.
You believed that?
Rock, paper, scissors.
Give me that ice.
Why did you do that?
- Good job! - Si Wan!
I'm so upset.
Why did you do that?
(He's not only smart but also hard-working.)
- Si Wan, you are... - He's such a reliable person.
I will just leave everything here.
You are amazing, Si Wan.
You're good.
(Si Wan is Team Ji Hyo's dark horse.)
(With his brain and quick wit,)
(he showed how well he could build a house in a jungle.)
- The third... - Where should I put it?
All right.
(He becomes Si Wan the Architect once again.)
If we put the pillars there,
it will be a right triangle.
It will be a triangle like this.
And we will build it up like this.
- If it can be supported... - Okay.
- Okay! - He's right.
Si Wan is the best.
- If it doesn't work... - He's a smart guy.
- Si Wan, you are... - He's such a reliable man.
This is really...
How can we do this?
- Si Wan is... - Si Wan is really diligent.
(They don't have much time left to finish the igloo.)
(Move, boys!)
Today's theme is a fairy tale,
but we are doing manual labour.
This is crazy.
(It's a fairy tale about a sweatshop.)
Gosh, my hands hurt.
Magic, magic.
Winter fairies came...
to help the tired boys.
- Fairies? - Fairies?
"We will help you build the igloo."
(Singing a yodel song)
(She cracks up.)
"But only one team..."
"gets to get our help."
- Which language is that? - What's wrong with the fairy?
- What is she doing? - She's just a woman from here.
Why is she singing a yodel song?
The boys decided to play...
"My Darling Sister" game...
and win the fairies' hearts.
- "My Darling Little Sister" game? - "My Darling Little Sister" game?
This is how you play the "My Darling Little Sister" game.
The boys will first lie down on the floor on their back.
Using both hands and feet,
they will support the board.
They will slowly move the board...
and move their little sister on top of the board.
The team of the girl who rings the bell first will be the winner.
Okay.
Kwang Soo, Haha, come here.
Let's win this.
- This is going to work. - I will move towards the bell.
Just support the part where I stand.
Don't mind the end part.
When we move, you move.
- Right. - We can do it.
- If you don't support it well... - Two people will be...
supporting you, so it won't be heavy at all.
- Okay. - It won't be hard.
- Do we have to crawl like this? - We can line up in one line...
and then go forward.
How?
We will just line up in one long line.
And then we will just go forward?
We will move the board in one line.
Wait. Wait.
Will we be able to support her?
- Go up. - Hey...
You can run too.
- Ready. - Support it well.
- We have to use our knees? - Let's...
Put your knees on the board.
Let's go.
- Let's go. - Do they touch the board?
(Team Ji Hyo moves in pairs.)
Hurry. Hurry.
- Just go. - Hurry up.
- Hurry. - Go forward.
- All right. Go more. - We are faster.
- We are faster. - Hurry.
- We are faster. - Move more.
- We are faster! - Hurry!
- We are faster! - Next person!
- I am here! - Hurry.
Hurry!
We are almost there! Come on!
We are almost there!
- We are almost there! - We are almost there!
Let's go to the end!
(Which team will be getting help from the winter fairies?)
- We are almost there! - We are almost there!
Let's go to the end!
- Come on! - Go to the end!
(Team Ji Hyo wins.)
Okay. We lost?
We won!
- We did it! - We did it!
Wasn't she supposed to do it while she's up?
We did it.
(We don't have to work now!)
- We did it! - We did it!
(Disappointed)
Team Ji Hyo won...
and got the fairies' help.
And the built the igloo...
in no time.
- That would scare the fairies. - The fairies!
Look at the fairies!
The fairies!
- They are the fairies! - They are the fairies!
(Winter fairies came to help.)
- This is amazing. - I envy you.
- They are here to help us. - I guess they are.
We were betting on that?
Since there are so many of them, we don't have to do anything.
Right.
- You should take this. - Take this.
- All right! - You cut this?
- No. - Cheer up, everyone!
- Cheer up! - They are so fast.
(With the help of the fairies, Ji Hyo's igloo gets done fast.)
Our team is amazing.
Just do three each.
- I am so thankful to them. - I love you!
Our igloo is so shabby.
(They are installing a tarp.)
That's a tarp?
This is not how it's supposed to look.
Good days will come too.
I will earn a lot of money and build you a nice igloo.
It's big enough to lie down.
Why don't we put another tarp over here?
Another tarp...
Our igloo is too shabby.
- This is not it. - Their igloo is so nice.
- Well, this is... - That's good enough.
Be quiet, everyone.
You have to wrap the igloo like this.
(Ji Hyo's ice palace is revealed.)
- Okay. - That's nice.
- Wow. - It's like a real house.
You're right. It's like a real house.
- Have a seat here. - There's no other way.
- Yes, there is no other way. - It's quite all right.
This is perfect.
The tarp should've been a little bit wider.
You can't keep breaking into our place.
- Hey. - I'm sorry.
- You are so fussy. - What are you doing?
- It was your place? - That's trespassing.
- Don't trespass. - I didn't know it was a house.
- You didn't know? - Gosh.
- You live there? - Yes!
It's our house. Look at my family all sitting down.
(Don't look down on us.)
- Gosh. - What's that?
We are naturalists.
Ji Hyo's got help...
from the fairies and...
built the house in no time.
- Magic! - Magic!
For Ji Hyo and A Sung,
who didn't get to eat while building the igloo,
the boys decide to go on hunting.
- Hunting? - Hunting?
Which of their brothers will be going hunting?
Get rid of this fairy tale!
- This is crazy. - Until when do we have to do this?
Please choose the most handsome...
- and the ugliest brother each. - It's Si Wan then.
- Start now. - It's Si Wan and...
- Kwang Soo then. - What are you talking about?
- You two should go. - What are you talking about?
- It's you. - Gosh,
- it's not me. - It must be so tough...
- for this team. - Hee Jun.
- I'm not the ugliest. - Why would you...
- I'm not the ugliest. - That's not it.
Hee Jun is voted as the most handsome because he's in our team.
- Seriously. - You're not that handsome though.
- You're lucky to be in our team. - Yes.
- Thank you. - The little sisters...
decide to follow their brothers on hunting.
- Oh! - Oh.
- Yes! - Maybe we will really go hunting?
- We will go now. - All right. Take care.
- Hunt a lot. We're starving. - We will hunt something.
- Hunt a lot. - We will hunt something.
- Please wait for us. - Our house is perfect.
(Team Ji Hyo heads to the hunting ground.)
I'm starving.
It turns out Si Wan is not that good at playing games.
I am not good at playing games.
I like playing games though. So I always watch Running Man...
- You like playing games? - Yes.
I love it.
(He's got passion, but he's got no talent for it.)
Do you cook well?
These days, I cook at home.
- You do? - Really?
I usually cook chicken breast fried rice.
I sometimes eat it with tortilla.
- How do you do it? - That sounds delicious.
It's really delicious.
I took a picture of it with my phone. It was delicious.
You were proud of yourself, so you took a picture of it.
- Yes. - I never knew you do that.
(This is the picture in Si Wan's phone.)
You're nothing like what I expected.
I cook sometimes these days.
But no one has tasted my dishes yet.
We can taste them today.
Anything tastes good...
when you eat outdoors.
But that's just my opinion.
(But that's just my opinion.)
Please don't be so sure of yourself.
I like fishing, by the way.
Where do you go fishing?
I usually go sea fishing.
I've caught a lot of rockfish.
I've even caught saw-edged perch a few times.
- Really? - In Jeju Island.
That's amazing. You caught saw-edged perch?
You must be good at it. Please show your skills today.
I'll do my best.
(If they go fishing today, Si Wan will be able to contribute.)
(A Sung and her family are also on their way to find food.)
As I'm an actor, I'm not used to being...
in front of so many cameras all at once. I get confused.
You have only one camera when you're acting.
You can ignore all of them.
What do the others do while we find food?
I'm sure they're doing something.
Of course.
(What are the others doing while we search for food?)
Until the brothers and sisters come back from their hunt,
the other members will find cooking utensils and other ingredients.
They're going to first decide...
which items they want.
And then they have to win games to acquire them.
(Up-to-date utensils vs old-fashioned utensils)
If we get that one, we can make anything.
Exactly.
Oh, there's dongchimi.
I'm suddenly craving some dongchimi.
Even just dongchimi and rice will be nice.
- We need spoons and chopsticks. - You eat dongchimi with rice?
- How can you do that? - Dongchimi is nice with rice.
- You eat dongchimi with rice? - It's delicious.
Really?
- I didn't know people did that. - You just don't understand.
Charcoal-grilled squid is amazing.
(It offended Gary.)
(Is he talking about me?)
(Now, he reminds everyone of squid.)
Put me on charcoal.
Go ahead.
- I'm just joking. - Try and see if I can be grilled.
(An angry squid)
(It's funny.)
The first game is called...
31 Lemons.
- What's that? - 31 Lemons?
We have 31 lemons here.
- You're going to eat them in turns. - Are we going to eat them?
The one who gets to eat the 31st lemon...
That's mean.
- That's too many. - I get the idea.
You can choose to eat 1 to 3 lemons at a time.
- Do we have to swallow them? - Should we start? Let's start.
- "Let's eat 31 lemons." - "Let's eat 31 lemons."
(Seok Jin goes first.)
- You have to pick the right one. - Done.
- Done. - Are you taking only one?
- Say how many you're going to eat. - I'll eat one lemon.
You can decide how many later.
Let's decide as you go.
I just touched it with my tongue and it stings.
I only touched it with my tongue.
I'm not going to chew it.
(Here it goes.)
(He bit the lemon.)
My stomach is sensitive.
(Sucking up the lemon juice)
That looks like a mouth guard.
Get up.
(Vitamin C overload)
- This is terrible. - I can feel his pain.
(Everybody's feeling his pain.)
The 31st person to eat the lemon will end the game.
I'll eat one.
It's awful.
It'll depend on what Gary will do.
(He becomes ugly.)
Look at his face.
(You look so ugly.)
(Too sour)
This is terrible.
Does he have to exaggerate like that?
- He's acting. - I'm not acting.
- He's certainly not acting. - Why does he have to act?
He's not acting.
- Are you stopping at one? - I drooled.
(Gary sets out to find out the truth.)
(Let's see.)
(Too sour)
You see?
- You said he was acting. - The squid is being grilled.
The squid is being grilled.
(This squid contains a lot of Vitamin C.)
(He's in pain.)
(The squid squirts the ink.)
Boy, it's sour.
(He is worried.)
- You have to finish that. - It's finished.
- There's some left. - Finish it.
- Are you stopping at one? - Yes.
Are you stopping at one?
I was going to eat two, but it's impossible.
Eat three.
Even eating two of them is hard.
- She seems to like it. - Do you like it?
- I'll just eat it up. - No!
- Is it tasty? - No, no.
(Sucking the juice)
Is this sour for you?
- Of course it is. - I don't think it's sour.
(Biting the lemon)
How can she do that?
(She ate all of it.)
How can this be possible?
- Were you hungry? - It's not an orange.
It's not sour. It's not bad.
Now they'll think we were exaggerating.
(Is her tongue made of steel?)
This can't be possible.
- How many is she going to eat? - Hey, you're crying.
Your eyes teared up as you were eating.
Why are you crying?
(Say something.)
(Your eyes are telling a different story.)
(Have you been crying on the inside?)
This lemon is...
so delicious.
Let's shuffle when we're halfway through.
Jong Kook...
is already calculating.
He's guessing Haha will lose.
(He's always looking ahead.)
- It's hard to even eat two. - It's too sour.
(Will Jong Kook conquer the lemon?)
(Squid number one)
(Squid number two)
(Squid number three)
(Squid number four)
(Which team will acquire the nice utensils?)
(The other members arrived at the hunting ground.)
Using the prepared tools,
catch as many trouts as you can.
(Catch the trouts under the ice.)
This one is better.
You have an hour.
You should catch as many as possible during the hour...
for your family.
(Taking care of his little sister)
Do we get blankets?
- Yes. - I brought it.
- It's not given. - It's her own.
- What? - She brought it from home.
I have one at home too.
Then go get it.
(Then go get it.)
(It's not a good idea to argue with Jae Seok.)
We brought a blanket.
We're fishing.
Why don't we start?
- Let's start. - Shall we go?
We'll get started.
They took all the tools.
Hurry up!
Let me borrow your blanket.
I think this one will be better than a lure.
- Is this better? - I think so.
(Si Wan even knows fishing terms.)
Is this how you do it?
Si Wan goes fishing a lot. Is this better?
Yes. That one is called "lure". But that one won't catch a lot.
I see.
I think we need some blankets, too.
(Let's see how many fish they'll catch.)
(Jae Seok is worried that A Sung would get too cold.)
A Sung, sit on the chair.
Wait.
Where's my blanket?
(The blanket is right on his back.)
(My blanket is gone.)
(It must be floating around somewhere.)
(He's getting goosebumps.)
(The wind blew the blanket off.)
There it is.
(The wind saved him.)
- A Sung, sit on the chair. - I'm fine, thank you.
You can sit here.
- Do you see the fish there? - Where?
Right here.
There you go.
(He's taking good care of A Sung.)
You can see the fish under the ice.
(They're looking for good spots.)
(A Sung tries catching one.)
(Trying to break the ice)
(Catch me if you can.)
I want to catch it. What should I do?
(I want to catch it. What should I do?)
I just want to catch at least one.
(I just want to catch at least one.)
A Sung,
do you see any fish?
No, I don't see any.
(No, I don't see any.)
Wait.
(Wait.)
(Did she find something already?)
(Will A Sung be the first one to catch trout?)
That wasn't it.
Trout are orange...
and the ice reflects my jacket.
(Are you sure you're not mistaking goldfish for trout?)
(I couldn't let the novice catch the first fish.)
(Si Wan takes action.)
(This is the beginning of a legend.)
I like fishing.
I've caught a lot of rockfish.
I've even caught saw-edged perch a few times.
Really?
(Fishing is all about patience and concentration.)
(Focused)
Si Wan.
Show me how to do it.
(Show me how to do it.)
First,
let me try.
Let me find out how we should do it.
I heard where you fish is also important.
Should we go out to the borders of the lake?
- Will that be better? - I'm not sure.
Should we try near the border?
(Si Wan tries to get away from him so he can concentrate.)
(But Kwang Soo follows Si Wan.)
The fish might be around the border since it's cold.
Si Wan, how do I take this out?
- Si Wan. - Yes.
How do I do it?
Si Wan.
(Exhausted)
(Shaking his rod)
I've tried fishing on other shows...
but I've never caught anything.
(He hasn't caught a single fish in the past 25 years.)
Never?
You should move your rod around now and then.
There's one.
You can see through the ice...
You can see whether the fish is biting your bait or not.
You're not on my team. Be quiet.
(I forgot we were enemies.)
We're still neighbours.
(Will he catch a fish for the first time?)
- It's here. - Really?
I saw a fish passing.
Where?
(A Sung doesn't even know what colour trouts are.)
(Kwang Soo doesn't have any idea how to fish.)
Where did it go?
That way.
Don't lie.
- Really. - That way?
(I saw it go that way.)
Is it really orange?
- No. - Okay.
- It's black. - Is it?
Yes, its back is black.
(What was I after all this time?)
Look.
Oh my.
(While she was gone,)
(fish ate all the bait.)
A fish ate the bait.
- What? - Really?
- Yes. - Did they?
The bait has gone.
(Fish are swimming around.)
(It's party time.)
Where was it?
It was over there.
Which hole?
It's the second one over there.
(Kwang Soo moves.)
(He doesn't stay in one place.)
I'm going to catch one.
(Waiting is important in fishing.)
(You have to wait like this.)
(He hasn't moved since he picked this hole.)
(He's patient.)
There's no fish.
Finally.
- Take 2. - Take 1...
- and one more. - Eat two.
- There's no point. - Hey.
- It doesn't matter. - Two is too much.
- Hey. - I'll do it.
- I'll do it. - Stop eating.
- Stop. - Hey.
- Do it! - Go!
You'll break your teeth.
(Jong Kook eats the 26th lemon.)
(He's shaking.)
Hey.
Seok Jin, please don't touch.
(Take your hands off.)
I heard him whisper.
I'll tell you.
Gary said, "We're done."
I was right here.
Do you know what Seok Jin said?
"Let's hide one."
I was right here.
(He's embarrassed.)
(We're done.)
(Let's hide one.)
(What?)
How could you say that when I'm standing right here?
- I can't believe him. - I need the cookware.
Eat one.
(Seok Jin eats the 27th lemon.)
Oh gosh.
He takes a big one.
- Eat it. - Take one.
(Haha looks like he's dancing.)
You can do it.
(Haha eats two lemons.)
- Stop it. - That's good.
(Haha eats three lemons.)
That is the last lemon.
He did it.
You did it.
(Team Ji Hyo wins and gets to pick first.)
(Team Ji Hyo: Gas burner, spoons and chopsticks)
(Team A Sung: Coals, grill, forks and spoons)
The second game is...
- Two-footed Basketball. - What?
You have to pick up a water bottle...
with your feet and throw it in the trash can.
Whoever puts in the most water bottles wins.
(Each person gets two tries.)
There's dongchimi!
Let's get rice.
- Shall we get rice? - Rice?
It won't be easy.
(Jong Kook goes first.)
We want instant rice.
- Do it right away. - Okay.
(Go!)
(Will he get it in on his first try?)
(It hits the trash can...)
(but doesn't go in.)
- It almost went it. - Yes.
(It was so close.)
I got the direction right but not the height.
(Jong Kook can try one more time.)
I'll try again.
(It's Jong Kook's last try.)
(Here it goes.)
(It flies high.)
(Will he get it in...)
(or not?)
- That's it! - It's in.
(Goal!)
(Team Ji Hyo 1 : 0 Team A Sung)
(That was awesome.)
- That's great. - He got it in on the last try.
You can do it.
- Do it. - No, not yet.
- Not now. - It's windy.
- No. - Wait.
- Wait. - Go get some air
You dried squid.
(Oh man.)
- Okay. - Do it.
- Do it. - It won't go in.
(Here it goes.)
(Will it go in or...)
(not?)
- It won't go in. - Do it properly.
(It barely misses.)
(It didn't go in.)
- What a shame! - That was so close.
- That was really close. - They are good.
(Haha's last try.)
(He is nervous.)
You have to wait for the right moment.
- You have to wait for that. - Okay.
- It's not time yet. - I know.
- You have to wait. - Okay.
- It's here. - It's now.
You have to do it now. In 1, 2, 3.
(Gary distracts Haha.)
(Haha gets distracted.)
(Haha fails both times.)
Gary.
(I will remember this.)
Gary, you have to get it.
Haha was distracted.
Jong Kook.
- Is is Eagle Five? - It's "Squid Alien".
(That's funny.)
Don't put it too close to my ears.
(Haha tries to distract Gary.)
It's windy.
Squid, squid, squid
Gary should sing this song.
- This song's perfect for you. - You should...
- shoot a squid commercial. - It's perfect.
I'll get in it the first time.
(Gary is ready.)
(Missed)
(It doesn't go in.)
(Gary was distracted by the "Squid Alien" song.)
Seok Jin, you have to put both bottles in.
How?
(Seok Jin has to succeed twice.)
(Will I be able to do it?)
- We lost. We already lost. - Yes.
- Okay. - We can still eat dongchimi.
- Right. - I can cook rice.
(We'll just eat what we have.)
We have some rice.
- That's it! - That's it!
(Goal!)
(Seok Jin made it!)
- He did it! - I did it!
(Team Ji Hyo 1 : 1 Team A Sung)
You're good.
(If he makes it, Team A Sung wins.)
Please.
Will we lose again?
It's hard.
It's not easy.
(He throws it.)
(Will Seok Jin...)
(succeed or...)
(fail?)
(Goal!)
(It's a miracle.)
(Can we eat delicious food?)
He got an award last year.
So he must be lucky this year.
(The award must be his lucky charm.)
It's cold.
- We should play this game more. - Yes.
Right.
- We shouldn't do brain teasers. - Take it.
I'll take this.
(Choosing food)
Shall I take kimchi?
- Hey. - Dongchimi is too cold.
- Okay. - We need kimchi.
- I want dongchimi. - Me too.
- I really want it. - Me too.
- It's great. - That's awesome.
- Do you want to switch? - I want dongchimi.
- Shall we switch? - No.
- I wanted dongchimi. - Really.
- That's what I wanted. - Me too.
- Really. - We need kimchi.
- I wanted dongchimi too. - I'll eat one now.
Dongchimi's delicious in winter.
- Of course. - I'll get frozen in winter.
Why do I feel like we lost?
(Why do I feel like we lost?)
(Team Ji Hyo: Sausages, dongchimi, hot chocolate and rice)
(Team A Sung: Kimchi, ice cream, instant rice and water.)
(So far, both teams caught no fish. They have 20 minutes left.)
(Without any fish, we might starve.)
Look at this.
(It's moving.)
I got a bite.
You have to pull it up!
(Fish eats the bait and leaves.)
It's gone.
- What? - It's gone.
- Did you lose it? - Did it eat the bait?
Yes.
That's good.
What are you saying?
How could you say that?
- What? - That's not nice.
(It's because I haven't caught anything.)
(He stares at the hole.)
I got it!
- I got it! - Really?
(Really?)
Really?
Did you really?
I got it!
(Will there be a fish?)
I've never caught...
a fish during a shoot.
There's no fish.
A fish just went by.
- It's for real. - I got it.
(There's a trout.)
(It's a trout.)
(It's a big one.)
(How lucky!)
Hee Jun!
- Wow! - I got it!
- Wow! - Look at this.
(Jae Seok catches a fish on television.)
(Jae Seok has never caught any fish on television ...)
I think I caught something!
(even though he has been on so many shows.)
- Finally! - Kwang Soo!
Kwang Soo.
(He's so touched.)
- I'll put it over there. - Okay.
- Bring it. - Take it.
I can't believe this.
This is amazing.
I think we could fill up to 5kg.
(Hee Jun comes over...)
That's huge.
I know.
(to congratulate Jae Seok.)
This is amazing.
- Look. - That's awesome.
I'm so happy.
- So it is possible to catch one! - Yes, I'm so happy.
- That's great. - Wow.
(You're so lucky.)
You can do it.
Oh my!
I got it! I got it!
(Suddenly?)
- I got it! - What is it?
(Did he really catch one?)
- What? - Wow.
He got it.
(He caught a fish.)
Kwang Soo.
Catch it quickly.
I got it!
- I got it! - Good job!
- It's really big. - There they are.
Si Wan, there are a lot over here.
(He wants to catch a big fish.)
Just wait for them like this.
(Maybe I'll get to catch a big one.)
(There is none.)
This is not going as planned.
(Should I just move to a different place?)
- A Sung. - Yes.
- Take an artificial bait and... - Okay.
- An artificial one? - move it up and down near...
the bottom of the lake.
I've never caught a fish before.
I see why people go fishing.
I could feel the fish biting the bait.
- Right? - This is fun.
My fishing pole just wouldn't stop moving.
(He's gained confidence.)
(Of all people Kwang Soo caught me.)
- Si Wan. - Yes.
You have to move it slowly.
You have to move it?
- Otherwise, they... - Right.
- won't bite. - I got it.
(But...)
(he was so confident about his fishing skills before.)
- This bait isn't good enough. - Really?
I see why people go fishing.
(How is Kwang Soo doing better than me?)
- I just lowered it... - Right.
- and it was just sucked in. - I see.
I must not be doing it right.
(And now Kwang Soo is next to him.)
I live to go fishing.
Now that I've caught one...
(Kwang Soo says he lives to go fishing.)
(Someone blows a whistle.)
There are fish over here.
(The fishing time is over.)
Oh, no.
Let me catch just one.
Give me just 10 more minutes.
I can see the fish going by.
I even felt the fish bite.
Hee Jun, do you want to come back here tomorrow?
Do you want to?
(He's disappointed.)
(Ji Hyo's family and A Sung's...)
(family each caught one fish.)
We're done.
Yes, it's boiling.
We're done. We prepared the food.
- This isn't our house. - I mean...
We're back.
- Right. - Hey.
Welcome back. Did you catch anything?
Did you catch anything?
- We got trouts. - Really?
- Yes. - It's slippery.
- We caught a lot. - Hey.
- We just have to grill this, right? - Right.
You can just grill it right away.
- Just grill it, right? - Put it on here.
Where do I put it?
Over here?
- Is this how you do it? - You...
- haven't done this before, right? - On the bottom.
Isn't this how you do it?
- No, I don't like camping. - This...
This is...
I think you put it here.
- What is this? - It's okay. What is this called?
We have budaejjigae and seafood soup.
Wow, you prepared a lot.
But it's not very good because we made it.
I can already tell...
that it's going to be bland.
Why are you so bad at cooking?
(At this rate, the food will never be ready.)
- How is it? - What on earth is this?
- It's really bad. - What is this?
We can't fix it by just boiling it.
Do you have any more ingredients?
We don't.
You put the noodles in too early.
Try this.
(Ji Hyo is using a strong double gas burner.)
Look at the lid.
- This is amazing. - Wow, it's boiling.
- Wow. - Wow.
(It's boiling.)
It looks really good.
This is unbelievable.
This is amazing.
(They are jealous.)
- Wow. - Ours isn't boiling.
It's like lava.
- We should try it. - This looks good.
- Goodness. - Let's just go to sleep.
- Let's... - Ours isn't boiling.
Eat this first.
Hey, can you lend us your gas burner?
How long do we have to wait?
(It looks it's going to take a while.)
(Ji Hyo's family has a secret ingredient.)
Just put it all in.
- Right. - Yes.
- Red chili pepper paste. - You don't have any?
(Ji Hyo is busy cooking.)
Ji Hyo is showing her feminine side, for a change.
- Right. - No, this is nothing.
- Wow, it's been such a long time. - It's been a long time.
- Now... - She's putting the ingredients in.
- She's such a good cook. - She's using garlic.
- What do you think? - Good.
I put the garlic in.
Wow.
- How is it? - Yes.
(With the gas burner, Ji Hyo cooks better.)
This is amazing.
(She's finished preparing the feast.)
Can't we start eating now?
(Kwang Soo wants to start eating.)
We have plates over here.
This soup is very good.
It's good, right?
I can't believe how good it is.
Later, let's put noodles in the soup.
Go on. Try it.
We're still cooking, but they...
They're already full.
We've been cooking for an hour now.
For goodness' sake.
The noodles are still not boiling.
Why didn't you win the gas burner instead of this?
Try playing the game yourself.
Oh, come on.
I didn't know it would be this important.
For how long do we have to light the fire?
Goodness.
Why is this so hard to do?
Are you a boy scout?
What?
What is that?
Oh no, I'm dizzy.
- I'm dizzy. - Why are you dizzy?
- What's wrong. - The gas.
- Did you inhale the gas? - I'm so dizzy.
- Hey, Gary. - What?
- Here, drink this. - I'm dizzy.
- It's dongchimi soup. - Okay.
- This is really good. - Wow, we had that?
Why don't we have dongchimi?
We don't?
(The soup revitalised him.)
- Is it good? - Do you...
want to try the dongchimi?
(Jong Kook brings the dongchimi.)
Yes.
Here, try it. You'll be able to eat a lot more...
after you drink this.
(He's amazed.)
This is unbelievable.
Here, you have to drink a lot of it.
- It gives you energy. - Right.
All right. I'm ready for anything.
(He is energised.)
- I feel like a new man. - Stop.
Everything goes so smoothly for us.
Please stop eating the budaejjigae.
- Right. - We have other food as well.
Okay. Goodness.
Just give it to our neighbours.
All right.
(That made them angry.)
They are annoying.
(Nothing seems to be going their way.)
- Wow. - What is this?
- Isn't this trout? - This is trout sashimi.
- Wow. - It looks like salmon.
It looks just like salmon.
Is it sashimi?
- Let's try it. - Do you think it'll be good?
- How is it? - What's this?
- Dongchimi. - This is tasty.
(Jae Seok wants to eat it, too.)
- Here. - Thank you.
(Si Wan tries the sashimi.)
- There you go. - We don't have any kimchi.
(He looks pleased.)
- It's so good. - Here.
- Kwang Soo, try it. - He doesn't want it.
Or he can have it later.
It's good.
Oh, my.
So this is what a trout tastes like.
What's wrong with our team?
(They put more seasoning powder in order to save the soup.)
(They put all of it in.)
He had a habit of doing that ever since he was on "Family Outing".
- What? - You secretly put a lot of in.
This will taste good now.
(The seasoning powder saved it.)
Look.
It's like udon, right?
(He's tasting the soup.)
It's savoury.
- It's very savoury. - I doubt it.
- Taste it. - It just tastes like ramyun.
This is a traditional flavour.
It's just like my mother's cooking.
Just like your mother's cooking.
This is very good. A Sung, try it.
- It's good, right? - It really is.
- It's astounding. - Here, Hee Jun.
I told you so.
It's really good.
(Hee Jun approves.)
- It's good, right? - Yes.
It's really good.
- Did you make this? - Of course I did.
We have a good cook, too.
- Is it cooked now? - Let's see.
It's ready.
Let's check if it's done.
- All right. - I think it's ready.
- You really grilled that? - I have a good feeling about this.
Wow.
The skin is peeled off.
It's been peeled off.
- Wow, it looks good. - How is it?
- The skin's been peeled off. - Look.
- Wow. - It looks good.
(It looks really good.)
It looks good.
(The pink meat looks appetising.)
Go ahead and eat it.
Go on.
(He takes a bite.)
(How does the trout taste?)
- How is it? - Wow.
This is the real deal.
(He's astounded.)
Kwang Soo, tell us how it is.
- It's good. - He told you it's good.
Of course, it's good.
Right. Of course, it's good.
I'm telling you. It's really good.
- This is really good. - See? It's good.
This is really good.
Of course, it's tasty.
It was freshly caught.
It was fresh, so of course it's good.
- Wow, it's good. - Ji Hyo.
- It's good. - I'm not jealous at all.
- Here. Try it. - It's really good.
- It's really good. - It's delicious.
I'm not lying. It's really good.
This is way better than...
what you guys had.
- Seriously. - It's good, right?
It's really good.
(Everyone's in love with it.)
It's really tasty.
It's so flavourful.
Si Wan, try it.
(Si Wan also tries the trout.)
It's good, right? It's not fishy at all.
(They finish eating the last bit of the grilled trout.)
- Here. - He wants some.
Okay. It's really good.
You grilled it well.
- Is the hot chocolate bad? - Hey.
- It's good. - Go get some.
- With water... - Give us some hot chocolate.
You seem very confident...
when you're making demands.
- Give us some hot chocolate. - But he doesn't like...
sharing his things.
- Give us some. - You're demanding hot chocolate.
- We have nothing to lose. - What?
- In exchange, I'll give you water. - We don't even have a house.
We're homeless and have nothing to lose.
A Sung is very funny.
Let's make a deal.
Go away.
Do you know how old she is?
- No. - She's 25 years old.
She's no longer the girl from "The Host".
Don't people get married at that age?
What?
You're not even married and you're 41.
She only 25. What are you talking about?
I wasn't talking about me.
- I'm talking about her. - You're 41 and still not married.
- Goodness. - Goodness.
What are you doing over here?
- Give me some hot chocolate. - What?
Go away.
Get out of my sight!
- What? - I said, get out of my sight.
- Are you kidding me? - He wants hot chocolate.
- Let's wrap this up. - Since it's cold here,
- should we rest inside? - Let's go.
Should we go back inside?
Since it's cold,
let's gather around the fire.
(Gather around the fire.)
- The fire? - Come by the fire.
I brought a heater for us.
- Look at that. - This also works as a heater.
It becomes a heater if you open it.
Should we remove some ice in the middle...
so the air will go inside?
Honestly, they are so annoying.
- Let's make a window for them. - Let's make a window for them.
Oh my gosh!
(Oh my gosh!)
Darn it!
I stepped on the puddle again.
- You could go around. - I soaked my feet in there.
- What's wrong with you? - Unlucky ones are always unlucky.
Goodness.
Look at that!
What?
(Jong Kook cracks up.)
I'm so upset.
(It serves you right!)
(My enemy's misfortune is my happiness.)
Gosh.
- That was amazing. - It's so cozy in here.
- Because the wind is blocked. - Aren't we the sweetest siblings?
I know.
I think I can even sleep here.
I feel like pushing the wall from behind.
I was going to do that, and then I dipped my foot in the puddle.
(What will happen to these two rivalling families?)
We should push the wall.
Gosh, I hate them.
When the night fell on the cursed Running Village,
the blizzard became even stronger.
(Listening to that makes them colder.)
Seok Jin and Jong Kook...
went to get firewood...
so that the siblings could spend the night in warmth.
Firewood?
This is crazy.
- Hurry up and leave. - Seok Jin and I?
This is the 21st century. Where can we get the firewood?
- Is it near... - What?
Where can we get the firewood in the 21st century?
Why do I have to do this with Seok Jin?
This is crazy.
Where should we go to get the firewood?
Are they actually going to get the firewood?
You are my firewood!
You are right.
You are my darling pollack.
Seok Jin and Jong Kook didn't come back after a while.
So Gary and Kwang Soo went to find him.
- Why? - We don't need to look for them.
They are not important to me.
Gosh, it was just getting peaceful here.
- Bye, pollack and squid. - What?
- Are we a set menu? - Yes.
I am not a pollack though.
- Then am I a squid? - No.
Squid and pollack.
What do we do? Where are we going?
(They came out, but they don't know where to go.)
Jong Kook!
Seok Jin!
(They start to worry.)
It feels like we are soon going to be scattered.
- It's not necessary. - We will disappear one by one.
(They are worried.)
Gary and Kwang Soo didn't come back either after a while.
So, Hee Jun and...
Si Wan went to find them.
- What? - Where is everyone going?
- I will look for them. - Come back safely.
- We will go look for them. - You must come back.
- Make sure you come back. - We will find them.
- Bye, Hee Jun. - Bye.
- Okay. - We'll come back if we fail.
(Hee Jun and Si Wan go to find their missing brothers.)
- Oh, gosh. - Be careful.
That's an ominous sign.
(That's an ominous sign.)
So far, who left?
Kwang Soo, Jong Kook,
- Gary, - And Gary,
- and Seok Jin. - Seok Jin.
Where did they go?
(Where did everyone go?)
It's so cold.
What's going on?
What's happening?
(They are the fairies who helped them build the igloo.)
(They take the two guys somewhere.)
(Where are you taking us?)
- It's strange. - It's warm.
What's strange?
Why are the brothers not back yet?
I will go look for them too.
- How about us? - How about us?
(How about us?)
- What? - What?
Where are you going?
- What's going on? - Are they leaving us behind?
(What are we supposed to do now?)
What?
Oh, dear.
The evil ice witch took the boys...
who went out to get the firewood.
(The witch took the boys?)
They actually tied my feet?
Where is my family?
You said this is a fairy tale!
This is such a cruel fairy tale!
(He's cuffed.)
What did I do wrong? What did I do wrong to get this?
(Si Wan tries to analyse the situation.)
Why am I cuffed?
(The six boys are held captive, not knowing what they did wrong.)
Guys!
(At that time,)
(some people appear.)
We were having a good day.
(Someone appears...)
(and removes the blindfold.)
(Is that...)
(a clown?)
What?
(Without saying a word,)
What's this?
(the clowns just dance.)
Are they clowns?
Why are you taking things this far today?
(Why are you taking things this far today?)
What are we supposed to do?
(Where are they? And why are they held captive?)
We have to now start looking for them, right, A Sung?
Yes.
(A Sung, Jae Seok, Ji Hyo and Haha go to find the boys.)
A Sung, you have to find them.
(I need to find and rescue them.)
It's spooky in here.
(They pass through the witch's greenhouse and go outside.)
(She stops.)
(Oh, my gosh.)
(It's a Dark Spirit!)
Haha! Haha!
What is it?
There are people wearing black masks outside.
So we can't let them see us.
We are not supposed to let them see us, right?
We have to be careful. Shall we stick together?
Shall we?
What?
Who are they? They are so scary!
Who are they? I'm scared!
(I'm scared!)
Are they the Dark Spirits?
What do I do?
(Will the little sisters be able to save their brothers?)
Wait. What's this?
(Walking)
What's this?
(The clowns bring a table.)
(It's a Korean beef meal.)
You want me to eat that?
It's Korean beef?
(Korean beef?)
(Is this a surprise Korean beef barbecue party?)
Korean beef?
They cuffed me, and now they're grilling meat in front of me.
What is going on today? I really have no idea.
(The meat is cooking nicely.)
(He's so desperate to eat the beef.)
Yes, please.
(He desperately wants it.)
(What is this? Will they give it to me if I beg?)
Please.
(He eats it.)
Really?
(I'm supposed to eat it?)
(Seok Jin eats a piece too.)
(Kwang Soo trembles.)
(He enjoys the beef.)
It's delicious.
(It's delicious.)
Oh, they're actually feeding me?
Why?
Really?
Gosh.
(They remove the table.)
What are you doing?
You gave me just one piece. That's it?
(Chewing)
(They remove the table too.)
I haven't eaten much yet.
(I haven't eaten much yet.)
(Why are they removing the table?)
Gosh, it smells amazing.
(It smells amazing.)
(Gary eats the meat.)
(It's amazing!)
Please give me some more.
(Please give me some more.)
Why? I only got the taste of it.
No!
It's unbelievably delicious.
(The clowns remove Gary's table as well.)
I wish I could eat a few more.
Why did they grill the meat?
(What is going on?)
(Meanwhile, in the witch's garden filled with the Dark Spirits,)
(A Sung is looking for the name tags.)
They hid it somewhere too deep.
(They hid it somewhere too deep.)
I have to find the name tags first, right?
(Oh?)
I found it!
(She found something.)
It was in the plastic bag!
The evil ice witch took the boys who went...
to get firewood.
In order to rescue them,
you must give them their name tags.
(They have to find empty name tags and write their names.)
Somewhere in the garden,
there is the Witch's Door, which will take you...
back to the village and lift its curse.
So you must open the Witch's Door with your brothers and...
return home.
But the door only opens once.
So you have to find it and open it before the other family finds it.
As soon as they heard what the Winter Fairy said,
Ji Hyo and A Sung...
hurriedly left for the witch's garden...
with their brothers.
Will they be able to...
escape this place together?
(Which name will A Sung write on the first name tag she found?)
Hee Jun.
(It's Hee Jun, who's been taking good care of her all day.)
(Now she has to find him and put it on him to rescue him.)
Those Dark Spirits.
(Jae Seok is trying hard to find the name tag too.)
(Where is the name tag?)
What is this?
(Running towards Jae Seok)
(Jae Seok is surrounded by the Dark Spirits.)
(Wait, this laugh...)
(sounds familiar.)
(Wait,)
(this is Yun Hwa.)
(Why is she here?)
An ice witch cast an evil spell...
on the once warm and peaceful Running Village.
(Yun Hwa was the one who welcomed the members to the village.)
(But it turns out that Yun Hwa was the ice witch.
(All of the traps were set up by the ice witch, Yun Hwa.)
What am I supposed to do?
I'm going to destroy everything. I'm coming at you.
Wait.
Ice witch,
what's going on?
Dark Spirits, turn him around.
Wait a second.
(The ice witch has control over all the spirits.)
Look.
Yu Jae Seok.
Wait.
(She ripped off his name tag.)
(The unexpected attack of the ice witch...)
(puts Jae Seok into the ice prison.)
(How are the captured members doing?)
My goodness.
(They're serving him beef again.)
What are they up to?
(Grilling the beef)
(Jong Kook opens his mouth.)
They're letting me eat.
(After one bite,)
(the table is taken away.)
Why are they doing this all of a sudden?
(The table is taken away after one bite.)
And they leave?
(What's going on?)
Here we go. We have the beef.
That's enough.
(They're even making a wrap for him.)
(Yum)
They're making me crave for more.
Look at that.
That looks amazing.
You know how to grill beef.
Red on the inside,
brown on the outside.
(The smell of the beef made him forget about his mission.)
This is delicious.
Thank you.
(Munching)
Where are you going?
(Where are you going?)
(I want some more.)
(It's Si Wan's turn.)
(The beef is being grilled.)
At a certain time,
they come in with a table...
and serve me beef.
(Then...)
(there must be something special about the beef.)
I'm okay.
(I'm okay.)
I'm too full.
I don't want to eat.
I'm okay.
I'm not going to eat.
(Disappointed)
(There must be something going on.)
I'm too full. I can't eat.
I'm okay.
I'm really okay.
(Determined)
I'm full.
I ate too much.
(The clowns leave the table behind.)
(What's going on?)
(Why are they clapping their hands?)
Is this it?
(The clown releases Si Wan's left arm.)
There you go.
(Si Wan's left arm is released.)
Thank you.
Right.
You're supposed to resist. You shouldn't eat.
(You're supposed to resist. You shouldn't eat.)
(Grilling)
(Tempted)
Am I supposed to resist to be released?
Then I'm not eating.
(Are you sure?)
(Agonising)
That looks amazing. It must be high-quality beef.
It smells so good.
(It's hard to resist the high-quality beef.)
(Frustrated)
(Sighing)
It's so hard to resist.
There must be something behind it.
(The smell weakens him.)
Maybe one more bite.
(I can't resist any longer.)
(Seok Jin gobbles up the beef.)
(As expected, the clowns take the table away.)
What's going on?
(He now knows the beef tastes good...)
(but has no idea what's going on.)
(Meanwhile, Jae Seok has been sent to the ice prison.)
- Jae Seok. - Yes.
I'll rescue you.
A Sung,
do you have a name tag?
I'll give you a name tag.
(A Sung is trying to rescue Jae Seok with the name tag she found.)
(She changes the name from "Hee Jun" to "Jae Seok".)
Thank you, A Sung.
(Jae Seok is released.)
Let's look for name tags.
They must be somewhere around there.
- Where? - We should run away.
Let's run.
(They hurriedly set out to find name tags.)
(Ji Hyo found a name tag and a pen.)
(I have to rescue my brothers.)
(She found another one.)
(After Si Wan passed the first stage,)
(the clown brought a tablet computer.)
Okay, I got it.
(This video clip is famous for making the viewer laugh.)
(Why are they showing this to me?)
(Am I supposed to laugh or not?)
(It becomes harder and harder to hold back a laugh.)
(This is a torture.)
I watched this play once.
They have fun with clowns at first but then it starts to turn creepy.
This reminds me of that play.
You eat.
If I eat, you'll stop.
You can eat.
Si Wan!
Where are you, A Sung?
Jae Seok!
(Tempted)
I'm fine. I'm full.
I'm full.
I'm not going to eat.
(This time, Seok Jin resisted.)
(His left arm is released.)
What's going on?
Are you releasing me?
Are you?
(Once they resist the beef, they pass the first stage.)
What did I do?
Am I supposed to not listen to them?
(I have to resist.)
That looks fantastic.
They're torturing me.
(Kwang Soo held out.)
(His left arm is released.)
Are you releasing me? So I was supposed to resist?
Was that the mission?
(That was it.)
They wouldn't feed me for no reason.
(Once he passed the first stage, they make him watch the clip.)
(It's the laugh-inducing clip again.)
(He bursts into laughter as soon as the clip starts.)
(Hee Jun also...)
(cracks up at the clip.)
(Giggling)
(Am I supposed to laugh with them?)
(Smiling)
(The smile is gone.)
What is it now?
(What is it now?)
Let me see.
(These two are still eating.)
It's hot.
(While looking for name tags,)
(Haha found Si Wan.)
- Why are you here? - Haha.
- What's happening? - Haha.
Why are you here?
It seems like...
I'm supposed to hold back my laugh watching this.
Don't laugh.
- I'll find the name tag, okay? - Then I'll be free.
- What smells so good? - Let's go together.
I was being tortured with beef.
- I'll bring it. Stay here. - Yes.
(Haha leaves to find the name tag.)
(Si Wan has to hold back his laughter.)
(He keeps a straight face.)
(He's determined.)
(He doesn't even move.)
(I won't laugh.)
(He's so good.)
(The video is almost over.)
(He makes it until the end.)
(He finished watching it.)
(Great job!)
I did it.
(His right arm is free.)
(He laughs.)
Can I laugh now? Show me again.
He's so funny.
(The old man is the funniest.)
His laugh is so funny.
He almost...
made me laugh.
I can get up now.
(Now he laughs.)
That old man...
was so funny.
They're here again.
(The clowns walk in again.)
(What is it this time?)
(He drops something.)
(What? Scissors?)
They gave me scissors.
(Scissors can cut...)
(this rope, can't they?)
These are for cutting.
The clowns left.
(They gave me the scissors to cut the rope.)
I won't use these...
until they come back.
(I won't use these until they come back.)
(He kicks them.)
(I won't fall for you tricks again.)
Si Wan.
Si Wan, I'll save you.
Where's the name tag?
(Trust me.)
Okay.
(Haha finds the name tag.)
I'll keep it.
If they notice, I'll use it.
If not, I'll save him. Okay?
Okay.
(The clowns are back.)
(I didn't fall into your trap.)
(Why is he still tied up?)
(Was I supposed to use the scissors?)
(They give him a new pair of scissors.)
(Do you want me to cut it?)
(The clowns exit again.)
I'll try one more time.
(I'll try one more time.)
If they bring me scissors again,
then I'll run away.
(He hides the scissors in the cameraman's pocket.)
(He goes back to the chair.)
(What will you do now?)
(They gave him another pair of scissors.)
What?
(What do you want me to do?)
(Do you want me to cut the rope?)
(They take a bow.)
(They exit again.)
Okay.
They told me to cut it. I'll cut it.
(I'll cut it.)
(Snipping)
(Wow)
(What's going on?)
(Did I pass?)
- Go, go! - Go, go!
(Si Wan is free.)
You actually gave me the scissors.
You...
tied me up.
- Are you free? - Yes.
- Thank you. - What happened?
- Well. - Hey,
- I got this for you. - What?
You know...
I don't usually do this.
I usually...
keep things to myself.
I'll give it to you because I like you.
Do you know that?
- Thank you. - You are...
the first-ever guest to start the race.
I don't want you dying right away.
- Okay. - Do you understand?
- I'll give this to you, okay? - I will...
rip two name tags, then I'll get mine ripped off.
I'll rip two name tags.
I'll rip at least two name tags.
(Yim Si Wan)
That's what I'm saying.
That's weird.
I can't believe I'm doing this.
(I can't believe I'm doing this.)
Let's go.
All right.
Show them what you got.
Let's go.
(These two are eating.)
(Jong Kook's being tempted.)
I won't eat it.
(I said I won't eat it.)
No.
(No, I won't eat it.)
I won't eat it.
I can't eat it.
(He denies the meat.)
(His left arm is free.)
What are you doing?
(Was this it?)
What?
What is this?
You're setting me free because I refused to eat.
(Now it's the video.)
(It's so funny.)
(He laughs.)
(The clowns exit.)
(He's serious.)
What?
(He shakes his head.)
I won't do as you say.
(I won't do as you say.)
That's right.
(His right hand is free.)
Okay, great.
Only one leg needs to be free.
(His leg has to be free.)
(They give him scissors.)
Do you want me to cut the rope?
(Do you want me to cut the rope?)
(He cuts it.)
(Snipping)
Is this it?
It's done.
Can I go now?
I can go, right?
I'm leaving.
This was it.
(Hee Jun passed the first two rounds.)
Is this a trick?
(He's given a pair of scissors.)
The simple way would...
be cutting the rope.
(The simple way would be cutting the rope.)
(Is it right?)
(He hesitates.)
Can it be this simple?
(Snipping)
(He isn't sure.)
(He cuts all.)
(Hee Jun is free.)
Okay, I'm free now.
Can I go now?
Good job.
Running Man is fun.
(Good job. Running Man is fun.)
Hee Jun.
- Hee Jun. - Yes?
- Where are you? - I escaped.
- Did you? - Yes.
We have to find Gary first.
(Gary is here.)
It's delicious.
I could live on meat alone.
(I could live on meat alone.)
Jong Kook is in this room.
- Hey. - Hey, Ji Hyo.
The four of us are here.
This isn't funny anyway.
- I thought I had to laugh. - Really?
We need to find Kwang Soo. I know where the secret door is.
Did you find my name tag?
- We have two. - We have two.
(They already have two name tags.)
He passed.
- Where's Kwang Soo? - Where is he?
- Where is he? - I can't find him.
(Snipping)
Good job.
(Jong Kook is free.)
- That's right. - That's good.
I should have figured it out earlier.
- We need to find Kwang Soo. - Right.
All we need is Kwang Soo.
We have both Kwang Soo's and your name tags...
But we can't...
find Kwang Soo.
Where could he be?
- Where is he? - I can't find him.
(I won't laugh.)
(He's about to cry.)
Did I really have to cry?
(No, you didn't.)
Am I free?
(Kwang Soo is free.)
(They give him scissors.)
Do I just cut it?
Really?
(Really?)
(Snipping)
(He cuts the rope.)
(It's a talent to be a simple person.)
I'm free.
I'm leaving.
(Now Gary is the only one who couldn't escape yet.)
(Meanwhile, A Sung and Hee Jun went to find the name tags.)
It's inside a zipper bag.
Where is it?
It's right here.
(Hee Jun finds a name tag that will lift the witch's curse!)
It's a blank one!
(Lee Hee Jun)
(Hee Jun is resurrected.)
He's back.
Kwang Soo!
- Come here. - There's the witch in the back.
- The witch is in the back. - The witch is there?
She's in the back down there.
- Where is your name tag? - I couldn't find it.
Si Wan.
- The witch is right there. - We are all here.
I don't have a name tag.
- Here's one. - We have to go there.
You got one, right?
(Kwang Soo gets a name tag too.)
There you go.
(Now they have to go to the Witch's Door.)
I know the way, so I will take the lead.
Si Wan...
(Ji Hyo will navigate.)
knows the safe way.
But we have to be fast.
- Hey! - Hey, Gary!
Did you find a name tag?
- I have to find a name tag? - Where have you been?
We need to resurrect you.
- Who? - You.
Gosh, Gary. What's wrong with you?
- You have to resurrect me? - Yes.
How did you know that?
What do you mean? I've been looking all over for you.
- You have? - Here. Where have you been?
(He puts the name tag on Gary first.)
- You can't... - Hey.
get caught.
All of us have to gather here...
and go through that door.
Okay.
Be careful.
Gosh, I should've eaten some more meat.
(At that time)
Hey, Gary.
(Look who it is!)
Where have you been?
- I've been looking for you. - Me?
- Yes. - Why?
What do you mean why?
- I have to rip your name tag. - No!
(I have to rip your name tag.)
(Catch Gary!)
Catch him!
(Gary is helpless inside the witch's garden.)
No!
No! No!
(It's ripped.)
(But I just got it.)
(At that time)
I will save you!
Don't come.
Go that way.
I'm going to put the name tag on him!
Run! Run, A Sung!
Run!
(A Sung gets her name tag ripped as well.)
Gary!
(I am sorry, A Sung.)
She ripped my name tag.
Did she?
(But she gets ready to be resurrected right away.)
(She puts her name on the blank name tag.)
Please put this on me.
Please.
(She's in a hurry.)
(Ko A Sung)
(I'm sorry, Gary!)
(I will find another name tag and come back to save you!)
That was so scary.
Run!
(Run!)
Let's go.
Over here! Save me!
- Save me! - Where's the path?
Where's the path?
Rip this, please!
Rip this!
- We have to hurry. - We have to be careful.
We might have to rip the others' name tags.
What are you doing?
- They are gathered. - They are complete.
Wait.
- No! - Rip it!
(Throw yourselves and defend the Witch's Door!)
Rip Kwang Soo's name tag!
(Oh my gosh!)
(They catch Kwang Soo.)
(Ripping)
Yes!
Hurry! Go!
Come on. You ripped it, right?
- We can do that, right? - I didn't know you could do that.
No.
(One person from each team is locked in the ice.)
- Hurry. - Hey.
Ta-da!
(It's a blank name tag!)
(Haha found a name tag a while ago.)
I found one.
(He hid it just in case he'll need it later.)
(He never knew it was going to save them.)
- I have one! - He's got one!
- You have a blank one? - He has one.
- You have a blank one? - Of course. I found one.
Hurry up.
Hurry up!
(If they resurrect Kwang Soo, they can escape right away.)
- Okay! - Hurry up!
- Here! - They might hear us.
- Come on out! - Cover his mouth.
- They are coming. - Jae Seok!
How do we go through this door?
(No way!)
(Will they succeed?)
Here we come!
(Here we come!)
(Team Ji Hyo successfully escapes.)
Ji Hyo and her siblings...
returned to the warm Running Village...
and lived happily ever after.
Meanwhile, where are A Sung and her siblings?
Good job, everybody!
- See you later! - Lovely.
Hee Jun, say something.
- It was really fun today. - Was it?
I got a name tag too.
I'll congratulate you in advance for your marriage.
(Hee Jun is getting married this spring.)
- Congratulations! - Congratulations.
He's marrying the lady who was once here.
- He's marrying Hye Jeong. - Hye Jeong.
After being on here three times,
my team finally won.
But most importantly,
I still haven't ripped someone's name tag yet.
You have to come again then.
- So I have a reason to come back. - Yes.
I will be happy to come back and give another try.
And let's give our special thanks to Yun Hwa...
who's been in the cold all day.
- You did a good job. - Good job.
- You did a good job. - She played three roles.
Team Ji Hyo wins!
(Regardless of the result, everyone had fun, and it's a happy ending!)
- What's that? - Something is coming down!
Those are footballs.
- Come here! - Come here!
I got it!
- It's an invitation. - An invitation?
We'd like to invite you to the ground filled with heat.
I will see you in Shanghai.
(Park Ji Sung)
(Song Joong Ki)
(Jung Il Woo)
(The mission starts as soon as they wake up!)
No! No!
Is this Mission Impossible?
(The mission begins with a football.)
I ripped it first.
(And they get the chance to score a goal!)
(Will Running Man be able to score a goal at last?)
It's finished!
(FC Running Man in Shanghai)