(The smell of the sea fills a romantic city, Busan.)
These dishes are famous.
These dishes in front of you...
are three dishes that Busan is known for.
These are Dongnae pajeon, eels,
and pork gukbap.
Each team will choose one dish.
- We want pork gukbap. - We'll choose pork gukbap.
- We said it first. - Who told you to pick first?
- We said it first. - We'll take the eels.
You can't do that.
- Let's have pork gukbap. - The thing is,
- I want gukbap. - I'm the team leader.
- We'll have eel. - Come on.
- We want eel. - But I said I wanted it.
What did you say?
- I just said that I wanted the eel. - So what?
- We'll have eel. - Ji Hyo.
We want eel, too.
- Can we get eel? - We want eel, too.
I've been craving some eel for a long time.
We should sort this out by rock-paper-scissors.
- Let's do that. - Okay.
- You should do it. - Rock-paper-scissors.
Nice.
(He laughs in embarrassment.)
- I'm always the unlucky one. - You are.
- This is really strange. - This is nice.
Today, we will do Busan Crossword Puzzle Race.
Busan Vacance
(They have to find the restaurants recommended by the people of Busan.)
We have guests who will join you with Busan Crossword Puzzle Race.
I wonder who it is.
- Are you serious? - Please come out.
(Who will join Running Man here in Busan today?)
- Oh, my. - I can't stop smiling.
(Here we come.)
(It's everyone's favorite girl group, Twice.)
(They swept the charts with their latest release, "TT".)
- "TT". - "TT".
- Ji Hyo. - I watched this yesterday.
(It's the famous dance Ji Hyo wanted to learn.)
- It's "TT". - This is so great.
(It's "TT" time.)
- They're so cute. - I can't believe I get to see this.
(Twice is here.)
(This is the dance.)
- So mean - That's the dance.
(Jae Seok is a big fan.)
(Is this how you do it?)
(This is their legendary hit song, "Cheer Up".)
I'm sorry
(Shy, shy, shy)
(Let's make some noise.)
(They take soft steps.)
I'll call you a little later
(Exclaiming)
(The song is reaching its climax.)
Let's go!
Let's make some noise!
(It's a therapeutic song that will make your pain go away.)
This is nice.
(It's a smooth finish.)
(The crowd is going wild.)
They're so cute.
Welcome, Twice.
(Today's guest is Twice.)
- Hello, we are Twice. - Hello, we are Twice.
Thanks for sparing your time for us.
Oh, my.
Hello, everyone.
Their new song, "TT",
- is doing so well on the charts. - It's a big hit.
Everyone around the globe is going crazy over Twice.
It's nice to see you again. We did a race together once.
There are three teams at the moment.
We prepared a game where you can be divided into different teams.
In front of you are the three most famous foods in Busan.
There are nine members of Twice with us today.
Maximum of three people can choose the same food.
We don't really care which one you pick.
- We like everyone. - That's right.
- Just pick what you want to eat. - Can I pick now?
- Yes. - Here I go.
(Da Hyun starts off.)
Please choose pork gukbap.
- Have you guys already decided? - They already know.
We'll all be teamed up with them.
(Three people picked pork gukbap.)
- I want eel. - Eel?
Four of you are lined up for Dongnae pajeon.
You should do rock-paper-scissors.
Let's do rock-paper-scissors.
(Rock-paper-scissors is always a good solution.)
- Rock-paper-scissors. - Rock-paper-scissors.
- That was quick. - I feel bad for her.
She was the first one to line up for it.
She had her eyes on pajeon since the beginning.
I feel bad for you.
(I feel like crying.)
(Team Dongnae Pajeon, Team Eel, Team Pork Gukbap)
Today's race is called Busan Crossword Puzzle Race.
You have to fill out your crossword puzzles...
with the names of the food recommended by the people of Busan.
When you complete a single row,
you have to move to a different spot and proceed there.
There are two chance spots where you can earn advantages.
If you succeed the mission, you can fill out two rows...
from a single menu.
You'll get a One Plus One Card.
One Plus One Card?
If you fill out the red boxes of the crossword puzzle,
you can remove a menu from another team's crossword puzzle.
I don't like that.
Why did you have to put those in there?
The team to finish five different menus first...
will win benefits they can use in the final race.
We will now begin a team game...
where you can test your team work.
(Team Work Mission gets started.)
The first mission is...
"Twice Statues".
While the person in front sings, "Twice Statues",
the teams will compete to finish their food the fastest.
The team that comes in first place will be able...
to fill out their crossword puzzle with the food they ate.
I see.
(Which team will finish this package meal first?)
How should we do this?
- Who likes coke? - Jong Kook.
You can drink the coke, Jong Kook.
If I drank two cans of coke,
(Jong Kook never drinks carbonated drinks.)
(Bottoms up, Jong Kook.)
Can I get diet coke instead?
(He's very picky.)
Just drink it.
Just drink it. That's not important right now.
You want me to drink both?
That's 224 calories.
Just drink it!
- Just drink it. - Just drink it already.
- Look how disappointed Mina is. - Look at her.
The person who will help us with the game...
is Yoo Kwon Ryeol.
(Twice lover, Yoo Kwon Ryeol)
It's Kwon Ryeol.
Don't look back so often just to see their faces.
(This is the man...)
(who was head over heels for Twice last summer.)
Look at him.
- Gosh. - What do you think you're doing?
You're blocking all the cameras.
(It's me again.)
(Long time no see.)
Pick up your chopsticks.
Ready...
(Who will eat faster?)
Ready, set, go.
(The mission gets started.)
Twice Statues
(Twice Statues)
(They have to stop moving when he turns back.)
(Pause screen)
(Glaring)
(He sneaks some food in his mouth.)
Twice Statues
(Twice Statues)
(She froze.)
(Can you let us eat this tteokbokki?)
(Coughing)
(Drinking coke can be dangerous.)
(Jeong Yeon caught the eyes of Kwon Ryeol.)
Da Hyun just...
(Da Hyun didn't do anything.)
smiled back at me.
- What are you talking about? - She smiled at me.
- Who would smile at you? - Okay.
Why are you blushing?
(Kwon Ryeol is taking full advantage of this game.)
If you caught someone, just say it.
What do you mean, "Okay"?
Call Da Hyun out if she moved.
- She smiled at me. - Gosh.
(He's too biased.)
(Thank you.)
(Is he going to be a better judge this time?)
Seok Jin's eomuk moved.
Seok Jin is out.
I thought that was his tongue.
That looks like his tongue.
It was this eomuk, not me.
Seok Jin is out. Please go over there.
(He's strict all of a sudden.)
- But this is... - Please leave.
But it was the eomuk that moved.
You should punish the eomuk, not me.
(Laughing)
Ji Hyo just laughed.
Ji Hyo is still laughing.
Ji Hyo is out.
(You're so mean.)
(Team Jong Kook is leading.)
Twice Statues
Where are you going?
(What are they up to now?)
(They're serious.)
Why did they get up? What are they planning?
(Moving swiftly)
(They form a barricade.)
(This is their chance to eat away.)
That's smart.
(Surprised)
- They're still eating. - They're not.
They're still eating behind the wall.
They're still eating.
(Kwon Ryeol walks over.)
- Keep eating. - Twice Statues
(What's this?)
(He's man-marking Team Haha.)
(What are you going to do now?)
(The other two teams eat away while Team Haha can't do anything.)
- Kwang Soo is out. - No way.
(Kwang Soo is out.)
Kwang Soo just ate something.
- What are you talking about? - His mouth moved.
(I don't know what you're saying, but I get that you're upset.)
We're allowed to eat while he's singing, "Twice Statues".
Kwang Soo is out.
(Swallowing)
Jae Seok is still drinking his soup!
(Spouting)
He's still drinking his soup!
- His mouth is sticky. - We're done.
(I got it on me!)
- We're done. - We're done.
- They're done? - Aren't they out?
I finished eating.
(The judge clears Jae Seok and Seok Jin's team.)
- Yes! - That's not fair.
Momo ate a lot of it.
This tteokbokki is really good.
- It is really good. - It's really good.
It's awesome.
- We were done, too. - Let's just eat.
We were done, too.
The winner of "Twice Statues"...
is Jae Seok and Seok Jin's team.
(Jae Seok and Seok Jin's team wins.)
What a great start!
- How incredible. They eat a lot. - They do.
The three of them helped out a lot.
The first place team will be awarded with the dish...
- to fill their crossword puzzle. - Is that right?
- It was Dongnae pajeon. - We'll deliver it to you.
(Dongnae pajeon)
The race starts now.
Jae Seok and Seok Jin's team can eat here,
and the other two teams will get moving first.
- All right. - Let's go.
Can we go after we eat, then?
I can guess which one that could be.
- We have to make up words that fit. - "Haha's favorite pork gukbap."
"Haha's favorite food is pork gukbap."
I can use abbreviations, right?
You can only use words that are in the dictionary.
What about "green onions in pork gukbap"?
Then you only get to eat the green onion.
"Demolishing pork gukbap".
That works.
- You can do that. - Okay.
- How do you eat it? - "Demolishing pork gukbap".
(Jae Seok's team finishes their pajeon.)
This person must be really picky to demolish their gukbap.
We made 1 word, right? There's 4 left?
- We have 4 left. - We did Dongnae pajeon.
It's not difficult filling this in.
We just have to meet a local.
Where is your hometown?
(He starts asking the staff members.)
Yours?
- I'm not from here. - And...
Can't we just lie? Right?
- Yes. - It doesn't show.
Nobody's from Busan. Where is your hometown?
- Where is your hometown? - I'm from Busan.
They're from Busan.
- They're from Busan. - That's right.
- Are you really from Busan? - That's right.
- Is that right? - "That's right"? That sounds funny.
Say my name in Busan dialect.
Seok Jin.
She is from here.
Where's your hometown again?
It's Busan.
Weren't you from Kyoto?
- It's Busan. - It is.
- Didn't you say Kyoto? - Say my name in Busan dialect.
- Seok Jin. - See?
- What about you, Jeong Yeon? - It's Busan.
She's from Busan, too.
(They're all from Busan now.)
You're all locals?
- Yes. - We know the geography well.
- Is that right? - I'm from here as well.
I wonder which restaurant has good eels.
Should we go near our next destination?
Let's go to an eel restaurant near Gukje Market.
All right. Let's go there.
Let's go there and try all the missions in the area.
That's not important. We need to feed them good food...
and have some fun. Don't you agree?
Sure.
I'm just happy that I'm with them.
We're not doing this so that you can be happy.
I'm still happy though. Aren't you all happy?
- We are happy. - See?
(They unite over Twice.)
Don't worry about it. It doesn't matter.
Let's have good food and play some fun games.
I'll look it up on the navigation.
Let's just go to the nearest one.
It's best if we go to a good restaurant.
There's one 370m away. It only takes a minute from here.
Really? Let's go.
(They get going right away.)
Let's go.
I'm so sad it took Twice this long to come back.
Shouldn't they stay overnight?
Twice is busier than you guys.
You didn't have to say that.
- We know that. - We do.
We know but that's not what we meant.
We want to go overseas with Twice.
- Thank you. - I want to go overseas.
Look at Sana's face. What should we do now?
I hope you make a lot of money, Sana.
Sana, Sana
Sana money, Sana
(They find it funny.)
Don't worry
How do you know this song?
Of course, I do. It's my song.
- Sana money. - Money.
(It's from a loan commercial.)
Are we here already?
- We are here! - There's no seasoning on it.
(They arrive at the pork gukbap restaurant.)
Where is it?
Where's the pork gukbap restaurant?
- Pork gukbap! - Here it is!
I think they're famous.
- Hello. - Hello
(Busan is known for their pork gukbap.)
Can we have two pork gukbap?
Let's order first.
- Write down the menu. - Sure.
(Pork gukbap)
No other team was here, right?
Thank you.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
You have to add a lot of chives.
Make sure you add a lot.
Thank you for the food.
- Thank you for the food. - Thank you for the food.
Thank you.
- Did I add too much? - Thank you.
(Slurping)
- It's really good. - It is.
(It's the best pork gukbap ever.)
How do you describe this?
It's my first time having pork gukbap.
- Really? - Yes.
The meat is soft...
and it tastes nice.
- It's nice? - Yes.
She sounds like an angel.
- I think it tastes nice. - Yes, Haha.
(Slurping)
(The more you eat, the better it tastes.)
It's really good.
It's great.
(The girls love it.)
They love it.
You must have been hungry.
I'm happy you ate a lot.
We're right by Haeundae beach.
What would you like to eat, Momo?
- Meat. - Where?
(Where are you talking about?)
- She meant meat. - Meat?
I thought she wanted to go somewhere.
- I thought she wanted to go there. - You meant meat.
I thought we talked about a place already.
What about you, Na Yeon?
I want Eonyang bulgogi.
- Eonyang bulgogi is good. - I like jjajangmyeon, too.
You all like meat.
Should we start with Eonyang bulgogi, then?
- Yes. - Let's do that, then.
- Momo looks so happy. - Do we have control over that?
We can meet a local person and give them a hint.
We can insinuate that we'd like Eonyang bulgogi.
Haha and Kwang Soo's team had pork gukbap.
Already?
- "Demolishing pork gukbap". - What does that mean?
Then let's do this.
- "Local Eonyang bulgogi". - Sure.
- That works, right? - We can continue this way.
- That's right. - She's right.
Once we get that, we can erase other people's words.
- We should reach there fast. - That's right.
That's right.
You pointed out something crucial, Jeong Yeon.
We should get there fast, then.
That's right.
We can do "everybody's favorite Eonyang bulgogi".
That's right. "Everybody's favorite Eonyang bulgogi".
Who came up with it?
(High-five)
(Maybe not.)
- Can I not high-five her? - Why?
Why would you do that? Na Yeon doesn't want to.
I was proud of her.
(They're funny.)
- We're at Haeundae. - Let's get off.
It's been a while since I've been here.
Let's talk to the locals before we ask them for words.
Let's mention that we want to eat meat.
Let's go. Look at this.
- The weather's great. - It is.
- Look at the water. - Girls.
Let's look at the water first.
- Sure. - This is Haeundae.
It's windy.
It's the ocean!
Isn't it great?
I think it's warm enough to play in the water.
(They're greeted by the winter ocean.)
It feels like summer.
(They're so excited.)
I can't open my eyes.
This is amazing.
Seagulls are not even flying away. They're enjoying the water, too.
- They don't care. - Look at the seagulls.
They're tanning. They look pretty.
They're not flying away.
(The girls start chasing the seagulls.)
They are so excited.
Na Yeon must like babies.
She does.
(Na Yeon's heart is stolen by a little boy nearby.)
She must like babies.
She loves babies.
I can see that.
Are you locals?
- That's great. - Excuse us.
- Excuse us. - Hello.
We are going to have a light lunch.
We all know that Busan is known for great food.
Don't answer right away.
- Don't say it yet. - Not yet.
Please listen to us first.
We have to go eat. Do you like meat?
(He attempts to insinuate.)
- Yes. - We want to have meat.
(Do you get it?)
Roasted clams.
(Roasted clams?)
(The insinuation has failed.)
- Roasted clams? - I told her not to say it.
(She likes meat but she recommended roasted clams.)
- I told her not to speak yet. - I wish you would have waited.
- Roasted clams? - Okay, roasted clams it is.
Thank you!
Thank you.
Do you like roasted clams?
Do restaurants open this early?
Are there restaurants nearby?
We have to find a restaurant that has roasted clams.
There's one.
Do you see one at the end?
It's by the waterfront.
We have to go that far?
I mentioned this before...
- but they don't open this early. - They don't. They open at night.
We have to eat if they're open, right?
We do.
But roasted clams are not served this early.
(They hope the owner of the restaurant slept in.)
Sir.
- Hello. - Hello.
Do you have roasted clams?
(Do you serve roasted clams this early in the morning?)
Yes.
You don't serve them this early, right?
We can.
- You can? - Right now?
Yes.
Do you serve them in the evening?
You usually don't serve them during the day, right?
We do.
- You do? - Let's eat.
- Roasted clams. - Let's eat.
- We'll give you extra. - Let's eat.
We'll have roasted clams.
I didn't mean to ask such question.
(The clams look as delicious as Eonyang bulgogi.)
- Let's finish this line. - That's right.
"Everyone loves roasted clams."
We can also finish this one with "Eonyang bulgogi is awesome."
We can write "Eonyang bulgogi tastes awesome."
- That'll do it. - Other teams might do it, too.
- Okay. - But it feels like summer here.
I can't believe they serve roasted clams at this time.
People usually don't eat roasted clams for lunch.
- Look at that. - Here you go.
(There's an abundance of side dishes.)
- Half-dried herrings are in season. - It's half-dried herring.
The side dishes alone are enough for lunch.
We used to put shells in bags and sell them.
- Have you eaten one? - How do you eat it?
- Put the wider part in your mouth. - And suck it.
- Suck it up. - Suck it.
- This is delicious. - Goodness.
Isn't that amazing?
(He hears a laughter.)
I'm sorry.
(Excuse me.)
- Is this your first time trying it? - Why are you laughing suddenly?
- Why are you laughing? - She eats it so well.
Is this your first time eating it?
- Yes. - I sold these on the streets.
(We love gastropods.)
- It's really good. - Isn't it?
It's better if you eat it while it's hot.
Goodness.
(Goodness.)
No, I don't want it.
(Laughing)
Why are you laughing?
- Why do you keep laughing? - Why are you laughing?
Why does Na Yeon's enjoying her food make you laugh?
It's not like you're eating it.
When people eat on a Japanese show, they would say,
- "It's delicious." - "It's delicious."
- Now, it's all cooked. Dig in. - Thank you.
- This is really tasty. - It's delicious.
(She takes a bite.)
- Isn't it good? - Yes.
It's authentic.
(At this moment, they forget about bulgogi.)
Seaweed soup is great.
(She finds it very tasty.)
Is it that good?
(Her reaction says all about the roasted clams.)
- She expresses herself well. - Right.
Jeong Yeon is quiet, but she expresses...
with her face.
Na Yeon expresses with her voice.
It's my first time eating roasted clams.
- Seriously? - This is your first time?
This is really your first time having roasted clams?
- Then it all worked out. - This is great then.
It's amazing.
If someone recommends this again, do we have to eat this again?
- Yes. - Yes, we have to eat it again.
Maybe we should ask the question in front of...
- a bulgogi restaurant. - That could work.
Let's look for the closest one from here and one that'll serve quickly.
Or we could ask the restaurant's owner.
- Can't we? - Should we do that?
- We can ask the owner. - The owner must be a resident here.
- That's cheating though. - I guess so.
Where is the restaurant for eels? Here it is. Let's go inside.
(They came to fill out the line for eels.)
Goodness.
I'm glad it's not crowded.
- Hello. - Let's go in.
- Can we order? - We filled in Dongnae pajeon.
"A famous restaurant..."
- "for eels." - "For eels."
This is excellent.
Last week, Ji Hyo tried to do your choreography.
I did it wrong.
I was angry that I had to watch the music video before going to sleep.
(Last week)
(Her dance stirred up resentment among the members.)
- She did watch the music video. - Really?
She couldn't help but watch.
You should demonstrate for her.
- This is how you do it, right? - Yes.
(This is how you do it.)
Just like TT
You don't know how I feel, you're mean
It's true.
You are mean.
Goodness.
(Do you want to try again, Ji Hyo?)
Just have your fingers ready and tilt your head a little.
Ji Hyo, try it one more time.
- In 1, 2, and 3. - In 1, 2, and 3.
I'm like TT
(She isn't as young as them, but she challenges herself.)
You don't know how I feel, you're mean
You're mean
Yes, it's true. You are mean, Ji Hyo.
You're mean, too.
(Cute)
(For Ji Hyo, sobbing fits better.)
Crying turned into sobbing.
Look, they're moving.
Goodness. They're alive.
- They're alive. - They're moving. Are they alive?
Yes, they're alive.
(Live eels are served.)
- This is amazing. - I'm surprised they're alive.
(It's a special dish and you can taste the freshness of the sea.)
I can see they're alive.
- They're trying to get out. - It's scary.
- How am I going to eat this? - What a scene. Look at the tails.
I think they might get out.
- Thank you for the food. - Thank you.
- Thank you. - Enjoy it.
Mina, you can eat them now.
You can eat now. Dig in.
- I know that. - Do you? Okay.
- What's wrong? - It's good.
(I can taste the sea in my mouth.)
The onions are good.
- It's delicious. - Goodness.
(Chae Young cools it down before she eats it.)
I can dip it in the sauce.
I wouldn't have guessed they were alive.
The texture is really different.
You can call...
(How can you not like this?)
(They succeeded in eating eels.)
The texture was something else.
- We'll use our chance. - Okay.
- Let's have barbecue. - We'll be on our way.
For today, Haha doesn't exist.
I'll forget about myself and spend today just for Ji Hyo,
Sana, and Da Hyun.
I don't care if I don't win for a year as long as I win today.
It's all for these girls.
I will give away today for you.
I'll be your servant for the day.
What will happen if we don't win?
Why do we have to fight over this?
You kept at it.
- You should've stopped. - I have a family.
It was done, but then you kept at it and I wanted to have the last word.
Who is your favorite member in Running Man?
Why does he ask this sort of question?
- We won't take it personally. - We'll think about something else.
Just think of a member you wanted in your team.
I'm a fan of Kwang Soo.
(He's deeply moved.)
I think you might remember. A long time ago,
we met before I made my debut.
- We met once, right? - That's right.
He was really handsome and he truly looked like a celebrity.
- The Kwang Soo I saw on TV... - He looked stupid on TV.
did stupid things and funny dances.
(For Ji Hyo, he was a top star.)
I remember thinking to myself how handsome he looked.
Personally, I really like...
- Haha. - Hold that thought.
I don't think Ji Hyo finished talking.
- Can you wait? - I'm sorry.
(Can you not interrupt?)
- You starred in "High Kick!" - They're so nice.
- You remember the mosquito dance? - Yes.
- He did it yesterday. - Did you?
- My younger sibling likes it a lot. - Really?
- One, two, three, four. - One, two, three, four.
- I can't. I'm too embarrassed. - You did it yesterday. Come on.
Give him a round of applause.
(Please show us your dance.)
A giant mosquito bit my foot
It was very itchy
(He regrets deeply.)
(They are satisfied.)
I can't believe I saw it with my own eyes.
I haven't done this for ages and I did it two weeks in a row.
Next up is Sana.
The reason I like Haha is...
because his name is Haha.
Doesn't it sound refreshing?
Yes, it does.
(Doesn't his name sound refreshing?)
(Sana likes Haha because of his name.)
- I'm serious. - Who says something like that?
- You should pick someone else. - This is the real reason.
- I really like your name. - Don't pick on Sana.
- Is she serious? Come on. - This is the funniest reason...
- I've heard so far. - Hold on.
- Your name... - So my name sounds refreshing?
- Yes, your name sounds refreshing. - I can understand that.
Right, my name is rather hot than refreshing.
I didn't mean anything by it.
- We've arrived. - This is it. We're here.
- Is there a mission? - Is there?
We have to get this one by any means.
- Here's your mission. - Okay.
The mission for your chance is "Race the VJs".
What was that?
- What is that... - Before each team's VJ...
finishes eating one serving of samgyeopsal,
you need to complete a cross-word puzzle.
If they finish eating first, it'll count as a failure.
If you have a misspelling, it'll be counted as a failure as well.
If you succeed, you'll receive the One Plus One Card.
- Okay, we got it. - Let's start right away.
(The VJs get ready to eat.)
Please eat slowly.
It's okay to take your time.
- Please eat slowly to digest well. - Look at the side dishes.
Please chew your food well.
I hope you enjoy your food.
She wants you to enjoy your food.
- Good food ought to be enjoyed. - You should enjoy good food.
Please cut the meat into small pieces.
Your mission starts now.
- Please eat slowly. - Eat slowly, please.
- Eat slowly for your digestion. - Please don't eat too fast.
(Their first try has begun.)
"What is the string that you use to dry your laundry?"
It's clothesline.
"What is the name of piled up rice?"
- Let's solve the second question. - What is the name of the role?
Good food should be enjoyed.
"What is the song Shin Jae Hyo composed during the Joseon Dynasty?"
- It's "The Sound of a Flower". - "The Sound..."
"of a Flower".
- Read it quickly. - "What is the part that's stuck..."
- "along the thoracic vertebrae?" - Please eat slowly.
Ji Hyo sounds a bit angry.
- Slow down. - You're eating too fast.
- You eat so fast. - Isn't it hot?
- Let's move to the third question. - Please chew your food well.
Make sure you taste the food.
She wants you to enjoy your food.
- You must enjoy good quality food. - You should taste the food well.
Isn't it hot?
Please have some kimchi with it.
- You are eating too quickly. - Eat slowly. Hold on.
- Let's solve the third question. - Chew slowly.
- Good food ought to be appreciated. - Enjoy your food.
Isn't it hot?
I think you need to cook it a bit more.
What's the 13th question?
(They're about to finish eating.)
- What is the number... - You can't be done yet.
- What is it? - It's some kind of a password.
Okay. Are you sure?
- What's question number 10? - Don't you want some water?
Stop them from eating, Sana.
(Why are you eating so quickly?)
- Don't you want some water? - Is the answer "galbi"?
- No, that's not right. - Aren't you thirsty?
Please drink some water.
(She secures the last piece of meat.)
(I can't let you have the last piece.)
(Can we talk this out?)
"A cool breeze" must mean "wind".
I think so, too.
(It's the War of Samgyeopsal.)
It's for row number two.
(I can't let you have it.)
I'm sorry, Sana.
Way to go, Sana.
- I'm sorry, Sana. - Give us a bit more time, Sana.
(Will she let him take it?)
- Is this... - It's Harry Potter.
- We're done. - We finished it.
I'm not sure if they're all right, though.
Team Haha was...
- faster by the slightest amount. - Yes!
We just need all the answers to be correct.
Please.
(Did they get the answers right?)
- You failed. - Why?
(But why?)
- Why? - You misspelled, "clothesline".
You misspelled that, Haha?
Haha.
You're embarrassing us in front of them.
How could you...
The VJs must be pretty full by now.
Have some water.
The water here is really something else.
I'm worried someone else might come here.
We have to do this quickly.
Are we doing the One Plus One Card thing?
(We should strengthen our position with the One Plus One Card.)
- Let's do this, Sana. - Okay.
- Let's go. - Let's go.
(Slightly full VJs go against Team Haha who can't spell.)
- One, two, three. - Let's get started right away.
(This is their second attempt.)
(Number 1 across: One of the members of Davichi who was on Running Man)
- It's Kang Min Kyung. - Number one is Kang Min Kyung.
(Sana is trying to disturb the VJs.)
You should cut it later.
You should cut it into smaller pieces.
There's no need to rush.
Let me do it.
You must be tired from holding up the cameras.
I'll do this for you.
(Blocking)
Not yet.
You might get an upset stomach.
(Clanging)
(It sounds like a fencing match.)
You shouldn't play with your food.
(I blocked him.)
- What's this one? - Don't.
(There are only three crosswords remaining.)
How many pieces of meat do you have left?
- Four. - Four?
We're almost there.
- What's question number 14? - Eat some kimchi.
We are 500m away from the samgyeopsal restaurant.
- There's a road sign. - There must be someone there.
Someone's already there.
- No way. - No.
No.
It's still raw.
(Team VJ doesn't mind eating raw pork.)
Is it "glutinous potato balls"?
- Hold on, Sana. - Glutinous...
- potato balls. - Hold on, Sana.
- Let's go over everything. - Apink, Eric Nam, Best Actor Award.
(We're almost done, Sana.)
That's the right answer, right?
That's right.
- He's in that group, right? - We're done.
- We're done. - We finished it.
- It's right, isn't it? - Can we not try this mission?
Please.
(Did they spell everything correctly this time?)
What are you doing here?
- It was really hard. - Please.
(Did they spell everything correctly this time?)
Team Haha succeeded.
(They blocked, they solved, they conquered.)
(They receive the One Plus One Card.)
Can we not do it now?
Eric Nam.
We did it.
Why does only one team get to do this mission?
We can't do this anymore?
- You guys are still hungry, right? - Yes.
We should find ourselves a different menu now.
- Let's get in the car. - We have the chance card.
- Don't use it on us. - Come on.
You guys are leading by a lot.
- That's nonsense. - That's not true.
You know I can remove a crossword from your puzzle, right?
I know that.
- Please go easy on us. - We're not leading by a lot.
- You wrote "eel". - What do you think of Kwang Soo?
- He's so handsome. - What?
Hear her out. How do you like Kwang Soo?
What?
- He's very handsome. - He is.
You look much better in person.
- Can you take a picture with me? - Kwang Soo.
Get yourself together.
- Can I take a picture with you? - Okay!
- Tell him you love him. - I love you, Kwang Soo!
- Oh, my. - I love you!
Don't do that. There are people here.
- Stop it. - Bye, Kwang Soo.
Stop it.
I love you, too.
- Don't use your chance card on us! - Don't use your chance card on us!
Of course.
- Let's leave this place. - You can trust me.
- We love you, Kwang Soo! - We love you, Kwang Soo!
(Do you want my chance card?)
Please don't use...
- The chance card! - The chance card!
(I'll do whatever you tell me to.)
- We love you, Ji Hyo! - We love you, Ji Hyo!
(Who? Me?)
- What are you talking about? - Please don't use...
- the chance card on us. - The chance card on us!
Live a long and happy life, all five of you!
Why are you doing this?
- Stop doing that. - You're making me uncomfortable.
Please don't use it on us.
- We have faith in you. - Let's hope he doesn't use it.
I won't forgive him if he uses it after all this.
- After everything we did... - If he still attacks us,
that'd make him a horrible person.
You have to go drink Moonlight coffee now.
- "Moonlight coffee"... - "Is the best".
- "Is the best". - "Is the best".
We should use the One Plus One Card.
"Is the best".
(They use the One Plus One Card to fill out the red box.)
You have filled out a red box.
You can remove a crossword from someone else's puzzle.
Do we have to decide now?
I know we should attack Jae Seok's team,
but Na Yeon was...
Did that change your mind?
Not quite.
I told you that I'll be devoted to you guys.
Then what's stopping you?
What are you worried about?
Is your favorite member of Twice in that team?
I think it's because they said they loved him.
It's been a very long time since anyone said that to me.
(They said they loved me.)
(Twice told me so.)
Is your favorite member of Twice in that team?
I think it's because they said they loved him.
Tell him that you love him.
- I love you, Kwang Soo. - I love you.
Kwang Soo.
(Whom will Kwang Soo choose?)
Let's attack them.
It's only right we attack them.
- Which one should I go for? - Let's go with that one.
- It's been removed. - What?
- What? - What are you talking about?
I think someone removed a crossword from our puzzle.
Your puzzle has been updated.
It's been erased.
(Team Haha removed "roasted clams" from their puzzle.)
It was Kwang Soo and Haha.
- Gosh. - That's harsh.
They even confessed their love to them.
He's a traitor.
- He really is a traitor. - He really is.
- He betrayed us. - We should punish him.
We'll have revenge on him.
This is war.
Is this Eonyang bulgogi?
- It's over there. - This is the place.
- It was close by. - We could finish the puzzle here.
Let's do this.
We have to take revenge in the name of justice.
- We have to get them back. - They need to learn a lesson.
Where is the place?
- It's over there. - There it is.
We should ask for recommendations in front of the restaurant.
We have to talk them into it.
"Where can we get some delicious meat around here?"
That's not what we should say.
They might not take the hint.
We should say, "There must be a place around here."
The food looks delicious.
(They arrive at a restaurant.)
Someone's coming.
There they come.
- Hello. - Hello.
Nice to meet you.
Can we ask you a question?
We were...
feeling a little hungry.
We want to ask the people of Busan...
what we should eat.
- Don't rush your answer. - Hold on.
We can't go far from here.
If you name a food,
we have to eat that.
We can't go far from here.
- What food... - Busan is famous for...
- a lot of food. - What should we eat?
(That's the place we want to go.)
- Eonyang bulgogi. - Eonyang bulgogi.
Eonyang bulgogi.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
- Thank you. - Eonyang bulgogi.
- Thank you so much. - You look skinny.
Some bulgogi will help with that.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
Let's go.
We kind of forced that answer.
When we're finished eating, we shall have our revenge.
I'm sorry, but do you think we could get two servings?
Thank you.
- I've been waiting for this. - "Let's eat some bulgogi."
"Let's eat some bulgogi."
After we eat this...
- We should have dessert. - Right.
"What should we have for dessert?"
- Coffee. - Coffee?
"How about a cup of coffee?"
Then we'll go get our coffee.
- I'll make them suffer. - Those traitors.
It's payback time.
I'll teach them a valuable life lesson.
We should punish them in the name of justice.
Our food's here.
We're sorry. We wish we could order more, but we have a mission.
(It's Eonyang bulgogi they've been looking for.)
(Roasting)
Look at it getting roasted.
It smells nice.
(They're mesmerized.)
I love the sound of meat getting cooked.
(Soft and tender bulgogi will motivate them to take revenge.)
I think it's ready to eat.
(Thank you for the food.)
Let's eat.
Thank you for the food.
(She takes a big bite.)
Try some of this.
How does it taste?
(It's delicious.)
Isn't it delicious?
(They're impressed by the taste.)
We worked hard to get here.
(She eats bulgogi with gusto.)
It took long for us to get here.
It's so delicious.
(Their work was worth it for the bulgogi.)
It almost melts in the mouth.
- We do it to win, don't we? - Jeong Yeon knows how to enjoy it.
Jeong Yeon, you've been so busy with eating.
(Her face is practically attached to her bowl.)
You haven't lifted your head once.
(They finish 2 portions in 1 minute.)
We cleared everything so quickly.
Didn't you have some pajeon before?
Didn't you?
We're the only ones eating so much.
Jeong Yeon doesn't even look up once when she eats.
Do you stare at the plate when you eat?
Her face is almost glued to her plate.
(It's a common eating position for her.)
- Her face is glued? - Right.
Her face is glued to her plate.
(She continues to eat.)
I heard you slurp, Jeong Yeon.
Are you happy to eat meat?
(Momo takes meat from the corner.)
I put some meat on the side.
(It's too delicious to resist.)
Goodness.
It's good to see you enjoy it.
(They take every piece of meat.)
(She eats a lot.)
People usually don't finish every bite of the meat.
Momo doesn't care about what we say.
You stopped talking in the restaurant.
You and Jeong Yeon are impressive.
She didn't lift her face once when she ate.
Should we order one more order?
- That sounds good. - Right?
- That would be perfect. - May we get one more order?
I think two servings were too little.
- Here you go. - Did someone attack us again?
- I brought a lot. - Is that right?
(Their premonition becomes true.)
What happened?
Why do they always attack us?
(Jae Seok and Seok Jin's team gets attacked.)
(Which team attacked them?)
Remember One Plus One Card that you earned?
(It was Haha and Kwang Soo's team again.)
(They used One Plus One Card and got another chance menu.)
- What kind of spoon worm? - Spoon worm.
It's Busan spoon worm.
- We got it. - It's Busan spoon worm.
We got a chance to attack.
We have a chance to attack.
(They attained the chance to attack other team.)
- That's great. - No one can beat us.
Shouldn't we eliminate a team?
Why don't we attack Jae Seok and Seok Jin?
Eliminate them.
(Jae Seok and Seok Jin's team is attacked again.)
(Haha and Kwang Soo's team is invincible.)
(Bulgogi is taken away from them.)
- No way. - I don't understand.
That's so horrible of them.
Did we lose bulgogi?
Did the green team attack us?
- What's wrong with them? - It was them.
- They attacked us. - How could they?
- What's Busan spoon worm? - How could they?
- We have to go this way. - That's right.
(The red square is the only way to take revenge.)
Let's eat first.
- Let's eat. - Let's leave after eating.
We should eat a lot when we're stressed.
Eat some more.
(Haha and Kwang Soo's team, you just wait and see.)
We'll show them how terrible life can be.
Drink up the coffee.
Cheers.
Let's win. Yes, yes, yes.
- Yes, yes, yes. - We've been winning.
Drink up.
(Haha and Kwang Soo's team is winning with three menu items.)
(Victory always tastes so sweet.)
This is a great way to express it.
Everyone, come drink coffee...
at Dalmaji Cafe.
(Dalmaji Cafe is like their lucky charm.)
(Slurping)
Are you okay?
Are you pouring out the last drop?
I finished it in one go.
Good job.
- Orange juice is good here, too. - She's so cute.
This is a spot to take photos.
(Let's enjoy some relaxing time.)
It's so pretty.
I'm happy because you're so excited.
I'm happier than ever before.
- I feel great. - I've never been so happy here.
(They take a photo to capture the moment.)
(Please let us win.)
Let's turn around and receive some good energy.
It's the energy of victory.
Let's become the winner.
(They receive the energy of victory.)
Mountain, don't worry
(Energy from Haeundae may lead them to victory.)
- That was great. - Good job.
- It'll make a good memory. - I know.
Let's take revenge.
- Thank you for the meal. - Thank you.
- Let's go now. - It's the cafe street.
Here's Dalmaji Cafe.
I want to eat ice cream here.
- Here it is. - Cake sounds good, too.
- Cake? - Wouldn't cake be delicious, too?
- Yes. - Let's get cake.
- There are cookies. - They have homemade cakes.
Let's eat here.
We should to talk to someone here.
Excuse me. May I ask you a question?
(Gosh! It's Twice!)
Could we talk to you for a minute?
Sure.
- We just had some food. - What a surprise.
We feel quite heavy because the food was greasy.
Wait a minute. Please take your time.
If you recommend a place, we must go there.
- Is that so? - We're very full.
We want to eat something sweet.
(They make a gesture as a hint.)
(Slurping?)
(Should I say it or not?)
Wait a minute, please.
I think he got the wrong hint and misunderstood.
(He may have misunderstood.)
(Isn't that it?)
What do you recommend?
Around this time...
- Please don't say it yet. - Is your nose bleeding, Na Yeon?
- Be careful. - Her nose is bleeding.
(It's their second gesture hint.)
Oh, I see.
You should get some coffee.
(You should get some coffee.)
Was that correct?
(He becomes their hero.)
He knows exactly what we need.
When I made this gesture, I was afraid that he misunderstood.
He thought we meant alcohol.
I'm glad you didn't say soju.
We'll take your advice and have some coffee.
- Sure. - Thank you.
- Thank you. - Goodbye.
(Aromatic coffee is best after a heavy meal.)
The machine is running.
- It smells good. - Hello.
Do you grind coffee beans here?
Hello.
- Let's see. - Please give us a pen.
- We can finally erase it. - Finally.
(They fill in the crossword puzzle.)
- Coffee. - Coffee Bravo.
What should we erase?
Shall we erase it?
(They attack Haha and Kwang Soo's team.)
We'll erase gukbap.
(They attack Kwang Soo and Haha right away.)
We need to erase one.
(We won't let them win.)
subtitles ripped and synced by riri13
(Kwang Soo gets a call.)
Hello, Jae Seok.
Kwang Soo.
- Who is it? - Who's calling?
- This is Na Yeon. - Hello, Na Yeon.
I really liked you.
Na Yeon, listen to me.
After what you've done...
To tell you the truth, I wanted to attack the black team.
- What are you talking about? - Listen to me.
It's over between us.
Let's talk in person later.
(He already lost his trust.)
- Na Yeon, we should meet. - Na Yeon.
I'm hanging up. It's a war between us now.
- Come on, Jae Seok. - We love you.
We love you.
- We love you. - We love you.
I'm sorry, but it's a war...
- between us. - It's a war.
They're declaring a war against us.
Let's take our chance.
Do we have 2 items? Most teams have 2.
(Current status of Crossword Puzzle)
I don't think this is it.
(Here's what's going on with Jong Kook and Ji Hyo's team.)
- There it is. - This is the place.
"How far have you gone inside Gukje Market?"
- Is it on the second floor? - Do we go upstairs?
- Please go upstairs. - What's going on here?
The chance mission at Gukje Market...
which has a variety of items...
is called "One in a Million".
Wasn't that mentioned before?
Five members on the team will run to the market in a relay.
They must buy five items that would fit...
in the Crossword Puzzle.
If you succeed, you get a chance.
(He thinks of choosing between a hat, gloves, and flowers.)
I'll find fabric with a floral print.
This is great.
Could you give me just a little?
I brought fabric with a floral print, Gukje Market's specialty.
Mini flowers.
I think this is good.
Jangjoah.
It's "Jangjoah Coffee".
What's wrong with that?
Jangjoah Coffee is good for the stomach.
May I get one Jangjoah Coffee?
This can be "Korean walnut cookie".
- Let's get some walnut cookies. - Let's go.
Tzuyu, make a left turn around the corner.
Okay.
I heard hanbok is very expensive.
Is it cheap?
(She got her attention.)
Welcome, try a walnut cookie.
(Here's what she's looking for.)
- Okay. - Welcome.
(She walks away from walnut cookies.)
Why are they displayed like this?
Is it so that you can choose...
the fabric for your hanbok?
Tzuyu.
(Tzuyu, where are you?)
Did someone stop her?
Is she giving someone her autograph?
Why isn't she back yet?
The blankets look so warm.
All the fabric is so soft.
(She takes a cup of tea while shopping.)
(She falls in love with Korean markets.)
It's delicious.
Tzuyu.
(How far did you go to buy walnut cookies?)
- Tzuyu. - Where is she?
- Is she a spy? - What if she is?
The shop is right around the corner.
- I can't believe it. - Where did she go?
I wonder where she went.
- Tzuyu, where have you been? - Where have you been?
Did you buy the walnut cookies?
- Here. - Do you know what they are?
She bought something else.
No, I bought some sweet potatoes.
- I bought some sweet potatoes... - What?
and walnut cookies.
Did you buy them?
- Did you buy walnut cookies? - She did.
(She realized what her mission was.)
There are two types of walnut cookies.
This is the original, and this is sweet potato-flavored.
- Sweet potato? - Yes.
- Really? - Yes.
Let me try it.
(She even tries a sample.)
Is it good?
(She tries a sample.)
It's in her hand.
I thought we lost you.
- Are you a spy? - Are you?
I'm not.
(Jong Kook and Ji Hyo's team clears their mission.)
We got it.
Okay.
(They get to write any dish they want.)
(One Plus One Card)
(Next team to arrive at Gukje Market is...)
Nobody's here, yet. What's this?
(Haha and Kwang Soo's team arrives at Gukje Market in second place.)
(They have to use the crossword the previous team used.)
We can't attack.
We can't.
We've been too nice.
- Look. - "King crab"?
They have two, right?
- It's four! - It is?
(They already have four?)
Is there something you want to recommend?
- Fish cake. - Fish cake?
Thank you.
Thank you for the food.
- I'm not big, right? - It's tasty.
I'm not really big.
Can you recommend one dish?
- King crab. - King crab?
Let's have king crab.
(It's good but they're running out of time.)
It's huge.
(They're clearing four dishes if they finish king crab as well.)
They also have One Plus One Card.
- Who does? - They have four.
(When did they get so many?)
- They only have one left. - Right.
This always happens...
but when we compete with Kwang Soo's team,
- Jong Kook always gets ahead. - He wins by default.
What about "pretty hats"?
- Sure. - That's a good one.
- Let's go. - See you later.
- Hurry, Da Hyun. - Sure.
(They are looking for hats.)
Do you sell hats?
Yes, I can use a handkerchief...
and make a hat.
Is it called a bandana hat?
Sure. It goes around like this.
- Did you get a hat? - It's a different kind of hat...
- so it works. - They do sell hats here.
- Hurry up. Who's next? - It's Sana.
You can get anything. Get anything.
- We can make up a word. - Get anything.
Anything? What should I get?
(She steps foot into the market where Tzuyu couldn't get out of.)
(Will Sana be able to navigate herself?)
Where's Sana going?
- Hurry, Sana! - Hurry up, Sana!
- We don't have time. - Where is she going? Sana?
She's a bit slow.
- Where did she go? - Isn't she a bit slow?
Let's look around later, Sana.
Sana?
- What starts with tofu? - Tofu?
"Du". What starts with "Du"?
(She asks the vendors.)
What starts with "Du"?
Bandanas.
- Bandanas. - Bandanas.
Durumagi.
Durumagi? What's that?
- Durumagi is for hanbok. - Durumagi?
How much is it?
- It's expensive. - Is it?
- I'll give you a cheaper one. - How much is it?
- What's the cheapest? - The cheapest? It's 10 dollars.
10 dollars?
We only have 30 dollars in total.
Can you make it five dollars?
(Can you make it five dollars?)
(She acts cute in front of the vendors.)
- I'll give it to you for five. - Really?
Thank you.
Thank you. Thank you.
(She's happy.)
- Sana's back. What is it? - It's durumagi.
I got durumagi.
- Durumagi? - Durumagi.
- Yes! - That's amazing.
- Durumagi. - Durumagi.
Durumagi.
Hello. I'm looking for gloves.
Men's gloves?
Do you have gloves?
Do cotton gloves work?
They do. Cotton gloves work!
Thank you. How much is it?
- It's free. - No, please take a dollar at least.
- Sure. - Thank you, Madam.
- I'll get cake. - You're next.
- I'll get cake. - It's right there.
- Already? - Thank you. What's it called?
How are you going to name it?
- "Very tasty cake". - "Tasty cake"?
- I don't know if this would work. - What is it?
- What's that? - Sit down.
(Why did he get this?)
- What's this? - "Fake flowers".
(I guess that works.)
This should work.
Approved.
Good job.
(Haha and Kwang Soo's team clears the mission.)
Can we leave?
Can we ask the waitress for the next menu?
Should we?
We...
We would like to stay in Gukje Market...
and tour Busan.
- What food reminds you of Busan? - What reminds you of Busan?
If we stay in the market,
- we have a good chance. - That's right.
- What food reminds you of Busan? - What reminds you of Busan?
Wheat noodles.
(Wheat noodles)
She said wheat noodles first.
Do they sell wheat noodles in the market?
Do they sell it? I think you have to walk a bit.
(Well)
We'll ask for real now.
The three of them spoke at once.
- I'm sorry but I asked her. - We're sorry.
Why did you answer for her?
Excuse me. Why did you get in the way?
I admit the cake is good, but...
This is your last chance. We'll go with what they say.
(They get another chance to ask the question.)
- What food reminds you of Busan? - What reminds you of Busan?
(What food reminds you of Busan?)
Wheat noodles.
(Busan is known for their wheat noodles.)
- Let's go with wheat noodles. - But you...
Let's get going.
(You have to try wheat noodles here.)
- Let's hurry. - Do they have wheat noodles here?
- Do they have wheat noodles here? - Let's get going.
- Let's go. - Thank you.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
(Thank you for recommending wheat noodles.)
(Jong Kook and Ji Hyo's team is still on king crab.)
Don't we have another chance?
While the other two teams were competing with each other...
- We took over. - We did.
We can't go without having king crab.
Who thought of this, by the way?
Do you like crabs?
(They even get to try king crab.)
It's taking a while though.
They have to steam it.
It takes around 25 minutes.
- Sorry? - That's the shortest it takes.
It might take longer.
(We have to wait 25 minutes?)
(The other 2 teams cleared 2 dishes each.)
They have everything here.
Excuse me.
Do you sell crock pots?
Where did he go?
He can get anything.
- Hello. - Hello.
(Haha and Kwang Soo's team arrives at the wheat noodles place.)
Can we have wheat noodles? It doesn't take long, right?
We'll eat quick. We'll take five minutes.
"Only wheat noodles".
"Only wheat noodles"? We can do another one, right?
(They have One Plus One Card.)
"Let's eat hotteok. All right."
- All right. - That works, right?
- All right. - All right!
"All right"? That works.
(Am I weird for not knowing this?)
(They finally completed four dishes.)
It's here.
(King crab is finally here.)
It's huge.
- It's as big as me. - Thank you.
(We only have one left after this.)
You're rolling up your sleeves so that you can eat a lot, right?
(Twice is eating all they want.)
They don't know how to crack it open.
How nice of you.
(They didn't say a word for 30 minutes.)
We need to speed up.
"Delicious bread".
(If Jae Seok's team uses One Plus One Card, they'll have 4 as well.)
- "Rose petal tea". - "Rose petal tea".
- Let's use it. - You can use it.
We're done, then.
(They have 2. Haha's team is working on their 4th dish.)
(They move their chopsticks fast.)
- Attack it, guys. - Eat.
Attack!
We have no time.
(Jong Kook's team is ahead of them and Jae Seok's team trails them.)
(Once they finish the wheat noodles, they only have one left.)
Try some spicy wheat noodles.
No, Sir. We are good with one.
(No, Sir.)
No, Sir.
(People in Busan are just so generous.)
- Just try some. - You're so kind.
Cut it up. Quick.
- This is great. - This is really good.
This is spicy wheat noodles.
It's good.
Okay. That's enough.
(Twice looks like they're on "Baek Jong Won's Top 3 Chef King".)
It tastes different.
(It's time for the last dish.)
It's okay!
(Hold on, please.)
Have one each.
It's okay!
(They're all impressed by the generous Busan people.)
- Thank you. - Thank you very much.
- I should sit back down. - It's tasty.
(They came for wheat noodles and they're having a course meal.)
Attack!
We have no time, guys.
(They only have one left to go.)
- Madam. - Yes.
Besides from wheat noodles, is there anything nearby...
that is famous in Busan?
(Her answer will decide their fate in the race.)
(Can we have something simple to eat?)
- Seed-filled hotteok? - Pork gukbap.
What did you say? Did you say hotteok?
(That is simple to eat.)
She said hotteok!
- It's close by. - Is it close?
Let's go quick.
- Is it across? - We...
We would like you to recommend something simple we can eat.
- Coffee? - Coffee?
Thank you.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
Let's get coffee here.
They sell seed-filled hotteok here.
It's here. Okay.
It's here!
They have seed-filled hotteok. Where's the board?
"Are you eating hotteok by yourself?"
"I'm mad."
(He invents a new menu.)
- "I'm mad." - "I'm mad."
(Isn't that perfect?)
- It's cute. - Approved.
(It's hotteok party.)
- Is it good? - Can I have one? Thank you.
You have to whisper after you swallow.
(It's only Kwang Soo left.)
Kwang Soo, Kwang Soo.
Hurry!
(Please hurry.)
- We... - Can we have five cups of coffee?
All right.
We have filled in five menus.
We have.
(Both teams are almost done.)
(Which team will clear their last menu first?)
(Whistling)
Clear.
(Haha and Kwang Soo's team is done.)
We're done. Did we overtake them?
(How's Ji Hyo and Jong Kook's team doing?)
Your team placed first.
(Haha and Kwang Soo's team finishes Crossword Puzzle Race.)
(We ate and won.)
We won first place.
(Results of Crossword Puzzle Race Round 2)
(Beautiful lights lit up the night sky in Busan.)
- I've wanted to come here. - It looks like a road with flowers.
(What's their last mission?)
- It's amazing. - It's so beautiful here.
Is this where the winning team sits?
Here are the prizes for the winners.
(There are 8 prizes.)
- A massager. - Giant octopus.
There are so many prizes.
We also have Eonyang bulgogi for Momo.
Does she like Eonyang bulgogi?
Momo loves Eonyang bulgogi.
You should win that prize.
- Does the winner take all? - The winner takes everything.
(The team that places first takes everything.)
- Really? - I'll give it to you as a present.
- We didn't have Eonyang bulgogi. - Eonyang bulgogi is delicious.
Haha and Kwang Soo's team was the 1st to clear the 2nd mission...
of Crossword Puzzle, so we'll give you 15 candies.
- Here are your candies. - Thank you.
(Why candies?)
Jong Kook and Ji Hyo's team gets 10.
Goodness.
Jae Seok and Seok Jin's team gets 5.
(Will we play a game with candies?)
- What's going on? - The final round is...
"Secret Run" that's based on a secret auction.
(Secret Run)
There are a total of three rounds.
The staff member will call out the game category.
The team that wants to play will make a secret bid...
with the number of candies they have.
We don't have that many.
It's better to have more candies.
The team with the highest number makes a successful bid.
If you win the game, we'll give you additional candies that you bid.
(They will be given additional candies.)
If you lose the game,
the candies you bid will be shared by the other two teams.
(Upon losing, the candies you bid will be shared.)
It's difficult to know the result.
- The other two teams take them. - We have a chance to win.
- We could win. - Who knows what will happen?
- It'd be amazing if we win. - I know.
Let's win this game.
(Will a miracle take place for Jae Seok and Seok Jin's team?)
Here's your first mission.
This is Round One.
It's "Split the Apples".
(Round One is "Split the Apples".)
One member from each team can play.
The time limit is 30 seconds.
The player who splits more than 18 apples wins.
- Jae Seok is good at splitting. - I know.
I'd give it a try if we had at least 10 candies,
- but we only have five. - We don't have enough.
You should have done a better job playing other games.
You erased two of our menu items.
Can you even play with only five candies?
- You wait and see. - This is so annoying.
- My goodness. - Give them some candies for free.
Shall we make a bid of five candies?
- Go ahead. - We'll make the bid.
After that, all of you can go home.
Right?
- Why don't you go ahead? - Hey.
After we make the bid, it's a war between us.
- It's a war. - Go ahead and make the bid.
- You have nothing to fight with. - Calm down.
- Make the bid. - Calm down.
- No, we can't. - Na Yeon, make the bid.
Look at those punks.
Jae Seok is good at splitting apples. Give me an apple.
Just give me one.
- I'm sorry. - Just give us one.
We don't have much, so please understand.
- We don't have any. - Give it a try.
- Try splitting one. - Let me see it.
- We have to split more than 18? - Go.
(He tries to forestall the other teams with his demonstration.)
(Completely in focus)
- He can't do it. - I can't do it.
(He can't do it.)
(Put the apple back.)
- No. - Don't even try it.
Give him a different apple.
- Don't do it. - Don't try it.
(They quickly give up on him.)
Let's forget it. Sit back down.
Thank goodness it wasn't the actual game.
Those apples are difficult to split.
Here are the bids...
that three teams made.
(How many did each team bid?)
In 1, 2, 3.
They made a big bid.
Three?
We made a successful bid.
If they lose, we take 2 and the other takes 1.
- That's right. - I'd be happy to win one.
You can do it.
- Goodness. - You can do it.
- There's too much pressure. - He looks handsome.
You can do it.
There's too much pressure.
- It's because of you. - You'll be sexy if you succeed.
Some apples are easier to split than others.
Don't try too hard to win.
Don't be disappointed even if I lose.
- Don't be disappointed. - We won't.
Don't be disappointed.
- You should start already. - Don't put pressure on him.
- Let's get started. - I was never good at this.
I'm telling you that I'm not good at it.
Just do a good job, Kwang Soo.
- There's a lot of pressure on you. - No way.
- He can't split 18 in 30 seconds. - No, he can't.
I bet he can't even split 10 apples.
Get ready.
He's tensing up.
- He's already tense. - He should be.
(I'm not alone anymore.)
(There are three ladies who depend on me.)
I love you, Kwang Soo.
(He received a lot of unconditional love.)
(It's too difficult if you like me too much.)
(You can do it, Kwang Soo.)
Get ready, go.
- It's a losing game. - He won't make it.
(It's a losing game.)
(Splitting)
He must split 18.
- Gosh. - The bigger side should go up.
The bigger side should go up.
- That's right. - He might make it.
- You're doing well. - You can do it.
- He might make it. - It's possible.
You can do it.
He might succeed.
Forget about this one.
(Forget about this one.)
You can't do that.
(He has 8 seconds left with 8 more to split.)
How many more does he have?
- This is amazing. - You're doing well.
(Da Hyun, Sana, Ji Hyo)
(I dedicate my day to all of you.)
(He's fueled by the power of love.)
How does he do that?
- You're doing well. - There are only 30 seconds.
You're almost there.
(The mission is uncleared.)
(The other team smiles.)
(I was so close.)
(They make crying faces.)
Look over here, Kwang Soo.
(He suddenly feels like a fool.)
It wasn't an easy game.
It's easy to split them when you have bigger hands.
- Good job. - Did you split 12 apples?
I'm sorry, everyone.
- It's okay. - We won two candies.
- We have six candies now. - Right.
We have more.
This is Round Two.
The second mission is "Splitting the Legs".
- What? - I can't do that.
Are you good at it?
(Everyone is confident.)
She can do it.
Can you do it? Who can do it the best?
Wait a minute.
How do you play the game?
Do we have to wait for another chance?
Mina danced ballet for 11 years.
Mina danced ballet for 11 years?
- Who? - Here's Mina.
Really?
Let's exclude Mina.
Everyone on the team must play it.
- We're doomed. - Goodness.
The total length of your split legs must be over 10m...
for the team to succeed.
- Is that 10m? - Is that 10m long?
- Goodness. - Is that how long it is?
That's really long.
- Our legs aren't that long. - We can't do it.
- I think we can do it. - Do you think so?
Isn't it too long?
- Her legs are long. - I told you they are.
You can do it one by one.
- Her legs are long. - How about us?
Jeong Yeon can split hers, too.
- Everyone else except me can do it. - We can do it, too.
Let me stretch first.
(Jeong Yeon starts to help.)
(Screaming in pain)
- Gosh, Jeong Yeon. - Yes?
- Jeong Yeon, please. - Are you okay?
I think you can do it.
(Screaming even more)
I don't think we can do it.
Let's go back to our seats.
We can't do it.
(Haha and Kwang Soo's team is having a serious discussion.)
Let's put our shoes on like this.
(She pulls her heel out of the shoe.)
(She learned only bad things from Haha and Kwang Soo.)
- Come on. - She's so cute.
(Everyone cheats on Running Man.)
- I thought she had a good idea. - Me, too.
Chae Young, Mina, Tzuyu, and Jong Kook can do it.
Help me a little.
- Shall we give it a try? - We can do it.
- Five is enough. - Let's make a bigger bid.
I'm confident about this.
- How about six? - Let's bid one more.
Come on, Ji Hyo.
- We live only once. - What's wrong with you?
Do you want us to lose everything?
(Ji Hyo gets risky with the bidding.)
I hope the team that plays loses...
so that we can get more candies.
Do you want candies without doing anything?
- We might even win. - I'm sorry,
but why did you even declare war?
This is a war.
- You need something to fight with. - Didn't you want a war?
Winning the war is more important than winning a battle.
- Let's go. - We made the bid.
In 1, 2, 3.
(What's the result of the bid?)
Why did you bid so much?
In 1, 2, 3.
- Why did you bid so much? - Yes.
- 10? - If they win,
- we don't get any candies. - They might lose.
- We can do it. - They're good at it.
Let's get into positions and try it.
Measure the length accurately.
We'll measure the length.
This is wider than I thought.
- Each person has to split the legs. - This is quite long.
- Let's give it a try. - They won't make it.
Wait a minute.
(But they have Mina on their team.)
You can do it.
(How flexible will Mina be with 11 years of dancing ballet?)
Isn't that too...
- Nice. - She did it.
(This is easy.)
- She did it. - Isn't that too...
(She went way over 2m.)
- Mina is good. - She's even better.
(Chae Young also knows how to stretch.)
(Mina isn't the only one who's good at this.)
Chae Young can't reach it.
- Come closer, Tzuyu. - There you go.
- This will definitely work. - Use your toes.
- They did it. - How is that possible?
(There are 3.5m left.)
(The success of this mission depends on Ji Hyo's flexibility.)
(How wide can Ji Hyo reach?)
(She did a decent job.)
- We can do it. - We did it!
(Jong Kook is the last one left.)
(Will they be able to succeed this mission?)
We did it!
- He went over. - We did it.
(They need to stay for 5 seconds to succeed.)
- In 5, 4, 3, 2, 1. - Stay like that for 4 minutes.
- They did it. - Mission successful.
(Jong Kook and Ji Hyo's team succeeds the mission.)
- We did it! - We did it.
- Good job. - We did it.
We have 22 now.
We did it.
We should have placed the bet. I told you they'd do it.
We should give it a try, too.
We could probably do it, too.
Let's give it a try just for the fun of it.
We probably would've been able to do it.
It's amazing how flexible they are.
- I didn't think they could do it. - They're really flexible.
How did they do that?
- I'm not that flexible. - Let's see how it goes.
Na Yeon and Jeong Yeon aren't touching.
Na Yeon is humane.
- Na Yeon is humane. - That's something new.
We can't do it, Na Yeon.
- This isn't going to work. - We can't do this.
(Let's give up.)
This isn't going to work.
- Na Yeon is very humane. - It's not going to work, Na Yeon.
- I told you I can't do it. - She's very humane.
I told you we can't do it.
- We can't do it. - It's because of me.
We wouldn't be successful even if we tried.
Haha and Kwang Soo's team has 28.
Jong Kook and Ji Hyo's team has 22.
This is the third and last round.
(This is the third round of Secret Run.)
It's "Team Jump Rope".
(Team Jump Rope)
- That's not bad. - It's a good game.
(A team of 3 has to jump the rope 35 times.)
- This will be easy. - Sure.
We have to go all in, Haha.
- Okay. - Bet them all.
They'll probably go all in.
We can't play the game even if we make the bet, right?
- No, we can't. - There's nothing we can do.
- No. - There isn't anything we can do.
I want to give this game a try.
You've never played games before?
This isn't just a game for you. It's a war.
You're warriors.
- They're at war. - It's a war.
It's a war without weapons.
(We do have six candies, though.)
Should we just eat them?
(Should we just eat them?)
Do you want one?
(The other teams are having fun practicing.)
It's good.
(They are forced to become the audience.)
Did you all place your bets?
- Yes. - We finished placing our bets.
We're here to win.
Let's check the bets. One.
(It's a battle between the safe choice and the bold move.)
(It's the only team to challenge the last mission.)
(Which team placed the highest bid?)
One, two, three.
We bet 13 candies.
- 13? - That's 1 more than theirs.
(Oh, my.)
(Their betting is higher than Haha and Kwang Soo's team's all in.)
If you fail, you will automatically come in last.
- It's all or nothing. - You could get a penalty.
(It's all up to Tzuyu, Chae Young, and Mina.)
If they fail, we'll be placed first.
Ji Hyo.
- Ready, - Let's go.
- Let's go! - Let's go!
- This is too funny. - Please.
- Let's go! - Please fail.
You're mean.
Ready.
(The final winner will be decided...)
(by this game of "Team Jump Rope".)
(You either win big or go home.)
(What will be the result of their bold decision?)
- Go. - Go.
(They have to jump rope 35 times in order to succeed the mission.)
- Two, three, four. - I think they'll make it.
(They have good teamwork.)
(Are they actually going to do it?)
- We did 10. - 11, 12.
(He's praying that they fail.)
- 16, 17, 18. - 16, 17, 18.
(The audience is excited.)
(The rope might hit the staff members.)
- 24, 25. - 24, 25.
(Only 10 more to go.)
(Why are they so good?)
- 30, 31, 32. - Why are they so good?
(They only need to do three more to become the final winner.)
(Don't do it.)
- 34. - 34.
(Only one more to go.)
(One more jump and they're the winner.)
(Will they be able to succeed?)
- 35, 36. - 35, 36.
(They went over 35.)
We did it. We did it!
(Team Jong Kook and Ji Hyo wins the Crossword Puzzle Race.)
It should be at least 50.
- Good job. - We did it!
(We'll take the prize while you two are battling.)
That was hard, wasn't it?
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry we had to put you through this.
I'm sorry we couldn't even give you an opportunity.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
I'm sorry, Da Hyun.
- Is it over? - I'm sorry.
Take your prize.
Mina said she wanted Eonyang Bulgogi.
- That's right. - Here it is.
- Thank you. - This is amazing.
We'd like to thank the nine members of Twice...
for joining us today in Busan.
(We'd like to thank Twice and the people of Busan for today.)
Will you stick together or play solo?
(This question...)
(visits the members out of nowhere.)
(Together or Apart)
(In Jeonju)
(It's the trip they have to fool the others and hide from them.)
(Together or Apart)
(What outcome will the decision bring?)
Let's part ways.
(Together or Apart)