(A special vacation to escape the heat wave)
(They compete with each other both physically and mentally to win...)
(the "Changing Lyrics Project".)
(Seven judges including Han Hye Jin, Park Bo Young and Im Jin Mo!)
(A music concert on a summer night!)
(What performances will they show us tonight?)
(On a very hot summer day)
(In a village in Yangpyeong)
- Hello.
-  Hello, Kwang Soo.
- You're here.
You must be so hot now, Kwang Soo.
I thought it's already autumn.
He's a fashion leader.
- Hello.
-  Hello, Gary.
Gary dressed as if it's winter now.
(Gary is in a black hooded sweatshirt.)
-You're ahead of the season.
-  It has fur inside.
Hello, Jong Kook.
- He changed his shirt.
-  Jong Kook is here.
What season are we in now?
What is it?
What happened to you?
- She is dressed like a hunter.
-  A hunter?
- You look like a theme park worker.
-  You're right.
- Hello, everyone.
-  Hello.
- She looks like a baby lion keeper.
-  She does.
You look like an animal trainer.
Everyone, it's your last shooting in July.
We'll take some time to look back on your performance in July.
(It's time to evaluate how they did in July.)
No way.
- Wow!
-  Gosh.
(A special guest joins them for the evaluation.)
- Wow.
-  Goodness.
- Hello.
-  Hello.
She is the queen of baseball.
She's the reporter, Kim Mi Na.
- Hello.
-  She's the queen of baseball.
How do you know her?
Of course, I know her. She hosts a sports show.
The one who's very tall?
- No way.
-  She's not the one?
(Are you talking about me?)
Hello, I'm a reporter Kim Mi Na of SBS Sports.
Hello.
It will be August soon,
so I came here to help you evaluate how you did during this month.
- I see.
-  I recognise her voice.
- Okay.
-  I like her voice.
We will evaluate your performances together today.
- Let's check out your report cards.
-  Report cards?
- That's not necessary.
-  Gosh.
- Report cards?
-  My goodness.
- Why did they make report cards?
You won't ask us to get our parents' signature, will you?
Let's find out how many times you became the final winner.
- I don't think there'd be my name.
-  Is my name there?
- Wow. Did Ji Hyo win three times?
-  I didn't win once?
(The number of each member's final wins)
- Wow.
-  Ji Hyo!
- I didn't win once?
-  That's amazing.
- The team ace Ji Hyo...
-  Did she win that many times?
- I failed to get even one title.
-  It's Ji Hyo's Running Man now.
- Unbelievable.
-  That is right.
Team ace Ji Hyo takes first place with overwhelming number of wins.
She excelled in both team and couple missions.
However,
unlucky Kwang Soo is the only member...
who failed to win even once.
- That's right.
-  His column is empty.
- Were you even with us?
-  How is that possible?
Kwang Soo even failed to win in Kwang Soo's Revenge episode.
How could I fail to get a single win?
(He lost even in Kwang Soo's Revenge episode.)
How can it be possible?
Moving on, Running Man is famous for its Name Tag Elimination.
This can be considered big data.
(The number of times each member removed others' name tags.)
- Okay!
-  Look at my bar!
(Haha and Kwang Soo both ranked top.)
Kwang Soo, what on earth happened to you?
When did I eliminate that many times?
The members who removed the most name tags...
- are Haha and Kwang Soo.
-  Wow! We made it.
- Kwang Soo...
-  Is this really true?
Teamed up with Seo Jang Hoon, Hong Jin Kyung and Lee Gi Woo...
in Kwang Soo's Revenge episode.
- I'm more amazed at Haha's record.
-  Right.
He was good in Special Agent H episode.
He did great then. He even removed Jong Kook's name tag.
Considering that you both didn't earn many wins,
you let others remove your name tags as much as you removed others' tags.
You lost as much as you earned.
- I'm like a bottomless pit.
-  He allows others to take his.
While some removed name tags, others lost their name tags.
Seok Jin, Kwang Soo and Haha lost their name tags the most.
- Betrayal cross!
-  Betrayal cross!
Betrayers take others' tags as much as others take theirs.
Didn't they remove each other's name tags?
It's because we're too nice.
As they become others' target often, they're considered...
weak members and pretty fair game.
I felt offended when she said pretty fair game.
Her calm voice makes me upset even more.
I don't want to be considered weak.
- I just tried my best.
-  This is my second time meeting...
Mi Na, and I see why she's the queen.
She keeps her hair on one side.
Isn't it bad for your neck?
- It will stiffen your shoulder.
-  What are you talking about?
She might have a disc problem on this side.
It has to be divided evenly.
- Her hair isn't that heavy.
-  It will be all right.
She loves to tilt her head like this to look pretty.
I've never seen anyone with such hair since I saw it in fairy tales.
If she goes to a higher place and has longer hair,
she'll be Rapunzel.
(If she only had longer hair, she would've been Rapunzel.)
Now, let's take a look at the average survival hour graph.
They prepared so many graphs.
In this graph, it's found that Jae Seok's survival hour
is the longest, which is 12 minutes and 23 seconds.
You were alive for a long time.
Most members survived for about 10 minutes.
However, the graph declines abruptly on Kwang Soo's column.
Was I alive only for 3 minutes and 34 seconds in a month?
- That's very short.
-  Kwang Soo was alive...
- for 3 minutes and 34 seconds.
-  He's so ephemeral.
- What do you mean by that?
-  You were...
You barely survived for a minute per week.
No, he survived for about three minutes every week.
I couldn't do anything.
I hope Kwang Soo survives longer in August.
- Only three minutes?
-  Right.
- Now, we'll watch video clips...
-  Is there more?
- that were viewed the most.
-  Is there more to go?
- The number of views?
-  We have top three video clips.
Let's check out the video in third place.
(Top three Running Man video clips)
(A scene from The Best Couple's Trip episode.)
- I remember that.
-  Yes.
My Hyo Lyn!
- I miss my lady, Hyo Lyn.
-  Look at the screen.
What's wrong with your hands?
- I had to dance with her.
-  You two were dancing.
I can't stand watching them.
Look at his face.
Let's find out the top two clip.
It's Gyeong Ree's dance on the beach.
- Was that one viewed a lot?
-  Really?
- I remember that.
-  Oh, that dance.
- I knew it.
-  Is that what viewers like?
That's why they asked her to dance.
People just wanted to watch Gyeong Ree dancing.
Then, let's check which one had the most views.
- Which one is it?
-  I wonder what it is.
- Is it Gary again?
-  Right. I knew it.
(Gary and Hyo Lyn's dance ranked first.)
Was our dance that spectacular?
- Their dance was awesome.
-  Oh, that dance.
- I remember that.
-  That's it.
My goodness.
Gary actually plays important roles from time to time.
(He's still embarrassed.)
- What is it?
-  What are you doing?
What on earth are you doing?
He couldn't stand watching them dancing.
The title of the video clip must be...
"Jae Seok Stopping the Dance", right?
- What are you talking about?
-  It must be "Jae Seok Stopping..."
- Why do you take credit for that?
-  That must be my scene.
That's ridiculous.
It's "Jae Seok Stopping the Dance" because I'm at the centre.
That would've been impossible if it weren't Hyo Lyn.
It dominantly defeated other videos with about one million views.
Congratulations, Gary.
- Thank you.
-  She congratulated Gary.
I'm happy although I failed to earn the final winner titles.
I don't think she meant it.
Not at all.
So, this is all for the July evaluation session.
As hard as you ran in July,
I hope you'll continue to do your best going forward as well.
- Thank you.
-  I'm Kim Mi Na.
Will you visit us every month, then?
- He's right.
-  "Will you visit us every month?"
I want to you see her every month.
This is how Jae Seok met his wife.
That's right. No, she's married.
- Gosh.
-  Really?
You really don't know who she is.
- Are you sad?
-  No.
(Thank you Mi Na for joining us.)
Are you leaving now?
Lastly,
we should talk about...
improvements we could make in the future.
Some said that there are too many betrayal and cheating...
although they sometimes make the programme fun.
- Oh, cheating.
-  There were many of them.
- So we made a bold decision.
-  What is it?
The Rio Olympic Games are being held now,
so we need to celebrate the Olympic spirit.
- For a month,
-  Without cheating?
We'll have a campaign against cheating and betrayal.
(Campaign against cheating and betrayal)
(Let's stamp out foul play and betrayal.)
- What is he talking about?
-  So for a month from today...
- Do you want us to die?
-  Actually,
no one wants to cheat or betray anyone,
however, to survive on this competitive show...
- It can't be helped.
-  What he's saying is accurate.
- If we don't, we'd be destroyed.
-  We would.
- All right?
-  Let's try not to cheat.
Aren't the results already determined?
For the next month,
we'll have a committee to ban cheating and betrayal.
- Really?
-  The committee members...
will keep you in check.
If...
you get more than three warnings by cheating or betraying this month...
and the committee points you out,
you'll be banned from participating in one episode of Running Man.
(Banned from participating in one episode)
- That's terrible.
-  Banned from participating?
Kwang Soo won't be on the show then.
Isn't that too cruel?
It's a very natural way to...
- let him go.
-  Wait a minute.
- Goodness.
-  You'll let me go?
- How could you fire me?
-  That's horrible.
That's a very complex way to let people go.
Please talk to them.
- That's how it's going to go.
-  Poor Kwang Soo.
I know.
- Isn't the result obvious?
-  It makes sense.
Gosh.
Based on the purpose of today's race, we'll divide you into teams.
Therefore,
we'll divide you into Team Singers...
and Team Non-singers.
Jong Kook,
Gary, Haha,
and Seok Jin are Team Singers.
Why Seok Jin?
- Is Seok Jin considered a singer?
-  Isn't that ambiguous?
It's been over 20 years since he released an album.
- Seok Jin is not a singer.
-  Yes, I am.
- He's not really a singer.
-  How is he a singer?
- Of course, I am.
-  He's a less experienced comedian.
How is he on my team?
I released an official album with eight tracks.
The remaining three...
are Team Non-singers.
Team Non-singers needs one more person.
We invited someone to fill...
the empty spot.
(A special guest is here for Team Non-singers.)
(Who's the special guest...)
(who will save Team Non-singers?)
- Goodness.
-  He's a real singer.
- Of course he is.
-  Gosh.
(Yoon Jong Shin)
(Running Man members, I'm here.)
(They're reluctant to welcome him.)
Is Jong Shin the only one who came today?
- Gosh.
-  No way.
Reporter Kim Mi Na left,
but why is Jong Shin here?
Jong Shin reminds me...
of Baek Il Seob quite a lot.
(He reminds me of Baek Il Seob.)
How could you say...
"quite a lot"?
He's gained a bit of weight.
You've become quite an old man.
I can't distinguish between...
you and Seok Jin if you have your sunglasses on.
He's a singer and producer.
He's the president of a large entertainment agency.
He's the head.
- Head?
-  Yes, the head.
Do you mean you'll drown me?
We invited Jong Shin, the head of an entertainment agency.
He's the CEO.
We'll start "Changing Lyrics Project".
- Changing lyrics?
-  Changing lyrics?
(Changing Lyrics Project?)
- What's that?
-  Jong Shin has composed...
- He's composed many.
-  Many popular songs.
With Jong Shin's songs,
we'll change the lyrics and compete.
That's the race for today.
I'm not happy with competing with non-singers.
- Jong Shin is on my team.
-  Jong Shin is a singer.
- That doesn't make a difference.
-  Why are you unhappy?
Most of them have voices that are louder than yours.
Do you know that? I'm sorry.
I still can't look at Jong Kook in the eyes.
There are words...
you must insert into the lyrics.
- Do we have to earn them?
-  Yes.
We have to insert them into the lyrics?
You must change the lyrics by adding the specific words...
that we give you.
Here are the criterion for evaluation.
There's 15 points for how well you change the lyrics,
and as you'll be performing, there's five points for performance.
- Five points?
-  Evaluating the change of lyrics...
will not only be based on what the audience thinks,
but it'll also be based on what seven celebrities think.
Celebrities?
(A celebrity evaluation group?)
The celebrity evaluation group includes...
actress Han Hye Jin.
- Really?
-  Actress Park Bo Young.
Lyricist Kim Ea Na.
Webtoon cartoonist Jo Seok.
DJ Song Eun I.
Music critic Im Jin Mo.
- Im Jin Mo?
-  We even have Jin Mo?
- This sounds difficult.
-  He represents music critics.
Lastly, we have anchor Bae Sung Jae.
We certainly have an award for the winner.
We'll give you Golden Musical Badge...
as an award.
As an additional award,
we'll give you a lost item that was found during last recording.
- What is it?
-  We'll give you...
two Golden Musical Badge...
and a Hungarian meal ticket.
- A Hungarian meal ticket?
-  Didn't he take it?
He received it last week but he left it behind.
Goodness, Jong Kook.
Why did you leave it?
Why did you do that?
You're not desperate at all.
Look at those messages.
Both teams will choose which song to sing.
- We selected four songs beforehand.
-  I want to sing "Patbingsu".
- It's definitely "Patbingsu".
- "Patbingsu".
-  I choose "Patbingsu".
- I definitely want to sing it.
-  "Patbingsu" is a good summer song.
- This is the first song.
-  This is it.
("Patbingsu")
- It's "Patbingsu".
-  Nice.
"Patbingsu" is one of the songs that represent summer.
Since Jong Shin releases many songs, we're always given one of his songs.
- I'm being serious.
-  It's a great song for the summer.
What are you talking about? It was organised beforehand.
- Did you hear what he said?
-  It was planned in detail.
"It was organised beforehand."
("Reincarnation")
It's "Reincarnation".
- "Reincarnation".
-  It's a different version.
It's from my fifth album in 1996.
("Reincarnation" was released in his fifth album in 1996.)
Isn't this originally a slow song?
- This is its reggae version.
-  I see.
Here's the next song.
("My Love Ugly")
It's "My Love Ugly".
- I see.
-  That's right.
- It was when Jong Kook debuted.
The song was competing with Turbo's songs.
That's right. It was released when Turbo debuted.
Shouldn't Jong Shin be on "Immortal Songs" instead?
(Every song that plays was a hit song in Korea.)
He should be somewhere else.
His songs are famous enough to be on "Immortal Songs".
- It came out when I was 10.
-  I know.
- Here's the last song...
-  It was when he was 10?
We selected.
("Highway Romance")
- This is also a great song.
-  I see.
- It's "Highway Romance".
-  "Highway Romance".
- I like this song.
-  Didn't Jang Hoon make it popular?
- That's right.
-  I was more famous than him.
Didn't it become popular because of Kim Jang Hoon?
- Didn't he also sing it?
-  I let him...
have it to save his career.
- Open the windows
-  Hey.
- And shout
-  Isn't it Kim Jang Hoon's song?
It is Jang Hoon's song.
- No, it isn't.
-  Didn't he sing it while kicking?
We know of it as Kim Jang Hoon's song, but it's actually Jong Shin's.
- Did you or Jang Hoon sing it?
-  Jang Hoon sang the song.
- I sang this version.
-  Did he remake it?
Jang Hoon can't sing like that.
(He mimics Jang Hoon's singing.)
He sings like this.
I told you that Jong Shin gets lucky like this.
- Also...
-  He did with "Highway Romance".
Why do you keep saying that? I'm not a boxer.
It's either "Patbingsu" or "Highway Romance".
- I want to sing "Patbingsu".
-  Yes, you should choose one.
- I want either "Patbingsu"...
-  "Patbingsu" sounds good.
I like "Highway Romance".
I also like "Highway Romance".
- I agree.
-  Okay.
- It suits summer holiday season.
-  Right.
It's also a great song to listen to while driving.
That's true.
You'll sing "Highway Romance".
- Shall we?
-  Gosh.
- It might be moving.
-  All right.
(The war on "Changing Lyrics" officially starts.)
- Non-singers, come here.
-  Okay.
We can't cheat, but can't we have physical fights?
Physical fights are okay.
The committee will determine if you're cheating or not.
They're really over there.
(We're watching you.)
(Why are you scaring us?)
For today's "Changing Lyrics Project",
there's an item that may help you. The winner of the game will get it.
(An item?)
What kind of item?
What? Is it an intro?
It's a great song.
(Why do we hear music instead of seeing an item?)
- Isn't that Kim Kyung Ho?
-  It's Kim Kyung Ho.
- Goodness.
-  What?
- It's Kim Kyung Ho.
-  Oh, my.
- He's the item?
-  No way.
I thought he was Kim Hyun Jung.
- What's going on?
-  Kyung Ho.
I didn't know it was Kyung Ho.
- I can't believe it.
-  Are you the item?
Kyung Ho.
- Are we having a pool party?
-  Is he going to sing?
(This is it!)
("People Who Make Me Sad" by Kim Kyung Ho)
Is this some kind of a party?
His voice is great for singing "Highway Romance".
- Really?
-  That's true.
That's awesome.
The item is a singer.
(Kim Kyung Ho is a great item everyone wants to have.)
He's a great item.
Let's play the game.
(Can't I be someone like him)
(To you)
(Everyone is hypnotised by him.)
(I love you, Kyung Ho.)
Stop it already.
(He sings in vibrato.)
(I want to run)
(I wish)
(I could tell him)
(This)
(I give you my everything, Kyung Ho.)
(To me)
(She's my everything in life)
Thank you.
(Kim Kyung Ho is the best item.)
Kyung Ho.
Team Non-singers...
gets to choose an item first.
- We should choose Kyung Ho.
-  Here's the next item.
- What did he say?
-  There's another one?
- It's "Mad".
-  What's this?
Everyone, turn it in circles.
(Turn it in circles!)
(She's here.)
Everyone, turn...
your finger in circles.
(Mad)
- Mad
-  Nice.
(Everyone's into her song.)
(Bada, the human megaphone)
(Pointing)
(Water gun is cast into the water.)
(Do you trust me?)
(Yes, we do.)
("Summer Time" by Bada)
(I want her on my team.)
(Dancing)
(The second candidate is also desirable.)
- Hello.
-  Hello.
You're great.
I guess we get to choose whoever they didn't choose.
Everyone.
Your items are Kyung Ho and Bada.
- They are both appealing.
-  I know. I want them both.
- We are satisfied either way.
-  Who should we choose?
- I like both of them.
-  Seok Jin.
- I know.
-  We do like both of them.
I'm a good swimmer.
How have you been, Seok Jin?
(Who will Team Non-singers choose?)
- In 3, 2, 1... Kim Kyung Ho.
-  Kim Kyung Ho.
(Kim Kyung Ho)
- Kyung Ho joins Team Non-singers,
-  Yes. Bada!
- and Bada will join Team Singers.
-  Mad.
(Team Singers and Team Non-singers are assigned.)
(They are holding hands.)
I'm so uncomfortable right now.
- Why?
-  I'm so...
- It's my first time seeing her.
-  Really?
- Do you really have to do this?
-  It's all right.
- It's all fine.
-  Is it?
(I don't want to let go of this hand.)
- Even I'm getting uncomfortable.
-  It'll be fine.
(Hula hoops are hanging over the pool. )
What is this? Do we have to get through these?
Are we watching a dolphin show?
What if they light a fire on it?
- Please, don't.
-  We aren't animals doing tricks.
(You should've expected this much. This is Running Man.)
The first game is "Toss Them In".
We'll have to hold up someone.
I knew this would happen.
- Let me explain.
-  Is this even possible?
- Choose one person among your team,
-  And you'll throw them in the air.
And pass the person through the hoops.
Whoever gets to the finish line first will win this game.
- An item will be given as an award.
-  We'll have to throw...
and the person will have to jump too.
We'll reveal the item first.
- Are they going to show us now?
-  There's another item?
You'll have to win the game first.
- What's happening?
-  What music is this?
- Are they men?
-  I guess he's not a fashion expert.
- I can't see his face.
-  They have poor sense of style.
(Who would they be?)
They have poor sense of style.
- Who are they?
-  It's Yoo Byung Jae.
Cho Jung Chi.
(Oh my.)
- It's Byung Jae and Jung Chi.
-  It's Byung Jae and Jung Chi.
- It's Jung Chi.
-  Jung Chi works for Jong Shin.
Did Jong Shin recommend him?
Jong Shin must've recommended him.
Did Jong Shin pay you to get him on the show?
- Why are you here, really?
-  Is your company facing crisis?
Your company must be facing crisis.
I paid for this water.
I paid for everything today.
- He says he paid to be on the show.
-  Jong Shin, don't be like that.
So do we have to play this game to take one of them?
I think the least two popular people...
from each company are here.
The least popular at YG,
and the least popular at Mystic 89.
Goodness.
- I respect you all.
-  You look great.
- We missed you.
-  Hi, Byung Jae.
- Who should we choose?
-  Jung Chi, good to see you.
- Hi, Jung Chi.
-  Hello.
- Hello, Jung Chi.
-  Musically, Jung Chi is talented...
- You shaved your beard, Jung Chi.
-  Byung Jae is good for performance.
- I agree.
-  Yes, performance is his strength.
- He's a writer.
-  Yes.
- That's right.
-  He'd be full of ideas.
-  It's true.
- Right.
-  I know.
Jung Chi has a baby now. He'll work hard.
(I need to support my family.)
Please choose a person to pass through the hoops.
(I'm so happy.)
(She must be very happy.)
Aren't you a member of Dynamic Duo?
(A member of Dynamic Duo?)
No, I'm not. Wait a minute.
- No, I didn't mean to...
-  She asked me if I'm Dynamic Duo.
Please, stop.
She asked me why I didn't feature her album.
I said I hadn't heard about it. Then she asks me if I'm Gaeko.
- Really?
-  She asked me if I'm Gaeko.
- What are you talking about?
-  No, what I mean is that...
- Do you not know Gary?
-  Did you say Dynamic Duo?
- I meant to say Two Ssang.
-  She just said Two Ssang.
I worked with Gaeko recently and people asked me...
if he was the one who wrote erotic lyrics.
- People get confused.
-  How can it be confusing?
Erotic lyrics...
Please be fair and square. It's a single-round match.
- Of course.
-  Throw her first.
- Hey, Gaeko.
-  Just do well.
(Fine. I'll be Gaeko then.)
Get ready.
(It's Ji Hyo versus Bada.)
(The winner gets to choose first.)
(Diving)
(Bada kicks off fast.)
- Let's go.
-  We are on the track.
(Ji Hyo swims fast to keep up with her.)
- Jump.
-  That's right.
- Hurry.
-  Go. Pass through it.
(Bada passes the third hoop.)
You're doing well.
(Ji Hyo passes the third hoop.)
(Bada is indeed good at swimming.)
- They are so fast.
-  Just step on me.
- Go, go.
-  Let's get going.
- Just step on my hands.
-  Hurry.
- Hurry up.
-  Good job.
- That's right.
-  You're doing great.
- All right, Ji Hyo.
-  Good job.
We almost got them.
Seok Jin, get out of our way!
(Bada passes the fifth hoop.)
- Let's go.
-  Seok Jin, move.
(I don't care about the referee. I'm going to win.)
- Let's go.
-  Come on. Hurry.
Great job.
(Ji Hyo passes the fifth hoop.)
Be careful.
- Hold her.
-  Be careful not to fall down.
-  Be careful.
(This is the last hoop.)
(We won't let that happen.)
No way.
(Grabbing)
(We knew they would play dirty.)
Pull her out.
(We'll drag you back to the other side of the hoop.)
(Jae Seok and Kwang Soo each get a warning.)
(It's chaotic here.)
(Aren't I here to sing?)
Let her go.
Stop her.
(Ji Hyo won't miss this chance.)
(Even Ji Hyo is trying to cheat.)
I won't let you pass.
(We don't know the meaning of fair play.)
(Are they doing all that just for us?)
Tilt her body.
(Who will get through this chaos first?)
- No way.
-  We're almost there.
(They pass the hoop at the same time.)
(Bada is slightly ahead of Ji Hyo.)
Bada got through.
- Are you guys all right?
-  Team Singer wins the game.
We won.
- Yoo Byung Jae.
-  Yoo Byung Jae.
(Thanks a lot.)
You guys are so slow.
- This game wasn't fit for me.
-  What?
Kyung Ho, I can't stand the scent of your shampoo.
- Was it his hair?
-  Yes, it's Kyung Ho's hair.
It was so sweet I almost fell asleep.
Kyung Ho, that was too much.
The scent reminds me of France.
This is hilarious.
- We are about to choose.
-  I think my mum uses that shampoo.
You guys are so indifferent. Show us something.
- He's right.
-  Show us something.
- We had to play a game.
-  Boast your charms.
Since I'm a writer, I know I can write good lyrics.
- What about you, Jung Chi?
-  He's also a good lyricist.
I wrote lyrics for 10 songs this month.
- Then he must be out of ideas.
-  Are there any popular songs?
(He must be out of ideas.)
We've reached a decision.
- Have you decided?
-  Yes.
(Between Jung Chi and Byung Jae, who will Team Singers choose?)
- Yoo Byung Jae.
-  Yoo Byung Jae.
Cho Jung Chi.
- Cho Jung Chi.
-  Cho Jung Chi.
(Byung Jae joins Team Singers and Jung Chi joins Team Non-singers.)
When it comes to music, Jung Chi is the right one.
Byung Jae is on our team now.
- What?
-  Byung Jae.
Hi, Byung Jae.
- He'll be really helpful.
-  Yes.
- We can see that he hates his team.
-  My shoulder hurts.
Look. He's sweating.
Byung Jae is...
one of my favourite people.
- Do you guys keep in touch?
-  No.
- Byung Jae, give me your number.
-  Yes, I will.
Jung Chi, you're not sick or anything, right?
Yes, I'm healthy.
What's wrong with your rash guard?
Your rash guard seems too big.
He makes it feel like we're here for medical treatments.
Don't say that.
- He's here to practise.
-  He's your employee.
Don't put it that way. Stop teasing him.
The winner of this game will get to choose the order of performance.
- This is really important.
-  It's important.
- It is.
-  We must win.
Whoever sings last will have the advantage.
We'll compete with the same song.
This mission is called "The Battle of Flamingos".
"The Battle of Flamingos".
Here are floating swans and flamingos.
Hop on the tube and knock out the others.
Whoever survives until the end wins.
- It'll be a lot of fun.
-  Can we get physical?
Getting physical is only natural.
It should be allowed.
Is the rule same as the cavalry-battle game?
- The cavalry-battle game.
-  You are correct.
The losing team must include "The Battle of Flamingos" in lyrics.
How do we include "flamingos" in "Highway Romance"?
- It's a total mismatch.
-  It doesn't make any sense.
You'll have to incorporate it using your ideas.
("The Battle of Flamingos" starts.)
Jong Shin, knocking out Jong Kook is really important.
- I think this will do.
-  How about this?
(They can pick a weapon to attack.)
- You can go over and push.
-  I like this one.
If Jong Kook attacks you, you shouldn't fall down alone.
- What do I do then?
-  Try to take him down with you.
- Take him with you.
-  Sacrifice yourself.
Like Nongae.
(I won't let it happen.)
(The order of performance depends on this game.)
- Can I try this on you?
-  Yes.
- Goodness.
-  What do you think?
- Does it hurt?
-  Try hitting my palm.
(Punching)
(I'll fly like a butterfly and sting like a bee.)
- All right, let's go.
-  Let's go.
(Both teams enter the pool.)
(Six swans versus six flamingos)
- Is everyone ready?
-  Yes.
Get ready.
(We will win and get the right to choose the order of performance.)
(Who will be the winner between flamingos and swans?)
("The Battle of Flamingos" begins.)
(Who should I attack first?)
Come on, Kyung Ho.
It's too fast.
(They are about to clash.)
(The players are looking for their opportunities.)
(Who will be thrown into the water first today?)
- It's too fast.
-  I'm keep losing my balance.
My tube is going flat.
(What happened?)
- I'm doomed.
-  What are you doing?
- Please come out.
-  What is this?
(Meanwhile, Gary is approaching Jae Seok.)
Hey. Gary is behind you.
- Be careful.
-  I'm scared.
- I got him.
-  Wait a minute.
(Gary and Jong Kook surrounds Jae Seok.)
Jae Seok, watch out.
(I'm coming for you, Jae Seok.)
(Charge forward)
No. Seok Jin.
(Jong Shin seizes a good opportunity and attacks Jong Kook.)
Jong Shin. When you play against Jong Kook,
try to fall in together. Grab him when you fall down.
- I shouldn't aim to survive alone.
-  Exactly.
(Will he able to dive in with Jong Kook?)
(Jong Shin, Gary, Jae Seok, Jong Kook)
(Falling)
(Jong Shin falls and gets eliminated alone.)
(Jae Seok is still in danger.)
(Ji Hyo is on her way to assist Jae Seok.)
(Hitting)
Seok Jin.
(But...)
(the tube is flipped upside down.)
My tube is flat.
(What?)
(Is he still in the game?)
Grab this.
Isn't he out?
(He hasn't touched the floor yet.)
- He is still in.
-  How come?
- Isn't he out?
-  No, he's not. He's still playing.
I'm not out yet.
- He's not out.
-  I'm not.
(Meanwhile, in the other side of the pool...)
What a great chance. I got this.
(Gary is our target.)
(Kwang Soo is holding something in his hand.)
(Gosh. They are scissors.)
(Kwang Soo punctures Gary's tube.)
He's out, isn't he?
(Goodbye, Gary.)
Hey, Ji Hyo.
My tube is going flat.
(What's going on there?)
(Referees couldn't catch Kwang Soo.)
(Laughing)
Look. Isn't he out?
(Ji Hyo is attacked by Gary.)
No, he is not out yet.
(Ji Hyo is out.)
Ji Hyo is out.
Dong Hoon. Haha.
- Please, rescue me.
-  Hang in there.
Please come and save me.
Hang in there, Gary.
Hurry.
(His tube is going flat.)
My tube is almost flat now.
Hurry up. Come and save me.
(Ripping)
(Kwang Soo continues ripping other tubes.)
(Kwang Soo the Scissorhands)
Why is my tube going flat?
What's going on?
(Kwang Soo hid his scissors under his gloves.)
(That's the reason why referees cannot catch him.)
(Kwang Soo is the master of cheating with six years of experience.)
(He continues to succeed in puncturing others' tubes.)
Why is my tube going flat?
What's going on?
- What is this?
-  Mine is going flat.
My tube is going flat.
- There's a hole here.
-  What is that in your hand?
Where is the head of my swan?
- Look at this.
-  He has scissors in his hand.
Look. Take a look at this.
(Who said you can use that?)
(They revenge Kwang Soo for his cheating.)
(Why are they fighting in the middle of the game?)
He cheated.
Kwang Soo made a hole on my tube.
(A cheater must be punished.)
(They are paying him back.)
Kwang Soo has a nail.
Why were you just watching?
He has scissors in his right hand.
He has scissors.
Stop it. Wasn't that enough?
(Because of Kwang Soo, Haha, Seok Jin and Gary are out.)
Jae Seok. No.
(Jae Seok is still holding on.)
My tube is flat.
(Jae Seok is in danger.)
Referees. Isn't he out?
I'm not.
- Isn't he out?
-  No.
He's still in.
(Jae Seok is really tenacious.)
- He's still in.
-  Hang in there.
- I'm still in the game.
-  He's not out.
Jae Seok. Hang in there just a little longer.
- Hey. What are you doing?
-  Hey.
(Jong Kook makes a hole on Jae Seok's tube with his teeth.)
(That's monstrous strength.)
Hey. What are you doing?
Hang in there. Just hang in there.
Swim, Jae Seok. You can swim.
(Jae Seok hasn't touched the floor yet.)
- Isn't he out?
-  No, he isn't.
He hasn't touched the floor yet.
- No?
-  Yes. I knew that.
(Won't you go out? Please?)
Take Jong Kook with you.
Jae Seok, grab Jong Kook and fall in together.
I can't.
(While Jae Seok is trying hard to survive, )
(Bada and Byung Jae get eliminated one after another.)
Jae Seok, grab Jong Kook and fall in together.
- I can't do two things at once.
-  Jung Chi.
We need more.
- Block the hole. Block it.
-  Come this way.
You should puncture his tube.
(Jong Kook approaches Jung Chi, who is a weaker prey.)
(There you are.)
- Don't attack Jung Chi.
-  Stay away from Jong Kook.
- Be careful with your legs.
-  He is really scary.
(You can't run away from me.)
- He's like a shark.
-  Grab him and dive in together.
That's right.
- Jung Chi, grab him and dive in.
-  That's right.
(He looks as scary as a shark.)
- Let my legs go.
-  Jung Chi, grab him and dive.
- That's right.
-  Jung Chi.
- No. Jung Chi.
-  Flip the tube.
(Flipping)
(Jung Chi is out.)
Hey, Jae Seok.
- He is the only one.
-  What an easy target he is.
(I'm coming for you, Jae Seok.)
- It's Jong Kook.
-  You can win this fight, Jae Seok.
- He's scary.
-  He looks like a pirate ship.
(Jong Kook is about to ram Jae Seok.)
No. Jae Seok.
- There you are.
-  It's a shark.
(To catch or to be caught, that is the question.)
- He's coming for your head.
-  Poor Jae Seok.
- Jae Seok, grab Jong Kook.
-  Yes. That's right.
- He's out already.
-  No, he isn't.
(I wasn't hanging in there for nothing.)
(It isn't over until it's over.)
Use your teeth. Rip off the head of his tube.
- That's it.
-  Rip it off. Yes.
That's it.
(It must be easier to bite with his protruding mouth.)
(Can you stop biting, please?)
- It's all over, Jae Seok. Give up.
-  It's over.
- Rip it off with your teeth.
-  He needs Kwang Soo.
(I'm not giving up here.)
- He's so desperate.
-  A little bit more.
Use your canine.
Don't do that. He will bite your hand off.
(That flamingo must be really delicious.)
- It's almost...
-  Yes. That's it.
Pull him down. Pull him.
(Jae Seok strikes back.)
(Yes!)
(Did Jae Seok win? Then it must be the biggest upset in Running Man.)
What is going on?
(Did I finally beat Jong Kook?)
(He never stood a chance against Jong Kook.)
(After all those years of humiliation...)
(I fought, and I won.)
(You finally...)
(Hold on!)
He's not out.
(Jong Kook isn't out yet.)
(Replay)
(Jong Kook managed to hang onto the tube.)
(Jae Seok touched the floor first.)
I thought I won.
(Team Singers has won "The Battle of Flamingos".)
- I thought I won.
-  But you didn't.
- I thought it was over.
-  Didn't you expect that?
No, I didn't. I thought it was over.
- He didn't touch the ground.
-  Yes, that's right.
- He turned himself around.
-  Exactly.
You hung on to that for quite long.
I was holding on...
to this dead flamingo.
(Team Singers wins the Performance Order Card.)
I was really surprised...
- in the waiting room. Really.
-  Why?
- What was the matter?
-  I thought...
there was another female guest with us today.
Really. I'm not kidding.
I often get surprised.
Actually,
it has been 22 years since I last took a shower...
- in a public shower.
-  What?
- Really?
-  Yes, 22 years.
- Why?
-  There was an incident before.
- Yes, I remember it.
-  I was called outside...
from a public shower by the police because of my long hair.
After that, I never went to public showers even with my friends.
Today I did. It felt strange and embarrassing.
Byung Jae was stuck in the corner.
While we were taking a shower,
he was standing in the corner by himself and...
(Looking around)
- Why are you so shy?
-  What's the matter with you?
Why are you always stuck in the corner?
You shouldn't be sitting here. Can you change your seat with him?
- You must sit here today.
-  That looks good.
- It suits him better.
-  Stay next to Jong Kook.
Don't stay at the sides.
- Stay at the centre.
-  He should.
(I envy him.)
We're going to begin a war with words.
You will toss words to each other by playing games.
Toss us really difficult or really strange words.
We have to win a game to toss words, right?
- Yes.
-  And our sentences must make sense.
- Of course.
-  Let's see.
- It'll be evaluated by experts.
-  You will...
- "Sweating madly" looks great.
-  "Sweating madly".
They have "bamboo floor".
"Piranha" is hard to pronounce.
"Piranha" seems good.
"Piranha".
- "Piranha" is ours.
-  That's terrifying.
Jong Shin's jokes are like piranhas.
I'm never the first.
If someone's bleeding, I get closer.
If someone drops a bait,
he bites it.
- "My love, Soo Ae" is a title.
-  There won't be much left.
- What?
-  "My love, Soo Ae".
There's Su Ae.
They won't be able to use "My Love, Soo Ae" well.
We'll have to take it.
- Let's choose a unique one.
-  "My Love, Soo Ae" is far-fetched.
Jong Kook, you should do mosquito repellent.
- Or what about...
-  That's good.
We need to repel you.
- Do you want him to die?
-  Do you?
You've seem to have lost it since it's been a while since we met.
- What did you say?
-  What?
This game is called "10 Songs Challenge".
- That's great.
-  If you stop singing...
or if the lyrics are incorrect, you will receive a warning.
It's possible that only one person tries.
So we win if just one person gets it correct?
That's right. The person who knows the song should sing.
You will be warned if you get it wrong.
You'll be able to see part of the lyrics.
Let's go.
- Let's do this.
-  We can do it.
Let's sing "Emergency Room".
- "Emergency Room".
-  Number five!
(They're a great team.)
It's related to summer.
Summer.
- This is...
-  It's about summer.
- That's easy.
-  Is this a summer song?
- My goodness.
-  Watch the pronunciation.
- Okay.
-  I know the whole lyrics.
(The lyrics are shown with blank spots.)
- You need to go on the ice.
-  Get on it.
- Go on it.
-  You need to go on.
(He's frozen.)
(It rids of the heat instantly.)
- Gosh, it's cold.
-  You need to bear it.
(I can't.)
Put one foot at a time.
(I'll dance the pain off.)
The prelude is so long.
Stay a while longer.
- A while longer.
-  I can't.
- In 1, 2, 3 and 4.
-  In 1, 2, 3 and 4.
When you feel gloomy.
Go up to the mountain and shout.
Like me, like me
(1st warning)
Kung ddari sha bah rah bah bah bah.
- Anyone
-  Happiness.
(They get it wrong.)
(Thanks to Kwang Soo, )
(joy and sorrow are exchanged.)
- He got it wrong.
-  Isn't it "Anyone could feel"?
- Anyone could feel
-  That it doesn't go their way.
- That it doesn't go their way
-  Then like me.
(Halting)
(I'm getting confused.)
I know it but I forgot.
It's easy to forget.
- It is.
-  It's too hard.
It would be amazing if they chose "Patbingsu" by Jong Shin.
I need to see the lyrics to sing it.
I can't sing without the lyrics.
Singers my age can't sing without the lyrics.
- My feet hurt.
-  Gary picks well.
- That's right. He's lucky.
-  My feet hurt.
- It's number 10.
-  Anyways...
- I know that song well.
-  It's "Eve's Warning".
- I know it.
-  Really?
- Are you sure?
-  Yes, I'm certain.
- Don't sing it in the original key.
-  Not the original note?
- Jump.
-  Pull it.
(The song starts.)
The prelude is really long.
I want to skip it.
You need to stay on it.
I thought it out wrong.
It's really long.
(She needs to be on the ice.)
- It's so cold.
-  Why did you go all the way there?
- You avoid me again
-  Not yet.
- In 1 and 2.
-  In 1, 2, 3 and 4.
You avoid me again while thinking of other things.
(It's a smooth start.)
Never been.
(She shuts her eyes tightly.)
If you know my thoughts today.
(She gets it wrong.)
- It's not that.
-  It was written.
- I tried not to look at it.
-  It was written on the board.
- Is it your first time hearing it?
-  I tried not to look.
- My goodness.
-  I memorised it.
Are you insane?
You're so mad.
I tried not to look at it.
I thought I had memorised it so I had my eyes closed.
You've failed.
I'm sorry.
- It's not as easy as you think.
-  It's difficult.
- It's difficult.
-  Number one.
- Isn't it "Patbingsu"?
-  It's "Patbingsu".
- I know this one.
-  Great.
I know this completely.
Can't I sing it?
- Byung Jae.
-  Byung Jae.
- You can't see it.
-  It's too cold.
(He slips on the ice.)
- He fails if he slips off.
-  Yes.
(Is he frozen?)
The intro is really important.
(The beginning is important.)
It hasn't started yet.
Wow, it's summer.
- Byung Jae, good luck!
-  It's really long.
It's a party.
(The prelude is really long.)
(But my feet are experiencing winter.)
- I don't need to do that part.
-  It's winter.
It's summer time.
What is this?
- What?
-  In this summer.
(He has no boundaries in range.)
I'm just home alone
I can't
- I'll just have
-  It's cold.
- To break up with you
-  Great.
The tears that you shed.
- He got it wrong.
-  It was difficult for me too.
(He fails.)
- It's difficult.
-  Don't go up on it.
This is stressful.
- It's harder than I thought.
-  No one completes it.
(The prelude was longer than the time he sang.)
I'm getting very stressed.
I want to go to a karaoke!
We'll give you two warnings from now on.
We will give you...
- Okay.
-  One more chance.
Let's pick a song we know.
- It's number 2.
-  Number 2.
I know this one!
Do you know this?
- Let's sing it together.
-  You need to go on the ice.
(Striding)
- Go on it.
-  Step on top of it.
- You need to go on top.
-  I can't do the rap.
Past summer.
(He feels the cold.)
(They're a perfect team.)
- He seems cold.
-  He won't make it.
(I'm a professional karaoke singer.)
Kwang Soo, isn't it cold?
In 1, 2, 3 and 4.
Past summer.
The girl I met at the beach.
Had long, dark hair.
There was no need to ponder
I just fell in love.
I fell in love.
(See?)
- Where?
-  I met her.
- The beautiful girl
-  You didn't know.
I can't believe it.
- She is so beautiful
-  You can't meet her.
- I was so lucky
-  Isn't it "I can't meet her"?
- You got it wrong.
-  You're incorrect.
- The starry beach
-  They said "sketch book".
Sing it instead of me.
(They receive their 1st warning.)
(Jae Seok takes Kwang Soo's spot.)
It's prelude.
(It's the prelude as soon as he steps in.)
You should have picked this.
After winter.
(They receive their 2nd warning.)
Please come back and save me.
(They fail.)
(That's a shame.)
- It's not easy.
-  Jae Seok.
- Like a crazy person
-  It's too difficult.
- It's number 4.
-  Number 4.
- Okay.
-  Number four.
- We only have one left.
-  "In Summer".
- Haha.
-  I know this one.
It's Deux.
It's Deux. Let's sing what we know.
(Singing)
(He looks at ease.)
Deux.
(He's full of confidence.)
- Story
-  Looking at you.
(He tries to distract them.)
I know it.
(They're determined to win.)
I'll sing the parts I know.
People who know the song, keep singing it.
Get ready.
The moment I've been dreaming of.
- Here
-  Is unfolding here.
(They receive their 1st warning.)
My heart towards you.
You accepted it.
(Bada says the lyrics in advance...)
(and Jong Kook sings it.)
(They're a great team.)
- Cool breeze
-  Cool breeze.
- Comes to me
-  I feel
- I feel
-  Happiness.
- Happiness
-  We did it!
(They only have the refrain left.)
- We're here
-  The sky.
The sky is open.
- Listen carefully.
-  Next to me.
(He tries to spot any mistakes.)
(It won't work.)
- Listen carefully!
-  You stand.
With a big smile.
You're the blue ocean.
(They pass!)
(Long live Deux.)
- Deux.
-  I don't know this song.
- That's it.
-  Team Singers win.
(Team Singers win "10 Songs Challenge".)
You can choose three words.
You can toss it to the other team.
Pick "Gimnyeong Seonsegi Beach".
- This one.
-  "Chogyeguksu".
- "Chogyeguksu".
-  "Gimnyeong Seonsegi Beach".
-  It's no good.
- Can it go in?
-  How about "straw handbag"?
"Straw handbag"? Let's go with that.
- "Straw handbag"?
-  "Hyo Lyn".
(He slyly joins in.)
- This is difficult.
-  Get out.
(Get out.)
What are you doing here?
"Kongguksu" looks good.
- That sounds good.
-  "Kongguksu".
It's boring.
We can make good use of Kongguksu.
- Try kongguksu in summer
-  Seok Jin.
- It's only seven dollars
(They're a great team.)
It needs to be opposite.
(I'm great at changing lyrics.)
It's great.
Do "the butterfly stroke".
That's boring.
Wait. If it goes with...
It's funny if they say they do the butterfly stroke in kongguksu.
The butterfly stroke is my star.
That's right.
(These are the words that they selected for each other.)
The next stage will be...
- tossing difficult words.
-  Great.
So we'll do proverbs.
- That's really difficult.
-  That's too hard.
- That's really hard.
-  I don't know many.
It will be limited to proverbs related to summer.
The winning team selects a proverb to give to the losing team.
The proverb should be added to the lyrics?
Yes, the proverb has to be included in the lyrics.
(How do we include proverbs in the lyrics?)
The next game is called "Exploding Karaoke".
- Is that right?
-  Will something explode?
We'll give you a topic without playing the music.
Then, you must at least sing four phrases, or one verse,
of a song that's related to the topic.
This is scary.
In three minutes, it'll explode.
- That's right.
-  We have to be careful.
- Shall we start?
-  Hold it like this.
We'll get started. The topic is...
- food.
-  Food?
- All right.
-  Songs that relate to food?
- It's difficult.
-  Either the lyrics include food...
- If food is included in the lyrics?
-  I don't know any.
- I have so many on my mind.
-  Let's start.
I'm afraid someone will sing the song I have in mind.
Start.
A woman who makes good kimchi bokkeumbap.
- That was one song.
-  Woman.
Bingsu.
- Patbingsu
-  Oh, no. What should I sing?
Don't melt.
What should I sing?
Yongyebaeksuk.
- Yongyebaeksuk
-  I have no idea what to sing.
- I have no idea what to sing.
-  Take it.
- Wait a minute.
-  Take your time. You have time.
- What should I sing?
-  You may run out of time.
I haven't thought of any.
- Give me a hint, please.
-  Americano.
Oh, that's right.
Americano.
That startled me.
(Goodness)
- No, this can't happen.
-  What did you do?
The time is almost up.
I like Americano.
Americano, syrup, syrup, syrup.
Naengmyeon, naengmyeon.
You might as well say kongguksu.
That's true.
Naengmyeon, naengmyeon.
You are too cold.
- Three minutes will be up.
-  It's.
Very delicious.
Naengmyeon, naengmyeon, naengmyeon.
- She did it.
-  Ji Hyo is impressive.
I haven't cooked for you once.
That was amazing.
The lyrics mention food.
The topic is food.
- Twelve legs of squid
-  Kwang Soo.
What did you say?
- What did you say?
-  I said squids!
- What was the word?
-  It's "Squid Aliens".
- He said squid.
-  Stop singing that song.
- What's that?
-  A glass of Bellflower whiskey.
- What's this song?
-  It's by Choi Baek Ho.
You're right!
- You have a minute and half.
-  We have enough time.
My hand keeps going.
- No way.
-  You can't sing that.
- It counts.
-  No way.
- It's a song from a commercial.
-  This doesn't count.
It's okay as long as you don't say the brand.
- Why doesn't this song count?
-  It doesn't count.
Hurry up.
About two minutes have passed.
I'll hand it over when three minutes have pass.
- Hey.
-  I can't come up with any.
- When it's been 3 minutes...
-  Take it from him after 5 seconds.
What if it explodes on me? Hurry up!
- It might explode on you.
-  If.
- There was no kimchi
-  If there was no kimchi.
There it is.
How will we eat rice?
- Give it to me now.
-  Hurry.
(Give it to me now.)
Mother said she didn't like jajangmyeon.
Take it now.
- Hello, it's me
-  At least, I passed.
It's "A Shot of Soju".
He passed.
(He sings.)
"Bob" is not food.
- You dropped the microphone.
-  Cuban sandwich.
- Put it back on now.
- Does that song work?
-  Cuban sandwich.
(He switches to a song about sandwiches.)
- Put the microphone back on.
-  I sang one.
- It's Jong Shin's song.
-  Hey, hey.
(Jung Chi is selected.)
Hey, hey.
- Did he lose?
-  No way.
Isn't it one of your songs?
Cuban sandwich.
He sang a song we didn't know.
He has a song called "Cuban sandwich".
- That song doesn't count.
-  Wait.
- Wait.
-  Why don't you listen to it...
- starting now?
-  No way.
- It doesn't count.
-  What?
- Why should we listen to it?
-  Cuban, Cuban.
- Look it up on music charts!
-  Stop singing.
- You'll find it.
-  What are you doing?
- Search it online.
-  What's your problem?
Who composed the song?
- The winning team is...
-  The song doesn't exist.
Team Singers.
(Team Singers wins "Exploding Karaoke".)
You must be confused,
but the order should have started again from the first person.
Let's just continue.
- It's a waste of time.
-  I do think...
that's the right order.
Let's start with Gary,
and he'll start again after Ji Hyo finishes.
Yes, that's fair.
Here's the topic. Listen carefully.
They'll give us a hard one.
It's either location or name.
- Gosh, all right.
-  Name of a person.
Get ready, start.
Seoul, Seoul, Seoul, a place I remember.
How many people came to visit?
Don't refuse.
- He's singing his own song.
-  He has his own.
- Good job.
-  Jae Seok has his own song.
Everybody, come to Haeundae.
("Busan Vacance" by Skull and Haha)
(Singing)
Everybody, come to Dongbaek Island.
The lyrics include so many places. Haeundae, Dongbaek Island.
- Crossing Jeolla Province
-  And Gyeongsang Province.
His songs are always depressing.
Ari, Ari, sseuri, sseuri.
- Where's the place?
-  It's "Jeongseon Arirang".
- Ari, Ari
-  He's right.
- Hill
-  Hill.
- Heeya, please look at me
-  What should I sing?
- It's "Heeya".
-  It is.
What should I do?
Annie.
- It's "Annie".
-  Do you know?
All right, I'll sing this one.
J, in passing wind.
- He's safe.
-  All right.
Can I sing this one?
Let's run to a rough field.
- Is it because of "field"?
-  Field.
Field.
(Field is not a location.)
That doesn't work.
That definitely doesn't count.
- "Field" doesn't count.
-  "Field"?
- Goodness.
-  Location?
- Wait, I remember.
-  Southeast of Ulleung Island.
Right, I remember now.
Southeast.
- Of Ulleung Island
-  It's "Dokdo is Our Land".
It's a lonely island, a homeland for birds.
When the boatman's singing fades.
- What song is that?
-  Dongbaek Island where flowers grow.
That's a great song.
That was one.
Yeosu night sea.
- Hurry and give it to him.
-  Is it my turn?
- Hurry up.
-  Give it to him now.
Can you tell me a song?
- Let's leave together
-  "The Blue Night of Jeju Island".
Let's forget everything and go to Jeju Island
- I said, I love you only
-  What's wrong with him?
- "Only" isn't a name.
-  "Only".
That doesn't count.
- "Only" can be a name.
-  No, it can't.
I know someone named Only!
That doesn't work.
- Which apartment does she live in?
-  In block 15!
- Hurry up.
-  Why doesn't it count?
- You don't have much time.
-  Hurry.
- The explosion won't reach you.
-  S, E, O, U, L.
S, E, O, U, L
A small boy named Dong Hoon.
Here you go.
- Hurry up.
-  Ja Ok.
- "The Honam Railroad in the Rain".
-  I was going to sing it.
Sing it.
(It's Jung Chi again.)
You should've sung that.
Both of them exploded near me.
- All right.
-  Goodness.
Why didn't you sing it?
Team Singers wins.
(Team Singers wins the second round.)
Take a proverb.
(Team Non-singers gets a proverb.)
"Weak things united become strong."
"When the season ends, mosquitoes start to disappear."
(They've decided immediately.)
- I've never heard of those.
-  What about mosquitoes?
We can use that in the lyrics.
Write down that proverb.
(Team Non-singers gets the proverb about mosquitoes.)
With the given words and proverb,
you'll change the lyrics.
- Really?
-  Get together.
Let's do it.
You can start.
There are so many.
We have to add 11 things.
This is a good idea.
Let's choose a topic.
- Seobinggo is a location.
-  Vacation...
Let's have Hyo Lyn as the person leaving.
Of course, Hyo Lyn should leave.
- Let's have Seobinggo...
-  Hyo Lyn didn't do anything wrong.
- the place of departure.
-  How does this sound?
Hyo Lyn, pack mosquito repellent, Baby.
- That's great.
-  You're good.
- He can do it so easily.
-  That sounds great.
Pack mosquito repellent, Baby.
Why don't you add piranha here?
- Pack mosquito repellent
-  Then Hyo Lyn becomes a piranha.
It sounds strange.
Kwang Soo, stay quiet. Just sing later.
- Just sing a verse and leave.
-  It's my first time.
- Pack mosquito repellent, Baby
-  I've never done it before.
- I don't know how the song goes.
-  "Mosquitoes there..."
"may get jealous of you". What if that comes next?
Those are the exact lyrics I hate.
- It's my personal opinion.
-  I get paid...
for writing lyrics.
- Gosh.
-  That wasn't very good.
- Shall we pick a theme?
-  Yes.
If we write lyrics with words that relate to food,
these will be easy to use.
Chogyeguksu.
A magical phrase to use when writing lyrics...
is "by the way".
Does it work every time?
You can say, "I love you, by the way, insect collection is..."
(That's right.)
- It works for everything.
-  This is it.
"I want to go to Hawaii. By the way, I'm craving chogyeguksu"?
Let's make the title of this song "By the Way".
That's a possibility.
We have to earn more points,
but it's hard because we need to use those words.
- When this season ends
-  When this season ends.
It doesn't fit the notes.
When the season ends, mosquitoes start to disappear,
- Baby
-  All right,
- that works.
-  I know.
- Just sing it a bit differently.
-  Disappear, Baby.
That's right.
It's Gimnyeong Seonsegi Beach.
- That's right.
-  We can also sing like this.
Gimnyeong Seonsegi Beach is great.
- Great, that works.
-  Make "Se" longer.
- Gimnyeong Seonsegi Beach is great
-  Let's do that.
-  No.
(Elongate the "Se", Jae Seok.)
How about this?
(I want it to be like this.)
- Yours sounds better.
-  Right?
I've never seen anyone fight over the notes.
- Let's move on.
-  We'll go back to that phrase.
For the "piranha", let's just say we cook and eat it...
after the beach part.
How about this?
Holding hands is too common of an expression.
Will you bite my hand once, piranha?
(How about this?)
(It is quite a scary song.)
Sometimes, you want to bite someone out of happiness.
- Right?
-  That sounds good.
When you love someone, you want to bite that person.
"Bite me like a piranha would."
I think that works.
(Team Singers are lost in too many food-related words.)
That's not it.
(Do I need to change it?)
Shall we change it to "let's be as passionate as Hawaii"?
We have to make it past tense.
I think the original is okay too.
Just use the original phrase.
Change it to "I like it because we are passionate, Baby".
- I like the first one better.
-  Okay.
- Let's start over.
-  It sounds more sophisticated.
Use the first one.
(It's a state of chaos.)
It's really difficult as we have so many singers.
Look at this.
- "The Battle of Flamingos".
-  Shall we shout out that one...
meaninglessly?
We can suddenly shout, "the Battle of Flamingos"!
It doesn't have to relate to the lyrics.
- It's to show our excitement.
-  That sounds fine.
How about this?
We say "hey" several times throughout the song.
It happens four times. So how about...
- Open the window
-  The.
- And shout
-  Battle.
- Then it's "open the window" again.
-  Of.
- And shout
-  Flamingos.
Wouldn't that be too sly?
- We'll be singing live.
-  This is just...
Throw it away.
(How will Team Non-singers change the lyrics?)
When they held hands, the hand smells like kongguksu.
- That's right.
-  It smells like kongguksu.
No, that doesn't work.
We should have a part that's funny.
Since it sounds too average,
- let's make it fun.
-  It should be fun.
Please give me a discount.
- That's awesome.
-  Isn't it great?
If you're going to be this late, you should give me a discount.
Gunmandu, mulmandu.
(What is that?)
- I knew he'd say that.
-  Did you?
- How about we do this?
-  No way.
(What kind of lyrics will Team Singers create?)
(It's time for the real competition.)
(Rehearsal on stage starts.)
Let's practise this part.
Let's try this at the end.
There are eight verses before that part.
(Is this the delivery dance to fit the food-related lyrics?)
In 1, 2, 3, 4.
(Team Non-singers make a cute and fresh dance to match the song.)
That's great.
It's better than the original.
The original song turned into a song about food.
It's unbelievable.
(Which team will win today?)
As you earned the Performance Order Card,
you may choose the order in which you'll go.
- Let's go last.
-  Wouldn't that be better?
It's better to watch them first.
- Yes.
-  All right.
- Team Non-singers will go first.
-  Okay.
Once the audience is seated,
you can start the performance.
(The evaluation group enters.)
We've invited a small audience to watch your performance.
They'll evaluate you fairly because...
they're students who study Literary Creation and Practical Music.
(There are even Practical Music students.)
No way.
(We're in trouble.)
- What?
-  They're music students.
(Students who major in music are ready to evaluate them.)
(This is their score card.)
(There are 4 criteria for today's evaluation.)
The seven judges have received the lyrics.
We'll also send them the video of your performances.
(The list of seven judges)
- Please go on stage.
-  Okay.
- Let's do a good job.
-  I'm nervous.
(Each half of the score comes from the audience and the 7 judges.)
Good luck. Competing isn't important.
I hope we all do a good job.
- You can do it.
-  Good luck.
Running Man's "Changing Lyrics Project" will start soon.
Please be seated.
- In 1, 2, 3, let's go.
-  Let's go.
Going last is better.
Team Non-singers will liven up the mood,
but we're the main singers.
("Highway Romance" is on standby.)
(Their hearts beat fast.)
Please welcome the first team.
(Finally, their song starts.)
- Hello, thank you for coming.
-  Hello.
(Who am I? Where am I?)
(3 late summer Running Man series.)
Game of Emperor's Throne.
(Running Man and Scarlet Heart Ryeo on August 28.)
Running Map, the ones who seek secrets of the map.
Train to Prison.
I think strange people appeared.
(Running Man and who else?)
(Game of Emperor's Throne, Running Map, Train to Prison)
(Finally, their song starts.)
- Hello, thank you for coming.
-  Hello.
(Who am I? Where am I?)
("Highway Romance" by Team Non-singers)
(It sings about Hyo Lyn's excitement as she heads to the ocean.)
They're dancing...
like this.
Hyo Lyn, pack mosquito repellent, Baby.
Baby.
When the season ends, mosquitoes start to disappear, Baby.
Will you bite my hand once, Piranha?
Piranha, piranha.
Is today real or just a dream?
Gimnyeong Seonsegi Beach is great.
Sizzling sun is great, too.
- Heatstroke
-  Heatstroke
I'm not afraid of it.
Where are we? Are we passing Seobinggo?
I feel like we're in the living room.
Go.
(The audience is evaluating objectively.)
A little faster.
(Let's get to the highlight.)
- Open the window
-  The.
- Goodness.
-  Open the window.
- Open the window
-  The.
- And shout
-  Battle.
We're going to the sea.
With a straw handbag and wearing off the shoulder tops.
We'll be back all tanned.
- Open the window
-  Of.
- And shout
-  Flamingos.
We love each other too much.
We lost our minds
I like travelling.
Summer dream.
(The original singer adds a lot of ad-lib.)
(He's doing a weird dance.)
One more time.
- Open the window
-  The.
- And shout
-  Battle.
We're going to the sea.
They're like a choir.
Let's...
do one movement at the same time.
They keep dancing.
- Open the window
-  Of.
- And shout
-  Flamingos.
We love each other too much.
We lost our minds
- I like travelling
-  One more time.
- Open the window
-  The Battle.
- And shout
-  Of Flamingos.
(They might as well open up a flamingo farm.)
(Their last shout)
(4 points for the content and the context)
Summer dream.
(They finish the song with a cute pose.
(They're satisfied.)
(Please give us a perfect score.)
Summer dream.
(Team Non-singers finishes performing.)
- Thank you.
-  Thank you.
Thank you.
I can't lift my face.
- What have we done?
-  We worked hard.
- Good job.
-  We worked very hard. Thank you.
- Gosh.
-  It's so embarrassing.
It's so embarrassing.
- It's so embarrassing.
-  Goodness.
It's much more embarrassing than I thought.
Why do I feel embarrassed when we did well?
They didn't laugh at all.
It's because they have to evaluate us.
- Shall we get off stage?
-  You have to do it.
It'll be better to get off stage.
- Shall we get off stage?
-  Do it when they clap.
(They add a little spice to their performance.)
This is quite organised.
We sang very well.
We sang well together.
(What's the score for Team Non-singers?)
Thank you for your support.
Please welcome the second team.
(They're very excited.)
(Bada appears.)
(She's the original idol.)
(She laughs.)
("Delivery Romance" by Team Singers)
It's so much fun.
(It sings about Bada who falls in love with a delivery boy.)
Isn't that too much?
That's too much.
I like that we're hot like Hawaii, Baby.
But I don't like your refrigerator pants, so bye.
(A man appears.)
- Will you hold my hand, Baby?
-  Baby.
We've been really waiting for this trip to Busan
I like chogyeguksu and also watermelon salad
I'd like to eat anything with you.
Is kongguksu here yet? Please be quick like a water gun
I won't forgive you if you're late.
What a quick delivery it is
I love you.
Can you hear my heart bouncing like a peanut boat?
As if you're doing an insect collection.
Please catch and trap me I love you so much.
Don't forget your helmet.
Bada, let's go!
- Let's go.
-  Look at the sea!
Bada, get on.
Here comes our motorcycle.
(He has transformed into a motorcycle.)
Let's go!
That wasn't in their original plan.
They just thought of it. There wasn't anything like that.
(They're near the climax of the song.)
Please catch and trap me.
(Amazing chorus by Bada)
I love you so much.
My goodness.
Bada is really good.
(They join the audience for a strong finish.)
They went down the stage.
(They try to "catch and trap" their audience's attention.)
Clap!
(We're definitely ahead in stage performance.)
Don't forget your helmet.
(The song finally ends.)
Thank you.
- I'm so happy, Bada.
-  Yeah.
Well done.
That was a neat finish.
There was something that was unscripted.
- Yes?
-  It was sudden.
- What do you mean?
-  You can be honest with us.
- Bada got on Jong Kook's back.
-  That wasn't planned, was it?
Everything went as we had planned.
We have different strengths.
Your performance was very plain and typical.
It was about harmony.
Ours was more of a free-style.
What happened to your lyrics?
We have all the words...
- and proverb in our lyrics.
-  We do, too.
"Hyo Lyn, don't forget to take the mosquito repellent, Baby."
"When the season ends, mosquitoes start to disappear."
- That's how you did it.
-  Can you see?
Look at how we put "Baby" at the end of the proverb.
It makes the lyrics sound a lot less typical and boring.
"Can you bite my hand once, Piranha?" Does this make sense?
- It makes sense.
-  How could it?
- "Find out whether we're..."
-  It makes sense, right?
You're asking the piranha to see if...
- you're dreaming or not?
-  That's right.
It will cost your finger at least.
"Be quick like a water gun. I won't forgive you if you're late."
Why is a water gun fast?
- It is fast.
-  It shoots water very quickly.
- It's slow. I can see the water.
-  Are you sure?
I can even dodge it.
You were talking about a trip and now, it's about a delivery man.
Look. The girl went to Busan for a trip and met that man there.
- She met a delivery man in Busan?
-  That's right.
Then there should've been Busan dialect.
I love it because it's hot like Hawaii.
- Like this.
-  No way.
That's what Jong Kook did.
He said it like this to mimic the dialect.
- That's from Jeolla-do.
-  That's a different dialect.
- But our opinions don't matter.
-  You're right.
(The audience's scores are what matters.)
(They begin their evaluation.)
(They have finished evaluating.)
(The 7 judges have finished their evaluations, too.)
Everyone, we have your scores.
I guess our scores must be really good.
You could get the maximum of 100 points from the students...
and another 100 points from the 7 judges.
So in total, you could get 200 points in total.
- I'll tell you the final scores.
-  Okay.
What are our scores?
(What's the difference between their scores?)
You got 140.1 points and 142.7 points.
- Really?
-  It's really close.
- Is it 142.7?
-  It is so close.
- What were the scores again?
-  The difference is only 2.6 points.
- Only 2.6 points?
-  That's it?
- No way.
-  Are you sure?
- So which team won?
-  I have no idea.
I really don't have any idea.
The lyrics from "Delivery Romance"...
are so closely linked together.
What a quick delivery it is
I love you.
"As if you're doing an insect collection"...
"Please catch and trap me". This part...
is really catchy.
I think it will stay in my head...
and make me hum.
- That's good.
-  That was a good evaluation.
I knew I could count on her.
The lyrics of "Beltway Romance"...
are not really...
connected.
They are somewhat simple, too.
Also, the sentences sound quite unnatural.
When the season ends, mosquitoes start to disappear.
Can you bite my hand once, Piranha?
I'm sorry to say this,
but I have no idea what they were trying to say with your lyrics.
I'm sorry.
That was really harsh.
- Disjointed and simple.
-  That's harsh.
"Beltway Romance"...
successfully created a big image with their lyrics.
It was a big harmony.
I knew I could count on him.
"Delivery Romance" did well,
(He compliments "Delivery Romance" as well.)
but their lyrics were disorderly.
- It was a disorder.
-  He loves that team.
Only Bada did a great job.
- That's true.
-  I guess he didn't hear our rhyme.
"Bye, bye, Baby".
You can go tell him.
We love another Jin Mo, Joo Jin Mo. Not him.
There's a talented person in "Beltway Romance".
- "The Battle of Flamingos" was...
-  It's because she knows Jong Shin.
A really difficult phrase to insert in their lyrics,
but they separated the phrase in many words and inserted them in.
- That was really smart.
-  She's so good.
- Nicely done.
-  We deserve points with that one.
Kim Ea Na is so good.
"Delivery Romance"...
seems lost with their lyrics.
When people who never wrote lyrics before...
are asked to write or change lyrics.
Many words are placed randomly.
Can I take out some points from them?
I can't?
Does she not know what "diversity" is?
I'm going to review every single song she ever wrote.
I will find every single mistake and post them on the internet.
- The webtoon artist, Jo Seok.
-  Yes. Jo Seok.
For performance scores,
he said that he's a big fan of Kim Kyung Ho.
(Jo Seok is a fan of Kim Kyung Ho.)
He said that he had to give the perfect score for performance.
The perfect score?
You should've kept dancing.
- Thank you.
-  He stopped in the middle of it.
- Yes, he stopped.
-  It's so unexpected.
About "Delivery Romance",
he questioned why the narrator suddenly...
went out for an insect collection while waiting for delivery.
Does he not know metaphors?
- What's wrong with him?
-  Does he really not know?
But he was okay about being bitten by a piranha?
- Was it okay?
-  I guess so.
That person lost his finger.
Park Bo Young evaluated very carefully and precisely.
She said it was unfair for the original songwriter to participate.
- That's right.
-  It's unfair.
- He shouldn't help.
-  Of course not.
You'll realise that it's not unfair at all if you come and work with us.
- That's right.
-  I had no idea.
He didn't help us at all.
Seriously. We were handicapped.
Announcer Bae Sung Jae mentioned that...
- Yes.
-  Announcer Bae Sung Jae.
He said "Beltway Romance's" lyrics had an impressive introduction,
but later parts were almost the same as the original song.
It was like an anticlimax.
How could he say that?
That is harsh.
Yes. Their song sounded almost the same.
They didn't change the lyrics.
Sung Jae. Don't be nosy and focus on your work.
Your commentaries were anticlimax.
Your brother is a lot better than you. He's a great actor.
About "Delivery Romance", he said the lyrics were...
closely related and that the words...
were catchy and well-placed.
- Bae Sung Jae.
-  Bae Sung Jae.
- He's good.
-  I knew we could count on him.
He knows something about lyrics.
- He's sensible.
-  He's the best commentator.
- Bae Sung Jae is so good.
-  He surely knows the trend.
He's amazing.
In total, it's 140.1 points versus 142.7 points.
- I have no idea about the winner.
-  I have no clue.
So...
(What is the outcome?)
The team that scored 142.7 points is...
(Which team was it?)
(Which team has won the game?)
Team Singers.
(Team Singers wins.)
(Team Singers wins by 2.6 points.)
- Yes.
-  That was so close.
- We won the audience over.
-  Yes, that's right.
- We won them over.
-  We did it.
- We performed well on stage.
-  Well done, Jong Kook.
- Bada did an amazing job.
-  No. I didn't.
- It was because they went last.
-  You're right.
We lost almost all the games today.
Here are two Special Badges...
and four Golden Musical Badges.
(The winning team receives the Badges.)
- Well done.
-  Good job.
- Thank you.
-  Thank you.
(We'd like to thank all the guests.)
(Next week's special is...)
(Running Women.)
Are you here to ruin Running Man?
They're toying with us. It's hopeless.
(The men are intimidated.)
Just stop it.
I will make you a hero today.
Take that!
(Are you ready to meet these women?)
Did I do well?
Jong Kook.
(Running Women)
(3 late summer Running Man series)
Game of Emperor's Throne.
Running Map.
Train to Prison.
(The Train to Prison)
(3 late summer Running Man series)