(Running Man in Dubai)
(Last week's episode)
Everyone, welcome to our individual travelling in Dubai.
(Welcome to Individual Travelling in Dubai.)
This is Dubai.
(Advanced city)
It's amazing here.
This is why people talk highly of Dubai.
Ji Hyo, this is so nice!
- Isn't this so nice?
- It's really nice.
This is freedom.
I love this kind of individual travelling.
(Running Man is in love with Dubai.)
Help me! Mum!
(The challenge)
(It was like they were having a perfect day in Dubai.)
This is the real desert.
(But of course, Running Man never gives them complete freedom.)
This is dangerous.
Some of you will sleeping outdoors in the desert.
(A battle of the members not to sleep outside)
That's insane.
That's so mean.
Wait. Not all four of us can survive.
Make sure you don't stray far.
You might die.
(The legend of the desert finally awakens today.)
Run!
"The Legend of Golden Grasshopper".
(The dangerous race in Dubai)
It's dangerous.
(Stake your all to win the dangerous race in Dubai!)
- Unfold it first.
- Do we just set it up here?
- This place looks nice.
- Have you ever put up a tent?
I have.
- We only have one.
- Is this enough space?
- Put it in there.
- This is large enough for us all.
- Is it?
- Yes.
The door should be...
It should face the opposite direction to the wind.
- Where is the wind coming from?
- It's blowing in this direction.
- Then we should turn it around.
- It should be this way.
- Should we turn it around?
- Yes.
Have you ever been in a situation like this?
- You might die.
- There might be animals.
Will there be snakes?
That kind is only found in North America.
- You're an expert.
- He knows a lot!
He's like someone from the "Discovery Channel".
I'm an expert at survival tactics. You should trust me.
- Our leader...
- Yes.
is a desert expert.
- You see?
- I feel safer with you.
- I feel reassured.
- Should I put it in like this?
Wait. We should zip the tent.
Otherwise, the sand will go in.
- Wow.
- You're amazing.
Leader.
- Yes.
- You're so experienced.
Who is the desert fox?
- It's Yu Jae Seok.
(Leader Jae Seok is the desert fox.)
(Seok Jin feels jealous because he wants to lead as the oldest here.)
(He wants to show off his leadership.)
What about here?
- We should put it there, too.
- As we are four,
each of us should work on each corner.
- You should take that out.
- I have one here.
Hold it tightly.
Why are you standing by?
(Jae Seok questions Seok Jin.)
(He squats down immediately.)
- It should go in here.
- It's done.
Let's see.
It fell off again.
- Did it?
- I'm not sure.
- It's too high.
- It's done.
Isn't this too high?
(What?)
(The tent is up in the air.)
What happened?
- He put up the tent in the air.
- My gosh.
- Gosh.
- Get out of the way.
- I did my best.
This part has fallen off.
Then put it back in yourself.
(Embarrassed)
Now, put sand over the edges.
- So that it won't get blown away?
- Exactly.
Have you ever lived in a desert?
It's nothing.
You sound very reassuring.
You sound professional.
It's done. It looks quite okay.
Normally, you're supposed to dig out ditches.
- Let's applaud.
- For what?
We've made the place to sleep for tonight.
- It's complete.
- We have to make one more of it.
(They still prefer to stay at the hotel.)
I am so happy.
It smells so delicious.
(These five are enjoying their luxurious dinner at the hotel.)
- It is good.
- Right?
It is really delicious.
- I think I was too greedy.
- How is it?
- It tastes good.
- This is tasty.
- I didn't expect it to be.
- It's so delicious.
I think we're eating six servings each.
Let's make sure we eat enough.
- We should.
- Right.
- We're having a lamb party.
Try this. Just try one.
- It's really good.
- Why are you being so nice?
- I regret for what I did.
- What do you take me for?
(They had to compete for a chance to sleep at the hotel.)
(Gary ruthlessly defeated Ji Hyo.)
- I made it!
- That's not gentle.
- I'll spend tomorrow just for you.
- He's feeling guilty.
No, thanks.
- You'll see tomorrow.
- No, I won't.
I'm swearing by the full moon.
I feel like if I make a wish by the full moon here, it will come true.
We must always keep the fire alive in the desert.
Fine, stop it now.
Just put them in.
- You're driving me crazy.
- Just put them in.
You haven't been here before either. Why do you speak like a native?
- Gosh.
- We all know you're not a local.
- We know you live in Apgujeong.
- I just...
Why do you act as if you're a desert expert?
I have slept in the desert before.
- What are you talking about?
- Sorry?
You must be lucky to be with me in the desert.
This ramyeon looks so good.
- Wow, we eat ramyeon in the desert.
- It's desert ramyeon, then.
I'll give you some.
(It looks delicious.)
It would have been better if we had an egg too.
(Slurping)
(Chomping)
- It is really good.
- I can't help but keep eating.
(They won't be able to eat ramyeon in desert again.)
It is very delicious.
Having ramyeon in the desert really invigorates us.
Yes, ramyeon in the desert is way too good.
I am so happy.
- I don't envy those at the hotel.
- Right, I don't either.
- I think I chewed some sand.
- No, there's no sand in here.
(They're spending a romantic night in the desert.)
- I'll close it.
- Here it is.
- Take this out.
- Okay.
There's the blanket.
(They look after Seok Jin and Jae Seok's tent first.)
- Thank you, Kwang Soo.
- You're welcome.
- Good night.
- You, too. You had a long day.
(Kwang Soo and Haha get ready to sleep after them.)
(Kwang Soo is brushing sand off his tent.)
Be quiet.
You're so mean.
(Seok Jin doesn't care about others as long as he's ready to sleep.)
You know who Seok Jin is.
I didn't know he was that mean.
You must be very tired.
(You must be very tired.)
- Good night.
- Be quiet!
(Seok Jin wants them to be quiet.)
(What a prankster!)
Good night.
I can't believe that I'm sleeping in the middle of desert.
(It's too surreal for him.)
(They try to fall asleep in the dark and silent desert.)
(Someone is snoring.)
(It is Seok Jin who's breaking the silence.)
(Jae Seok can't sleep because of Seok Jin.)
(Tapping)
(Seok Jin becomes quiet for a while,)
(but he starts to snore again.)
(Kwang Soo and Haha...)
(are tossing and turning, finding it hard to fall asleep.)
(Seok Jin's snoring is so loud that the other members can't sleep.)
It is so cold.
What should I do? It is too cold here.
(Haha wakes up and finds it very cold.)
(It's a sleepless night for them because of the noise and the cold.)
It's so cold.
(This strange place is so hot during the day and cold during the night.)
Gosh, it is so cold.
It is way too cold.
(Haha puts the camera back in its place.)
I don't know what time it is now,
but Kwang Soo and I woke up because it's too cold here.
(It's too cold for them to sleep.)
(Will he find a way to fight the cold?)
I'll go back to sleep because I'm too tired.
(Now I bet you envy the members sleeping at the hotel.)
(Jong Kook is in deep sleep.)
(The best place to sleep)
(Even Gary looks handsome sleeping in the hotel.)
(Is Haha really not jealous of sleeping in the hotel?)
(The worst place for deep sleep with never-ending snoring of Seok Jin)
(Tapping again)
(Seok Jin becomes silent.)
(Jae Seok is relieved.)
(What is this sound?)
(It's Seok Jin's fart bomb.)
(He keeps farting.)
(What is waiting for them now?)
(They must be ready for anything after this.)
(The starry night in the desert...)
(is finally over.)
(The beautiful sun rises...)
(as it brightens the dark desert.)
(There might be peace again in the desert...)
(where they suffered overnight.)
(Jae Seok opens his eyes.)
(He is relieved to find himself alive.)
(Haha and Kwang Soo)
(Jae Seok walks out of the tent.)
- Is Seok Jin still in sleep?
- Sorry?
Is Seok Jin still in sleep?
(Is Seok Jin still sleeping?)
Seok Jin snored heavily overnight.
Gosh.
(He's still half asleep.)
Hey, Seok Jin.
Wasn't it cold?
It was so cold,
but there was nothing I could do.
Jae Seok.
- I figured it out, though.
- How?
I farted, and it warmed my body.
Seriously.
You snored too heavily.
I don't snore.
You should check the recorded video.
Check it out.
You drove me crazy. I thought I was sleeping with an animal.
(Animal Seok Jin)
(They are still tired.)
- Well, let's...
- Sorry?
- What?
- What are you talking about?
(I haven't even washed my face.)
- I was going to go to the restroom.
- I just got up.
- We can't start anything now.
- My bad. Go ahead.
- What do you think you're doing?
- I just...
You should at least give us some time.
- There are items in the box.
- What?
Us these items...
(They have to make use of the items in the box.)
(We just woke up,)
(and they're starting the mission right away.)
(What will they be using to clear the morning mission?)
(At the same time)
(The same box is provided to the members slept in the hotel.)
(What is that box for?)
Good morning.
You have to use the items in the box from now on.
(You have to use the items in the box from now on.)
You have to take morning photo-shoots.
(You have to take morning photo-shoots.)
(Take photos and bring them to me.)
You can decide wherever to have photo-shoot.
Choose the best one, and give it to us.
Your photo will be competing with others', and you will be given...
different qualities of breakfast depending on the result.
You may go ahead and start having your photo-shoot...
with one of our cameramen.
(They only get 15 chances to press the shutter.)
(He checks the items inside the box.)
I'll take this.
(He takes the sunglasses to cover his puffy eyes.)
I didn't expect it to be so real.
Let's see.
(What is his next item?)
(He takes a kettle out.)
(He takes a small stool, too.)
What are these for?
Please take beautiful pictures.
With this kettle?
(He will be having a photo-shoot in the desert with daily necessities.)
- The local drivers...
- Yes.
will vote for the best photo.
You'll be given different kinds of breakfast depending on the results.
Can't you just give us for nothing?
Please don't do this.
- Why do you have to...
- Take a look inside the box.
(What are the items in the box?)
This is just too much.
(Scarves, hula hoop and sunglasses)
What is this?
(Nothing useful is in the box.)
I heard Kwang Soo complaining about the cold last night.
Isn't this his head?
(He found Kwang Soo's head.)
(He has such a bad sleeping habit.)
I think this is his head.
(They pat Kwang Soo on his head.)
I couldn't sleep at all. It was too cold.
We couldn't close the tent completely.
All the cameras fell over.
- Film inside the tent.
- It was way too cold.
I feel bad for them.
(What a disastrous footage it is!)
- You can sleep a bit more.
- Right.
Yes, sleep more.
- Old man.
- Did you call me old man?
You snore too much.
Me? Snore?
- You have a big nose for a reason.
- Don't lie to me.
My wife told me...
that I sleep like a baby.
- That's not true.
- She told me that.
- You don't sleep with her, do you?
- Like this.
(Shaking)
If you're going to laugh, just wake up already.
(If you're going to laugh, just wake up already.)
He says he sleeps like a baby.
- He snored so much.
- Right?
- Really?
- Yes, it's really bad.
- What happened with your nose?
- My nose?
Seriously.
- You two are so weak.
- Right.
(While they are talking about what happened overnight,)
I'm going to have a cool photo-shoot first.
(The Thinker)
(Pressing)
(Wobbling)
(He shakes as if he's dancing.)
(It's hard to understand the art of photography.)
(Snacks for the Desert)
I'm going to roll down from here.
- Take a photo of me doing it.
- Okay.
(Il Woo plans to take active photo-shoots.)
(Here I go.)
(Rolling down)
(He imagines himself to be like...)
(a real hero in an action movie.)
(It is going to be a masterpiece.)
I'll stop here.
(He's sure of himself to be depicted as a tough guy in the photo.)
(He's satisfied.)
I just can't stop myself from being cool.
(But the result isn't cool at all.)
Choose your best photo-shoot.
Do I choose one now?
Do you have any computer programme to edit photos?
(Do you have any computer programme to edit photos?)
(He's not confident of the result.)
This one is good. He is such a good photographer.
No one would notice that I took it right after waking up.
(No one would notice that I took it right after waking up.)
There are so many good ones that it's hard to choose.
(I'm so perfect in my eyes.)
I'll choose the one with the kettle.
(I'll choose the one with the kettle.)
(Snacks for the Desert is chosen to be his best photo-shoot.)
It's going to be like I'm drinking the sun.
(Jong Kook is trying to express a lion devouring the sun.)
It should be like the sun is seeping out from the kettle's spout.
It should be like I'm drinking the sun.
Did you get that?
(Drinking the Sun)
This is good.
I should leave more room between me and the kettle.
It's too close, right?
It has to look like the sun is coming out from it.
There should be enough space in-between.
It would be nice for my face to show up.
(Nervous)
(Reversed version of Drinking the Sun)
(Final version of Drinking the Sun)
This is perfect.
I'd like to try various photo-shoots other than that.
I want to ask you a personal favour.
I saw that in some of the photos,
the sun is shown much smaller than...
it is shown in the other pictures.
Could you do that again?
Is it possible? I think you change the exposure a bit.
You already used your 15 chances.
(It is right to refuse bad customer's request.)
Wait a second.
I want the image of the sun to be more solid and smaller.
But what's shown in the photo is too spread out.
I have a strong feeling to win this competition.
It's just incredible.
I...
(Kwang Soo starts to plan for his photo-shoot mission.)
Do you see the horizon in the desert?
It's so still and silent.
I'll stand there alone in solidarity...
while doing hula hoops.
(He will do hula hoops on a calm desert in solidarity.)
I want to express a feeling of loneliness.
It's going to be like a fight with myself.
That's out of nowhere.
In this vast desert,
the only friend I have is this hula hoop.
He's no wonder a dumb.
(He aims it to be sad, but it's funny.)
- Kwang Soo?
- Yes.
It's called, Sorrowful Hula Hoop.
(Sorrowful Hula Hoop)
(Haha is trying to express his thirst in the desert.)
Focus on my desperate hand.
(Focus on my desperate hand.)
(I Have an Empty Water Bottle)
This will work out well.
(He expresses his gullible self through the flapping scarf.)
That looks the best so far.
(My Gullible Self)
I'll express the first footprints in the desert.
I want something like "Lawrence of Arabia".
(His footprints leave marks on a clean desert.)
(Sinking)
- Wait.
- What are you doing?
- I don't see any of them.
- It's rather like "The Himalayas".
- This isn't what I imagined.
- You're not making any footprints.
Jae Seok, you just look like an old lady climbing Mount Bukhan.
Try to roll yourself down from the hill.
Listen, I'm going to run down here.
(He is about to be a free self.)
(Running)
(No one can stop me from running down.)
- I think it'll be nice.
- He's like a grasshopper.
(Falling)
- He really is a grasshopper.
- Seriously.
- You really are a grasshopper.
- Really!
(The Fast and Furious Grasshopper)
This one is great.
(They chose their best photos.)
(Next model is...)
That's amazing.
(It's Gary.)
Isn't my face too puffy?
(Next model is Gary.)
(He doesn't want himself to look ugly.)
Here is your morning mission.
Go over there.
Stand where the box is.
Did you see the animal footprints over there?
(Did you see the animal footprints over there?)
- They must have come overnight.
- Those are Jong Gook's.
It's Jong Gook's?
(Those are human's footprints?)
Those footprints weren't there yesterday.
(They look like animal's footprints.)
That's amazing.
I need to have at least one cool photo-shoot.
- I'll throw this in the air.
- Okay.
(Gary wants to show something Korean.)
(Side kick)
Korean traditional style.
(Taekwondo Spirit)
How can I express this as if I'm in an oasis?
(She's trying to use the pool unlike the others.)
Well... Here I go.
(Her mouth is wide open.)
It's like my thirst is relieved after finding an oasis.
(My Thirst for the Oasis)
Here I go.
(Ji Hyo wants to express running person in the desert.)
Did you take it?
It's like a desert runner in the morning.
(Desert Runner in the Morning)
(Rest of the members also selected their best shots.)
(What will be the result of this competition?)
- Well...
- There's a cat.
(Roaming)
We woke up at 7am.
Why are we having breakfast at 10am?
Isn't this supposed to be brunch?
It's a brunch in Dubai's desert.
Do you have seonji haejangguk?
No, we don't. We just closed the voting.
- Really?
- Participants for the voting...
were 12 locals in Dubai.
They voted for the best one, right?
Yes, the results are out.
- The person in the first place...
- Yes.
gets to have not only all the food here.
- What else?
- Okay.
- The winner also gets a cup noodle.
- Gosh!
(The winner gets to have all the dishes and a cup noodle.)
- I really want it.
- No kidding.
- This is crazy.
- The results are out.
(The second gets to have 3 dishes, the third 2 and the last 1.)
Show us.
- It's here.
- I'm sure they did it objectively.
(Who will be the winner among four members?)
(Which photo would you select as the best?)
- Yes, it's me!
- I knew it.
- Gosh, I'm in the second place.
- Goodness.
- Am I the winner?
- Don't lie.
Are you sure I'm in the third place?
Jae Seok, you can start having...
all of these breakfast dishes...
- while we boil the water for you.
- Okay.
- Open these for me.
Which one should I have?
- Is this edible too?
- Those...
The three of those make one dish.
- These?
- Yes.
I should eat that one.
- Which one?
- I get to have only eat dish.
- That one looks a lot.
- Seok Jin.
Move your body, and stop standing still.
I'm walking now, you jerk.
- These are those!
- Jujube.
- Jujube!
- It's called dates.
It's a speciality of Dubai.
- Is it good?
- Wait.
(Dates are a common ingredient in the Middle East.)
- I've seen them at the stores.
- Gosh, It's cold.
It's delicious.
Is it? Let me try.
(I want to try.)
You can give me one.
- This is...
- I'll have that one then.
(He chooses the dates as his dish.)
I'll have that.
- This?
- Hey, you. I'm having that one.
What did you say?
I'm the leader here.
- I mean...
- Gosh!
- This is good.
- I made up my mind.
- Which one?
- This one.
- The dates?
- Go eat them over there.
Why?
Go to the end of the table.
Why? I want to sit here.
Sit over there.
The shade is for us.
I didn't know we have our own seats.
You knew that. You knew.
(He pretended not to know about it.)
Who wants one?
Let's trade.
Anyone want to trade?
Answer him, anyone.
(Answer him, anyone.)
Kwon Ryeol, answer him.
- Who is he talking to?
- Talk to him.
Kwon Ryeol,
you should be his talking buddy.
Desert is a lonely place.
He might die.
(Your attention might be able to save Seok Jin.)
I told you I'm an expert at survival tactics.
Can you accidentally spill two pieces here?
(Can you accidentally spill two pieces here?)
- That bread over there.
- It's good.
- Give me one.
- No, I don't want to.
(No, I don't want to.)
(It didn't work.)
I never knew a whisper could sound so cold.
- He asked for something I can't do.
- Enjoy, Kwang Soo.
You all had your photo-shoots.
- Yes.
- Now, let me announce you...
the result of this competition.
- The first place received 10 votes.
- Really?
The last place didn't get any.
- Nothing?
- Not a single vote?
- Really?
- Are you sure?
The last didn't even get a vote.
(Jong Kook and Il Woo are the only two left.)
- The first place goes to...
- Yes.
The first place with 10 votes goes to...
(Is it Jong Kook?)
I'm nervous.
(Or is it Il Woo?)
It's Jong Kook.
(Jong Kook wins the first place.)
(Oh no, I lost.)
Il Woo, you lost.
- Il Woo.
- I knew it!
- You got none.
- I knew it.
People know what art is.
They understood my work.
You will be given different sizes of plates.
- We get different plates.
- The plate sizes are different.
(They get to enjoy the hotel breakfast with their plates.)
What should I eat?
There's so much to choose from.
(Jong Kook is relaxed with his large plate.)
This is amazing.
I'm going to stack it up as high as possible.
(Gary is frugal with filling his plate.)
Right, melon is delicious.
(Ji Hyo only takes the most delicious ones.)
(And)
(Il Woo is performing a circus with his plate.)
(Laughing)
I feel like I'm playing Jenga now.
My goodness.
(I'll be sure to show them something next time.)
I can smell it.
- Only the winner gets that noodle.
- Gosh.
You look sexy with the moustache.
(You look sexy with the moustache.)
(That's nice of you to say.)
(Slurping)
(The power of compliments)
Your moustache grows like...
that of a European man.
(Pass)
I feel so much better.
Since when were you so masculine?
Look at your arms.
(Since when were you so masculine? Look at your arms.)
You look sexy, Jae Seok.
(Whatever)
Kwon Ryeol, answer back.
(Kwon Ryeol, answer back.)
Can I taste a sip of the soup?
(Can I taste a sip of the soup?)
What?
- Are you talking to yourself?
- Wait.
- Am I...
- hearing things?
- I know.
- It's so hot.
- What is going on?
Yes, you're hearing things.
(Seok Jin, are you ill from the heat?)
(The hot sun is beating down nonstop.)
(Gosh, when will they come?)
- Isn't it just too hot?
- It's seriously...
(What is that?)
The lucky ones are coming.
- They're so far away.
- They will definitely laugh at us.
They'll ask if we slept here, and we'll say of course.
- They're here. They look so clean.
- Look at them.
They're from the city.
Look at them.
- Really.
- The celebrities are coming.
- It's the stars.
- They look so clean.
- Really.
- Are you all right?
- They look so lively.
- Look.
- Do you think we're all right?
- You lively people.
- They dressed up for the desert.
Are you here for a photo?
- I'm sorry.
- Are you here for a photo?
- Hello.
- Are you all right?
Gary, did you sleep with us last night?
- Why didn't you dress up?
- No.
I did. Doesn't it show?
(He is a very modest man.)
- It is very cool under here.
- You guys smell so nice.
It's very cool in the shade.
- What?
- Why that little...
- What should I do about him?
- Why don't you stay the night here?
It's nice here.
- Stay here then.
- No, it's fine.
I thought my back was going to snap.
Because I curled up my body while sleeping.
It was too cold.
Why didn't you turn the heater on before you went to sleep?
- Where?
- That little...
- Hey, you!
- Where is the heater here?
I really wish I was good at fighting.
My goodness.
- What are we going to do now?
- You must have had a tough night.
- Oh, my.
- What is this?
It's a mission.
- Look at them throwing things.
- Is this how they give missions?
- I was surprised, too.
- What is it?
"The Legend of the Golden Grasshopper"
Long time ago, the Golden Grasshopper was guarding Dubai.
(The legendary Golden Grasshopper?)
- I knew it.
- It's treasure hunting, right?
(Today's mission is to find the legendary treasure.)
"The Legend of the Golden Grasshopper".
("The Legend of the Golden Grasshopper")
Long time ago, the Golden Grasshopper was guarding Dubai.
But as the time passed by, the Golden Grasshopper became forgotten,
and it suddenly disappeared without a trace.
(It became forgotten and suddenly disappeared without a trace.)
Many went on the search for Golden Grasshopper...
and found that Golden Grasshopper had turned into stone.
(Many went on the search for the Golden Grasshopper around Dubai,)
(but they only found the Golden Grasshopper turned into a rock.)
(Hundreds of years passed by.)
(Hundreds of years passed by. And in the year 2016,)
(the nine members of Running Man starts to search for it.)
("Hourglass Race")
(The nine members...)
(share the hourglasses representing their lives.)
Let's go.
Be careful. He's too fast.
(They will be divided into three teams to scour Dubai.)
(It is their first time in seeing the real Dubai,)
(the mystical and secretive city.)
Isn't that it?
(There is the one thing that they should never forget.)
I'm alive.
This is confusing.
(They have to turn over the hourglass to keep themselves alive.)
Did you find it? What is that?
Seok Jin. Seok Jin.
- Take it off.
- You shouldn't do that.
- Catch him.
- It's dangerous.
(Who will restore the Golden Grasshopper back to life?)
(Before they go on the search, they will split up into teams.)
(The teams have been formed.)
(They will turn over the hourglass before they go on the search.)
- Okay.
- Yes.
- In 1, 2 and 3.
- And 3.
My life depends on this.
- You can't touch the others'.
- Okay.
We will play only one game.
We will play a three person kickball.
(Winner gets a second chance when their hourglass runs out of time.)
You first roll the ball from the blue spot.
And another person kicks the ball from the right over there.
The right side is the first base. The second base is on the left.
You get a point when you return to home.
- Oh, I see.
- I haven't played this in a while.
- Which team is doing the defence?
- Let's do this.
- We're offense.
- Okay.
Is that so?
(Gary is the first batter.)
- Let's go.
- Good luck.
(Il Woo is the starting pitcher.)
(He looks like an expert.)
- You're out if it's three strikes.
- Il Woo, show us breaking ball.
- Go, Gary.
- He is a fast runner.
Il Woo, you have a great posture.
- It's too close.
- It looks like...
(Stumbling)
Goodness, Il Woo.
- He's faking it.
- You look great.
(He concentrates again and throws the ball.)
(Come to me, ball.)
(Kicking)
(It struck perfectly.)
Over here.
(Il Woo caught it at once.)
- Wait.
- Over here.
(He throws to Seok Jin on first base.)
(Gary is running at full speed on bare foot.)
(There may be blue...)
(and better blue.)
Are you serious?
- Over here.
- Throw it.
(He throws it to the ground.)
- What was that?
- What are you doing?
- What is that?
- This was to get him out.
- What were you doing?
- You looked as if...
you were a professional kickball player.
- We had to get this one out.
- Gosh.
Kwang Soo.
(Maybe I'm ill from the heat of the desert.)
- Good luck.
- Yes.
(I'll make it this time.)
- Show us a breaking ball.
- Please.
- Wait.
- Strike.
(What?)
(Did he make a high-five with a ball?)
- Strike.
- Is that a strike?
Why are you doing this to me?
- Strike.
- Why are you doing this to me?
You shouldn't touch it.
- It's hot.
- Yellow card.
One strike.
I'll tell you.
- Okay.
- I'll tell you.
(I will kick you.)
One strike.
(The weather is hot, and he's angry.)
- It's two strikes.
- Il Woo!
Il Woo, it's two strikes.
- Strike him out.
- It's two strikes.
I've never seen a strike out in kickball games.
Wait a minute.
- I've never seen one.
- Wait.
He worries me.
If he misses it again,
(I will get you out.)
(I can't get out.)
There's no way of missing this.
(Will he kick it?)
(Kicking)
- Catch it.
- Stay there!
(The ball flew high up in the sky, and he catches it.)
- Okay.
- Great.
(Il Woo catches it.)
What's wrong with you?
It's all right.
I kicked with my left foot.
I hurt my pride.
One out.
- Let's not give them any point.
- Ji Hyo, I'll tell you.
- Okay.
- If I tell you to run, run.
(Gary and Kwang Soo are changing positions.)
Il Woo is doing great.
Il Woo is amazing.
(Gary kicks the ball.)
(The ball heads straight to Il Woo.)
(Will Gary be put out?)
(What?)
- Run!
- He missed it!
- Oh, no. Il Woo.
- Il Woo.
- Here.
- Ji Hyo, run.
Ji Hyo.
(Ji Hyo runs to the second base.)
(Jae Seok throws the ball to second base.)
(It is the ball versus Ji Hyo.)
- Ji Hyo is out.
- Safe.
(Jong Kook missed the ball, so she is safe.)
- It's safe.
- Oh, my.
- You had to get her out.
- You should have caught the ball.
It's safe.
You need to catch it.
Ji Hyo, you go.
Change. You kick.
- Should I kick?
- Yes. Kwang Soo come here.
Il Woo, you can't miss the ball again.
- Okay.
- I've never seen him like this.
- Do you want to be out of the game?
- Form a tight defence.
- Da Hey, focus
- Did they score one point?
- It's so hot here.
- Da Hey, come to the front.
Wait.
- Run.
- Get the ball.
- Oh, my.
- Here.
- Run.
- Catch it.
Okay.
(Slow)
- Catch it.
- Run.
- What are you doing?
- Quickly.
Run.
(Meanwhile, Ji Hyo has reached the second base.)
(She slides and touches the second base.)
- Gary.
- One point.
Two points.
It's not that he can't. It's just that he won't.
This is...
- Why did you throw it?
- I threw it, so you could catch it.
Why did you throw it?
- You should have caught it.
- Why did you throw it at me?
I thought if I don't catch it,
- the game pauses.
- This is like baseball.
- Wait.
- I got it.
I thought it was a stone but it was poop.
Poop is everywhere.
Why is there so much poop?
(The ground is covered with poop.)
I thought it was a stone but it was poop.
Are you sure it's not yours?
Mine doesn't look like this.
- Gosh.
- You said you're constipated.
(Please stop talking about poop.)
(It's sizzling hot in the desert,)
(but no one would give up the second chance.)
Gosh, this is...
(He kicks the ball.)
(Gary hit a home run.)
Run!
- Gosh.
- Run!
Gary was standing too close.
(They scored two additional points.)
(Team Kwang Soo has scored five points so far.)
It was a home run!
Il Woo, you let them score five points.
Four of them were by you.
We have only one out left.
(Ji Hyo is waiting to kick the ball.)
This might be a chance.
- Nice. Run!
- Run!
- Hurry!
- Throw the ball!
Hurry!
- Ji Hyo is out.
- Out.
Gosh.
Out.
Il Woo is no better than me.
(Team Kwang Soo has scored five points.)
He jumped just like me!
(Meanwhile, the sand in the hourglasses keep flowing down.)
Is it our turn?
I'll show you something amazing.
Throw it gently.
(Seok Jin pitches for the first time.)
- Gosh.
- Run to the first base!
Here!
(Haha...)
(made it to the first base in time.)
- Gosh.
- Stay there.
(Team Jong Kook is the dream team.)
Hey!
Look at him.
- Gosh.
- Why?
It's okay.
(They scored nine points quickly.)
(Seok Jin and Jae Seok switches positions.)
If they score one more point, it'll be over.
(When one team has 10 more points than the other,)
(the umpire can end the game.)
Gosh.
(Jae Seok throws the ball.)
Oh, my.
(Il Woo missed the ball.)
That was unbelievable.
(What just happened?)
As we're far behind,
I'll make it really difficult.
(Jae Seok is determined.)
(Flying)
- I'm sorry.
- What did he do?
Il Woo is terrible.
(Il Woo keeps making mistakes.)
(I'm not allowing you the second chance.)
(We'll make it a called game.)
(Aim for the target.)
- Three strikes.
- Out.
(Il Woo missed the ball again.)
- Three strikes.
- I didn't know it's possible.
Il Woo.
You should go on the Guinness World Records.
Get in touch with them.
Three strikes.
We'll remember it even if you win.
Even if your team beats us 100 to 0,
we'll never forget this.
I feel sorry for him.
(Sadly, that's true.)
(Team Haha has 9 points with 1 out.)
- No, don't.
- Gosh.
I said, don't.
- To the first base!
To the first base!
Seok Jin!
(Because of Seok Jin, Il Woo reached home.)
- Why didn't you catch the ball?
- Too bad.
(With Team Haha scoring 10 points, the game ended.)
What's the score?
It's 10 points.
We won.
Seok Jin let them score so much.
(Team Haha won the kickball.)
Team Haha gets two second chances.
Nice!
- Team Kwang Soo gets one.
- Nice!
- I didn't know we'd get one.
- Is this for us?
Team Jae Seok gets none.
- Okay.
- We didn't want it anyway.
(Team Jae Seok gets no second chance.)
- You get none.
- I'm sick of this.
- We're chased all the time.
- Send us somewhere else.
- I'm sick of this.
We were not expecting to get any second chance.
- Gosh.
- Let us go.
We don't want any second chance.
We're done with our tasks in the desert.
- Finally.
- Let's move.
We're finally leaving the desert.
(What will be waiting for them in their next destination?)
It's downtown.
It must be some kind of market.
I want to look around here.
We're here. Let's get off here.
- Okay.
- We should get off.
(Team Jae Seok arrived at the destination first.)
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
(We're happy as long as we're not in the desert.)
(Where are they?)
I have sand in my shoes.
(Souk is a traditional market divided in three sections.)
- This must be a traditional market.
- Wow.
(It consists of Gold Souk, Textile Souk and Spice Souk.
Do we have time for shopping?
- I guess we don't.
- We don't.
- I'm happy we're not in the desert.
- This place looks exciting.
- It's nice.
- I love markets.
Right?
Are we getting on a ferry?
Are we?
- It's a water taxi.
- Wow.
(Getting on a ferry makes them excited.)
Dubai is so nice.
This is so romantic. I want to come back here with my girlfriend.
It's so nice.
(They're happy to be on the water...)
(instead of in a desert.)
It's nice.
Isn't that a bus?
(Is this a recycled bus?)
It has wheels.
- What if it sinks?
- I wish I could take pictures.
Is that really a bus?
That ferry looks amazing.
(A buffet ferry)
It has a buffet in it.
Look at that. I wish I could take pictures.
(After a pleasant ferry ride,)
(they arrived at their next destination.)
Is that a fishing boat?
That boat is so tall.
(What mission will be waiting for them here?)
- What could this be?
- It looks like a fishing boat.
(They arrived at an exotic dock.)
They've been waiting for us.
What is this?
Please open the parchment and read it.
And put down your hourglasses on the carpet.
Let's read the mission first.
After leaving the desolate desert, they arrived...
at a market where people sell gold, spices and textiles.
When they split up into three groups and found the hidden answers,
another legend regarding the stoned grasshopper revealed.
- Finally.
- Escape from the desert.
You arrived...
at Souk, the traditional market in Dubai.
- I see.
- Souk?
The markets are on the both sides of the river.
Three people from each group...
will look for the answer in each market.
When all three members have found the answers, the team can leave.
You cannot leave this place until all members are finished.
- Decide who will go to which.
- I want to go to the gold market.
- Where should I go?
I'd like to...
- I'll go to the gold market.
- I want to go there.
- Let me go to the gold market.
- I'll go.
I'll go to the gold market.
Jong Kook is going to the gold market.
(Is that so?)
- I'll go to the spice market.
- Let me go there.
(Avoiding Jong Kook is his priority.)
- I want to go to the spice market.
- I'll go there.
- You wanted the gold market.
- Just go to the gold market.
- I'm disappointed in you.
- I...
Let me go to the spice market.
- I'll go to the spice market.
- Okay.
The ones going to the gold market, please step forward.
- The gold market.
You should see the gold from Dubai.
We should see the gold from Dubai.
- I'm worried.
- Each has a different question.
Please read yours starting from Jong Kook.
- Do we have different questions?
- Yes.
Are they different?
"A leaf with glowing-red veins...
climbs up the wrist and meets another."
- What does this mean?
- Are we supposed to find this?
Mine seems easy.
"A necklace with two peacocks under a bloomed lotus."
- That's easy.
- This one is easy.
He should look for a necklace that looks like peacocks.
"A necklace that has one great moon with five jewels..."
"and nine moons with three jewels."
- That sounds hard.
- Five of what?
One great moon with five jewels.
Isn't that squid?
I think your answer is squid.
- Find a squid-looking necklace.
- Please change it to six.
Squids have 12 legs
You're to take a picture of the described item.
- Take a picture?
- Okay.
You should finish before all the sand flows out.
Then should we go back and forth?
You can head to the gold market right now.
- Okay.
- Where is it?
Let's hurry.
Is it far from here?
Really? What should I do with the hourglass?
Then should I go back and turn the hourglass around?
(They're worried about their hourglasses.)
Look at that.
(Wow! It's gold everywhere!)
This is amazing.
So this is the gold market.
There's so much gold.
Look at all these.
It must be here.
Oh, it's here.
(What does the gold market in Dubai look like?)
There's gold everywhere.
Wait.
There are so many golden items. I don't know where to start.
(Gold Souk is the biggest gold market in the Middle East,)
(and 10 percent of gold transactions in the world take place in here.)
Look at this.
This is unbelievable.
How much would that cost?
Look at this golden football shoe.
This is amazing.
(A golden shoe and a golden ball)
Look at this.
(You can find everything in gold.)
(Bling-bling)
Look at this. It reminds me of Cleopatra.
It's amazing.
How could anyone wear this around?
I feel like I'm mesmerised.
(They're mesmerised by gold.)
I can't think of anything.
I want to buy them.
- Textile Souk is across the river.
- Textile Souk.
- Oh, my.
- Really?
- Kwang Soo, sorry.
- Find the answer there.
We'll tell you names of the stores and items you should buy.
- Buy it with the money we gave you.
- We have to go buy it.
We'll tell you just once, so listen carefully.
- I'm not good at this.
- The names of the owners and items.
- We're starting from you, Da Hey.
- Okay.
"Buy Pel Bunapssaji from...
Assan Amin's store."
("Buy Pel Bunapssaji from Assan Amin's store.")
Assan Amel?
Phen Bunapssaje?
An...
- Da Hey.
- Assam Anel and Phen Bunapssaje?
It's Assan Abel's store.
Gosh! I am so confused.
It's Assan Amel and Phe...
Phe bunapssaje.
"Buy Warud Tattris...
from Parkashu Mulani's store."
("Buy Warud Tattris from Parkashy Mulani's store.")
- Let's go.
- Warussa...
- Phen Bunapssaje?
- Was it Parkashua?
Parkshua Tamil.
- Parkshua Tamil.
"Buy Nal Asuwad...
from Kakairela's store."
- Kakailla and Nal Asuwal.
- Way to Go! Il Woo.
- Go!
- Nal Assuwal?
- Nal Asuward.
- Kakaila.
It's Assan Abel and Pel Bunapssaje.
(They're repeating the words to memorise them.)
Nal Assuward. Nal Assuward.
(He continues to memorise the word.)
Nal Assuward.
(He concentrates on memorising the Arabic words.)
Gosh, I forgot to flip my hourglass.
- What?
- I forgot to turn it around.
You have to come back again then.
(There's not much sand left to go down in Kwang Soo's hourglass)
(He has to complete his mission as soon as possible.)
What do you have to buy, Il Woo?
(He looks at something.)
- Assan Abel...
- I should go to Parshadame's store.
- Wait. He wrote it down.
- Warud...
He wrote it down by using his sunglasses and nails.
- No, I didn't.
- He wrote it down with his nails.
(Before taking the abra ride)
Warkaradame.
(Il Woo writes it down to regain his honour.)
What was that?
It's cheating!
- I didn't write it down.
- He wrote it down with his nails.
No way.
(Kwang Soo scratches Il Woo's envelope with his nails.)
Let's switch our envelopes.
- Come on!
- Kakarela. Kakarela.
- Kakarela.
- Isn't it cheating?
He unashamedly looked at it.
(Who will be able to buy the item first?)
- It's our turn now.
- Last one is Spice Souk.
We'll make each of you try different spices...
without actually seeing it.
- Are we tasting it?
- Yes.
(Spice number three)
Gosh.
Remember the taste and smell of the spice in your mouth...
- and buy it.
- Gosh!
(They're trying hard to taste the spice.)
(What is this?)
What's this?
(Oh my goodness!)
You can take off your eye patches and leave now.)
(Let's go to find the spices!)
We will give you money for this mission.
Buy just one gram of each spice.
- How many grams?
- Just one gram.
- That's the smallest amount...
- Gosh.
What is this taste?
(She's shocked by the taste.)
Where is the spice market?
How does it taste?
- It's sour.
- Is it sour?
It is too spicy.
It is so hot.
- Is it hot?
- It is very hot.
My spice tastes a bit weird.
- Gosh!
- It tastes strange.
(Jae Seok is experiencing the spiciness of Dubai.)
I don't think Jae Seok can go to the market. He's lost his control.
- Goodness.
- Is it that hot?
Does anybody have water to drink?
I need to buy a bottle of water first.
(Jae Seok buys a bottle of water to wash off the taste in his mouth.)
It's so hot.
I think this one is the one.
Hi, how are you?
What is that?
- It's chili, and it's very hot.
- Is it very hot?
(Is it very hot?)
What if this is spicy, too?
(Jae Seok is scared.)
It is very hot.
Okay. Wait a second.
This looks like the one I tasted.
(Jae Seok puts it into his mouth to verify its taste.)
It is too hot.
It is so spicy!
(What is this taste?)
This looks like the one I tasted.
Gosh! This is it!
(It is spicy.)
It is hot. It is hot.
(He purchases it right away.)
It is very hot. I think this is the one.
(He seems to be in pain.)
Oh, thank you so much.
(He gives Jae Seok water to relieve the spiciness.)
(Everyone in traditional markets around the world seems very nice.)
- Take this.
- This one?
(The owner impresses his customer by giving him sweet dates.)
This is so delicious.
He is very kind.
(The Dubaian merchant repeats after Jae Seok like a parrot.)
Can I have one gram of this?
One gram? Okay.
(Jae Seok buys the spice from the first store he visited.)
- Yes. Thank you very much.
- Thank you.
(Is this the one Jae Seok tasted earlier?)
See you next time. Thank you.
- Bye.
(Meanwhile, Ji Hyo walked pretty deep into the market.)
I'm looking for a spice.
(Ji Hyo doesn't have a clue so far.)
It's small, and something inside it popped when I chewed.
- Do you want to take a look?
- Yes.
When I chewed it, something popped inside my mouth.
(Spice Souk is a traditional market that sells a lot of exotic spices.)
I can smell all the spices.
(She's enjoying the smell.)
What is this? Oh, it's black pepper.
- Do you want to try?
- No, thanks.
(Black pepper)
(And white pepper)
Can I try this?
(Let me taste Dubai's pepper.)
(Ji Hyo chews to taste it.)
(My goodness!)
It's so hot.
It is very hot.
(It is very hot.)
(It's so hot that she can't speak.)
(You still have black pepper to taste.)
(She tries black pepper bravely.)
- Which one is better?
- This one.
(Her eyes are trembling.)
This is...
(Goodness!)
(Oh my goodness!)
It's so hot!
(She can't take its spiciness.)
(She's in panic.)
Oh my! Give me that water.
(She tries to cool it down by drinking water.)
(But it doesn't work.)
It's so hot!
(It is extremely spicy.)
It is so hot.
- It is too spicy.
- It is unbelievable.
- We came back so soon.
- Did you already find them?
- Yes.
- Wait.
How can you...
put this into my mouth?
I got the right one, right?
I used my tongue...
to figure out its shape when you put it in my mouth.
Me, too. I found mine easily because I remembered the shape.
(Me, too. I found mine easily because I remembered the shape.)
(I am sure nothing would be...)
(as spicy as this one.)
(Let's see if Jae Seok bought the right spice.)
- You got it right.
- I knew it.
(Jae Seok completes his mission.)
It's called chili.
I see. This is chili.
(Chili is Chilean pepper which has an extremely spicy taste.)
- I want the members to try it.
- I ate it all.
This is called saffron.
It's saffron.
I am very confident.
I can even bet all my wealth.
I'm sure this is the right one. It's saffron.
I think I'm genius. I found it so quickly.
- Are you sure?
- Yes, I am.
I can even bet all my wealth.
- Correct.
- See?
(Haha completes the mission.)
Here it is.
It is saffron.
(Saffron is the most expensive spice in the world.)
Saffron.
Here you go.
(Jae Seok and Haha cleared their missions in Spice Souk.)
You can go if the other members of your team complete theirs.
- Really?
- Yes.
The necklace with two peacocks.
("A necklace with two peacocks under a bloomed lotus.")
So it's a peacock necklace.
"A necklace with two peacocks under a bloomed lotus."
The necklace with two peacocks.
(Which store here would have it?)
It that it?
Oh, there it is.
(He found the gold.)
Look at all the golden items.
Let's go to find the necklace.
(Will he be able to find the necklace there?)
Excuse me.
I'm looking for two peacocks.
- Peacock?
- Peacock.
The necklace with two peacocks.
(Follow me.)
(He understood what Seok Jin said.)
I think they have it.
I think I will find it here at once.
(I think I will find it here at once.)
Two peacocks.
(Two peacocks)
They have to face each other.
Wow, yes.
(It's the splendid golden peacock.)
- Did you mean this?
- Well...
It's supposed to be 2, but this has 4 peacocks.
(This necklace isn't the right one.)
It's 100,800 dollars.
(How much is this necklace?)
It is 100,800 dollars.
(It is 100,800 dollars.)
Gosh, it's 100,800 dollars.
- Is it heavy?
- Yes.
- It's 2kg.
- Really?
Yes, it is.
Okay, see you later.
(Extremely expensive)
See you again. It's too expensive.
That's too much.
I've seen 2kg of meat, but not 2kg of gold.
I see gold everywhere.
(It's gold everywhere.)
(Wow!)
Is this gold, too?
Heavy golden items are so common like meats in this market.
(He calms himself down and goes in to find the item again.)
The necklace with two peacocks.
It's the necklace with two peacocks if I remember it correctly.
(Seok Jin is looking for the necklace with two peacocks.)
Two Peacocks.
(Due to everything being gold, it's hard to tell the shapes.)
- Hello.
There are two birds. Two peacocks.
- Two peacocks?
- Yes.
It's a necklace.
- Necklace?
- Yes, a necklace.
What? Is that it?
(Could this be it?)
I think that's it.
Right?
This must be it.
This is it.
This is the one.
This is the one. This is the peacock necklace.
This is 11,700 dollars, which is about...
13,000,000 won.
I think everyone would be really curious.
I think this is the right one.
Right?
Is this the lotus?
(A necklace with two peacocks under a bloomed lotus.)
I think I really found it. I hope it's the right one.
There's Seok Jin.
Did you find it?
- Did you find it?
- I think I did.
- Seok Jin!
- Hold on.
Can you check if this is right?
- I hope it's wrong.
- Once Da Hey comes, we're done.
Is it right? It has a lotus,
and the peacocks are looking at opposite sides.
- Da Hey needs to come.
- The lotus is on top.
I'm right. This is the peacock necklace.
(A necklace with two peacocks under a bloomed lotus.)
- Is it right?
- Am I right?
- Correct.
- Yes!
- No way.
- How did this happen?
It was really hard to find.
The necklace...
Wow. This feels great.
You just have to wait for Da Hey to come back.
- Can we go when she comes?
- Yes, you can leave immediately.
(They can go visit the place where the Golden Grasshopper sleeps.)
(Il Woo, Kwang Soo and Da Hey are going to the fabric market.)
Lala Fried.
- This is so hard.
- Is it "Lala Fried"?
How do you say it again?
- Alsa Nabe.
- What did you say earlier?
- Isalam.
- Was it "Lala Side"?
- How do you say it?
- Alsala Nabe.
Come on.
You made me forget!
Is it "Lala Side"?
Hold on.
- What did I say...
- Nuwat Sabe.
Is it "Lala Side"?
- Lala Side?
- It's "Lala Lala".
- Is it "Lata Side"?
- What?
(Il Woo runs off as soon as they get to the dock.)
(Let's go.)
Was it Mr Kakarela?
(Dubai Textile Souk has 500 kinds of textiles and traditional clothes.)
Is he Mr Kakarela?
(Where would the item be at this huge textile market?)
(He talks to a merchant at the local market.)
Excuse me, are you the shop owner?
- Yes, I am.
- Is your name...
(What's your name?)
(Courageous Il Woo)
(Whom will be the person he meets for the first time?)
Purchase Warud Tattris from Parkashu Mulani's store.
(Purchase Warud Tattris from Parkashu Mulani's store.)
(Now, I have to remember.)
Parsha Dame?
Parsha Dame? His name is Parsha Dame.
- Parsha Dame?
- Yes.
Parsha Dame...
Parsha... Parsha Dame.
- No. That's the wrong name.
- There's no one by that name.
- Parsha Dame?
- Parsha Dame.
- Did you write it down?
- No, no.
- Did you write it?
- Parsha Dame.
- Farsha Dame?
- Parsha Dame...
- Parsha...
- Dame?
- The name you have is wrong.
There's no one by that name.
- Parsha Dame?
- Parsha Dame.
- Farshu?
(Communication has failed.)
(Purchase Warud Tattris from Parkashu Mulani's store.)
I can't remember what I heard.
I'm slowly losing it.
(He's losing it in the middle of the street in Dubai.)
- Assana Bear?
- Hi.
Assana Bear?
(Da Hey is making up words, too.)
This is driving me crazy.
Assana Bear?
- What is your name?
- Assan.
- Assan?
Do you have any fabric called...
(She successfully finds someone with the same name.)
- Pel...
- Come, come!
Pel... What was it again?
(Purchase Pelbunapssaji from Assan Amin's store.)
For...
What's that fabric's name?
- My name?
- No, the fabric's name.
Pel...
(She has the first syllable right.)
Assanabel and Pel... Pelbonocchia?
What was it?
(Go purchase Pelbunapssaji from Assan Amin's store.)
I really forgot. What am I going to do?
Pelbonasase?
(She's desperate.)
Do you have anything similar?
Pelbonapsase?
(She's trying to say it gracefully.)
I don't think this is it.
I'm...
I'm in trouble.
Hello, Kakarela? Kakarela?
(Kwang Soo is focusing on "Kaka".)
Kakarela? What's your name?
- Hamil.
Nice to meet you, Hamil.
(We're looking desperately for Mr Kakairela.)
Kakarela?
Kakarela!
(Purchase Nal Asuwad from Kakairela's store.)
Kakarela?
(Kwang Soo didn't flip his hourglass, so he has little time.)
Mr Kakarela?
Mr Kakarela? Kakarela?
- Yes.
- Kakarela?
(Kakarela, I hear your voice.)
Who's Kakarela?
Kakarela?
(Is it really Mr Kakarela?)
I'm sorry, I don't know what you're saying.
- I'm a friend.
- A friend?
- Kakarena.
- Kakarena?
Kakarena, nice to meet you!
Kakarena!
(But Kwang Soo is wrong. The mission asked for Kakairela.)
Kakarena, I found you.
You're my brother!
You're my family!
(Welcome to Kakarena's store.)
(He immediately dresses up Kwang Soo.)
That's not it.
- What's your name?
- My name is Abdullah.
- Abdullah?
- Yes.
You said you were Kakarena?
My Arabic name is Abdullah.
- I see.
- My Pakistani name is...
- Kakarena?
- Yes.
Apra... Apra Side?
Abra?
I forgot.
Apra Side?
(Mr Kakarela,)
(can you understand what I'm saying?)
This is cheap. It's Gangnam style.
- Gangnam style?
- Yes, this one's Gangnam style.
- This is Gangnam style.
How is this Gangnam style?
Just try it.
(Try it first.)
No, this isn't it.
Apra Side?
(This is Apra Side style.)
Kakarela.
I need Apra Side.
Amura Side?
Amura Side!
- Do you want it?
- Yes, I want it.
Okay.
(From "Nal Asuwad" to "Apra Side" to "Amura Side")
It's a mission! Is Amura Side even correct?
Is this it? This is big.
Check.
What is this called?
This is Kandora.
- Kandora?
- Yes.
I don't need Kandora, I need Amura Side.
It's the same.
- Is it the same one?
- Yes.
You can try this one.
(Now he's trying to make Kwang Soo change.)
- It's your size.
- It's not for me.
You can try this one.
There's no need...
I don't need to try it.
(Prince of Dubai)
Check it.
No, I need Amura Side.
Yes, Amura Side. Look at the mirror.
(I didn't need to buy a new outfit...)
This isn't what I needed...
Amura Side?
Okay.
How much is it?
54 dollars?
Okay?
Amu...
I need Abu... Amura Side.
This is Amura Side.
(He's still unsure.)
Nalbura... Nal Brown.
- Light brown?
- No, not light brown.
(One's accepting a bargain, one's just confused.)
La... Lala Sound?
(They cannot understand each other.)
I'm not asking him to give me a discount.
(He's giving Kwang Soo a discount.)
Lalo Sound?
(Fine, I'll reduce it a bit more.)
- This is the best I can do.
- Okay.
Okay.
Thank you.
- Okay, bye.
- Bye.
It's cheap.
Cheap?
What was your name again?
- Kakalop.
- Kakalop?
- Yes, Kakalop.
- It wasn't Kakalop before.
(He was Kakarena 10 minutes ago.)
Apra Side?
Lapra... Life Side?
If I get it right, that would be crazy.
This is hard.
Is this...
(He's going back to see if he bought the right fabric.)
Is this right?
Amura Side?
Apra Side?
- Do you know Amura Side?
- Yes.
What's the name of this?
- Kandora.
- Kandora?
Kandora.
Is there another name?
- This is Kandora.
- Kandora?
Kandora?
No, this is Amura Side!
Kakarela told me...
(Kakarela told me that this is Amura Side...)
Abdullah...
That is Kandora.
- Is this Kandora?
- Yes.
(I've been fooled.)
(It's too late to turn back. The "Kandora's box" is open.)
(Goodbye, my lovely Kakarela.)
This is cheap. This is Gangnam style.
(He's feeling bitter.)
I have to hurry back and flip my hourglass.
(There is only a minute left in his hourglass.)
I have no...
time.
(He's desperate.)
I will...
die.
(Giggling)
I...
I have to hurry.
My life is on the line.
I have to flip the hourglass.
(I have to flip this hourglass because my life is on the line.)
Go faster.
(Grinning)
The other boats are passing us.
(They're getting further and further away.)
I feel like everyone else is on motorcycles, but I'm on a bike.
My life is on the line!
I have to flip the hourglass...
(Please, hurry up.)
Go faster.
We're here. Thank you.
(Time is gold. I have to save the hourglass.)
(Running)
(Kwang Soo is back.)
- You're fast.
- Kwang Soo, you're amazing.
- I knew it.
- Kwang Soo, you're out.
You're dead already.
Kwang Soo is dead.
Kwang Soo already died.
- He's dead already.
- Can you tell him he's dead?
Kwang Soo is really dead.
Kwang Soo, you're out.
- You're dead.
(Please tell me I'm dreaming.)
- Write it down.
- You were dead long ago.
- If everyone agrees...
- Kwang Soo is out.
(Kwang Soo is out.)
You're out.
You died in Dubai.
(He can't believe this.)
(What is with this Golden Grasshopper?)
(Why did I strive this much?)
- It's the same?
- Yes.
(I can't lose so helplessly like this.)
Are you going to use your second chance?
- I need to.
- Without consent?
You need consent.
I need to use it before my team members come.
I'll use my second chance!
(The person whose hourglass ended can be given a second chance.)
(Kwang Soo is given a second chance.)
You are truly a betrayer.
How could you use it already?
I need to live.
- Do you think they'll help me?
- You are truly a betrayer.
It's best that they're not here.
You're right. It's a good thing that they're not here.
They wouldn't have let you use it.
Is he with Ji Hyo and Gary?
(What will Kwang Soo's fate be?)
(Meanwhile, Gary and Ji Hyo are unaware of this.)
(They are diligently performing the mission.)
Look!
Wait.
There's 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8...
(There are exactly nine moons.)
There are nine.
This is it, right?
"The huge moon holds five jewels."
Three.
Four. Five.
It's this.
(Will he succeed in carrying out the mission?)
I'm done.
(Ji Hyo's discerning the spices.)
(Will her taste buds come back to life after the pepper incident?)
Ji Hyo is here.
Here's the jewel.
Gary, you're right.
Okay! Ji Hyo!
I am hoping this is right.
I'm sure.
I hope it's right, Ji Hyo.
- You're right.
- I knew it.
- Isn't it coriander?
- Oh, that's coriander.
I could smell it.
Jong Kook is in trouble.
He doesn't have much time.
He probably has calculated everything.
He does have a second chance.
I bet he is counting down the seconds.
There's a lot.
(The shining red leaf runs up the wrist and meets the leaf.)
I don't know which it is.
I really don't know.
I think it'll be here somewhere.
Is it that one? Are those the red veined leaves?
(Will Jong Kook's hunch prove to be right?)
There's not much time left. I need to go.
I don't have any more time to spare.
Let's go.
Jong Kook.
You need to come quickly!
I told you he's meticulous.
Here. "The shining red leaf..."
"runs up the wrist and meets the leaf."
Jong Kook, you're right.
I knew it.
- I wasn't even worried.
- But...
they looked all the same. There was a bunch of these.
Il Woo needs to come.
Il Woo isn't as smart as I expected him to be.
What are we going to do about him?
Da Hey still needs to come.
We can leave once she comes.
- She needs to come soon.
- The actors aren't doing well.
Yes, including Kwang Soo.
It's all up to the members looking for fabric.
(Everything depends on the members in the fabric market.)
(They have cleared each of their missions.)
(Let's make a run for it.)
Lala Side. Kakarela.
It's this one. Hello!
I need Wareud Tattris.
- What's your name?
- Kakairela.
Kakairela? Hello.
Really?
It's nice to meet you.
Assan Amin?
(I have finally found the place.)
Give me a hug.
Assan Amin!
Wait a minute.
(Purchase Pel Bunapssaji from Assan Amin's store.)
Fel Bunapssaji?
- Yes.
- Fel Bunapssaji?
Pel Bunapssaji?
Pel Bunapssaji. This colour?
Do you know Pel Bunapssaji?
The first word is "Wa".
Wa... Wa?
(Purchase Warud Tattris from Parkashu Mulani's store.)
War Kar...
- Lala Side. Please...
- Lala?
Lala Side, please!
(Purchase Warud Tattris from Parkashu Mulani's store.)
(Wareud Tattris?)
Hey, I think that's right.
Okay. Okay.
(Purchase Pel Bunapssaji from Assan Amin's store.)
- Nal Asuwad?
- Nal Asuwad. Black colour.
Is it black? I want...
- Are they shoes?
- Yes.
I don't know if this is right.
(If you've made a choice, then make a run for it.)
I need to go quickly.
I need to go quickly. I don't have much time.
Assal Amin!
My heart feels like it's about to burst.
(The fate of the three teams depends on these three.)
It's more difficult than skydiving.
(Which team will be awarded the advantage?)
Quickly. Go quickly.
It's hot.
The sun is too hot.
Da Hey!
Jae Seok!
I got Pel Bunapssaji!
Da Hey, come quickly!
Please be wrong, please be wrong.
(If she's wrong, she needs to go back to the market.)
(Running)
- Please be wrong.
- I got Pel Bunapssaji.
(Jae Seok, I'm back.)
- You got it, right?
- Yes.
- Please be wrong.
- It's this.
- We'll check it.
- It can't be right.
Assan Amin...
- Kwang Soo.
- Really.
- We'll check.
- Please, please, please!
- Please.
- Please!
You bought Pel Bunapssaji from Assan Amin, right?
- Da Hey.
- Yes?
(Will Team Jae Seok be able to win the advantageous position?)
(She can't be right.)
- Da Hey.
- Yes?
You're right.
(Da Hey is right.)
(Team Jae Seok can go to the final location.)
- Hey!
- We did it.
We did it!
- Where do we go now?
- All right.
(First place winners are given the ultimate clue.)
- It's this.
- Is this the clue?
(The Golden Grasshopper is hidden somewhere. Sand can turn it back.)
What does this mean?
(Each team will hide their hourglasses.)
- It was really difficult.
- It must have been.
Good job, Da Hey.
- Oh, my.
- Good job.
- This has low battery.
- Look over there.
This is how it works.
(They are taking a photo to celebrate their victory.)
- Come over quickly.
- Do it like this.
- This is how you do it.
- Oh, my.
- Like this.
- Okay.
It's done.
Let's take one.
(Since we're in Dubai, we need to take a photo.)
Let's celebrate our victory.
One, two...
(Let's find the Golden Grasshopper!)
- Okay.
- We can do it.
- Hey!
- Is it Il Woo?
Haha!
- I'm here!
- Did you find it?
(Il Woo arrives in second place.)
It's this. It's this.
(This is Warud Tattris!)
(I love you.)
(He is 200 percent confident.)
Goodness.
(What are you doing, Kwang Soo?)
- I'm here.
- It's see-through.
It looks beautiful.
This is Warud Tattris.
Il Woo,
you got it right.
(Il Woo got it right.)
- Yes.
- Warud Tattris.
(We're ruined.)
Gosh, I'm so jealous.
(The Secret of the Grasshopper: To change it into gold,)
Oh, my.
(it needs 9 hourglasses. If your name tag rips, you will lose sand.)
It's what we're great at.
- Oh, my.
- This is the game for us.
We can take this.
(They have lost hope.)
What? Did Il Woo succeed?
(Kwang Soo's hourglass has been sitting here for a long time.)
(Running)
Is there still time left? How is it?
Nal Asuwad.
Did you buy Nal Asuwad from Kakairela?
Yes.
Kwang Soo.
(He can't be wrong.)
(What will their fate be?)
Kwang Soo.
- You're right.
- Yes!
(Kwang Soo got it right.)
(They have made it!)
Good job.
Let's go.
Here's your clue.
"You will be given the opportunity to change your time..."
"with another's when you go to this place."
- "with another's."
- What does it mean?
- We can change with others.
- Maybe we can switch them.
(This is the location for the final mission.)
(Team Jae Seok has arrived first.)
I get nervous every time I come to a mission location.
This is the last mission.
- It's the last one?
- It's the last.
- Oh, my.
- We only need to win this.
I'm so tired. Why is it so long?
"This place was not generous to strangers."
"The Stone Grasshopper is hidden somewhere. and it needs sand..."
"to be turned back into the Golden Grasshopper."
"First, each team will hide their precious hourglasses somewhere."
"And set off to find the opportunities to win."
"Opportunities". We need these opportunities to win.
Opportunities...
The reason why it needs sand is...
It mentioned something about name tags.
It said that if your name tag is ripped, you lose the sand.
- Their sand will become ours.
- I will keep on...
maintaining my time in secret...
while getting rid of others' through ripping their name tags.
Let's go to the opposite building.
This place is very large.
- It is.
- It's nice here.
What is this place?
- This place...
- Over there.
Maybe it's a mosque.
(Bastakiah is the oldest residential area in Dubai. There are...)
(ancient ruins alongside traditional houses, mosques and restaurants.)
- It looks like an ancient city.
- It looks very ancient.
(Bastakiah)
It looks like an ancient city.
It's beautiful.
I want to take pictures.
- It's beautiful.
- Indeed.
We should turn the hourglasses around now and then.
(Team Jae Seok is looking for chances.)
Is it connected to here?
(Looking around)
(Oh, my.)
Oh, my goodness.
How did I find it?
This is exciting.
(This is exciting.)
(Da Hey finds a chance.)
Thank you.
I should tell the other members.
(What does this chance say?)
What is this? "Chance to Exchange".
"You can exchange your hourglass..."
"with someone else's."
Good.
I should go tell the other members.
(What are the other teams up to?)
It'll be hard to find here, Kwang Soo.
(Team Kwang Soo is still hiding their hourglasses.)
Lift me up. One, two, three.
(They hide their hourglasses on top of a high wall.)
You won't be able to reach them when you're alone.
Does this one have more?
Yes.
How can we find such small things?
They should be somewhere.
I'm sure they're on trees.
(Keeping a sharp eye)
Is this car immobile? Is it supposed to just stay here?
- Seok Jin.
- Kwang Soo, what are you up to?
- Have you found anything?
- No, I haven't.
- Seok Jin.
- Is your hourglass smaller... No.
(Has your hourglass gotten smaller?)
How much sand is left?
(Seok Jin is trying to change the subject.)
Has my hourglass gotten smaller?
(Has my hourglass gotten smaller?)
Will my hourglass get smaller?
(Will my hourglass get smaller?)
- Will my hourglass get smaller?
- No, it won't.
- You said so.
- No.
- I heard it.
- Gosh!
How will it become smaller?
- Seok Jin's hourglass got smaller!
- No, it didn't.
- Am I right?
- No, that's not true.
Have you found anything?
No, I haven't.
- See you around.
- Bye.
Bye.
I should find something.
- Gosh.
- Oh, my.
- Goodness.
- Da Hey, has your hourglass...
gotten smaller?
Why would it become smaller?
- That's what Seok Jin said.
- Will it become smaller?
(Da Hey is pretending that she has no idea.)
- He said it'll get smaller.
- What are you talking about?
Did the hourglasses become smaller?
Gary, Seok Jin says his hourglass has become smaller.
- What?
- I'm not sure.
- Really?
- Do they become smaller?
- That's not it.
- How much is left?
(2 versus 2)
- Hourglasses must become smaller.
- How much sand do you have left?
Why do you want to know that?
How does it get smaller?
(Ripping off your name tag makes it smaller.)
You're asking me when I'll die.
- Seok Jin.
- Why?
Why did you stare at Gary's name tag?
I didn't. I was just looking.
Seok Jin...
Can we rip off the name tags?
- We can't.
- We're not supposed to do that.
- Try if you want.
- Are you sure?
Sure.
(Seok Jin pushes them away.)
Rip it off!
- That's not it.
- Try ripping it off.
- Rip it off.
- I guess we just need to rip them.
- That's not it.
Has your hourglass become smaller?
- No.
- Thank you.
Why would it become smaller?
- Seok Jin.
- What?
- Why did you say that?
- I didn't mean to.
You should have just kept talking.
Then I could have ripped it off.
Seok Jin is being scolded by Da Hey...
- No, he's not.
- for telling me about it.
That's not it.
Gosh...
(Oh, my.)
- Why did I do that?
- How can you do that?
I would've guessed it, too.
Something must happen when you rip off a name tag.
Should we try? Should we?
Let's do that.
(The desert is glowing with sunset.)
(Night is falling...)
(on every street in Bastakiah.)
(Jae Seok came to check his hourglass.)
Where's Seok Jin?
(Seok Jin does not have a lot of sand left.)
Seok Jin!
(His hourglass might be changed into a smaller one.)
- Seok Jin!
- What? Who is it?
- Who are you?
It's me. Hurry up and come!
Where are you?
(Hurrying)
(Gary follows them.)
- Hurry and turn it around.
- What do you mean?
- Turn it around.
- My hourglass?
(Am I running out of time?)
(Less than a minute is left.)
That was close.
- Oh, my.
- Turn it around right now.
- Thank you.
- Did you rip off anyone's name tag?
(Did you rip off anyone's name tag?)
(Gary heard everything!)
You messed it all up.
Get him! Go get him!
We're supposed to rip off each other's name tags!
(He realises everything now.)
He heard us. Get him!
(Catch Gary!)
Go that way.
No!
- Rip his name tag off.
- Okay.
We should do that.
(Hiding)
Come here, come here.
(Careful)
(I heard something.)
There! Gary's over there!
(Gary is there.)
(They set out to corner Gary.)
(They'll attack him from both ends of the street.)
Gary.
- Gary.
- Don't come close.
That's not it.
- We need to talk.
- Give me a second.
We need to talk.
- Come here.
- Seok Jin.
(He's surrounded.)
Wait!
- Get off of me!
- Just a second.
(We have no mercy for you.)
Wait.
Let go of me!
(Da Hey rips Gary's name tag.)
Get off of me!
(Once your name tag gets ripped off,)
(your hourglass is changed into a mini-hourglass.)
(Does it have to be that small?)
That's about 5 minutes long.
(He is on a time crunch.)
Ji Hyo!
Kwang Soo, Ji Hyo!
Come here!
(Gary calls for them.)
- What's wrong?
- We need to rip off name tags.
- I heard they attacked you.
- Hey.
- My name tag was ripped off.
- Yours?
- I was attacked by three of them.
- Who were they?
It was Team Jae Seok.
When it gets ripped off, it turns into a mini-hourglass.
- Was yours changed?
- Yes.
So we have to rip off theirs.
Wait. Jae Seok is here.
(They spot Jae Seok.)
Should we rip his name tag off?
Jae Seok! Let's make a deal.
You know there's two second chances, right?
- Team Haha has two.
- Really?
- They have two.
- You have two, right?
No, I don't.
- Jae Seok.
- Stop.
(Kwang Soo attacks Jae Seok.)
(This is for Gary.)
(Gary rips his name tag off.)
What goes around comes around.
Now, let's cooperate.
Let's cooperate.
- Let's cooperate.
(Jae Seok has a mini-hourglass now.)
Is this because your name tag was ripped off?
(Team Jae Seok is developing strategies.)
Since this one doesn't last long,
I shouldn't be away too far.
Let's stay here.
- Okay.
- We'll stay here...
and exchange it with someone else like Jong Kook.
Whom should we exchange it with?
It'll be hard to rip off Il Woo's name tag.
He won both times before.
If he wins again, it'll be his third win.
We shouldn't let it happen.
- Sorry, Il Woo.
- Goodness, Il Woo.
Here in Dubai,
Arabian Nights will begin.
Let the magic begin.
(This night will be dedicated to Il Woo.)
(Jae Seok's mini-hourglass is exchanged with Il Woo's.)
What is this?
- Why is yours so small?
- What happened?
- Is Il Woo out?
- Is he?
(Il Woo ran out of time.)
We should find chances.
We shouldn't mind the time, go back and forth often.
I wonder why they chose Il Woo instead of me.
(Il Woo is in danger.)
Did they think I'm the ace?
- That could be possible.
- Is that so?
- Kwang Soo.
- Hi.
Hi. I just stopped by.
Did you exchange your hourglass?
- What?
- You have a chance.
- This...
- Wait!
(Sneaking)
(Da Hey attacks Kwang Soo.)
- Wait!
- Seriously?
- If you do this...
- That's not it.
- That was her own decision.
- I don't believe it.
- I just wanted to try it.
- If you do this...
- Is this what you were going for?
- No, that's not it.
- We should change our plan.
- Calm down.
Think about how your next hourglass will look.
There won't be another one.
(He tells them everything.)
- That's not true.
- That's not it.
- There won't be another one.
- Then we should...
- That's the last hourglass.
- Gosh. What's wrong with you?
- There won't be another hourglass.
- Really?
Will Jae Seok be out?
Why did you have to say that?
- I don't know.
- Seok Jin is flustered.
- Look at Seok Jin.
- Should we leave here?
He has given me at least four hints so far.
Thanks to him, I found out the hourglasses will become smaller.
(Seok Jin is The Giving Tree of hints.)
Aren't I humane?
Listen up.
- That team...
- I'm worried.
thinks... No, it's okay.
It'll be gone in a second.
Let's exchange it, then.
- What were you saying?
- Team Jae Seok...
- is not hard to beat.
- Right.
But we won't be able to beat Team Haha.
Right. I agree with you.
Then let's exchange it now.
Should we go for Jong Kook?
(They're going to exchange it right before it finishes.)
We'll use our "Chance to Exchange".
(Their target is Jong Kook.)
(Team Jae Seok and Team Haha are together.)
You should be careful.
- Jong Kook, you're out.
- What?
- Why?
(Am I out?)
(Guess what?)
(Our strategy worked.)
(I'll be back.)
There are only two left.
(This is our chance.)
Ji Hyo! Ji Hyo!
(Team Jae Seok is thinking the same.)
It's just us now.
- Haha, it's just us.
- Don't do this.
We should do it now!
- We should do it now!
- Hold him!
You should have grabbed him!
(Jong Kook, where are you?)
What?
(Haha is caught.)
Rip it off.
(Gary rips it off.)
(Haha has a mini-hourglass.)
Gary!
- Gosh.
- Gary.
Where is Gary?
- Gary!
Gary!
Gary! Gary!
You should've ran.
Why did you stay still?
That's not true.
What do you mean? You stayed there doing nothing.
Okay, I'll run.
(Gary runs away.)
Catch him!
Kwang Soo, help me!
(Kwang Soo comes to help Gary.)
I'll take care of this.
Run! Run away!
(Kwang Soo catches Da Hey.)
(I am sorry, Da Hey.)
I got it!
(Da Hey's turns into a mini-hourglass.)
We did it.
Gary,
you're permanently out due to your hourglass running out of time.
When did they switch my hourglass?
I guess one of them switched it.
No, no one switched it.
- What are you talking about?
- You just had little time left.
- I saw it.
- What?
- I mean your hourglass...
- I had an hour!
How did I run out of time?
An hour has passed long time ago!
I can't believe it.
(I should've set a timer.)
(Now,)
(three warriors...)
(are ready for the final battle.)
(Let's enjoy our last night in Dubai.)
Hello, guys.
(All the teams have gathered.)
We all meet here.
- It is...
- How could we...
meet like this?
This is how it goes.
- We have no choice.
- Yes, this is...
You have three healthy men.
- But you have the ladies.
- What do you mean?
Then let's exclude the ladies.
Why?
- What?
- We want to be with them.
We are a family.
It's not fair.
- You have the ladies.
- They may be better than us, men.
That's what I mean. Your team will have an advantage.
What do you mean?
Let's just do it. We have no time to hesitate.
- Let's do it.
- Okay.
I'm fed up with this life.
- Right. I'm fed up.
- I don't want to live like this...
- any more. I'm going.
- I want to finish...
this way of life.
Look at Jong Kook. The look in his eyes changed.
- Look at him.
- Be careful.
- He's angry now.
- I'm scared.
He's angry, so be careful.
We have to make a circle and move around.
That's exactly what we think.
Let's move around.
(Jong Kook grabs Seok Jin...)
(and rips his name tag off.)
(Seok Jin is out in a blink of an eye.)
Move away.
What...
My goodness.
(The battle continues.)
(Kwang Soo and Da Hey cooperate...)
(to take Haha down.)
- Rip it!
- What? No way!
- Grab him!
- Hurry!
Ji Hyo is permanently out.
She ran out of time.
Why?
- Gosh.
- Jae Seok, I'll be right back.
- Wait, Kwang Soo.
- What?
We have to make sure we have enough time.
Can we run away like this?
(Let's catch Jae Seok and Kwang Soo.)
Jae Seok, keep running.
There they are.
No. It's too dangerous.
Watch out.
(Da Hey grabs Il Woo's name tag.)
- Il Woo is out!
- I got his name tag!
Il Woo!
(Da Hey's attack was unexpected.)
(Il Woo is out.)
(Jong Kook versus Jae Seok, Kwang Soo and Da Hey)
Gosh, he's too strong.
(All of them are very exhausted.)
(Jae Seok grabs Jong Kook.)
(Jong Kook grabs Jae Seok.)
(Ripping)
(Jae Seok removed Jong Kook's name tag first.)
(Jong Kook is out, too.)
(Jae Seok and Da Hey versus Kwang Soo)
Wait.
(Kwang Soo is out.)
No, I thought...
- After Jong Kook removed...
- It's just...
Jae Seok's name tag, the game paused, right?
Wasn't Jong Kook...
- out?
- Listen to me, people.
- No, it's...
- You didn't betray this time.
I did my best...
I did...
- Didn't you...
- Jong Kook removed your name tag!
(Da Hey is smarter than Kwang Soo.)
Kwang Soo, it's over.
- This can't be true!
- Go home, Kwang Soo.
(It's time to meet "The Legend of the Golden Grasshopper".)
(The winners, Jae Seok and Da Hey,)
(enter the secret room.)
(They pour the sand of life into the bowl in front of the platform.)
- Oh, my.
- It's your friend.
It's your friend and your ancestor.
Hurrah for the Grasshopper!
- We won!
- We did it!
(Hurrah for the Grasshopper!)
- Good job, guys.
- You all did so well.
I'll take the photo now. One, two, three!
(They a selfie to keep their memories of Dubai.)
Wow. Look at this palm tree.
(Our two days in Dubai was very memorable.)
(This city on top of a desert is 10 hours away from Seoul.)
That building is really high.
(A lot of fans greeted the Running Man members.)
- That's amazing.
- Skyscrapers are everywhere.
(They ran around the city and flew in the blue sky.)
I've been on Running Man before.
But still, you all took care of me, so I'm really thankful.
(Thank you for helping me.)
It was fantastic.
(Da Hey will never forget her days in Dubai.)
(Mission complete: Running Man in Dubai in 2016)
Is this gold?
We'd like to say, "Thank you" to the people who helped us...
here in Dubai. Thank you very much!
- Thank you!
(Next week!)
An angel came here today.
- I am a bad guy.
- Yu Jae Seok has said that he'll...
reveal everything in detail.
Kwang Soo, the Asian Prince, is...
(No one really knows who they are.)
Haven't you loved me at least for a day?
(You'll see how they really are.)
(Get to thoroughly know the members. "All About Them".)