(2016 Running Man Project)
(Running Man "Wish List Episode 1")
Running Man survey.
- The restaurant I want to visit.
- The special episode I want.
You have to go to seven restaurants that you picked...
within 12 hours.
- All of them?
- We have to hurry.
We really don't have time.
- Thank you for the food.
- It's unbelievably delicious.
- It's unbelievable, isn't it?
- We have to go.
- Let's go.
- We don't have time.
- It's here!
- It's open!
(And...)
- Let's go on a trip together
- Together
- Let's forget everything
- I'm happy right now.
- Are you?
(Gary and Ji Hyo have been together for 6 years.)
- Is this an engagement ring?
- Engagement ring?
Do you think things would've been better if we did this earlier?
Fate brought us together.
(Could they have been better off if they did this earlier?)
(February 15, 2016 at Mokdong SBS building)
Wow.
(There's a table filled with delicious desserts.)
- Yes. What's this?
- Hello.
- What's this?
- What are we doing today?
- Oh dear.
- What's this now?
- Wow!
- It's our breakfast!
- Something amazing will happen.
Whenever they feed us something nice, they make us work hard.
- I know. This is a sign.
- They make us work even harder.
- I have a bad feeling.
- Don't eat it.
- Since it's here, I'll eat it.
- Is this what we always...
Since it's here, we should eat it.
We might as well eat it since they're going to make us work.
Recently, we did a survey.
- Yes.
Running Man survey.
Special episode that I want to do?
- I want to go to the States and...
- Which special do you want to do?
We did a survey.
And they asked us to be honest.
So this was one of the questions.
"What do you think is your strengths and weaknesses?"
- I'll read Seok Jin's answer.
- Why?
Your answer was the longest for your strengths.
"I am humble, considerate and loyal."
"I'm good to my family and I'm not greedy." You are a liar.
- Seriously.
- I was being honest.
This is your weakness.
- You're good to your family?
- I was just being honest.
I am so good to my family though.
Why did your eyes turn red?
- What's wrong with that?
- Gosh.
Isn't his strength that he lies often?
(What's the weakness of this perfect man?)
His weakness is that he loves to lie down and he's dull.
Sometimes I worry when he lies down for a long period of time.
- He's sleeping and...
- We check if he's still alive.
(They love Seok Jin.)
Seok Jin! Seok Jin!
He really surprises us.
It's too much.
Next is Jong Kook.
His strength is that he has a good personality.
- Hey!
- Come on.
- Why did you...
- That's the best part about me.
- I'll fix it. He has a temper.
- He has a temper.
- He sure does.
Gary's strength is that...
he listens to other people well.
- He is gullible.
- He is.
- This is...
- I wrote that as my weakness.
- I said I am too gullible.
- What did you write?
- It's here. "I'm too gullible."
- Really?
Why didn't you write "I'm too ugly"?
That's the last bit of my pride.
Don't mess with my pride.
Why didn't you write "I'm a fish"?
Ji Hyo's strength is that she forgets things fast.
- Really?
- You forget too many things.
Isn't this your weakness?
You hurt other people, and you forget it fast.
- I know.
- That's my problem.
What's her weakness? She wrote it well. "Quick temper."
(Her weakness is having a quick temper.)
- I wrote it.
- She knew about it!
- I always admitted it.
- I got goose bumps.
- I...
- She's so honest.
- She has a quick temper.
- But...
I can't help myself having a quick temper.
- I know. Ji Hyo wrote...
- You have a quick temper.
"I have a quick temper, and I feel sorry."
But it takes a little bit of time for her to feel sorry.
- It takes some time.
- We don't know if it will take...
- That's not it.
- a year or two.
We don't know about that.
She apologised today for what she did on episode five.
- Is that right?
- Yes. It took five years.
Ji Hyo feels sorry and apologises eventually.
She has a soft heart.
To the question "Which game are you confident to win?",
Seok Jin said, "Game of slap-match, not getting upset and not smiling."
- I think the last two are wrong.
- Why?
I can refrain from getting upset in any situation.
I don't get upset easily.
- You...
- I don't get upset easily.
- Let's see.
- His face is red.
- Darn it!
(He's surprised.)
He gets upset!
- Hey! That was uncalled for.
- I am sorry.
He doesn't get upset easily.
I'm sorry, Seok Jin.
- I'm sorry.
- What was that for?
- Erase this.
- That was too much.
You lost to me when we played the game of slap-match.
No way.
- You're upset.
- He's upset again.
- No, I'm not.
- I'm not upset.
- Yes, you are.
- You're upset.
- He's very upset.
- His face turned red.
- It's a normal reaction.
- He's very upset.
"Which food do you eat when you feel weak?" You can't eat that now.
- Why not?
- You can't eat right now.
Are you upset?
(Is he upset?)
(Oh! I forgot.)
- He has a quick temper.
- He does.
- He gets upset so easily.
- He gets upset easily.
He gets upset really quickly.
- Go to the hospital.
- His ears are turning red as well.
You get upset really easily.
You need to get an anger management therapy.
Your face turned red.
- Your face turned red.
- This part turned really red.
To the question "Which restaurant do you want to take the members?",
Seok Jin wrote, "Ganghwado mud eel".
Ganghwado mud eel is amazing.
It sounds delicious.
- It's delicious.
- Gary wrote a good one.
Apgujeong's cold buckwheat noodles and pork cutlet.
And Kwangju Restaurant's spicy octopus stir-fry.
- Where is that?
- It's in Daechi-dong.
Haha wrote "Jeju's pork kimchi stew".
Remember that place?
We went there together. We got the business card.
Ji Hyo wrote "Half-dried herring". You mean your cousin's, right?
- He sends it to you.
- I'm...
- from Pohang.
- Yes.
- And its specialty is...
- Her cousin sends it to us...
- when it's in season.
- Yes.
- The season is...
- It's over.
- He sent it once.
- It's over now.
- He sent it twice.
- Why did I only get it once?
(He's upset.)
- Stop getting upset!
- He's upset again.
- This is too much.
- You're burning inside.
- No. No.
- Your face is red.
- Seriously.
- He gets upset so easily.
No, he doesn't.
From now on, we will reflect your wishes...
when coming up with missions.
- I see.
- And that starts today.
I will announce today's race.
2016 Running Man Wish List episode one.
It's called "Seven Spoons".
- "Seven Spoons"?
- "Seven Spoons".
There were many restaurants you recommended in the survey.
We narrowed them down to seven restaurants.
You have to visit all 7 restaurants in 12 hours.
- All of them?
If you succeed within 12 hours,
you will get a gold spoon.
If you fail, you will get punished.
After you finish eating at each restaurant,
you will be given the chance to increase your chance of success.
There are different chances available.
You don't know which chance you will get until you pick it.
There are people who recommended two restaurants.
So you have to pick one and go there.
- We should pick a near one.
- Okay.
- How about Jejudo Island?
- We have to go to Jejudo Island.
Will Gary pick one first?
That's up to you guys to decide.
- Gary...
- Please pick one for me.
- Which restaurant did you write?
- Haha, please pick one.
But they are both close. It's either Apgujeong or Daechi-dong.
- Hurry up.
- I hope you pick buckwheat noodles.
Pick it!
- Apgujeong!
- Great.
- This is good.
- We did it.
It's pork cutlet and buckwheat noodles.
- You picked it well.
- I'm in trouble.
We have to eat a lot, so pick something less stuffing.
- Where are the restaurants?
- Ganghwado Island and Sinsa-dong.
- Ganghwado Island is too far.
- Let's pick Sinsa-dong.
It'll be too far.
Should I pick the one on the right or on the left?
Which one do you want to pick?
- Sinsa-dong would be nice.
- I will pick this one.
- The one on the right?
- Yes.
Then we should pick the one on the left.
Okay.
(Here we go!)
(Will they go to Ganghwado Island?)
(Or will they go to Sinsa-dong?)
It's Ganghwado Island.
(He's unlucky all the time.)
Hey! I said I wanted to pick the other one.
You should've picked the opposite one of the one you wanted to pick.
- You are...
- You are really unlucky.
Ji Hyo's pick is crucial.
It's...
either Pohang or Muan.
- What?
- Mud octopus is in Muan.
Pick one.
(It's Ji Hyo's turn.)
- Which one should I pick?
- Pick one.
They are both bad.
- We don't have any expectations.
- They are both too far.
(They are both too far.)
- Hurry up.
- We have a time limit.
- They are both the same.
- It's Pohang.
It's Muan.
(They sigh.)
- It's frustrating.
- It is really frustrating.
All right. What's next?
You just made it very awkward.
(They are done choosing the seven restaurants.)
- If you fail the mission...
- And?
If you fail to visit the seven restaurants,
one of you has to get punished.
Oh.
If you fail to visit five restaurants, one of...
the five people will get punished.
- In the ending spot,
- The more, the better.
you will spin the roulette.
- Oh dear.
- You will vote for...
the punishment to give to each other as a gift.
Let's do something fun.
What should I pick?
(Gary cracks up.)
I don't know what to write.
(Shave his head?)
That's crazy.
(Jae Seok asks Haha to shave his head as punishment.)
Just the thought of it cracks me up.
He fixed his hair so nicely.
(You're going to make me shave my head?)
All right.
Just two words.
Just like an octopus head.
An octopus doesn't have hair on its head.
I should write this for Haha.
Go to a competing barbecue restaurant and do an event.
(That event will bring all the restaurant owners together!)
That's too much.
That's a good one.
We did it already.
I will give Gary something really easy.
(What will Gary's punishment be?)
- He will do an event wearing that?
- A squid mask?
- Oh my gosh!
- I just wrote...
I wrote "Wear a squid mask and go to an event."
- "Go up on the stage with it."
- And nobody will see a difference.
They will just say, "Go, Gary!"
- "Gary, you are handsome!"
- Nobody will notice the mask.
"Gary is so handsome."
"He looks much more handsome in real life."
They will just think it's me. They won't think I'm wearing a mask.
- Jae Seok's done everything.
- He doesn't have anything...
- Pick something he hates.
- that he dislikes.
I wrote this. "Wear contact lenses and shoot an episode."
(Wear contact lenses for a shoot)
(The viewers have to put up with Jae Seok's face.)
- That's a good one.
- That's really brutal.
Isn't one episode too much? It'll disturb the viewers.
That's too much.
I'm going to make Ji Hyo collect insects.
- That sounds great.
- Why did you hit me?
- That'd be fun.
- Why?
That'd be great.
That'd be nice.
Mantes, caterpillars and everything.
I wrote something for Ji Hyo.
She should shoot "We Got Married" with Gary.
I'd love to see that.
Ji Hyo and Gary shooting "We Got Married".
Right?
Why are you doing it only with Chen Bolin?
Exactly.
Find us a tiny apartment.
(Let me be right next to you.)
So that we can be right next to each other.
A tiny apartment?
(Will Gary's wish come true?)
Then, please decide in which order you will visit the restaurants.
- At each restaurant,
- Wait...
you have to follow an option.
- What's that?
- They're your destinations.
Ganghwado Mud Eel.
Chicken kalguksu!
- The one near Kwang Soo's place?
- Yes, you're right.
- They only do deliveries.
- Around Kwang Soo's apartment.
We should eat at his place.
They only do deliveries.
(They want to intrude Kwang Soo's apartment.)
- Wait.
- You didn't tell me about this.
- Why at my apartment?
- The thing is...
I didn't know the name of the restaurant.
So I wrote your name instead.
And I have no say in this?
They only do deliveries.
- This is Kwang Soo's apartment.
- It looks better now.
Someone's in the bed. I mean it.
Stop the nonsense.
What are you installing?
Let me use the bathroom.
Why is everyone using my bathroom?
Isn't it nice to have some people in your apartment?
Right?
(We'll show you the limit of Kwang Soo's patience.)
Are these our chances?
No, they are...
the options you have.
- What is this?
- "It Has To Be Me"?
- "Times 2".
- Do you get 2 portions?
- Will they give you big portions?
- What do they mean?
Guys.
We'll start the timer now. Start.
- We should hurry.
- Wait.
We should use this. Where should we start?
- Kwang Soo.
- Yes.
Should we start in Samseong-dong?
Let's start from the farthest one.
- Samseong-dong.
- And then Apgujeong.
- Apgujeong.
- And then Geumho-dong.
- Geumho-dong.
- Are we going to my apartment?
- Of course.
- Really?
- All right.
- Ganghwado.
- And then...
- And we split?
- Yes, we will.
Let's go. We don't have much time.
- Let's go.
- Time is ticking.
- Let's start now.
- All right.
Give me my jacket.
- Let's go.
- It's not a lot of time.
We'll visit a lot of restaurants today.
(Spicy beef noodles soup, pork cutlet, chicken kalguksu,)
(kimchi stew, barbecue, eel, octopus)
Let's get going.
Wait. Was this place recommended by Gary?
- No, it was me.
- Oh, was it you?
This place is amazing.
- I've been there once.
- Especially in this weather.
Their spicy beef soup comes with noodles in it.
I love spicy beef soup with noodles.
- It'd be perfect for the weather.
- It'd be perfect.
I don't want to shave my head.
I love my hairstyle now.
If we clear our mission, no one will have to be punished.
Seok Jin, you have longer hair than your wife.
(Spicy beef noodles soup in Samseong-dong)
(Recommended by Kwang Soo, in Samseong-dong, Seoul)
- It's here.
- Oh, it's here.
It's here. Let's get off.
- Let's go!
- We don't have a lot of time.
I'm looking forward.
I think it'll be amazing.
An hour and a half has passed.
An hour and a half has passed already.
- It's here.
- Come here.
(There's no time to hesitate.)
Oh, it's here.
- It looks nice.
- It looks great.
Wow, I'm so excited.
It smells so nice.
- Oh, my goodness.
- It smells so good.
It smells fantastic.
- Who recommended this place?
- I did.
- Was it Kwang Soo?
- This looks amazing.
It looks delicious.
They serve only one dish...
- just as good restaurants should.
- This must be it.
You get noodles and rice.
Let's start eating.
We have 10 hours and 37 minutes.
- We should hurry.
- An hour and a half has passed.
- The food is here.
- It's here.
Hello.
- This is it.
- That looks good.
- I'm so looking forward to it.
- Stop. Put down your chopsticks.
- What? Why?
(Stop)
- Why?
We have an option to follow.
Oh, right.
- We should eat it before it cools.
- For spicy beef noodles soup,
- you chose an option,
- Yes.
- "It Has To Be Me".
You chose "It Has To Be Me".
Only six of you can eat here.
The one the owner chooses...
won't get to eat.
That's impossible.
I'm starving.
We have to eat.
This soup is amazing.
It's perfect for our first meal.
- It's our first meal.
- But...
the one who gets chosen shouldn't eat.
- We have to follow the rule.
- We can't help it.
- Let's do it for real.
- Are you going to choose?
- I recommended this place.
- Please.
- It was me.
(Please don't choose me.)
(Who will be the unlucky one?)
I hope it's Kwang Soo.
- It's Seok Jin.
This is impossible.
It's Seok Jin.
(Does it have to be me?)
You're cruel.
- Gosh.
- Thank you.
(Seok Jin's soup is taken away.)
This is absurd.
It wasn't even a prank.
- Thank you.
(Seok Jin has been unlucky for the whole six years.)
- Try it.
- Let's try.
- It's perfect for the first meal.
- This is amazing.
Gosh.
I love spicy beef noodles soup.
I didn't know this place.
They have other stores in Samseong-dong...
- and in Samgakji.
- I didn't know I would be chosen.
This tastes amazing.
This tastes really good.
- The soup is so flavourful.
- You can take it away as well.
It's perfect for the weather.
(I'm going crazy.)
(Seok Jin feels left out.)
You guys don't even look at me.
- Are you angry?
- No, I'm not.
- You never get angry.
- Hey.
(They're almost sticking their faces in their bowls.)
This tastes great.
- Kwang Soo chose the right place.
- I agree.
(They love Kwang Soo's recommendation.)
- It's spicy.
- You usually wait in a line.
Just this.
- I should be allowed this much.
- No, you're not.
Let me taste it.
(Seok Jin is desperate to taste it.)
This is amazing.
How could I be chosen?
It should have been Kwang Soo.
My goodness.
Eat a lot in the next place.
- What will we eat next?
- This tastes amazing.
This tastes really good.
If you don't eat this... Wait.
These noodles are raw.
I'll dip it in the soup.
(Seok Jin's chopsticks are taken away.)
- It was amazing.
- How can you be so cruel?
Please give us some rice.
They must have boiled the soup for a very long time.
The beef is very soft.
Let me just take a look.
- Let me see this.
- They're just green onions.
Just a piece of green onion.
(Jae Seok doesn't let Seok Jin taste the food.)
Why are you so desperate?
Desperate?
Are you angry?
(Did you say I look desperate?)
- Are you angry?
- No, I'm not.
I'm not angry. I'm just talking.
- Are you sure?
- Of course.
This is perfect for the weather. I can't think of anything else.
- Nothing is better for today.
- You're right.
- I love spicy soup.
- Me too.
It'll be perfect for hangover.
You're right.
I would drink just so that I can eat this soup.
Exactly.
- I'm happy you like it.
- This calls for alcohol.
Should we share what we thought of the soup?
Let's start from Haha.
This is a dish for world peace.
There will be no war as long as we have this soup.
- Good job!
We should worship this soup.
The greatest spicy beef noodle soup.
I worship you, spicy beef noodle soup.
- I worship you.
- You should call it "Hundred Soup".
- Why?
It deserves 100 points out of 100.
This should be called "Hundred Soup".
- Spicy beef noodles soup.
- And what?
(Spicy beef noodles soup...)
You have to live with me from today.
- What?
- Be mine.
Like the song.
Be mine
- Be mine
I love only you
- I do
This shouldn't be called just "soup".
- This is "The Greatest Soup".
- "The Greatest Soup".
Go away, frozen shoulder!
Really?
I can raise my arms after having this soup.
(Full of energy)
I can straighten my back now.
Wait.
I'd like to dip your hair in the soup.
This looks like spaghetti.
I could even eat his hair if it's dipped in this soup.
While you're enjoying yourselves...
- Oh, we have a limited time.
- We forgot about the time.
- Let's go.
- Let's hurry.
- Let's go to the next place.
- We have no time for this.
- Let's go.
- Aren't we using the chance?
- Let's use it later.
- What was the next one?
- We'll use it later.
- The buckwheat noodles.
- Let's go now!
- Let's go!
This was amazing.
- It really was.
- I feel so proud.
Thank you for the food.
- Thank you.
- See you again.
- See you.
- Ji Hyo.
- I feel so proud.
- It was amazing.
- It's not cold.
It's not cold after having the soup.
We sweated.
It's just that the temperature has risen.
(Jae Seok is excited.)
Should I take my shirt off?
It's not cold after having the soup.
It's just that the temperature has gone up.
- No, it's the soup.
- Your ears are red.
- Gary.
- Are you sure it's not cold?
- It's the soup.
- You guys are funny.
I feel so proud.
My goodness.
- Gary, that was great.
- Was it that good?
- It was fantastic.
And it was perfect for the first meal.
- I know what you mean.
- What is our next meal going to be?
It made me feel so happy.
- Right. It really did.
- Right, Ji Hyo?
It made me feel so happy.
Are you teasing me?
No. Are you angry again?
- No, I'm not.
- You...
apparently have an anger management issue.
(Seok Jin is diagnosed with an anger management disorder.)
I like how we planned this. After having the spicy soup,
- we'll eat buckwheat noodles.
- I'm going to eat them.
I love buckwheat noodles.
I'm already so full.
My stomach is half full.
(It's time to taste the food recommended by Gary.)
(Apgujeong)
(Buckwheat noodles and pork cutlet, Apgujeong-dong)
Okay. Let's eat!
Let's go. It's right here.
- We're going to the good places.
- Let's get off.
(They're extremely excited.)
- It's buckwheat noodles.
- Wow.
It's right here.
I love today's special episode.
This is it.
This is where we do "Times Two".
- Hello.
- Hi.
- Let's sit.
- It smells great in here.
- Goodness.
- This is the place.
Shall I order?
- You got here quick.
- Let's hurry up.
This is where we have to do "Times Two".
What is "Times Two"?
This place was recommended by Gary.
- That's right.
- He did.
He's confident after that spicy beef noodles soup?
- Isn't this place famous?
- Yes, it is.
- What is it?
- I will put...
(I will put this pork cutlet in the centre.)
- Okay.
- What is it?
- There are seven pieces.
- Okay.
There are seven numbers underneath each piece.
One of you have to pick up a piece.
Whatever number shows up,
you have to double the number and order that many portions.
If 2 comes up, we have to order 4 pork cutlets.
- We have to eat four.
- We'd have to share.
- Up to 3 will be good.
- Let's pick under 3.
- Seok Jin will choose.
- I'll pick.
- He didn't get to eat before.
- He's unlucky though.
- What would be the worst?
- It'd be seven.
- It's seven.
- That's the worst.
- I think three is good.
- We'll have to eat.
Three would be good.
That's true.
(He picks one.)
(What number...)
(will it be?)
- What is it?
- It's four.
- That'll be 8.
- That's 8 orders.
- Seok Jin can have more.
- That's right.
- It's not bad.
- We can eat eight.
- That's fine.
- You can have two.
- You didn't eat before.
- That was a good pick.
We don't have time.
- We have to go.
- Let's get five noodles.
- Order 5 buckwheat noodles.
- And 3 pork cutlets.
Give us 5 buck-noodles and 3 porks.
- Order 5 buck-noodles and 3 porks.
- Come on.
Nobody says it like that these days.
- Who does that?
- What's wrong with that?
That's not cool.
(That's embarrassing.)
Do you know how to say 2 jjolmyeons and 2 ramyeons?
- Of course.
- It's "Jjoljjol, rara".
(That's old school.)
- What?
- That's so old.
- "Jjoljjol, rara".
- Oh goodness.
Tteokbokki 1, jjolmyeon 2 and ramyeon 2 is...
"Tteok, jjoljjol, rara".
(That's embarrassing.)
The food is here.
- Oh gosh.
- That looks good.
(The pork cutlet is here.)
- Thank you.
- That must be delicious.
- You two can share.
- Okay.
We ordered three pork cutlets.
We ordered five buckwheat noodles.
(It's delicious.)
- How is it?
- It's good.
(It's yummy.)
(The buckwheat noodles are ready.)
Could you give us more soup?
It's over there.
- This is great.
- It's nice.
Do you want it warm?
(It looks amazing.)
- Doesn't it look delicious?
- My gosh.
Thank you, Gary.
- Thanks.
- Thank you.
- Let's eat.
- Enjoy.
(The noodles look yummy.)
This is fantastic.
- Wow.
- It's so delicious.
(She slurps it down.)
It's been so long since I had this, but it still tastes the same.
(Cold buckwheat noodle is perfect to have in winter.)
This is really delicious.
I could eat this even when I'm full.
It's so delicious.
(He sucks in the noodles.)
The noodles and pork cutlet go together so well.
- Seriously.
- Don't they?
The vegetables are really delicious too.
You have 9 hours and 38 minutes left.
Are we using the chance now?
The chance you pick now...
will be used on the next round.
- Let's do it in Geumho-dong.
- Okay.
Please use the chance.
- What?
- First, I need to...
use the bathroom when we go to your house.
Come on.
(What is he talking about?)
Let's use the chance.
- Let us all use your bathroom.
- The bathroom here is better.
This is actually good because...
I need to stop by your place.
I have to empty my stomach and start eating again.
I don't like people using my bathroom.
- I want to use it by myself.
- You and I go together well.
- We're perfect.
- Why? Why?
I like doing it at other people's houses.
He likes to do that.
(Kwang Soo is dumbfounded.)
That's how I am.
- It's yummy.
- Nice.
- We have to make a comment.
- Yes, we do.
Gary should start.
Buckwheat noodle is like love.
Really?
Because it knows how to play a game.
(Buckwheat noodle is like love.)
- That's right.
- Okay.
- It's Kwang Soo's turn.
(He feels pressured.)
(He looks at others.)
- Kwang Soo.
- Can you think of anything?
(I want to know what you think.)
Get ready to get slapped.
Buckwheat noodle is...
(Buckwheat noodle is...)
(Haha slaps Kwang Soo.)
- What was that?
- Didn't you finish?
- He's not done.
- I think my tooth...
just came out.
- I am sorry.
- Was it my tooth or rice?
You should've slapped him after he finished.
I'm sorry. I didn't know.
- Okay.
- Buckwheat noodle is...
- like a tattoo.
- Why?
(Buckwheat noodle is like a tattoo.)
- I don't know.
(I don't know.)
(Did you just blurt that out to avoid getting slapped?)
- I don't want to explain why.
- Okay.
- Haha is up next.
- I said...
spicy beef noodles soup was world peace.
Buckwheat noodle is...
- war.
- Why?
(Kwang Soo throws water.)
(He takes revenge.)
What do you mean, war...
on a nice day like this?
Don't you think that was too much?
Hey. Don't overdo it.
(It's Seok Jin's turn.)
First of all,
it's teasing me.
- That's not how you do it.
- That's wrong.
It has to be one line.
- You have to make it quick.
- It has to be one line.
The noodle is teasing me.
- I don't think that works.
- Why not?
- Try again.
- How about memory of first love?
Well, that's a bit...
That's too vague.
Are you saying no to everything?
- You are, aren't you?
- Are you mad?
No, I'm not!
(I'm not mad.)
I am not mad!
(It's his fourth try.)
Buckwheat noodle is like...
- Jae Seok's glasses.
- Why?
Because it covers embarrassing points.
I'm not embarrassed.
(I'm not embarrassed.)
(I'm good looking and I'm proud.)
What are you talking about?
I'm getting angry.
(He starts to get angry.)
- He's angry.
- No.
When Seok Jin gets mad his lips go like this.
No, I'm not mad.
- We don't have time.
- You should try.
- Me?
- Yes.
- Buckwheat noodle...
- Everyone get ready.
Everyone get ready.
(I told you buckwheat noodle was war.)
(Water)
(Pickled radish)
Isn't this too much?
I'll make it work.
- Okay.
- Come on.
- Get ready.
- Wait.
- If...
- Yes?
- Let me say something.
- Okay.
If someone attacks me, even when I succeed,
- I'll attack back.
- Fine.
(Let's see how Jae Seok does.)
- Get ready.
- You should move over.
- Wait.
- What's this?
- Gosh.
- Could you do it...
- in this situation?
- You have to...
- overcome it.
- Can you?
- You have to.
- I can do it.
- Yes, you can.
- I can.
Buckwheat noodle...
You're so pretty, so pretty
(You're so pretty, so pretty.)
(Slapping)
(Kwang Soo and Haha throw water at Seok Jin.)
Hey!
- I'm sorry.
- Hey!
How dare you?
- I aimed wrong.
- Really?
- I'm sorry.
- I am sorry.
- Did you do it on purpose?
- No.
You idiot!
(I missed my target.)
I didn't do it on purpose.
- Same here.
- I'm sorry.
- I didn't do it on purpose.
- Yes, you did!
- I aimed wrong.
- Are you mad?
- I'm sorry.
- No, I'm not.
- I missed my target.
- Look at this.
Look at this.
- I'm so angry.
- Are you mad?
No, I'm not.
I knew it. He doesn't get mad.
We'll go to the restaurant I picked, right?
- Yes.
- Okay.
Will you use the chance now?
- No.
- Not now.
- Yes.
- No, we won't.
- We have to use it in Jejudo.
- That's right.
- Let's go to Geumho-dong.
- Yes.
We have to go there.
Because I need to use the bathroom.
(I have to take care of a business.)
- Let's go.
- Okay.
- Let's go!
- We have to go with Kwang Soo.
- Let's go.
- Wait.
You never ask my opinion.
The good restaurant I know...
Why does it have to be my place?
It's your house.
- Your opinion doesn't matter.
- It's my house.
- Who suggested?
- Wasn't it delicious?
- It was really delicious.
- So we're going to your house.
My choice is your house.
(Seven Spoons)
(They're on their way to Kwang Soo's place.)
We'll have to do everything in my house, won't we?
Yes.
(Sighing)
I'll move back to my parents' house.
I can't live like this.
I don't know...
how to react to...
someone who's coming to...
my house for toilet.
You're the only one who thinks your house is your private space.
We eat chicken kalguksu in Geumho-dong and...
go to Jejudo Island using the chance.
Going to Muan is the problem.
We might get the eraser chance.
- We could erase that.
- Yes.
Wouldn't it be better to erase...
- Muan instead of Jejudo Island?
- Muan is better.
You should be glad I picked Kwang Soo's place.
Seriously, it was a good choice.
(Chicken kalguksu, Kwang Soo's house)
Is this the famous place?
This is the place I know.
Why did you pick here?
To be honest, I can't...
remember the name of the seafood kalguksu place.
But why did you pick my place?
- Look. It's a game.
- What's that?
What?
It's a game.
- What is this?
- If we do it, do we get more time?
The option you chose was...
- "It Has To Be Me".
- Right.
Cover your eyes. Whoever jumps over the long stick...
without dropping it can eat kalguksu.
- Really?
- If I fail, I don't have to eat?
Whoever fails doesn't even need to enter my house, right?
(I will succeed.)
- Jong Kook.
- Shall I go?
(Jong Kook is first.)
- Go ahead.
- It'll be hard.
(He walks forward with his eyes covered.)
How is that even possible?
- Is that possible?
- How?
Go straight.
- Keep going.
- Go straight.
- Take two more steps.
- You have to go over it.
Go over it. That's it.
(Taking big steps...)
- Wow.
- Oh, my.
(Haha also manages to succeed.)
- Go for it.
- That's it. Big steps.
- Big steps.
- Goodness.
(Everyone succeeds in order to visit Kwang Soo's place.)
- That's it.
- Okay.
(Jae Seok even manages to jump over.)
Goodness.
How did you do that?
This is too easy, right?
- Yes,
- Yes.
(Jae Seok is fooling around.)
Stop right there.
You're nearly there now.
You have to take big steps. Big ones.
Make big steps.
- You're there. You're touching it.
- Move a little to the left.
- No, no.
(Struggling)
(What is this?)
- You come over here.
- Are you mad?
Yes, I am mad.
(Yes, I am mad.)
(He looks like he could fall ill from anger.)
Goodness.
Yes, I am mad.
- In 1, 2, 3, 4...
- Going 3, 4...
- Higher.
- That's it.
That's it. Higher.
(It was close, but he succeeded.)
- Did I make it?
- Success.
You can go in and order the dishes you want to enjoy.
- Really?
- Can't we order in advance?
- If we check the time...
- They do good food.
- Isn't it?
- The soy sauce is really good.
Where is it again?
(Where is Kwang Soo's apartment?)
What's interesting is that all the staff know where Kwang Soo lives.
- It's that way.
- That way.
I lived here for 2 years and we've shot here 6 times already.
(It must be kind of a film set to be shot 6 times in 2 years.)
- You did a live broadcast once too.
- How did you know it's that way?
(How did you know it's that way?)
How did you know it?
(The staff know of the shortcuts.)
- They've been here so many times.
- They know the way off by heart.
Goodness, your home.
How did you find the way by yourselves?
(They finally enter Kwang Soo's apartment.)
- The next door...
- You all know the door code, right?
- You all know the code, right?
- Let me do it.
- Since the owner is here.
- The owner is here.
I know the door code too.
(Kwang Soo opens the door.)
This is really...
I call second for the toilet.
I call next in line after you.
Your house looks better.
Kwang Soo.
(Last spring,)
(they had a surprise housewarming party.)
(Surprise!)
- It's a housewarming party.
- Hello.
Kwang Soo, do you sleep over here?
I have a right to search here.
To search what?
What is this?
What do you think you're doing?
What are you guys doing?
Everyone, get out.
(It was still an unfamiliar place at that time. )
(Now it's become so familiar.)
I'm not even shocked any more.
- The view is great up here.
- It looks better than last time.
- Pardon?
- Did you buy this?
- Yes, recently.
- First,
I need to use the toilet, Kwang Soo.
Okay, Jae Seok.
- There is someone on the bed.
- What are you doing?
(There is someone on the bed?)
Someone is on the bed.
Stop talking nonsense.
I'm telling the truth.
See, someone's lying down under the covers.
(What is that on the bed?)
- That surprised me.
- Me too.
I was surprised too.
You startled me.
(It was a bunch of pillows.)
I thought someone was under the covers.
(Kwang Soo, please tidy up your bed.)
Why did you leave it like that?
I don't know. I was so busy in the morning.
- You're going to be very free.
- Jae Seok.
- Yes?
Can I use it first?
All right, you use it first.
(Wait a minute.)
His house smells different.
(His house smells different.)
What?
It's the scented candles.
As soon as possible, please.
- Yes, thank you.
- Kwang Soo.
- I have a really...
- Jae Seok.
sensitive nose.
It's because of the scented candle.
It smells like he had a woman over.
- It's not that.
- It smells like a woman's perfume.
It's because of this candle.
(It's no woman but this candle, I tell you.)
Stop talking nonsense.
(Stop talking nonsense and just have your chicken kalguksu.)
- Really.
- All right, then.
- It's because...
- What are you setting up?
What is this that you're setting up?
(The place looks like a film set.)
- We don't have much time left.
- Are you remodelling the place?
What is this?
- This looks dangerous.
What are you doing?
- I'm back.
- All right.
Kwang Soo, did you order the chicken kalguksu?
I did.
Ask them to be quick. We only have 8 hours and 30 minutes.
- You're right.
- We're in trouble.
(Come here, chicken kalguksu)
Do we need to order it now?
- We already ordered it.
- We ordered it.
- Did we order?
- Yes, we did.
(Screaming)
(A scream is heard in the midst of silence.)
- He's giving birth.
- Jae Seok.
You can do that at the next place.
Goodness.
He always leaves behind something.
Is it his first time in a few months?
(What was that scream?)
I dozed off.
- What?
- I dozed off.
(It's so warm and comfortable.)
- Why would you do that?
- It's so warm in here.
(He is very satisfied.)
I love this house.
(What do you mean?)
- Jae Seok.
- What are you talking about?
- Don't close the door.
- Come on.
- Gary.
- Why?
It's not what you think it is.
(Don't worry.)
Something here makes it work.
This place is paradise of excretion.
(This place is paradise.)
What are you talking about?
Why would you name my home like that?
I designate this place...
as our sacred place of constipation.
The association of constipation will call you soon.
You are appointed as the manager of this sacred place.
(Kwang Soo is appointed the manager of sacred place of constipation.)
You have been appointed.
No, this place is not related to any of that.
(The door bell rings at that moment.)
- It's here.
- It's quick.
- The scenery is really nice.
(The chicken kalguksu is here.)
The view is really nice.
Isn't it nice?
Get ready to go.
(Get ready to go.)
Bring the dishes then.
It's like the newlywed's home.
- Kwang Soo.
- You two are like a married couple.
Can we shoot "We Got Married" here?
Why would you do it here?
Why does my home look like a newlywed's home?
I know the place.
Yes, it's perfect.
Let's shoot it here.
- Hello.
Here you go.
We're really big eaters.
- Thank you.
- Enjoy your meal.
- Enjoy the meal.
- I recommended this place.
- Jae Seok loves this.
- Yes.
- Thank you.
- I wish you all the best.
- You two prepare it.
- Yes.
Shoot a mini "We Got Married".
(Gary and Ji Hyo are given the chicken kalguksu.)
- If this were real...
- Honey?
I hope to see a serious version of this later.
(Here is the chicken kalguksu.)
There's a lot of soup.
Isn't it your first time doing this?
(Lovey dovey)
- Of course I've done this before.
- Is that so?
(When it boils, it's ready to eat.)
Not any where else but you have to eat it at Kwang Soo's.
- Who wrote Jejudo Island?
- But...
- Haha.
- I like Jejudo Island too,
but on a day like this, you should have known better.
Look who's talking.
- What?
- So you wrote down my home?
Look, Kwang Soo.
The route is perfect.
First, it was Samseong-dong, then Apgujeong then Geumho-dong.
- And then Jejudo Island.
- Stop going to the toilet.
What took you so long?
- Touch.
- How many times are you flushing?
(Haha goes in next.)
- Look.
- Give 30 dollars when you leave.
Why are you having a toilet party at my house?
You should leave the door open.
So that when our colleagues...
come over, they can ask to use the toilet.
They would have heard...
about the rumour.
Is this the famous Kwang Soo's toilet?
Who's up next?
(I feel refreshed.)
Kwang Soo,
don't you love having company around?
(Don't you love having company around?)
Right?
Isn't it nice having people around?
I almost forgot it was my home.
(How nice is this to have company?)
It should be filled with people.
- I saw you go like this.
- Gary.
Ji Hyo is really nice.
(She seems lady-like.)
- The soup is ready.
- It's ready.
This...
Everyone,
enjoy the food I recommended!
- Wow.
- Okay, let's go!
It'll be really tasty.
Let's enjoy.
- Sit down.
- Look at this.
- There's a whole chicken inside.
- Although there wasn't much fat...
A few days ago,
- Come and sit down.
- it was Seok Jin's birthday.
We weren't prepared to give him a present then so we all chipped in...
and prepared a present for him today.
Congratulations.
Happy birthday to you
- Happy birthday, dear Seok Jin
- Are you going to give it to him?
- Are you going to give now?
- Happy birthday to you
You shouldn't have.
Surprise.
We were so sorry that we missed out,
- so we've prepared an oven glove.
- It's quite cold these days.
Try it on.
(An oven glove right out of Kwang Soo's kitchen.)
- It must be cold.
- You have to wear it.
You have to.
(The prank succeeded.)
Try it on.
- I thought it was for real.
- His face is so red.
I really thought it was for real.
- Try it on.
- Come on, try it on.
Seok Jin, try it on. We all chipped in to buy this.
- You should wear it all day.
- Wear it all day today.
What's this?
(One of the glove is already burnt.)
- Happy belated birthday.
- This is heartwarming.
(This is a real heartwarming birthday party.)
- I really thought...
- Seok Jin really thought...
- His face was so red.
- This is really...
Don't do this again.
I was worried how to react.
- This is really tasty.
- I'm not kidding. Have a taste.
- We keep on having noodles.
- Three in a row.
Haha, the funny thing is that I have room for more.
We have room for more.
Here's a chicken breast for Jong Kook.
I'll have it.
(Now that they're full, they've become childish.)
- This looks great.
- Let's enjoy.
- It looks great.
- There must be a drumstick in here.
How's the noodles?
- It's good.
- It's well cooked.
(They enjoy the chicken kalguksu.)
I'm so full.
This is the best.
It only tastes good at Kwang Soo's.
- I get what you mean.
- Do you see what I mean?
- How many drumsticks did you eat?
- Two.
There are only two.
How can you eat both without asking?
- You should've offered.
- Do you want one?
- You eat it.
Okay.
I feel uncomfortable about eating it.
Gosh...
Are you upset?
- Are you?
- Are you angry?
- He's upset.
- I just felt uncomfortable.
Are you upset?
Why would you get upset because of that?
Jong Kook, I feel so uncomfortable. You eat the drumstick.
I feel so uncomfortable.
- I feel uncomfortable.
- You eat it.
No, it's okay. I don't have to eat it.
I will eat it then.
Is it okay? Do you want the drumstick?
No, it's okay.
Tell me. Jae Seok?
- I don't want it.
- Okay.
- That was really good.
- It was great.
We are done.
Let's pick a chance.
- The eraser chance is the best.
- Let's erase Jejudo Island.
(The eraser chance is the best.)
- Ji Hyo.
- I don't know. I just chose it.
- Okay.
- Good job.
What is it?
It must be a good one.
Separation chance!
That's a good one.
You're amazing.
So we have to go to Jejudo Island.
We have to go to Jejudo Island.
Who wants to go?
Let's pick who will go.
- Are we really going?
- Let's pick who will go.
- Let's pick it.
- Let's be fair.
I'll mark two sticks. Give me one more.
- I always get picked.
- Me too.
Raise your hand if you want to go.
Let the volunteer go.
Let's see if there's a volunteer.
There may be someone who wants to go. Right?
All right, everyone.
We will pick two people to go to Jejudo Island.
- Don't look at it yet.
- Okay.
Please...
- I don't know.
- Don't look at it yet.
- It's on this side.
- You would know.
I will just pick one.
Should we check it together?
I think I'm going.
- I don't know either.
- Don't look at it.
Don't look at it.
When will we go there?
(Jejudo Island is good. But it's going to be very tiring.)
- I really can't go.
- I hope it's not me.
I'll get the last one.
Please.
I'm really scared to ride an aeroplane.
- Let's check one by one.
- I will go first.
Please!
(What will be Gary's fate?)
There!
Is there nothing?
- It's him.
- It says Jejudo Island.
Yes!
- Yes!
- Now one is out.
- Please.
- Seok Jin, you're next.
(Seok Jin passes.)
It's not there.
- Next is Jong Kook.
- This is crazy.
How could I pick that?
And you were the first one to pick.
(Jong Kook passes too.)
- It's not there?
- You have a big smile.
- It should be Haha.
- It's not there.
It's not there! Yes!
- Maybe it's going to be me?
If Ji Hyo picks it, she's meant to be with Gary.
In 1, 2, 3.
- It's not there.
- Hey...
- It's one of them.
Check it at the same time.
- Gosh...
- This is crazy.
In 1, 2, 3.
(Who will be the one to go to Jejudo Island?)
Three.
(Ji Hyo is picked.)
- Who is it?
- It's Ji Hyo.
I'm going with Ji Hyo!
- It's Ji Hyo?
- Really?
- I got goosebumps.
- It's really Ji HYo?
Chen Bolin,
you're out.
You guys are meant to be together.
Stop it!
(Gary and Ji Hyo are going to Jejudo Island!)
Let's go, Ji Hyo.
Let's go to Jejudo and get some fresh air.
I never thought I'd go to Jejudo Island with you.
I saw it coming.
I really didn't think I was going to pick it.
This is crazy.
(They are meant to be together.)
I never thought...
we would go on a trip like this.
I know, right?
This is...
crazy.
(The crew is serious.)
What should we do?
It's snowing in Jejudo Island.
Really? Just don't tell them.
- That's even better.
- That's not it.
Maybe they will go to Jejudo Island...
and really fall in love.
They will be falling in love after six years.
This is a heavenly chance.
Gary shouldn't miss this chance.
There are many people who get stuck in Jejudo Island.
They get stuck?
Because of snow storm,
flights get cancelled, and they get stuck for 3 or 4 days.
If we get stuck there for three days, what should we do?
(If we get stuck there for three days, what should we do?)
What do you mean?
It's been a while since I said it. What do you mean?
(What do you mean by that?)
Since we are going there anyway, let's have fun.
Yes. Let's just think that we're going there on a trip.
Get some fresh air in Jejudo
In a place where there is no one
But it's really fascinating that Gary and Ji Hyo got picked.
- It's not easy.
- It's not.
It's really not easy.
What's the probability?
It's two-sevenths.
You're right. It's not too big.
What is the probability of Ji Hyo and Gary going to Jejudo Island?
There's a very small probability.
Are you upset?
Why don't you...
- Why don't you get help?
- I can't say anything to you.
You're addicted to getting upset.
I think you have an anger management issue.
(I'm not smiling right now.)
We're here!
Let's go to Jejudo Island.
(They already got the airplane ticket.)
Can't we just take a camera with us?
Do you have to follow us around?
(Gosh...)
It's too uncomfortable.
Why are you uncomfortable? They are our team.
The crew should rest.
We could film ourselves. There's no problem with that.
(The crew is so slow-witted.)
The last flight is at 9:30pm.
It's 9:15pm.
I see.
Let's leave together
- Only the two of us
- Let's forget everything
Let's plough a field
And grow tangerines together
You said it. You said we should farm tangerines together.
If you really
Feel alone
(She's excited.)
Should I take a swimming suit?
- We can buy a swimming suit.
- Okay.
- We don't have to take anything.
- I'm so excited right now.
Why are you excited?
(He's too excited.)
I can wear a triangle swimsuit.
(He confesses.)
(He's too excited.)
(What kind of a journey is awaiting them?)
(The two of them will get to look at the Jeju sea together.)
(They can drive along the shore and ride a horse.)
(Wait for us, Jejudo.)
Bye, Gary.
Take a nap.
Don't you think you said bye too early?
You should wait at least...
until the seatbelt sign is off. That was way too fast.
I think you will be like that even on a honeymoon.
Bye, Honey.
We're here.
Let's go.
(The five members arrive at the next restaurant.)
(It's a barbecue restaurant recommended by Jong Kook.)
(It's located in Seogyo-dong, Mapo-gu, Seoul.)
This is tough.
(They will eat one order of meat barbecue.)
First is Jong Kook. Second is me.
Third is Haha, and fourth is Kwang Soo.
Let's sit in the order.
Okay.
(They sat in the order.)
Jae Seok, are you hungry? Or are you full?
I'm full.
(All of them are full.)
- Looking at the grill,
- Thank you.
- I feel hungry again.
- When you see it,
you will say, "That's it?"
- That's it?
- It's going to be delicious.
One order is too small.
- That's one order?
- I will eat it alone.
- No, it's okay.
- No.
- I should eat it.
- Which part is it?
- I will eat it.
- Hold on.
- Jong Kook loves it.
- It's beef.
- It's not about being loyal.
- It's the opposite.
He could eat everything alone.
You know I wrote beef as my favourite health food, right?
I'm sure we can eat one piece each.
- You have to let me eat too.
- I can eat all of that alone.
- Me too.
This is what life is about.
(He's got all the authority.)
Get me a drink.
Give me some.
I feel like drinking when I can't even drink.
- Gosh...
- That looks delicious.
It's the opposite.
I'll eat the parts with less fat.
(They just stare at the meat.)
That looks delicious.
- You're going to eat only those?
- No.
Gosh, he's going to eat everything.
Why are we looking at you eating?
I heard you have a good personality.
Yes.
Then you should be considerate of the others.
I'm doing this because it might be too hard for you.
- You're worried.
- That's why I'm eating these.
This is driving me crazy.
- That looks so delicious.
- Being full doesn't matter.
Let's make an acrostic poem with the word "beef".
Go on.
I love beef.
Next is Haha.
What's wrong?
(He got eliminated on the first verse.)
- I had it all planned out.
- But the start was...
I had it all planned out.
The start was too terrible.
(That was enough.)
I didn't want to hear more.
I will do something else.
- Please give me the word.
- I don't want to listen to it.
- Please.
- So.
Bye, water strider.
Bye, hedgehog.
- Ki.
- Let's go, Ki Sung Yueng!
What's wrong?
(He opened a new age of an acrostic poem.)
I did it.
"I love beef. Bye, water strider."
It's cooked.
- Medium-rare is perfect.
- Oh, gosh.
Why do we have to watch him eat?
- That looks amazing.
- I'm starting to feel bad.
I'm happy just by looking at him.
Does it taste good?
Is it amazing?
(It smells fantastic.)
Do you have to make that face?
Why are you doing that?
Aren't we a team?
What are you doing?
Why are you teasing us?
You even closed your eyes.
Only if it wasn't Seok Jin after me.
I would leave some meat if it wasn't Seok Jin's turn after me.
I'll have to finish everything.
- What do you mean?
- Do you have something against me?
Would you leave some if it was Haha after you?
I would.
- What about for me?
- Of course I would.
- What about me?
- Not for you.
(Not for you.)
Of course not.
Why do you even ask?
Stop cooking.
Are you going to put more?
(The beef is almost gone.)
- Should I stop?
- You don't have to do this for me.
What are you saying?
That was it. He's a nice man.
He was grilling them for us all.
He's grilling them for us.
- He won't eat them all.
- Of course not.
Of course not.
I needed some protein.
(It's yummy.)
How can he make that face?
(The beef must be very sour.)
This is unbelievable.
He's so cruel.
(He opened his eyes to beef.)
How can he do that?
(Appreciating the flavour)
This is amazing.
Are you going to stop now?
No.
- There's nothing left.
- It's almost gone.
There's nothing left.
There are eight pieces left.
(Eight pieces left)
Each of us will get two pieces.
Do you want a piece?
Me?
It'll be my turn next.
What makes you think that you'll get to eat?
Seok Jin rarely gets this good result in games.
I came in second place after a long time.
But I don't think I'll get to eat.
Seok Jin won't get to eat after all.
Exactly.
He was happy when he came in second place.
I'm sure he'll never get angry.
(Seok Jin will not get angry.)
You're right.
Why do I never get to eat?
- Are you getting hungry?
- Seriously.
Why do I never get to eat?
(One of the last pieces goes onto the grill.)
No way.
- He won't do this.
- Fine. Finish it.
- No way.
- Finish it.
Jong Kook, finish it all.
Sir, finish it.
Sir Kim Jong Kook, calm down.
Jong Kook.
- Calm down.
- Jong Kook, eat them all.
- Jong Kook, finish them.
- He won't.
- Calm down.
- No way.
(What will happen to the remaining three pieces?)
(One of them is gone.)
(Are you really doing this?)
There are two pieces left.
(One of the two is gone.)
How could you...
(There's nothing left for me now.)
(The last piece)
(Seok Jin)
(It's not over yet.)
He'll cut it for you.
I will.
- Really?
- I was about to.
Okay.
Can you not cut it into three pieces?
I knew it.
Is that it?
It's fat.
Excuse me. What are you doing?
(He's cutting the fat out.)
This is not what the game is about.
I'm such a loyal man.
(Jong Kook finished all the meat for his team members.)
Let's move onto the next.
Can we eat what you left?
It's my turn.
(Seok Jin did taste the meat after all.)
We have five hours left.
(The remaining time)
I saved some time.
I feel great.
All right.
Will you use a chance now?
We should.
- We should.
- We have only two places left.
We have to visit 2 more places and we have 2 chances left.
Let's complete our mission in Ganghwado first.
And use the two remaining chances there.
- We can use two.
- That's right.
Let's go.
- Let's have some good food there.
- Let's go.
- Let's go there first.
If we use the 2 chances there, we could skip 1 place.
That's a great idea. I'm so full.
We'll eat eel soon.
(Meanwhile, Gary and Ji Hyo...)
Ladies and gentlemen.
We arrived at Jeju International Airport.
(Wait.)
(The sky is...)
(full of dark clouds.)
Jejudo is having the coldest winter in 32 years.
The heavy snow has blocked most of the roads...
and there have been many power failures.
All roads in Mount Halla are blocked.
(We're doomed.)
(There will be no romance in Jejudo.)
(Disappointed)
I didn't expect this.
Me neither.
- This is not right.
- Before we left,
the weather was fantastic.
It was great before we left.
It's freezing!
(Welcome to the frozen island.)
It's even colder than Seoul.
The wind is so cold.
It's snowing. Look.
- It's snowing.
- It really is.
It's snowing in Jejudo.
My goodness.
(How can this happen?)
It's snowing in Jejudo.
- Is it here?
- It's here. I've been here.
(They arrived at the eel restaurant in Ganghwado.)
This place is amazing.
I recommended this place.
I've been here a couple of times.
(Recommended by Seok Jin, an eel restaurant in Ganghwado)
I recommended this place.
It'll be amazing.
This place is great.
How much time do we have?
We have 4 hours and 20 minutes.
- With that little time left,
- We should hurry.
This will be our last place.
Let's eat.
Give us the food.
- We have an option here too.
- We have an option.
For this place,
- "Staff".
- What is it?
All the staff who came here,
including your cameramen will eat together.
Until they're finished,
you can't leave this place.
We were going to stop here anyway.
We were going to stop here.
- Four hours is enough.
- It's enough time.
(Four hours would be enough time for everyone to enjoy the food.)
For you to move onto the next place,
the staff have to be finished.
It's no problem.
- Eat as much as you want.
- You can do that.
One of the cameramen will get married this week.
He needs to eat a lot.
(He needs to eat a lot.)
- We are such big-eaters.
- How many eels would we have?
Is she a relative of yours by any chance?
- No, she isn't.
- Wait.
Do I have a big nose?
"Do I have a big nose?"
Do you remember me?
Is this place related to Seok Jin?
- Never.
He's our regular customer.
I come here often.
Before you start,
have some eel extract.
- Sure.
- Thank you.
- I love eel.
- Yes!
- Thank you.
- It's good for your health.
- Indeed.
You never gave this to me before.
I don't really need this.
(Laughing)
Don't lie.
I already have...
to much stamina.
It's not like I can show it to you.
(Drinking the extract)
I won't be able to sleep tonight.
No one leaves anything.
It's Gary.
It's a video call.
- Gary.
- Guys.
Guys.
It's colder here than in Seoul.
It's snowing here.
It's snowing.
(Hilarious)
- What?
- It's snowing.
(Will you be back tonight?)
Ji Hyo, how is it there?
The sun has already set.
Look at the sky.
It's covered with dark clouds.
I think the flight will be cancelled.
No, it won't.
See you later.
We won't be back tonight.
No, we'll see you guys later.
- We won't see you.
- We won't.
Bye.
(Even the weather is cooperative.)
- Bye.
- We won't see you tonight.
- Gary is smiling.
- Look at Gary.
It's nice.
- He was smiling the whole time.
- I've never seen him happier.
This is great.
(Will this trip bring romance to their relationship?)
They have made it to Ganghwado at least.
They made it in time.
Let's get back as soon as possible.
I'm more worried about our punishment.
Kwang Soo wrote "collecting insects" for me.
As kids, we even ate grasshoppers.
I can still eat them.
- Can you?
- Yes.
- Really?
- They're tasty.
And you're scared of them?
I just can't touch them.
Then again, you can be scared of pigs even if you can eat them.
Exactly.
You can be scared of birds even if you can eat chicken.
That makes sense.
It seems to be here.
It's here. We're here.
(They arrived at the kimchi stew place in Jejudo.)
- Oh, I remember this place.
- Right?
Let's go.
(They came all the way to Jeju Island for kimchi stew.)
Thank you.
Look.
Hello.
(Recommended by Haha, kimchi stew in Jejudo)
We're here to try...
your kimchi stew.
You've come a long way.
For this place,
you chose option "Seven Boxes".
I think I know what it is.
I think, in those boxes...
are tools for us to eat with.
You have to eat with the tools in the boxes.
Choose a box you'd like.
Which do you want?
I'll take number our.
- Number four?
- Yes.
(Gary chose number four.)
Thank you. I'll just send one picture.
Here.
It didn't feel good when I picked it up.
Really?
I don't feel anything.
(It feels light.)
I recommend number six.
Okay, I'll pick number six.
(If it's a toothpick and teaspoon...)
- Got it.
- Here.
- Here. In 1, 2, 3.
- Gary, first.
(What did they choose?)
In 1, 2, 3.
This isn't bad!
But it's hot.
It's okay. I'm good at using chopsticks.
(I'm good at using chopsticks.)
Ji Hyo, please open yours.
(She got measuring spoons.)
In order to eat, we have to be together.
He has chopsticks and...
(Is it destiny?)
I have measuring spoons.
Let's feed each other.
- Does it taste the same?
- Yes.
(They eat with straws and measuring spoons.)
Put some side dish on top.
(They have to help each other.)
- I'll give you some meat.
- Give me meat and kimchi.
- Oh no.
- Gosh.
I dropped it.
(It's wasted.)
(He can't do anything right.)
You need a lot of help.
Why do we have to eat like this?
It's driving me nuts.
(I really want to do well today.)
- It's good for your health.
- If that's the case...
(They start eating grilled eels.)
- Oh my.
- Goodness.
It's sizzling.
- It looks good.
- It's really big.
All the staff members look...
- happy.
- They do.
(It's a good working environment.)
They look pleased.
(The eels look delicious.)
It looks amazing.
Try eating it with some greens.
- How is it?
- It's delicious.
It's amazing. It's not cooked yet.
- Gosh.
- Isn't this done?
- Put only a bit of salt.
- This is something new.
- Just salt.
(Look at me.)
Doesn't it look delicious?
(It does, doesn't it?)
(The mud eel has such rich flavour.)
- You can eat this.
- Try it.
How is it?
It tastes fantastic with greens.
(It's tasty.)
It tastes different with different sauces.
(Thank you, Seok Jin.)
This is so tasty.
This is the highlight of the day.
Gosh.
Shouldn't we give him a round of applause?
- Gosh.
- Thanks.
(Good job, Seok Jin.)
This is great.
Didn't I tell you?
- Everyone's clapping.
- Gosh.
(It's the first time in six years he gets applauded.)
- I wish Seok Jin pays the bill.
- Yes.
(I don't get upset nor do I pay the bill.)
Let's give a comment.
Eel,
what shall I do?
where have you been?
That's great.
Eel,
how will I sleep?
(Eel, how will I sleep?)
(Eels make you sleepless at night.)
How will I sleep?
What can I do?
Eel, are you kidding?
Gosh, what shall I do?
(Are you kidding? What shall I do?)
(Two staff members are still eating.)
Hey, Gwon Yeol.
Gwon Yeol.
Congratulations on your marriage. But shouldn't you stop eating?
Well,
they're married men.
Good luck tonight!
(Good luck tonight!)
This is amazing.
What could be more amazing is...
(It's time to pick a chance.)
- If we pick...
- Yes?
an eraser chance, there will be no penalty. Am I right?
- Is that right?
- Yes.
- That'd be perfect.
- It'll be a perfect ending.
I really want to see Ji Hyo and Gary appear on "We Got Married".
- I really want to see that.
- Yes, really.
(They still want Ji Hyo and Gary to get the penalty.)
I feel like we were destined to meet each other.
- Ji Hyo.
- You have a chopstick...
and I have a spoon.
Get a spoonful of rice. I'll give you some side dish.
(They are already shooting "We Got Married".)
Why couldn't we have met earlier?
We finally meet in Jejudo.
Would we have been closer if we met earlier?
- Eat your meal.
- Okay.
(Eat your meal, Gary.)
(Don't say things like that at a dinner table.)
This is hard.
(Do you want some meat?)
I'll eat it myself.
You eat yours.
(She's mad.)
Gosh...
I have to suck the rice that gets inside the straws.
(I have to eat them later.)
(I don't want to know.)
- Do you want kimchi?
- Yes.
Are you eating slowly on purpose to miss your flight?
- Miss our flight?
- What time is it?
(Are you trying to miss your flight?)
I wasn't even thinking about getting on the plane.
- What time is it?
- Let's go to another restaurant.
I know a place...
(What are you talking about?)
I know a place in Seogwipo...
that's famous for whole chicken soup.
It's near...
- a beach.
- Hey.
It's eight. We have to eat quickly.
We have enough time.
The plane is at 9:30, so we can leave here at 9:30, right?
(We can leave here at 9:30, can't we?)
(This place isn't right by the airport.)
We should leave here at 8:40.
(Ji Hyo takes Gary's hand.)
(She puts a ring on his finger.)
(It's a measuring spoon ring.)
Is this an engagement ring?
What are you talking about?
You...
(You...)
You played me for six years like this.
(Oh goodness)
Are you going to do this to Chen Bolin?
You...
What do you mean I played you?
This is the first time...
a girl gave me a ring.
It's a ring from the measuring spoons.
Anyway, I've never received a ring before.
- Really?
- This is the first time.
This fits perfectly on your pinky.
(It fits perfectly on your pinky.)
Are you trying to figure out my ring size?
(Are you trying to figure out my ring size?)
My gosh.
It's 13.
(A romantic relationship starts in Jejudo.)
Gary, it's a crab!
I got one in Dubai!
- Isn't it pretty?
- The shell looks like you.
(Is it the real "We Got Married"?)
- Hey.
- Stop!
(Married? No, it's a fight!)
(It's trouble in the desert.)
- It's a desert.
- Gosh.
It's endless.
(An exciting adventure in the desert)
(Running Man goes to Dubai.)
- This is cool.
- It's amazing.
- Isn't it cool?
- Yes.
This is really cool.
I've never eaten so much before.
Seriously.
It'll take four hours...
to get to Muan.
That's not going to work.
You have two remaining chances.
And there are four left that you can pick from.
- Are there four left?
- There is an eraser,
- Okay.
- delivery,
avatar and the ability to switch menus.
Delivery...
- won't work.
- No, it won't.
- That's out of the question.
- It won't work.
You can't send an avatar...
- all the way to Muan.
- Right.
- It won't work.
If you pick the eraser chance...
- and don't go to Muan,
- We'd erase it.
- then you all win.
- Okay.
- It'll be done.
- It makes me sad for some reason.
Okay, then regardless of...
- Hey, then let's...
- I'm talking here.
(I'm talking here.)
- Are you mad?
- No.
- I think you are this time.
- Really.
- I think he is.
- He's mad.
- I saw him get mad.
Nobody could stand this situation.
- You should go ahead.
- No, it's okay.
- Go ahead.
- No, it's fine.
- You should go first.
- Really?
Go ahead, Seok Jin.
Then I'll go.
- Okay, so...
- Do you have an idea?
- You go ahead.
- What I'm saying is...
- we need to...
- I just remembered.
- We need to...
- Okay, I got it.
Are you angry?
I'm not angry.
- I understand.
- Do you?
I understand. You just thought of something.
- Go ahead.
- I thought of something.
Let's leave it up to chance.
- Okay.
- Let's leave it up to luck.
- Let's go by the rules.
- Okay.
- Let's go if we have to.
- All right.
(Out of 4, 2 are duds.)
What would be a good pick?
Shouldn't there be 2? Why are there 4?
Gary has to be chosen, correct?
(Seok Jin chooses.)
- If we pick eraser, we all win.
- Right.
- That's right.
- Then it'll be over.
I don't think that's it.
(What...)
(will it...)
(be?)
It's a switch chance.
He can pick another one.
- That's right.
- I'll try.
- I'll do it.
- You go ahead.
(Kwang Soo will pick.)
Why are the unlucky two picking?
- Jae Seok.
- Are you lucky?
Let's get the eraser chance this time.
Get the eraser, Jae Seok.
(Jae Seok will pick.)
- Okay.
- Are you the lucky one?
Guys, go back to your seats.
(Go back to your seats.)
- I almost believed you.
- You're not lucky.
(Seok Jin, Kwang Soo and Jae Seok are all unlucky.)
- You aren't lucky.
- Come on.
- Gosh.
- Let's see who's the unlucky one.
- You don't have much luck, too.
- Let's see who's the most unlucky.
(It's all up to Haha.)
We will all pick one. Those will be the bad ones.
- One at a time.
- Okay.
- You two pick first.
I'll make the final choice and open it.
- All right.
- We are the unlucky ones.
- I picked that one.
- I'll pick the bad one.
- We'll get rid of the bad ones.
- Okay.
- This is it.
This is the final one, okay?
- Okay.
- That's the final choice.
- What will it be?
- We need the eraser chance.
The eraser chance shouldn't be on this one.
(Who has the eraser chance?)
- Delivery.
- Look at this.
- Do you see how unlucky I am?
- Gosh.
- What did I tell you?
- Oh goodness.
I knew it all along.
- Look how unlucky I am.
- Let's do this.
- We need to deliver it.
- As long as this isn't eraser.
- Right.
- It shouldn't be eraser.
If you did pick eraser, then you're really unlucky.
You might as well be the unluckiest person in the world.
Let's cross our fingers.
If he picked eraser...
(Will he be the unluckiest guy alive or become a hero?)
It can't be.
(Everything rests on Kwang Soo.)
(Please. Please.)
- Eraser.
- It's eraser. Goodness.
Eraser, really?
You ruined everything.
Kwang Soo, you are really unlucky.
How could you pick the most important one?
You picked the delivery chance,
and you're telling me I'm unlucky because I picked the eraser?
This is nothing.
- You are no different than me.
- It's just...
- a step back.
- In this situation he means.
- You really have the worst luck.
- In that situation.
- I really have bad luck...
- You're just bad luck.
but you have the worst luck.
(Worst luck ever)
What's this?
Avatar?
That allows for a person in Muan,
or you could send a person to Muan and if the person...
finishes the small octopus of Muan in three hours, you succeed.
I don't know anyone in Muan.
- No one in Muan.
- I don't know anyone in Muan.
Or you could use the switch chance.
- So there are two valid options.
- Since I picked it earlier on?
Let's use the switch chance.
We can call someone that lives in Ganghwado Island.
- Do you know someone?
- Yes.
You do?
- I know the owner of a pension.
- In Ganghwado Island?
- Really?
- Yes.
- Call the person.
- Okay.
Call the pension owner.
Call the pension owner and if the person...
- Ask about the best restaurant.
- It will be in Ganghwado Island.
- Right?
- He's a pension owner here.
- All right.
- Ask him.
The problem is...
what if he recommends Ganghwado eel?
- No way.
- We need to eat it then.
We need to eat it.
We need to avoid the penalty.
That's true.
I hope he picks up.
Hello.
I'm in Ganghwado Island right now.
(I'm in Ganghwado Island right now.)
Ganghwado Island?
Is there any restaurant that you recommend?
The restaurants are closed at this hour.
- It's all right. We can go quick.
- Recommend a place for us.
Anything simple like ramyeon.
Desert is fine too.
- A convenience store perhaps?
- Like sherbet.
A famous convenience store.
Something like persimmon or rice punch.
(We hope you get the idea.)
I heard that Ganghwado Island...
- is famous for ice cream.
- You're right.
Ginseng ice cream.
- Byeong Soo.
- Yes.
You get the point, right?
(You get the point, right?)
- Talk quietly.
- All right.
- You're our last hope.
- Really.
- Ready?
- Yes.
Is there a nice place to enjoy something light?
In 1, 2, 3.
How about pork cutlet?
- Pork cutlet.
- What?
- He said pork cutlet.
- Pork cutlet.
Ask him about the name of the restaurant.
What's the name of the restaurant?
It's pork cutlet.
- Pork cutlet.
- Then we will go there.
Is he affiliated with the place?
It's famous for giving big portions.
(It's famous for giving big portions.)
(A bolt from the blue)
- That can't be.
- Goodness.
- My goodness.
- All right, Byeong Soo.
I'm so full.
- I don't think I can eat any more.
- I thought this was the last place.
Me too.
- At least...
- What are we going to do?
How are we going to finish it?
- I'm so full.
- Same here.
We should have picked the exemption option.
How could Kwang Soo pick that?
If we picked the exemption option, we would be done already.
Then we can go home.
Kwang Soo, why did you do that?
Take a good look at yourself.
There must be something left.
- What was the last one?
- The last one...
It's Gary.
Can you see this?
- Did you get matching rings?
- What is that?
It's symbolic of our bond.
Bond?
Goodness.
- The bond between you and I
- Where are you headed?
- What happened?
- We need to go eat pork cutlet.
- We're going to another place.
We thought that it was our last place, so we ate so much.
Gary, get waxed or...
Ji Hyo collect some insects from Jejudo Island.
I'm getting annoyed.
- Stop it.
- Okay.
Don't push it.
(She has a quick temper.)
We came all the way to Jejudo Island to eat kimchi stew,
so please don't do that.
We'll succeed.
Complete the mission, all right?
- Okay.
- Have a safe trip back.
We're going to go catch the plane now.
- Okay.
- It's snowing a lot here.
Really? Then the plane might be cancelled.
Let's go already.
- All right. See you later.
- See you.
(Gary and Ji Hyo succeed the mission in Jejudo Island.)
- The plane won't get cancelled.
- It could.
- It might be.
- Let's go.
- We don't have time.
- Why?
(Jae Seok's team are on their way to Gimpo.)
Oh my goodness.
Thinking of eating pork cutlet is driving me nuts.
There might be an easy way out.
How about getting a kid's meal or something?
- All right.
- It's for you.
- Is there a kid's meal?
- Yes.
Then let's order that.
But only children are allowed to order that.
I'll play the child.
- I can pretend to be one too.
- Same here.
You have to act cute.
- We need to eat this.
- We need to.
We need to clear the mission.
But I really can't eat pork cutlet.
- Pork cutlet.
- How could he say pork cutlet?
We ate a bunch of food that doesn't go well with pork cutlet.
- Spicy seafood stew is way better.
- You're right.
- Because it's spicy.
- And we had pork cutlet already.
Since we had eel, which pairs well with spicy seafood stew.
Does the place open until late at night?
(Will it be open?)
- What if it's closed?
- What if it is?
- If it's closed, we fail.
- We fail.
We receive a penalty.
Goodness.
(I've got a bad feeling about this.)
I'm really full.
We're eating nonstop today.
- I've never eaten this much before.
- Me neither.
I thought about it before.
We're nearly there. We have 400m left.
I think so. They looked like they wanted to.
- Do we need to go further?
- It says 160m.
- We're in trouble.
- It's over there.
It looks like it gives big portions.
It's closed.
- It's closed?
- It's closed.
- It's closed. Oh, no.
- Really?
- Oh, this...
- It's closed.
- It's closed anyways.
- What are we to do?
- What should we do?
It's really closed.
It's their day off.
- Why?
- It is?
Why?
They're closed on Mondays.
What are we to do?
- This isn't good.
- Is this the place?
- It's usually open.
- What are we to do?
- We're in trouble.
- How much time do we have left?
- How can it be closed?
- Excuse me.
They're closed on Mondays.
What are we going to do?
What should we do?
Did we fail then?
(Oh, my goodness)
What are we going to do?
Did we fail then?
- There's two hours left.
- Let's call another person.
- Again.
- That person...
- Do you have anyone you know?
- Call someone you know.
- We can tell them, right?
We need to know the time.
Let's go.
I never could have guessed it was their day off.
It is.
If it's their day off...
- How could this be?
- Call another person.
- Try again, somewhere close.
- Try again.
Someone that lives in Gimpo.
- Shin Young.
- Call her.
- She lives in Gimpo?
- Shin Young lives in Gimpo.
She might be in a shoot.
(Pick up, resident of Gimpo.)
She wouldn't...
- Hello.
- Shin Young.
Hey!
- Yes.
We're in Gimpo.
You're in Gimpo?
- Yes.
- Yes, Gimpo.
- We...
- We don't have time.
We don't have much time. Could you recommend a simple dish?
Snail rice porridge.
- Snail rice porridge.
(Snail rice porridge)
Shin Young, where is that place?
- It's better than pork cutlet.
- What?
The cheonggukjang is handmade at the place...
- and they serve Korean snails.
- Really?
- The address.
- What's the address?
- We need to go there.
- Is it...
the snail rice porridge place?
- Yes.
- Snail?
- We found it.
- In Gimpo.
In Gimpo.
Gimpo Han River new town.
- Okay.
- All right.
- Shin Young, thank you.
- Thank you.
- It's over here.
- Is it Running Man?
Yes, it's Running Man.
Hello everyone.
(I'm Hong Geum Bo.)
- Hong Jin Pao.
- Thanks, Shin Young.
- You're welcome.
Wait a minute.
Let's go over there.
That's a relief.
- Thanks to Shin Young.
- In Gyeonggi province, Gimpo,
- Ojang-dong.
- Is it still open?
It's a relief.
- Really.
- Let's go.
I thought it was over.
There's not much time left.
How much time does it take?
It's 14km away.
- It's quite far away.
- Let's hurry.
It takes 40 minutes.
- 40 minutes?
- Yes.
But it's a relief.
Thanks to Shin Young.
Is it this way?
(One team is in Gimpo, while the other team is at Jeju Airport.)
- We could fail.
- Indeed.
(At 9:15pm, they arrive near the snail rice porridge place.)
Wait, we're here.
Wait, go a little further.
It looks dark though.
- It's ominous.
- There's only 100m left.
Wait, what is this?
It can't be.
It's here.
(It can't possibly be closed again.)
- What if it's closed?
- It can't be.
- It's closed.
- What?
- Really?
- It's closed?
- I can't believe this.
- It's closed.
- Really?
- It's closed?
- This can't be.
- This one is closed too?
- Really?
- Is it closed?
- Unbelievable.
This place is also closed?
- It's closed.
- We don't have time.
- It's only 9pm.
- Hey.
- It's closed.
- What?
- Really? It's closed?
This can't be.
- This one is closed too?
- Yes, it is.
We don't have time.
- It's only 9pm.
- Hey.
Let's call Shin Young again.
- We have an hour left...
- What's this?
We have an hour.
- This one is closed too?
- It's driving me mad.
What is this?
I need to call Shin Young again.
You got to be kidding me.
Just tell her that we're on the way to her house.
We should go to her house instead.
Since this is Gimpo,
- there should be another place.
- Shin Young should know.
- We don't have much time left.
- Hey.
We'll have to ask Shin Young again.
- Shin Young.
- Yes.
Unfortunately, the restaurant is closed.
- Oh, no.
- Nine minutes has passed.
Shin Young,
- would there be any place open?
- We don't have much time left.
- In Janggi-dong,
- Yes.
- there's a dumpling restaurant.
- Dumpling?
- A dumpling restaurant?
- Yes.
- They serve dumplings.
- Would they be open?
I guess.
What's the name of the restaurant?
Sam Dumplings.
Sam Dumplings?
They serve handmade dumplings.
- I found it.
- We found it.
Shin Young.
- Thank you.
- Sam...
- Handmade Dumplings.
- Thank you.
- If things don't turn out well,
we might go to your place.
(She laughs hysterically.)
- Janggi-dong.
- All right.
Thank you.
- Good luck.
- Thank you.
- I think they'll be open.
- It's located over there.
- We have to move again.
- Gosh.
- What are we doing?
How much time do we have left?
Every restaurant is closed.
I can't believe this.
- It's 3.2km away.
- It's quite close.
- Let's hurry.
- We don't have a lot of time.
(The dumpling restaurant is 3.2km away.)
It'll only take 10 minutes to get there.
And dumplings can be served right away.
That's right.
Dumplings are easy to eat as well.
We can have just one each.
Gosh.
(At 9:25pm, they are heading to the dumpling restaurant.)
- It should be around here.
- It should be here.
Where is it?
- Please.
- We don't have a lot of time.
I see a sign that has dumplings.
- There?
- It says dumplings.
- It's here.
- They're open!
We got this.
- Is it here?
- They're open.
- Let's go.
- They won't close.
- Is it really here?
- Let's go.
Is it here?
- Is it here?
- It's here.
I don't think it's here.
Wait.
It's not here.
- What was the name again?
- Sam something.
It's not here.
It's that one over there.
- Are they closed?
- It's here.
Wait.
- Are they closed?
- Call and ask her again.
(No way!)
She said they open until late.
- It's closed?
- It looks like it.
It's here.
It was this place.
Gosh.
What's going on? Is this some kind of prank?
Is it a prank?
- Is Shin Young a spy?
- She said they were open.
All of them are closed.
From the pork cutlet place.
- I can't believe this.
- It's closed.
- It's dark.
- It's over.
- Really? Is it closed?
- I can't believe this.
- This place is also closed?
- Yes, it is.
We don't have enough time.
It's only 9pm. Why are they closed?
We should hurry up.
Ask her again.
Let's find a place within walking distance.
- Hello?
- Shin Young.
- They're closed again.
- What are you thinking?
- Shin Young, sorry.
- You...
Don't be like that. Shin Young.
They're closed again.
Shin Young, we see a hamburger restaurant.
- Shin Young.
- Let us go there.
- Jae Seok.
- Yes.
- I'll hang up.
- Shin Young.
- Please don't.
- Don't hang up.
- Let's do this.
- Please tell us where to go.
- Shin Young.
- Within walking distance.
A castella place.
- Great!
- Nice!
(That sounds nice!)
There's a castella place.
Okay.
- Would they be open?
- I'm sure they're open.
- Okay.
- They have to pay a high rent.
To make ends meet,
they have to close late.
- I found it.
- We found it, Shin Young.
We found it. Thank you, Shin Young.
- Let's hurry.
- Thank you, Shin Young.
(They're headed to a bakery now.)
- Let's go.
- Let's hurry.
We're running out of time.
- Where's our car?
- Seok Jin.
- How can we get there?
- Go straight.
(At 9:35pm, they are heading to a bakery.)
How can this be possible? Every restaurant is closed.
It's only 9:30pm.
What are we doing?
- Gosh.
- Seriously.
- We have to succeed.
- I'm determined.
I'm determined this time.
We thought we had enough time.
We wasted so much time.
- I think it's around here.
- We're almost there.
- Go straight.
- It must be on this street.
- I think it's on the left side.
- It's there.
- We're here!
- We made it!
We're here. It's open!
(If they're open, they'll easily complete their mission.)
- It's open!
- We're here.
- It's dark inside.
- They're closed.
- Really?
This is impossible.
- Are they closed, too?
- Yes, they are.
- Really?
- Yes.
Really?
- They're closed.
- This is crazy.
She said there's another place across the street.
- She said something.
- Are they really closed?
- Yes.
- How can this be possible?
This is unbelievable.
- Are they really closed?
- They are.
- She said they were open.
- I'm going crazy.
- I can't believe this.
- Gosh.
Nothing's working out.
Are they really closed?
Or why don't we ask Shin Young...
to search for a place near here?
- A dessert shop or something.
- This is unbelievable.
Shin Young must be stressed too.
There's something here.
- Hello?
- Shin Young.
- It's closed.
- Shin Young, they're closed, too.
- We're running out of time.
- Then try this place.
Which one?
Which building?
It's across the street.
Across the street?
It's over there.
Okay. On the first floor?
Okay. Shin Young,
- you sound tired.
- Her voice is very low.
(Shin Young is getting tired of helping them.)
Shin Young, we're sorry. We'll make sure to find the place.
- Thank you.
- Let's run.
It must be over there.
I'll find it.
(We're in a hurry!)
Excuse me.
It's around here.
(They have to run now.)
Did you find it?
- Did you find it?
- Run, hurry.
I'll find it.
- They're closed.
- Not again.
Really? Are they closed?
I can't believe this.
- This place is closed as well?
- Is it closed?
We don't have enough time.
Our flight would have been cancelled if we had gotten here a bit earlier.
What?
I think they failed.
I have a feeling.
I'm getting stressed.
(Will we be penalised?)
- It's snowing here too.
- It's snowing.
I'm already worried about the penalty.
I have a feeling they failed.
(What will be waiting for Gary and Ji Hyo?)
I think they failed.
They're coming.
(Through the snow storm,)
(they're finally back.)
Gary.
- Good job.
- If it had started snowing earlier,
the flight would have been cancelled.
- Really?
- Yes.
The flight could have been cancelled.
We barely made it.
(By the way...)
I get the feeling they failed.
(Will they have a happy ending?)
I hope we didn't come all the way here to get penalised.
(What will be awaiting them?)
(By the way...)
I get the feeling they failed.
(Will they have a happy ending?)
I hope we didn't come all the way here to get penalised.
(What will be awaiting them?)
Run. It's this way.
I'll find it.
- It's this way.
- Let's go.
(We have to make it this time.)
Have you found it?
(Will they succeed this time?)
- It's here!
- We found it!
- It's here.
They're open. They're closing up.
They're closing up.
(Did they really find it?)
Did you find it?
Oh, it's here.
Are you guys still open?
You're closing up? But you're still technically open, right?
When do you close?
- We close at 10pm.
- Thank you.
- We don't have much time.
- We have 13 minutes left.
We nearly failed.
Thank you.
(They're celebrating the success with cakes.)
(The taste of success)
I feel great.
Thank you.
This tastes great.
- Shin Young, thank you.
- It's kind of...
- Cheers.
- All right.
- Good job.
Good job.
Great job.
We almost failed.
If this place was closed...
and Shin Young didn't answer the phone...
(61 minutes until the deadline)
This is delicious.
(The food race is over.)
I can see why she recommended this place.
I agree.
(Mission completed)
You completed the mission.
Really?
(The prize is handed.)
- Wow, look at that.
- We made it.
- Wow.
- Look.
Are they made of gold?
Look at the colour of it.
This is a golden spoon.
If we carry this around and eat with it,
- it'll look amazing.
- That'd be cool.
- It'll look fantastic.
- This looks amazing.
- Good job.
- Thank you.
We made it!
(Team Running Man completed their mission.)
(But...)
(they had no idea what was waiting for them.)
(Dubai)
(A city with both futuristic landscapes and vast deserts)
(The flower in the desert, Dubai)
(Team Running Man in Dubai)
This will be amazing.
Can I do whatever I want?
(Mission Impossible in Dubai)
- I don't think I can do it.
- Oh my gosh!
(Only the person who tests his limit has...)
Mum!
(The right to enjoy the city)
(They will hug Dubai's sky in their arms.)
(They will adventure into the desert.)
Let's go.
It's a real desert.
It's endless.
This is Dubai.
(The extreme mission race will be held in the real desert.)
It's dangerous!
Will we sleep here?
(In the middle of the desert,)
(they will beat the odds and survive.)
(Next week, "Songs of the Sun and Sand")