(Spring special! Running Man, "All About Them")
(Running Man members reveal their true faces after 6 years.)
- Hello.
- Hello there.
(Their true selves will be unveiled.)
Jae Seok is a good person, but...
(And shocking truths about them continue to be revealed.)
(Is Yu Jae Seok truly a decent man?)
I am getting upset too.
If he had the fighting skills, he would've been more evil than me.
He would have. Yes.
Would you have accepted my love if I had confessed my feelings?
What?
- Ji Hyo.
- Ji Hyo dolled up for Gary!
(They will go on a real date and confirm each other's feelings.)
- Let's stay like this.
- I think I have butterflies.
- It's nice.
- They're sweet.
Because it was officially a date, I got a little bit nervous, but...
(They will get a scientific approval of their feelings.)
Check Gary's brain reaction when he sees Ji Hyo's picture.
You will see that there is a heart shape in the middle of his brain.
- What?
- Really?
- There is a heart?
- So does Ji Hyo really like him?
Goodness.
Hello!
(Running Man, your best choice for Sunday afternoons)
The director who had been...
- leading Running Man...
- Leading...
resigned as of last week.
- And we got a new director.
- The director has changed.
So for a new change...
- Hey.
- Yes?
Let's use this as an opportunity to bring in Joong Ki.
- What are you talking about?
- He's very popular these days.
- You never wanted him before.
- Call Joong Ki.
Can't he join us once every two weeks?
I am sorry, but...
who doesn't want him here?
- We know how great he is.
- So let's tell him and...
It's been three years since you last mentioned his name.
- I know.
- Hey.
- You never cared for him.
- One person is getting sick here.
We feel really bad too.
- He got anger management issues.
- Right.
- Joong Ki is...
- I'm so jealous.
- Now...
- He used to be the same.
You can try to have a hot body.
But you will forever be below Joong Ki's feet.
What do you mean his "feet"?
- Why should I be below him?
- You're rather like a sole pad.
- Don't say that. Kwang Soo...
- You're like the sole pad.
is close to In Sung and Joong Ki.
We always tell him that he's just a butler.
- You're a butler.
- That's too harsh.
It's the truth. Goodness.
- What are we doing today?
- I'm curious too.
You will be communicating with some of our viewers.
- Have we not been doing so well?
- I've seen the preview.
You would've seen it through SNS.
You will be satisfying the viewers' curiosities.
It's called "Running Man Q and A".
("All About Them")
(What?)
- Have the viewers asked questions?
- Yes.
(Through various social networking sites,)
(we received a total of...)
(6,271 questions.)
(The third most popular question was if Ji Hyo was really pretty.)
(The second most popular question was if Ji Hyo and Gary are in love.)
(The most popular question was if Jae Seok is a decent man.)
We sorted the questions for each member.
"When will Ji Hyo and Gary shoot 'We Got Married'?"
- Yes.
- "We Got Married".
"What are the chances of them becoming a real couple?"
- What do you think?
- They are very interested in them.
The chances are lower than that of getting hit by a lightning.
It's like the chance of Kwang Soo catching up with Joong Ki.
Why would you compare to that?
We might have more chances than that.
- Are your chances better?
- That can never happen.
We have at least a chance of one percent.
Several days ago, I went to Jong Kook's concert...
and went up on stage with Joong Ki.
- So?
- Actually, I was a little worried.
I called them out on stage, but...
I know that Kwang Soo is quite popular.
- Kwang Soo's very popular too.
- So I was afraid he'd...
be better received than Joong Ki.
That would make me feel sorry for Joong Ki.
- But I shouldn't have been worried.
- I am worried.
- He was like a normal person.
- He didn't have to worry.
After introducing Joong Ki,
I introduced Kwang Soo, and he was treated normally.
Whenever I said something, people stopped laughing.
(Frozen)
And when Joong Ki started to speak again...
- But...
- And for Joong Ki, they prepared...
- They prepared something nice.
- a pretty box to cover his face.
- It was like Primary's.
- Yes.
But they made me wear a black plastic bag.
Here we go.
(They gave the top star a special treatment.)
All right. Here we go.
Hello, everyone.
- Yes, I am a gentle person.
- Yes.
- Should we walk forward?
- Sure.
(Hot for Joong Ki, but cold for Kwang Soo)
(Kwang Soo was humiliated.)
Joong Ki is a man with a sense of loyalty.
- He's loyal.
- What do you mean? I was there too!
This is the next question.
"If you could switch bodies with another member, who would it be?"
What about you, Kwang Soo?
(I don't really have anyone.)
- Who?
- I want to be Ji Hyo.
Why?
He's a pervert.
- What?
- Why aren't you answering?
- Why?
- He's a sly man, isn't he?
- Ji Hyo is offended.
- Where are you going?
- You...
- It's not what you think.
- Hey!
- It's not like that.
- Ji Hyo is upset.
- What did I do wrong?
- Ji Hyo!
- Ji Hyo's face is so funny.
- You're funny.
- She's very offended.
- Why...
- Tell us the reason then.
Explain yourself.
I don't want to.
(Only he knows the truth.)
Okay. Okay.
- I don't need to answer that.
- He just said it for no reason.
- I want to be Jong Kook.
- Why?
I want to be Jong Kook, and eat instant noodles...
and burgers. I will destroy his body in just a month.
I will make his chest sag all the way to the floor.
When you stop exercising all of a sudden, your muscles sag.
- Really.
- Yes.
I'd like to become Jae Seok...
and curse everyone I see.
I'll spit everywhere too.
- And smoke like this.
- And when kids come,
- I will say, "Get lost!"
- "Get away from me!"
To the security guard, I will say, "What?"
I want to be Jae Seok too. I will go clubbing all the time.
I will go clubbing and dance dirtily.
- And I'll grind on the girls.
- Okay.
- I will get 100 girls' numbers.
- Okay!
Do whatever you want with my body!
Use my body!
- How about you, Seok Jin?
- I just like being myself.
No, no. The question is, "Who eats the most?"
(He's given a new question.)
Come on.
- It's a new question.
- You didn't even tell me that.
- It's all about the flow.
- You're right.
- The flow wasn't right.
- There are too many questions.
- I need to keep it flowing.
- We don't have time.
- I am so confused.
- We don't have time for everything.
Now, we picked...
the most popular questions and the questions...
that need to be answered.
- Is that right?
- That's amazing.
- Okay.
- It's going to be fun.
- This is...
- Really.
(We'll begin now.)
- I'm nervous.
- Let's enjoy it, Ji Hyo.
Do you want to see what normal couples do?
(If they really went on a date,)
I think he would feel the same as I do.
(will they realise their true feelings?)
Through MRI scans, we will check their real feelings.
There have been many studies. You will see that...
there is a heart shape in the middle of their brains.
(We will not reveal their true feelings!)
Today, we will be communicating with our viewers.
That is what today will be about.
They might hope to see us acting lively as usual...
Should we show them?
- Where?
- How can we show them here?
So will you two fight?
Yes. Let's have a one-on-one match here and show them.
- Rip my clothes, but not my flesh.
- We can go there.
- Okay? Don't rip my flesh.
- Of course.
Give it time to heal.
Seriously. Here we have...
- some questions.
- Let's see some.
No way.
(What is the truth behind Ji Hyo and Gary?)
- I am very curious.
- I want to know as well.
- What is the truth?
- We are curious too.
- We are really curious.
- I want to know too.
- Actually...
- We don't know either.
Let's sort this out.
- We're so curious.
- Just say yes or no.
Right. Tell us now.
- I am so curious.
- I want to know the answer.
- That's right.
- We're also curious.
Can I be honest about my feelings towards you?
These two agreed to be a couple on Mondays.
- Right.
- They're the Monday Couple.
- That's good news.
- Yes, so the two...
- It's Monday, so...
- On Mondays, Gary is mine.
If I had asked you out then, would you have said yes?
(Will "All About That Couple" give us answers?)
I want you, Kang Gary!
- What are you doing?
- Hey, Ji Hyo.
(Their actions have confused the viewers numerous times.)
(They are the most skilled at playing with the viewers' hearts.)
Ji Hyo.
- Is this all real?
- I'm curious too.
- We don't know either.
- Frankly, we don't know.
We think that...
since six years have passed...
- Let's get the facts straight.
- I need it too.
- Tell us if it's true or not.
- Yes, you can tell us now.
- I just want to ask one question.
- They're confused too.
When you're shooting this programme, you must feel a certain emotion.
Have you ever developed a particular feeling for each other?
- Did you feel anything?
- Yes, that's right.
- Sincerely.
- Not as a colleague.
- Even the slightest emotions.
- Should they say at the same time?
- Actually,
- we're playing a certain role.
- Answer yes or no.
- One, two... Yes or no.
In 1, 2 and 3.
(How will they answer?)
(The investigation will begin.)
It's Gary's house.
I'm told to go on a date all of a sudden.
It's been so long since I've gone on one. I don't know where to go.
Since it's nearly dinner time...
Is he looking up places to go?
- He must be excited.
- I made a reservation.
- Really?
- I should look things up.
- He's great.
- Don't you go where you usually go?
I think the chef's name was Choi Hyun Seok.
I think he has a restaurant somewhere.
(Luxurious first date)
If we go to a famous chef's restaurant,
I'm sure women will really enjoy their time there...
But is this all really necessary just for Ji Hyo?
- He seems a bit haughty.
- I'd like to make a reservation.
He's wondering if this is necessary.
- It's his charm.
- Is six o'clock all right?
He is truly charming.
Okay, then we'll be there by six. Thank you.
- He prepared a lot.
- I know.
I've never made reservations like this ever in my life.
Women might find that attractive.
Is that his dressing room?
I should change.
- Goodness.
- Amazing.
- Oh, my.
- He's definitely a star.
He's a star.
It looks like a celebrity's house.
Gary is a celebrity, indeed.
- I can't show my house now.
- Look at his hats.
My room can't be compared to that.
- Look at his clothes.
- When did he buy that many?
- Which one...
- Why do you have so many?
- There so much clothes.
- There are only toys in my house.
(His biggest worry is choosing what to wear.)
Which one...
Did you wear a hat or style your hair?
Will it be cold?
I didn't wear a cap but a fedora.
I only wear this watch twice a year.
(He wears a luxurious watch on his wrist.)
I'll cut the meat like this.
He wears that watch only three times a year.
Isn't this Dok2's house?
Did he sponsor you his house?
Because of this date...
(He puts on a golden necklace.)
Oh, my.
(Embarrassed)
Did I really need to wear all that just because of her?
- I know you like it.
- Who does she think she is?
Who does she think she is?
I need to act macho once.
It suits you.
You look like a little gentleman.
(Ji Hyo, I'm on my way.)
- Ji Hyo.
- He looks handsome.
- He looks great.
- I know how anxious he'd feel.
- It's a beauty parlour.
- It's a salon.
- It's Ji Hyo's salon.
- It's Ji Hyo's.
Ji Hyo, did you put makeup on for Gary?
(Embarrassed)
- Hey, you.
- You put makeup on for Gary.
- She's preparing to flirt with him.
- She is.
- You are quite something.
- Oh, my.
- She looks girly.
- She wants to impress him.
Really.
- What is she wearing?
- She wants to knock him out.
Does Ji Hyo wear those styles?
I'm looking more like a girl now.
You know, she looks fit to be a bride.
Really.
- It's my first time wearing that.
- You rarely wear makeup...
But...
do people usually dress up like this for a date?
Of course.
Actually, this is ordinary.
Is that so?
Is this normal?
It's quite...
embarrassing to dress up like this and meeting...
Gary alone.
(Shy)
I think I'm nervous.
Are you nervous?
I must be.
Did you say that you're nervous?
- Did you say you were nervous?
- I heard her.
- Oh, my.
- But...
I want to see them on a date.
A woman needs to wear make-up.
(She realises this.)
- This is the main part.
- It's what the viewers want to see.
- They're curious.
- This is the main part.
- Really.
- It's making me nervous.
- Oh, my.
- My goodness.
Men are a bit...
(Dazzling)
- Oh, my.
- She put on make-up for Gary.
- She's preparing to flirt.
- She is, indeed.
- It's possible.
- She looks pretty.
- It looks like a photo-shoot.
- Thank you.
Isn't it too unfair for Gary?
That's why I put on my accessories.
(She's about to meet him.)
- Oh, my.
- My goodness.
Ji Hyo. You really look like a bride.
Should I walk like a girl?
- Of course.
- No.
I like her style.
- She even has a handbag.
- Yes.
What is it?
(It's the 6-year-old Monday Couple's first date ever.)
(What will their first greeting be?)
- Gary.
- We're wearing matching hats.
It's so awkward!
(Beware of the awkwardness.)
It's exciting.
It's making me embarrassed.
We're wearing matching hats. Gary.
- I don't usually do this.
- Don't...
do this.
- I've never done this before.
- This doesn't suit me.
- I'm wearing make-up today.
- It's so embarrassing.
- Fine.
- Watch your head.
(He shows his escorting charisma.)
Did he really do that?
Isn't that what the police do when they put a criminal in their car?
- I was in a rush.
- He squished my hat.
(He was so tense.)
- It's nice, though.
- They look great together.
It's spring for them.
When the spring breeze blows
It's making me nervous.
- Really.
- It's making me very nervous.
This is interesting.
They told me to dress up for you today.
So I went to the salon to put make-up on.
What's the occasion?
This is fun.
Isn't this the first time...
we meet alone?
It's not even Monday today.
- You're right. It's not Monday.
- I know.
(Like a real couple, they're on a weekend date.)
What is the occasion?
Oh, my. You're wearing full make-up.
I put on make-up and did my hair.
- What are we going to do today?
- I don't know.
Did you eat yet?
No, so I made a reservation.
You even made a reservation?
I'm embarrassed, Ji Hyo.
I was so embarrassed I couldn't tell you.
You even made a reservation?
Yes, well... Somewhere...
I don't think our relationship requires us to make reservations.
I know. We're completely fine with eating gukbap.
But I automatically began searching the web today.
They're going to the restaurant now.
(Arrived)
We're here.
Wait, Ji Hyo.
Don't get off yet, okay?
(He is such a gentleman.)
- Oh, my.
- Gary, do you...
usually do that in real life?
- No.
- You don't, right?
Hey!
Open the door.
(What is he doing?)
I'm sorry.
I've never done this before.
My goodness.
I had to unlock it beforehand.
You had to unlock it.
But you know, you can win over a woman if you do that for two years.
It doesn't even take two years.
- Where is it?
- Over here.
- Wow!
- Is it a room?
(The special dining place that Gary prepared for today)
You two look too awkward.
- Gary, this is...
- Do we?
It looks like we're on a blind date.
It's so awkward having to eat at a place like this with you.
- It's all good experience.
- Since we're here,
let's have fun.
Of course.
(He gets up.)
(He continues to act like a gentleman.)
- He's doing it again.
- I've never done that before.
- You're great.
- You look natural.
(Laughing)
Did you just do this for me?
- Of course.
- Thank you.
She seems to enjoy it, though.
(Embarrassed)
- She's smiling a lot.
- Ji Hyo,
here's a flower that looks like you.
(Here's a flower that looks like you.)
Gosh, his comment...
What is he saying?
Here's a flower that looks like you.
All right.
If it were in the past, I would have said it more naturally.
Why do we need to eat here?
Why did you reserve this place?
This is really awkward. Is this the bell?
(Is this the bell?)
Why did you say that?
- I saw it for the first time.
- Since we're here,
- let's enjoy our meal.
- Then is it a bomb?
It was just way too awkward.
But that's making me more interested.
- I'm nervous.
- Here's the menu.
- Is this the menu?
- Yes.
(The waiter gives them a fancy menu.)
- We have a special course menu.
- Okay.
I'll take your order when you're ready.
What do pretty ladies usually order?
Gary, it's 110 dollars.
(Oh my goodness.)
Why do you care about the price?
(Ji Hyo, don't worry about that.)
Ji Hyo...
He's showing off.
Ji Hyo,
you don't have to worry about the price.
The manager is here.
Just eat.
- I'll have tenderloin.
- Tenderloin, it is.
How would you like your tenderloin?
It should be like...
Ji Hyo's lips...
(It should be like Ji Hyo's lips?)
(Smiling)
- You shouldn't have said that.
- It's embarrassing.
(It's the worst comment ever to bring out a smile.)
What did you mean by that?
He used to say those comments more brazenly.
Since we'll be driving,
we won't be able to drink.
- Are there non-alcoholic ones?
- Yes, there are.
- Oh, really?
- I'll get it for you.
- Thank you.
- Thank you. Make it tasty, please.
I'll have a non-alcoholic cocktail...
that is as fresh as Ji Hyo's scent.
(I'm so fed up with you.)
- As fresh as her scent.
- Okay, I got it.
I could say these things smoothly three years ago, right?
It's so awkward now.
It's been quite a while.
It was hard to say these comments.
She picked you as the person she feels the most awkward...
- to eat with.
- Right, she did.
I actually...
had a meal with Kwang Soo once.
You are the first member to see separately other than him.
- Right.
- I went tanning with Jong Kook...
several times.
(What?)
It's weird that you went tanning together.
(Jealous)
Will you go with me too?
He's jealous.
I want you to tan with me.
Our food is here.
I will serve the appetiser.
(He serves the appetiser.)
How should I eat this?
(It's an interesting one.)
(Munching)
Oh, it's a course meal.
Wipe her lips! Wipe her lips!
- Wipe her lips!
- Wow.
(Shall I lay my hand on her lips?)
- Wipe her lips!
- Wow.
It's so refreshing.
(In your dreams)
- It's refreshing.
- Is it delicious?
- Yes.
- Ji Hyo did it by herself.
- That's a bit too...
- Well, you...
- What do you mean?
- That's what the viewers want.
You should have intentionally put the foam on your lips.
You better kiss before the end of the date.
Lovers usually take breaks...
and talk while eating.
Do you want to see what lovers usually do?
- What do they do?
- Give me your hand.
(Open your hand like this.)
This is what they do.
(This is what they do.)
Don't they?
(It's their first date...)
(as well as their first physical contact.)
(Will they continue on as real lovers?)
- How do they eat?
- They don't.
Eating isn't important.
(She takes her hand away.)
(Irritated)
(Flinching)
- We came to eat, so we should eat.
- She's really irritated.
Don't you really hate that?
You look like you just saw a bug.
Ji Hyo, how's Chen Bolin?
Is he nice to you?
(Her Chinese "We Got Married" partner is Chen Bolin.)
He is nice to me.
Is he?
Gary eats so pitifully.
I can't ask any more.
Chen Bolin also cooked me dinner.
- Really?
- Is he good at cooking?
- Yes.
What do you call him?
Do you call him Bolin?
I was so jealous then.
I will whisper it in your ear.
- Really? What is it?
- Is she going to whisper?
They really had a nickname.
(Whispering)
(Giggling)
- What did she say?
- What was it?
- Really?
- I'm curious.
- Really.
Let's make our own nicknames.
I'll call you "Jiji".
(Please...)
- Please don't.
- Why?
Don't do it.
But you call him "Bobo".
(But you call him "Bobo".)
- "Bobo"?
- What does "Bobo" mean?
- The "Bo" is from his name.
Oh, because it's Bolin Chen.
- So it's "Bobo".
- Does he call you "Mengmeng?"
- How did you know?
- Right?
Is it really "Mengmeng"?
- It means cute in Chinese.
- Right.
Right? "Mengmengda" means cute.
Right.
Let's do something after this.
(After we are done eating...)
Do you want to go watch a movie...
like how ordinary lovers do?
(Do you want to watch a movie?)
- Do you want to watch horror movie?
- No.
Lovers should watch a horror movie.
That's how they get closer.
I want to watch...
Something like...
(Is it romance, comedy or action?)
"My Love, Don't Cross That River".
(It's a serious movie.)
(Sharing thoughts on life and death on their first date)
- What was that?
- "My Love, Don't Cross That River".
They no longer show it at the theatres.
Why do you have to watch that kind of movie?
- Come on.
- I really like...
family movies.
- It's over now.
- But...
this is Ji Hyo. It's Ji Hyo.
Ji Hyo was so defensive yesterday.
I booked a nice place.
- Did you?
- Yes.
- Really?
Is it only for two?
It's a place only for two.
Ji Hyo!
- It's dark already.
- Thank you.
- They had dinner.
- The car is on your right.
- Gary!
- Yes?
I think it gets more interesting at night.
Put your arm around mine.
- They are holding hands!
- Wow!
(Naturally)
- Put your arm around mine.
- They are holding hands!
(Gary and Ji Hyo are holding hands.)
- This is a date indeed.
- You let me hold your hand!
All right.
(They've become closer.)
Ji Hyo, come here.
(He becomes too shy and lets go of her hand.)
He became too awkward.
- He's really shy.
- Wait, I'm stuck.
Ji Hyo, I'm stuck!
Ji Hyo!
(He exaggerates because he likes her laughter.)
She laughs so much.
- She's in a good mood.
- I like the vibe.
Are you in a good mood?
It feels different at night.
A date officially starts when the sun goes down.
Does it?
What did you prepare next?
(What is this special theatre that she prepared?)
I'm really excited to find out what you've prepared.
- Let's watch a movie.
- Okay.
Today,
it doesn't feel like I'm working, but...
- Like your playing?
- Yes, it does.
(They're in a great mood and having fun.)
What is this? Ji Hyo,
did you rent a place?
It's not a theatre.
Let's get off. Wait, Ji Hyo!
Don't open it yet!
(Wait!)
(He acts like a gentleman once more...)
(but fails again.)
Don't do this.
You had to unlock and open it.
- Yes.
- I waited to see how you'd do it.
I forgot again.
- I love this vibe.
- You are so funny.
Where are we going?
Going to a theatre is also nice.
(Going to a theatre is nice.)
But since it's our first time watching a movie together...
(She wants something special.)
Ji Hyo, you look so pretty today...
in this dress.
- Is it nice?
- Yes.
I wore this for you. I never wore this before.
You are the start of spring.
(Ji Hyo is the beginning of spring.)
Women like such comments although they say they don't.
It's strange.
(Welcome to Monday Couple's personal theatre.)
Oh, what is this?
Ji Hyo, where are you taking me?
(Welcome to Monday Couple's personal theatre.)
Oh my goodness.
Well...
- Wait!
- Wait?
- Can I come in?
- Ta-da!
What? What is it?
- Wow!
- Is it their private theatre?
Wow, Ji Hyo!
(Romantic theatre that used the sky as a ceiling)
Did you prepare the candles?
- Those? It's great, right?
- Yes.
- Look at the view.
- It's our...
(Touched)
This is awesome.
Samseong-dong is that way.
Look over there.
- That's Samseong-dong and...
- This is just amazing.
(A night view of Seoul)
- That way...
- That's Gangnam Station.
- Watch out for the stairs.
- The view up here is so nice.
I know. Wow!
And what are these?
- Wow, what is this?
- Gosh.
- Gary.
- Yes?
- Pour me some juice.
- Okay!
They're having the time of their lives.
- The vibe is so good.
- It's nice.
Isn't the vibe great?
Wasn't it a bit cold outside?
- It was.
- Of course.
- She's fixing her makeup.
- She is.
Why are you suddenly fixing your makeup?
Why are you applying lip gloss while I'm pouring juice?
What are you trying to say?
What does that mean?
(He pours grape juice instead of wine.)
- Cheers!
(Cheers!)
- Wow, the sound is nice.
- Look at their glasses.
- It's great.
- The vibe is nice.
They're feeling great.
(They don't seem to be awkward any more.)
- Goodness.
- They look so nice together.
(They don't seem to be awkward any more.)
(He acts like a gentleman and feeds her marshmallows.)
It's so awkward.
It wasn't even in my mouth, but you pulled the spoon out.
Did I pull out too early?
(He still lacks some skills.)
She's shy.
- It was so cold.
- Let's watch a movie.
- Shall we?
- Sure.
Let's watch "Begin Again". But before that, Ji Hyo.
(Wait a moment.)
Since you prepared...
such a nice place...
- Are they socks?
- I got these from the States.
- Really?
- They're matching socks.
Oh, really?
I think the red one will suit you.
- Okay.
- I will take the white one.
- Are you going to wear them now?
- Yes, it's cold.
Okay, then.
Gary, thanks!
- I will wear on top of this.
- A big present is too much.
- It's better than expensive gifts.
- It will be too much.
- Start with small gifts.
- Gary,
don't I look like an American football player?
Gosh, Gary.
Your socks...
- I already feel warm...
- They are in a good mood.
after wearing them.
Gosh, I love this.
(A couple's love begins at the theatre.)
It feels great.
(Gary tries to get close to Ji Hyo.)
- We were both tired.
- I'm so tired.
- I was sleepy.
- Gary always sleeps during a movie.
Gary always sleeps.
- I'm so tired.
- He slept during my movie too.
Oh, goodness. I'm getting sleepy.
(Gary looks for an opportunity to touch Ji Hyo.)
(She sits up.)
- She was very defensive.
- I knew it.
(I know what you're thinking.)
- Gosh.
- Your nose is red.
(Let me lay my head on your lap.)
Look at her face.
- Your nose is red.
- I didn't see her face back then.
Cover yourself with this blanket. It's chilly.
- I'm okay.
- You should.
- I'm really okay.
- Don't be like that.
You're making me uncomfortable.
(Ji Hyo is annoyed.)
- She's annoyed.
- She got angry.
She did seem angry.
I guess it won't work out for them.
- It won't work out.
- It won't.
(Monday Couple is still not close enough.)
- Use this blanket. I insist.
- No, really. I'm fine.
- You make me uncomfortable.
- I have socks on.
That doesn't make any difference. You even have holes in your pants.
- I'm okay.
- Don't worry about me.
- Don't be like that.
- I'm really okay.
- I would feel bad.
- Then let's share it.
(She proposes to share the blanket.)
(Yes!)
- I'll cover you.
- Okay.
You're sharing a blanket.
- And then...
- You're sharing a blanket.
- Let's share it.
- Cover yourself.
A moment like this can be awkward.
(Gary tries putting his hand around Ji Hyo's shoulder.)
There you go.
Don't do this.
(Ji Hyo keeps pushing Gary away.)
- "Don't do this."
- She kept pushing me away.
I wanted to try something new.
"I wanted to try something new."
I'm just wondering.
Did it make you nervous to go on a date with me?
I realised one thing.
- It's not awkward to be around you.
- Of course, it's not.
- It doesn't look awkward.
- I knew it wouldn't be,
- Why don't you look at each other?
- but...
the idea of going on a date did make me nervous.
But you made it so fun.
What will you be doing on Wednesday?
(Gary wants to ask her out.)
- I'll be busy.
- Right. Me too.
(It's their first date in 6 years.)
(Monday Couple enjoys their romantic night.)
(The movie is over.)
It's over.
Ji Hyo, thank you so much.
You're welcome. Thank you.
If it weren't for you, I would've never worn...
matching socks with anybody.
We should wear them on our next shooting day.
- Tomorrow?
- Should we wear them tomorrow?
All right, let's do that.
Oh, that's what happened.
Are you sure you didn't throw them away?
You said you would wear them today.
- You're not wearing them either.
- I am wearing them!
(Gary kept his promise.)
But look at you!
You're always like this!
- Ji Hyo, Gary is wearing them.
- I kept my word!
Ji Hyo, you should be wearing them.
Gary must be so disappointed.
- Gosh...
- I just found out.
We have one more thing to do.
- What will that be?
- What do we have to do?
What kind of car is that?
- Do you know what it is?
- Can't you leave us alone?
Where are we going?
I should have taken the wheel.
(Where would their last destination be?)
(They arrive at their last destination.)
No way.
Where are we?
Is this a hospital?
A hospital?
- It says "Examination Centre."
- Why are we here?
(Why are we at a hospital?)
- What's happening?
- What's going on?
- Did you have a check-up?
- It's late at night.
You'll find out soon.
- Really?
- Yes.
- I don't know the results yet.
- Ji Hyo.
Why are we here?
We must be getting an MRI scan.
- Why? Why are we here?
- I don't know.
- Is it...
- Is it to see if they're in love?
- Yes, to see if we like each other.
- Exactly.
If you like the other person,
- can we see that?
- Usually, we scan our hearts.
- But we had our brains scanned.
- Really?
- It will be impossible to lie.
- It was real.
- Will we see the result?
- We had an MRI scan.
(Let's find out how they really feel by scanning their brains.)
- Hello.
- Come in.
As you can see,
- this is the MRI room.
- Yes.
We're going to find out...
what you two really feel about each other.
(Will our true feelings be scanned?)
- Can you actually find that out?
- Yes, we can.
Do you think love can be figured out through one's brain?
By examining the response of your cerebral nerves,
- we can find that out.
- That's amazing.
Is that really possible?
Can you really do that?
You'll be surprised at the result.
Ji Hyo, we won't be able to hide our feelings any more.
Exactly, because it's scientific.
- But...
- We had our heartbeats checked,
and we even took a lie detector test once.
Will it be impossible to manipulate the result?
This is one of the most accurate tests.
Really?
I don't know why, but I'm getting scared.
(What will happen to them?)
- I haven't done this before.
- So will we get an MRI scan?
Is that really possible?
- Everything will become clear.
- Really?
- Let's see.
- It'll answer our question.
It'll give us an answer.
We will definitely find out each other's feelings.
Will we get to see the result today?
- Really?
- The result should come out.
You two must be nervous.
- Everything will become clear.
- Really?
So we will find out today.
(How will science define their feelings?)
Part of me is scared.
So many people love Monday Couple.
(Science will give her the answer to something she doesn't know.)
I hope they'll take it well regardless of what the result is.
What's your guess on Gary's result?
(What's your guess on Gary's result?)
I bet he feels the same way as I do.
Ji Hyo, although we don't know what the result will be yet,
if it turns out that you have feelings for me,
I'll give us a second thought.
(He'll give them a chance.)
What are their true feelings?
(What will their true feelings be?)
- All right.
- I can't wait to find out.
Let's find out their MRI scan results.
I wouldn't be surprised if they had feelings for each other.
Please welcome Professor Kim Byung Jun.
Hello.
- Hello.
- Is the result reliable?
Although this method is not widely being used yet,
- a lot of research is being done.
- Oh, I see.
I see.
Professor Kim will tell us the truth behind Monday Couple.
Please announce the MRI results.
As you watched, they put on special goggles.
We showed Ji Hyo some pictures of Gary,
and we showed pictures of Ji Hyo to Gary...
to examine which part of their brains were activated.
This is very scientific indeed.
- Let's look at Gary's result first.
- Let's see it.
We showed him 12 pictures of Ji Hyo for 4 minutes.
- For 4 minutes?
- Yes.
Let's look at how Gary's brain reacted to pictures of Ji Hyo.
Do you see the heart shape in the middle of his brain?
- It's called the "Brain stem".
- I see.
When you're passionately in love,
this part of the brain is activated.
When shown pictures of Ji Hyo,
(What are his true feelings towards Ji Hyo?)
it made him very calm as if he saw something very familiar.
- Is that what you feel?
- It's just friendship, right?
When shown random pictures,
an average person would find at least some of them intriguing,
but it didn't happen to Gary. He remained very calm.
I see.
- She's like a mum to him.
- She makes him comfortable.
Wow.
- It's Ji Hyo's turn.
- How did she react?
This is when Ji Hyo was shown pictures of Gary.
As you can see, many parts of the brain were evidently activated.
Here is the heart-shaped part.
This part is activated when you see someone you love.
We could see that this part of her brain was activated.
- Really?
- What's going on?
- Ji Hyo!
- Was Ji Hyo the one in love?
Goodness.
- Is that why you pushed him away?
- Was that me?
- What's going on?
- Really?
Was Ji Hyo the one in love?
- So that's why.
- You little cutie. Goodness.
The basal ganglion which indicates positive affection...
- was activated as well.
- Is that how she feels?
What? Really?
Love sometimes can take the form of comradeship.
In the brains of people in long-term relationships,
the cortex, which is in charge of perception, is activated.
Her brain indicated mild affection rather than passionate love.
- Mild affection?
- Yes.
- It's comradeship.
- It's more like comradeship.
That's right. This can be found...
in the brains of new couples...
- In the early stages?
- or very old couples.
- "Old couples".
They're not even a couple.
They're like an old couple.
I know you're called "Monday Couple"
Unfortunately, the examination was on Sunday.
- Sir!
- Sir, you're pretty witty.
Gosh...
Wait. Are you really a doctor?
- Is he a comedian?
- I know.
You're saying the result could be different if tested today, right?
- Is that right?
- Well, there is a chance.
- That made me question him.
- I know.
- There are comedians...
- He was so serious.
- There are comedians like him.
- You're right.
- You showed him other pictures too.
- How did he react...
to Seolhyun's picture?
- His brain's reaction showed...
- What is it?
a typical pattern of a person madly in love.
(It's official that he's in love with Seolhyun.)
- You were too passionate for her.
- Seolhyun.
(A picture of Seolhyun made his brain go crazy.)
Really?
Partially, it's a sign of...
- Desire?
- a sexual...
- What?
- You piece of trash!
- How dare you?
- Do you want to die?
- I will...
- Seolhyun will...
This has nothing to do with my own will.
It's my brain.
How did Ji Hyo's brain react to Bo Gum's picture?
How did she react to Bo Gum's picture?
Ji Hyo only showed humane affection towards him.
- You are strange.
- Right.
- How did she react to Kwang Soo?
- Open your heart, Ji Hyo.
Part of the brain related to love was activated,
but the part related to fear and terror was also...
Part related to fear and terror...
From Kwang Soo?
The part related to unpleasant feelings...
"Unpleasant feelings"?
Those areas also were activated.
Both of them had that reaction to Kwang Soo's picture.
- They're afraid of being betrayed.
- Why?
- He always betrays people.
- What's wrong with me?
They felt unpleasant and scared when seeing your face.
- Honestly, Kwang Soo,
- I am not threatening.
I just laughed when I saw your face.
- I laughed too.
- It felt unpleasant.
- Why?
- I didn't think of anything.
- But your brain showed it.
- The result...
- It showed.
- It showed. How fascinating.
Do I look unpleasant?
(Do I look unpleasant?)
(So don't betray us.)
So he was excited to see Seolhyun.
All right. Please give it up for Professor Kim Byung Jun.
Thank you!
- That was fun.
- That was really fun.
Getting tested on a Sunday was the problem.
It's more fun when it's explained by him.
So are you two a couple just for work?
- It's more like comradeship.
- That's right.
- That's it.
- It's comradeship.
We should've done this...
- on Running Man's second year.
- You're right.
If they got the scan back then,
- it would've been different.
- Right.
- Next.
- Who is it?
- Who is it now?
- Me?
- Let's check it.
(Is Seok Jin really gullible?)
(Me?)
I really want to rip your name tag.
I am not the spy.
Then should I rip his?
- What are you doing?
- I'm so frustrated.
Make a decision.
My friend runs a chicken farm.
And there are six legs on a chicken.
When you plant the seed,
ginseng grows on the bottom and tomatoes on top.
Gosh, I want to invest 20,000, or better yet, 200,000 dollars.
(Is he really gullible?)
- "Is Seok Jin really gullible?"
- Seok Jin is...
- He is.
I think he is.
- But he has a lot of doubts.
- Right?
We talk about starting a business a lot.
- But his idea always changes.
- Right.
- But he also doubts a lot.
- You're right.
- I have a lot of doubts.
- He always doubts.
Seok Jin is like this.
He has a lot of doubts, so he is very thorough.
But in the end, he chooses the path nobody would choose.
- Right?
- Yes.
- That's why he gets fooled easily.
He doesn't trust what people around him tell him.
But he easily trusts people he meets for the first time.
(He trusts strangers easily.)
- So he gets scammed a lot.
- And...
- That's right.
- I trust people who are nice to me.
Usually scammers are nice.
- But...
- He's very biased.
Isn't everyone like that though?
- Oh gosh!
- What was that?
(What just happened?)
- That really surprised me.
- What's that?
Gosh, that surprised me.
- What's happening?
- What?
- What is it?
(What's happening?)
(Someone appears.)
(Who is he?)
(No way.)
Look at the screen.
Gosh...
- Here?
- He recognised us a while ago.
- Isn't he the prince?
- The prince...
- He's the owner.
- What's this?
What's going on?
- What's going on?
- I should go outside.
(What's happening to Seok Jin?)
(Several days ago at a restaurant in Gangnam)
(Jong Kook and Haha checked to see how gullible Seok Jin is.)
This is a business proposal.
- This business proposal is...
- Yes.
a result of a growing health awareness in Dubai.
- It's a very special proposal.
- It's "Jewel in the Dubai Palace".
(Let's take a closer look.)
- It looks believable.
- Rice puffs will replace popcorn...
- In Dubai.
Seok Jin will buy the idea at this point right here.
This is all he needs.
"Monthly profit of Dubai theatres' popcorn sales..."
"is three million dollars."
(It's a candid camera designed for Seok Jin.)
The game is over. It's already over.
He needs an Arabic name.
The first condition for becoming the business partner...
- is getting an Arabic name.
- He will gladly do so.
Of course.
If Seok Jin is the target, we don't need this meeting.
(Seok Jin appears.)
- Welcome.
- Why are you alone?
They all went out to make phone calls.
(Jong Kook naturally leads him to the designated seat.)
- Gosh...
- Hey.
Did you come from the gym?
Of course.
Seok Jin, it's funny.
You know that Korean rice puffs became a huge hit in Africa, right?
- I don't know.
- You don't know?
- Listen to him.
- Rice puffs became a huge hit.
- Really?
- But that's not important.
Do you remember that man who managed everything in Dubai?
Remember that prince?
- Prince?
- And...
even though we aren't Arab, they approached us.
Anyways, I'll cut to the chase.
They want to sell rice puffs in Dubai.
It's...
And he...
- really loves you.
- What?
- He really loves you.
- He does.
- Why?
- We don't know.
- We don't know the reason.
- Who is this?
- I think they saw you...
- The prince?
- during our shoot in Dubai.
- Really?
- I think so. I'm not sure.
First of all, their family...
owns about 80 percent of all the theatres in Dubai.
- Really?
- Yes.
The conditions are good.
For the three of us...
How much? Tell me.
(He's very excited.)
It's the price for the three of us.
- So how much is it?
- For the three of us...
- It's the down payment.
- Okay.
- They will give us 10.
- 10 million dollars?
- Yes.
(He's very happy.)
But wait. Listen.
They secretly installed the camera.
Did you guys put cameras in there?
- He's really shocked.
- Gosh...
He was really shocked.
He has no idea.
(He's shocked.)
What's this?
(He can't believe what just happened.)
Dubai's king is...
- Hey.
- What's that?
- His face turned red.
- Was that really a lie?
(I'm sorry, Seok Jin.)
- This is crazy.
- Gosh...
So that's all gone?
- Did he really believe that?
- It already sounds strange.
- How could he believe that?
- I made it believable.
- I really did.
- He talks so well.
You would've been fooled too.
He would've been fooled too.
The contract will range from 2 to 3 years.
They are suggesting a five percent running guarantee.
Is that per person? That's nice.
- The rate is high.
- I don't think it's per person.
It doesn't make sense, right?
Let's just take it as five percent per person.
- Five percent per person?
- Let's insist.
- Let's do that.
- Let's say,
"Isn't it five percent per person?"
"That's what we thought."
(He's a genius entrepreneur!)
You just have to say that.
- He's good.
- He's a genius dealer.
- I'm pretty good.
- He's a genius.
But first, let's make it more...
This isn't a prank, is it?
Wait. Wait.
You're reacting as if we're on candid camera.
I was surprised that time.
I guess you wouldn't do that when money is involved.
- Of course.
- Of course, it'll be on TV.
You can talk to him on the phone and ask him for the details.
This is all we know so far.
(Afraid he will find out, they get help from a friend.)
(A friend arrives to save them.)
- Hello.
- Did you come from Taiwan?
- He surprised me.
This is the business proposal they sent us.
- What?
- The word "Rice puffs" is...
highlighted in red.
We just mentioned theatres in this proposal.
- This is it.
- So that's it.
- That's how it became famous.
- But...
- we won't just target theatres.
- Korean culture must be popular.
- Yes. We will be dealing with...
- This is crazy.
everyone in the entertainment industry.
- Not just the theatres...
- We should make...
Arabic names right away.
(He's so cool.)
- Let's make about five of them.
- What will be yours?
- "Abdul"?
- And the profit...
(Abdul?)
(This future rice puff dealer is very funny.)
I will name myself "Abdul Wangko".
(He's already very excited.)
- How about "Kodull"?
- Seok Jin,
"Abdullah" means...
How about "Kodullah"?
- "Kodullah".
My first name is Kodullah.
My middle name is Hassan.
My last name is Mohammed.
Kodullah Hassan Mohammed.
- "Mohammed"?
- Also known as...
"Ko-Ha-Mo".
(He will be known as "Ko-Ha-Mo".)
He loves it.
He's so happy.
We need to come up with our theme song.
(The contract requires them to make a theme song.)
- For this one,
- We have to write a song?
I recommended you.
Seok Jin is good at writing songs.
He sang in Chinese back in China.
He did.
Rice puffs
(He immediately makes a song on the spot.)
Prince of Dubai and Korean rice puffs
(Prince and the Korean rice puffs)
Kodullah, Kodullah
Rice puffs
They stick to your mouth
Kodullah
Korean rice puffs in Dubai
Where are you going to place it?
Korean rice puffs Korean rice puffs
(Korean rice puffs)
Seok Jin looks so excited.
(Thanks to Seok Jin, everyone is laughing.)
He looks like he's having so much fun.
Dubai Korean rice puffs Dubai Korean rice puffs
Goodbye, popcorn
- This is it.
- Goodness.
- This is going to be the song.
- That sounds perfect.
- It's in English too.
- Right.
- Korean rice puffs in Dubai
- Goodbye, popcorn
It's going to be our song.
Seok Jin looks really upset now.
- I'm upset.
- Seok Jin is more upset...
- that he can't get the money.
- I'm really upset.
The prince is currently in Shanghai.
He said that he wants to come here to meet you.
We're more than happy to meet him.
- Of course.
- He can sleepover at my house.
This is going great.
This is great.
Just before Seok Jin loses a great deal of money...
through investment, he has that look on his face.
(Beware of fraud!)
He's flushed and excited.
We wrote a contract.
- We wrote a contract.
- He already wrote a contract?
- Really?
- Actually,
- we knew this already.
- You guys are the worst.
We've known of this already.
Seok Jin was completely fooled.
- Right.
- Yes.
(The meeting with the prince)
(He visits the Running Man waiting room.)
- You can sit over here.
- Yes.
- This way.
Please sit here.
Sit down. Sit down, please.
(Sit down. Sit down, please.)
You are really handsome.
(You are really handsome.)
(Laughing)
You look very handsome.
Handsome.
(Haha arrives.)
After 20 years.
Hello.
Thank you. You're here.
(Seok Jin is half shy and half excited.)
(Speaking in a foreign language)
He doesn't remember seeing...
the other members, but he recognises you, Seok Jin.
Thank you. Thank you so much.
(Thank you so much.)
- Hello.
- This is awesome.
- Could you introduce yourselves?
- A good name.
Okay.
To show my respect,
I came up with my Arabic name.
(He got an Arabic name to sign the contract.)
(Haha bursts out laughing.)
(Nudging)
(Don't be so rude in front of the prince.)
- What's your Arabic name?
- Kodullah.
(Kodullah?)
- He said to make it Jadullah.
- Jadullah?
- He recommends it to be Jadullah.
- Jadullah.
"Jadullah Hassan Mohammed".
(Jadulla Hassan Mohammed)
In short, it's going to be "Ja-Ha-Mo".
Call me, "Jahamo".
(Call me, Jahamo.)
Like we talked about last time,
he would like to sign a provisional contract.
- Do I sign here?
- Yes, at the bottom.
Write the date too.
(He signs the contract as if he's signing an autograph for a fan.)
Rather than being business partners,
I hope us to be close like brothers.
(Like brothers)
(Seok Jin wants to get closer to the prince.)
Isn't that too much?
- That's not it.
- Don't rush like that.
- Take time to get to know him.
- I think he's uncomfortable.
- That's not it.
- He looks uncomfortable.
I thought that...
(They made the enormous contract with a blink of an eye.)
(The prince leaves.)
Hey.
- We did it.
- We're going successfully well.
(We did it.)
We did it.
Is it really happening to me?
(I'm going to be rich now.)
Oh, my.
This is nonsense.
(It was all a dream.)
Goodness.
- Thank you.
- Are you not the prince?
He's the fake prince.
- Can you speak Korean?
- A little.
(He is in despair.)
(Screaming)
Goodness.
Prince, is this the contract?
- Seok Jin signed the contract.
- He signed it.
- I'll read what's written on it.
- This is what Seok Jin agreed to.
- Yes.
I will not be late for the shooting.
I will do whatever the staff tells me to do.
I will not get angry for whatever I'm told to do.
I'll help out the staff to clean after shooting the programme.
(He took the lead in agreeing to regulations.)
I will be the last to leave after the shooting.
- It sounds great.
- Really?
This is what Seok Jin agreed to.
- Yes.
- You need to keep it.
You need to follow the contract.
- I must say...
- Oh my goodness.
he was surely happy.
- It wasn't captured on camera,
- I was really...
but when we went out for a break,
he held my hand tightly.
He then said, "You did great. Now is the time."
His eyes were teary.
(Eyes teary and heart piercing)
I felt really sorry. He kept on text-messaging me.
(He's furious.)
- I'm angrier at you.
- Oh, my.
- Stop it.
- You should take up acting.
- He's super gullible.
- Really.
He is surely gullible.
He was born a nice person.
(Jae Seok is the best MC and show host in Korea.)
He is really nice.
(But his instinct is hidden deep inside.)
(Is Jae Seok really a nice person?)
(Running Man Q and A)
We have prepared the answers...
for some questions regarding...
the appearance of the members.
- It's about Ji Hyo.
- Many people asked that question.
- Really.
- We were asked so many times.
- They ask if she is really pretty.
- Right.
- I tell them it's true.
- Ji Hyo is pretty.
- I answer them she is pretty.
- What do you say, Gary?
- I tell them she is pretty.
- Right.
It's true that she's pretty.
She looks prettier on the photos of news articles...
- rather than on Running Man.
- That's right.
- Or at a film preview.
- She is always pretty.
- Or at an awards ceremony.
- I get surprised on those days.
- She is pretty.
- How do we answer this?
- We invited someone to prove it.
Are they analysing Ji Hyo's face?
- Are they analysing me?
- They can't possibly.
We have Doctor Kim Jong Myung with us today.
- Welcome.
- He's Jong Kook's brother.
- Real brother?
- Hello.
He looks very gentle.
My family.
He has different genes from me.
- Is he your real brother?
- Yes.
So are you starting a reality show with your family now?
- What?
- A family reality show.
- No.
- He may be.
- Isn't this the beginning?
- No, it's not.
- Are you going to be on the show?
- No, it's not like that.
How is Jong Kook as a brother?
Though he looks very tough,
he acts like the youngest when he's home.
- He is very tender-hearted.
- Does he act like a baby?
- Yes.
- Does he...
Why does he change when he steps out of the house?
He's too rough outside.
Have you ever been hit by him?
- I've never been hit.
- Really?
It's a relief that he doesn't hit his own brother.
I hit him a lot when we were young.
Really?
I can't imagine Jong Kook getting hit.
- I don't hit anyone.
- You've come to verify today.
- Yes.
- If Ji Hyo is really pretty.
How can we prove if she is really pretty?
We will analyse her face.
We'll see if she is really pretty and if she is a beauty.
- Please show us.
- We'll check that now.
Oh, gosh. Her eyes look swollen.
It was taken just before.
- Hey, you...
- Yes, my face was swollen.
The picture on the left is the typical beauty...
- according to golden ratio.
- It's a typical beauty.
- They're nearly the same.
- You're right.
- In the case of Ji Hyo,
- She does look very similar.
she has the young-looking face...
- according to this ratio.
- Young-looking face.
- She does look very young.
- She does.
The golden ratio means the forehead, middle part...
and bottom part of the face are in exactly the same ratio.
So the same ratio for forehead, middle part and lower part?
- Is that so?
- Yes.
Nowadays, people prefer the ratio to be 1 to 1 to 0.8 or 0.9.
- The lower part has to be smaller.
- It's 0.8 for Ji Hyo.
She has a really young face with her bottom part of the face nearly 0.8.
He is verifying it.
- Yes.
- Wait.
His facial proportion is 1 to 1 to 3.
Does that make me look old?
- His face is too long.
- What's up with my face?
- His face is closer to looking old.
- Old.
(Old-looking)
- He does look old.
- Right.
His nose and bottom part of his face are big when it comes to the ratio.
- He has a long chin.
- Though the proportion isn't great,
looking at the balance of his face, he is considered handsome.
What is that angle about?
It is to check if she has the perfect angle.
If you take a look at the photo,
it's exactly the angle. It's the typical.
- It fits perfectly.
- She has a very beautiful face.
- Really?
- Wow.
- So there's no doubt she's pretty.
- Right.
My goodness. Ji Hyo doesn't even blush.
- It's natural for her.
- What if she did a surgery?
- I'm just surprised.
- Are her eyes natural?
- I think so.
- Is it true?
- Is your nose natural?
- Yes.
- Didn't you do plastic surgeries?
- I did not.
- Can I touch your nose?
- Yes, do as you please.
(Sure, you can touch my nose.)
(He pushes her nose up.)
(Seriously?)
(Let's take a look at your nose.)
- Didn't you get a nose job?
- I didn't.
- Didn't you?
- I didn't put anything in.
I just cut some off like shortening trouser cuffs.
(He just cut some off like shortening trouser cuffs.)
- You cut your trouser if it's long.
- Right.
My nose was too big,
so I reduced it a little.
So my nostrils are slightly different.
The next question is... I'm curious about this too.
- It's about Gary.
- Gary.
- Does he really look like a squid?
- Squid?
- I ate that for lunch today.
- I'm curious.
- Gosh.
- Isn't that an absurd question?
- I'm really curious.
People usually call those...
ugly people like Gary like that.
(Ugly people like Gary)
We say those look like a squid.
(What is that?)
(Ta-da!)
(A comparison of a squid and Gary)
(That's hilarious.)
- They look similar.
- Doctor.
Why don't you use a human figure for me?
Why can't I be compared with a human?
(Are you trying to make me cry?)
Doctor, give that to me.
- Gary, you look alike.
- Give it to me.
- Gary.
- It's hilarious.
- Are you serious?
Oh my goodness.
Doctor,
isn't it more appropriate for me...
- to be compared with a human?
- They look exactly the same.
- It's so funny.
- Why should it be a squid?
(He should have used a human's face to make the comparison.)
- Get out of my way!
- Goodness.
You should have used a human picture first...
and changed it to a squid.
- This is so funny.
- I laughed so hard.
- Well...
- But...
- they look similar.
- It's strange.
Wow, seriously.
They look so similar!
- Wow, really.
- You used human drawings before.
We compare ugly people with a squid like this...
because they don't usually have clean-cut features...
and have flat structured faces like squids.
If you insist on asking if he looks like a squid, I have to agree to it.
(If they keep asking if Gary looks like a squid, he has to admit it.)
- Stop, please stop!
- Goodness.
(Stop! I can't take it any more!)
- Stop!
- Flat structured face.
- It's so true.
- Really.
He's so persuasive. I got him right away.
- They are not exactly the same.
- They look alike.
(It's official that Gary looks like a squid.)
- Oh, really.
- It's so strange.
- Moving on to the next question.
- I want Haha's comparison.
- All right.
- It's about Haha and Gary.
I'm curious about this.
- Who asked this?
- This is a very sensitive question.
This can't even be a question.
- This is harsh.
- How will that come out?
This is too much.
It's impossible to decide who's handsome and who's ugly.
Look! I'm so cute!
Goodness.
(Their faces are shockingly ugly.)
Here it is!
(It's Gary versus Haha.)
(This is an unexpected big match.)
Can I have a squid's picture here?
Can I have a squid, please?
- It's cute!
- In the middle, please.
- It's cute, isn't it?
- Wait a second.
- Isn't it?
- He looks like a sea anemone.
- A squid and baby octopus.
- I look so cute!
You two are both from the sea.
- Haha looks like a baby octopus.
- I'm so cute.
I thought it's Gary before and after the perm.
Please, don't.
- I mean it, really.
- Hey.
- You go and see yourself!
- Gosh.
- It's like pictures in a hair shop.
- I've never been mad at you, right?
- Right.
- Don't make me mad today.
- Okay.
- This is too much.
(You and I are neck-and-neck.)
- This isn't right.
- I analysed and compared them.
The biggest differences between them are nose and face contour.
Haha has bigger nose and clearer contour,
making his face more solid.
If I have to decide who's more handsome,
I'd say that Haha's face is more likeable.
- I agree with him.
- I admit that.
Being likeable is different from being handsome.
- Now, it's time for me.
- This is going to be interesting.
- This must be huge.
- Let's go!
(Does Jae Seok really look like Yoda?)
- Oh, Yoda.
- I'm fully sure of this.
- It can't even be a question.
- This is so not true.
They look the same.
Goodness.
(They're all surprised to see the comparison.)
(They look exactly the same.)
- This is hilarious!
- He should take off his glasses.
This is...
What is this?
This is hilarious.
- I can't tell the difference.
- Doctor, you went too far.
- This is too much, really.
- It should be without his glasses.
I can't tell who's who!
- Why are you doing this to me?
- If you put glasses on Yoda,
they will look exactly the same.
Take off your glasses.
- Are you saying we look alike?
- You look alike.
- Me and Yoda?
- Right.
- There's no need to explain it.
- Totally.
- This is too much.
- No need to explain it.
They do look alike surprisingly.
- Is that so?
- They both have a protruding mouth.
- They have protruding eyes too.
- Really.
Also, their forehead bones above the eyes are protruding.
- Right.
- Those points make them look alike.
- He said everything outright.
- They might look the same...
if Jae Seok does the double eyelids surgery.
He gets double eyelids when he becomes a little tired.
- I'm sure they would exactly same.
- It's Jae Seok with double eyelids!
- Now, this is...
- What is that?
- They look exactly the same!
- What is this?
If Jae Seok takes his glasses off and has double eyelids,
- they do look similar because of...
- I got goose bumps.
their eye wrinkles and protruding eyes and mouths.
I wasn't sure at first, but they are more similar than I thought.
- Did you say we look alike?
- Yes.
Our viewers gave you that nickname for a reason.
Of course, there is a reason for it.
- Goodness.
- You two are really similar.
You two really look similar.
I thought the squid was the end,
- but here came something worse.
- You beat the squid.
Anyway, Doctor Kim Jong Myung joined us today...
to answer viewers' questions on our appearance.
Please give him a round of applause!
- Thank you.
- He talks very well.
- Moving on to the next question!
- Okay.
(Is Jae Seok really a nice person?)
- Goodness.
- What kind of question is that?
- Is he really a nice person?
- I said this so many times...
- that he's a well-presented person.
- He is nice.
- He's a nice person.
- That's true.
- It's true that he's a nice guy.
- I didn't expect this coming.
- People do wonder about this.
- That's right.
- They actually come and ask me.
- They do.
- I have to say...
- He's very playful.
If he had the fighting skills, he would've been more evil than me.
He would have. Yes.
- That's why no one has it all.
- Right.
- That's right.
- That's why I can't fight.
I demonstrated Kwang Soo's water-proof phone for him today.
- Do you have the footage?
- I have it.
- I took the video of it.
- Did you take the footage?
This is how he teases people in the waiting room.
- Look at this.
- Try it.
- It isn't water-proof! Wait!
- Look.
- Don't worry, Kwang Soo!
- That's funny.
He didn't do anything at the back. Is this part water-proof too?
I said it's all right!
No, wait! It's not water-proof!
I said wait!
Stop it!
I told you it's water-proof! Trust me!
- Not the back side, though.
- I said it's going to be fine.
- Kwang Soo.
- It's water-proof anyway.
- It's water-proof.
- Hey.
- Kwang Soo.
- It's water-proof.
- This isn't.
You are Kwang Soo, and it's water proof.
- He says it's water-proof.
- It's not!
(Although Kwang Soo was teased, his mobile phone was okay.)
He is too playful.
- A classic joker.
- He's so naughty.
- I am...
- Both are heavily playful.
- They are differently playful.
- They are different.
I think Kwang Soo would know well. How are we different?
I would have beaten both of you hard if you were younger than me.
(He would have hit them hard first.)
I want to be older than them for once in the next life.
Just once is enough.
- I've never beaten by younger ones.
- I wish I were older than them.
As many viewers are curious, we should answer their question.
- How do we do it?
- There's a way.
- We will begin from step one.
- Okay.
- Let's hear from the members...
- That's right.
- about you first.
- Okay.
His weakness is that he is such a perfectionist.
- His weakness is...
- He knows his weakness.
that he's such a perfectionist.
- It makes people around him tired.
- It's a bit tiring.
- That's right.
- That happens.
I can be late sometimes, but I get nervous when I'm 10 minutes late.
(He becomes nervous because of Jae Seok.)
I'm nervous if my manager takes the blame instead.
Have you ever not picked up his call on purpose?
- I have.
- He has!
(I have.)
At first.
I didn't pick up because I knew what he was going to say.
- I see.
- This is so funny.
I want to see him late at least once.
He was never late for the last six years.
- Not at all.
- Right.
- He's a born nice person.
- But he's too obsessive.
(He's an obsessive perfectionist.)
I'm serious.
Once, Jae Seok, Kwang Soo and I practised for the overseas concert.
We did.
I think we practised for about 300 times.
- He was so lazy, though!
- Seriously.
I couldn't tell him that it was enough and I wanted to rest...
when he asked me to practise more.
I just had to follow him.
I don't even remember how many times we practised.
(They practised to perform for the foreign fans.)
Even after we arrived there he wanted to practise.
Three of us danced in the hotel room even before we went to bed.
- We danced and did this.
- Never ending practise.
I fully memorise it. I can even do it in my sleep.
We practised so much.
I think Kwang Soo has a lot to say.
- I do.
- Go ahead.
- Let's hear him.
- Do it.
I want him to stop giving me advise about my relationships.
- That means he's concerned.
- Stop it, really.
- Don't if you can't make it better.
- It was going so well.
- He ruined it all.
- I really need to say about this.
As I said before, it wasn't going to happen anyway.
- Telling her your feeling wasn't...
- No!
- going to affect the result.
- It's because he's...
- such a good man.
- Saying it affects the result.
He didn't want you to get hurt.
- That's right!
- Right!
But why is he so happy when I get dumped?
I have one complaint about him.
I want him to take care of his health.
Gosh, he's the worst!
- Why?
- Goodness.
- That's not right.
- You are supposed to come after me!
- I should praise him first!
- I did it first...
- before you on purpose.
- Calm down.
- It's all right.
- Jae Seok, take care of your body.
- Stop being nice to people.
- And I...
- Your body isn't yours.
- Think of yourself too!
- It belongs to Korea.
- We fight in the show,
- I love you.
- but I have to say he is flawless!
- Stop it already.
- What is with you?
(Embarrassed)
- You shouldn't do that.
- He's so...
- Okay, quiet down.
- I can't find any of his weakness.
(It's flatterers versus accusers.)
He supported me financially when I moved my workroom.
- Really?
How dare you tell such a story with your legs twisted?
(It's so rude to twist legs when telling such a story.)
(Flinching)
From where I see it, You are a rubbish!
(From where I see it, You are a rubbish!)
You're the worst!
Jae Seok is such a nice person, and Haha is a scum.
- He's a rubbish.
- Gary...
- Gary, calm down.
- Come outside!
- Calm down, Gary!
- Goodness.
- I'm so furious.
- Drink some water.
I twisted my legs because my back hurt. So what?
I was trying to sit up.
("Six Witnesses" is over.)
There are some people...
who know about him better than us.
- We invited the people around him.
- Oh, really?
- They work with him.
- Let's hear them.
- We have three of them here.
- Will they talk about him?
- Are they here?
- Yes.
- Is that right?
- Their voices will be altered.
They should be careful with the way they speak.
- Are they really close to me?
- The second stage.
It's "Inside Men".
- "Inside Men"?
- I wonder who they are.
- Are they really close to him?
- Is his manager here?
- Yes, they are.
- Really?
(Jae Seok seems nervous.)
Who will they be? Who are they?
(3 informants are sitting behind the veil.)
(Who will they be?)
That's obviously Kwon Ryeol in the middle.
Hey, turn around or something.
- That's Kwon Ryeol.
- Turn around.
They're Kwon Ryeol, Cheol Min and Jong Yoon.
- That's his manager.
- That's the manager.
That's my manager, Jong Yoon.
- That's too obvious.
- That's too easy.
Let's start today's "Silhouette Talk".
I know who they are.
It's producer Jeong Cheol Min,
cameraman Yoo Kwon Ryeol...
and manager Lim Jong Yoon.
- Just be honest.
- Right.
I'm sure all of you have a lot to talk about.
Let's start with this question.
Is Jae Seok really a nice person?
Please be honest.
Yes, Jae Seok is a nice person, but...
- Okay.
- "But".
Last week or the week before,
we had an unusually high viewer ratings.
(He was excited to see the higher ratings.)
I texted him that I'm happy about the result with the graph.
Okay.
I expected him to say something like, "Well done."
- Of course.
- He didn't?
You deserved the compliment.
He called me as soon as he read my text.
What did he say?
He started pointing out which parts could have been better.
(He started pointing out which parts could have been better.)
Without any compliments?
- Is that true?
- I mean...
- What's so wrong about it?
- Hear him out.
"Shouldn't we have filmed this part this way?"
"Shouldn't this part have been edited that way?"
- I'm sorry.
- I thought,
- "He's professional. He's amazing."
- Are you sure?
He called me again five minutes later.
- Five minutes later?
- Again?
"I do think that part should have been that way."
(He called again to point it out again.)
- Again?
- That's too much.
- Just five minutes later?
- Yes, I did say that.
- Sit down.
- Calm down.
- I did say that.
- Be quiet.
- He repeated the same thing.
- Seriously.
- How did you feel?
- Goodness.
"He's making me sick."
I thought, "He is a scary man."
- But...
- Yes.
One day, he wanted to meet me around his house,
so I went to see him.
Did he tell you to come?
- What did he talk about?
- He told you to come over?
- Around his house?
- He said, "I just want to..."
- "have a chat with you."
- I see.
It ended up as a five-hour discussion.
Five hours?
(He thought he was going crazy.)
- That's too much.
- We talked for five hours.
Say something to Cheol Min. Call his name.
Cheol Min, I'm sorry.
I'm not Cheol Min.
- Stop it.
- All right.
- Please tell him I'm sorry.
- Okay.
- Let's hear from Kwon Ryeol.
- Kwon Ryeol, say something.
- What do you think of him?
Mr Yu Jae Seok is...
- He sounds so polite.
- a nice person.
- He is.
- He is a really nice person,
but as a cameraman, I often have to run around next to him.
When Jong Kook pops up out of nowhere,
who wouldn't be surprised?
- Who wouldn't be scared?
- What did he say?
- But he always gets upset about it.
- About you being scared.
- What can I do?
- He got me into so many troubles.
- That's true.
- You're right.
What can he do, though?
(When Jae Seok is surprised, Kwon Ryeol is even more surprised.)
Why are you more surprised than me?
(It is scary.)
- Gosh.
- Why?
(Kwon Ryeol gives up shooting and runs away.)
Why did you run away?
(He even tripped over Jae Seok.)
What are you doing?
You can't help being startled.
- That's right.
- Right.
He runs away instead of filming me.
Sometimes, Jae Seok turns back all of a sudden.
- He bumps into the camera.
- Right.
Then he gets angry at me.
(He gets angry at me.)
It's his fault.
What is that?
- Gosh.
- It was his fault.
- I'm getting angry too.
- Kwon Ryeol sounds angry.
- He must be angry.
He should have stepped back.
(Bumping)
What are you doing?
(Jae Seok walked into the camera.)
- He can't predict where you'll go.
- Should I turn on a blinker?
- What do you expect me to do?
- How would he know?
I can't carry around a light on my back, you know?
- Kwon Ryeol, continue.
- He was doing his best.
Tell us everything.
When we have female guests,
he suddenly becomes so sensitive...
and tells me off for focusing too much on them.
He does focus on them too much.
- It is true.
- You really do that.
- When we have female guests,
- I just happened to be near them.
That's why I was filming them.
He scolded me for focusing too much on them.
You tend to have your mouth open while filming them.
That's true.
What's so wrong about smiling when I'm happy?
- He doesn't let you smile?
- That's too much.
Am I not allowed to smile? We're doing a variety show.
- We're supposed to be happy.
- He turns his camera away from me.
- It's a variety show.
- Why can't he smile?
I can't wait to hear from the last person.
- Jong Yoon.
- He worked for seven months.
Is Jae Seok really a nice person?
- Do you think so?
- It's not been so long.
Have you ever been disappointed in him?
(Let's watch a candid shot of Jae Seok.)
Jae Seok is...
(In front of Jae Seok's apartment a few days ago)
Please look as natural as you can.
I'll try to act naturally.
Can you keep my face out of the screen?
We'll make sure to hide your identity.
- Thank you.
- Your face will be kept out.
(Cameras are installed in the car.)
(The cameras are securely hidden.)
(He's trying to hide his face.)
(Jae Seok appeared.)
(Jae Seok is completely unaware.)
(He has a programme to shoot.)
- Good morning.
(The secret observation starts.)
(He puts on his seat belt as soon as he gets in the car.)
Where's my script?
(He looks for his script.)
(The script is here.)
- Jong Yoon.
- Yes.
(Focused)
- Did you have breakfast?
- Yes, I did.
(He's totally focused on reading his script.)
Why did you come out early today?
I saw you waiting outside.
(He looks very serious unlike in the show.)
(He doesn't take his eyes off the script.)
I have worries these days.
(He's too focused to answer back.)
I want to work, but I want to see my girlfriend too. What should I do?
Quit and see your girlfriend often.
(Quit and see your girlfriend often.)
But I want to work as well.
Then work hard.
What if I want to see my girlfriend as well?
(Sighing)
(He goes back to reading his script.)
(All of a sudden...)
Work hard, and do your best for your girlfriend.
That's it.
You're using work as an excuse.
(You're using work as an excuse.)
Okay.
(Back to reading script again)
- Be nice to her.
- Okay.
(After a short piece of advice,)
(he continues reading the script.)
(As he's too focused,)
(the manager can't distract him any more.)
(They arrive at the broadcasting station.)
(This was all we could get from the secret camera.)
I have a question.
Before you started working for Jae Seok,
you must have imagined about him.
How was he different from your imagination?
I thought he would be really nice,
but he's kind of picky.
(He's kind of picky.)
He's a picky person.
There you go!
- Now, we're talking.
- Go on.
- Now, you're talking.
- Continue.
It's nothing serious.
Well...
Jae Seok doesn't drink coffee.
- That's right.
- He doesn't.
- For his throat.
- One coffee shop...
- sells mango banana juice.
- I see.
Jae Seok wants it...
without mango, and the milk should be low-fat.
(Mango banana juice without mango?)
He's worse than me.
He's so picky.
The milk should be low-fat?
He's pickier than me.
It should be without mango, and the milk should be low-fat.
(No one expected this.)
I'm sorry. I thought it was on the menu.
- And?
- Is there anything else?
(Another disclosure)
While driving,
a lot of managers...
listen to music.
(A lot of other managers listen to music while driving.)
But I can't.
- Why?
Although Jae Seok loves music,
I was informed that he doesn't want it to be noisy in his car.
- Why is he so picky?
- Who told you that?
Why is that?
- That's not true.
- Who told you that?
- On the way,
- Goodness.
I usually read scripts or newspaper. That must be why someone said that.
But when I see him in the rear-view mirror,
he's listening to music loudly with earphones.
Alone?
- I listen to it alone.
- Alone?
I wish we listen to it together.
- It's because he...
- Okay. I will plug you in too.
- Wait.
- I will plug you in when you drive.
- Look.
- Calm down.
By the way, Jong Yoon, will you be all right?
I don't think I will be able to go home.
- Yes.
- It's your last day, right?
You ride in the back today, Jong Yoon.
(He's clenching his teeth.)
- I will drop you at your place.
- Goodness.
- He will play a song for you too.
- Yes, I will play a song for you.
Now, you can listen to whichever song you want to listen to.
I wonder...
what is the good for us...
to do this.
(What good does it do to them?)
(After the exposure, he tries to save himself.)
- All of a sudden.
- I'll be uncomfortable around him.
- What will I do now?
- Jong Yoon.
I will tell you what remains between us now. Bitter feelings.
Only bitter feelings remain between us.
We are at war now!
(He's upset.)
You betrayers! We are at war now!
- Goodness.
- Okay.
- I have something to say.
- Jong Yoon.
- He's very brave.
- Lastly...
I never knew he was like that.
- Jae Seok.
- Yes.
I like you.
(He tries to win Jae Seok's favour again.)
- What's that?
- I like you too.
- I love you.
- It's too late!
- I really love you.
- Goodness!
- Hey!
- Jae Seok!
(The second stage ends as it remains bitter feelings.)
(Running Man Q and A)
Let's move on to the third stage.
- Is there a third stage?
- This is the last stage.
- What is it?
- This is good.
It's a known fact that Jae Seok remembers...
- the staff's names well.
- Right.
That's how attentive he is.
- But now...
- What's the question?
"Does he remember the names of all the staff?"
He will pick 5 of the 50 names in the box.
He has to put the name tags on the right people.
- Did you say 5?
- Yes, 5.
If you get it wrong, you will be punished.
- So please make a careful choice.
- Okay.
I am very curious about how it will turn out.
- I think he knows everyone.
- This is a nice one.
So he will pick the names and take them to the right people.
Choose five cards.
They're all wearing blank name tags.
- They are.
- That's where you stick them.
Does Jae Seok know all their names?
This is nerve-wrecking.
What's for sure is that I don't know everyone's name.
Even though you don't know everyone's name,
- All right.
- "Ko Eun Mi".
He's lucky.
Eun Mi?
That sounds very familiar.
- But not the full name.
- I've heard it a lot too.
Same here. It sounds new with the last name.
- Eun Mi sounds familiar.
- We know who Eun Mi is.
All right. "Jo Seong Oh".
It's my first time hearing this name.
(Second person is Jo Seong Oh, in charge of filming Gary.)
- "Park Soo Yeon".
This is crazy. It's my first time hearing this name.
- Yong Woo.
- It's Yong Woo.
I know Yong Woo.
- Gyu Ho?
- Do we have such a person?
- We have Gyu Ho?
- Give it a try.
- I'm going to Yong Woo first.
- Yong Woo.
- I will go to Yong Woo first.
Yong Woo is right here.
- You can't avoid him.
- I know him.
- It's confusing with last names.
- Right?
- You can't avoid him.
- I know you, of course.
Yong Woo is...
(He looks at his face again.)
I knew it.
He's one of the producers.
He's Producer Park Yong Woo.
- I'm worried about the rest.
- Who's Soo Yeon?
Soo Yeon, Eun Mi...
(He has to find Eun Mi, Soo Yeon, Seong Oh and Gyu Ho.)
They are not here. I know you all.
(Why did he have to choose tricky ones?)
Come on.
- Aren't you Soo Yeon?
- If you are, please blink.
- Wait.
- Jae Seok.
There is one here too.
- Come over here.
- It's either her or...
Soo Yeon...
They are Sin Hye and Mi Yeon.
Soo Yeon is... Wait.
Jae Seok.
(Is Soo Yeon one of them?)
Soo Yeon... Well...
- Soo Yeon is over there.
- None of them is Soo Yeon.
- Wait.
- Oh, Soo Yeon.
Soo Yeon!
(He finds a girl who is suspected to be Soo Yeon.)
- Is it her?
- Soo Yeon!
- Is she the one?
- She's Soo Yeon.
- Wait, is she Soo Yeon?
- She is.
- You are Soo Yeon, right?
- Soo Yeon.
- Show your face.
Don't try to look pretty.
Are you Park Soo Yeon?
- Is she Soo Yeon?
- Is your last name Park?
- Leave her alone.
- I think she is Soo Yeon.
- In 1, 2 and 3.
- Wait.
(He will receive an unbelievable punishment if he fails.)
(What is...)
(your name?)
I think they will shoot you with a water gun.
- Oh, dear.
- It's Hyo Im.
(He gets shot with water guns.)
- It was Hyo Im.
- It wasn't her.
- It's not her.
- I am sorry, Hyo Im.
- It's okay.
- No, she's...
You're Soo Yeon, right?
I told you.
- You should've given it to her.
- Gosh.
Yes.
(He missed the youngest scriptwriter's name.)
She is Soo Yeon.
- She's the scriptwriter.
- The scriptwriter.
You are new, aren't you?
- She's not new.
- I told you.
- She's been here for a while.
- She's been working.
She always puts us on standby.
- Really?
- Yes.
- Eun Mi sounds familiar.
- I have that feeling.
- Eun Mi does sound familiar.
I'm not sure about Gyu Ho, though.
- It's my first time hearing it.
- Same here.
- I have a friend named Gyu Ho.
- Gyu Ho is my friend's name.
I think the guy over there is moving like Gyu Ho.
I can't help it.
I will just find a person that looks like Gyu Ho.
Over there.
- I think he's one of them.
- Isn't this...
- Check over there.
- fascinating?
- Over there.
- I'll find someone that looks...
like Gyu Ho.
- Someone must look like Gyu Ho.
- On the right side.
Gyu Ho.
Hey, Gyu Ho!
It's been a while!
(He picks a random staff.)
- Gyu Ho!
- Is he looking for an old friend?
- We've known for...
- What's that?
- What if he's not the one?
- Look at him.
You are not Gyu Ho, are you? Your face turned red.
His face is too red. That means it's not his name.
(He leaves without any hesitation.)
Gyu Ho!
You are Gyu Ho.
You are Gyu Ho, aren't you?
Jae Seok.
Give it a go.
- Give it a go.
- His face...
doesn't change at all.
- He's always like that.
- Give it a go.
You're always with Haha, aren't you?
- Yes.
- I didn't really get to...
work with Gyu Ho. Right?
- Yes, right.
- So you are Gyu Ho.
(It's Gyu Ho.)
Are you stupid?
- He is Gyu Ho.
- You are such an idiot.
- That's bad.
- That's really bad.
(If he can't remember it, he makes a smart guess.)
Gyu Ho!
- Jae Seok is smart.
- Hello.
- I know.
- Gyu Ho knows me.
I know Gyu Ho.
- Now, I have to find Eun Mi.
- Eun Mi and Seong Oh remain.
- I heard she's in the audio team.
- Actually, we don't know them.
- We don't get to talk to them.
- Right.
- We don't know.
- There aren't that many.
I know a girl who looks like Eun Mi.
Eun Mi.
Eun Mi. You are not Eun Mi.
You are not Eun Mi.
Jae Seok, you are really unlucky.
At the critical moment, he's very unlucky.
Why did he pick those names among all the names he knows?
- I know.
- He's so unlucky.
Joo Hee is here.
(Let's see.)
Eun Mi!
(He finds her.)
She's here. I found her.
- Come here, Eun Mi.
- Did you find her?
- I found her.
- Is that right?
- Eun Mi works really hard.
- Are you sure?
Really?
Where is it?
- Eun Mi.
- What if it's not her?
- I am sorry.
When you are struggling and working hard,
I never got to give you kind words. I am sorry about that.
Eun Mi.
(Eun Mi,)
(I'm sorry for everything.)
She's our producer.
- She's Eun Ji.
(He gets shot again.)
- She has the similar name.
- You were very close.
- Eun Ji is really upset.
- She's Eun Ji.
Eun Ji is...
- Eun Ji is really upset.
- You were too confident.
(She shot him with a water gun with fury.)
Where is Eun Mi? Let's see her face.
- Where is Eun Mi?
- Eun Mi!
- Oh, you were there.
- Yes!
- You are Eun Mi.
- How long have you been with us?
You're in the wardrobe.
- I've been here for a year.
- It's been a year already?
Kwang Soo, she's in the audio team.
Really? I am sorry.
(I should've kept quiet.)
- She's Eun Mi.
- Next is Seong Oh.
- You should know him.
- Let's see.
- Seong Oh is...
- You know...
- He's our floor director.
Seong Oh is?
(Maybe he's not.)
It's known that he remembers all the assistants' names.
Does he really?
(He gives a hint as he coughs.)
(His cough somehow sounds like an English word.)
- Hey!
- What was that?
(I got it.)
One of the cameramen here recently got married.
- Gi Jin.
- It's Seong Yong.
- Seong Yong got married.
- Seong Yong.
- Congratulations.
- I'll give you a wedding gift.
I am sorry. I will give you a wedding gift too.
You always work so hard.
- Seong Oh.
- Is he the one?
- It must be him.
- You work so hard too.
It must be him.
He's been working with us for a long time.
He's my cameraman, Seong Oh.
- Bingo.
- I am really sorry.
It didn't sound familiar because of your last name.
(He got Seong Oh right.)
- It's tricky with the last name.
- It is tricky.
They've been working with us for a long time, and we should...
- be aware of their names at least.
- Let's get to know them more.
- We're done verifying Jae Seok.
- He's a decent person,
but he's not very good at memorising names.
He's a decent man who's not good at memorising names.
- Yes. Thank you. – Yes.
(They are done with all the questions in the end.)
Great.
(However, the verification is not over yet.)
"Who is the unluckiest?"
(Who is the unluckiest?)
(The most popular question)
- Who is the unluckiest?
- A member with the least luck.
So it's a good thing to have the least luck.
- Lucky seven.
- What's this?
Four!
Welcome to the world of bad luck!
- You?
- You are...
- Hey!
- I broke up just yesterday.
(The members look for the unlucky celebrities.)
I resent Yu Jae Seok!
(It's the battle between two unlucky people.)
(What stops misfortune is a bigger misfortune.)
Gosh...
- Tae Hee just called me.
- We were going to fetch you.
Tae Hee, do you consider yourself lucky or unlucky?
(Next week's special is The First Unluckiest Festival.)
(Running Man)