(The First "I'm Sorry, I Love You" Special)
(A special project for the 300th episode.)
- "I'm sorry"?
-  I'm sorry.
(Some guests had a bad experience on Running Man.)
- I'm sorry.
-  I'm sorry.
- I want to apologise to you.
-  Please accept our apology.
(Running Man will apologise today.)
- You're so pretty.
-  That's too much.
This is too hard.
(They are customised apologies.)
You jerk.
(Will the apologies be accepted?)
Don't hold him.
(They confess the truth for the first time in six years.)
I wasn't healthy, so I was put in a slump.
I thought I should leave Running Man at this point.
Thank you.
(The Running Man stories will now unfold.)
(It's 8am on the day of filming.)
(Jae Seok begins the day with a cup of tea.)
(Seok Jin's nose is swollen.)
Shall we go?
(Ji Hyo woke up early today.)
(Let's go)
- Are we leaving now?
-  Yes.
(This is how the Running Man members begin their commute.)
The weather is nice.
It's a lovely day.
(Enjoying the spring day, they turn on the radio.)
You're listening to "Beautiful Morning" and I'm Kim Chang Wan.
You must be caught in traffic and feeling tired right now.
I have a letter that will wake you up.
It's a letter from Jee Seok Jin who lives in Bundang-gu...
to Lee Kwang Soo who lives in Geumho-dong.
"Dearest Kwang Soo."
- "This is Seok Jin."
-  Is this from Seok Jin?
"Do you remember? While we were filming,"
"I told you that no matter how hard you try,"
"you'll only be as handsome as Song Joong Ki's feet."
"I'm so sorry."
"I never expected the staff would put a foot on your face."
"You're the Prince of Asia. I just wanted to be funny."
It was funny.
"Let's continue to work hard."
"I hope we'll all be happy. From Seok Jin."
Let's listen to a song that speaks Seok Jin's mind.
"A Foot" by Shin Il Soo.
(Laughing)
Is there a song called "A Foot"? Seriously?
What does a foot have to do with me?
This is the happiest foot in the world
I'll read the next letter.
It's a letter from Haha who lives in Mapo-gu.
"Dear Gary. It all started last winter."
"While we were playing a game in the X-Man Special,"
"I asked you if you're a squid."
"Everyone burst into laughter at my joke."
"It's been a few months and everybody calls you a squid now."
(Who are you to call me a squid?)
Did you see it?
(Giggling)
(What is it?)
He is the real squid.
(Meet the squid's friend.)
(It's hard to decide which of the two is uglier.)
Let me read you the last letter.
It's from Kwang Soo, the youngest member of Running Man.
"Dear Haha."
"Do you know what my favourite part of our team dinner is?"
"It's when we switch roles and I get to be older than you."
"One day, you said I only have three more chances to do that."
"I've already used all my chances."
"I wasn't able to restrain myself and I used them all."
"It's only April."
"I can't wait to treat you as if you're younger than me."
"I promise I won't waste more chances. I'll see you soon."
- "I'm sorry I treat you like..."
-  Chang Wan's voice...
makes the stories sound so beautiful.
They're not supposed to be beautiful.
"See you in a bit, smiling. I love you."
I'm touched by the friendship between the Running Man members.
I hope this warmed your hearts on the way to the set.
I'll always cheer for Running Man.
You've listened to "Beautiful Morning" and I am Kim Chang Wan.
I love Chang Wan's voice.
This was nice.
(What will be waiting for them today?)
(The members arrive at SBS.)
Did you listen to the radio on the way here?
- Yes.
-  It was embarrassing.
I can't look at the person I wrote to in the eye.
- It is a bit embarrassing.
-  It is.
Haha, will you give Kwang Soo more chances?
- I already gave him enough.
-  Wasn't it more than 10?
- He doesn't need my permission.
-  It's a free pass for him.
I can even do it now. Hey!
- Also...
-  You guys are funny.
- Continue to talk like that.
-  You should...
pay him for more chances.
- You should pay him.
-  I accept credit cards.
- Today's theme is...
-  Yes.
Today's theme is this.
Something's coming down.
(It's a spring special.)
Today's theme is this.
- "I'm sorry?"
-  "I'm sorry."
Today, we'll shoot the First "I'm Sorry, I Love You" Special.
If there's anyone among our guests...
that you feel sorry to or wish to make things better with,
you'll go apologise to them and do them a favour.
(The members will provide a special apology service.)
Among our guests, I feel sorry for Kwang Soo.
- Why?
-  Why am I a guest?
- Aren't you a guest?
-  What are you talking about?
- You've been a guest for six years.
-  Shouldn't I be accepted by now?
- He's been with us for six years.
-  That's why I'm sorry.
He always manages to match his clothes with us.
Do you think I prepared these clothes?
Do you think I bought them myself?
You kept coming back for six years.
That's absurd.
You were our first guest and you came every week.
- We couldn't kick you out.
-  I'm a member.
We're so kind.
(I'm Sorry, I Love You)
(The members visit the guests they feel sorry to.)
There's someone I feel sorry to.
(Feelings of regret begin to form.)
- Haeryung from BESTie.
-  Exactly. Haeryung.
- I failed to lift her on my back.
-  I remember.
- That's right.
-  I didn't succeed.
- Haeryung.
-  That's right.
- I feel most sorry to her.
-  I see.
I feel so sorry to G-Dragon as well.
- G-Dragon.
-  Do you remember?
- I felt sorry, too.
-  He seemed dispirited later on.
- We should feel sorry for him.
-  Really.
G-Dragon was going through a hard time back then.
He was having a hard time.
(Spring flowers are in full bloom in the streets of Samcheong-dong.)
(Today's first guest is shooting a commercial.)
(He's dazzling like the spring weather.)
(It's the popular actor, Park Seo Joon.)
Tell me how the driver is doing!
(He's stolen many hearts with his acting.)
You're so cute.
- How are you feeling?
-  This is so nice.
(Through his four appearances on Running Man,)
(he has proven himself as an entertainer.)
You don't look like yourself.
You're still handsome.
- Everybody, Seo Joon is here.
-  Seo Joon!
- I'm sorry!
-  Seo Joon, we're sorry!
- Seo Joon, I'm sorry!
-  Seo Joon, I'm sorry.
- It's Park Seo Joon!
-  What are you sorry for?
(Why are they apologising to Seo Joon?)
- I'm sorry, Seo Joon.
-  It's good to see you.
- I'm sorry.
-  You look so handsome.
You're so handsome. Why are you so handsome?
He actually has the best type of face.
- You'll never get sick of him.
-  No, you won't.
- He only becomes more charming.
-  By the way,
you've only met Seo Joon as a guest on the show.
But I've watched him film in other places.
- He's a big star.
-  Wasn't he handsome?
There were these huge umbrellas covering him the whole time.
- That's amazing.
-  We're sorry.
- We have to hold it ourselves.
-  Does anybody have an umbrella?
- He's going to get sunburned.
-  Seo Joon.
- Seo Joon, we're sorry.
-  Why are you...
treating me nicer than usual?
(They're suddenly treating him nicely.)
Make sure his face doesn't get covered by the shade.
- It's covering his face already.
-  I'm sorry, Seo Joon.
- Seo Joon!
-  Thank you.
We should have done this for you earlier.
Let me hold this for you. I have so much energy left over.
He has a lot of energy remaining.
This is Seo Joon's fifth appearance on our show.
- Already?
-  Really?
- He's appeared a lot on this show.
-  No kidding.
And every time he was on it, he always worked hard.
I'm pretty sure you all know already,
- but let me read this for you.
-  Go ahead.
"Park Seo Joon is like family to Running Man."
Isn't that just our opinion?
"During the winter, we made you walk..."
"barefoot in the icy water."
"And even worse, during the Beautiful Youth Race,"
"your name was mistakenly written as Lee Seo Joon."
"We sincerely apologise."
- He deserves an apology.
-  We were wrong.
That's like saying Park Jae Seok instead of Yu Jae Seok.
- That was bad.
-  We must apologise.
Seo Joon, we're really sorry for the mistake with the captions.
Mistakes like that happen.
I was okay with it, but my parents...
(My parents were hurt.)
That's even more hurtful.
You changed my father's last name to "Lee".
- You guys should know better.
-  You hurt his family.
- Let's toss him in the air, then.
-  All right.
- What?
-  All of a sudden?
- Seo Joon.
-  No, we owe you this much.
- Come here, Seo Joon.
-  Come here.
- We have to do this for you.
-  Don't worry.
(This is the best way to apologise.)
- In 1, 2, 3.
-  In 1, 2, 3.
- One more time.
(This looks like a World Cup celebration.)
- Be careful.
-  That was good.
- That came out of nowhere.
-  No, it's because...
I don't know if this is enough to receive forgiveness.
Seo Joon got frostbitten last time.
I was in the middle of shooting a drama at the time.
I ended up with a bad flu the next day.
It was cold that day.
We walked barefoot for that episode.
The ground was covered in snow and we walked on it with bare feet.
- It wasn't even for a short time.
-  Exactly.
It was very cold but Seo Joon acted like he was fine.
Why did you do that?
- Because it was my first time.
-  It was his first time on the show.
- He wanted to try his best.
-  I wanted to do my best.
- That's why.
-  You're the best.
It was freezing, right? He kept on saying he wasn't cold.
- Let's take care of his feet today.
-  Let's wipe them for him.
- Let's do it together.
-  I hope it's not too late.
- Let's wash his feet.
-  All right.
Let's get ready.
- Seriously?
-  Come on over.
- Come here.
-  Don't feel troubled, Seo Joon.
We thought about bathing you, too.
- This doesn't look right.
-  Have a seat.
- Have a seat.
-  Sit down, Seo Joon.
This is a full set.
- Seo Joon, take off your shoes.
-  Take them off.
I'm sorry, Seo Joon.
- I didn't know.
-  I'm wearing socks.
- It's okay. You can take them off.
-  That's not a problem.
- Just take them off.
-  His feet are handsome, too.
- Get comfortable.
-  Don't be shy. It's all right.
It looks like you got a pedicure.
Look at your feet.
- They're so white.
-  Why are your feet so white?
Look, there's a beauty mark between his first and second toe.
- Let's wash between his toes.
-  Is this right?
This is how you do it.
- During my lifetime
-  During my lifetime
(They begin their apology with a song.)
- There's one thing
-  There's one thing
- He was frostbitten.
-  I must do
You know what?
You need to release tension in other areas as well.
(This is too burdensome for him.)
- Even if I stand
-  You have to massage here.
(In apology, they pour their hearts...)
(into relieving Seo Joon's stress.)
(Foot massages are good for your health.)
- If one pine needle falls
-  If one pine needle falls
- The tears will flow
-  We're sorry.
(Seo Joon must be uncomfortable.)
(He's dazed.)
Isn't this refreshing?
- Do you like it?
-  Seo Joon.
- Weren't we bad?
-  Really.
(The members put their all into the apology.)
Your feet look nice, Seo Joon.
(Hard feelings have been resolved.)
(But his eyes are losing focus.)
- Isn't this refreshing?
-  Do you like it?
Aren't you happy, Seo Joon?
Yes, sure.
Your feet look nice, Seo Joon.
- That's it.
-  Am I hurting you?
- Look at his feet.
-  Stop feeling uncomfortable. Enjoy.
- Stay still.
-  Pretend there's nothing here.
- Don't look.
-  There are so many cameras here.
Seo Joon, let's take a photo now.
With his feet?
(Seo Joon's feet look the prettiest.)
(This kind of photo shoot is a first.)
This photo should be titled, "His foot is Most Handsome."
- We have to wash it again.
-  We should.
- Thanks so much.
-  Handle it with care.
- Your feet will have a nice scent.
-  Sorry.
We're really sorry.
(Kissing)
Hey!
You went too far. Don't make him feel uncomfortable.
That made me feel very uncomfortable.
That was a good one. Good one, Seo Joon.
Go away, you punk!
Get lost!
He kissed Seo Joon's foot.
- What was that for?
-  Why would you do that?
- That was unnecessary.
-  What was that for?
He's uncomfortable.
Here are your socks.
- Your socks.
-  He'll feel uncomfortable again.
Why? What's wrong with putting on his socks?
- That's okay.
-  He'll put them on by himself.
It doesn't smell bad at all.
- Don't smell them.
-  He'll feel uncomfortable.
- It doesn't smell bad.
-  Why would you smell it?
- Why would you smell it?
-  Try it.
- Smell it.
-  I'll take it.
- His socks...
-  Move over.
His socks smell like flowers.
They smell like black locust flowers.
- What do you mean by flowers?
-  They smell like flowers.
(His feet went through a lot more than before.)
- I'm getting sweaty.
-  That was good.
This is nice. It puts us at ease.
Since it's time for lunch, we'll serve food.
- That sounds like a good idea.
-  Yes!
That sounds good.
- They're three-layered lunch boxes.
-  Look at the lunch boxes.
That looks great.
- That looks good.
-  No kidding.
This is great.
- You should sit, Seo Joon.
-  Goodness.
- Sit back down.
-  Just stay still.
You should stay still.
- Don't do anything.
-  I'll get upset if you move.
- I'll get upset, too.
-  We won't just watch.
This is nice.
- Have some.
-  Thank you for the food.
- Aren't you guys having some?
-  I'm going to take some.
Me, too.
(There are salads, sandwiches and side dishes.)
The sandwiches are delicious.
Seo Joon, do your feet feel refreshed?
Yes, I'm not planning on washing them tonight.
- All right.
-  They'll feel better.
You can take some of our energy.
(Laughing)
Look who's talking.
Stop making him angry.
- You're annoying him.
-  Why?
Aren't you happy, Seo Joon? Take all our good energy.
- Sorry.
-  Seo Joon.
Seok Jin keeps telling me that people think he's in his 30s.
Isn't that exaggerated?
Don't people think you're in your 20s?
- I'm in my 20s.
-  Really?
(We're all embarrassed of Seok Jin.)
- I'm sorry.
-  Seok Jin.
Why do you keep upsetting him?
Is there a mission you must complete?
- Are you a spy? Should I rip this?
-  What is it really?
What's your role today?
I'm learning so much about Seo Joon today.
What is he saying?
Stop talking.
I don't know how to resolve this situation.
(It's hard to apologise.)
Before we send him off, we have something else for him.
Last time, he was Ji Hyo's partner.
- But she gave him a hard time.
-  That's right.
- I'm sorry, Seo Joon.
-  Ji Hyo didn't treat him well.
(During that episode...)
It's okay.
You're really bad at describing things.
(Ji Hyo scolded Seo Joon that day.)
As an expression of our apology,
- we'll replay charades again.
-  Okay.
- I'm really bad at this game.
-  Whoever doesn't guess it right...
will get a flick in the forehead.
That sounds good.
Seo Joon's really bad at this game, though.
No matter how he acts it out, you must get it right. If you don't,
the penalty is on you.
- So we have to guess it, right?
-  He won't get punished, then?
- No, he's exempt.
-  Right, we put you through a lot.
Whoever gets the wrong answer will get a flick in the forehead.
Let's go, Jong Kook.
- Can we talk?
-  I think it'll be hard.
Seo Joon, we would love to hit Jong Kook's forehead.
- Can you make it extra hard?
-  Hold on.
- How should I do this?
-  Make it hard.
Get set, go!
(Spring)
- Hurry.
-  I can't think of anything.
Oh, dear.
- There are five seconds left.
-  Can you pause the time?
- He doesn't know what to do.
-  Either way, it's not his fault.
- But he needs more time.
- Time's up.
- Okay.
-  How...
How was I supposed to act this out?
- It's not his fault.
-  That was a difficult question.
- What was I supposed to do?
-  It's still our fault.
(Jong Kook receives the punishment!)
- Let's watch.
-  Isn't Seo Joon supposed to do it?
Seo Joon is doing it. Why are you guys getting close?
Get away! He's supposed to do it. Come on, Seo Joon.
- I can't hit you.
-  It's okay. Go ahead.
- We'll do it for you.
-  Just flick your finger.
- We can show you how to do it.
-  Right.
I'll just show him how to do it.
Sure, I'll show him then.
(Sure, I'll show him.)
Watch me. Reveal his forehead...
Slap like this.
(Slapping hard)
- That's the way.
-  That looks nice.
- No, that's not how you do it.
-  Yes, it is.
- He did it right.
-  No, hold on a second.
- That's how you should flick.
-  Hold on a second.
- Hold on and take a seat.
-  If you...
- If you don't know how to flick,
-  Okay, show me.
I will show you. Take a look.
You just pull the hair back and...
Slap.
This is the way. Got it?
We should hurry up.
- I'd like to give it a try.
-  Seo Joon.
It's okay. Give it a try.
Stretch your hand wide to make the sound louder.
Stretch your hand wide.
- How can I...
-  You can do it.
- Why not?
-  Come on.
- Give it a try.
-  Come on, Seo Joon.
Slap hard.
- Okay then.
-  Right.
Let me pull back more hair.
(Just a little bit more)
- That's it.
-  Good.
I'm sorry.
- It's all right.
-  That's okay, Seo Joon.
- But I must slap you properly.
-  That's right.
- Sure.
-  Yes. Slap him properly.
(Chilled)
- I'll count to three.
-  Go, Seo Joon.
Come on. Just slap him.
(Slapping)
(High five)
Don't grab him. Don't touch him.
- Let him be.
-  Seo Joon.
- Leave him.
-  Don't look at him.
- Turn around.
-  Don't look.
We have to make guesses.
- Seo Joon, go ahead.
-  Give us the next word.
- I'm taking a look.
-  What are you doing?
- Let's move on.
-  That was loud.
Let's move on.
Next one.
What is this?
The sound was too loud.
- That was really loud.
-  You did well.
- That was fine.
-  Good hit, Seo Joon.
- Seo Joon did it.
-  That was nice.
(Right in his forehead)
- He really did it.
-  It makes me feel good.
- I feel good.
-  That was a big slap.
- I'm sorry.
-  That's fine.
- Wow.
-  Well done.
Well done, Seo Joon.
That really was good.
I didn't expect such sound.
Feel free to slap others too.
- Okay. Next.
-  Who is the next person?
- It's you, Kwang Soo. Right?
-  Yes, it is.
I'm going to get this right.
- Okay.
-  Please do.
Ready.
Hold on.
- Okay.
-  Be casual.
- All right.
-  I will get it.
(Both seem to be determined.)
- Ready, set..
-  Did you see it?
- Yes, I did.
-  Start.
- Is this the one?
-  Yes.
(Squid)
Squid... Squid...
(Master of Cheating)
(What? An onigiri?)
You really are...
Squid.
(Squid)
- No, that's too late.
-  Here, take a seat.
(He was close but timed out.)
- Hey, Jae Seok.
-  It's over. Isn't it?
Can you slap him instead?
- How about Haha?
-  Yes. Haha is good.
- Will Haha slap me?
-  No. Not Haha.
I'd like to learn how to slap.
All right. I'll teach you.
- Put some water on your hand.
-  Water is too much.
(Haha puts water on his hand to enhance the pain.)
That will give him a nice slap.
- A big slap.
-  And shake off excess water.
Shake off water. Good.
- He has a wide forehead.
-  Hold his hair back.
- Hold his hair.
-  There.
Open your arms. Good.
I'd rather take a quick hit.
I think so, too.
Ready.
(Slapping)
(Ouch)
He collapsed.
(That was really loud.)
Let's take a look.
That doesn't seem right.
He slapped your skull inside.
What is this?
Why does the back of my head hurt?
He slapped your skull, not your skin.
I was slapped front, but the back of my head hurts.
- That's funny.
-  Because he slapped your skull.
- I see.
-  That's why, Kwang Soo.
Okay. And here comes the last person, Ji Hyo.
Don't spare your hands because it's Ji Hyo.
- Don't.
-  Actually, we are here...
- because of Ji Hyo.
-  That's right.
- Seo Joon, come forward.
-  I'm so sorry, Seo Joon.
- No, I'm fine.
-  I'm sorry.
- How can I do this?
-  Will she get it right?
You are a genius if you get this.
(It must be a difficult word.)
Set, start.
(Australopithecus)
She looks like she got it.
- He's really good.
-  Tyrannosaurus.
- She's almost there.
-  What did you say?
- Tyrannosaurus.
-  That was close.
- He suddenly stood up.
-  Oh, is it...
Is it...
(He walked erect as a hint. Can she guess the answer?)
Is it human?
(Human)
- Evolution. You know, evolution.
-  You're close.
Can't you remember the word?
- Oh, what is it?
-  Remember the word.
- Say the word.
-  She doesn't know.
Oh goodness.
That was close.
Oh, it's Australiapithecus.
- What?
-  Australia?
(Did human originate from Australia?)
- Australia?
-  So did we originate from there?
- From Australia?
-  What's Australiapithecus?
- No way.
-  Australiapithecus.
That didn't make any sense.
How about Austriapithecus?
- All right. It's your turn.
-  Okay.
- We are all here to apologise.
-  Yes.
I'll go easy on you.
- I will slap you on three.
-  Okay.
- You'd better close your eyes.
-  I'm okay.
- You won't?
-  No.
(Slapping)
It's just for fun.
What is wrong with you?
What's the problem?
- Where are you going?
-  That's scary.
What are you doing?
Hey, you. Come here.
No, Ji Hyo. No.
(Let me put an end to this.)
Calm down, Ji Hyo.
- Calm down. Patience, Ji Hyo.
-  Hey, you. Come on.
Patience, Ji Hyo.
Calm down, Ji Hyo.
- Wow. Kwang Soo.
-  Ji Hyo.
(Scared)
Calm down, Ji Hyo.
- Calm down.
-  That was funny.
(Kwang Soo unleashed her inner self.)
That was really scary.
(That's how they get along.)
All right.
This is for Seo Joon.
We are going around to apologise today.
I'm worried we might be hurting each other's feelings instead.
We'll see how things will turn out.
- We will see.
-  All right. Seo Joon.
- Yes.
-  Please accept our apology.
- I accept.
-  Thank you.
Have a bite of an apple.
- Should I?
-  Yes.
(Biting an apple shows that he accepted the apology.)
(That was a big bite.)
He accepted it.
- Show yourself again in the show.
-  Probably as a producer.
- We will surely entertain you.
-  We will.
- We will do our best.
-  Without making any mistake.
- So please show yourself again.
-  Please.
- Please call me later.
-  Thank you.
You are cool, Seo Joon.
- Sorry, Seo Joon.
-  I am sorry.
- We're sorry, Seo Joon.
-  Thank you.
- Thank you.
-  I love you, Seo Joon.
I won't blame you next time.
(I'm Sorry, I Love You.)
She was in my team and I felt so sorry to her.
She had a tough day.
She is a mother of three children.
She hadn't been on TV for a few years.
She hadn't been for a long time,
so we hoped her to have a memorable time with us.
Probably we should have taken better care of her.
But at that time,
she had a really tough day with us.
- We had not much to talk.
-  There she is.
- There she is.
-  Hello.
(She...)
(has arrived.)
(Who is today's second guest?)
- Hello.
-  I'm sorry.
(She's the popular actress, Lee Yo Won.)
(An outstanding actress)
(She showed herself in dramas, movies, adverts and more.)
(She had a tough time on Running Man.)
- Hello.
-  I'm sorry.
- Hello, Yo Won.
-  Hello.
- Hello.
-  Hello. Nice to see you.
-  Hello, Yo Won.
- You've lost weight.
-  Yes. I've been busy.
- She's in a drama now.
-  She's been acting recently.
She's acting a hot-tempered character.
(She's acting a hot-tempered character.)
Yo Won had a really tough time...
on Running Man last time. Was it your first entertainment show?
Was it your first time?
- I had been on really old ones.
-  Really old ones?
She had been on really old ones and showed herself on Running Man.
And had a really tough time.
You were almost exhausted, weren't you?
You had some hard time in the swimming pool.
- Yes.
-  In the swimming pool.
We're sorry, so we're going around providing Apology Service.
- So we'd like to apologise.
-  Okay.
(You have my ears.)
"Running Man was your first entertainment show."
"We handed you many short scripts,"
"and gave you many troubles."
"Your hair became all scruffy throughout the show."
"We're sorry that your image as an actress was tarnished."
- We are so sorry.
-  Sorry.
Isn't it normal to show such images in entertainment shows?
Isn't it?
- Aren't we here to apologise?
-  Keep your words to yourself.
Even men would have found the game difficult.
And you participated in the game.
She was holding on to her clothes really tightly.
We have brought this for you today.
(The memory of the day...
that she doesn't want to remember.)
You had a tough day.
- You looked like a prisoner.
-  It's because...
- she was totally exhausted.
-  Like a prisoner on the run.
On that day,
- I was really fatigued.
-  You were.
I felt really awkward at first because there were so many cameras.
I usually see 1 or 2 cameras at once.
I was so aware of the cameras at first.
But later when I was like that,
- they were just out of my sight.
-  That happens.
- Because you were so tired.
-  I couldn't see any.
I still remember her when Haha was leading the way.
Haha found a way and she said "Well done!"
Yes, right. She did.
- Yes, she did.
-  She said "Well done!"
That was really impressive.
- So we called her mum.
-  Yes, we called her mum.
Step forward and sit on the couch.
(She showed that she was warm-hearted.)
Go forward. A bit more.
- There.
-  Nice. Good job.
(Well done)
Anyway, Yo Won is here today.
- And we must make our apologies.
-  We do.
- We must apologise.
-  We are here for it.
First, we should make her stand out the most.
Just make Gary sit next to her.
- What should we do?
-  We don't need to do anything.
- She needs to sit still.
-  That will be enough.
- That is...
-  To be honest...
Not many will suit these accessories.
- You look nice, Kwang Soo.
-  Look at Kwang Soo.
(What are they doing?)
All right.
- You look amazing.
-  That hair suits you well.
(His face is like a weapon.)
- Look at Gary.
-  That doesn't look good at all.
He looks like he could fight well.
He really looks scruffy. A scruffy beggar.
They are all weird.
- What is this?
-  Are we back in Joseon Dynasty?
- You look like you're on a war.
-  I'm afraid to see Gary's face.
He is outstanding.
(He is outstanding.)
- Are you the runaway slave?
-  More like a beggar I think.
That's amazing.
Today, Yo Won must be...
in the centre and highlighted the most.
- That's really nice.
-  It is.
That's really good. Look, Yo Won.
- It's very bright.
-  You look gorgeous.
- Thank you.
-  What we're doing now is...
It doesn't look like we are making her stand out.
It's more like she's taking us in and looking after us.
- You're not at an award ceremony.
-  Right.
She was kind enough to encompass us all.
- We look like aliens.
-  I really mean it.
- Gosh.
-  We should make weird looks.
- Whoever looks normal gets penalty.
-  Okay.
Loser will get a hit on his forehead.
One, two, three.
(Feeling sorry, they try hard to make weird looks on their faces.)
(We are still humans.)
Pick one person who looks fine in the photo. He'll receive a penalty.
- This is very hard...
-  We all have unique characters.
because some people don't even have to try to look ugly.
- Right.
-  So who is that?
Gary.
(It's obvious.)
I am jealous.
- You're the best.
-  He was born that way.
- We can never beat him.
-  Wasn't that a bit unfair?
Please choose the one who you found hard to judge.
- Please choose one.
-  We did our best...
- to make ugly faces.
-  This is really difficult.
It's okay. Just name one.
(This is hard.)
Seok Jin and Haha.
(They are ugly. But they're not ugly enough.)
Wow.
- Should I pick just one person?
-  Yes, please.
I really tried my best.
- Please be subjective.
-  This is really hard.
You should be subjective so that the viewers can agree with you.
I am sorry.
- She said sorry to you.
-  Is it Seok Jin?
(Seok Jin gets the penalty.)
- Yes!
-  Don't be sorry.
- I am fine. I am.
-  I am so sorry.
- I think Haha tried to look stupid.
-  Yes.
But I look ambiguous, don't I?
- No, I mean... A little ambiguous.
-  You look creepy here.
If I can make Yo Won happy by sacrificing myself...
Please do not use such noble word as "sacrifice" here.
That's not what we call sacrifice.
I want Yo Won to hit my forehead.
- Then, would you do that for him?
-  Okay. Let's do that.
Hit him hard.
She stood up right away because she wants to hit me.
- My slaps tend to be powerful.
-  It is okay.
Seok Jin got used to it because he has been hit a lot.
- Take a seat.
-  Don't worry.
- I am okay. Hit me.
-  So do I hit like this?
- Yes, hit him hard.
-  That is right.
- I'm sorry.
-  Don't be.
Please take your ring off.
- I did.
-  Be careful with your bracelet.
- Seok Jin is kneeling down.
-  She's like my high school teacher.
- Yo Won, he will be okay.
-  Just hit him hard.
Get ready. One, two...
- I've never hit anyone before.
-  She is a talented actress.
- Now or never.
-  Use your palm and hit him.
(Hard spanking)
- You were good.
-  Good job.
- It is okay.
-  You did a good job.
- She was amazing.
-  My goodness.
- It's okay.
-  My hand hurts.
- He is okay.
-  Gosh.
- It's fine.
-  He's okay.
(Apology Service succeeded.)
We've changed the game Yo Won played before a bit.
We'll put a cup on each member's head.
Then, Yo Won will wear an eye mask and pour water into the cup.
If the water in your cup is between these two lines, you succeed.
But if you fail, you'll get the water splashed on your face.
- Then, as I was in the same team...
-  You were in the same team.
She was like the mother figure in our team before.
Let us three, me, Haha and Yo Won play.
- Then, we will go first.
-  Mothers have keen senses.
- Yo Won must be good at this.
-  You can do it.
- Okay.
-  Get ready.
- Yo Won, be confident.
-  Take your hands off.
Okay.
- Jae Seok should call for stop.
-  Yes, Jae Seok calls for stop.
Start!
Good. You're doing great.
Wow, you're good.
Great. Good.
Stop. Stop.
(Water overflows a bit.)
(Although it overflew, Yo Won skilfully topped the cup up.)
This is amazing.
- Look now.
-  Take your eye mask off.
- It's amazing.
-  It's unbelievable.
- Wow.
-  You did a great job.
-  Isn't this good enough?
- Please dash water over his face.
-  It's still a fail though.
- Is this a fail?
-  Does he get water splashed?
- A full cup is a fail.
-  I was so close.
- It's Haha's turn now.
-  Nice.
Here is your cup.
- Please get ready.
-  She is good.
- Okay.
-  I'm sorry.
- Start.
-  Hold the cup tight.
(She pours water without hesitation.)
(Gushing)
(Water flows over Haha's face.)
(I was wet too.)
- Stop. Stop!
-  That's it.
(Wait)
- Can I take the cup down?
-  You succeeded.
- You made it!
-  Success!
Gosh, why are you interrupting me?
(Splashing)
(You deserve a water slap.)
Haha.
- This is so funny.
-  It was a mistake!
- You know it was a mistake!
-  But he could've succeeded.
- I did it out of habit.
-  What are you doing?
I'm going to wipe up the water.
- Kwang Soo wants the splash too.
-  Yo Won.
It's Kwang Soo's turn.
- I think I know when to stop now.
-  Okay.
- It takes about 4.5 seconds.
-  You have only 1 chance.
- I timed it. It took 4.5 seconds.
-  Get ready.
I think it was five seconds. Good. Start when I tell you so.
- Okay.
-  Start when I tell you to start.
I didn't tell you to start yet.
Can she start without me telling her to start?
Start!
One, two, three, four, five. Stop.
(Stop now)
(Kwang Soo took a short shower.)
- Good job.
-  My goodness.
- She watered you.
-  You did a good job.
- She watered you a lot.
-  Wow.
I didn't touch his cup.
- Jae Seok will receive penalty.
-  Only me?
I am sure you've shot this scene a lot.
- I've done it.
-  In "Ms Temper and Nam Jung Gi"...
I'm sure you're familiar with these scenes.
- Was it the first episode?
-  To Mr Kim.
You did it to Mr Kim.
You jerk.
(Yo Won splashed water over Mr Kim's face, pleasing the viewers.)
(Would you present such impressive splash to Jae Seok too?)
Ready, action!
Gosh, you're so pathetic.
Why did you come to my office? You're annoying.
You shouldn't have come here.
(Splashing)
(You jerk)
(Yo Won hits Jae Seok hard with the water!)
(Yo Won, it's all my fault.)
- You did a great job.
-  Wow.
- I was really frightened.
-  You did good.
- You did great.
-  Good, good.
(Apology Service is completed.)
- This is a gift.
-  Apples?
- Yo Won, we're really sorry.
-  Thank you.
- Thanks for accepting it.
- Thanks.
-  We're sorry, Yo Won.
- It means you accept our apology.
-  Right, take a bite.
This is clean.
(Hesitating)
I am sorry, but are you mad at us?
- You accept our apology, right?
-  Yes.
I'll never forget the look on her face.
- I was really...
-  "You jerk."
(Her eyes were scarier than the water splash.)
- So, do I eat this apple?
-  Yes, please.
Please take a bite.
(She bites the apple.)
My teeth are weak.
(Yo Won's teeth are too weak.)
- Don't do it.
-  Don't bite it then.
- Yo Won, don't do it.
-  We understand you.
We don't want your teeth pulled out because of this.
- It is okay, Yo Won.
-  Thank you.
Good.
- That was funny.
-  We succeeded.
(I'm Sorry, I Love You)
Wow, there is the panel.
- Look.
-  Gosh.
- We are in this webtoon.
-  Right.
I am a big fan of Jo Seok.
- We should apologise to him.
-  We are sorry.
- Especially, Kwang Soo...
-  Right, I am sorry.
- should have tried harder.
-  Right.
- It's your fault, Kwang Soo.
-  But you failed to make it fun.
- Right. It was my fault.
-  Okay.
- Wow.
-  He is here.
Hello.
- Hello.
-  We're so sorry.
I am a big fan of yours.
(This 10-year-old webtoon has 1,000 episodes with 50 billion views.)
(The creator of "The Sound of Your Heart", Jo Seok)
(He appeared on our show as Kwang Soo visited him.)
(However)
(He appeared on the screen for about 5 minutes out of 95 minutes.)
- It was nice meeting you.
-  Thank you.
(Soon after...)
(Hello, everyone. I am the webtoon master.)
(Okay, goodbye then)
(Is this Running Man? I love this show.)
(- You did great job today.
-  Thank you. Bye.)
(He expressed his feelings through his webtoon.)
(You must be very disappointed.)
- I am your big fan.
-  We are sorry.
- You look very cute.
You look happy today. But on that day, you had a grim look.
- We would like to apologise.
-  It's okay.
We all read your webtoon.
I drew it because I thought I was never going to see you again.
(Running Man just started. Oh, there is our Seok!)
You were pretty disappointed, weren't you?
You even drew that episode. Right?
I was okay with that. But many around me kept asking me.
- "Were you really on the show?"
-  I see.
So lied to them that they must've missed the scenes that I appeared.
- I see.
-  I never expected to be here again.
"Jo Seok. Thank you for making time for us despite your schedule."
"We're sorry we let you down. You didn't appear on the show much..."
"when you were excited about the name tag ripping game."
"Again, we apologise for disappointing you."
- We're sorry.
-  We're sorry.
- We have him here with us, today.
-  Right.
When other programmes ask him to appear on their show,
- he doesn't easily go.
-  He's hard to cast.
He doesn't appear on many programmes.
Jo Seok said he'd love to play the name tag ripping game.
(The name tag ripping game?)
- Let's make him win.
-  Here?
I'll make him win.
(It's a uniform for Jo Seok.)
- You didn't have to do this.
-  Let's do this.
Jo Seok is worried that things are getting out of hand.
It's not what he intended.
Who would you like to play against?
- I gave it some thought.
-  Right.
- As it's a rare chance...
-  Jong Kook?
I'd like to play against Jong Kook.
You should.
I wouldn't mind getting beaten up by him.
You don't have to feel embarrassed even if you lose to him.
- It's a good experience.
-  Please keep in mind that...
I'm a huge fan of yours.
- Okay.
-  I always read your cartoons.
- I love them.
-  Start.
(A name tag ripping match between Jo Seok and Jong Kook)
I feel bad.
- I feel so bad for him.
-  Hey.
- Why?
-  What are you doing?
I'm a huge fan of his.
How will he walk around his neighbourhood?
His neighbours are watching.
You humiliated him in front of his neighbours.
Next. Start.
(Jo Seok versus Gary)
(Ripping)
What are you doing?
It's Kwang Soo versus Jo Seok. Get ready.
Start.
(Kwang Soo has many things to apologise for.)
(I will undo my wrongs.)
Go ahead.
(Ripping)
(Hey)
This is so cruel.
(Was this a good decision?)
- Why don't you play once more?
-  You should.
Play once more.
Play against me.
- Why don't you play against Ji Hyo?
-  Play against me.
- Beat me.
-  Okay.
- Are you okay?
-  I want to go home.
You should win before you go back.
I'll never draw such a cartoon.
- That's not why we're doing this.
-  It's not.
- That's not why we came.
-  It's not that.
We're not here for revenge.
- That's not it.
-  We're here to apologise.
- You wanted to play the game.
-  I want to apologise and go home.
- No way.
-  You don't have to apologise.
- We should apologise.
-  You can beat me.
He said, "I'll never draw such a cartoon."
It's more embarrassing if you go home.
- I'm sure you can beat me.
-  Start.
Seok Jin is stronger than you expect.
I can see that.
(Struggling)
You have to win this time.
- He's strong.
-  Let go of his hands.
(Seok Jin grabs the name tag.)
(His hand slips.)
- Let go of his hands.
-  Come on.
Be careful.
(Seok Jin grabs Jo Seok's name tag.)
(I'm winning unintentionally.)
- His arms are too short.
-  This is too harsh.
He won!
He's being too harsh.
(Jo Seok ripped off Seok Jin's name tag.)
- He won!
-  He won!
(Jo Seok won.)
- He won!
-  Let's toss him into the air.
- In 3, 2, 1.
-  In 3, 2, 1.
(It's Jo Seok first win.)
- In 3, 2, 1.
-  He was strong.
- He was so strong.
-  You did a great job.
He was strong.
- You're the best.
-  Seok Jin almost won.
- Seok Jin was trying to win.
-  He was.
- Seok Jin lost. – He's really strong.
Jo Seok is finally smiling.
- You won!
-  You did a great job.
If you didn't win, you wouldn't have been able to sleep tonight.
Jo Seok will draw us.
- Really?
-  That'll be amazing.
- Give us your autograph, too.
-  Your autograph.
- Who is he drawing?
-  I think it's Kwang Soo.
It's obviously Kwang Soo.
- It looks like Kwang Soo.
-  It does.
Do you draw the webtoons yourself?
He does.
He's so tall.
- It's that body.
-  I recognise this body.
- It's the body from his webtoon.
-  It's a rubber body.
I'm not that tall.
It's exactly like his webtoon.
Are you angry at me?
(Smiling)
- That's amazing.
-  Thank you.
- Pose like the drawing.
-  Okay.
- Thank you.
-  It does look like him.
Who would you like to draw next?
It's Gary.
- It's Gary.
-  Is it Jo Seok?
Isn't it Jo Seok?
- I think it's Jong Kook.
-  No, it's Gary.
- Is it Jong Kook?
-  It's Gary.
- It's Jong Kook.
-  It's obviously you.
- Look at the hair.
-  It is Jong Kook.
It's you. Look at the eyes.
- It's me.
-  The neck is the same.
- It's the same.
-  It's really me.
- It looks exactly like you.
-  It's definitely me.
It's definitely Jong Kook.
(A satisfied fan)
(Jo Seok drew the other members, too.)
- Jo Seok, we'd like to apologise.
-  Right.
We'll give you a golden name tag.
It's a golden name tag.
We'd like to give you a golden name tag.
Thank you.
Will you accept our apology?
I wasn't sure if I should come today.
Now, I think it was a good idea.
- It was nice today, wasn't it?
-  Yes, it was.
I'll put this on my studio wall.
- Thank you.
-  We'll put this on our walls, too.
- Since he accepted our apology,
-  Right.
- let's give him a big hand.
-  Okay.
- Thank you.
-  Thank you.
-  We'll look forward to your work.
(We were sorry.)
(They're on their way to meet the next person.)
Don't you feel sorry to Kyuhyun as well?
- I do.
-  That episode in particular.
I feel sorry to everyone in that episode,
- including Yenny.
-  Everyone.
- I feel sorry to everyone.
-  Rap Monster.
- Rap Monster, too.
-  And John Park.
I feel so sorry to Kyuhyun.
Does anyone have his phone number? Why don't we call him?
- I have his number.
-  Let's try it.
(They're calling Kyuhyun.)
- Hello?
-  Kyuhyun.
-  Hi.
- It's me.
-  He sounds cold.
- He's cold.
-  Kyuhyun, I'm sorry.
He must really be upset.
It's the first time you've called me.
(Jae Seok is embarrassed.)
That's why I'm sorry. Where are you?
I'm in Japan right now.
Are you in Japan?
- Japan?
-  Yes.
I've apologised to you...
many times.
- Have you really?
-  Hey.
- He must be really angry.
-  I did.
- Yes, I have.
-  Apologise to him.
I want to apologise. It's Gary.
Gary...
was the one who initiated it.
- Gary is sorry.
-  Right.
So Gary, can you go to Fukuoka?
- Me?
-  You should go.
Kyuhyun.
- Yes.
-  Then...
- Gary, you should go.
-  I'll...
- You should go.
-  meet you in Fukuoka...
and apologise.
(Really?)
I finally arrived in Fukuoka.
(Gary is in Japan.)
I'm here to meet Kyuhyun.
(Let's find Kyuhyun in Fukuoka.)
So many of his fans are here.
(Kyuhyun, please accept our apology.)
- In 1, 2, 3.
-  Go, Kyuhyun!
- Go, Kyuhyun!
It's here. Kyuhyun!
(Will Kyuhyun accept our apology?)
(The global Apology Service is coming soon.)
(Who's the fourth person to receive an apology?)
- I hope Hee Jun will show up...
-  Right.
chubbier than before.
- Wait.
-  Really.
It's all your fault.
It was your personal mistake.
- We don't have to apologise.
-  You laughed, too.
We laughed but he might have been hurt.
I remember that day.
We had to go into the water a lot.
(Let's review what happened.)
Get down, you fatty.
You should give it to me.
(Fatty)
Fatty?
My mum is watching this.
No one could have called him fatty during his H.O.T. days.
- Really.
-  If it was back then,
Jong Kook wouldn't be living in this country.
His fans would cut out my eyes in my pictures.
You'd be killed.
He's coming.
- He wouldn't be here.
-  He's coming.
(He's finally here.)
(A chubby figure approaches.)
(Moon Hee Jun)
- He's here.
-  Hello.
You're even chubbier now.
I won't sit down until Jong Kook leaves.
Hee Jun, come here.
- Hee Jun.
-  Jong Kook should leave first.
It's been a long time.
Hee Jun.
- We're sorry.
-  Hee Jun.
One of the members of H.O.T. is here.
- Where have you been?
-  Stop that.
Has that incident...
- caused you any trouble?
-  Be honest.
- Since that incident.
-  Did you have a hard time?
- Has it caused me trouble?
-  Yes.
(Did I have a hard time?)
- When I search my name...
-  Why?
- What happens?
-  What?
Does the word "Fatty" show up when you search your name?
"Moon Hee Jun Fatty", "Fatty Moon Hee Jun"...
and "Fatty". All three of them show up.
It drives me crazy.
If it was only one, I could do something about it.
But all the different word combinations show up.
One in the Western way and one in the Korean way.
"Moon Hee Jun Fatty", "Fatty Moon Hee Jun"...
- and "Fatty".
-  "Fatty".
I searched for "Fatty" and all I find are pictures of you.
- Read it.
-  "To the legendary idol, Hee Jun."
"We're sorry we upset you by calling you "Fatty" and "Yoyo"."
"We're also sorry for upsetting your mother as well."
We're sorry.
You should apologise to his mother first.
My mother was really hurt.
- She was?
-  Was she really?
She has been texting me every day since then.
- Does she tell you to lose weight?
-  Yes.
I'm sure she wanted to say that to you anyway.
Jong Kook. I have never heard my mother...
swear in my life.
But she said, "Is that jerk out of his mind?"
Really.
Just because you have a fit body...
- She was sad that I was hurt.
-  I didn't mean it.
It was just my cute way of calling you.
- Why don't we give her a call?
-  Are you calling my mother?
- Jong Kook must apologise.
-  Are they really calling my mum?
(He'll apologise to Hee Jun's mother over the phone.)
- Mum.
-  Yes?
It's me.
So?
She doesn't care.
- Do you remember?
-  She's not in a good mood.
- What?
-  When I was on Running Man,
- Right.
-  Jong Kook called me a fatty,
- so you got mad, right?
-  Of course!
- Right?
-  "Of course!"
Running Man visited me...
Did they call you a fatty again?
No, they didn't call me a fatty.
- They came over to apologise.
-  Really?
They all came.
- Jong Kook is actually next to me.
-  Let them talk.
I'll give the phone to Jong Kook, okay?
(He's flustered.)
- Hello, Mrs Moon.
-  Hey.
Yes, Mrs Moon.
- My granddaughter...
-  Yes?
keeps calling Hee Jun a fatty after she saw you say it.
(Her uncle is a fatty.)
She's my sister's daughter.
- Is that what she said?
-  She's your sister's daughter.
I'll take charge and make Hee Jun exercise.
- This is good.
-  I'll keep my promise.
- That sounds like a good idea.
-  That's great.
- I'm being serious.
-  That's nice of you.
- Sure.
-  All right, Mrs Moon.
(He apologised to both Hee Jun and his mother.)
- Thank you, Mrs Moon.
-  Take care!
I'll take charge and give you some training tips.
It turned out well in the end.
- What's that?
-  It's a gift.
I didn't know there was a gift.
- What's this?
-  Are you going to mock him?
- They look like pyjamas.
-  Let's open this first.
- This one first?
-  Yes.
(What's the first gift?)
- What's that?
-  What is it?
- I have a bad feeling about this.
-  It's a shirt.
- It's a t-shirt with a design.
-  There are muscles on it.
- Why?
-  What is it?
I have muscles.
(It's a t-shirt with a muscular body on it.)
- Goodness.
-  This is even sadder.
I don't think it'll fit you.
(He manages to put his head through.)
- That's not how you do it.
-  This is small.
It fits.
- It fits you.
-  It does fit.
It fits well on top of your shirt.
Do you agree, Kwang Soo?
- I can't even breathe.
-  Well, I mean...
- Does it have a hood?
-  You need to take it out.
Can you take a picture of it and post it up on SNS?
- Post it up for him.
-  Sure, I will.
Can someone take a picture for us?
In 1, 2, 3.
(Hee Jun is not a fatty.)
- We're sorry.
-  All right, Hee Jun.
- Please accept our apology.
-  Okay.
Thanks so much.
- Hee Jun.
-  Take an apple...
You must take a bite of an apple to accept our apology.
- Is that so?
-  Yes.
I'm rooting for you, Hee Jun.
(Taking a bite)
It's delicious.
He accepted the apology.
I'm seriously rooting for you.
(Hee Jun accepts their apology.)
(I'm Sorry, I Love You)
(They're going to meet the last guest.)
Who are we apologising to?
- I'm not sure.
-  Who could it be?
(Who could be the last guest?)
Who could it be?
Thank you for the ride.
(They have reached the end of a long day.)
You have all worked hard to serve the guests.
The last Apology Service is the most important one.
It's time...
for an Apology Service amongst the members.
(It's an Apology Service amongst Running Man members.)
No way.
I'm cringing already.
This is quite awkward.
In case you don't know what to say, write it down first.
Can't we just talk amongst ourselves?
- What are we doing?
-  We'll talk amongst ourselves.
(They can't help but laugh.)
What am I sorry about?
I've never thought about this.
Do I just write anything?
(It's the first time they're writing to each other in six years.)
(They meet every week.)
I finished.
(Would they have anything to say?)
- Are you done?
-  Yes.
(They slowly fill the pages with their words.)
I don't know what to write.
(Among them, Jae Seok has a difficult time writing.)
(He doesn't know how to condense his feelings onto a single page...)
(for the 6 members who spent the past 6 years with him.)
(Gathering courage, he picks up the pen and begins to write.)
Jae Seok, you can go into the white room.
- Me?
-  Yes.
Kwang Soo, you can head to the recreational vehicle.
(Kwang Soo will share a conversation with someone there.)
- Seok Jin.
-  Yes.
- Go to the food stand.
-  The food stand?
Okay. I don't even drink.
(Seok Jin heads to the food stand.)
(These spaces are perfect for two people.)
(Jae Seok enters a white room.)
(Who will join him?)
(I knew it was going to be you.)
- I knew it was going to be you.
-  What is this?
- Why...
-  Gosh.
- What is this, anyway?
-  I don't know.
- Why do we have to do this?
-  I have no idea.
(This is so awkward.)
- Goodness.
-  What? Why?
- Did you write to me?
-  No.
- Me neither.
-  Gosh.
- Seriously.
-  Goodness.
So...
- I don't know what this is about.
-  Well...
Why do we have to face each other? It's awkward.
Exactly. Oh, dear.
I never thought it was awkward between us before.
- This makes us awkward.
-  It does.
What's this about?
- It's awkward like this.
-  Exactly.
I don't know what we are supposed to talk about.
I didn't write anything special.
I just wrote this. It must be the same for the rest of us,
but since we have different roles on this show,
sometimes...
I end up acting aggressively.
- But I had to because...
-  Of course.
- everybody is so nice.
-  Right. We know...
that you have to take on a certain role in playing the villain.
Exactly. So even when I talk,
I speak aggressively.
- I get it.
-  Gosh.
Sometimes, I know I've gone too far but I still say those words.
- Right.
-  I say them on purpose.
This is part of the show.
- Of course.
-  Since it's part of the show,
- I think that you'll understand me.
-  Certainly.
But still, I sometimes...
think you and Seok Jin might be offended by what I do.
But for our show, we have to get physical so it can turn violent.
That's understandable.
I mentioned this before,
but athletes reach their prime as well.
- You know what I mean, right?
-  I know.
Since my body is starting to ache,
there are more things I can't do on Running Man.
That's when I was in a slump.
It was because...
I knew people had expectations for me.
But my body wouldn't heal.
So I couldn't fulfil my role in those moments.
I was put down every time that happened.
There were times when I questioned...
- my place on this show.
-  Right.
But I knew that if I gave this up,
I wouldn't be invited to appear on other programmes.
So there was a time when I struggled with the thought.
(Jong Kook expresses his anxiety for the first time.)
- I know.
-  Because of that, when I spoke,
I was being aggressive to cover up my flaws.
- I see.
-  That's what I turned to.
But I think that could have been too much for the members and guests.
(Jae Seok quietly listens to Jong Kook.)
(Meanwhile, Kwang Soo is waiting inside the van.)
(Someone is here.)
(Laughing)
(He bursts into laughter...)
(as soon as he sees Ji Hyo.)
This is insane.
This is so awkward, Kwang Soo.
(This is so awkward, Kwang Soo.)
Oh goodness.
(His face has turned red in embarrassment.)
What is this for?
Why are you making us do this?
What are we supposed to do here?
(He can't breathe.)
What are we supposed to do?
This atmosphere is...
What is this?
(Wailing)
- I can't believe this.
-  I can't look at you in the eyes.
I know.
What are we doing? What is this supposed to be?
What do you want us to do?
(They're suffocating in the silence.)
I'll just tell you what I wrote, then.
Did you write to me?
I did.
- I wrote what I was grateful about.
-  What is it?
I'm truly grateful to you...
(I'm truly grateful to you...)
(Sighing)
I thought...
(He's laughing already.)
It actually occurred to me many times.
I always questioned whether this was really my place to be.
(Is this my place to be?)
I was absorbed in it.
It's been six years now.
But in the beginning, I couldn't mingle with the other members.
(She couldn't open up to the members.)
I felt bad during that time.
(I felt sorry at the time.)
I cried a lot...
(I cried a lot.)
And I had a hard time, so I told you that I wanted to quit.
(I cried a lot and I wanted to quit.)
- You told me.
-  I did.
Whenever I said that...
(Whenever I said that...)
You held on to me.
I'm so thankful...
(I'm thankful.)
You listened to me.
(I'm so thankful that you listened to me.)
- That's what I wrote.
-  You're thankful I listened to you.
I'm thankful about that...
(Kwang Soo quietly listens to Ji Hyo.)
And I'm also thankful that you continued to treat me the same.
That's just...
(I'm thankful that you treated me the same.)
How I felt.
(He is an actor as well, so he could understand her deeply.)
I did.
I guess they have a lot to talk to each other.
(She tries to change the subject.)
I got something in my eyes.
- What are you doing?
-  What am I doing?
- What are you doing, suddenly?
-  I got something in my eyes.
What am I doing here?
We should be ripping off name tags.
I wrote what I feel sorry about.
What makes you feel sorry?
I...
I think I act rudely towards you too often.
We've spent several years together. I know the things that you dislike,
and I know that I may hurt your feeling if I act in certain ways.
But I don't how I must act for the best result.
I want to do well so I do my best, and try hard. But in the end,
I'm not just saying...
(I might have hurt Ji Hyo.)
I am so sorry. But if I say sorry,
then I shouldn't act like that again. It's really difficult.
I know.
Don't worry. I'm fine. Actually, I can't remember.
What a relief. Because I may keep doing what I was doing.
Yes, keep behaving like that.
I think that's better for us. More than talking like this.
More than talking like this.
- Oh my.
-  This is crazy.
They must have a lot to talk about.
(How are Jae Seok and Jong Kook in the white room doing?)
I'm really grateful to you for thinking about me like that.
To be honest, in the team,
- I usually stand as an opponent.
-  Right.
That's not an easy job for me.
- Because you're doing it alone.
-  Yes. And at the same time,
I have to stand against you, out of all the others. It's not easy.
- I see.
-  And things were like that before.
I did something to you, and it became really controversial.
I try to forget the burden. I don't have any options.
- Because it's my job.
-  It is.
So I try not to think about that these days.
I used to say that...
I can't do anything if people blame me.
- Because it's my role.
-  You're right.
- As long as we're fine about it.
-  Right.
Anyway, because it's my job, I keep on acting that way. As I did before.
- So no matter how much...
-  You must act like that to anyone.
That will put us in different situations each time.
Every member in Running Man is really important.
And everyone has to do their best in their role for Running Man.
I must take care of the things that I didn't know until you told me.
- Jong Kook.
-  You just keep yourself healthy.
- You need to keep your health, too.
-  Of course. Both of us need to.
I've worked in other entertainment shows, but I think...
we've spent many years together, and we have the best teamwork.
Right, of course.
So if we keep ourselves in good shape,
- we will be able to keep rolling.
-  Let's do it.
That's it.
- That's right.
-  Okay. We're done.
(They feel embarrassed after all the talk.)
- Okay. We're all set.
-  Okay.
- Okay. Keep treating me like that.
-  I will.
- Keep it on.
-  What is it?
- Okay. Let's go.
-  Let's go.
Let's go, Jae Seok.
All right. We're done.
(Who's visiting Seok Jin's food stand?)
(Haha is the one.)
- Oh my.
-  My goodness.
Okay. Take a seat.
- Nice to see you here, Seok Jin.
-  Yes. Help yourself.
- Isn't it the first time?
-  For us to sit by ourselves.
- Cheers.
-  Cheers.
(It's first time for them to drink together just by themselves.)
Have I upset you in any way?
You haven't upset me.
(How should I put this?)
- I should apologise.
-  What are you talking about?
What are you talking about all of a sudden?
Oh my.
For the first few years,
I kept asking myself...
why I am doing this every week.
- But I didn't feel like to quit.
-  I see.
Because the style of the show was far too different from others.
I used to say that it took several years to get used to snap backs.
Just like that, it took several years to get used to the show.
I didn't think I fit in well in the team.
- Did you think that way?
-  I did.
I talked to the producer several times about quitting.
Haha. The thing that I want to tell you is that...
everyone can be like that. Some may not fit in the show.
But my fault is...
that I blamed you guys for it at that time.
Whatever you said, I was easily offended.
I just realised that with such act and attitude,
I couldn't be a comfortable friend or a colleague to you.
It took a long time for me to realise.
Then I asked myself, "What should I do?"
So I started accepting everything.
(I accepted everything.)
I realised that I shouldn't feel offended.
So one day, I started off a race, smiling...
- We all applauded.
-  That made me feel comfortable.
- About that...
-  I am sorry. I am.
(Who will be the second guest for Jae Seok?)
- Hey, Gary.
-  Yes, Jae Seok.
Do we need to keep the side open?
- Hey, Gary. Why are you here?
-  I was asked to come in.
- Really?
-  Yes.
- I am here, so let me tell you...
-  All right.
- My concern is...
-  Okay.
My concern as an entertainer is growing bigger these days.
Jong Kook talked with me about that, too.
Okay. So...
Personally, I kept thinking that this might be the end.
Then I shake my head and cheer myself again.
But I am afraid that I might lose everything.
When I try to work on music seriously,
I often feel that I'm not serious about music.
I can't concentrate when I didn't make any progress in composing.
So such things concerned me heavily.
(Those things concerned me.)
What burdens me is the question,
"So, what should I do now?"
Honestly, I thought I had to quit. It was the best for this show.
I thought I had to quit...
for Running Man. Honestly.
I think everyone including myself will have such concerns.
We are trying to change ourselves.
You know, we all used to play in a playground when we were young.
But as we get older,
we can't play in the same place forever.
We won't have much fun playing with the same rides over and over.
To find different sides of us, we shouldn't do the same things.
For that, staff members are working hard.
We don't have any other way but to do our best.
- I am thinking hard...
-  Of course.
- about what I can do for this show.
-  Of course, I know.
Staff members are working hard, too.
That's what we must do for Running Man.
Staff members are looking for new environments that we can play in.
That's their concern, and that's what we must do for the show.
- I will do my best.
-  Of course.
- Hey, Gary.
-  All right.
(Cheer up, Gary.)
- Let's go.
-  All right. That's so simple.
- It is simple.
-  It's not difficult at all.
Oh. come in.
Take a sit.
We were having a sincere conversation.
I am in the middle. Especially, regarding age.
Yes, you are.
And Kwang Soo had some difficult times, too.
- So we talked to each other often.
-  Did you?
- He found things difficult, too.
-  I talked about it with Haha a lot.
So we cheered up each other and one day,
Kwang Soo began showing his presence and the show went well.
I know this is awkward.
But I want to say I'm really thankful to you, Kwang Soo.
And you helped me a lot when I had to be funny.
Seeing you working really hard, I was also motivated a lot.
Kwang Soo is an actor. So I'm sure it was not easy...
for him to give up on his image as an actor.
So I think you should rather be an entertainer than an actor.
(Do not waste your talent as an entertainer.)
You're just too funny to remain as an actor.
Don't try to look handsome.
That is not what I want.
- I never tried to look nice.
-  Okay.
It's really nice to have this conversation with you.
(Who is it for the last Apology Service?)
Hello, you're here.
It took very long.
I know, we had a lot to talk about.
Seok Jin told me his story.
He told me what happened in his life before.
(Silent)
I was going to...
Gosh, what is this?
What I want to apologise to you is...
Oh, my. This isn't what I expected.
I am sorry that I said you're very ugly.
- But I know I am ugly too.
-  Well...
- What you said is true.
-  So...
That is what I thought.
It is true that I am ugly.
(They burst into laughter.)
Haha and I aren't like this!
My goodness!
(What is going on between the ugly brothers?)
Anyway, as we got this chance to talk, I want to tell you this.
You know I've never appeared on such entertaining shows before.
And I think...
you're my role model as an entertainer.
(You're my role model.)
(This is so awkward!)
Okay, I did it!
I said it.
So just know that I am grateful to you.
Okay, I know.
And you are the best in my life.
- I love you.
-  You're my role model.
Oh, my. You know what?
I am your fan.
(Their conversation is full of lines that make you cringe.)
Gosh, what is this?
(The Apology Service between the members are over.)
- Cover your body with this.
-  No, thanks, my role model.
- Haha, do you need anything?
-  I am okay.
- Then, give that to me.
-  He is my role model.
(I'm fine. You can use it.)
Haha is my role model.
(They now have strong friendship.)
You're my idol.
- Can we wrap this up now?
-  Yes.
- So we don't read the letters?
-  Please...
burn the letters.
- Let's burn them.
-  Okay.
- Great, let's burn them.
-  Please.
- Please burn them.
-  I think I was out of my mind.
- I don't want the letters.
-  I must have been out of my mind.
(Let's burn the grudges off along with the letters.)
- Then, let's burn them.
-  Okay.
- Let's count to three.
-  One, two, three.
- Let's burn them off.
-  Goodbye.
- Goodbye.
-  Bye.
- Let's not feel sorry any more.
-  I must have gone out of my mind.
- And more than 300 guests...
-  Right.
appeared on our show.
- Our guests.
-  Yes, our guests.
We were able to meet only a few of them...
- in this special.
-  Yes.
And please join us as our guests...
if you're willing to.
We'd like to take this opportunity to say thank you to all the guests.
And we promise you here that we'll cooperate and...
work harder to make our guests enjoy the shooting...
and to make the programme much more enjoyable.
We will see you next week.
Shall we hold each other's hand?
- No.
-  What are you doing?
- Gosh.
-  No way.
- Let's hold each other's hand.
-  Thank you, everyone!
- Hold hands.
-  My hands are in sweat.
- Let's hold each other's hand now.
-  Gosh!
- My goodness.
-  Are you living in the 90s?
- It is very heart-warming.
-  Why do we have to do this?
- It is heart-warming.
-  Thank you, everyone!
- Thank you!
-  Thank you!
- I am sorry, I love you!
-  I am sorry!
- Thank you.
-  Great.
- It feels good, doesn't it?
-  Right.
This makes me feel good.
- Ji Hyo.
-  Jae Seok.
(Next Sunday at 6:25pm)
(The second episode of "I'm Sorry, I Love You", "Seven Loves")
(Jae Seok's high school classmate, Lee Seung Joon)
He's Lee Seung Joon, my high school classmate.
Jae Seok had a long-term girlfriend.
She was tall but not pretty.
You can't do this.
Seung Joon reveals everything about Jae Seok today.
He is my role model.
(Haha's idol, Lee Moon Se)
I started dreaming to be a singer after listening to his songs.
Is that your best?
- Ma'am!
-  Jong Kook's mother.
- He is like a daughter.
-  Daughter?
- He acts like a daughter at home.
-  He is a cute boy to his mother.
See? He's like a daughter.
(Isn't he?)
- Hello.
-  Hello.
Hurry up.
(A fierce race to find the seven loves.)
- Hello?
-  Hello?
How have you been?
She is my first girlfriend.
It feels weird.
(Kwang Soo meets his first girlfriend in 20 years.)
I don't know why I was like that...
("Seven Loves" will be aired at 6:25pm next Sunday.)