(Christmas is full of love and joy on the streets and in the hearts.)
(It's the only day of the year.)
(It feels like there will be a miracle today.)
Christmas season has returned.
- Is it Christmas already? - Merry Christmas.
- Time flies. - Merry Christmas.
For our Christmas Special,
we have invited a lovely Christmas fairy today.
- That's great. - Who is the Christmas fairy?
- We must see a fairy on Christmas. - Make us happy for once.
- Who is the fairy? - That's awesome.
Christmas fairy, please come out.
(Running Man members have worked hard for a year.)
(Who is the fairly to present a great Christmas for the members?)
There is a fairy?
(Christmas fairy, who are you?)
- Who is that? - My gosh.
(Kim So Hyun is the Christmas fairy and MC for the day.)
(From a child actress, she grew up to be a lady.)
(So Hyun is the pretty actress with acting skills.)
(Christmas fairy has descended.)
- Goodness. - It's Kim So Hyun.
What are we going to do?
- Kim So Hyun is here. - I can't believe it.
- She does look like a fairy. - It's been a while, So Hyun.
- Hello. - My gosh, what brings you here?
- She sure is a fairy. - Indeed.
Why don't you move this way?
- Should I move there? - Please come this way.
(Fairy, please come this way.)
Because of her, I can't quit drinking the sports drink.
(She is synonymous with purity.)
Is that why?
(She promotes a sports drink.)
- She has turned into a lady now. - Indeed, she has.
My goodness.
- How old are you now? - I am 18 years old.
- She's 18 years old? - 18 years old?
Are you only 18 years old?
- Yes, I am. - Go ahead with your hosting.
I came here as a Christmas fairy today.
- You are truly a fairy. - You really are.
- No, I am not. - That's great.
But why don't you have wings?
(What did he just say?)
- What's the matter with you? - She's only 18 years old.
- What are you trying to do here? - I mean...
His lines are out-dated.
So Hyun, do you not like this kind of lines?
- So Hyun. - She acted like she didn't hear it.
- You hated the line he said, right? - I'm sorry.
She doesn't like these things. I got it. I know what she likes now.
- I found out what she dislikes. - It's because of me.
- Did you get that? - Yes, I got it.
- So Hyun, it's almost Christmas. - Okay.
What is your plan?
- What did you do when you were 18? - I...
stayed up all night with my friends.
- Where? Doing what? - Why did you stay up all night?
I had a girlfriend at that time.
(Shy)
- What did you say? - Stop lying.
(Is that from your imagination?)
- You're driving me crazy. - You didn't have a girlfriend.
- He thought we'd let it slide. - It's only your imagination.
No one liked you when you were young.
We played games and talked all night long.
My gosh, I had a great time. I wonder how they are doing.
(I miss you, my friends. Are you well?)
- Anyway... - That was great.
- So... - She didn't listen to my story.
Shouldn't you tell us your plan since we were on the subject?
I should make my Christmas memories here.
- Here? - Yes.
- It won't be easy. - I don't think you can.
She's well-prepared. She has all the answers.
The Christmas Special you will have with me is...
Christmas Race with Bad Santa.
(Christmas Race with Bad Santa)
You see the thermometer here, right?
Through several missions, you need to make it reach 100°C.
Today's race will be over then.
Before the race ends, you have to be each other's bad Santa.
- You must bully each other. - Bully each other?
But you can't let them know whom you are supposed to bully.
- Is it a secret? - Yes.
(Christmas with Bad Santa)
If you successfully bully without getting caught, 1,000 dollars...
- will be donated under your name. - It's a donation.
So we'll be doing a good deed and a bad deed together.
- You'll be a good Santa for others. - A bad deed will be a good deed.
He is the expert in bullying.
- No, you're the expert. - How can you let this happen?
I don't know whom I will be bullying,
but I won't be held responsibility if that person cries.
Since you let me play jokes on people...
When Jong Kook bullies, I can forget about it on that day.
When Jae Seok bullies, it lasts a week.
- That's right. - That's the problem with him.
It's going to last a week.
I'm worried, too.
I'm worried about two things.
First one is who will be bullied by Jong Kook.
Second one is who will bully Jong Kook.
- Please. - I'm really...
- Right. - I really hope...
- that won't be me. - Please don't let it be me.
- What I want to know is... - But how can you not...
get caught if you are to bully Jong Kook?
- That's inevitable. - I want to know...
what the limit is.
- I want to know the limit. - You all know Jong Kook, right?
- He will say, "What are you doing?" - Right.
"Are you the Bad Santa?"
- I won't be able to talk then. - That will be tough.
(He's warming up.)
Starting now, you will choose your Bad Santa.
I will call on each member and you will go up one by one.
You will choose a bag that has the name tag of the person you'll bully.
We will go to another room and you will...
come up with a list of five pranks.
Shall I choose?
I will choose now. Please.
Please let it be anyone, but Jong Kook.
(He will be okay as long as it's not Jong Kook.)
(He grabs a bag.)
(He is flustered.)
What am I going to do?
(Jae Seok is an expert in bullying. Whose Bad Santa is Jae Seok?)
I will choose this one.
(He already feels sorry.)
(It's everyone's concern. Who will be bullied by Jong Kook?)
(Everyone has chosen their target to bully.)
- It's your first time. - I picked the wrong person.
It's too easy to bully him.
(She's full of confidence.)
Gosh, what should I do?
They'll find out that it's me.
(Who is Kwang Soo's target?)
(They make a list of their bullying missions.)
"Stepping on their foot like it was a mistake" sounds good.
I'll pick "stepping on their foot".
That's a good one.
(Whose foot will he destroy?)
"Undoing the shoelaces".
"Undoing the shoelaces" shouldn't be too difficult.
(They write down similar things.)
"Pulling on the sideburns and spraying water on the face".
This is what I wrote so far.
(They finish completing their list.)
(Who's their Bad Santas?)
(Their bullying list.)
I tucked it in because I have a smudge.
- Just pull it out. - No, I want to tuck it in.
- Pull it out. - No.
- Have you started already? - Start what?
- Did you start your bullying? - Don't tuck it in.
That hurt.
(He starts bullying in any way he can.)
What's going on?
What's wrong?
(Kwang Soo steps on other members' feet.)
(He's warming up.)
- Why did you step on my foot? - I'm sorry.
You should do it discreetly.
(They fight before the mission starts.)
You should step on the foot discreetly.
(Everyone loves bullying each other.)
Discreetly.
- Has bullying started? - No.
Don't start yet.
- Haven't we started? - No.
- Why are we starting so late? - My goodness.
(It's a big mess.)
Gosh, what's going on here?
The mission starts when you get in the car.
- Okay. - Is that when we start?
- Let's go. - Shall we go?
- Let's go. - Let's go.
(They move to the next location.)
She's so cute.
All I can think about is bullying.
I want to do the ones that I didn't write on my list.
- They suddenly come to my mind. - Me, too.
I changed my mind.
Regardless of what I wrote on my list,
I'll bully the person in any way I can.
So Hyun, be careful since we might also bully you.
- We should let her know. - Something may happen to you, too.
- I won't stir up anything. - Anything could happen to you.
- It's winter. - Turn on the air conditioner.
It's so hot.
(Jae Seok bullies the wrong person.)
Don't do that.
(He waits for his chance.)
(He pulls Kwang Soo's sideburns.)
(Punching)
- Hey. - I didn't do it.
(Bullying starts right away.)
- I didn't do it. - Jong Kook hit me to be funny.
- Come on, Jong Kook. - What?
I don't like hurting you.
I told you this would happen.
(Scratching)
(Punching)
(It's more like a combat.)
You're basically hitting him.
(He presses her head down.)
Why do you always punch when you're being playful?
He isn't being playful. He's actually hitting me.
This is bullying because we don't know when or what will happen.
(Spraying)
What was that?
(Haha can't breathe.)
- What was it? - Isn't that a hairspray?
My cheek is sticky.
It's a hairspray.
I carry it around for a reason.
I'll be merciless today.
(He pokes his eyes.)
(Seok Jin has no lenses in his glasses.)
- My hand is sticky. - Just take them off.
- Take them off. - Are you bullying me?
I think she's bullying me.
- Good job. - We won't go easy on you, either.
- Good job. - We won't go easy on you.
(Bullying should be fair.)
(Let's see.)
(He moves up his hair.)
Seok Jin hates that hairstyle the most.
I hate it the most. Don't push up my hair.
He always presses it down.
It's because of the shape of my head.
(Is that so?)
Goodness, stop it!
(He makes it worse.)
- I don't want my hair to go up. - That's a good thing.
I've never seen your hair like that.
(He presses it down.)
(Seok Jin tries to fix his hair.)
(Jae Seok spits.)
(He attacks Kwang Soo's head.)
No, don't ruin my hair!
I went to the hair salon today!
(It only takes two seconds to ruin his hair.)
What's wrong with you?
You did a good job.
(He'll take revenge.)
- Are you okay? - What's wrong?
(He punches everyone.)
(Disregarding the mission, he attacks everyone.)
Calm down.
(Will they complete their mission?)
- This is So Hyun. - Stop that.
(SBS Prism Tower in Sangam-dong)
(It's full of Christmas decorations.)
(This is Bad Santa's house.)
Bad Santa's Miracle Race.
Here's how to raise the thermometer.
(Anything sounds good.)
Do you see all these boxes of presents behind us?
- Yes, I do. - If you...
carry out the missions that are written inside the boxes,
you may earn a minimum of 10°C...
to a maximum of 30°C.
If you fail to carry out the mission,
one of you will be punished.
The higher bet you make, the worse your punishment will be.
- Keep that in mind. - The higher bet...
- we make? - Yes.
The punishment will get worse.
It's very easy to understand.
She's good.
She's very calm and concise.
- It's easy to focus on her. - I know.
If she had been my teacher in high school, I'd have earned all A's.
Don't say things like that.
(He deserves some bullying.)
- I'm sorry. - I forgot about bullying.
- I almost forgot. - I'm sorry.
I almost forgot.
(Thank you for reminding me.)
All right, how about...
(He hits Jae Seok out of nowhere.)
(His throat gets attacked.)
He hit his throat.
Are you my Bad Santa?
(Being traumatized by bullying can be intense.)
(Punching)
That was worse than mine.
- That really hurts. - What's wrong?
- You should have warned me. - What?
- His punches are too strong. - That's true.
(Here's one for you, Haha.)
That must hurt a lot.
Now,
we'll start "Raise the Thermometer".
- Please pick a box. - Shall we?
- Let's do it. - All right.
- Do we pick only 1? - It's 1 per person.
Do we pick one?
Shall I pick a small one?
I'll pick this one.
- This one? - It has Santa Claus on it.
That box stands out the most.
I'm afraid its mission will be difficult.
(In the first box,)
(what kind of mission will they find?)
(The first mission is "Guess the Game".)
- What's "Guess the Game"? - What's that?
You'll be given a tool and hashtags. Based on those,
guess the game you played on Running Man...
and make your temperature bet.
It's one of the games we've played.
- We'll know based on the hashtags. - It'll be easy to guess.
We'll play this game based on the hints, right?
(You must be quick to succeed.)
(Here's the first hint.)
I know what it is. It's breaking boiled eggs.
(There are 12 eggs.)
Here's the hashtags.
The hashtags are "raw eggs", "couple", "Seok Jin and Kwang Soo".
(Raw eggs, couple, Seok Jin and Kwang Soo)
Let's think carefully. One of them is "couple".
- What does it refer to? - One of them is "Seok Jin".
- Why is it me and Kwang Soo? - Neither of them are lucky.
- Oh, I know what it is. - Neither of them are lucky.
It's because we played the final round at Unluckiest Festival.
- That's right. - It's the final round.
- It's the final round. - That's right.
(Unluckiest Festival on March 27, 2016)
(To determine the unluckiest one,)
(Seok Jin and Kwang Soo competed in the final round.)
(That day, they used their unlucky energy to its fullest.)
(Kwang Soo showed off his unlucky energy in the raw egg game.)
(It's "Random Raw Egg".)
- Who's the unluckiest? - It was about that.
- It was at Unluckiest Festival. - Right.
- This is it. - I'm not sure.
(It doesn't seem right.)
(Water Fairy Race on March 15, 2015)
(They played "Making Eggs Stand" at a rest stop.)
(Episode 28 of Running Man on January 30, 2011)
(Joong Ki and Kwang Soo played "Rock-Paper-Scissors Eating Eggs".)
Rock-paper-scissors.
(Something doesn't feel right.)
- Please make your bet first. - Let's do that.
- 30. - Shall we bet 30?
- Let's bet 30. - Isn't it too high at first?
How about 20? It's in the middle.
- 20 is good. - Let's bet 20.
- How about 20? - I bet 20.
There isn't much of a difference between 20 and 30.
Raise your hand for 20.
Five people are in favor of 20. Voting is pointless.
(Don't you know democracy?)
Please talk to him, So Hyun.
(What did I do?)
Please decide for us.
- Let's go with 20. - Okay.
- We don't know the outcome. - It probably hurt his feelings.
It's okay, I'm fine.
Ready, set.
- Challenge. - Challenge.
The time limit is five minutes.
(Is there a time limit?)
Hurry up and choose.
(Here's the answer to the first round of "Guess the Game".)
(Time limit is five minutes.)
(It's "Protecting Raw Eggs".)
(Dangerous Brides on April 26, 2015)
(It's not "Random Raw Eggs".)
(The game is protecting the raw eggs until the end.)
(In the 5 minutes, if 1 person breaks all the eggs, they fail.)
(They must protect the eggs with care.)
Two for Kwang Soo.
(They try to guess which ones are boiled.)
Keep them in with you.
- Let's go. - These are raw eggs.
- I'm doomed. - I don't know which one is raw.
- Are these all raw? - May I see one?
(May I see one?)
Wait a minute.
(Why did So Hyun...)
(break the egg?)
(She cracks it open.)
- What happened? - Why did you do that?
What did you just do?
(They're all startled.)
(The judges approach them.)
This must be a different game.
- What's going on? - Oh, dear.
What's wrong?
What is this?
- Why are you doing this? - What are you doing?
(Their eggs get taken away.)
Why? What are you doing?
- Why are you doing this? - Why?
- Why? - What are you doing?
(Eggs are so expensive these days. The judges cracked all of them.)
Mission failed.
- Why? - Why?
- This mission... - I shouldn't be happy.
- What was this about? - What is it?
- What was that, So Hyun? - Why was she happy?
- This is strange. - We didn't play a game like this.
- We did. - Did we?
We played the game where we had to crack eggs.
It was Dangerous Wives special with Jessi.
Sorry?
("Protect the Raw Eggs")
(The game was played in pairs.)
(Seok Jin and Kwang Soo ruined the game for everybody...)
(and they were humiliated.)
(Raw eggs, Couples, Seok Jin and Kwang Soo)
- It was in Dangerous Wives special. - That's right.
Sorry?
- Right, Jessi. - We were at a grocery store.
- That's right. - Right.
- Do Yeon was my partner. - It was "Protect the Raw Eggs".
- It was "Protect the Raw Eggs". - That's right. I remember.
I remember because Jessi cracked the egg in my mouth.
Even if we all succeeded, Jae Seok already failed...
You can't.
Exactly.
- What? He put the egg in. - No way.
- It can't be. - What?
- He put the egg under your shirt. - You must have cracked it.
Really?
- Really? - It got cracked?
I didn't crack it.
I just put it in.
- Did it crack? - Really?
- I just put it in. Did it crack? - I think it did.
- It didn't crack. - It didn't.
- It must have cracked. - Hey.
It didn't crack.
What is he doing?
(Why is Jong Kook working so hard?)
One person has to be punished.
The person who couldn't protect their egg is Jae Seok.
- I think Jae Seok deserves it. - He was the first one to fail.
- Do you have one left? - Yes, I do.
- You have one left? - Yes.
Let's pick the person who still has one left.
- You pass. - I pass, right?
Both of my eggs cracked...
but Seok Jin's cracked first.
I saw them losing their eggs first...
and just followed.
What about the two of you...
pull on each other's sideburns...
and whoever makes a noise first loses?
- Get set, - Don't pull too hard.
Whoever makes a noise first...
- is the loser, okay? - Sure.
In 1, 2, 3.
(First one to scream loses.)
(They don't know what the punishment is so they must avoid it.)
(Their sideburns must endure.)
(Who will take the punishment?)
(They show no mercy from the beginning.)
They're all resisting.
(They're about to rip each other's scalp.)
That looks painful.
(Seok Jin lets go.)
Let's take a break.
(He wants to take a break all of a sudden.)
He's done.
He let go first.
No, that was a break.
You can't do that.
- It's Seok Jin. - That's not how you play.
(He was in so much pain.)
That was so painful.
- Okay. - Let's take a short break.
It's Seok Jin.
What is the punishment, anyway?
(What would the box contain?)
(They haven't seen it before.)
What is that?
(What is that smoke?)
- What's that? - I see something.
I don't like scary things.
Why is today's special scary?
Don't do this. Don't try to startle me.
Seok Jin, put your head in the box.
(He has to put his head in the box?)
- My head? - I hate this.
That's good.
(His eyes move fast.)
- You want him to put his head in? - Like this?
Is there a crocodile in there with its mouth open?
He'll come back alive, right?
- This is it, right? - My goodness.
What am I supposed to do?
(He puts on protective goggles.)
I can't see anything at all.
What is it?
- I don't know. - There must be something.
I'd rather get slapped a few hundred times.
(There's the fear of the unknown.)
One...
(I'm getting nervous too.)
Two...
(He merely wanted to take a break but this is too cruel.)
In 1, 2, 3.
(What is the punishment that awaits Seok Jin?)
What is it?
Does he have to kiss somebody?
(That doesn't sound too pleasant.)
Six, seven,
- What's that? - What's that?
- I'm scared. - What's that?
Is it a crocodile?
What was that? It felt like a tongue.
(Why is there a tongue?)
(What was the punishment?)
- What is it? - Oh, my goodness.
(His faced got covered in ink.)
(It makes the rest of them walk away.)
- I don't like the look of that. - He startled me.
(It's as if only his body is floating in air.)
- Oh, my goodness. - What?
What was that?
- What? - What was that?
It looks hideous.
What was it?
What's this?
It's ink?
What happened to my teeth?
Look.
(That was only worth 20°C.)
It keeps on spreading the more you wipe it.
(Grabbing)
(Punching)
- Hey. - I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
- This is what the game does to you. - I'm sorry.
It's not going away.
That looks great.
(He looks like a hard worker.)
Let's just go with this.
Let's do this until the end.
We have to be smart with our choices.
- That's right. - We have to.
- Let's do better. - I understand now.
- Let's succeed. - This is no joke.
(Here's the hint for the next game.)
- What is this? - Gary's back?
- Gary's back again? - Gary knows something.
The second tool is Gary's name tag.
- "Unclean". - "7012" and "Apgujeong".
This sounds recent.
What's "unclean"?
It was recent.
What did we do the day after Gary quit?
- What did we do? - We were unclean?
- What did we do? - We went to Han River.
- Our farewell was unclean. - We went to the photo booth.
- We made stickers out of it. - We went to the karaoke.
- That was unclean. - What about this name tag?
Like I said,
they might have put something obvious as a trap.
We should think about it another way.
What's "unclean"?
What kind of games have we played involving "7012"?
There was a storage.
The lock code was 7012.
- It was a diamond pattern. - Underneath the bed...
(It was the first time that they used 7012.)
- Look for it. - Gary was trapped.
Do we have to find Gary and stick this on his back?
(Is Gary here?)
- Gary... - Is he here?
(Is Gary disguised as a staff member?)
Let's bet 30°C and try it.
Should we try 20°C first?
- Sure, let's do 20°C. - Let's do that.
- We'll start once you're ready. - Okay.
- Let's go. - Go.
- I think we have to find him. - Really?
It might be somebody related to Gary.
- This is helpful. - In 1, 2, 3.
- Start. - Start.
You have five minutes.
- Look for him. - That's it?
- Yes, that's it. - Gary must be here.
- That's it? - Yes.
- Really? - We have his name tag.
- His name tag... - We have to find him.
It might be something related to him.
(The second game is "Find Mini Name Tags".)
- Is Gary really here? - Gary?
(Running Man can't break up with Gary and he can't leave.)
(They called Gary back for one last time.)
(They had to find mini name tags in Gary's studio.)
(They have to find 6 name tags in 5 minutes.)
- Kwang Soo. - Yes?
- Look for him. - Yes, Jae Seok.
(Gary can't be here.)
He must be somewhere close.
- Gary. - Try calling Gary, Kwang Soo.
- I'm calling him right now. - Gary.
7012 and Gary.
Gary.
(Where are you, Gary?)
Gary... Hold on...
What game involved Gary's name tag?
- Gary. - Gary.
- Seok Jin. - Yes?
- I can't see you in the dark. - Hey.
Don't we have to find name tags? We played it at his place.
- What was that? - Those small name tags.
- Those small name tags. - That's right.
- Look for something white. - We have to find name tags.
Look for name tags.
- Look for name tags. - Come here. Isn't that it?
- Small name tags. - They're white for sure.
- Look for small name tags. - Small name tags.
- I found one. It's Kwang Soo's. - Really?
- It's Kwang Soo's. - I found one.
- It's here. - We have to find all of ours.
- Our name tags? - You found one?
- I found Kwang Soo's. - You guys are amazing.
I can't believe he found it.
- I found Haha's. - Okay.
- I found Haha's. - We have to find all our name tags.
- Let's succeed this time. - We found Kwang Soo's.
I told you we should bet 30°C.
We don't even know if we'll succeed. What are you talking about?
(We might fail. What are you talking about?)
- He's just... - I found myself.
- Did you? - Really?
- Ji Hyo, can you find mine? - How did you all find it?
Ji Hyo, can you find mine?
You're going to be punished if you don't find your own.
- Ji Hyo. - Find some more.
- Ji Hyo, can you find mine? - I'm looking for it right now.
Ji Hyo.
- It's here. - Where?
- Jae Seok's is here. - You found mine.
(You found mine.)
I didn't even find mine. What am I doing?
- Your shoes. - Where is it?
- In ten, - Just a second.
- nine, - Sir.
- eight, - Give us 30 more seconds.
- seven, - Give us 30 more seconds.
- six, - Okay.
- five... - Did you find it?
I found one but it's Seok Jin's.
Four...
(Seok Jin runs for it.)
- Stop. - Hold on.
- Two... - What's next?
(Time's up and they fail their second game.)
We didn't find Jong Kook's name tag.
- We only had one left. - Time's out.
Should a person who found nothing go?
Or should the owner of the name tag that we didn't find go?
But I supervised and controlled the whole game.
No, you should go since you didn't find anything.
- Let's have a vote. - No, that's not right.
Okay, let's shuffle the name tags.
Let So Hyun choose one name tag and that person will go.
- Whoever remains should go. - Whoever is picked will survive.
Okay, whoever is chosen won't have to go.
- Whoever is left will have to go. - You saw me, right?
You saw how horrible the punishment can be.
- Okay, So Hyun. Please choose one. - Please.
(To avoid the punishment, the name tag has to be drawn out.)
This person won't face the punishment.
(Who is the first person who will be exempt from the punishment?)
- Who is it? - Yes!
(What a surprise. It's Kwang Soo.)
Okay, then. Kwang Soo will face the punishment.
That's it.
You can't do this to me.
- He's not bullying me. - He is.
No, it can't be. Are you my Bad Santa?
- Are you supposed to bully me? - Fine.
- You're not, right? - Okay.
- We will let you pass. - That was...
- That was the rule. - We will let you pass.
- We will let Kwang Soo pass. - It could've been funny.
So Hyun, please choose my name tag. Is it mine?
- It's Jong Kook. - That's right. Jong Kook is exempt.
(He smiles brightly.)
(Third person to be exempt is surprisingly Seok Jin.)
This is no fun.
- It's Ji Hyo. - My gosh.
- This is crazy. - It's either one of you.
You are not doing this on purpose, right?
(Only Jae Seok and Haha remain.)
- It might be Haha again. - It will be one of you.
- It will be funny if it's Haha. - How can this happen again?
(Who will get to experience the punishment?)
(Please...)
- This person will be exempt, right? - Okay!
This is great.
(Jae Seok is chosen. Haha is exempt.)
- This is awesome. - Jae Seok will...
You are chosen to face the punishment.
- It won't be the same, will it? - No, it won't be.
- Don't open your mouth. - Will it be the same?
Just have your mouth closed.
I'm telling you. It's a horrendous place.
- What could it be? - I can hear them getting ready.
What are they ripping there?
- Can I put my hands first? - No, you can't.
- My goodness. - Don't put your hands in.
- Get ready. - It's only 10 seconds.
Someone is already here.
- They are well-prepared. - Jae Seok.
We are the country of the courteous people.
Get ready. He went in.
- It started. - What is that?
(He has to endure it for 10 seconds.)
My gosh. What is it?
- It's no joke. - What is it?
Are you rubbing something?
- It's crazy. They're rubbing it. - Is it perfume?
- What is this? - It's only 20°C.
- Is it 20 or 30? - It's 20.
(Shivering)
(Get out now. It's past 10 seconds.)
- Why isn't he coming out? - They must be holding him.
(He is coming back, right?)
(The second victim raises his head.)
(Everyone is curious to see him.)
- Why isn't he coming out? - They must be holding him.
(How will Jae Seok look after facing the punishment?)
What is that?
- It wasn't ink? - My goodness.
That scared me.
- That caught me off guard. - Did you see him?
(His face is colorful like a tree.)
Are you okay, Jae Seok?
(This is the Christmas I dreamed of.)
(Please leave me alone. I want to be left alone.)
Is he crying?
He is really crying. Please give us some tissue.
This hurts so much.
- Does it hurt? - Jae Seok.
- My gosh. - Here's tissue.
- How can you do such a thing? - Goodness.
You just made him...
(Now, it's beginning to look like Christmas.)
Shouldn't you experience something like this, too?
Right, you are on a variety show.
- Okay, the third... - She's professional.
- She is professional. - She's so good.
- But she's so cold. - Right.
You're good at this, but you are cold-hearted.
- Please bring in the toy hammer. - It's the toy hammer.
(The hint for the third round is a toy hammer.)
- What episode was that in? - My gosh.
We did a lot of games with this.
We popped the head with it. I mean the balloons.
- What? - Agility?
- There's a heart? - What is this?
- You popped what? - "The back of the head"?
(The hashtags are agility, heart, and the back of the head.)
- Here's the toy hammer. - Can this be the game on agility?
- We covered our heads with a pot. - The one with the pot?
(The Heirs Special was 166th episode of Running Man in 2013.)
(It's the first game with the toy hammer that came into his mind.)
(But how does the heart fit into this game?)
- We had balloons on our heads. - I remember.
It's the game we had balloons on the back of our head.
(Is it the game we popped the balloons with the toy hammer?)
But how is "heart" related?
(Agaility and back of the head are difficult to figure out.)
This is it. The heart...
- Right, it's the game we glued it. - We had to...
It's when Lee Joon Gi appeared on the show.
(The game they played with Joon Gi)
(Game of Emperor's Throne was 314th episode.)
(They had to remove the hearts...)
(on the back of their heads with a toy hammer.)
(Is this game right?)
- This is the one with heart. - That sounds right.
- It's the game with Joon Gi. - That's right.
Let's not rush into a decision. We did that before.
- We might... - It doesn't matter if we rush...
or not because we are the ones who face the punishment anyway.
- I mean... - You didn't face it.
I bet it's my turn next since these two already got it.
- This is so odd. - Just put me in that box already.
- We'll end up facing it again. - It's between us three.
I'm the only one left.
- See? - What is the next punishment?
How much will you be betting?
- Let's bet 30. - Let's go with 30.
- So Hyun, this is... - We'll fail anyway.
- In 1, 2, 3. - Start.
- The time limit is five minutes. - That's too long.
(Backing away)
When she said the time limit, she backed away.
(Hold on. Does So Hyun...)
- She backed away when she said it. - I was just giving you space.
How will I avoid them for five minutes?
Why isn't anyone coming?
Is this it?
Why isn't anyone coming? Is this it?
(He found a heart as soon as he started.)
- What is that? - Seriously?
(Wait, this heart is from the game with Joon Gi.)
(They hunted for hearts with the toy hammer in the episode.)
- What is it? - Seriously?
I found it.
(Beep)
That isn't...
- That's not how it should be done. - You just hit her.
- "Back of the head". - Did you hit her?
- This was the mission. - Okay.
- Wasn't that amazing? - How did you figure it out?
- That was great. - You successfully completed it.
- How did you figure it out? - As soon as we started,
- she moved back a bit. - Right, she did.
I was wondering why she moved back.
Haha, we collected 30°C.
- I wish it was 40°C. - You got it since you succeeded.
- This is the first. - Great.
- I bet the staff was disappointed. - Right.
- I'll do the slate. - Which one is me? I can't tell.
One, two, and three.
(Punching)
(Kwang Soo got hit in the stomach.)
(Seok Jin writes on his name tag.)
How can you try to complete a mission now?
(Let me take your shoe since you are lying down.)
(They remove his name tag and throw his shoe away.)
(They are like hyenas attacking their prey. It's a chaos.)
(It's a party for the bullies.)
(They try to bully anyone whenever there's a chance.)
(Kicking)
Hey.
(They give a massage and cold water therapy for Seok Jin.)
- Someone bullied me, too. - Who is my Bad Santa?
- Who is it? - I can't figure it out.
You will open the window and confess how many times...
- you bullied so far. - I think Jong Kook picked me.
- But that will be too extreme. - I think everyone picked me.
(What is the result?)
(It's "Bully's Confession".)
Which window? That window?
I managed to do four things from the list.
I stepped on the foot, rubbed ink on the face,
threw the shoe,
and poked the cheek.
(Like an expert, he is fast and accurate.)
(It's hard to count how many times Jae Seok bullied.)
(He threw three people's shoes.)
My gosh, Jae Seok.
(He bullies everyone randomly. Whose Bad Santa is he really?)
It's so hard to guess who my Bad Santa is.
(Whose Bad Santa is Jae Seok?)
Out of 5, I successfully did 4.
(Jae Seok and Seok Jin are tied.)
I put spray on the person in the car.
I managed to pull the side hair luckily during the game.
Haha, Kwang Soo, and I pulled the side hair.
I pulled the side hair at that moment.
(It was to decide who would face the punishment.)
(Whose Bad Santa is Seok Jin out of these two?)
I hit the person hard.
(Surprisingly, he's not doing so well.)
I put something in their clothes. I completed two so far.
(He only managed to do two on the list.)
It's me.
(He punches.)
If you hit like that, I won't give this to you.
(He managed to hit really hard twice.)
- Because Jae Seok failed... - Right.
(He mostly attacked Jae Seok and Haha.)
(Who is his real target?)
I untied the shoelace...
(Haha's list of pranks)
and splashed water on the face.
(After checking, he only managed to do one.)
I did two.
I stepped on the person.
(He completed 4 like a bullying mania.)
I splashed water on the body.
(He is an expert in bullying.)
I untied the shoelace.
(He's in the lead.)
I hit the throat when the person was talking.
I completed four on the list.
I completed one by removing the glasses.
I still have a long way to go.
(Status Report on Bullying)
Jae Seok, 3 of us did 4 so far.
- Really? - I heard...
- No wonder. - How can the 3 of us do 4?
No one can beat us when it comes to bullying.
- I'm so proud. - The confession...
- has finished. - But I don't know who picked me.
- I don't know that, either. - Right.
We prepared "Guess Your Santa" for those who suffered from bullying.
For this game, choose one member whom you think is your Bad Santa.
Take them to Room of Truth.
If you guess the right member,
your Bad Santa will turn into Rudolph and serve you as the master.
And they will receive the final punishment.
If you guess the wrong member,
the member you chose will spank you five times.
(The member you choose will spank you five times if you guess wrong.)
I'm sure it wasn't easy even for Jong Kook to bully discreetly.
That means all three of you did four types of bullying.
- They almost finished. - They don't say a word.
(They stay silent.)
Please continue what you're saying.
I think they picked ones that are easy to bully.
Let's take a guess.
- Rock-paper-scissors. - Rock-paper-scissors.
(They decide who will guess first.)
- I won. - My gosh.
- Did Jong Kook win? - At once.
(Open, Room of Truth.)
Gosh, Jong Kook always wins at a time like this.
I don't think it'll be fun for me to guess.
One of you three should guess.
- Give us a chance. - Should I?
- Give me a chance. - Give me a chance.
- Jong Kook. - To whom?
Please give it to me.
- I think I know who it is. - Please, Jong Kook.
I'll bring Rudolph and come back to you.
(He'll bring Rudolph to Jong Kook.)
- Please, Jong Kook. - Give it to me.
(They beg him to give them a chance.)
(Kissing)
I know who it is. Please give me a chance.
- I'll give it to Kwang Soo. - Yes.
(Kwang Soo gets a chance.)
He could take a wrong guess.
- This is driving me crazy. - Goodness.
Come with me, Rudolph.
(He beckons Jae Seok.)
(Get ready to turn into Rudolph.)
Come with me.
- Hurry up. - My goodness.
Run, Rudolph.
(Kwang Soo picks Jae Seok.)
Oh my goodness.
I asked you to give me a chance.
- Let's go. - Good luck.
Kwang Soo is driving me crazy.
(Is Jae Seok Kwang Soo's Bad Santa?)
- Come in, my Rudolph. - My goodness.
(Everyone gets excited about what's going on.)
- I think he's right. - We have a long way to go.
- I think Jae Seok is it. - Really?
(It's the first guess. Will Kwang Soo be spanked?)
(Or will Jae Seok turn into Kwang Soo's Rudolph?)
Kwang Soo's Santa is...
Bell of truth.
(Is Kwang Soo right or wrong?)
- Please ring. - Ring.
Rudolph, just come out.
(What happened in Room of Truth?)
(Kwang Soo will be spanked.)
Oh my goodness.
(He guessed wrong.)
That looks hilarious.
(He's the master of bullies.)
I think Kwang Soo had a misunderstanding.
I'm sorry. He bullied me more than 30 times today,
but those were without any reason.
- Please spank him hard. - Okay.
You have to spank me five times, so go easy at first.
(It's the result of Kwang Soo's wrong guess.)
(Merry Spanking Christmas)
- That's really painful. - My gosh.
- What did he do so wrong? - It's for when you punish someone.
- He's completely fine. - Rudolph.
Come here, Rudolph.
(Get ready to become Rudolph, Seok Jin.)
- Rudolph. - Who's his Rudolph?
(Is one of them his Bad Santa?)
- Where's my Rudolph? - Who is it?
(They earn 30°C after the first mission.)
That's it for "Guess the Game".
The second mission is called "Childlike Missions".
- "Childlike Missions"? - Let's move to the kindergarten.
- Let's go. - Okay.
(What kind of mission awaits them?)
(Wow, it's Running Man.)
For the children to live in a beautiful world,
- Right. - we must make it.
- That's right. - We must change this world.
Please walk on the right side.
For the world to be just...
(What's the next mission at the kindergarten?)
- Where shall we go? - There are many boys, too.
(What kind of dance is that?)
They look like they're five years old.
(It's a lovely dance by children who wait for Santa Claus.)
- We can do anything - We can do anything
(What's the "Childlike Missions" these children prepared?)
Look at the child in the back. He's the only one not dancing.
He isn't dancing.
(He doesn't care.)
He's too shy.
I couldn't go to a kindergarten.
I went to a kindergarten.
Me, too.
(He's proud.)
- Kindergarten - Kindergarten
Why are all the kindergarten songs the same?
- For nice and cute children - For nice and cute children
(This is the song.)
I thought only my kindergarten had a song.
There are three tasks for "Childlike Missions".
1st is hearing a specific comment from a child within 3 minutes.
- That's really difficult. - It is.
2nd is keeping 15 children quiet for 10 seconds.
(Keeping 15 children quiet for 10 seconds)
For 10 seconds.
(How will they keep these children quiet for 10 seconds?)
- I think 10 seconds are too long. - That's too difficult.
Third is to put on Santa Claus gloves and take off the name tags...
of 15 children within 60 seconds.
That's easy.
(Gosh, that's so easy.)
Are you going to attack the children?
They are children.
Will you give them their worst memory?
- These children are innocent. - You might traumatize them.
It's a Christmas nightmare.
We have to earn 20 points.
That's right.
Except for So Hyun, I'm the most childlike.
- What did you say? - Come on, Kwang Soo.
You should quit smoking first.
(What are you talking about?)
Stop going to clubs.
- Why does that matter? - Goodness.
Guess who's the one living like a child.
- Who is it? - Who?
I live like a child because I don't do anything.
Then why do you look so old?
When I'm off work, I go home and sleep after eating.
If you don't do anything,
it means you're unemployed.
(Seok Jin is an unemployed old man.)
(Ji Hyo and Kwang Soo must hear the following in 3 minutes.)
(It's fun. I love you. Stay strong.)
(Kwang Soo is good at fidgeting like a child.)
Let's go in, Kwang Soo.
(Will they succeed the first part of the mission?)
Let's start by saying hello.
Hello.
- Hello, everyone. - Hello.
(They're from Running Man.)
- What's going on here? - I've seen you before.
- Have you seen me? - Hello.
- Do you know Running Man? - Yes!
Running Man is about that.
What? Do you know what it is?
- I've watched all of it. - I know what it is.
You have?
(The children are loud and energetic.)
Right, take a look.
It'll be hard to make them quiet.
It won't be easy for 10 seconds.
They don't stop talking.
- In 1, 2, 3. Start. - Start.
What do you think of Running Man?
(He doesn't need anything else, but "It's fun.")
It's strange.
(Is it that bad?)
(He's such a merciless critic.)
Good job. The children are doing well.
They're so cute.
It's fun.
Is it fun?
(Did you just say it's fun?)
Is Running Man fun?
- No. - It's fun.
What do you think of Running Man?
(They succeed in hearing "It's fun.")
- It's fun. - It's fun.
- It's funny. - Everyone.
Do you know what this is?
- It's a heart, isn't it? - Tell me what you think in three.
- In 1, 2, 3. - In 1, 2, 3.
(A heart obviously means "I love you." Will you say it?)
- It's fun. - It's fun.
(The heart is fun too.)
- That one is over, okay? - What's this?
(Laughing)
"That one is over."
- That one is over, okay? - What's this?
- What did you say? - Say it again.
- I love you. - I love you.
- In 1, 2, 3. - In 1, 2, 3.
(They succeed in hearing "I love you.")
Everyone.
(They're expert on this.)
- The children are so innocent. - They're very good.
Look at me, okay?
(They go for the last comment.)
What do you think about me?
(Hurry up and answer.)
- What do you think about me? - You're a middle-aged man.
- A middle-aged man? - What?
- I'm only 32 years old. - What do you think?
- What's this? - What do you think about me?
Who wants to arm wrestle with me?
Do you want to arm wrestle with me?
- Do you want to play? - Who wants to play?
In 1, 2, 3.
- You're very strong. - In 1, 2, 3.
(They try to make them say, "You're strong.")
(Instead, Kwang Soo loses the arm wrestling match.)
- I want to play. - Shall we?
He should win instead.
He must win so that they say, "You're strong."
Gosh, he should make the children hang on him.
Let's play one by one.
How am I?
(Everyone plays at the same time.)
Don't take off my name tag.
(We hope he keeps his name tag.)
- Here's what's difficult. - They're getting more energetic.
(They only have 40 seconds.)
- What am I like? - How do I look?
(He tenses up without having any muscle.)
How do I look?
(Punching)
(A child hits his face.)
- He got hit in the face. - Gosh.
(He gets hit by a child.)
He should make the children hang on his arm.
(Oh, no! Only 10 seconds left.)
Is he strong or not?
- What do you think? - You're not strong.
- You're strong! - How am I?
(They try to make them say it.)
- Be quiet. - Look at him.
- Look. - How am I?
(Please, children. You know what you need to say.)
(There are 2 seconds left. Please say, "You're strong.")
In 1, 2, 3.
You're not strong.
(You're not strong.)
(6-year-olds are scary these days.)
Mission failed.
(Ji Hyo and Kwang Soo fail.)
- Let's go. - It's not easy...
- but it's doable. - They have 10 seconds?
(Jong Kook and Haha must silence the children for 10 seconds.)
(Would they be able to achieve silence in 10 seconds?)
(They act bright.)
It's Haha.
- It looks dangerous. - They're very hyper right now.
It's not easy.
(Even 1 second will be a challenge.)
He's dangerous.
(He's full of energy.)
Look at him.
- Hello, Haha. - Thank you.
- Hello. - Hello.
(Hello, everybody.)
Everybody.
We're going to play a fun game.
(Exclaiming)
Clap.
(They focus at the word "game".)
- Haha is good. - It's looking good.
- It's looking good. - It is.
The children are focused on them.
Do you know what game it is?
- Yes. - Yes.
We have to rip name tags.
- We have to rip name tags. - Ripping name tags?
The winner gets a chance to rip our name tags.
If you win this game,
- you can rip our name tags. - That's right.
You have to win this game.
(Are they in or not?)
(He makes weird sounds.)
They're not ordinary. What are we going to do with him?
(Chuckling)
- He's covering his ears. - Third row, right?
We need to watch out for him.
He's the most dangerous child for our mission.
(He's full of energy.)
They're not ordinary. What are we going to do with him?
Everybody.
If you stay silent for 10 seconds, you win the game.
If you make noise first, you're last place.
What do you do if you want to be the winner?
- You must be quiet. - You must be quiet for 10 seconds.
In 1, 2, 3.
(Would they achieve silence for 10 seconds?)
(They have their mouths sealed.)
I think it's hard for them.
- Aren't they so cute? - They are.
(We're almost there, guys. Please hold on a bit more.)
(They succeeded the mission.)
(Great job, kids.)
- You won. - You won.
You're all first place.
- You're first place. - You won.
Wasn't that it?
(They did it again.)
- Thank you for not talking. - You won.
- Were you scared? - It ripped.
(You can walk in here on your own but you can't leave.)
You're so good at this.
(A kid starts doing sit-ups.)
What is he doing?
(This is how children say farewell.)
Haha is flustered.
Isn't Haha struggling?
(I want to play with you, Haha.)
- Nobody's here. - Nobody's here, right?
(Haha is popular amongst children.)
What are you doing?
(Lifting)
Bye, Haha.
- I love you. - You'll get to rip name tags soon.
- I love you. - Bye. I love you.
(Haha and Jong Kook earn 20°C.)
(The last mission is to rip children's name tags in 1 minute.)
- Hello. - Guys.
Hello, guys.
(The last duo enters confidently.)
"Infinite Challenge".
Hello!
(Jae Seok is a star amongst children too.)
- Guys. - Guys.
- Guys. - Sure. What?
(Crowded)
Polar bears?
They're not even going to Seok Jin.
Seok Jin.
Gather around Seok Jin.
- All right. - Let's do this.
I'm the devil.
(Their plan is to play "Angel and Devil" game.)
I'm the good person.
I'm the angel.
They're going to gather the children and rip their name tags.
That's a good plan.
If you want to be an angel, you can line up in front of me...
and if you want to be on the devil's side, go to him.
- Yes. - Yes.
If you come to me, I'll slap your bottoms.
(He acts mean.)
(Nobody wants that.)
Let's get started. Let's say, "Start."
In 1, 2, 3.
- Start. - Start.
Don't run.
Come to the angel. One by one.
Hold on.
I'm the devil. I'm going to rip your name tags.
The devil's going to rip your name tags.
Tae Hee.
If you want to be on the devil's side, come here.
(The kids try to fight the devil.)
I'm the devil.
Why is Seok Jin getting punched?
I don't know.
The children are united. They want to become angels.
The devil can rip the name tags, too.
Why am I getting absorbed in this?
- Hurry up. - Seo Hyun is next.
You should rip them too, Seok Jin.
- Seo Hyun. - The devil's going to rip it.
I'm the devil. You're on my side.
Hold on.
Help him, Seok Jin.
He needs to help.
- He's supposed to help. - My gosh.
They have no time so Seok Jin has to help.
He should rip them too.
Stop, Seung Soo.
- Hold on. - Hey.
- Seung Soo. - What are you doing?
It's not coming off.
I'm going to rip it.
This won't work.
- I'll help. - Hold on.
- I guess there's no time. - Seriously.
Why weren't you helping?
There's not enough time.
- You were supposed to help. - I see.
He's a fool.
- He thought he was a real devil. - I agree.
- He was absorbed in it. - He's red like the devil.
He thought he was Red Devil.
(The kids are punishing the devil.)
(They're eradicating the devil.)
I love you, guys.
- Thank you... - I should have helped.
for joining us on Running Man.
- Yes. - Always listen to your teacher.
I hope you grow up healthy and bright.
- Thank you. - Yes.
- Bye. - Bye.
(Thank you for reminding us of our inner child.)
(There's a surprise for the children.)
(The staff delivered gifts for each child.)
(Merry Christmas!)
(Christmas with little angels)
(They've accumulated 50°C.)
I was so absorbed into being a devil.
- Why didn't you rip the name tags? - I know.
- I was so absorbed in my role. - Why didn't you help?
What was that?
(Hitting)
It's still a mystery to me.
(Come on.)
Why didn't I help?
- What are you doing? - It's getting started again.
It's getting started.
(You never know when they'll start attacking each other.)
Jong Kook is...
(Jae Seok finds a new target.)
(My gosh!)
- What are you doing? - That's Jae Seok's mission.
He has to spray water on someone's face.
- Is it me? - He has to spray water.
There's something to this.
I know you're not my Bad Santa.
What are you doing?
(Here I come.)
(Kicking)
Did you really kick me?
Wasn't that a low kick? That actually hurt.
- It wasn't. - It really hurt.
(Why is he pinching?)
(You idiot)
- He's kicking him for real. - That looks painful.
(They go back and forth.)
What should we do?
(We're close.)
(Jae Seok joins in as well.)
(They kick as hard as they love each other.)
(Collapsing)
(Bad Santas work hard even during break.)
That's so funny.
It's funny.
The second mission has ended.
It's time for "Bully's Confession" again.
- Let's do it again. - Let's do it.
- All right. - Okay.
(How many bullies did each member complete?)
My list...
hasn't changed. It's still the same.
When we went to the kindergarten,
I stepped on the person's foot as soon as I sat down.
(Jong Kook's list of pranks)
When we got back, I tripped the person.
I did two more.
(Haha's list of pranks)
(I can't do it.)
(I couldn't do any.)
I did five.
Did you clear them all?
(Jae Seok's list of pranks)
I just hope it's not Jong Kook.
(Jae Seok is Ji Hyo's Bad Santa.)
What now?
How can I bully Ji Hyo?
("Bullying mission")
(He stepped on Ji Hyo, poked her cheeks, and put dirt on her face.)
(He also sprayed water on her face and took her shoe off.)
I'm done.
(Kwang Soo is Jae Seok's Bad Santa.)
I'm in trouble.
("Bullying mission")
(Kwang Soo untied Jae Seok's shoelaces, stepped on his foot,)
(pinched his thigh, got water on him, and hit his Adam's apple.)
(Jae Seok and Kwang Soo cleared their mission.)
(Jae Seok and Kwang Soo succeed and Haha comes in last.)
When will we ever get a chance to pull pranks like this?
Today is like Jae Seok's birthday.
- That's true. - There's no time.
- Did Jong Kook finish? - Look at Jong Kook's.
- Is he Ji Hyo's Bad Santa? - I think he's my Bad Santa.
- He kicked me, didn't he? - He did.
Jong Kook bullied a lot when we came back here.
He seemed so determined.
- He bullied me a lot just now. - He kicked me once.
Now, it's time for you...
- She's really good. - to guess who your Santa is.
It's not easy to interrupt like that.
You'll play "Guess Your Santa" again.
- Let's play rock-paper-scissors. - Let's do that.
- Rock-paper-scissors. - Rock-paper-scissors.
(They play to be fair.)
- Okay. - Okay.
(Seok Jin and Kwang Soo win.)
- Rock-paper-scissors. - It's one of them.
- Come in with me. - Me?
I said to come in right now.
Wait.
- Go in. - I'm not it.
- Go in. - Go in.
- Let's go in. - I'm not the one.
We have a lot to do.
If I'm wrong, you can spank me five times.
- Just come in. - Kwang Soo.
Just come in. We'll find out.
- Let's go in. - I'm not your Santa.
You'll be spanked again.
- I'm sure about it this time. - You'll be spanked again.
I'm sorry, but if it's not Jae Seok, it has to be Seok Jin.
Kwang Soo's Bad Santa is...
(If he's right, Seok Jin's donation is made under Kwang Soo's name.)
(Did Kwang Soo guess correctly?)
Is it Seok Jin?
- I don't think it's Seok Jin. - I think Seok Jin...
is Kwang Soo's Bad Santa.
All right.
- Bell of truth, please ring. - Please ring.
- What's the result? - Please, please.
Rudolph.
(Let me introduce my Rudolph.)
(Kwang Soo guesses correctly.)
Shouldn't Rudolph be on all fours?
Didn't Seok Jin make it too obvious?
- My goodness. - You should be on all fours.
Finally, I have my own Rudolph.
You have a big nose just like your nickname.
- That's true. - I thought it was your real nose.
"Guess Your Santa" is over.
Please choose another box for the next mission.
Someone else should choose one this time.
- Let's pick a big one. - Can my Rudolph pick one?
- Yes, I'll pick one. - My Rudolph will do it.
- Okay. - He's good at picking.
How about a small one?
- That's not a box. - It isn't?
How about this one?
I was supposed to pick one.
- It's okay. - You said I should pick one.
You should pick one fast, but you couldn't find the boxes.
(What's their next mission?)
- It's inside. - It's "Guess the Result".
What's that?
The third round is "Guess the Result".
You must predict whether the member will clear the mission...
or fail.
If you're correct, you'll earn the number of degrees...
- that you bet. - Do we play this as a group?
If you're incorrect, one of you will be punished.
- Just one person? - The category is music.
Please choose two members who will compete.
- Music? - I don't feel confident.
Shouldn't singers do it?
Let's have Jong Kook and Ji Hyo play.
- Give it a try, Ji Hyo. - Okay.
- You must bet on... - Bet 30°C.
- who will clear the mission. - It should be 30°C.
- 30°C - Let's bet 30°C.
Let's bet 30°C.
(They bet 30°C.)
- Is it difficult? - It's guessing the song title.
When the music plays, put on the headphones.
Guess the title of the song that I'll sing.
- Are you going to sing? - Yes.
Are you good at singing?
- You won't hear me sing anyway. - Right, right.
She's wondering why you want to know.
It doesn't matter whether she sings well or not.
- You can't hear her anyway. - I can sense the feeling.
- She's very witty. - Don't miss her singing.
So Hyun is quite witty.
I'm sad that I won't hear her sing.
You're witty, So Hyun.
Please play the music.
It depends on what the song is.
- Jong Kook is better at music. - Let's bet on Jong Kook.
Let's bet on Jong Kook.
In 2, 3.
(Is it Jong Kook or Ji Hyo?)
- In 2, 3. - Jong Kook.
(They bet on Jong Kook's success.)
Get ready.
You don't know whom we chose, so you must do your best.
That's right.
Do your best.
- What did you say? - Good luck.
- Do your best. - Of course, I will.
Get ready.
Start.
(Jong Kook must guess 2 out of 3 first for the bet to succeed.)
(Will they win their bet?)
Get ready, start.
("Wrong Meeting" by Kim Gun Mo)
After we had a big argument
She's singing with the wrong melody.
This isn't the right one.
Without any contact
"Any contact"?
I finally realized
The melody sounds strange.
Just say you can't sing it.
- One day - Gosh.
(It's difficult to guess.)
- "You and I"? - "Who's Your Mama" by JYP?
(Wrong)
After a big argument
"At home"?
- "You and I"? - After a big argument
"We could fight"?
"You and I"?
(So Hyun continues to try.)
"You and I are friends".
That's not it.
- Guess the song title. - "You and I are friends".
- That's not a song title. - "You and I"?
- "After a big argument"? - You look so out of it today.
(She looks out of it.)
You and my friend
- Stopped contacting me - "Stopped contacting me".
- What's next? - You seem
To avoid me
- They should know by now. - You seem to avoid me
"You and my friend stopped contacting me".
- Which song is it? - What are the lyrics saying?
Gosh, what are you trying to do?
"You and my friend stopped contacting me".
Someone is cheating on someone.
- What are you doing? - That's not what the song is about.
Yes, it's about cheating.
You can't contact them.
Is it "Wrong Meeting" by Kim Gun Mo?
That's right.
That's correct.
Is that correct?
What's the answer?
We did it.
It was "Wrong Meeting" by Kim Gun Mo.
(Answer one more, Jong Kook.)
Good job.
Jong Kook wins one point.
("Eyes, Nose, Lips" by Tae Yang)
This is Jae Seok's favorite song.
(He copies Tae Yang.)
- "Love"? - Every
- "Love"? - Fingernail
(Which song is this?)
(He also copies Tae Yang.)
I can still feel you
(Neither of them can guess which song it is.)
This is a difficult song.
I know.
(If Jong Kook answers correctly, they win the bet.)
Sing it again.
"Only Look At Me" by Tae Yang?
No.
Is it "Eyes, Nose, Lips" by Tae Yang?
- That's correct. - Is that correct?
- That's amazing. - How did he guess it?
- That was amazing. - What is it?
- It's "Eyes, Nose, Lips". - Just watch this on TV.
Just watch this on TV.
Is the game over?
- Is the game over? - You helped us, Ji Hyo.
It's a good thing that you didn't guess correctly.
- We bet on Jong Kook. - Did you?
- Yes. - Didn't I do a good job?
- Yes, you did well. - Now,
the thermometer reads 80°C.
- We're almost there. - We have 20°C left.
We only have 20°C left.
The second category for "Guess the Result" is...
"Rudolph's Horns".
What's that?
Please choose one member who will play with me.
"Rudolph's Horns"?
- Would Rudolph like to try it? - Okay.
Seok Jin will give it a try.
(He's the best member to play it.)
What kind of game is it?
Predict if a member can hook at least 3 out of 10 rings...
on Rudolph's horns by throwing them.
By throwing them?
Do we bet whether they will succeed or not?
He has to put on the horns.
Is that the end if we succeed?
Is that it?
- Yes. - That's it.
I have to guess my Santa before it ends.
(Let's earn 20°C so that the others can be punished.)
(When the temperature reaches 100°C, the 3 are punished.)
(Jae Seok and Kwang Soo are exempted from the punishment.)
(Jong Kook won't let it happen.)
Let's bet 10°C for now.
- Let's bet 10°C. - Yes.
I say we bet 20°C.
- Why should we bet only 10°C? - What do we have to do to win?
Be quiet. I'll explain to you later.
Let's bet 20°C.
That's good.
- Let's play rock-paper-scissors. - Let's do that.
- All right. - Let's play.
- Rock-paper-scissors. - Rock-paper-scissors.
- The three of you stay. - Goodness.
- Please, Jae Seok. - Come on, Jae Seok.
- We have to get 20°C. - I can do it.
- You can do it. - You can do it.
Rock-paper-scissors.
(How will their fates turn out?)
(Jong Kook wins.)
- Bet 10°C. - 10°C.
There we go.
- Why did you lose? - 10°C.
It's possible to hook three rings.
- This is difficult. - Really?
I've done it in elementary school.
- I don't think it's possible. - 3 out of 10...
I'll do my best.
In 1, 2, 3.
(They bet on Seok Jin's success.)
(Show us what you can do.)
- Get ready. - This isn't easy.
- So Hyun, you can do it. - You can do it.
- That's right. - Start.
Let's go, So Hyun.
(The result depends on So Hyun and Seok Jin's teamwork.)
- Gosh. - She failed.
(She misses the first ring.)
She still has nine left.
You need to catch it.
- You need to catch it. - Did she make it?
You succeed if you make two more.
It may be possible.
(She hooks the second ring.)
- I did it. - Did we win?
Not yet.
(If she hooks one more, they can earn 10°C.)
Wait.
(She becomes more confident.)
(Please put it on your horn, Rudolph.)
(She hooks the third ring.)
- Was that a success? - I did it.
(This is a Christmas miracle.)
- What happened? - We did it.
- We won! - Mission accomplished.
(The second "Guess the Result" mission is a success.)
So Hyun was so good.
(It was a perfect collaboration between So Hyun and Seok Jin.)
Seok Jin.
I did good.
How did you manage, So Hyun?
It's nothing but I'm happy.
(They earn 10°C and accumulate 90°C.)
- This is amazing. - Right?
(They're almost at 100°C.)
The third game is called "Telepathy".
- "Telepathy". - Pick one person...
and they can write down one answer...
to my question.
The rest of the members can discuss...
and guess 3 out of 5 to succeed.
We have to pick a person who thinks normally.
Don't pick somebody who has unique views.
- We need somebody normal. - Pick somebody with common views.
- It's me. - I think I'm the most...
normal here.
- Then you should go. - Sure. Let's pick Haha.
Write down something we would know.
I'll write down something very simple.
Don't write down your thoughts. Make it simple.
We can do it.
We can catch one Rudolph.
- We have to hear the question. - Haha is not ordinary.
Here's the first question.
(What is the first question?)
When do you think you look the most handsome?
(When do you think you look the most handsome?)
- This is... - We talked about this.
We talked about this?
(When do I look the most handsome?)
When is it, Haha?
- The most handsome. - When you think you look the best.
- Okay. - That's normal.
- Make it normal. - Let's make it normal.
(When he takes a shower?)
- Okay, this is it. - Okay.
(They pick shower.)
One.
- After taking a shower. - After taking a shower.
(Did we get it, Haha?)
(They matched.)
(Guys look the best after taking a shower.)
- Right? - That's when you look sexy.
(Let's keep this going.)
- This is how it goes. - Good job.
Here's the second question. How do you relieve stress?
- Isn't this it? - This is difficult.
(Doesn't Haha like basketball?)
- This is too general. - This is difficult.
Hold on. I have to get this right.
Can I just pick one answer and you try to guess it?
- Sure, let's do that. - That sounds right.
- Haha, pick whatever you like. - Pick whatever you like.
Don't try to guess what we're going to say.
Should we do this?
(That's the Haha I know.)
- It's this. - Stop doing that.
- Stop it. - That's it.
You know me, right?
- Yes. - That's the only way.
- See? This is it. - What about this?
(Is it alcohol or basketball?)
No, that's not it.
- It's this. - It's this.
- In 1, 2, 3. - It's this.
- In 1, 2, 3. Alcohol. - Alcohol.
(Haha, do you relieve stress by drinking?)
(They matched.)
(Talking with good people while drinking)
(It worked. They're happy.)
That's what Haha does.
(They've been together for 7 years.)
- I like to talk. - We know a lot.
- We know a lot about you. - I wrote it down right away.
- This is it. - It's alcohol.
It's the last question.
That was a bit difficult.
- Think about me. I'm the standard. - Right.
Here's the third question.
Which celebrity do you want to switch looks with?
He talks about this person all the time.
There's one.
(It's G-Dragon.)
(They've heard Haha mention his name way too many times.)
It changed recently.
(I have a new idol now.)
He has a new one now.
Just write the one you always mention.
I think it hurts his pride to say it.
(It's a dilemma.)
This is a really difficult question but I think I know the answer.
- Sure, it's simple. - Sure.
You always say this on Running Man.
Write down what you think.
(Whom did Haha pick?)
Haha has a few in mind.
- In 1, 2, 3. - In 1, 2, 3.
- G-Dragon. - G-Dragon.
(If they get this right, they'll achieve 100°C.)
(Did they get it right?)
(G-Dragon)
(They matched.)
- G-Dragon. - G-Dragon.
(They get three questions in a row. They achieve 100°C.)
He liked G-Dragon for a long time.
Let's do five questions.
- Shall we continue? - I'm so happy now.
- You have already... - I'm getting goosebumps.
- Haha. - We matched.
What was that?
- I love you. - He likes G-Dragon.
You have already cleared the mission.
- We cleared it. - Let's go for five questions.
(This is a special round.)
They know so much about me.
Here's the fourth question.
What do you think is your best body part?
- How am I supposed to write this? - His right arm.
(He used to show off his muscular right arm.)
- How am I supposed to write this? - He always flashes it at us.
He always flashes it at us.
(Haha, you know your right bicep looks good, right?)
- In 1, 2, 3. - Right arm.
(Will they get four in a row?)
(Right arm)
(They matched.)
Is this a prank? Is it?
I'm getting goosebumps.
(It's 100 percent real.)
What was that?
Is this a prank?
(They're united over the right answer.)
I can't believe it.
Shall we try one more? How did we get it right?
- This is unbelievable. - We didn't get any wrong.
- Here's the last question. - We got 100 percent right.
- This is a bit difficult. - I'm touched.
When do you feel like an adult?
I know.
- It's that time. - When Dream was born.
(Is it when Haha became a dad?)
- That's right. - Please. This is the last one.
(We can read each other's minds.)
(Would they get 5 in a row and make the impossible possible?)
Please. This is the last one.
(Dream)
- When Dream was born. - When Dream was born.
(It's correct.)
(They get 5 in a row.)
(You don't have to say it.)
It's Dream.
- This is amazing. - It's obvious.
- I'm about to cry. - We can guess 200 questions right.
I guessed it first.
- What just happened? - I'm about to cry.
- This is a miracle. - It is.
- I told you. - We spent a long time together.
(It's a miracle created by the 7 years they've been together.)
- I'm touched. - Me too.
Nobody would guess his right arm.
Nobody would.
The thermometer's full.
- Okay. We did it. - Yes!
(They achieve 100°C.)
You have achieved 100°C. Here's the final "Bully's Confession".
(If they don't want to be punished,)
(they must complete their lists.)
(Haha only completed 1.)
If Seok Jin has him, he can't attack, right?
I can't. I am done.
(Glancing)
(Haha does something to Jong Kook.)
He's going to kill you.
This wasn't the right timing. I can't help you.
(Did you just touch a tiger's cheek?)
I have no time.
Just do it quickly.
I think he has him.
(Haha sprays water on him.)
(I have no mercy.)
(Jong Kook pays back to Jae Seok instead of Haha.)
Why are you twisting my arm?
All Santas, except for the Rudolph,
open the window and say your last confessions.
(Jong Kook has 4, Ji Hyo has 2, and Haha has 1 so far.)
When he was drinking water, I hit his hand and spilled it.
(Jong Kook had 4 before so does that make it 5?)
(5 hours ago, while picking his opponent)
(Who is Jong Kook's prey?)
(Congratulations, Haha.)
He's my younger brother.
(But I still need to do it.)
I'm reluctant.
("Bullying mission")
(Jong Kook stepped on Haha, tripped him, put something...)
(in his shirt, spilled his water, and hit him.)
Mission cleared.
(Jong Kook clears the mission.)
(Ji Hyo's target was Seok Jin.)
I didn't get anything.
(She only took off his glasses and knocked his knees.)
I untied his shoelaces, dabbed his cheek, and sprayed water on him.
(Haha was being a coward and only got 3 done.)
(He couldn't splash coke on him or hide his shoes.)
(Jae Seok and Kwang Soo cleared the missions.)
(Jong Kook also cleared his.)
We're all done.
The three members who didn't clear the mission will be punished.
We'll penalize just one person.
- That's good. - Whoever gets picked...
- Let's do a lottery. - Let's do that.
I have a feeling it'll be me.
(The lottery starts.)
Please hand them out, So Hyun.
(Only 1 out of 3 cards is the penalty card.)
(The unlucky Kwang Soo is interested in this.)
Let's see how you react.
In 1, 2, 3.
(Which member is the unlucky one on Christmas?)
(Ji Hyo has the penalty card.)
(Oh dear, Ji Hyo.)
Would you like to switch?
Why is it "Oh dear"?
(Should we switch or not?)
Life is not that complicated.
Okay.
(Seok Jin and Ji Hyo switch.)
(Seok Jin has the penalty card now.)
(Would you like to switch?)
No, no.
(I refuse.)
(I don't have a good feeling about that one.)
I don't want it.
I think he has a bad feeling.
(It's time to check the cards.)
- In 3, 2, 1. - In 3, 2, 1.
Open it up.
(Seok Jin has the penalty card.)
I'll never switch with you.
Over my dead body.
(Seok Jin has the worst luck.)
Don't ask for it.
(I'm exempt.)
- Was it me before? - It was you.
(Seok Jin and Ji Hyo's fates have changed.)
- All right. - I told you to switch.
What? What did I do?
Haha just looked at his.
(You shouldn't switch without thinking.)
The ultimate penalty goes to...
Rudolph Seok Jin.
(Rudolph Seok Jin will get the last penalty.)
- Go in. - This is driving me nuts.
There goes Jong Kook.
I'll escort him. Here he goes.
Get set, go. Put your head in.
- This is too funny. - My goodness.
(What kind of Christmas nightmare is in the box?)
- You're almost done. - It must be something intense.
I think it's hurting him.
(My goodness)
(What is wrong with his face?)
I'm relieved.
(It's clothes pegs, ink, and flour all at once.)
(Welcome to the Christmas horror show.)
- That's horrible. - I'm so relieved.
(Jae Seok, Jong Kook, and Kwang Soo get to donate under their names.)
Anyhow, Merry Christmas, everybody.
Viewers,
- Merry Christmas. - Merry Christmas.
(Merry Christmas)
(On Christmas morning)
- Hello. - Why is it so dark in here?
- Hello. - Hi.
I never thought I would see you all again.
- And yet, we are here again. - Yes, we are.
What is this?
(What is it?)
- They are apples. - Lift the whole box?
- Apples? - They are apples.
(It's a basket of apples with a Christmas card.)
- Should I read this? - Yes, please.
"Dear beloved members of Running Man,"
"we apologize for hurting your feelings in this past week."
"We will endeavor to be mature and to do our best."
"Once again, we are sorry. We love you. From the Running Man staff."
In the upcoming year,
- we will do our best. - Yes, we will.
Once again, we would like to apologize for worrying you.
Everyone, Merry Christmas.
(Have a happy Christmas.)
(Next week)
(2017 Kickoff will be held.)
(Running Man will have a big project in 2017.)
(Their grand project will be revealed.)
(2017 Kickoff)