(Parental guidance advised for viewers under the age of 12.)
(The year of the monkey)
(Running Man 2016)
What? What are we doing?
One, two, three.
Tell us the appearance of someone who would go well with us.
Who here is taller than 170cm?
- I found the person! - What?
- We have to decide. - Who should we leave out?
- Take a picture... - Who should I eliminate?
This is so nerve-wrecking.
- Where is it? - Please!
I don't care as long as it isn't me.
- Really? - That's impossible.
(Who will be the first loser and the winner of 2016?)
The new year, the year of the monkey, has dawned upon us.
- Happy New Year. - Happy New Year.
- Don't just start with that. - My back...
- Tell us before you do that. - Well I just...
Tell us before you do that.
Tell you what?
Haha, do you have any wishes for 2016?
- I wish all of you good health. - I see.
I hope you stay healthy and...
- happy this year. - That's right.
- That's right. - We should all stay healthy.
- We should all stay healthy. - That is my wish this year.
Gary, how about you?
Like Haha, I hope all of you stay healthy and happy...
- this year. - Okay.
Thank you. Jong Kook, how about you?
- I hope I stay healthy. - I see.
- Even healthier? - You're already very healthy.
- How can he be even healthier? - He'll live for 300 years.
- I need to live a long life. - I see.
- I'm sure all of you have lots... - Right.
- to say, but let's wrap it up. - All right.
Okay, I'm fine with that.
- Well, we have to... - Just stay put.
Seok Jin, just stay put.
- Let's start off... - Yes.
- the new year with a bang. - Let's start.
- Let's go that way. - Let's go.
- Yes. - Let's go.
(Today's special mission will soon be revealed.)
(This buffet restaurant is filled with mouth-watering food.)
- Didn't we do this before? - Wow.
What is this?
- Yes, there it is. - There it is.
- It's the... - It's the Food Bingo.
- It's the Food Bingo. - What is this?
- I love this game. - Wow.
- This is... - I'm very hungry.
- Last time... - What is this?
It's a buffet.
- We'll tell you about today's race. - Okay.
Today, with the viewers...
(With the...)
(viewers?)
You will play the Comment Avatar Race.
- What? - Comment Avatar?
(The Comment Avatar Race)
We prepared this game in order to communicate with...
our viewers and show how thankful we are.
Communication is important.
On the phones that will be given to you,
you will each have an active SNS account.
Are they our actual accounts?
No, we made fake accounts that you will use for the race.
Before you perform any mission,
you will post a description and a photo, then receive comments.
- Today, you will become... - Who should we eliminate?
- the avatars of the viewers. - In the black coat.
You can only perform actions based on the viewers' comments.
- What kind of comments? - This is going to be hard.
Based on the results, you will be given Running Balls.
You will either get punishment or luck.
(The ultra strong punishments are back.)
We have to wear these?
(Who will receive the first punishment of the year?)
It's all right to post one as a test, right?
- That's all right. - So?
- You can log into your account... - This is how you do it?
- This is what you call a comment? - I got it. That will do.
- It pops out when you press this. - How does it go?
- The comments are coming up. - These are the comments?
(You look so handsome!)
My face is swollen today.
(He's never been so awkward in front of a camera.)
I posted one.
(Post more pictures!)
This is tough.
I did it only for a moment, and I'm tired. I'm not meant for it.
Me neither.
(With Gary's help, Ji Hyo uploads her first post.)
I did it.
(You make a good couple.)
(You are so handsome!)
(Please be nice to me today!)
(Go, Haha.)
(Go, Seok Jin!)
(This account is for today's show. Hello, Jong Kook!)
(Everyone has finished learning how to use it.)
(The first mission is Food Bingo.)
I only have three minutes. Can I pick anything?
I love all of these.
(He can pick only 25 out of all dishes.)
Marinated crab!
There are so many delicious dishes here.
This is crazy.
One.
Wait. Wait. Is this any good?
(Eating)
(Haha chooses what he likes.)
I can't choose!
One, two, three, four.
(It's filled with food I love!)
This is really crazy.
They are leaving many comments.
Kwang Soo got 120 comments as soon as he posted one.
They are...
- all very nice. - Ji Hyo got 700 comments.
She got 800 comments.
- This is too difficult. - This is really tough.
- The letters are too small. - How does it work?
I really love this.
Thank you for the food.
Pasta.
Spaghetti. Of course I'll take both.
I love spaghetti. There's no jjolmyeon, right?
They all look so delicious.
Gosh.
(Exclaiming with joy)
Salmon sushi.
I should choose the ones many people would like.
What would I eat if I were a viewer?
I should choose the food people generally love.
Tuna sushi.
I have to take what they are not taking.
I need to get kimchi.
Oh my gosh.
They all look delicious.
What do I do?
Do I have to arrange them in the order of preference?
Wait. Just put them down first.
Just arrange it randomly.
I won't be the one to choose.
- I will arrange it in the order. - Let's put the most delicious one.
You can freely arrange them.
First, you have to take a picture of your dishes.
When you post the picture, ask them which food you should eat.
You will read the first comment and eat the food.
- We read the first comment? - That's right.
The very first comment.
(First round is Food Bingo.)
- Please post it. - Hold on. I'm posting it now.
- Okay. - Okay.
- Please. - I posted it.
- So you eat what the comment... - What's the first comment?
Read the first comment.
- What is it? - Please!
- Please! - How can we...
- Where is it? - It's up.
- Please. - Please. But...
a lot of people will comment.
I know.
- I got one. - Okay.
It's oyster.
- Wow! - Yes!
- It's oyster! - Yes!
(They have it too!)
I didn't get that.
- I took it because I had no time. - I forgot it.
- I don't like raw oysters. - Me neither.
- I don't eat it. - I don't eat raw oysters.
Kwang Soo, take the picture and post it online.
- Okay. - It looks very nice.
Can't we take pictures ahead of time?
But different food disappears each time.
That was stupid of me to say.
Gosh.
- Gosh. - I posted it.
What is it? Please!
- Please choose this. - Just give me one.
It is...
What is it?
(Number 10)
- Gosh. - What is it?
- Korean pancakes. - What?
- Bravo! - Okay.
- Korean pancakes? - Yes!
- This counts too, right? - Right.
- Chive pancakes count. - It's delicious.
(Thanks to those comments, they get to eat.)
It's delicious.
Why would you eat Korean pancake?
This. This.
This is bad. I didn't get anything two times in a row.
This is it, right?
- How many do we have to make? - We have to make two lines.
- Two is not going to be easy. - I know.
(Why don't I tease Seok Jin a bit?)
What was that?
(What just happened?)
Something sharp came out.
(Jae Seok teases Seok Jin.)
Hey!
(Even in the new year, it's still fun to tease Seok Jin.)
- Hey... - I was...
I thought you'd change in 2016.
I will post the picture.
- I need to get one. - Please. Please.
I will post it and refresh it.
- What is it? - I will go with this one.
- What is it? - It's this one.
It's inari sushi.
- Oh yes! - No!
(Gary, Ji Hyo and Haha succeed.)
- I forgot to get that. - How did I forget it?
- This is crazy. - I don't have inari sushi.
You didn't bring that?
- But now... - I've had none for three rounds.
- It's going to be tough. - I got it.
Jae Seok, you can say "post it"...
to the phone.
You really think of me as an idiot, don't you?
- Actually... - This is it, right?
- Look at this, and pull it down. - Pull it down.
Read the one at the top. The first comment.
Oh! Here it is.
- What is it? - It's takoyaki.
- Yes! - Which one is it? The round one?
- This is it, right? - Yes.
- Jae Seok, hold it up. - Is this the one?
(Everyone has it...)
(apart from Jong Kook.)
Jong Kook failed four times.
- How is that possible? - What did you even bring?
What do you have?
I already gave up.
Mine are all so spread out.
Eating more of them is not important.
- Their location is more important. - Yes.
I reloaded it. I can choose the one on top, right?
- Yes. - The one on top.
Just choose what you want.
- Salmon sushi. - Yes!
- Wait. Salmon sushi! - This is it, right?
- Isn't this the one? - That's not it.
That's not sushi. That's a roll.
- Hey. - This is it, right?
- I knew it. - I don't eat raw food.
They said you will help me a lot in 2016.
I shouldn't have picked the food I want to eat. Gosh.
Reload it.
(Number 17)
- Oh! - You have it?
- Yes. - What is it?
- Pineapples! - Yes!
- Why would you eat pineapples? - Why would you eat that?
Pineapples.
(Gary and Kwang Soo got it.)
- I didn't see pineapples. - Why would you eat that?
- Why would you eat fruit? - That's for dessert.
(I didn't pick it.)
- I should see it by now. - You eat dessert first?
- I have to stay near. - Pineapples!
- Pineapples. - I am too hungry to eat pineapples.
It's over. I just got to eat one.
One is not enough.
So now they will look at the cards and help me.
Right. Or they could ruin you.
(It depends on the comment.)
- I posted the picture. - Okay.
- Please! - The timing is important.
Be honest.
All right. I reloaded it.
- What's wrong? - Marinated crab.
- Yes! - Yes!
- Marinated crab! - Yes!
- I almost picked that. - Isn't this the one?
- That's not it. - That's not the one.
- That's fried. - That's fried crab.
- I said marinated crab. - This is marinated crab.
It needs sauce.
That's fried crab.
It's too salty without rice.
Don't eat raw food. It's not good for you.
(Bingo status)
(They are so cute!)
(Hello, Gary and Ji Hyo!)
(What's your mission, Seok Jin?)
(Where are you? Are you in the toilet?)
Now put your cellphones down.
- Haha will begin. - Say what you want.
Here we go. Are you ready?
- Yes. - Yes.
- Pizza! - Pizza!
- What did you say? - Pizza.
- Pizza. - Pizza.
- That's it! - Everyone except Jong Kook got it.
Jong Kook, did you eat anything yet?
You all are so different from me.
(I know.)
This pizza is made with squid ink.
Oh? I am sorry, Gary.
(Did someone call me?)
I think this might be popular.
(It's better to choose the one the others don't have.)
Fried eel.
- Yes. - Fried eel!
Counting 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6. I got six.
Grilled squid.
- Let me see that. - I have it.
(I have it.)
(Finally, Jong Kook got to eat something.)
- See? It's Round One, right? - That's it.
- It's your species. - Wait.
Crab meat and sea urchin roe.
It's the one with salmon on top, right?
- Isn't this the one? - Isn't this the right one?
This is it, right?
- Is it this one? - It's this one, right?
Seok Jin, it's not that one.
It's not.
Was there something else other than this?
- It's not that one. - It isn't?
What about this one?
(Clattering)
(Surprised)
- What are you doing? - What's going on?
Hey!
- What's up with you? - What are you doing?
I tripped.
Gosh.
We're eating.
That's so annoying.
What's up with you?
It's not that one.
- Jong Kook, what would you pick? - Pick that one.
- Should I? - Yes, pick that one.
- Something healthy. - I'll pick this one.
Yes, pick something healthy.
Soft tofu.
(Soft tofu)
(We're at a seafood buffet.)
- Why would you eat tofu here? - Seriously.
- I wasn't expecting this. - Oh, here.
I have soft tofu.
Kimchi tofu doesn't count?
Did they have soft tofu on the menu?
Was there soft tofu?
- I'll pick one. - Okay.
Ji Hyo, pick a good one.
- All right. - Please.
Tomato with mozzarella cheese.
- No. - I had almost picked it up.
- Tomato with mozzarella cheese - Tomato with mozzarella cheese
(What's that?)
- Was it really there? - Yes.
Girls love it.
- Gary. - It's Gary's turn.
- Yes. - Go for something expensive.
Let's see.
What about ox feet?
I'd go for tomato sauce spaghetti.
- Yes! - I have it here!
(Gary completed one column.)
Tomato sauce spaghetti.
I'd go for tomato sauce spaghetti.
Yes!
I had almost picked that one up but changed my mind.
- I have tomato sauce spaghetti. - Me, too.
We have completely different tastes.
(Only the four young members had tomato sauce spaghetti.)
Raise your hand when you have two complete lines.
This round, let's go back to the SNS.
It's about time I complete a line.
It's difficult.
Can I mention which one I want?
No, you can't.
- Why not? - No, you can't.
- Why can't I do that? - SNS is all about communication.
Keep your eye on them and check if they mention a number.
(Now, it all depends on the commenters again.)
Which one should I eat?
- I'd like those dumplings. - Which one should I eat?
Ask which one to eat.
(Will the comments be helpful?)
- I'm done. - What number did you get?
(Which one should I eat?)
- It must take some time to load. - Oh, now I got it.
- Please! - Okay!
What number is it?
(Number 1)
- Be honest. - It's mandarins.
- What? - Yes!
- Mandarins! - Is that what the comment says?
- Mandarins! - Yes, it is.
It was in the comment. Look at this.
I had almost picked mandarins up.
They really told me to eat mandarins.
Haha seems to have almost completed a line.
- Gary. - Yes.
I hope I'll get one of these ones.
(Gary almost completed two lines.)
I'll refresh the comments. In 3, 2, 1.
Be honest. Don't pick the one that's good for you.
(Number 7)
Be honest.
Why would anyone pick this one?
- Shouldn't someone check on him? - What did you get?
Someone should watch him.
Why this one?
Come on.
(Number 7)
- What did you get? - Sorry?
- What did you get? - Tofu kimchi.
- Yes! - Yes!
This spot is so random.
- Tofu kimchi it is. - It's obvious...
which one I should pick right now.
Gosh.
Why didn't I bring tofu kimchi?
Someone even picked a number that's already taken.
It's obvious which ones you should pick.
It's about time I complete a line.
- Please. - Let's see!
Okay, I got it.
(Number 22)
Octopus sushi.
Nice!
- I had put it back down. - Octopus sushi.
I was going to take that.
Why didn't I take octopus sushi?
- Jae Seok has eaten so much. - I know.
I ate seven and I still have no complete line.
I ate so much but they were too random.
I just need one more to finish the line.
What if they don't choose this one?
(There is only one left.)
But the commenters are quite mischievous.
They'll know when they see the picture.
(If he gets number 21 this time, the line will be completed.)
- I need just one more. - But...
Wait. It's this one, right?
- Refresh just once. - Okay.
(Number 21)
It's this one.
This one!
It was a smart choice.
It's grapes!
Did they have grapes?
(No grapes)
I have grapes but it doesn't help so much.
(Jong Kook and Jae Seok seem to have similar tastes.)
I'm so lucky.
(Jae Seok completed a line.)
Thank you.
It was going so well but then it stopped.
I should give the commenter something in return.
Thank you so much.
(Take my heart in return.)
(He seems to be getting hooked on SNS.)
- I can't stand it. - What are you talking about?
What did I do wrong?
- I'm getting jealous. - You should slow down.
It was going so well but then it stopped.
This is so slow.
Kids must not like this dish.
I'm worried.
There's no chance they'll pick this one.
(Is that kimchi? Eat kimchi with rice.)
- This is so slow. - I'm already full,
but I haven't completed a line.
(Kwang Soo, you must be full. Stop eating!)
Would there be anyone who completed a line?
Haha seems to have finished a line.
Ready!
- Please. - In 3, 2...
- Please. - In 3, 2, 1.
I'm not playing any tricks.
- What did you get? - Which number?
What are they thinking?
(What are they thinking?)
Hey, don't be rude.
(Jong Kook is scolding the commenter.)
Serves you right!
It serves you right!
Don't think everyone on your page is your fan.
Why would anyone pick this one?
(Why would anyone pick this one?)
What did you get?
I don't understand.
- Egg sushi. - Yes!
Yes!
(We're happy!)
I'm so lucky.
Did they have egg sushi?
They sure did.
My goodness.
Jae Seok is doing so well.
Why are they being mean here?
I have a bad feeling.
What if they don't pick this one?
(It's Ji Hyo's turn.)
Wait.
Ji Hyo, tell us what it is.
Why are they doing this?
I'll eat number 2.
Sorry, number 2 is...
braised pollack.
- What? - What's braised pollack?
- They pick nothing I have. - Braised pollack.
- They have to pick this one. - Oh, it's here.
(If Gary gets number 5, he'll win the game.)
Gary, please.
What did you get?
Wait a second.
- I haven't got it yet. - Gary.
- Gary. - Gary.
I haven't even got the comment yet.
You guys have to pick this one.
Okay.
(Number 5, please.)
(What...)
(did the commenters...)
(choose?)
Number 5!
Kimchi!
(Number 5, kimchi)
Bingo!
Kimchi!
(Gary finished the game first.)
- Are you finished? - Kimchi.
- Are you finished? - Yes.
- I'm not lying. - I do have kimchi.
You see?
Salmon!
- Salmon! - Salmon!
- Okay! - Did they have it?
- Okay, salmon. - Bingo!
Bingo!
(Ji Hyo completed two lines.)
Ji Hyo, really?
- Kwang Soo. - Hey.
You're so bad.
What are you doing?
Are you eating anything?
(What kind of food did you pick?)
(Angry)
Fried rice, bingo!
Fried rice.
(Jae Seok completed two lines.)
(Jae Seok receives two Running Balls.)
Wait.
Kwang Soo almost finished all his food,
- but still doesn't have two lines. - I only need one more.
Why aren't they choosing this one?
For me, they have many options.
I'm going to check the page.
Why no bingo?
Why are they doing this?
Almost all his food is gone.
They're not helping us.
- He's almost there. - What's up with them?
Do they have something against me?
This one is not bad.
This one.
Cold jellyfish salad.
- Okay, bingo! - Bingo!
Bingo!
- Bingo! - Bingo!
Did you finish with cold jellyfish salad, too?
It was the last one for me.
Is this possible?
Cold jellyfish salad was number 5.
(Now, it's time to decide who will be the last one to finish.)
- Okay. - Let's go.
I'll upload the picture.
If I don't get number 25 this time, I'm doomed.
It's been a long time since I needed number 25.
Please.
They can't choose anything else than number 25.
If the commenters know how Kwang Soo is,
they'll not choose number 25.
They shouldn't.
There's no other option. I've been waiting for so long.
I'll refresh it.
- What number is it? - Please.
Please.
(Will he get number 25...)
(this time?)
- What number is it? - Please.
- Please. - Yes!
(It's number 25.)
He got number 25.
I got number 25!
- No way. - He got it.
The next commenter said number 13.
It was close.
The next commenter said...
number 13.
They picked the ox feet in the centre...
so randomly.
It was so close.
Only if you had refreshed it once more.
Oh, it's this one.
(The number of Running Balls depends on the result of the game.)
- It's been a long time. - Oh, this one.
Then is Jong Kook getting no ball at all?
So you all have your Running Balls now.
- Thank you. - Am I getting one ball?
How are we supposed to carry them around?
Do it well.
(I hope you stay on SNS. Nice to be able to talk to you.)
I guess we don't have any guests today?
Are we going by car?
- It seems so. - What's this?
Car number one.
- Car number two. - Are we supposed to choose?
Can we get on whichever car we want to?
You have to ask the commenters which car you should get on.
Really?
Seriously?
It's unbelievable.
What if we all end up in one car?
I'm new to SNS.
This is too much.
Take a picture of both cars.
- Excuse me. - Go back a little.
- Excuse me. - Move back.
(They try to take good pictures.)
- Go this way. - Get out of my way.
What's this?
- Come on. - I should say the colour.
- Do it like before. - That's why.
- Yes. - Let's do it at the same time.
- Okay. - Got it.
- Let's do it. - Not yet.
- Not yet. - In one...
- Hey! - In one, two...
- and three! - Wait.
- I need a question mark. - It's up.
- It's uploaded. - It's done.
For goodness' sake.
- It's up. - Yes.
Is it done?
- Refresh the feed. - How do I do this?
- Like this. - Scroll down.
- Mine's not working. - Scroll it down.
- This is the new post. - You should use SNS...
- more often. - It's not that.
(You're too bothersome.)
- Use this. - Capture this.
- Push this. - No.
- Screen capture comes later. - Look.
- I already did it. - I see.
- I have red. - We'll do it at the same time.
- She says at the same time. - Not yet.
- I did it already. - We'll go again.
- I did it. - Do it at the same time.
- I don't know. - Please listen!
- But how? - Let's do it together.
- In 1, 2, 3. - In 1, 2, 3.
- Okay. - It's done.
- What's the first comment? - Red one.
- Red one. - Red one.
- Red car. - Red car.
The red car is in front. So everyone says red one.
- They're all red. - I have blue.
My comment says "Let's go, Kwang Soo!" so I'll go again.
- Okay. - Do it again.
- I don't know. - I got red.
- I'll go again. - What is it?
I got red.
- This and this. - I have red too.
- Let's pick one. - How many got red?
- Write the names down. - There are six reds.
- There are six. - Yes.
- Only four can get in. - Yes.
- They have to decide. - We'll ask the followers...
- who will ride the blue car. - Kwang Soo can do it.
- I'll upload it. - We have to be in the picture.
- Take a picture. - With us in it.
- That's right. - Just the six people.
Look here.
(Choose wisely.)
I'll take it for you.
- I took it already. - It's okay.
Gary.
- I closed my eyes. - Gary looks really funny.
- Just upload it. - Hey.
- Hey, come on. - I'm sorry.
Oh, poor Gary.
- That's funny. - He looks funny.
- Look at his eyes. - I always take bad pictures.
Doesn't he look funny?
- Okay, I'll check. - Check the comments.
- Refresh the feed. - I'll do it.
- Refresh it. - Don't come too close.
- Be fair. - Okay.
- Be fair. - Why would I be unfair?
- Sometimes you are. - Just show it.
- Show it to everyone. - Show us.
- I refreshed the feed. - Okay.
- I'll do a screen capture. - Okay.
- What does it say? - Oh, no.
- What is it? - It's Gary.
- Is it? - Gary?
Scroll it down one more time.
I'll go one more time.
- Capture it. - Okay, okay.
(Who'll be kicked out of the red car?)
- Nice. - Who is it?
- Who is it? - Jong Kook.
- Yes! - That's great.
(Jong Kook will ride the blue car.)
- You two are a couple. - This team's awesome.
- Wow. - That's what I'm saying.
(Red: Jae Seok, Seok Jin, Kwang Soo, Haha)
(Blue: Jong Kook, Gary, Ji Hyo)
We're leaving.
Here we go.
(Ilsan W Mall)
(They head to the next destination.)
- Let's go. - Okay.
Do I hold on to the phone?
I think so. I think there will be another mission.
We're going the opposite way.
- They already started. - What are they doing?
I think we have to post something again.
What is it?
Take a selfie of yourselves.
Upload it and say, "A passer-by will play a game with us."
"Who should it be?"
"Tell us about their appearance."
- What kind of passer-by? - Jong Kook.
(They will find the person based on the comments.)
In one...
(He looks indifferent.)
(He grins.)
(Pouting)
Tell us with whom...
we should play a game.
Please write a detailed description of their appearance.
Okay, here we go.
(Team Jae Seok takes a selfie.)
(Please go easy on us.)
Okay, in 1, 2, 3.
Please tell us in detail who we should play a game with.
- Good. - I'll upload it.
You need to bring three people.
Someone 12 years younger than me.
This one's easy. Someone 12 years younger than me...
would've been born in 1988.
- A person with a nice body. - Okay.
- A person with a black hat. - Nice body?
- Or someone born in 1988? - Someone wearing blue clothes.
It'll be hard to find someone with blue clothes.
Is it better to find the right person quickly?
- Yes. - Really? We have to find them fast.
Blue clothes will be hard.
We just have to find two people.
- Right. Only two people. - It's easier for us.
A woman with long straight hair and a black coat.
- Just one person? - One person?
A woman who's taller than 170cm and has short hair.
- Someone over 170 cm. - Short hair.
Is anyone taller than 170cm with a short hair?
Is any lady taller than 170cm?
Is any lady taller than 170cm with a short hair?
Black coat.
(Finding the person faster is better for them.)
Is it a black coat?
- Is it a black coat? - Yes.
- It's a grey coat. - A grey coat.
- A black coat. - You have long straight hair?
- Straight hair? - Long hair?
- I'm sorry. - You have long hair, right?
- Long hair! - You have long hair.
- Great. - Come this way.
- Black coat. - Long hair.
Is anyone over 170cm and has short hair?
- Short hair and 170cm. - That's hard.
- Wait. - Are you over 170cm?
- No. - Okay, thanks.
- What do we do? - It's too hard.
- It's too hard. - It's too difficult.
Jae Seok, there was...
a comment telling us to find...
- someone taller than Kwang Soo. - Really?
- No way. - That would be impossible.
A strong person.
I think he looks strong.
- Me? - He's strong.
Jong Kook.
Please come with me.
- He looks strong. - Okay, good.
- Yes. - He was born in 1988.
He was born in 1988.
I'm wearing blue.
Let's see.
- She's wearing blue. - Show them.
- Yes. - It's too cold.
She's wearing bright blue.
- I found her! - You did?
- He found her! - Good!
- She's 170cm! - How did you find her?
- Really? - Where?
- How did you find her? - Really?
- Here. - She's 171cm.
Are you over 170cm?
That's great.
- Hello. - Come this way.
- You'll play a game with us. - Yes.
- It's a Tongue Twister game. - Okay.
Within a given time, everyone has to read the sentence out loud.
- Okay. - If anyone makes a mistake,
you need to start over as a team.
- Okay. - You have one minute.
Okay. Please pick one...
out of these two.
- Please pick one. - Yes, here.
- This one. - Okay.
We'll take this one.
Then we get this one.
(He drops it.)
Hey.
- What was that for? - Why did you do that?
- That's mean. - Hey.
(He's being mean.)
- You're a bully. - What's wrong with you?
- Why did you do that? - You're a bully.
(They get in a fight.)
Come here please.
Jong Kook. Do you want to go third?
- Shall I? - Let's shuffle.
Okay. Gary.
- You should go first. - Me?
- Gary is a good rapper. - He should go first.
- That doesn't matter. - Yes, you go first.
You're good at speaking.
- I am? - Right.
It's too cold. I don't know if I can move my lips quickly.
- We're ready. - You have one minute.
- Ready. - Ready.
(You need to be fast and...)
Set.
(articulate to win this game.)
Go!
Are the pea pods in the field open or not?
Does it matter if they're open? Whether they're open...
Whether they're open...
(Startled)
- What? - What's wrong?
He said it wrong.
Go again.
Are the pea pods in the field open or not?
Does it matter if they're open?
Whether they're open or not, they're all pea pods.
(Okay.)
Are the pea pods in the field open or not?
Does it matter if they're open?
Whether they're open or not, they're all pea pods.
Are the pea pods in the field open or not?
Does it matter if they're open?
Whether they're open or not,
- they're all pea pods. - Good!
Are the pea pods in the field open or not?
- Go slowly. - Does it matter if they're open?
Whether they're open or not, they're all pea pods.
- They're all good. - Are the pea pods in the field...
- open or not? - They're good.
- Good. - Does it matter if they're...
open?
- She's calm. - Whether they're open or not,
- they're all pea pods. - Good.
- Good. - Are the pea pods in the field...
open or not? Does it matter if they've opened?
- If they've opened? - Oh, no!
(Back to the first person!)
- Hey! - Come on.
- Song Ji Hyo! - Come on.
- Switch with me. - No.
I'll start.
Are the pea pods in the field open or not?
Does it matter if they're open?
Whether they're open or not, they're all pea pods.
They're all pea pods.
(Time's up.)
(I'm sorry.)
It's our turn.
- It's our turn. - We can do it.
- Do it slowly. - We can do it.
- Slowly. - Let's do it.
- Read it slowly. - We can make it.
- Do it slowly. - No need to hurry.
- Go slowly. - Jae Seok, go first.
- Okay. - Do it slowly.
- Okay. - He'll go last.
- We have one minute. - Go last.
Let's do it!
- Let's go! - Use all the time.
- Okay. - No need to hurry.
- Don't make mistakes. - Okay.
Ready.
(What kind of a tongue-twister will they get?)
- Start. - Go slowly.
- Wow. - This is hard.
(A very difficult one.)
Our village people like all kinds of pea soup.
- My family likes black pea soup. - Wow.
But others don't like the soup we like.
- Good! - Our village people like...
all kinds of pea soup. My family likes brack pea soup.
Brack pea soup.
(Wrong!)
- Again! - Do it again!
- That's hard. - Wow.
- My family likes black pea soup. - Go again.
My family likes black pea soup.
- Go again! - Our village people...
like all kinds of pea soup.
My family likes black pea soup.
But others don't like the soup that we like.
- Good job! - They picked a good one.
Our village people like all kinds of pea soup.
My family likes black pea soup.
But others don't like the soup that we like.
- There you go. - There you go.
Our village people...
like all kinds of pea soup.
My family likes brack pea soup. Brack pea soup.
(She made a mistake.)
- How did she get that wrong? - What?
- Brack pea soup. - She said "brack".
- It's because of her braces. - What?
- It's because of her braces. - Blame her braces.
- She said "brack". - It's because of her braces.
That's just how she speaks.
Our village people like all kinds...
of pea soup. My family likes...
- black pea soup. But others... - He said it right.
But others don't like the soup that we like.
Our village people like all kinds of pea soup.
My family...
likes black pea soup. But others...
don't like the soup that we like.
Wow. She's good at this.
My village people like all...
kinds of pea soup. My family...
(She's got a nice rhythm.)
likes brack pea soup. Brack pea soup.
- Brack pea soup? - She did it again.
- What is this? - Why are you doing this?
Why is this wrong?
- What is this? - It's her accent.
- Black pea soup. - No, I just...
- What's wrong with you? - She has an accent.
- She can't... - She has an accent.
- No, she... - She's from Daegu.
- She can't... - Are you against accents?
Are you?
- Come on. - She has braces.
- Rules are rules. - She has an accent.
- She has to say black. - She's an exception.
- Say, black. - Black.
- I got it. - Black.
- Black. - Black, not "brack".
(They spent all their time complaining.)
- She can't do it. - We were almost there.
All right. Let's do this.
- Get ready. - Let's practise before we do it.
Start!
Are the pea pods in the field open or not?
Does it matter if they're open?
(He's blocking his sight.)
Does it matter if they're...
- He's cheating. - What are you doing?
- What is he doing? - He didn't mean to do that.
Get out of the way.
Are the pea pods in the field open or not?
Does it matter if they're open? Whether they're open or not,
- Whether they're open or not... - Oh, my.
(They're blocking his sight again.)
They're all pea pods.
Are the pea pods in the field open or not?
Does it matter if they're open?
Whether they're open or not, they're all pea pods.
Are the pea pods in the field open or not?
Does it matter if they're open?
Whether they're open or not, they're all pea pods.
Are the pea pods in the field open or not?
Does it matter if they're open?
Whether they're open or not, they're all pea pods.
- We're in trouble. - There you go.
Are the pea pods in the field open or not?
- Does it matter if they're open? - Does it matter if they're open?
Whether they're open or not, they're all pea pods.
Are the pea pods in the field open or not?
Does it matter if they're open?
Whether they're open or not, they're all pea pods.
- You did it! - Yes.
(They succeeded.)
- We did it. - We did it.
- We did it. - Yes, we're done.
This is going nicely.
We just have to speed up.
- We can still win. - We just have to speed up.
- We just have to speed up. - They were so fast.
- We can still win. - Should we rearrange the order?
- Let's do this. - We have to...
- From the top. - It's black, not "brack".
- We can do this. - Hey, we're counting on you.
- Let's win this thing! - We can do it!
Get ready.
(They only have one shot at this.)
- We just... - We have to speed up.
(Can Team Jae Seok beat Team Jong Kook?)
Get ready. Start!
Our village people...
like all kinds of pea soup.
Like all kinds of pea soup.
Our family likes...
(This is the hard part.)
- It's black. - Please say black.
Don't get it wrong.
(Will she be able to avoid making a mistake?)
Our village people like all kinds of pea soup.
My family likes black pea soup.
My family likes black pea soup. But others...
don't like the soup that we like.
Our village people...
like all kinds of pea soup.
My family likes black pea soup.
But others don't like the soup that we like.
Our village people...
like all kinds of pea soup.
My family likes black pea soup.
But others don't like the soup that we like.
Our village people...
like all kinds of pea soup.
My family likes black pea soup.
But others don't like the soup that we like.
Our village people...
like all kinds of pea soup.
My family likes black pea soup.
But others don't like the soup that we like.
Our village people...
like all kinds of pea soup.
My family likes black pea soup.
But others don't like the soup that we like.
- We did it. - Yes.
- Did we win? - We don't know yet.
- It's okay, we won. - It's all right.
- Did we win? - We still beat them.
- We won. - Good job, everybody.
- They were fast. - Good job.
- We were fast enough. - Good job.
- Good job. This was a close one. - We don't know yet.
- We don't know yet. - This is going to be a close call.
- No, it's not. - This is a close one.
The winners will get three Running Balls.
The losers will get just one Running Ball.
The team with Jong Kook, Gary and Ji Hyo...
came in at...
(What's their record?)
46.86 seconds.
- Wow. We did well. - 46.86 seconds.
- And Team Jae Seok... - I don't know...
(Team Jae Seok's score will be revealed.)
(Who will receive three Running Balls?)
They came in at 50.25 seconds.
(Team Jae Seok is disappointed.)
(Team Jong Kook wins.)
- All right. - Thank you.
(Jong Kook, Gary and Ji Hyo all receive three Running Balls.)
- Thank you. - Thank you very much.
- Thank you so much. - You did a good job.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
(They're the best team. I will cheer you on.)
(At a cafe in Janghang-dong)
You guys are all here, right?
Before the final mission, we'll give you a mini mission.
- Really? - Yes.
This game will also utilise comments.
Oh really? This should be fun.
- This is the Comment Speed Quiz. - Wow.
- Wow. - Wow.
- This is so strange. - Wow.
But all my followers just goof around.
My followers don't know much like me.
You will provide your followers with the quiz questions.
In this can, there are seven different adages.
After you pick one out, you will film a video that explains it.
The winners of this game will be decided based on...
whoever gets the right answer first in the comments.
If I win again, I will be legendary.
How am I supposed to win when my followers goof around?
I can't win because of you guys.
- My followers are... - Then let's ask them...
who should go first.
- Let's take a picture. - That sounds good.
- Okay, let's take a picture. - No, you're...
addicted to SNS.
- He's addicted. - It's all he can think about.
- Let's take the picture here. - I realised that...
I know my way around SNS.
- Over here. - I'm so good at it.
- Move back. - Come over here.
- Let's all get in the photo. - Gary and Ji Hyo.
- All right. - Then...
who should go first?
- Please choose the order. - Choose the order.
Let's go.
- It's not turned off. - Here we go.
- Refresh the page. - I posted it.
- There we go. - Seok Jin.
- Seok Jin. - Seok Jin.
- You're first. - Refresh the page.
- We already did. Next is Kwang Soo. - Do it properly.
- What? - Next is Gary.
- The third is Gary. - Then, it's Jae Seok.
- The fifth is Ji Hyo. - Now we will take your phones away.
I need my phone because...
I'm addicted to SNS.
- I can't live without it. - Just come on in...
to the world of SNS.
You should use it more. I'll be your follower.
- What an honour. - But I have to take pictures.
I don't like getting my photo taken.
(But he's been...)
(taking selfies all day long.)
You only have 10 seconds to explain with your body.
You can't make sounds.
(What is his adage?)
- What is it? - Is it hard?
- Guess what it is. - You have 10 seconds.
- That's why... - You can't make any noise.
Ready. Start.
(He's panting.)
(What on earth is this?)
(What's up with his gesture?)
- I get it. - I figured it out.
This one is easy.
- We're in trouble. - This is very easy.
- This one was... - He did a really good job.
- Did you figure it out? - I think Seok Jin was...
putting dung over his body.
He was trying to be the dung-stained dog?
- Is it "He who smelt it, dealt it"? - He really tried...
Is this hard to figure out?
"The dung-stained dog reproaches the chaff-stained dog."
- That's correct. - Now the followers have to get it.
But because this was a hard question...
(Now they post the video.)
(How long will it take for them to figure it out?)
(Please get it right.)
(Next up is Kwang Soo.)
I think Seok Jin's adage was the easiest one.
Kwang Soo may not know what the adage even means.
- This one is hard. - Really?
At least you're a good actor.
- Go on, do it. - This is impossible.
(Kwang Soo practises.)
- Are you a dog? - He's a dog.
It's a rat.
(They can't figure it out.)
- "Every rat has his bright day." - That's correct!
- That's right. - This one is easy.
You have 10 seconds. Get ready.
- He's doing a good job. - Just do what you just did.
- Just do what you just did. - Get set.
(He tries his best to describe it.)
The time...
Time's up.
- Stop. - Wait.
He didn't get to describe the last part, "bright day".
It ended with the rat.
- How can you end it with the rat? - How can you...
- How can you stop there? - But the rat part was tough.
It was really tough to describe.
You couldn't describe "bright day".
It was hard to describe a rat.
- Next up is Gary. - Gary.
By the way,
the ones who followed me today...
- Wait. - We will guess it.
It looks easy, but it's going to be tough.
- Is that right? - What is it?
It would have been easier with an animal.
Show us.
- Should I try it? - Give it a try.
(He pretends to cut his throat.)
- Squid walking on a tightrope. - Enemies...
"Enemies always meet on a tightrope."
- You got it. - That was really easy.
Why would you bring up squid there?
It wasn't about squids?
Goodness.
What kind of an adage is that?
- Tightrope-walking squid. - Tightrope-walking squid.
Is this how squid walks on a tightrope?
Tightrope-walking squid!
Here we go.
(They will record a video for 10 seconds.)
Ready. Go.
(He's determined to defeat his enemy.)
(He's good at expressing the tightrope.)
That was perfect.
- Good job. - That was perfect.
People will know it.
- It's perfect. - It's perfect..
Gary is so good.
- I'm next, right? - Jae Seok.
I'm next.
(Jae Seok is up next.)
Please open the envelope.
(Which adage did he pick?)
It's easy but tricky.
- We will try to guess it. - Gosh.
Just give it a try.
- It didn't start yet, right? - No, it didn't.
(Watch carefully.)
Watch me.
Start.
A cat.
- A cat. - It's a cat.
"The silent cat goes on top of the stove first."
That's it!
(Seok Jin got it.)
This is the only adage you can think of.
- Right. - Yes!
- I did it! - There's...
- I did it. - You did it.
- That was easy. - What else could it be?
I'm jealous.
Start.
(Acting like a cat)
(Jumping)
Jumping, jumping
It might not be easy.
They might say, "Hard times are soon forgotten."
I am sure someone will mention "Tom and Jerry".
Someone's going to mention Seolhyun for sure.
- AOA. - AOA.
Someone will mention AOA.
But that's not it.
I couldn't meow.
(The fifth player is Ji Hyo.)
What's this? I haven't...
What is it, Ji Hyo?
- I will give it a try. - Okay.
(Here and here.)
Okay.
(Dancing)
- Grasshopper. - One man sows and...
"One man sows and..."
"another man reaps."
No, the owner reaps?
"Don't order others to do things at their own party."
- What? - She's going to lose!
It looked nothing like that.
I will bet everything I have.
- She's bad. - She's going to lose.
- This is too difficult. - I will bet my life.
Ji Hyo, you are ruined.
This is too difficult for me.
Ready.
Start.
This is a difficult adage.
(She's describing other people.)
You have 10 seconds. Hurry up.
(She describes the party.)
(She tries her best.)
What's that?
- Okay. - This is too difficult.
- You're officially the loser. - Hey.
I won't be the loser for sure.
I will beat at least one person.
- I'm relieved. - I just have to be a bit better.
Just a little bit.
(Will the followers of Ji Hyo surprise them with a twist?)
Haha.
Is it something difficult?
Watch me and guess it.
(He looks around.)
(Oh!)
Watch out before you lie down.
That's it.
Yes.
That was a good one.
I described it well, didn't I?
- It was really good. - He described it well.
- That's a very kind description. - I'm going to lose!
Hold your legs and stretch your knees.
- Gosh. - The Great Mountain, they say...
Nothing is more difficult than what Ji Hyo got.
Ji Hyo's was the toughest one.
Ji Hyo, yours was really difficult.
(Good clothes give you wings.)
- It's a tough one, isn't it? - Is it difficult?
- Is he the new loser? - Is it hard?
I think you can guess it really fast.
Is that right?
- Hold on. - Jong Kook is good at this.
Why are you taking off your clothes?
- Here we go. - Okay.
(This)
A pervert.
(These are my wings.)
- I don't know what it is. - "You're inside me"?
That was funny.
A duck-down parka?
(A duck-down parka?)
(They keep giving wrong answers.)
- Go on. - That's all.
So you don't know it. People will get it right for sure.
Ready. Go.
(He's fluttering his wings.)
(Oh!)
I get it.
He should've lifted the outer layer.
(Please post your answers.)
(The seven videos have been uploaded.)
(Which one of them will get the right answer first?)
We have the result.
I just hope I will be one of the top three.
- Please. - Please.
- I will announce the third place. - The third.
- Being third is okay. - I want to be third.
- I want to be third. - The third is good.
- How many balls does he get? - How many balls?
- He gets 2 balls. - You get 2 balls?
- Two balls. - I won't get greedy.
Two balls are enough.
The right answer was on the 15th comment.
- That was fast. - There were faster ones.
(Winning the third place is safe.)
(Which one will receive two extra Running Balls?)
It's Gary.
(Gary wins the third place.)
Okay.
I thought he would lose.
Third place is good.
- I thought he'd win. - I get two balls.
- Enemies... - I get two balls.
Yes.
He will also get two Running Balls.
The fourth place will also get two Running Balls.
- The fourth is all right. - I just want to be fourth.
- Please. - Being fourth is good enough.
The 18th comment had...
- the right answer. - It's me.
- Who is it? - It's Haha.
(Haha wins the fourth place.)
(Watch out before you lie down.)
Two balls are enough.
- This is crazy. - I know.
I will announce the fifth place.
- Does he get 1 ball? - Only 1 ball?
The fifth and sixth get one ball each.
The 30th comment had the right answer.
(The 30th comment had the right answer.)
It's Kwang Soo.
What was Kwang Soo's answer?
- "Every rat has his bright day." - "Every rat has his bright day."
That's about the only saying with a rat.
(Is it "The pot calls the kettle black"?)
He gets two balls?
- Jae Seok's was really easy. - I get one.
Was mine hard?
- No, it was easy. - It was easy.
- Jae Seok's was easy. - He'll be in second place.
Don't worry. I'm the loser.
- The sixth place. - It's me.
It's me.
It's Jae Seok.
Am I the second one?
(The 34th comment had the right answer.)
Yes!
Yes! What was yours?
"The silent cat goes on top of the stove first."
- Is that right? - I can't believe it.
Was it hard?
Now it's time to announce the winner and runner-up.
I'm nervous.
For the winner, the 13th comment had the answer.
For the runner-up, the 14th comment had the answer.
- That was close. - I will announce the winner.
The 13th comment had the answer for the winner.
It was the 14th comment for the runner-up.
I'm out of luck this year.
(Will it be Seok Jin?)
"Good clothes give you wings."
(Or will it be Jong Kook whose adage was easy?)
(Whose follower got the right answer first?)
It's Seok Jin.
- He's the winner? - Yes.
He used up all his luck here?
(He used up all his luck here?)
Only bad things will happen to him now.
I don't want to spend my luck here.
- I'd rather not. - You won.
I'm the winner.
He used up all his luck here.
The 13th comment had the answer.
- Poor Seok Jin. - "The dung-stained dog..."
"reproaches the chaff-stained dog."
Seok Jin tried hard to describe it well.
He probably got...
He didn't get many comments.
For the last one, 167th comment had the answer.
Someone actually got the answer?
We should give that person a gift.
Thank you.
- Thank you. - Give him a gift.
Reply to his comment.
He deserves to get a gift.
He really deserves a gift.
Let's move on to the next mission.
Let's go!
Give me the phone. I want to check my SNS.
(Give me the phone. I want to check my SNS.)
Give me back my phone.
Don't do it.
- I'm addicted. - We get to take our phone?
They are waiting for me.
They are waiting for my news.
- They're waiting for me. - You're addicted.
They're waiting for me.
I have to get online fast.
(They are so cute.)
(Good job, Seok Jin!)
(He's so funny!)
(I want to put him in my pocket.)
(SBS station in Tanhyeon)
We will probably be using our phones again.
- What will be the punishment? - What's this?
- This is the last mission. - Yes.
This is going to be an individual race.
It's Targeted Name Tag Ripping Game.
(Targeted Name Tag Ripping Game?)
(They've played it numerous times.)
(They are professionals.)
(But today's game is different.)
(It's going to be SNS Targeted Name Tag Ripping Game.)
(It starts right now.)
(Targeted Name Tag Ripping Game?)
What's that?
This is crazy.
So the followers must pick the target.
On your SNS,
you will ask which person's name tag you should rip.
You can rip the name tag of the first person that comes up.
It will be me.
(He might be the public enemy.)
That's not true.
(I know how it's going to be.)
- It's luck. - Yes.
The last one standing will...
will receive 10 Running Balls.
(The final survivor will receive 10 Running Balls.)
The second to last survivor will receive six.
The next one five, and so on.
The first one to be eliminated will receive only one.
They get one at least?
Yes.
There is a new rule.
Five Running Balls...
can be exchanged with one name tag.
(Five Running Balls can be exchanged with one name tag.)
My goodness!
Can we exchange them whenever? Or do we have to do it now?
- Now? - You can exchange them only once...
before we start.
- It's worth investing in. - So that's it.
So everything depends on the commenters.
They'll decide whose name tag we should go for.
(Their target will be selected by the comments.)
I'm in trouble.
What should I do?
I don't have that many Running Balls.
Since the commenters must be fans of Running Man,
there's a good chance that they'll choose me as the target.
My goal is to be included in the last four to survive...
and have more than 10 Running Balls.
That's my goal.
Today,
I don't expect to be the winner.
I just want to avoid the punishment.
(They just want to avoid the punishment.)
Who will be my target?
I'm sure a lot of them will choose me as the target.
I'll be a better person in 2016.
I didn't know we would play a game like this.
I know I've been bad.
I apologise.
Please give me a chance.
I'm so afraid.
They'll definitely aim at me. I'm the race starter.
They'll definitely choose me.
I'm sure I'll be the target of at least one of the six.
- Now. - Yes.
Post, "Targeted Name Tag Ripping Game."
"Whose name tag should I rip?"
What if I get Jong Kook?
Can't I add more details?
No, you can't.
Everyone should write the same thing.
"Targeted Name Tag Ripping Game."
"Whose name tag should I rip?"
(Sighing)
I should look determined.
(Determined)
(He can't stop sighing.)
Please don't say Jong Kook.
Please.
(Smiling)
(Looking innocent)
I tried to look weak.
(Will his strategy work?)
(Posing for the photo)
(Focusing on her selfie)
What are you doing?
Please understand me. Selfies are important to girls.
I'm so bad at it.
(Targeted Name Tag Ripping Game. Whose name tag should I rip?)
(Whoever the commenter picks will be my target.)
Whose name tag should I rip?
(He even bends his knees.)
Please be nice.
I'll upload it.
(I'll upload it.)
Do you think it'll work?
(Please have mercy on me.)
(It's time to check who their target is.)
I'm worried.
(Time to read the comment)
(Who will be Jae Seok's target?)
Please.
(Goodness)
(Jae Seok's target is Haha.)
Haha is no easy target.
Oh, I got it.
It's Gary.
Why does it have to be him? This is crazy.
Why does it have to be him?
(It's Haha's rival, Gary!)
It's motivating me.
I got it.
- Who did you get? - Seok Jin.
(Gary's target is Seok Jin.)
Jong Kook is right under.
Really?
(Gary barely avoided Jong Kook.)
It could've been so much worse.
Oh, I got Gary.
It's Gary.
What should I do?
(Ji Hyo's target is the betrayer, Kwang Soo.)
It's Kwang Soo.
(Ji Hyo's target is Kwang Soo.)
Let's see.
(Who will be...)
(Jong Kook's target?)
It's Kwang Soo.
I'm sure Kwang Soo's target is me.
(Will his target really be Jong Kook?)
Please. I'm desperate.
I only have three Running Balls. I have nowhere to turn.
Oh.
It's Haha.
What should I do?
(Who will win the Targeted Name Tag Ripping Game?)
(Targets summary)
I should watch out for Jong Kook.
Jong Kook's target is likely to be Kwang Soo.
(I'm rooting for you, Jae Seok!)
Where's Kwang Soo?
(I'm sure Jong Kook will win.)
(Don't rip Jae Seok's name tag.)
(Jong Kook is on his way!)
Jong Kook, Seok Jin, Haha.
Jong Kook, Haha.
Where's Kwang Soo?
Where is he?
(Jong Kook is getting close.)
Turn off the light.
He must be there.
He should be there.
(Nervous)
He's looking for someone.
He's searching everywhere for someone.
(Kwang Soo, he's looking for you.)
I'm scared of him.
How could I rip Gary's name tag?
Gary is, in my opinion,
the second or third best one among us.
He's the second or third most popular one.
- Gary. - Yes.
- Who did you get? - What about you?
- Kwang Soo. - Kwang Soo?
I got Seok Jin.
I'm telling the truth. I can even turn my back on you.
I had a feeling that your target could be me.
Your name came up, but Kwang Soo's was first.
I think Jong Kook got either me or Kwang Soo.
I actually don't think his target is me.
Because they probably thought I was no match for him.
Ji Hyo might have advantage in this game.
No one chose Ji Hyo as my target.
- No one would choose her. - I couldn't see her name.
- You go first. - It's a bit narrow here.
(They won't show their back to the other.)
You go first.
Fine.
(Extremely careful)
This is crazy.
We should watch our back.
We should watch out for Kwang Soo.
- We should watch out for him. - Oh, it's Ji Hyo.
Who did you get?
Oh, my gosh.
I got Seok Jin.
(My target, Seok Jin,)
(is right there.)
(Oh, it's Gary.)
How could I rip Gary's name tag?
(There you are.)
Who did you get?
- Did you get... - Did you, by any chance...
Is it us or not?
- It's not you, I mean it. - My target is Kwang Soo.
- Kwang Soo? - What about you?
I got the same.
- We both got Kwang Soo. - Really?
- Seriously? - Yes.
Then none of us are aiming at any of us?
- No. - Then...
- I mean it. - We should help each other.
When there's Jong Kook around, we should help each other.
- Let's team up. - Let's do this.
So we're safe here.
- Trust us. - Okay, I got it.
Kwang Soo.
Hey.
(Jong Kook finally found Kwang Soo.)
Tell me who your target is.
Who's your target?
- Is it me? - No.
- Be honest. - I mean it.
- I can even show you. - Tell me the truth. In 3, 2, 1.
- It's Haha. I can show you. - You're being suspicious.
- I mean it. - Tell me the truth. Show me.
(Nobody trusts me any more.)
Give it to me.
- Is this it? - Yes.
Your target is not me, is it?
(Your target is not me, is it?)
(My target?)
(Do you want to know?)
I got Kwang Soo.
(It's you.)
Kwang Soo's target must be me.
(My answer is...)
Of course it's not you.
My target is Jae Seok. I mean it.
(Doubting)
So many chose me as your target.
And you're telling me your target is not me?
You're spending so much time here.
I couldn't possibly be your target.
Of course not. Why would I be doing this otherwise?
I was thinking that if your target is not me,
we should cooperate.
- Sure. - Right?
- Who's your target again? - It's Haha.
(Answering without hesitation)
You see?
(Jong Kook is finished checking.)
- Then what should we do? - Did you check every comment?
Of course.
You're unbelievable.
(Jong Kook checked thousands of comments.)
Let's do it like this.
You rip Haha's name tag first.
Is that an easy thing?
Sure. And you help me with ripping Jae Seok's name tag.
I got it.
Let's do that.
You fully trust me, right?
Put your hand on my name tag.
(What?)
(I can put my hand on your name tag?)
(How lucky am I.)
Okay.
(Jong Kook, we're now allied, right?)
(Ripping)
(He ripped it off!)
(He ripped the name tag.)
Lee Kwang Soo is eliminated.
(What just happened?)
My target was you.
(A slap in the face)
(He got me.)
My target was you. I didn't want to struggle.
That's why I did this.
(Kwang Soo, I'm sorry.)
(What should I do with you?)
- Kwang Soo. - How can you do this?
You're not worth my time.
Kwang Soo,
- I really tried. - Okay.
Please, understand.
- I had no choice. - I...
I'll get the punishment today.
(Kwang Soo is the first one out.)
(Jong Kook sets a new target.)
(Who would be the next target?)
Kwang Soo is gone. Gary?
(His next target is Gary.)
I think Gary will be...
(Jong Kook is after Gary now.)
- Let's get one person. - I think...
- We have to get one. - There's no end.
- There's no end to this. - If we go on like this...
- There's no end. - He's right.
(We can't keep dragging the game like this.)
(My target, Haha is...)
(right in front of my eyes.)
(This is the perfect chance!)
(He makes a move.)
(What?)
(He rips the name tag.)
(A sudden attack)
Was it Haha?
(I'm sorry.)
It was Haha?
(Haha lost his words.)
- Look at that! - It was Haha.
- I knew it. - Sorry.
- I knew this would happen. - You can't trust anyone.
- They're all enemies. - Hey.
- It was Haha. - Thanks.
I'm sorry, Haha.
A lot of people wanted you as my target.
(That was scary.)
I'm glad it wasn't me.
I can't trust anyone now.
(The second person out is Haha.)
What a perfect timing.
(Jae Seok gets one Running Ball.)
(He has to set the next target.)
I feel sorry for Haha.
(He feels sorry for Haha...)
(but soon takes a selfie.)
(He smiles.)
I'll put Seok Jin's name.
Seok Jin.
I don't want Jong Kook.
(Oh, no!)
(It's really Seok Jin.)
Thank goodness. The next comment said Jong Kook.
(He almost got Jong Kook.)
That was close.
That's why I put down Seok Jin first.
(Jae Seok's next target is Seok Jin.)
We have the sixth and seventh places, right?
- Seok Jin. - I don't trust you.
- Seok Jin. - I'll trust Gary.
- I'd rather trust Gary. - Is Gary your target?
Is Gary really your target?
(Is Gary really your target?)
- Go get him quickly. - Will you catch him?
- Okay. - Please.
- You want to join me? - Gary can't know about this.
It has to be Gary.
- Really? - You can't catch him alone.
I'd rather go for Gary than you.
I don't trust him.
I can't trust anyone.
Because Jong Kook got Kwang Soo,
his next target could be me.
You're lying.
I saw what you did to Haha.
(Look who's lying.)
(Gary showed his back.)
(Will Seok Jin get Gary's name tag?)
(No!)
What are you doing?
(They fail to catch Gary.)
- You're both after me? - No.
(It's too late for Gary.)
Gary. Gary.
(Oh, no!)
(Gary fails to grab Seok Jin's name tag.)
- Gary. - Gary.
- Hey. - Hey.
(He rips it.)
(Seok Jin rips Gary's name tag.)
- No! - I'm sorry.
Gary.
- I should have ripped his. - Gary.
I'm sorry. I had no choice.
Kwang Soo. I'm sorry, Gary.
What are you?
(Kwang Soo the Grim Reaper)
- Sorry, Gary. - I knew it.
I'm sorry. Please understand.
(Seok Jin sets a new target.)
It's Ji Hyo.
First comment says Ji Hyo.
(Seok Jin's next target is Ji Hyo.)
Gary is eliminated. Gary is eliminated.
I need to change my target.
(Gary was Jong Kook's next target.)
Who will it be?
People are getting their name tags ripped off fast.
I didn't expect that.
I didn't expect that to happen.
(Only Jae Seok, Ji Hyo and Seok Jin are left.)
Oh my goodness.
(Ji Hyo is his next target.)
It's Ji Hyo. What will do I?
It's Ji Hyo.
(Why does it have to be Ji Hyo?)
Ji Hyo is the hardest target.
(Jong Kook is weak against pretty women.)
- Hey. - Think this through.
Is Jong Kook your target?
(Is Jong Kook your target?)
I think your...
next target is me.
You have to think carefully.
I don't care which side you choose. I stand neutral.
- Who's your target? - Jong Kook.
- You can't take him out alone. - You're right.
- Help me. - That's right.
- So help me. - To be honest,
- whoever it is... - Ji Hyo, think about it.
- Think about what? - If you help me take Seok Jin out,
- you can win the third place. - Right.
- Yes. - It's better to get more people.
- Your target is me. - It's not...
- important. - Your target is me.
(Seok Jin attacks first.)
(They reach for the name tags at the same time.)
(He rips it.)
(Seok Jin is out.)
I knew what you were trying to do.
(Jae Seok gets another Running Ball.)
Who is out? Is it Seok Jin?
Did Jae Seok get him?
Then I wasn't his target.
It was my chance to get Ji Hyo.
- You should've told me. - It's not...
easy to get Jae Seok...
- or Jong Kook. - No.
(Jae Seok takes a victorious selfie.)
(The only targets left are Jong Kook and Ji Hyo.)
I think it's up.
It's Jong Kook.
I was expecting it.
I have to be ready for this.
Let's go downstairs.
Let's go.
(Jong Kook hides first.)
- Jae Seok. - Listen.
Listen carefully.
- Your target is Jong Kook, right? - Yes.
It doesn't matter if it's me.
- My target is Jong Kook. - I've decided.
- You can't catch Jong Kook. - Right.
It's hard for the both of us. So it'll have to be me.
- You rip Jong Kook's tag. - Okay.
- Got it? - Okay.
If your target is me,
take me out gently.
You're really not my target.
Ji Hyo, do it gently.
- Okay? - You really aren't my target.
(Jae Seok is ready to sacrifice himself.)
- Think carefully. - Really.
We should stick together.
(Jae Seok and Ji Hyo are allies.)
(On the other side...)
I knew this would happen.
Good thing I bought a name tag.
(Good thing I bought a name tag.)
(A name tag?)
With every five Running Balls,
you can buy a name tag.
(Seok Jin looks happy.)
I won't buy it.
It's not about having another name tag.
I like to invest.
When an opportunity comes along,
I invest. So I'll buy it.
- I'll take one. - Here you go.
(He buys a name tag with five Running Balls.)
Put it on please.
(Will he win the game...)
(with this new name tag?)
Do they know that I'm back in the game?
Nobody knows? That's awesome.
Jae Seok's target could be me.
His new target is Jong Kook.
He was assigned a new target.
(But...)
(look who it is!)
(Seok Jin is so unlucky.)
- He bought a name tag. - What?
He bought a name tag.
(They are shocked.)
He bought a name tag?
(That was unexpected.)
Who knew?
What do we do?
If he's back in the game, I'm still his target.
(Ji Hyo is Seok Jin's target.)
I wasn't expecting this.
(I need a new strategy.)
They saw me. Goodness.
Hide. Don't go that way.
(Seok Jin came this way.)
You're standing in a place like this.
Are you after Ji Hyo again?
- Wait. - There's something I want to say.
Let's get Jong Kook first.
- Okay. - You're nobody's target.
So you have to grab Jong Kook.
Okay, I'll help you.
I know what you're saying.
Ji Hyo, trust me.
I'll come with you.
Okay. You're not my target anyway.
- Right. - You're not my target either.
(I was listening to you talk.)
They're together over there.
(If they are all after me,)
(I should hide.)
How will we get him?
He might pop up all of a sudden.
He's difficult to get.
(Where is Jong Kook hiding?)
Let's look at the security cameras.
- There he is. - Where?
- Can we take a look? - Sure.
He's right here.
Excuse us.
What floor is this?
The third floor? Okay. Thank you.
- Did you see him? - I saw him on a security camera.
(They go to the third floor.)
(They are nervous.)
I will lead. Okay?
(It's Jong Kook!)
(Seok Jin bravely runs towards Jong Kook.)
(Jae Seok and Ji Hyo follow him.)
(Jong Kook is attacked.)
(You surprised me!)
(Jong Kook attacks Ji Hyo, his target.)
Ji Hyo.
(Protect Ji Hyo!)
(Just as they planned, Jae Seok and Seok Jin grab Jong Kook.)
(Ji Hyo needs to rip his name tag off now.)
Rip his name tag.
(Now Ji Hyo can rip his name tag.)
(They all fall.)
(Jong Kook grabs Ji Hyo.)
(Will Ji Hyo be out like this?)
(Jae Seok rips Jong Kook's name tag!)
I ripped it first.
(Jong Kook's name tag is removed.)
You had Jong Kook.
(Exhausted)
Darn it.
- We got him. - He's so strong.
- Are you all right? - I am okay.
Are you okay?
That was crazy.
- It took three of us. - I almost got him.
Gosh.
He was like a tiger.
I couldn't do it because it was Ji Hyo.
I would've fought back if it was a guy.
He couldn't fight because his target was a woman.
Don't forget my sacrifice.
I won't forget it.
- You know it, right? - I know it well.
(Next time, let's fight man-to-man.)
Kim Jong Kook is eliminated.
(Jae Seok has to get a new target.)
In the end,
I have to win.
(He makes a pitiful face and takes a selfie.)
(Between Ji Hyo and Seok Jin, who should I get?)
(I'm really tired.)
There you go.
(Jae Seok's next target is Ji Hyo.)
(Between Seok Jin and Jae Seok, who should I get?)
(Ji Hyo gets another target.)
(Ji Hyo's next target is Seok Jin.)
(Now Jae Seok, Seok Jin and Ji Hyo remain.)
You really fought hard. Really.
Who's your target?
- Is it me? - No.
- I feel bad. - Why?
Seok Jin helped me, and now he's my target.
I feel so sorry.
What do we do?
(He's worried.)
- Your target is Seok Jin too? - Yes.
You're lying.
(You can't fool me.)
I am sorry.
(It's you.)
(What do we do?)
I am sorry.
It was for...
a short while,
but we became really close...
while trying to catch the tiger.
(At that time,)
(Seok Jin attacks.)
Oh gosh!
I have no other way to go.
Hold on. Ji Hyo.
- Hey! - Jae Seok!
(Ripping)
(Jae Seok successfully rips Ji Hyo's name tag.)
I am sorry, Ji Hyo.
(Jae Seok earns one more Running Ball.)
Ji Hyo.
What did I do?
I am sorry, Ji Hyo.
I can't believe it's down to two of us. Let's end it.
I never knew I would face you like this.
Now that I got this far,
- I really want to win. - I know you do.
I think it would be nice...
to begin the new year...
as the winner.
Let's grab each other's arm.
(They grab each other.)
Gosh!
(They rotate.)
(They are standing even!)
I...
- Let go. - I want this.
I want this.
(If he wins, he will get10 Running Balls.)
- Wait. - I heard a crack.
It's all right. Come on.
(Jae Seok grabs Seok Jin's name tag.)
(And Seok Jin grabs it simultaneously.)
(Ripping)
(Jae Seok rips Seok Jin's name tag first.)
Darn it!
- No! - I did it.
This is crazy.
I won.
(Jae Seok earns 10 extra Running Balls.)
(Jae Seok ends up with 18 Running Balls.)
What? No way.
What?
How can this be?
- We are supposed to choose one? - It's been five years.
What's this?
What is it?
- We have to wear it. - It's the punishment?
- It's intense. - I will tell you the punishment.
- How can we... - It's a costume?
- It's a costume? - It's Gary's!
We are supposed to go somewhere in these?
This is the punishment.
- One person... - This is better.
who doesn't get anything...
will walk to the nearest subway station.
- No! - That's too much.
One person?
These are okay to wear.
This one is the problem.
- How can someone wear this? - How can we...
Your manager will be waiting for you at the station.
You can walk there and take the car back here.
- Not in a million years. - No way.
- So one person... - Gosh.
- is going to be safe. - It's lighter than toilet paper.
(The Running Ball draw will determine who will wear what.)
Here we go.
Please!
It's been such a long time.
(Their Running Balls are inside the machine.)
I beg you. Please!
- Please! - Please!
Please. Please...
The first winner is...
Please.
I would be so happy.
(The ball came out.)
- I would be so happy. - Is it out?
- Is it out? - Is it out?
- It's out. - It's out? Who is it?
- The first winner is... - Please!
- Please. - Just this once.
- It's me. - Who is it?
(Who will be the first one to avoid the punishment?)
(Jae Seok is the first winner.)
Jae Seok!
(It's Jae Seok.)
The start of this year is good.
It's because you got rid of all the bad luck.
That's the power of having 18 Running Balls.
That punishment I got last year...
was really worth it.
(He's benefitting from last week's.)
I've never been lucky like this before.
- First time in six years. - It's the first time!
- Don't look. - I won't.
- I will just face the front. - Please.
This is the second winner.
- Please. - I've never been so desperate.
- I've never been so nervous. - Is the ball out?
Please.
- Is the ball out? - Did it come out?
- It's out. - It's supposed to be a lucky year.
I'm supposed to be lucky this year.
Who's the second winner?
He doesn't look happy.
This is a miracle. It's Haha.
(It's Haha.)
(Haha, who only had six balls, won.)
(No way.)
(This is a miracle.)
(They get more nervous.)
- This is crazy. - I will donate it!
(He doesn't know what he's talking about.)
(He shouts loudly.)
Thank you!
We will choose the next winner. Please face the front.
- I will... - This doesn't make sense.
- I will keep this forever. - Come here.
Leave Haha and come here.
Please!
- Please! - The third winner is...
I can't wear this.
Don't worry, Jong Kook.
It doesn't make sense.
It's all mixed.
There's 95 percent chance.
Thank you so much.
- Thank you so much. - It's Ji Hyo.
(Ji Hyo is the third winner.)
(She's always lucky.)
Really? Wow!
I thought I was going to wear that.
Scream!
It's not me!
- Scream! - It's okay as long as it's not me!
It's okay as long as it's not me!
I will pick the fourth one.
It's going to be me this time.
It has to be me this time.
(Who will be the fourth winner?)
This is crazy.
We have the ball.
- It's out? - It's out.
Don't say it's Kwang Soo.
It's Seok Jin.
(Seok Jin is the fourth winner.)
I get to keep my pride at least.
(Bye, costumes!)
(Now Jong Kook, Kwang Soo and Gary remain.)
Now,
- when there's only one... - In the past,
I wore them with confidence.
Two singers and...
- and one actor remain. - Why do I hate it so much now?
Two singers and one actor.
All right.
(Who will be the fifth winner?)
Please come this way.
- Is it out? - Yes.
Is there a special reason...
why you shouldn't wear one of these costumes?
Honestly, there's no particular reason.
- How about you, Jong Kook? - Why do I not want to wear it?
It's because I'd rather look hideous than funny.
- How about you? - I think it's going to be...
funnier if one of these two wears it.
- Today... - You are right, Gary!
(Gary is the fifth winner!)
(He's saved at last.)
(Now Jong Kook and Kwang Soo remain.)
- It's my lucky year! - Hey,
who are you to me?
(Who are you to me?)
(Last week,)
(Jong Kook and Kwang Soo were chosen as the best partners.)
(As if they are proving it,)
(they won the "X-Man" special together.)
(However,)
(why are they like this now?)
Please. Please. I am going to...
- be a good man in 2016. - Seriously.
If it's going to be really funny,
- Kwang Soo should do it. - It's out.
It's out.
Now I don't even know the result.
I didn't look at it yet. All right.
I didn't look at it yet.
- This new year... - Kwang Soo has a higher chance.
That's not true.
- He has better luck. - On the episode of 2016.
(Only one person will be saved.)
Who will it be between them?
In 1, 2, 3.
(Who will be the last winner...)
(to avoid the punishment?)
Go.
Kim Jong Kook.
(Kwang Soo is the one who will receive the punishment.)
This is crazy.
(While Jong Kook is happy,)
(Kwang Soo is in despair.)
I'm so happy.
Will this be decided by the first comment, too?
Yes.
It says, "The monkey costume".
It's the monkey costume.
They were supposed to answer with a number.
Why are they not doing as instructed?
(Taking it out on the commenter)
What's the username?
- It's the monkey costume. - It's the year of the monkey.
- That's right. - It's the year of the monkey.
So you have to wear this costume...
and walk from your home to the closest subway station.
Once again,
today,
for Running Man,
so many people...
participated and cheered for us on SNS.
We appreciate it.
- Thank you so much. - Thank you.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
(Thank you for participating in Running Man.)
As I said earlier,
unlike the other members,
Ji Hyo and I don't have our personal SNS pages.
Our pages were on for just today.
- I'd like to prevent any abuse. - It could happen.
- So let us make it clear. - Okay.
Ji Hyo and I are never going to have SNS pages.
The pages used for today...
- will be... - Deactivated.
- deactivated. - Yes.
Anyway, Kwang Soo will receive his punishment.
See you next week.
Please be with us this year, too.
- Happy New Year! - Happy New Year!
(Happy New Year, everyone!)
What should I do?
- My phone is off. - Three, two, one.
Come closer.
(The next day)
You're all insane.
(Kwang Soo is here.)
This is crazy.
It's freezing.
You have to walk to Geumho Station.
I'm going crazy.
What am I doing? People are going to work.
I can't do this.
I'm rarely this afraid.
(In the middle of a rush hour traffic jam,)
(a bunch of monkeys showed up.)
(Is that a human being or a monkey?)
Oh, hello.
(It's for the show.)
(I'm a normal person.)
I didn't know the station was this far.
Oh, I'm here.
Hello.
Good morning.
Happy New Year.
Because it's the year of the monkey,
I'm wearing a monkey costume.
Do you want one?
- I want one. - Sorry?
- I want one. - Oh, sure.
I want one, too.
Oh, hello.
Oh, ma'am.
Ma'am, you don't have to.
(A lady puts her scarf around Kwang Soo.)
Thank you so much.
Here you are.
I want a pink one.
- A pink one? - I want a pink one, too.
- Thank you. - You're welcome.
(The ladies left one by one.)
What just happened?
Why did I end up like this?
Thank you.
(He's wearing the scarf the lady gave him.)
This is so warm.
- Hi. - Hello.
I'm shaking.
While I was shaking in the cold, you've been sitting in here.
I thought it was a sauna.
Thank you for coming to pick me up.
Happy New Year.
Thank you. Happy New Year.
(Kwang Soo completed his mission.)
I'm freezing.
I can buy anything.
Send me 270 million dollars right now.
(A game secretly suggested to them)
The game of the heirs?
I'll be your hostess today. My name is Lim Ji Yeon.
Are we playing hopscotch?
I got it!
You should stay in Ji Hyo's land.
What am I doing?
Did you just step on my land?
(Win the game to win the land.)
It's driving me crazy.
What's that?
(The heirs bet everything on the games.)
(Things are going out of control.)
(There's something special about this house.)
I win!
(Next week on Running Man, The Hopscotch)