Previously on Running Man.
I'll choose this since it's been a while.
(I, James Bond, have been waiting for this moment.)
(Operation: Scene-stealer)
(Steal a shoe from the members.)
(Target 1: Lee Kwang Soo)
(Deceive the members completely and steal a shoe from them.)
How should I take it?
(Operation: Tracing Kwang Soo's foot)
Please let me do it.
Is it so difficult to put your foot on this?
(Footprint is just an excuse.)
(Stealing your shoe is my real goal.)
Hold on.
Catch him.
He's a thief.
What's this?
(First mission: Stealing Kwang Soo's shoe was a piece of cake.)
(Target 2: Song Ji Hyo)
(Operation: Secretly, greatly)
(While they are spacing out...)
(And from the weakest...)
(He successfully obtained members' shoes.)
(However,)
(Jae Seok's identity is released to the members one by one.)
(And he faces the strongest enemy.)
(Kim Jong Kook)
I'm on the run now.
(The members are chasing after him.)
Hey, Sleepy.
(Avoiding the members, he needs to steal Jong Kook's shoe.)
I have to do my mission as Scene-stealer.
(How would he manage to go through this crisis?)
It said we should watch out for the Scene-stealer.
Why?
Hence the name, Scene-stealer. Are you supposed to do something?
Not really. I'm supposed to...
take 10 percent of your time on the video.
- It'll be mine. - 10 percent?
Then you should work out with us.
(What?)
(He's now forced to work out.)
- Come on. - No, I don't want to...
- You must work out. - No, I can't work out.
I've come to the wrong place.
Really. Jong Kook.
- Let's go. - Let's go.
- You can do this. - Just follow me.
You don't need anything to work out.
- All right. Can I use the restroom? - No.
- I really need to go. - No way.
- Stop lying. - It's an emergency.
- Come on. Don't do this. - I'll be right back.
Just let me use the restroom.
- Now, let's do some squats. - Let me use the restroom.
- Let's start with squats. - I need to use the restroom.
- I'll be right back. - Move your hips backwards.
- Your hips... - That hurts.
Goodness. I nearly wet my pants.
- That was really close. - I told you to pull your hips.
I'm now...
- Come on. - I really need to use the restroom.
- I really need to go. - Are you sure?
- Yes, I'll be back. - I think you're trying to run away.
He's acting strange.
What's he up to? What is the Scene-stealer?
(Jong Kook is very suspicious of him.)
What should I do now?
It was just as I thought.
(He's thinking of a strategy.)
Oh, dear. If so...
What should I do? I can't stay here for long.
I don't think he can take up 10 percent of our time.
(He's acting strange.)
It's 10 percent of 3 minutes.
Ji Sun, come here.
(Ji Sun, come this way.)
(Jae Seok approaches Jong Kook's stylist.)
Ji Sun.
(Me?)
- Please help me for once. - How?
Can you change Jong Kook's shoes?
Why?
Don't tell anyone.
I need to steal a shoe from him.
(Please help me.)
I'll be outside. Tell him that I left.
- You know what I mean. - Okay.
Please bring his shoe outside and give him any reason.
- All right. - You can do this for me, right?
Please.
(Secretly, obsequiously)
If he only needs 18 seconds, I think we can make it happen.
- I give up. - What?
- I give up. - Why?
- I'm leaving. - Why? Where are you going?
- Where are you going? - See you later.
He's strange.
What's so strange? Can't I leave?
Our mission is easy. He's really weird.
I think he's up to something.
- It's very suspicious. - I know.
- Even you think he's weird, right? - Right.
It's all up to Ji Sun.
(Ji Sun, today's mission is all up to you.)
(Ji Sun initiated the operation.)
Can I go? Can I go home, now?
(Everybody is busy after the mission.)
- Can I go home, now? - Yes, you can.
- I'm leaving. - Good job, Sleepy.
- You were impressive today. - All right.
- Bye. - Thanks for your hard work.
(Ji Sun is on the move.)
(Let's change your shoes.)
Why?
(Will she successfully finish her special mission?)
(Jae Seok is waiting anxiously.)
Goodness.
This is nerve-racking.
(Will he manage to steal Jong Kook's shoe?)
(Goodness)
(It's a success.)
I'll buy you a nice dinner. Thank you, Ji Sun.
Ji Sun, how did you manage to do it?
I told him he needs to wear another pair of shoes.
Ji Sun, I'll buy you a nice dinner. Thank you so much.
Thank you, Ji Sun.
I think I'm in trouble.
Stay away from him for a while.
Tell your boss and...
go somewhere else.
Ji Sun, dinner is on me.
Thank you, Ji Sun.
(A perfect strategy gave him a victory.)
Goodness. What a great success.
I knew it. There must be something.
What?
(Catch James Bond, the Scene-stealer)
"Catch James Bond, the Scene-stealer."
"Eliminate James Bond who steals your shoe and your number of views."
My shoes?
(The shoes that he carelessly took off for his stylist.)
(You mean that was...)
How can he steal my shoe like that?
He should at least take it in person.
Did he do that to other members, too?
There must be a reason. What was your reason?
Come here.
(Ji Sun, come here.)
You must have your own reason. Come here.
What was your reason?
What was that?
Tell me your reason.
(Are you a spy?)
He was begging for help.
Do you help everyone who begs you?
I didn't know what he was up to.
How can you do this to me? You're unbelievable.
This is impossible.
I'm going to get him.
(Angry Jong Kook starts to chase Jae Seok.)
Let's go. Now that you've all worked out,
- I feel good. - let's show them the results.
(Jong Kook)
(Jae Seok)
(Jae Seok is escaping from Jong Kook.)
(Haha)
Sinsa-dong, 667. Goodness, this is driving me nuts.
(The chasers are after Jae Seok.)
He moved to another location.
Jong Kook must have lost his shoe, then.
Now,
let's go to Gary.
(Jae Seok is on his way to meet Gary.)
I'll just ask for his shoe.
I want to make it out of the voices of our members.
- Really? - Yes.
Can you just say, "Run"?
- You have to help me later. - Of course I will.
(It's my time to ask for a favour.)
He might just give it to me if I ask.
(He's on his way to steal.)
(Meanwhile, Kwang Soo is working on "Finding Ms Right".)
(He's calling the third applicant.)
- Hello? - Hello, Sun Bin.
(Sun Bin?)
- Yes, hello. - Hi, I'm Lee Kwang Soo.
(Rising star Lee Sun Bin)
You don't exactly know what this is about, do you?
They wouldn't go into details.
Right.
This is awkward for me to say it myself,
but I'm meeting the people that mentioned...
that I'm their ideal type for short dates.
- I see. - Is there a date idea...
you've been wanting to do?
Well, maybe the arcade?
- The arcade? - Or maybe the ball park?
- A ball park. - I like being active.
- I see, you like being active. - Yes.
Things that I saved to do later with my boyfriend.
(I've been saving it for you.)
- The arcade... - I see.
Okay, then. We'll try to go to the arcade or the ball field.
- Okay. - I'll be over soon.
- See you soon. - Bye.
Things like "See you soon"...
really drive you nuts.
You know.
(He's already way ahead of himself.)
I'm already so happy.
(Although he only has one shoe on,)
(his mind is completely ready for the date.)
It must be here.
(His exciting date starts now.)
Hello, Sun Bin.
Hello.
(Embarrassed)
Nice to meet you.
Hello.
Baseball? Is this a baseball place?
- Your shoe... - Yes.
I should have bought a new pair. They took away my shoe.
- Really? - Yes. There must be something more.
- Should we go up first? - Yes, here...
I was going to buy something on my way, but...
- It's not necessary. - there was so much traffic.
First...
(Glancing)
(She's in love.)
Such an experience is so hard to come by.
- I never imagined this. - Right.
It's so hot.
My face turned red, right?
What kind of men do you like?
You.
My...
Like that...
(He came to me.)
Have you done a date like this?
No.
- Is it your first? - Yes.
I haven't, so I wanted to try it.
Then let's...
- Should we try it? - Okay.
- There's something I want to ask. - Okay.
How many people did you call before me?
(Did you call other girls before me?)
Sit for a second.
- Is that important to you? - Yes.
It's important.
Let me just say one thing.
- There were several categories... - Okay.
I could choose from today, and I chose this category.
I picked it for you.
I mean it.
So how many were there?
I saw...
- You're the third person to meet. - Pardon?
- Is that important? - Yes.
You must have done a lot of things.
What is this?
(Song Ji Eun's initials are on his nail.)
- What is this? - Hold on, hold on.
SJE. Who is SJE?
(What is this?)
(Just say that it's Seok Jin.)
Should we increase the volume?
(We're in Gary's studio.)
(Jae Seok is here for his next target.)
- Jae Seok. - Gary.
Hey.
You promised to help me with my mission.
What is your mission?
With Gary, it's best to just say what my mission is...
and ask him for it. That would be faster.
(Will the strategy work on Gary?)
- I'll be honest with you. - Okay.
You and I need to exchange something.
- That way I'll clear the mission. - Exchange what?
Shoe or something.
How many did you get so far?
Right now,
- I've done three. - I need to think about this.
I helped you before.
You're so close to succeeding.
There's nothing bad in it for you.
It's just a matter of me succeeding or not.
(Thinking)
- Then Jae Seok... - Just switch shoes with me.
- Shoes? - Yes. Is your size 270mm?
- Yes. Are you the same? - Yes, my size is 270mm as well.
Please switch them with me. I'm so tired. I'm not joking.
(Hold on, Jae Seok.)
Let's switch just one shoe for style.
(I have to keep my style.)
Left or right?
- Whichever one you want. - Then the right shoe.
The right shoe.
It fits perfectly. It looks pretty good.
- We're such a good match. - You're right, it fits perfectly.
See? I'll get going.
Are you leaving already?
I already did my mission. I have to go somewhere else.
- Okay. - Thank you.
- I helped you. - Okay.
- Thank you for keeping the promise. - No problem.
You kept your promise.
- I'm helping you so you won't fail. - Okay, I'm going.
(After finishing his mission, James Bond leaves the room.)
He came and left like the wind.
I'm out of it.
(His fashion style improved.)
Gary and I are exactly the same size.
Gary brought it up first.
He thought that switching both might be weird.
All I needed was one shoe.
(He's so clueless.)
(You just lost 10 percent of your final rating to the Scene-stealer.)
(He's figuring it out now.)
(Sighing)
What is this?
(He only has to get Haha's shoes.)
Haha is the problem.
What should I do?
I should think carefully about it.
This is driving me crazy.
Where am I supposed to go?
(His mission will be complete with Haha's shoe.)
We just exited the highway.
- Where are we now? - Let's see.
(The chase is on.)
(Jae Seok)
I wonder where he's hiding.
(He came to Han River to lure Haha in.)
He's at Han River.
It's Han River.
(He succeeds in luring Haha,)
They're all coming this way.
(but now everyone is coming towards him.)
All of them.
(What will be the Scene-stealer's fate?)
Hit it. Hit it a little more.
(They're having a very active date.)
This...
Am I doing it right?
It's over.
(I'll do it if you like it.)
(She can hardly breathe.)
I'm confident about this one. Hold on.
(He hits 30 points.)
(Did you see that, Sun Bin?)
Is this how you do it?
- Really? - Loosen up the shoulders.
(I'll teach you.)
Loosen up your shoulders.
Bring your arm out. Bring it out.
(He's getting close to her.)
- Look. - Here?
Make sure your view is straight. Align this and this.
(She looks good.)
I'll shoot.
Yes.
(She shoots 50 points.)
(Whatever she shoots,)
This is crazy.
(she gets it on the bullseye.)
- Am I doing well? - You didn't miss any, right?
- Pardon? No. - You didn't miss any, right?
- You're so good. - Look at this.
(You're really good.)
Gosh.
(She's getting them all.)
- Do you come here often? - Did I do too well?
Tell me.
You came here last week, didn't you? Who did you come with?
(After their sweet date,)
(it's finally time for the truth.)
I'll ask you the question.
Lee Kwang Soo is really my ideal type.
(I really like Lee Kwang Soo.)
Yes.
(Is she telling us the truth?)
This is actually...
This...
(Liar warning)
(She's clenching her teeth.)
Pardon? Nothing happened.
(It's a misunderstanding.)
Let's go again. Can we do it one more time?
(Again?)
(Do you want me to feel the pain again?)
- You need to press it faster. - Are you nervous?
- Pardon? No? - Let's see.
(Nervous)
My...
ideal type...
is Lee Kwang Soo.
Yes.
It hasn't been that many days.
- It couldn't have changed. - Of course not.
You even said so on television.
(It's impossible.)
(It's possible.)
What?
I'm being honest.
(What's wrong with this machine?)
Enough with the lying detector.
Are you sure you're not using a remote control?
- This is upsetting. - How did you stand that?
I tried to stand the pain, but it really hurts.
(Sun Bin, does your hand hurt?)
- It hurts. I'm being honest. - Thank you.
Thank you so much.
(Kwang Soo fails his mission.)
(Meanwhile, Jae Seok is waiting with his trap.)
Over there. I see cameras.
(Haha has arrived.)
(It's Haha.)
Good.
(He's starting to hide.)
(Jae Seok has to be here somewhere.)
(He's waiting for his opportunity.)
(Steal Haha's shoe and his mission is complete.)
Let's go.
Let's hurry. Run, run, run.
- I've never done this before. - You see...
Everyone's really fast.
- As runners? - Yes.
They're fast. Aren't you?
I used to run track and field.
- Really? - I can run.
You can't just run after them.
You must ambush them.
Didn't I look cool saying that?
- I just realised that. - I can tell.
I'm telling you things about...
- what you don't know. - Exactly.
- I think I feel so sexy. - Okay.
Don't you agree?
(Trust me.)
- I get it. - So...
(Meanwhile, by the river)
- What? - Is Jae Seok not here?
(They search for Jae Seok.)
We haven't found him yet.
Where is he?
Where is he hiding?
I'll show you what I can do.
(James Bond's target is Haha's shoe.)
(An ambush is the only way to go.)
(Haha approaches Jae Seok's trap.)
(Haha, is that you?)
(Come on, just a little bit closer.)
What are you doing there?
Wait a moment.
- Open up. - What's going on?
What's going on? Why is it you?
What's this?
(No! It's Ji Hyo.)
(He opened the door expecting Haha.)
What are you doing there?
Wait a moment.
- Open up. - What's going on?
Why is it you?
No! No!
No!
We got you.
(Ji Hyo captured James Bond.)
I don't believe this.
(Ji Hyo takes the views Jae Seok stole.)
(Jae Seok loses 50 percent of his views.)
Hang on.
What was all that about? I lost my will to work now.
After all you put us through?
That was nothing.
It wasn't nothing. It was raining.
- Okay, fine. I'm sorry. - Darn it.
- My shoes are soaked. - You were working out.
What if he comes first even with minus half the views?
(It's down to the viewers.)
The winner of today's mission is Ji Hyo.
- She ripped my name tag. - You eliminated Jae Seok.
- I thought everyone had left. - Jae Seok stole...
10 percent of everyone's views but they all go to Ji Hyo.
She'll win then.
- She'll win. - She'll win.
That alone was fun.
We'll count the views for 24 hours.
Those results will affect...
the following race.
- I see. - I have a disadvantage.
I lost 50 percent. I'll come last.
You should've done better, then.
You got to play the lead. You should've done better.
- I did. I got your stylist to help. - What did you do?
Stop complaining.
- Please watch our videos. - Please do.
(What are the results of today's super hot mission?)
(30 minutes later)
(Here's the couple we'd forgotten about.)
(It can't be...)
Seriously?
Did they all leave?
Did they go home?
How can you film the ending without me?
This is so annoying.
Okay, so...
I had no idea this would happen.
- We decided to start dating. - What?
(Oh, my goodness.)
Dear viewers.
We'll announce our wedding plans next week.
Everything about our love story...
(Check it out in their 3-minute video.)
It's all in our video.
Thank you.
(Kwang Soo and his maybe-girlfriend finally complete their video.)
(Kwang Soo is my ideal type.)
(We counted the views logged at 8am the following day.)
(View ratings)
(One week later)
Okay, so...
I'll announce the standings of the number of views.
- It was so hot. - Already?
We know who came first and last.
The one with the most views is Kim Jong Kook.
Kim Jong Kook.
Hey.
Did you contact your fans?
- Did you? - I did not.
Ji Hyo, you got 10 percent of his views and he still won?
What's going on?
- Jong Kook's too... - Thank you.
I think I should run for office.
I don't believe this.
I should run for some online office.
Anyang Constituency.
He always bosses people around.
- He will if he runs for office. - He's bossy wherever he goes.
I'll run for some online office.
Coming in second...
- Haha. - Really?
- You owe it to Got7. - He did nothing.
Coming in third is Ji Hyo.
- Fourth is Gary. - What would've happened...
if you didn't take my 10 percent?
Poor Ji Hyo.
- Kwang Soo came fifth. - Kwang Soo?
- Wasn't that the hottest clip? - I was so curious.
I wanted to watch his.
Kwang Soo actually likes them all.
(He had an ulterior motive.)
- What do you mean? - What will you do?
- Is it Ji Eun or Sun Bin? - Who is it?
I'll explain everything in our chat room.
- It's Sun Bin. - Oh, please.
And then...
in sixth place...
is Jae Seok who lost half his views.
- What? - Seok Jin's last?
Excuse me?
- Seriously? - Are you kidding me?
People really must not care about you at all.
- Are you serious? - They don't care.
- I thought I'd come last. - Seok Jin came last.
He lost half.
I lost half my views.
Focus on your radio show.
Get the listeners to support you.
I just don't get it.
I told you a week ago that...
this ranking would affect today's game.
Today's final race is called...
"Running Man Go".
- You have 200 minutes. - 200 minutes?
- You'll be chased... - 200 minutes?
by 102 hunters.
You'll be chased by 102 hunters.
102 hunters?
(I can barely evade 1 person and they're sending 102?)
(24 hours ago)
(All over SBS)
(Lee Wan, actor)
(It's a poster recruiting hunters!)
"Hunters"?
"Running Man will appear all over Yeouido."
Is this that?
A marathon?
Do they evolve each time they're caught?
(Growing horns)
Will we get to chase the Running Man members?
In real life?
- I want in. - We have to apply.
Can we be on Running Man?
- Can we take part? - Yes.
Can I apply?
You should apply.
Only you can go after Jong Kook.
- Hands up if you want in. - Me.
(Running Man Go)
(Running Man Go starts.)
(Yeouido Hangang Park)
(D-day has arrived.)
(The 102 hunters gathered in Yeouido.)
Thank you.
Here you go.
(Idol singers, actors and comedians all applied to take part.)
Let's show them us eating.
- We have to eat. - I'll explain what to do.
Press it once.
You can film with others, too.
(They film themselves.)
Hello.
Hello, everyone.
I hope Chang Ryul and Jong Kook don't fight.
According to the ranking, Jong Kook gets seven hunters.
Haha gets nine.
(9 Haha Hunters)
11 Ji Hyo Hunters.
13 Gary Hunters.
(13 Gary Hunters)
15 Kwang Soo Hunters.
(15 Kwang Soo Hunters)
20 Jae Seok Hunters.
(20 Jae Seok Hunters)
Seok Jin will be chased by 27 hunters.
(27 Seok Jin Hunters)
(7 versus 102. Running Man members, be very careful!)
You got 27.
- They'll come after me? - I got 20.
- Just 2 people can get me. - I got 25.
- It can't be 25. - If...
the hunters take all three of your name tags off, you're out.
You have to find the Blackmon.
The person with the Blackmon at the very end wins.
- We have to search for him. - Yes.
Whenever we meet someone, we have...
- to run away. - Just run.
(Where's the Blackmon that has to evade the members?)
I'm ready.
My laces are tight.
(Blackmon Cho Jae Hyun)
(He's a charismatic and captivating actor.)
(Blackmon Chae Soo Bin)
(She's a great actress as she is pretty.)
Your goal is to evade the members...
for the duration of 200 minutes.
As the Blackmon, you two...
will be given a special role.
One of you will wear a "zero dollars" tag.
The other will wear a "10-dollar" tag.
If the one with the 10-dollar tag gets away without being caught,
you will win.
(If the Blackmon with zero dollars is caught, the Blackmons win.)
(The Blackmons take the prize.)
So whoever of us it is,
the one with the 10-dollar tag...
- should stay safe. - Correct.
I get it now. Do you think you can evade them?
- You have to run. - I'm not confident.
It shows on my face when I lie.
(Which of the Blackmons has the 10-dollar tag?)
Whenever we meet someone, we have...
- to run away. - Just run.
- Yes. - Just one meeting...
Idols these days...
My clothing colour is too flashy.
I need to hide.
- This sounds tough. - Okay.
The rules of the game are in the pouches...
you were given.
Please follow the rules.
- Are there rules? - Yes.
We should eliminate the name tags of those who chase after us.
If I had Blackmons...
- That would be so... - What is that?
(Wait, what is that?)
(Are they the hunters?)
- Has it begun? - Already?
- Gosh. - It has started?
I didn't even know.
(The hunters have already begun the chase.)
What is going on?
- Has it begun? - Already?
- Gosh. - It has started?
(Has it begun already?)
- Already? - Gosh, has it begun?
How can this start all of a sudden?
(Let's run for now.)
- Where should we go? - You can't start like this.
- Gosh. - Who are those in red shirts?
Let's just run quickly.
(Jong Kook, wait for me!)
You can't start like this!
Let's go.
They're following me. Let's run.
(102 monsters are after the members.)
Who are those in red shirts?
(Target spotted.)
- Go get him! - How far can we run away?
Tell me how far I can run away!
(He's running at full speed.)
He's so fast.
Do we have a car we can use?
- Hurry! - Hurry!
Hurry!
Hurry up!
What's going on? There's no camera man.
(Jae Seok evades 20 hunters.)
Hey.
Who are those in red t-shirts?
Why are they chasing after me?
My goodness.
- I got you. - Hello.
Gosh, how many of you are chasing after me?
(There's only 7 of us because you ranked top before.)
- Hello. - Hello.
You two...
Gosh, wait. What are you doing?
- All of our members... - Wait, Kwang Soo!
- Kwang Soo! - Jong Kook.
(Kwang Soo betrays Jong Kook again.)
Step back.
(They remove one of Jong Kook's name tags.)
- Congratulations. - Jong Kook!
Congratulations.
(This isn't time...)
(to congratulate others.)
Gosh.
Get away from me.
Where were you guys hiding?
(They tear his name tag.)
(One of Kwang Soo's name tags is removed.)
I could manage to escape.
It happened all of a sudden.
(Ji Hyo Hunter finds Ji Hyo.)
(The monster catches her.)
(He rips her name tag.)
(Ji Hyo loses one name tag.)
I got it.
You did very well.
Gosh.
Why are you so fast?
How can you guys be so healthy?
Stop it.
(Gary's name tag is eliminated.)
Gosh.
(The monsters are much faster than the members.)
- Did you get it? - Yes.
Okay.
(What about Haha?)
Hold on.
Wait a second.
- What's going on? - Hello.
Please hold on.
Wait.
I said wait. Please.
What's going on here?
I got it!
You got me too easily. This isn't fun.
Then sing a song.
(Trot singer Ma A Sung eliminated Haha once.)
- Wait. - What's all this?
(Running Man members are helpless.)
- We... - You should've gone that way.
It's impossible to survive for 200 minutes.
Haha.
- This is ridiculous. - Did they remove your name tag?
- They removed my name tag. - What?
- What about you? - I haven't lost any.
- Gosh. - Did you lose only one name tag?
They have no mercy.
They don't even care that it's an entertaining show.
Of course, they have no mercy.
They're just chasing after their targets.
Jae Seok is here!
(Haha shouts out loud.)
(Haha informs others about Jae Seok's whereabouts.)
Haha. My goodness.
I'm so angry now.
Goodness.
Hello.
- Are you looking for Jong Kook? - No.
- Then who? - Kwang Soo.
- Sorry? - I'm looking for Kwang Soo.
Kwang Soo? You must go that way.
No, that way.
- He went that way. - Thank you.
- Don't tell anyone that you saw me. - Okay.
Hey, you should go that way.
(What's important is that I survive.)
I see a lot of monsters there.
They're waiting for me.
They're coming towards me.
Goodness.
Guys. Guys.
Go get him!
- Hello, I am Yoon Dong of Halo. - Guys.
- Hello, I am Yoon Dong of Halo. - Hello.
- Hello. - Ji Ho.
- You guys are... - Hello, Jae Seok.
- Hold on. - We got you.
- We're sorry. - Take my name tag.
Just remove it.
- Gosh. - In 1, 2, 3.
- My goodness. - Hello.
- I'm Yoon Dong of Halo. - Hello, Yoon Dong.
- Hello. - Yoon Hwa.
- By the way, - Yes?
Yoon Hwa went to a convenience store, is it okay?
It's okay. Were you thirsty?
(Meanwhile, Seok Jin goes to the same convenience store.)
How can the round start all of a sudden?
(Hunters find Seok Jin right away.)
This is so weird.
Hey, can we talk later?
Good. Introduce yourself.
- You're a member of 24K, right? - I am.
I really like you, Jin Heung.
Let's get out of here first.
No.
Wait there.
Excuse me, Ma'am.
I'm sorry.
(Bewildered)
Seok Jin.
There are many monsters out there, right?
Gosh.
- Hello. - What's going on?
- He's here. - Gary...
(Gary Hunters inform other hunters that Seok Jin is here.)
(Let's go, Purplemons!)
Hey.
- You guys. - Wow!
You guys are 24K, right?
We'll give you a chance to run away.
- We will... - We'll step back for a while.
You mean 30 seconds? You should wait 30 seconds then.
- Okay. - We'll give you 30 seconds.
Way to go, 24K!
- Let's go for it! - Let's go for it!
- Ready, start! - Ready, start!
Run!
(Seok Jin runs as fast as he can.)
(We'll give you 30 seconds to run away.)
It's a long time, isn't it?
(Seok Jin...)
Wait!
(is hiding in an underground passage.)
I had 30 seconds.
(Jae Seok has 2 name tags left.)
Gosh.
(He runs away again.)
(He's running all day long thanks to 20 Jae Seok Hunters.)
Hey.
This isn't the time for...
You guys can't do this to me.
There are more.
You know, this isn't a party or something.
- You're really fast. - Listen to me, guys.
(I must distract them.)
Lift the camera.
What are you doing? We must take photos.
Make sure you're inside the frame. Lift up your face.
Turn the camera this way. Let's take a photo.
That's it.
(He tries to distract his monsters.)
Good. Let's take it.
Let me take a photo with Halo.
Let's take it with Halo.
(Everyone takes a photo with Jae Seok.)
Good. Come here, "People Looking for Laughter" members.
- "People Looking for Laughter". - Come over here.
(Jae Seok Hunters almost forgot what their mission was.)
My goodness.
We need two more...
Bring two more monsters.
There is Haha.
Where?
(Jae Seok starts running again.)
(Will he be able to make his way away from the monsters?)
They're coming from that way.
Gosh.
Come on, guys.
Goodness.
- Hello. - Hello.
You can't escape this time.
(Jae Seok's name tag is removed.)
I'm sorry.
I know I cheated.
But the looks in your eyes...
have totally changed.
You looked very nice on the stage before.
Halo, you guys are the same. What's the matter?
- I'll make sure to stop them. - Okay.
- Please hide well. I'm exhausted. - Okay.
This is driving me crazy.
- I will... - Stay right there for a while.
Sung Ki, stay there.
Min Ki, don't come close to me.
(Where should he hide?)
- Goodbye. - Bye.
Gosh.
This is crazy.
I got a message.
This is where the Blackmons are.
Where is this place?
I have no idea where it is.
Don't you think the cab drivers will know?
(Let's go ask the taxi drivers.)
I think it's near Yeouido.
Korea National Assembly Building?
Isn't this 63 Building?
(They head to the place where the Blackmons are.)
- Jong Kook, Redmons are coming. - Really?
(Jong Kook Hunters show up.)
Why are they so tenacious?
Hello!
- Gosh. - Chang Ryul is here, too.
- They just got my name tag. - Hello.
- I just lost my name tag. - Hello.
- I said, they just removed mine. - Congratulations!
- But it wasn't me. - Hello.
- I said they just removed mine. - Congratulations!
My goodness.
Congratulations!
(Selfish Kwang Soo runs away by himself.)
You can't do this to me.
We're close. Why are you so ruthless?
- Don't trust anyone. - Gosh.
Please, cut me some slack.
We used to be close.
Please let me go.
- Okay. - Chang Ryul!
You guys.
You guys will also grow old.
You'll grow old like me someday.
We'll go have lunch.
You can run away.
- You need to eat. - Okay, we'll have lunch.
- Tell your manager to pay for us. - Okay.
I will.
I found it. It's over there.
(Is Ji Hyo at the right place?)
Here is a taxi. They won't be able to follow me if I take a taxi.
What's the name of the cafe?
(Kwang Soo finds out the name in the picture.)
There is the name of the cafe.
(He's happy.)
I think I can do well today.
Considering that I enlarged the picture...
and found out the name of the cafe,
I think I might win today.
This is the place I'd like to go to.
Thank you.
(190 minutes before the game is over)
(He's getting closer to Blackmon.)
This looks similar to the picture.
It's over there.
Is that right?
I'm getting tired.
(The one who finds Blackmon first takes the advantage.)
That's the place.
(Who will catch Blackmon first?)
Do others know exactly where I am?
They can chase you only with GPS.
(Before Jae Hyun notices she's here,)
(she runs towards him at full speed.)
What's happening?
(I need to run.)
(She's running fast.)
How far should I go?
Jae Hyun.
Gosh, she's coming close.
(The one being chased...)
(versus the chaser)
Give up now.
It's over.
Jae Hyun, give up now.
(It's not over yet.)
Stop it.
(Is Blackmon Jae Hyun 10 dollars or zero dollars?)
I said it's over.
Wait.
- Come here. - Wait a moment.
- You... - Okay. I'll just hold you for now.
- Gosh, Jae Hyun. - Long time no see.
Why did you keep running away?
- I'm tired. - Me, too.
Do you know how much I ran because of you?
This isn't catching Blackmon.
It's like a chase scene in an action movie. That was crazy.
You can relax and just walk around with me.
We have to meet all seven members.
They are desperately looking for you.
- You'll regret if you catch me. - They're serious.
What are you going to do?
Anyway, I have to take off your name tag.
I'll tear it off.
Are you going to put yours now?
(Now, Blackmon Jae Hyun belongs to Ji Hyo.)
(Song Ji Hyo)
(Jae Hyun's score 200 and Ji Hyo's score 0)
(Jae Hyun's score 199 and Ji Hyo's score 1)
Hello.
(At the place he found with the picture...)
Be careful.
(Soo Bin is on her mission now.)
(Blackmons have to do a mission every hour...)
(to avoid Running Man members.)
On the ship, the girl lifted her arms...
(He sneaks from behind the staff.)
I'll skip this one.
You failed.
Hello, I failed.
(My name tag is taken off.)
Hello. I'm sorry.
Hi, I apologise.
- It's unbelievable. - Isn't it?
- Su Jin, I'm on Running Man. Hello. - Hello.
This is Running Man.
Don't you think...
we look like a couple? What should I do?
- She belongs to you now. - You're mine.
It feels like she's really mine.
(He's interested in something else now.)
I won't lose you anyway.
So don't even think about running away.
I won't lose you, indeed.
Even though Jae Hyun has 10 dollars on his back,
I don't have any intention to take off his name tag at all.
(I'm now with Soo Bin, you know.)
I didn't expect this mission would turn out this way.
This is making me crazy. Thank you.
(Why is the phone ringing at this moment?)
- Hello, Jong Kook. - Where are you, Kwang Soo?
I'm now...
with a lady, so I can't talk to you for long on the phone.
You mean her?
Yes. That's what happened.
I know. Why?
Jong Kook, she is so...
No, I'll stop talking.
She might be shy.
Okay. I see.
(She holds Kwang Soo's hand.)
(He's laughing.)
She's holding my hand right now.
- Why? - I'll hold it for you.
Now, let go of it.
(They're holding each other's hand tight.)
(It's raining in Seoul,)
(but the sun has appeared in Kwang Soo's heart.)
Wait.
(He's falling down.)
(I knew something nice would happen today.)
(He can't help but smile.)
I didn't know this would happen.
If I had known, I would have put on cologne.
You didn't give me any notice.
(In fact, love comes without notice.)
Do we have another mission?
No.
Your eyes are so...
(She stares at him.)
I don't usually say something like this,
but I'm captivated by you.
(He can't keep his mouth closed.)
I'm happy to be teamed up with you.
(He laughs in happiness.)
What should I do? I want to give everything to you.
What's this? Do you need this?
- Do you want this? - I have one, too.
It's nice to do this on a rainy day.
I think they're going across Han River.
We can't cross the river here.
I'll give an urgent notice.
Since Blackmon cleared the mission,
your location will be revealed to the hunters for 10 minutes.
My location?
Your GPS is turned on now.
This is crazy.
- Is it only me or all of us? - All of you.
(Five minutes ago)
That's what happened.
(Blackmon's hidden mission is to hold his hand.)
(If she clears the mission, the locations are sent to the hunters.)
(She's looking for the right moment.)
(Without knowing anything, he's just so excited.)
Why?
I'll hold it for you. Now, let go of it.
(She holds his hand tightly.)
Wait.
(Blackmon Soo Bin completes her hidden mission.)
(Hunters got the locations of the members.)
Where is exit number three?
Gosh.
(What did he see?)
(The hunters are gathering near the members.)
(They are Jong Kook Hunters.)
(They are coming closer because his location was sent to them.)
How did they know that I'm near exit number three?
(Here are Seok Jin Hunters, too.)
They're wearing purple. They're looking for Seok Jin.
Incredible. They are everywhere.
(They gather near the building where Seok Jin is.)
This is a problem.
- Hello. - Hello, Seok Jin.
- Where are you? - Where are you?
I'm near the parking lot of the building.
I'm also heading towards there,
but there are a lot of people who are looking for you.
- Where? - Here...
There are some in front of a convenience store, too.
Near the building?
They are everywhere.
Then I shouldn't be there.
Gosh, there are tons of them here.
You'll be in danger here.
While shooting Running Man,
I have a keen sense now.
Rock Hyun, Chan Young and Min Woo are passing...
by the building you're in.
Get out now quickly. There is nobody.
- Okay. - Get out quickly.
- There is nobody now. Come quickly. - I see.
(Will he escape with the help of Jae Seok?)
There he is. He's walking towards us.
He's doing his best to run, but it looks like he's walking.
- Come quickly. - Gosh.
- Because of Kwang Soo... - Seok Jin.
- Make it quick. - The phone keeps ringing.
They are here again. Move quickly.
(What do you mean they are here?)
What's wrong?
(Here come Seok Jin Hunters.)
My goodness.
Hey, Jae Seok.
- Run fast, Seok Jin. - What did you do to me?
I was foolish to trust you. What did you do to me?
Catch him.
Calm down.
Please calm down.
What should I do?
Sorry, Seok Jin. I didn't do it on purpose.
- You brat. - I didn't know at all, either.
- What do you mean? - Trust me.
(Seok Jin becomes the first to get eliminated.)
- Hey. - I didn't betray you.
You made a deal with him, right?
No, we didn't. It was just the three of us.
Please tell him I'm innocent.
There are people wearing pink.
They're wearing pink shirts. Pink hunters are...
after Kwang Soo, aren't they?
Shall I give them a ride?
There they are again.
Guys,
do you want to go to the Korea National Assembly Building?
- We're going there. - Okay.
Then...
I'll give you a ride.
- Really? - Let's go to get Kwang Soo.
- Great. - Good.
Sit in the front seat, too.
- Thank you. - Okay.
Please remember I did something nice to you.
Do you have only one name tag left?
I only have the last one.
- Let's go straight down the road. - Excuse me?
(The hidden mission is to ride on Kwang Soo's back.)
(If she clears the mission, the locations are sent to the hunters.)
What are you doing, Soo Bin?
- Let's get inside anyway. - Okay.
Too many people are after you.
- Kwang Soo. - Yes?
By the way,
- my legs hurt. - Right. You must be too tired.
We can't keep walking like this.
I can't walk any more.
(She's acting so cute.)
I...
(He's blushing.)
Should I give you a piggyback ride? What should I do?
- Are you okay with it? - Of course.
- It could hurt your back. - Don't worry.
What's going on all of a sudden?
I came out early this morning. My legs hurt too much.
(Kwang Soo gets tricked into giving her a piggyback ride.)
I've never done this before.
(The locations of the members are sent back to the hunters.)
- Am I heavy? - Not at all.
Wait.
(Did Kwang Soo finally notice something suspicious?)
I had no idea you were on my back.
(I had no idea you were on my back.)
- You're so light. - I think you can put me down now.
You want me to put you down now?
You're volatile, aren't you?
Thank you.
- No problem. Let's go. - Okay.
- Everywhere's closed. - I know.
(Kwang Soo spotted the hunters approaching him.)
- Soo Bin, do you have a mission? - What mission?
I think they're tracking your GPS.
- Where am I doing the mission? - Let me take a look.
If you succeed the mission, you can turn the GPS off.
You have to turn it off.
(That's not what you should worry about right now.)
We met here, right?
- We have to go there. - There's Ankara Park.
It's either of these two spots.
- What should we do? - Let's take the taxi over there.
- We can't do that. - They don't have our number.
Who's that?
It's Kwang Soo. You have to hide.
Keep hiding and sneak out later.
The taxi is taken.
What?
Oh, no!
(Screaming)
Open the door. Get off now.
Start running.
Oh, no!
(He left his umbrella with her in the middle of everything.)
No!
Soo Bin!
Hello. Come this way.
- Come this way? - What?
Come this way. Let's go.
It's nice to see you.
Here you go.
- Soo Bin! - Where are you going?
Have you seen Blackmon?
Soo Bin!
Kwang Soo, have you seen Blackmon?
No.
(Gary thinks Kwang Soo is being chased by the hunters.)
That could happen to me.
Soo Bin!
(Kwang Soo is an idiot.)
(Kwang Soo is an idiot who doesn't know anything other than Soo Bin.)
(He doesn't even know Soo Bin actually tricked him.)
I'm sorry, Soo Bin.
Soo Bin!
Let's see how things pan out.
I have to catch Kwang Soo.
Do you want some coffee?
- Are we going to stay in the taxi? - This is a taxi interview.
Hello.
- Hello. - Hello, Soo Bin.
I wonder if you're the real deal.
I wonder.
I think Jae Hyun is...
(Soo Bin says Jae Hyun is...)
the real deal.
(Soo Bin says Jae Hyun is 10 dollars.)
I've got nothing.
I'll be no use to you.
You know what? I'm not a good liar.
Maybe I'll take my name tag off to find out.
You don't have to do that. I said I'm not a good liar.
I don't trust actors and actresses any more.
Especially the ones that appear in Running Man.
The actresses...
look so innocent.
You have no idea what's inside.
- Hey, Ji Hyo. - Where are you?
- Aren't you at Hangang Park? - Hey.
I heard you're busy chasing after name tags with Blackmon.
I'm on a run right now. I managed to escape.
Haha is after me.
(He sneezes.)
- Is that Haha? - Yes.
Okay, bye.
Can you tell him that...
I won't be nice to him any longer?
I'll send him your message.
- Okay. - Nobody knows that I got caught.
Why did you have to sneeze?
(Is this how you're going to behave?)
Gosh, you're making me nervous.
Nobody has a clue that I got caught.
Kwang Soo is baiting me.
Did he say something about Haha?
(Ji Hyo tries to get Haha on the phone.)
- Hey, Ji Hyo. - Haha.
Are you chasing Kwang Soo right now?
(Haha is putting on an act to hide his possession of Soo Bin.)
Did you talk to him?
(He sneezes loudly.)
Who was that?
- Who was that? - Gosh.
I'll call you later.
- I'm right here. - Who's there?
I got caught.
Excuse me.
(Ji Hyo, Gary and Jong Kook)
You're a lot of help.
You should take a right.
He should be here somewhere.
Sir.
Please make a right turn over there.
There she is. That's Ji Hyo.
(He found Ji Hyo in middle of the street.)
Can you make a left?
Pull over please.
(I have to get off without her noticing.)
Ji Hyo caught Blackmon.
(Did he make eye contact with Jae Hyun?)
We don't know when the other members will come here.
(He sneaks his way around.)
(He's after Blackmon Jae Hyun.)
Yes.
(Ji Hyo is completely vulnerable.)
What's going on over there?
Go.
Hey, Ji Hyo.
(It's Jong Kook.)
I got you.
There.
(Jong Kook is the new master of Blackmon Jae Hyun.)
(Gary runs back the way he came from.)
What is this?
- What's going on? - How am I supposed to catch them?
- What's going on? - I have to escort him.
I have to escort him, right?
I have to escort him.
- Hurry. - Where did Jong Kook come from?
Gosh.
I was a second late.
Come say hi to the members.
(Take a look at my Blackmon.)
- We have to hurry. - Can you start the car?
Please start the car. He's scary.
He's so scary.
Jong Kook's timing was perfect.
Thank you, Jae Hyun.
I hope you didn't get too wet from the rain.
(Running Man Go, current situation)
He's scary.
He's so scary.
(They're still traumatised by Jong Kook.)
- Hey, Haha. - What's going on?
Jong Kook just...
took Jae Hyun from me.
Jae Hyun said he's zero dollars.
- Did he? - Yes.
(Does that mean Soo Bin is 10 dollars?)
Fill me in with the current situation.
Gary and Jong Kook came at me at the same time.
You have to start taking people out.
We won't go near you.
Okay, sounds good.
(Wait a minute.)
(He's brainstorming his next move.)
I know what I have to do.
I'm going to turn off the GPS.
Take a taxi again...
and when they come for me, I'll take them out.
(You're going to take off the members' name tags?)
(Taking off Blackmon's name tag gives you possession of it.)
(The person with Blackmon can attack other members.)
Can you take us to Hangang Park?
He's going to Han River.
- Who? - Let's catch Haha's Blackmon.
Yes, let's go for him.
(Alliance means nothing to them.)
He's going to Han River.
(Other members are also tracking him down.)
Haha is with Soo Bin?
(Soo Bin, what are you doing there?)
Can you wait for us here?
(Haha and Soo Bin arrive at the place for the mission.)
They're not here, right?
Where is the mission?
There it is. This is it.
This is it. That's the flag.
- This is the place. - Can you pull over?
You can pull over right here.
This is the plan. I'll go on first.
You just follow my lead.
(Everyone is closing up to Haha.)
Let's get it done fast.
- This is it. - Okay.
- Is this it? - Yes.
Let's get a slice of cheese to go with it.
This is it.
Where's gimbap?
I'm so nervous.
Why isn't it cooking?
I should cross.
(I can smell Blackmon from here.)
He's down there.
(Haha Hunters are also heading towards Haha.)
(He's on a lookout.)
Gary's coming.
(Gary's coming.)
Hey there.
(Let me take a look at your Blackmon.)
- Are you with her? - What?
Hello.
You can take me out, right?
Catch Gary.
I said catch Gary.
I won't go for you. Just catch Gary.
I won't go after you. Please catch Gary.
(I'm not falling for that.)
(Gary joins her.)
Let's get started. Let's eat.
- Haha. - This is the mission.
This is insane.
What is this?
Hello.
(Blackmon Soo Bin escapes voluntarily.)
- Hello. - Can you take it off?
(The master of Blackmon Soo Bin changes unexpectedly.)
What's going on?
(Gary can now attack other members.)
Wait, where did she go?
Soo Bin!
If you take mine off...
(Kwang Soo arrives at the middle of the chaos.)
(I heard you're giving out a free Blackmon.)
I become your Blackmon.
(Will Gary end up with taking over Soo Bin?)
(Kwang Soo is now in possession of Soo Bin.)
(Kwang Soo can attack Gary now.)
I got it!
(Gary has one name tag remaining.)
Kwang Soo, I wasn't going to go for you.
- That's nonsense. - He's lying.
- Goodbye. - He's such a liar.
Come on, let's go.
We're going to follow you.
This is not looking good.
- Hello. - Hello.
(Sneaky Jae Seok ambushes them.)
(He bites Kwang Soo.)
Get in quickly.
(Gary and Ji Hyo join the second Blackmon War.)
Rip it off quickly.
- Hold on. - Soo Bin!
- Wait! - No, Soo Bin!
No, Soo Bin.
Let me go!
(He rips Gary's name tag.)
(Gary is completely out.)
(Whose is this?)
Let me go!
(Jae Seok rips Kwang Soo's name tag that was attached to Soo Bin.)
(Jae Seok can now attack other members.)
I'm sorry, Sir.
Hello, Soo Bin. Long day, isn't it?
Let's go, Soo Bin.
Lock from inside, Soo Bin.
Lock the door.
Hurry.
(I'm ripping a name tag before I go.)
(The hyenas are after Soo Bin.)
Close the door.
Hello.
(She unlocks the door.)
Are you kidding me?
(They open up the door with the help of the driver's seat.)
(She screams.)
(This just in. There are zombies after Blackmon near Han River.)
Help me!
- Take it off. - Help me!
(Whose hand is this?)
(Kwang Soo takes back possession of Soo Bin.)
(Kwang Soo can now attack other members.)
(She's a total wreck.)
Soo Bin, don't leave me any more.
Come here, Ji Hyo.
Soo Bin, come over here.
(Don't go anywhere else and stay by me.)
We have to get out of here.
Is this how it usually is?
I'm sorry about everything.
(They are addicted to Blackmon. They're going after it.)
Here they come.
Can we come inside for a minute?
Thank you. Get in here, Soo Bin.
Come here, Soo Bin! Get in here!
Hide here.
(Can I come in, too?)
Lock the doors!
(She falls into his arms.)
Go around.
(Is this a zombie film?)
Go away.
Not like this.
Attack him if you have two name tags.
I'm going to take you out.
- I have two. - Oh, no.
Wait, hold on!
- Soo Bin! - I got it.
I got it.
(Jae Seok takes off Kwang Soo's name tag.)
I'll hold onto him. Take the name tag off.
(They plan to take Kwang Soo out.
(I should get rid of Kwang Soo now that I have the possession.)
Don't go for me.
(I'll get going then.)
Soo Bin!
(I'm sorry I couldn't protect you.)
We have to go after him. Come here.
We have to take him out for sure.
Soo Bin!
(I'm sorry I left you all alone with those hyenas.)
I'm sorry, Soo Bin!
Soo Bin!
- Am I heavy? - Not at all.
She's holding my hand right now.
(Even though I'm getting married, my feelings for you were true.)
I'm sorry, Soo Bin!
(All I can do now is wish her luck with the new owner.)
Are you well?
I hope we meet again!
(Soo Bin, I want you to be happy.)
Soo Bin!
Soo Bin, stay safe!
Where did he go?
He's going over there.
(Soo Bin is back in Jae Seok's hands.)
Soo Bin, stay safe...
(He gags.)
(That was a gagging monologue.)
- Hey. - Chae Soo Bin!
Get yourself together.
- Where is she? - Get yourself together.
- Chae Soo Bin! - You're going to...
- Pull yourself together. - Soo Bin!
Are you going through a breakup or something?
Soo Bin has zero dollars.
I don't care!
(Do you think I'm after the prize?)
- Hey. - I hate Cho Jae Hyun!
Soo Bin!
You're a fool in love.
(He is stupidly in love.)
- Wake up, you idiot. - This time, it's genuine.
It's for real this time.
I get that she's your type of girl,
but she has zero dollars.
Choose between Sun Bin and Soo Bin.
He likes those with "Bin" in their names.
- He fell in love again. - He looks sincere.
Which one is it?
You said you liked Sun Bin.
Kwang Soo.
(Jae Seok can attack other members.)
I've been through a lot.
What are you talking about?
Haha came after me...
and took Soo Bin from me.
We should clear things up by getting rid of him.
I don't even want to do anything today.
We have to put an end to you.
Your time is up.
- Hold still. - Soo Bin!
- Wait a minute. - Soo Bin!
- This is a waste of time. - Okay.
I have zero dollars.
You have to go after Jae Hyun.
What are you talking about?
You're confusing me.
We don't have time for Kwang Soo.
I'm...
Come help me get this off.
- You're the only one who can. - Soo Bin!
- Just hold him still. - Soo Bin!
You're not going to...
I don't need 10 dollars.
- You shouldn't fight over me. - Soo Bin!
Come help me!
(We have to take matters into our own hands.)
- Wait. - Take it off.
- I said take it off. - Okay, just relax.
Soo Bin.
- Hurry. I'm counting to 10. - Haha!
Rip it off and Jae Seok's after!
Take hers off and Jae Seok's after.
You...
- You brought this upon yourself. - Do it.
Soo Bin! Don't look.
- Don't look, Soo Bin. - Don't move.
- Soo Bin! - Go home.
- Soo Bin! - Please.
(I don't want you to see me like this.)
- Soo Bin! - Rip it off.
You make me sick.
(Kwang Soo is completely out.)
You're done now.
Soo Bin!
Friends.
- What's your next move? - I did as you said.
I listened to you and took Kwang Soo out.
- Be careful. - Stay back.
- Be careful. - Don't come any closer.
I regret nothing.
(He regrets nothing.)
I'm sorry, Soo Bin!
(I'll remember you.)
It's a good weather to love.
(It's a good weather to love.)
Don't come any closer.
- Don't raise your hand. - Okay.
- I have my hand on her name tag. - I get it.
I won't come closer.
Haha, take hers off and take Jae Seok out.
What are you waiting for?
Stay out of this.
Let me share a cab with him.
We can split the cab.
Let's all go home together.
(He's got a point.)
- He's right. - Don't listen to him.
- Don't listen to him. - Let me share a cab with him.
- Wait. - Take it off.
(Haha is in possession of Blackmon now.)
Take Jae Seok out.
This is insane. Hey, Ji Hyo.
A ride for two, please.
We're two people.
- Pull over here. - Go away.
- Hey, Ji Hyo. - Is this how you want to play?
- I said go away. - Ji Hyo.
Go away.
Don't come any closer.
Just rip it off!
Wait a minute. We should call over Haha Hunters.
That's the best solution.
(What did you say?)
Don't move.
- I'll do it, too. - Wait a minute.
Kwang Soo, give me my phone!
Are there any Jae Seok Hunters near Wonhyo Bridge?
I don't care what colour. Just send all of them!
I don't care if you're after Ji Hyo or Jae Seok.
I knew this would happen.
- Get them over here. - Blackmon is right here.
- Send them all. - Haha.
- Where are you going? - Take it off. Quickly.
- Don't do that. - Take it off.
(Ji Hyo can now attack other members.)
- Why did you do that? - Hey, Seok Jin.
Good job, Ji Hyo.
- I have Soo Bin now. - Calm down.
- We have to get rid of him. - Hold on.
- Wait. - We have to get rid of him.
- What's going on? - Take it off.
- What's going on? - There you go.
- We should at least take one off. - I did it.
- This is how it should be. - Now, Jae Seok can do the same.
(There is no alliance here.)
- Go away. - Get him.
(They go for Jae Seok this time.)
- Get him. - I only have one left.
That's my last one!
(Jae Seok is completely out.)
We're bad, aren't we?
- How could you do that? - We're really bad.
- I'm sorry, Jae Seok. - How could you?
I'm sorry. It had to be done.
- All of you should get ruined! - You scared me.
All of you!
- Soo Bin! - Hey, Soo Bin.
- Good work, Jae Seok. - It's too bad.
- I have to go now. - I'm sorry, Soo Bin.
Soo Bin!
I'll go to your concerts.
Hey.
You have problems.
Why are you like this every time?
Go! Go away!
- I hate you. - You make things so much worse!
- You ruined everything. - I hope you get ruined as well.
- I don't want to see you any more. - Gosh.
This is upsetting.
- Soo Bin! - Go away.
(It's been fun, Soo Bin.)
Everyone, this is...
Everyone, I didn't end up with her.
We got an action message from a viewer...
- to Kwang Soo. - An action message?
Yes, I'll read it for you.
(He slaps Kwang Soo.)
I delivered him...
the message.
- Thank you for that. - Thanks for you attention.
Last week, Kwang Soo spent a good time with Song Ji Eun.
I delivered the message from Song Ji Eun.
- Is it from Ji Eun? - Yes.
Thank you, Ji Eun.
(He slaps him again.)
All right.
Whom is this from?
You've met in the beginning. It's from her.
- Seung Hyun? - Yes.
I also delivered the action message from Seung Hyun.
Didn't you say I'm not your ideal type?
- Shall we go to prison then? - Okay.
Let's go.
See you next week.
(Jae Seok delivered all the messages.)
Do you want some?
It's fun but hard.
Honestly,
I have no idea what's going on.
I really don't know what I should do.
(What is he trying to say?)
I...
(He hesitates.)
- You're doing well. - Can I tell him now?
I shouldn't tell him about my tag, right?
- You can't say that. - I have no idea...
(Is he going to tell Jong Kook about his tag?)
Turn the cameras off. Mine is zero dollars.
(Did he just say he has zero dollars?)
Well...
This is... Well...
(They have 4 minutes left.)
- Where is Jong Kook? - Haha is...
- Ji Hyo! - Ji Hyo, run!
(Ji Hyo, run!)
There are Yellowmons!
(Ji Hyo Hunters show up.)
(She's frozen.)
Soo Bin! Hurry!
What should we do?
They're right behind us!
Goodness.
No, no way!
(Hunters catch Ji Hyo.)
(Her name tag is removed.)
Goodness. Guys.
Does Soo Bin have to stay with Ji Hyo?
- Gosh, what is it? - I'm freed!
What is he doing?
Soo Bin, stop right there. You know I can get you.
(The reward is mine.)
- Soo Bin. - Go away.
- You should come with me. - Go alone.
(The one with Blackmon is likely to win.)
- Please go alone. - What?
- Let's hurry. - No way!
(1 minute and 27 seconds remain.)
(Haha owns Soo Bin.)
(Now, Haha and Jong Kook are close to winning.)
- I think he went that way. - Let's hurry.
- That way? - Let's go this way.
I think I'll run into a monster.
(The race is almost over.)
(Who will get the Blackmon with 10 dollars?)
Let me thank you all...
who joined Running Man today.
They ran around Yeouido all day long...
to catch us.
The scariest ones are Jong Kook Hunters.
- I thought you were thugs. - We're not thugs.
- They are so scary. - They are.
Look at Chang Ryul, Ha Neul and the rest of the members.
They also look scary. There is also Ma A Sung.
- M. Tyson. - Right. M.Tyson and Min Hyuk.
I've never seen such scary group before.
- Right. - Min Hyuk...
Min Hyuk joined Running Man before,
and he's performing in Southeast Asia now.
- He went to Vietnam. - He performed in Vietnam.
- That's right. - Sing for us!
(He's singing.)
(Good Job, A Sung.)
So you're popular. It's amazing.
Ji Hyo Hunters are ToppDogg and young comedians.
I mistook Eun Hyung for a ghost.
- You really scared me. - Eun Hyung,
- Yes? - when are you going to get married?
- They'll in April, next year. - We'll marry in April.
- Congratulations. - Great.
(Congratulations!)
Where is your groom? He's right here.
So you'll finally get married.
- In April. - You're going to get married.
We have 24K and KNK with us.
I am really sorry.
It's the largest number including them.
- I didn't know a lot of them. - 27 monsters ran after Seok Jin.
Do you remember Hae Ryeong?
- She played with Seok Jin before. - You're right.
So he posted on his SNS account.
- It was "Hae", not "Hye". - Right.
- He was confused. - I made the mistake twice.
And he asked her who she was today.
(I am sorry I have a short-term memory.)
- Now, Haha will make a decision. - Right, I will.
(Does Haha get to decide?)
(1 minute before the game ended)
(Jong Kook owned Jae Hyun.)
My goodness.
They're coming again!
(Jong Kook Hunters appeared.)
(If they remove Jong Kook's name tag, Jae Hyun will be freed.)
- Now! - Remove it!
(Haha removed Jong Kook's name tag and took Jae Hyun.)
We need the Blackmon to win.
I will remove their tags...
and see what tag they have before I decide.
I just need to know how much they have.
They both denied. They're good at acting because it's their job.
- It's Soo Bin. - Really?
Haha.
(It's Jae Hyun.)
This is so difficult.
Do you know who it is, Jae Hyun?
I knew it but I forgot.
The left is for 10 dollars and the right is zero dollars.
- Yes. - Please stand on this.
Don't unfollow Hae Ryeong.
- This is for zero dollars. - Gosh.
- I didn't know. - And you'll stand on this.
It was a mistake.
- You think Soo Bin has 10 dollars. - Right.
Haha owned Jae Hyun for seven minutes.
- It's 70 dollars. - That'd be 70 dollars.
And he owned Soo Bin for 97 minutes.
- 97 minutes? - You made a better choice.
It's Soo Bin, right?
- She is. - She is, Haha.
One!
I have zero dollars.
You must find Jae Hyun.
Why are you confusing me?
I'm really bad at lying.
- Two! - It's her.
I know you have zero dollars.
- Mine is zero. - Sorry?
What are you talking about?
(Does Jae Hyun really have zero dollars?)
Three!
(Is it Soo Bin or Jae Hyun?)
(Who has 10 dollars?)
(Soo Bin...)
(had zero dollars.)
Was I wrong?
(Haha fails.)
Goodness, I knew it!
- My goodness. - All right.
- Let's check, then. - Gosh.
What's going on?
Gosh.
- He has 10 dollars. - This is my shoe insert.
(Ta-da)
My goodness.
You should've put it somewhere else.
- Why did you put it on the insert? - He put it on the insert.
- Jae Hyun. - I can't believe this.
- This is a kind of etiquette. - He has a 10-dollar bill.
Therefore, these two Blackmons...
earned 310 dollars of reward!
(They won 310 dollars.)
Really?
Thank you again for your participation.
Thank you!
(Thank you Jae Hyun, Soo Bin...)
(and the 102 hunters for joining us.)
- Thank you! - You all did a great job!
Goodbye.
In 1, 2!
Thank you very much!
- Thank you. - You did a good job.
- Thank you. - Thank you!
Say cheese.
- Thank you. - Thank you for joining us.
Go for it, Running Man!
Thank you.
Thank you. I'll enjoy this.
Thank you very much.
- Thank you. - You all did a good job.
- Thank you. - Goodbye.
(And...)
(this is the first mission for the members and the guests.)
("Walk politely before someone who's in much higher position.")
(Find out how to say this in pure Korean words...)
(and bring it to us.)
(We'll give an advantage to the one who brings it to us first.)