(July 11, 2010)
Don't walk, but run. Running Man.
(This is how the history began.)
(6 springs, summers, autumns and winters)
(6 years)
(6 years ago, Kwang Soo was a 26-year-old nameless actor.)
(With 7 million Chinese followers on SNS, he's the Prince of Asia now.)
(And...)
(Ji Hyo and Gary used to be awkward with one another.)
(Now, they've become the Monday Couple and lifelong friends.)
(On the other hand,)
(40-year-old Seok Jin who felt nervous to join an outdoor show...)
(has now become a guaranteed "Race Starter".)
(Also,)
(Haha, who confessed his love to every female guest,)
(met a woman and confessed his eternal love to her.)
(71 months)
(Jong Kook showed his amazing strength for the last 71 months.)
(He hasn't changed.)
(Jae Seok, who was standing in the centre for the last 71 months,)
(has realised that he is a centre-seeker.)
(2,142 days)
(Many guests have joined Running Man for the last 2,142 days.)
We don't look the same.
Really?
(650 guests)
When did you become so cute?
(The Running Man team visited various countries around the world.)
(Thailand)
(China)
(Australia)
(Macau)
(Vietnam)
(Hong Kong)
(Running Man's 300th episode begins today.)
(The beginning of an unexpected, but dangerous challenge)
("300" is the enemy that the 7 Running Man members must defeat.)
(Imagination becomes reality, and reality becomes a nightmare.)
(They took the bait.)
(In the darkness, there are traps set up for the Running Man members.)
(If a member gets caught in a trap, the darkness deepens.)
(Escape, if you can.)
(P tower in Sangam)
(A 3 tier cake is prepared to celebrate the 300th episode.)
- Wow, look at that.
-  Hello.
(There are 300 nameplates with all the episode titles of Running Man.)
(Here, you can see the 6-year history of Running Man at once.)
- These are all the episodes.
-  "Mafia Game".
- That's the first episode.
-  This is touching.
- We went through so many episodes.
-  This is quite touching.
- There are so many.
-  What is this?
I can't remember this episode.
This episode was the best. Yu Bond Spin Off Virus.
I think this episode was the best. First Love Race was the best.
Do you remember? In this episode, Boarders of 2014, Guk Joo joined us.
Really?
(It was a strong women special that is hard to forget.)
The Supernatural Baseball episode is here.
- Supernatural Baseball was fun.
-  It was really fun.
(MLB players Ryu Hyun Jin and Choo Shin Soo joined this episode.)
Choi Min Soo was in Grasshopper Hunting, right?
- That's right.
-  It was really amazing.
- It was really scary.
-  When was it aired?
The grasshopper was really scary.
- I was scared, too.
-  It was so long ago.
This was Sherlock Holmes. Seok Jin ruined this episode. Remember?
- It was a big mess.
-  It was the 79th episode.
(Seok Jin played a crucial role.)
First Love Race.
Will we ever have a First Love Race again?
(Haha spent a good time with Han Ga In.)
I have a good memory of that episode.
There is a question mark for the 300th episode.
It's because today's the 300th.
Wow, it's 300.
300th.
Today is the 300th episode.
Congratulations.
First, we'd like to show our gratitude to all the viewers.
- Thank you.
-  Really.
- We'll try harder from now on.
-  It's a special day.
- We must try harder.
-  Of course.
Come to think of it, we've spent a long time together.
- We really have.
-  It has been 300 weeks.
There's a question mark on the title of the 300th episode.
Please remove the sticker and reveal today's mission.
By ourselves?
- By ourselves?
-  Please remove the sticker.
Today's episode must be like a blockbuster episode. Right?
- I'm really looking forward to it.
-  In 1, 2, 3.
(What is today's 300th episode special?)
- What?
-  "7 vs 300"?
(7 vs 300?)
- 7 vs 300?
-  What is this?
What is this about?
- How can we beat 300 people?
-  Today's special...
is the 300th Episode Special: 7 vs 300.
From now, for two days,
you will go through missions related to the number 300.
If you successfully complete each mission,
we will give you puzzle pieces for hints...
that are essential for the final mission.
If you fail a mission, you will be heavily penalised...
according to the mission you've failed.
So please work together for the missions ahead.
(So this isn't a 300th episode celebration.)
This is the 300th episode, so you'll be rewarded with a completion fee.
A completion fee?
- Will they give us 3,000 dollars?
-  Because it is the 300th episode,
we will reward you 3,000 dollars.
Oh my goodness.
- Really?
-  3,000 dollars?
- Can we really take the money?
-  Oh my goodness.
(3,000 dollars in cash)
- Oh my goodness!
-  It's real.
- Really?
-  Is it real money?
- What's so special today?
-  Even if we share it equally...
(The completion fee is exceptional. It's 430 dollars for each member.)
The first mission of today's 7 vs 300 special will be revealed.
(The first mission is revealed.)
(What is the first mission with the completion fee of 3,000 dollars?)
The first mission will be revealed now.
- Dollars?
-  3,000 dollars?
(300th Episode Special: 7 vs 3,000 dollars)
3,000 dollars?
This must be the bet of the game.
(How will they compete against the completion fee?)
Everyone, from now on,
if you remove the sticker on the title of each episode...
on the nameplates around you,
you will find a quiz for each episode.
Every member has to solve a quiz, so there are seven quizzes in total.
The completion fee will be reduced by...
10 dollars for every second that is passed.
- 10 dollars for every second?
-  One second?
- Do we have the first mission here?
-  It means you're not paying us.
- Just tell us that you won't.
-  We must get all the answers right.
No, if you hurry, you can take quite a bit of money with you.
- We only have 300 seconds.
-  It means we have 5 minutes.
Is the quiz related to the episode...
- that we choose?
-  Choose the ones you remember.
For example, choose an episode that you played a crucial role in.
- We should choose carefully.
-  I will choose the First Love Race.
(299 episodes were aired for the last 6 years.)
(To win, they must remember what they did on those episodes.)
(How many episodes will the members remember out of 300?)
Let's do the 7012nd episode first.
- That's the most recent one.
-  A recent one is a good idea.
- Right.
-  Then...
Let's start with 7012 special.
Let's decide the order.
Let's line up first. The one in front of the line runs first and...
- Okay.
-  Then,
- Haha will go first.
-  Me? All right.
Start.
(The first runner is Haha.)
(How much out of 3,000 dollars will they get?)
(The Running Man Quiz has 299 questions.)
Start!
(The Running Man Quiz has begun.)
- Hurry.
-  Look, they take a dollar every...
"Who was the guest that was Han Ga In's first love?"
(Haha chooses Episode 87, First Love Race.)
(Who was the guest that was Han Ga In's first love?)
It's me, Haha.
(Me, Haha)
(Haha had a great time with Ga In 4 years ago in 2012.)
(Haha chose the episode that Ga In joined as a guest.)
My first love.
(Will Ga In's first love be Haha?)
It's me, Haha.
- Correct.
-  Okay.
- Good.
-  Choose the one you can remember.
- Where is the Avengers episode?
-  Hey,
- find the one you remember now.
-  Find them in advance.
(Gary chooses Episode 81, Gary Knows.)
- You're too short.
-  Hey!
"Where in England did Gary shoot 'Gary Potter'?"
Do you know the answer?
- Do you remember it?
-  You should know the answer.
- Hurry, Gary.
-  Hey.
- Hurry up.
-  Say anything that comes to mind.
- Gary.
-  I don't know.
- What are you doing?
-  Manchester.
- Just say anything.
-  Pass. Ji Hyo.
- Let me go for it.
-  Try to remember.
- What was the name of that station?
-  I'll choose "Avengers".
- "Which guest became a super hero?"
-  What was the name of the station?
- Who became a super hero?
-  That's him.
- It is...
-  Seok Jin.
- Wait. Who was he?
-  I think...
It is...
So can we share our powers now?
(The one who visited Running Man "Avengers" was...)
Come at me!
(Super hero, Choo Sung Hoon)
(Has Ji Hyo forgotten such a furious hero?)
- Wait. Who was he?
-  I think...
It was...
(Come on. Who was he?)
Hey, look at how fast the money is going down.
Choo Sung Hoon.
- I got it right.
-  Good.
Hurry!
(Seok Jin chooses Episode 79, Sherlock Holmes.)
"Which comedian team visited us to perform on the treasure ship?"
Who were they?
- They're...
-  My goodness.
- I remember a dog. Who were they?
-  Right.
- Goodness!
-  There was a dog.
- Boksil.
-  Can others answer this question?
- Come on. Tell me.
-  My goodness. Hurry.
Goodness. I'll go for it. You're unbelievable.
Gosh, where's mine?
Where's the one I picked?
(Jae Seok is in confusion.)
- Where is it?
-  That's the one...
- It is...
-  Just pick any!
- Right. Just choose one.
-  Right.
- You should've decided earlier.
-  Just take it off.
("Which phrase does Kim Su Ro hate the most?")
- What?
-  What does he hate the most?
- He is...
-  I can't remember that.
I don't know. No one can remember that.
Wouldn't it be a swear word?
- Just give up.
-  How am I supposed...
It reached 2,000 dollars already. Hurry.
- I can't remember.
-  Then get out.
- Pass.
-  What was the answer?
- You can never beat Jong Kook.
-  What are you talking about?
That's what he hates to hear the most.
(The answer is "You can never beat Jong Kook.")
- What's this?
-  Choose before your turn comes.
- Which one should I choose?
-  Jung Woo Sung.
"How many CCTVs did Jung Woo Sung use to monitor the members?"
(Jung Woo Sung visited Running Man as the King of Terror in 2013.)
(How many CCTVs did he use in the episode?)
(How many CCTVs did Woo Sung use to watch over the members?)
Gosh, this is pretty exciting.
"How many CCTVs did Jung Woo Sung use to monitor the members?"
- Gosh.
-  What is that?
- Just guess.
-  There were a lot.
(It's a hard question even for Jong Kook.)
How many were there?
108?
(Were there 108?)
(Is...)
(108...)
(the answer?)
"You're the King of Revenge."
"There are 108 CCTVs inside the building."
"You can use 108 of them."
(The answer is 108.)
- How many were they?
-  108?
- How did you know that?
-  You're great.
(Is he human?)
- How does he remember that?
-  How can he remember that?
- How did you remember the number?
-  Gosh.
How could you remember the number exactly?
My goodness. Do you watch previous episodes every day?
Jong Kook must be a huge fan of Running Man.
I'll choose Happy Kwang Soo's Day.
"What was Kwang Soo doing when the members invaded his house?"
How did you know it was 108?
- I know the answer.
-  I was brushing my teeth.
Kwang Soo, it's me.
(The members visited Kwang Soo's place without warning.)
Kwang Soo.
(Kwang Soo opened the door with toothpaste on his mouth.)
- I was brushing my teeth!
-  You're right!
- Yes!
-  Good.
- Hurry!
-  Run!
Hurry up.
(They got 4 questions correct. They need 3 more to succeed.)
- Wait.
-  Jong Kook.
Do you watch Running Man every day?
- He looks...
-  "What did Sung Kyun's t-shirt..."
("What did Sung Kyun's humiliating t-shirt say?")
I remember this.
It's "I'm younger than Haha."
- Yes!
-  Good.
(The answer is "I'm younger than Haha.")
Hurry. The money is going down!
- Hurry.
-  It's 1,600 dollars.
What did you choose?
- Hidden camera?
-  What is hidden camera?
("Who were the two people that revealed the hidden camera?")
(They had a Treasure Hunt Race in Australia in 2014.)
(The two guests who had joined the Adventure in Australia were...)
(regular guest, Kim Woo Bin,"
(and the world star, RAIN.)
(Will Gary remember who he was with in Australia 2 years ago?)
- Who were they?
-  I got it.
RAIN and...
- Hurry.
-  Kim Woo Bin.
- Wow.
-  That's correct.
(The last question of the 7 vs 300 Quiz)
- Choose the one you remember.
-  What's wrong with you?
"What did Seok Jin have to buy at the rest stop?"
- What did he have to buy?
-  Gosh, this one is difficult.
- This is really difficult.
-  I can't remember it either.
- I can't remember it.
-  Was it food?
Was it fish cake?
- My goodness.
-  It's my turn!
- We need to answer seven questions.
-  Did you get yours right?
- You already got it right.
-  Right.
Isn't it my turn?
"What was Cha In Pyo's rail bike mission?"
- What is this?
-  What's a rail bike mission?
- It's 1,200 dollars now.
-  He did that with you.
He did that with me.
- What's the mission?
-  Do you not remember?
Didn't you eat something?
You made tteokbokki.
It's tteokbokki.
(They had to re-enact a scene from "Peppermint Candy".)
Choose the one right up there. Jae Seok!
Jae Seok, choose your special.
Okay. Good.
Gosh, he remembers nothing.
- Pick it!
-  Go for it!
(Why is Jae Seok so lost?)
Take it off.
- "Which disease did Gary want..."
-  "Which disease did Gary..."
- "to treat?"
-  What was that?
- Isn't it piles?
-  Mythomania.
- That's not correct.
-  Gosh.
I want to get rid of my celebrity disease.
- Really?
-  I never thought you'd have that.
I used to have it before.
- Is he a spy?
-  Why would I have mythomania?
- "Who appeared with psychic power?"
-  I don't know.
- Is it celebrity disease?
-  Who is it?
Choose another one.
- Go, run!
-  Gosh.
Folk Tale of Nine-Tailed Fox!
Where is it?
It's right there. The nine-tailed fox.
"Which part of Kim Soo Mi's body is as sharp as a big nail?"
- Gosh!
-  I don't know!
- A big nail?
-  Did she mention it?
My elbow is as sharp and hard as a big nail.
(The answer is her elbows.)
- "Who was hit by Wax's leek?"
-  What is this?
It's him. Kim Tae Hee's brother.
"Here's my sword!"
(The answer is annulled due to Haha's cheating.)
- Gosh.
-  Choose a recent one.
Don't choose a recent one. Pick an old one.
Gosh, it's 600 dollars now.
"What was the shape of the rice ball eaten by the one who ranked fourth?"
- Gosh.
-  "What was the shape?"
- You've got to be kidding me.
-  This is weird.
- It is.
-  It had a heart shape.
It's a heart shape, you fool.
"What did Evra say in Korean?"
What did he say?
- He said, "It's tasty".
-  Jae Seok, I say this a lot.
(What did Evra say in Korean?)
(Evra said something to PD Ko Dong Wan who was in female attire.)
You're so funny.
(You're funny.)
- "You're so funny."
-  What did he say?
He said, "You're so funny."
He said "You're so funny".
(Do you remember when Evra said, "You're so funny"?)
- "I love you"? "That's a lie"?
-  Isn't it "Cool"?
- It's not the answer.
-  What did he say?
My goodness. It is driving me crazy.
- Gosh.
-  Why are the questions so hard?
- We are done for.
-  We have only 370 dollars now.
- This one.
-  You know this one.
- You know the answer, right?
-  Good.
- Come on.
-  It's Announcer Kim Hwan.
(Who was the commentator of Running Man Olympics' opening ceremony?)
- No way.
-  I will be today's commentator.
I am Jung Jae Hyung.
- Don't you remember?
-  Choose one from there.
- My money!
-  Choose "I am MC Yoo".
- Great.
-  This is driving me crazy.
- Do it quickly.
-  Jae Seok!
"Who is the guest who visited in place of Cho Jung Chi?"
It's his wife.
- Who?
-  Jung In.
- Is it wrong?
-  No way.
My goodness.
(The answer is Eddy Kim.)
- Hurry!
-  Isn't it Eddy Kim?
- What is it?
-  Hurry up.
- "What did Yoo Ah In cook?"
-  We ran out of money. It's over.
- Yoo Ah In...
-  We have no money left. It's over.
(What did Ah In cook?)
(Ah In cooked something spicy and sweet.)
(What did he cook?)
(I think I can remember.)
- It's...
-  He doesn't know.
- Hurry.
-  I don't remember.
- Gosh.
-  This is ridiculous!
(This is ridiculous.)
- We failed!
-  I can't believe this.
(The answer is galbi stew.)
- Gosh.
-  You're making me really mad.
- How can you not know anything?
-  Jong Kook remembered 108.
- Gosh.
-  How can you not remember anything?
- My goodness.
-  The questions were...
- He is weird.
-  He is.
- I'm disappointed.
-  He's so weird.
Is this Jong Kook versus Jae Seok?
It was a practice game, wasn't it?
- How could he get nothing right?
-  Goodness.
You've gone crazy, haven't you?
It's amazing that Jae Seok remembers nothing.
But it's more amazing that Jong Kook knew the exact number of cameras.
- How could you remember that?
-  That was amazing.
- I remember there were 108 of them.
-  Goodness.
Jong Kook must be a big fan of Running Man.
- Jae Seok...
-  Is he a famous blogger?
I couldn't remember anything.
Now, I remember that.
I was confused with another episode.
I can't believe that Jae Seok didn't remember anything.
- You're right.
-  But I really couldn't think of it.
And I was pressed for time.
Remit 430 dollars to everyone's accounts.
(He needs to pay 430 dollars each.)
If the money is divided, it's exactly 430 dollars each.
- This is unbelievable.
-  Goodness.
- We could've made it.
-  It was really close.
I'll be mistaken as a spy.
- Aren't you a spy?
-  You must be.
If you didn't know the answer, you should have moved on.
I did, but I still failed!
If you didn't know, you shouldn't have gone back and forth.
- You should've moved on.
-  But...
This is what I think.
If you rip one and don't know the answer, rip the next one.
Keep going until you find the one you know.
Why would you say you don't know and come up...
(Why would you say you don't know?)
(Hesitating)
- He's right.
-  That's right.
- What was that for?
-  He's right on the dot.
He was trying to be cute.
- Oh, gosh.
-  Were you right or wrong?
Were you right or wrong? Say it.
You ruined the 300th episode.
How could you not know?
There's no way he couldn't remember.
- I seriously had no idea.
-  No way. You would know.
We should have kept at least 1,500 dollars.
(What's the truth behind this?)
(What's the second mission?)
What's this about?
I'm being accused as a spy. This is not fair.
- I was flustered so it's possible.
-  I have my eyes on you.
- I almost ripped your name tag.
-  My goodness.
- Let me reveal the second mission.
-  Okay.
- Watch the LED screen behind you.
-  Oh, dear.
You prepared an LED screen?
This is something different.
Running Man always impresses me.
(What is...)
(the next 7 vs 300 mission?)
(They're tensed up.)
(300th Episode Special: 7 vs 300m)
The second mission...
(300m?)
- Metres?
-  It's 300m.
- What's this about?
-  What's this?
The second mission is "300m Essay".
- What?
-  An essay?
(Do they have to write a 300m-long essay?)
Please look behind you.
- I'm good at writing.
-  You'll see manuscript paper.
The total length of this paper is 300m.
Each box is 10cm long...
and it fills 3,000 letters in total.
(Each box is 10cm, and they must fill in 3,000 letters!)
Each member...
should write at least 430 characters.
- Really?
-  430?
- Do you want us to write a book?
(It's like writing a novel.)
You'll divide yourselves...
into two groups and start on both ends.
The theme of "300m Essay"...
is the 300th episode.
You must fill up the paper in 30 minutes.
If you cannot finish on time,
flour-filled balloons will pop on top of your heads,
so please try to finish on time.
(3,000 characters...)
(in 30 minutes?)
Jae Seok, you have to get it this time.
Why would I not get it?
- Give him a good spot.
-  We have to watch Jae Seok.
That's enough.
(Will they succeed?)
Once we meet in the middle, it has to flow well.
It's too long.
- Jong Kook, just write whatever.
-  Right.
It's freestyle writing.
Ji Hyo, write a lot.
What should I write about?
Ji Hyo, just keep going.
It's freestyle writing, anyway.
It has to be on topic.
- I know.
-  Of course.
Get the timer ready.
Let's get ready. Timer.
(They have balloons attached to their heads.)
Start the timer.
- Yes, let's go.
-  Start!
(It has begun!)
- Yes, let's go.
-  Let's go!
(They only have 30 minutes.)
Ji Hyo, you're slow.
(Wow, this...)
(What will become of them?)
Write whatever.
Good job.
- Yes, let's go.
-  Let's go!
Write whatever.
Good job.
Keep going. It's smooth.
- Good job. Write all of our names.
-  This is good.
That's right. Good one, Ji Hyo.
- You're smart!
-  Good one.
Hold on. Haha and Gary...
Write Kang Hee Geon. Fill up another space.
Write Gary.
- Write Kang Hee Geon.
-  This is difficult, Ji Hyo.
You came far.
- This is so hard.
-  You still have a long way.
We have to fill up a row each.
"We run and run again."
That flows well.
It's pretty good.
- "We run and run again."
-  Well done, Ji Hyo.
Ji Hyo, I didn't know you were good in writing.
- I'm not.
-  That was unexpected.
(Ji Hyo is the best in writing, too.)
(It's literary, yet strategic.)
Ji Hyo, that's good!
I like those zeros.
That's 1, 10th, 100th, 1,000th, 10,000th, 100,000th, 100,000th,
a million, 10 million, 100 million,
one billion and...
- 300 billion.
-  You should have been a writer.
- Jae Seok.
-  "In my next life,"
In my next life...
You came far.
(She'll be on Running Man in her next life, too.)
Jong Kook, why are you still there?
You're so slow.
Jong Kook is writing an emotional essay!
(He's writing an emotional essay!)
- How sentimental.
-  He's starting his literary career!
(Every day passes by like a flash.)
- "The past days..."
-  "The past days..."
(We shared so many good and bad times. The seven of us...)
This is heartwarming.
(Used to be awkward but overcame it to be here today. We wouldn't be...)
"Every day..."
- "passes by like a flash."
-  That's right.
Hey, hurry up!
Jong Kook, you're being too sincere.
Hey, write all of our names.
Write my name. You have to make it longer.
Write each of our names.
- This is too long.
-  We took care of each other...
This might pop.
We're doomed if you take a break!
Hurry up!
You're almost there.
Jong Kook, Ji Hyo is almost done!
What language is this?
It's illegible near the end.
I can't even understand.
(Scribbling)
- What's that?
-  "Geu".
(Ji Hyo fills up 300 characters.)
- "Geu"?
-  "Geu".
And...
- Good job.
-  everybody,
- Wow.
-  "With utmost sincerity..."
Hello.
"Everybody, hello?" You're supposed to add "With utmost sincerity".
I'm being sincere.
I have to introduce myself.
There needs to be a space here!
Every space counts!
Make up words.
- Don't just say hello.
-  Skip a space.
"With all my heart..."
"Wholeheartedly..."
Gosh! What do you think you're doing?
Why are you picking on me?
- It's obvious you're a spy.
-  Hurry up!
You're driving me nuts.
- Write giggling signs.
-  Jong Kook, hurry up!
You need to skip a space!
I usually don't skip spaces.
You can't do that.
There are spaces in Korean.
Hurry up. Hurry.
- Okay.
-  Hey.
You need spaces!
(Ji Hyo explodes.)
(This must be forced labour.)
Skip a space! Why aren't you?
Draw a smiley face.
And then?
It's already been...
- "Already..."
-  300 episodes.
- "This day has..."
-  "This day?"
"finally come."
"This day has finally come."
- Smiley face!
-  "Is this reality?"
- Smiley face.
-  "If not,"
"am I dreaming?"
"Am I mistaken?"
"What do you think, everybody?"
"I didn't know 300 episodes..."
(Gosh)
- Skip spaces!
-  Please, stop!
Write something along the line!
Skip spaces.
- You have to, Kwang Soo.
-  Hurry up!
- Write like you're typing.
-  Why are you doing this?
Hurry up!
This is too painful.
(Kwang Soo will suffer for life.)
This is difficult.
- He's finished now, Jae Seok.
-  All right.
(No more agony, please!)
How...
- "Can I express it in words?"
-  can I say it...
(Kwang Soo is being polite until the end.)
For you to feel my sense of gratitude?
I...
(Ji Hyo and Jae Seok are still watching him.)
Will live life to the fullest.
(He's a slave of 300 years.)
Until the 400th episode,
(The abuse...)
500th episode,
(Ends here.)
- 500th episode.
-  "500th episode".
(It's Jae Seok's turn. What will we write?)
600th episode,
700th episode,
- 800th episode,
-  Good job, Jae Seok.
We'll let you write until the 1,000th episode.
- 900th episode,
-  Jae Seok.
Write 901st episode.
Are you disregarding the 901st episode?
901st episode,
902nd episode,
We'll let you write until 905th episode.
903rd episode,
- 904th episode,
-  "904th episode".
(He'll be on Running Man in his next life, too.)
905th episode...
and...
(And)
Finally,
the anticipated...
(And the anticipated...)
1,000th...
(And the anticipated 1,000th episode.)
- Episode.
-  Jae Seok, how can you stop there?
Until then, we'll work our fingers to the bone...
- What?
-  "To the bone"?
And we'll not...
spare ourselves.
We're not even halfway done.
I, Yu Jae Seok,
- Jae Seok,
-  Rush yourself.
Give him some water!
- This is not easy.
-  Seok Jin...
Jae Seok, mention Hwan Jin.
- Why?
-  Lee Hwan Jin,
(We need something different.)
Producer Yong Woo...
- Cheol Min.
-  Cheol Min.
and Cheol Min.
- Writer Lee Hee Yeon...
-  "Writer".
(He takes care of each staff member.)
Writer...
Director Kang Chang Hee,
Park Seong Bae, Jeon Seong Ho,
Director Kang Yong Yoo.
And Cameraman Kwon Ryeol,
Gi Jin, Yoon Sang,
- Can we have your names?
-  Give me your names.
- Tell me your names.
-  We need names from the audio team.
- Give me your names.
-  Tell us your names.
Director Nam Hyun Geun,
Director Kim Won Chip.
- Kim...
-  "Won Chip".
- Director...
-  What's your name, Director?
And Chae Jae Won...
You went from "I, Yu Jae Seok" to all the way here.
All right. I promise you this.
- I...
-  There are 10 minutes left.
thank you...
- sincerely.
-  You're almost there.
I don't know how to thank you.
- Are you sure about the spelling?
-  Yes.
- Heart.
-  We did it.
- We did it!
-  Jae Seok.
- We finished.
-  We finished it!
Gosh, I am so thirsty.
We're done. We finished.
- When?
-  We are almost there.
- Put a question mark.
-  For the 79th episode,
- it was the Sherlock Homes special.
-  Good, Sherlock.
- I'm...
-  I was so upset.
(Is he doing a mission or ventilating his anger?)
I just had to take down Jong Kook and...
- His explanation is very detailed.
-  Ji Hyo.
- He must've been very upset.
-  For the 79th episode.
- He has a lot of anger.
-  Jong Kook and Ji Hyo.
(300th Episode Special, I can finally say it.)
You're so inhumane.
I was trying hard...
- to make things work and win.
-  There you go.
- Just a little bit more.
-  I...
- want to...
-  We are almost done.
- be in the centre.
-  We have to wrap it up.
- In 1, 2...
-  And happy new year.
- Go, Running Man.
-  End it with 7012.
7012.
(Like we've done for 300 episodes, let's continue on together forever!)
- There you go.
-  You're done, right? We're done!
(Seok Jin succeeds as well!)
- The second mission ended.
-  We succeeded.
For the "300m Essay",
(The second mission was "300m Essay".)
Running Man has succeeded.
- We had a lot to say.
-  This is just the beginning.
In just 23 minutes,
- you wrote a 300m long essay.
-  You're right.
- We didn't just write things.
-  There is a story to it.
Ji Hyo was clever enough to use longer terms for everything.
- We won using such methods.
-  Of course.
- Take the puzzle pieces.
-  Right now...
They will provide the most important hints for the final mission.
(What is the purpose of these puzzle pieces?)
It must be a map.
What's this?
(They must gather all the pieces to escape from the dark!)
- I saw it.
-  It works.
(Running Man's 300th Episode Celebratory Dinner)
This is amazing.
Seok Jin, you did a good job for the past 300 episodes.
- Why are you saying that?
-  You're here on the 300th episode.
You wanted to quit in the middle.
Yes, that's right. I only said it to the producer, but...
apparently he talked about it with the entire world.
- Was it around episode 42?
-  It was earlier than that.
- It was around episode 30.
-  What are you talking about?
It was around episode 20 something.
I called Jae Seok every day and told him that I wanted to quit.
- Seok Jin, really...
-  He drank and cried a lot then.
I used to do that.
I tried so hard to stop him.
Gosh, I regret it.
- Gosh.
-  We did so much for him.
In celebration of the 300th episode,
- we prepared a feast.
-  They must cherish us.
The third mission is...
(It's time for the third mission.)
It's 7 versus 300...
bowls.
(300th Episode Special: "300 Bowls")
"300 Bowls".
- What?
-  Bowls.
The Running Man members who have been running for 300 episodes...
- will compete against seven...
-  The cameramen?
- The cameramen?
-  cameramen who always assist you.
On the table,
- there are 300 different dishes.
-  We can't finish that.
- We're at a disadvantage.
-  We lost.
- You will eat as much as you can.
-  You have to be considerate.
When you can't eat any more, the next person will take over.
- We have to eat as much as we can.
-  Is that right?
- Jong Kook doesn't eat anything.
-  He's such a picky eater.
I can eat a lot, but the kind of food is the problem.
- Cameramen, please come on out.
-  I can eat a lot.
Look at them. Look how big they are.
Are they really the cameramen?
- They eat so well.
-  Actually,
the cameramen have been...
- working with us for 300 episodes.
-  That's right.
Right. The ones here...
- They've been here from the start.
-  Most of them have.
They've been working hard with us.
They sometimes make us get busted.
Thanks to Kwon Ryeol, I always found you.
(All about Running Man's cameramen)
I know.
(For the Running Man cameramen, filming is the basic of the basics.)
(They experience horror and fall down with the members.)
(They are cameramen, but they are required to play games well, too.)
(Or else, they'll be scolded by the members.)
(It's very tough to be a cameraman for Running Man.)
- I know.
-  You're right.
Since it's the 300th episode,
let's hear how they feel.
Can you honestly tell us what you don't like about me?
- Anything?
-  I don't have anything.
- It's okay to be honest.
-  It's okay.
- It's okay. Say it.
-  Be honest.
He still complains about what I said about him last time.
- He always bears a grudge.
-  He bears a grudge.
He always bears a grudge.
I deserve to get kicked.
You should kick me once.
- Treat him nicely.
-  Gosh.
- Anything you want to say?
-  This is a dream job for him.
- Please be honest.
-  He went home early at the start.
- Tell us your honest opinion.
-  Many people are mistaken.
- About what?
-  That my work is easy.
But actually, he's the one who won second place most frequently.
He lasts until the end for no good reason.
(He lasts long for no good reason.)
- He can't win.
-  And his parts don't get aired.
And he's not funny.
His parts don't get aired, and he's not funny.
- He works hard to film you.
-  But it's all meaningless.
His work doesn't get used.
I understand.
Anyway, they eat really well.
Like I said, you currently have zero money.
It's because we failed the "3,000 Dollars" mission.
- It's frustrating.
-  So if Team Running Man loses,
- I prepared a card machine.
-  What?
If your team loses, one of you will swipe your credit card.
How much is the total?
- One person will pay for it.
-  We're paying for this food.
Ready!
(They get ready for the game.)
(The team that eats more food within the given time wins.)
Ready and go.
- I...
-  He loves jelly.
- He loves that.
-  Haha really loves that.
- Mix it all and eat it.
-  Hurry up.
You can eat as much as you can.
He's very serious.
Why are you so relaxed?
Just put it in your mouth first.
- Just swallow it.
-  I think you should...
- go to the next dish while chewing.
-  Yoo Seok is good.
How can he be so relaxed?
Yoo Seok is very relaxed.
(This place has good food.)
- He's a true foodie.
-  He eats so well.
People like him last long.
- Come on.
-  Hey.
Be careful with those marshmallows.
Haha loves marshmallows.
(Marshmallows take long to swallow.)
It takes long to chew those.
(But Haha doesn't hesitate to eat them.)
You're winning right now.
How would it taste to eat cucumber kimchi with candy?
- It must be terrible.
-  Why did they arrange it that way?
- That's a macaron.
-  He eats so well.
- You can do well, too.
-  He finished 20 dishes.
(Yoo Seok finishes with the cucumber kimchi.)
(Haha's cameraman, Seong Yong, goes next.)
What is he doing?
Yoo Seok is already out.
- He's eating the candy.
-  They are very slow.
We shouldn't eat too much in the beginning.
- Pass it to the next person.
-  Right.
Your turn will come back.
- You should eat what you can.
-  Let's change.
- Eat what you can eat.
-  Kwang Soo. That's right.
Kwang Soo eats well.
- We might win. We never know.
-  We are winning.
- They eat a lot, but they're slow.
-  Why are they so slow?
- What's this?
-  It's garlic.
It's a grape. No, it's a raw garlic clove.
Just swallow it.
- Just swallow it.
-  Don't. It will smell all day.
- Eat it.
-  Just chew it. That's better.
(Garlic sterilises and has an anti-bacterial effect.)
Gosh, you can smell it.
Kwang Soo usually stores food in his cheeks like a squirrel.
- It's all right.
-  Nice. His cheeks are fat.
He's unbelievable.
If you can't eat, switch.
- Switch.
-  This is salted fish.
Do you have to eat all of this?
- Pass it to him.
-  Do I need to eat flour?
- Do I need to eat flour?
-  You have to eat it!
- You have to eat that!
-  You can't not eat it!
What are you talking about?
What are you doing?
(Seong Yong is out and Ji Hyo's cameraman, Si Yeon, enters.)
Swallow it. Nice.
- How many did you finish?
-  Just shove it in your mouth.
- Come on.
-  Hurry up.
- That's it.
-  Good job.
They caught up.
Seok Jin, they caught up with us!
- Hurry up!
-  Just shove it in your mouth!
Flip the plates!
If you can't eat, switch.
(There's still a long way to go.)
We are only two plates faster.
Just put it in your mouth. Focus.
- Gosh.
-  You didn't even eat so much!
- What is this?
-  It was enough.
- Gosh, Jong Kook is amazing.
-  Go, Jong Kook!
It's been such a long time since Jong Kook has...
- eaten food like that.
-  It's been a long time.
I can't believe it.
They put so much butter in this.
Just eat it. Gosh.
My goodness!
Do you know how many of those we eat every day?
Jong Kook, are you doing that chewing-for-30-seconds thing?
(Jong Kook is chewing for 30 seconds.)
Are you eating for your health right now?
- Are you?
-  He takes 30 seconds to chew.
Next is Ji Hyo.
- Flip the plate.
-  She's not a big eater.
- But she's eating very well.
-  Good job.
- That's it.
-  Mix them together...
- like bibimbap.
-  That looks delicious.
- That's like bibimbap.
-  You should enjoy it.
- Bravo.
-  Good job.
You should eat two plates at a time.
(He doesn't even bother using chopsticks.)
- It's like you're eating sushi.
-  Hey!
- Look at him.
-  He's crazy.
He's unbelievable.
He combines several plates and eats it in one bite.
- Gosh, what's up with him?
-  We have to focus!
- Look at him.
-  Is it my turn already?
They caught up.
- They did.
-  It's curry rice.
Good. You have to add water.
- I can't put water in it.
-  Eat it.
(Jae Seok chases them fiercely.)
There's ginger, too.
There's ginger and onion.
(Ginger and onion await Jae Seok.)
Eat the onion with bread.
That's going to be delicious. There's sauce, too.
Hey.
(Finally, they are halfway done.)
- Go!
-  Hurry up.
- Who's next?
-  I had kimchi.
(Everyone is reaching their limit.)
Just put it in your mouth and swallow it.
Stuff the bread in.
You must hurry. They are on their 160th plate.
Seok Jin, hurry up and eat that muffin.
Just put it in your mouth.
It's not an ordinary muffin. It's a chocolate muffin.
- Look.
-  Eat that muffin.
Are you crazy?
- Hurry up!
-  Eat that muffin!
- Just put it in your mouth.
-  Quickly!
I have two chocolates to eat!
Hurry.
(Delicious)
- Hurry up, Seok Jin.
-  Quick.
- He's done.
-  All right. He's finished.
My goodness.
(Jong Kook really hates chocolate.)
Hurry up. Eat it.
What am I eating?
Hurry. Kwon Ryeol is eating so fast.
(Finally, the man has arrived.)
(Cameraman Kwon Ryeol devours food like a black hole.)
We have a time limit.
Swap after you put food in your mouth. You can swallow it later.
Hurry up, Seok Jin! You must eat faster!
Seok Jin!
- Hurry up and eat!
-  Just switch.
- Seok Jin, it's your turn.
-  I can't eat any more.
Let's swap. Quick.
Let's swap, Seok Jin.
My goodness.
What is this? More. Eat more.
(7 Running Man members vs Cameraman Kwon Ryeol)
- Go on, go on.
-  Go, go, go.
Just put it in your mouth. Put it in.
(206 plates for Team Cameramen, 203 plates for Team Running Man)
- You're next, Seok Jin.
-  We're on the 207th dish.
Jong Kook and Kwang Soo. Eat quickly.
Swap quickly. Hurry.
(They are close to the time limit.)
- Hurry up.
-  I can't eat more.
- Didn't you swallow the muffin yet?
-  Is that it?
Wait.
What's the number?
221.
(Team Running Man finished 221 plates.)
(What about Team Cameramen?)
(In order to win, Team Cameramen should eat at least 222 bowls.)
226.
(They finished 226 plates.)
My gosh.
(Team Cameramen wins.)
It was tough.
Is it over?
They tried so hard.
Oh, man.
Please come over here. Will you?
What should we do now?
- Who's paying?
-  If we spared 1,500 dollars before,
we could've paid it all easily.
- You're right.
-  I'm not joking...
- You're so weird. Don't you agree?
-  Why?
- You did so badly before.
-  If you spared 1,500 dollars...
If you spared 1,500 dollars, then we'd be able to pay for this.
It's 1,140 dollars in total.
- No way.
-  Are you serious?
- What are you talking about?
-  That's too expensive.
Jong Kook really hates paying through the nose.
He has been like this for several years.
Jong Kook never pays through the nose.
I really don't.
- You can choose one person to pay.
-  To pay 1,140 dollars?
Yes. Here's the invoice.
- Then...
-  Only one person?
- Should we roll the dice?
-  How about this?
Let's write the amount to pay...
- on seven pieces of paper.
-  For each person?
- I see.
-  It must be fun.
That sounds good.
- Like, "Pay zero dollars?"
-  Yes, exactly.
I'll first write 1,000 dollars.
- Okay.
-  That's good.
- 100 dollars for the second one.
-  100 dollars sounds good.
30 dollars.
Let's make the next one seven dollars. It'll be annoying.
- You have to pay for what you get.
-  I will pay up to seven dollars.
- I'll pay up to 30 dollars.
-  Write "Dance" on one of them.
- The person who gets this...
-  You'll dance in joy if you get it.
- must dance.
-  Dancing time.
(Should I pay or just dance?)
(I can dance many times if I don't have to pay.)
Please! I want to dance!
- He's practising.
-  Let's make some room.
- Please step back a bit.
-  My note is folded so finely.
This means it's one of the first to be folded.
- Mine is folded tightly, too.
-  Why don't you open it first, Haha?
1,000 dollars. 1,000 dollars.
(Haha reveals his note, first.)
- 1,000 dollars. 1,000 dollars.
-  In 1, 2, 3.
(How much will Haha pay?)
- It's 30 dollars.
-  30 dollars? It's okay.
Yes. I like it.
- 30 dollars sounds all right.
-  30 dollars.
30 dollars? Thank you so much.
30 dollars. Thank you.
- It's Gary's turn.
-  I hope it's 1,000 dollars.
- 1,000 dollars. 1,000 dollars.
-  I think I'll pay 1,000 dollars.
-  Okay, Gary. In 1, 2, 3.
- It's three dollars.
-  Oh my goodness.
Three!
- It's three dollars.
-  Oh my goodness.
I don't need to dance.
You're so lucky to pay only three dollars.
It's your turn, Ji Hyo.
Please play the music with no haste if the note shows dance.
- One,
-  1,000 dollars.
- two...
-  You can pay this time, Ji Hyo.
(Ji Hyo is one of the luckiest members. How much will she pay?)
(Dance)
(Dancing in joy)
(Same dance for the past 300 episodes)
It means...
- These four people.
-  two won't pay any and...
one person will pay 1,000 dollars and another will pay 100 dollars.
We are really lucky.
- You are really lucky.
-  They really are.
- You guys are so unlucky.
-  Gosh.
We have three unlucky people on this side.
- Anyway...
-  How can it turn out like this?
- It's driving me mad.
-  Anyway,
- Jong Kook is rather lucky.
-  Will you open up first?
Please open it first.
- I have a bad feeling about this.
-  1,000 dollars.
- We have unlucky Kwang Soo, too.
-  If he has to pay 1,000 dollars,
- it will be amazing.
-  I may be the unlucky one today.
- Go, Jong Kook.
-  Please.
I wish you'd pay 1,000 dollars, Jong Kook.
He's unlucky for these kind of games.
- Jong Kook, pay 1,000 dollars.
-  Please.
Here's 1,000 dollars.
(Not this time,)
(please.)
- Here.
-  1,000 dollars.
(Jong Kook will pay 1,000 dollars.)
(Jackpot!)
Poor Jong Kook.
(It's okay, as long as it's not me.)
Jong Kook.
(Jong Kook is the new unluckiest person in the group.)
- Poor Jong Kook.
-  How can this be?
(Why did luck turn its back on me?)
He even ate all the food that he doesn't normally eat.
- Jong Kook.
-  The big guy of the party.
He finally...
- got a new nickname in six years.
-  When I...
- picked it up, I had a bad feeling.
-  Gosh.
- Jong Kook.
-  Jong Kook pays big for the party.
Jong Kook always pays big amounts.
(He had to pay for a big staff party last year.)
- Jong Kook is so generous.
-  Jong Kook is the big guy.
- All right. It's the three of us.
-  I can open it happily now.
- 100 dollars is not small.
-  One of us have to pay 100 dollars.
- 100 dollars is not a small amount.
-  It's not small.
In 1, 2, 3.
Kwang Soo first.
What's your guess?
You can exchange your notes.
- You can.
-  I want to change.
Fold it again, first.
- Okay.
-  Exchange your notes.
- Okay, I will.
-  Do you think I should?
- I read it on your face.
-  Okay.
- Let's exchange.
-  I read his facial expression.
- One...
-  Swap again.
Open them up first before you swap your notes. Let us see.
- In 1, 2, 3.
-  In 1, 2, 3.
- Goodness. Wait.
-  Let's swap again.
Exchange your notes. This is your last chance.
- Okay.
-  This is the last time.
(They are all happy and swapping notes again.)
- All right.
-  Let's go.
- In 1, 2, 3.
-  In 1, 2, 3.
(How much will they pay in the end?)
(Kwang Soo will pay 100 dollars, and Seok Jin will pay 7 dollars.)
Look at your notes.
Yes!
- Kwang Soo got 100 dollars.
-  I only have to pay 7 dollars.
This wasn't even what I had at first.
- Who was holding that memo first?
-  Look. I'm free.
- Was I?
-  I got zero dollars.
Congratulations, Jong Kook.
100 dollars is not cheap, but he has to pay 1,000 dollars.
You're amazing, Jong Kook.
He's the big guy.
(Thank you, Jong Kook.)
It's so hard to win.
It's impossible to win against the cameramen.
- It was sweet, salty and spicy.
-  By the way,
it was so nice to see Jong Kook eating cheese.
I've never seen him eating cheese before.
I don't eat cheese that often because of the fat.
- I've never seen it before.
-  It was my first time.
Why did I have to eat so many chocolates?
Doesn't it feel great to see Jong Kook paying 1,000 dollars?
I feel so relieved because there are many unlucky people here.
- Jong Kook always pay big.
-  The big ones.
- Large-scale.
-  The expensive ones.
He usually ends up paying around 1,000 dollars or more.
- Jong Kook, you're just a big guy.
-  A big guy.
You're a big guy, and...
- He usually gets small penalties.
-  You're right.
Do you remember this place?
We crossed that river.
- Yes, I do.
-  You're right.
We have so many memories everywhere in Seoul.
We were there with university students on a cold, winter day.
I never thought that I'd ever go into that river in my lifetime.
- I never imagined it before.
-  But we all went into the river.
- In the middle of winter.
-  Back then,
I couldn't stop laughing.
- I kept laughing.
-  It was really difficult.
- I fell into the river.
-  It was so cold.
You could tell it was cold from everyone's facial expressions.
Are there 300 boxes out there?
(What are those boxes out there?)
Why so many?
- Gosh.
-  This is amazing.
- What is that?
-  What is that for?
Didn't we once play Jenga with boxes and ruin everything?
We did. Ji Hyo climbed up at the time.
- What are these?
-  What's going on?
(There are boxes everywhere. What is this mission about?)
There are so many boxes.
This is your fourth mission.
Gary, can you please push that question mark over there?
- Go, Gary.
-  Gary.
(Anticipating)
- 7 versus...
-  It must be 300 boxes.
- Boxes.
-  "300 Boxes".
"300 Boxes"?
What is that about?
We have special guests for this mission.
Really?
- There's a car.
-  Do we have guests?
I think they'll be bodyguards.
Judging from that car...
- Idol group members?
-  Maybe they are bodyguards.
They must be idol group members.
- TWICE?
-  TWICE sounds nice.
I think they're bodyguards.
- They're men.
-  Maybe I.O.I?
(The car looks out of the ordinary. Please show us who you are.)
- They're guys.
-  They are not female idols.
- Who is it?
-  They're coming out.
(They are watching with great expectation.)
(BTS is here for Running Man's 300th special mission.)
They're BTS.
- Look, that's Jimin.
-  Are they BTS?
- Yes, they are BTS.
-  Welcome, BTS.
Nice to see you!
- Yes.
-  It's so unexpected.
(A talented and popular idol group with many fans.)
(All the members of BTS have come to Running Man.)
I didn't know that BTS would be here today.
(They begin with a powerful dance.)
(They are warming up with their dance.)
- Their dance is so powerful.
-  Go harder.
(Are you ready to play?)
Dance harder, will you?
(This is how young idols dance together in a group.)
- They are dancing exactly the same.
-  That's amazing.
(It's a powerful dance.)
(Wriggling)
- They are great.
-  You can't not like them.
Wow, BTS.
(That was marvellous.)
You're on fire.
- How can I not like you?
-  You're so good.
- You guys are great.
-  I really loved...
when Rap Monster acted...
like this in the end.
That's it. It looks so nice.
I should learn those moves.
I should learn it so I can do it myself.
(He distorts his face.)
How can you look so different with the same facial expression as his?
(Same face, different feeling)
That's why I must learn.
Should I bite my lower lip?
You all have your own...
special gestures.
You have your own special gestures just like him.
- We will show you one by one.
-  Show us, please.
Okay. Please show us.
(The lesson starts.)
All right, V!
Wow.
This is it!
Do I do it like this?
(Gary counterattacks with his ugly dance moves.)
Jungkook.
Look at him.
Jong Kook, show us the old version of that dance.
- Why?
-  You know the old version.
- Why should I?
-  Come on.
- It goes like this.
-  Please...
- show us some old dances.
-  Like this.
- This one.
-  I can't do this alone.
- What?
-  I need one more person.
- Haha, do it.
-  Come with me.
Dance like old idol groups.
- Okay.
-  Show us some old dances.
(We'll show you something you have never imagined.)
(Turbo's Jong Kook has a charismatic aura.)
Come to the middle. Let's dance.
In 1, 2, 3.
I'll kneel in front later.
(Two ugly guys side by side)
Show us old ones.
(Jong Kook and his ugly boys)
(They dance seriously with passion.)
You all dance differently.
(We're here to give you energy.)
- In 1, 2, 3!
-  In 1, 2, 3.
(Three!)
(Here we go!)
(This is what we call retro swag.)
Did you guys see?
That's it.
- We won.
-  You did great.
- We did it like this.
-  Right.
What about this one?
- That's it.
-  That was so nice.
I liked the old ones.
So what should we do with BTS?
- Right.
-  The fourth mission...
is to move 300 boxes with...
BTS.
- 300 boxes?
-  So we should carry them.
- There are 300 boxes of ramyeon.
-  Yes.
You should use the handcart that has your team's initial on it...
to move as many boxes as possible to your team's truck.
Those who move more boxes will win.
If you win, we'll donate the boxes you carried in your names.
So please do your best.
What if we lose? Do we have to pay money again?
(If we lose, do we have to pay money again?)
- Let's stop paying.
-  If you lose...
- Let's do it again.
-  No, let's stop.
If you lose, you must donate extra ramyeon which will be...
the same amount as the originally donated ramyeon.
- I see.
-  We have to...
You have to win in order to get another puzzle piece.
- We only have one piece.
-  But at the moment,
you've obtained only one piece so far.
- Please go to the start line.
-  Okay.
Let's go.
Guys, let's do it seriously.
- We can do it!
-  Don't grab here. It's heavier.
Okay.
- Let's go for it.
-  You won't be able to win easily.
- Let's do it.
-  I look forward to a nice game.
Let's carry those first.
(Will the members with a lot of experience win?)
(Or will young BTS win?)
(They'll load boxes in five spots and carry them to their trucks.)
(Each team has their own truck.)
Ready...
Let's go!
(The race has begun.)
(Run!)
- Gosh.
-  They're so fast.
Goodness, they're so fast.
They run really fast.
Hey, get out!
(He takes boxes even before the handcart arrives.)
Get out, get out.
(He doesn't wait for the handcart, but runs to the truck right away.)
Just take it there.
(BTS has 3 boxes and Running Man has 0.)
Hey, get out!
(BTS's handcart is going really fast.)
(Their strategy is to move as many as possible at once.)
Won't they fall?
Is it enough?
Go first.
(J-Hope pushes the cart with 10 boxes.)
This is heavier than I thought.
Get out of the way.
Gosh!
(Cheating expert, Kwang Soo, attacks the cart.)
Stop it!
(They hug Kwang Soo.)
Stop him.
Hey, take boxes from them!
(Jimin and V hold onto Kwang Soo.)
- We have to take their boxes!
-  No!
- Hurry!
-  We have to protect ours!
(BTS members are loading the cart.)
(But their cart suddenly leaves.)
Seok Jin!
(Thief, Seok Jin, shows up.)
Seok Jin! No!
(Jin struggles against Seok Jin.)
Seok Jin, that's our ramyeon.
- That's ours.
-  Seok Jin, stop!
Let's try again. These are ours.
What's this?
These aren't ours.
What's going on?
Gosh, this is so difficult.
(Jung Kook attacks Running Man's cart.)
Hey! Hey, hey!
(Jung Kook interrupts Jae Seok and Seok Jin.)
(Haha counterattacks immediately.)
Hey, come here.
- Gosh.
-  No!
(Thanks to Haha's defence, Jae Seok runs away.)
- This is really hard.
-  Hey!
- Why are they so fast?
-  Gosh, get out.
- Hey! Stop.
-  These aren't yours.
These are ours.
Jae Seok!
(Jae Seok loads the truck, but...)
Thank you, Jae Seok.
(Thanks, Jae Seok.)
Isn't this truck ours?
No, it's not!
Thank you, Jae Seok.
(BTS: 28, Running Man: 14)
Why are they so competitive?
They always work hard.
(A BTS member even attacks Running Man's truck.)
Stop!
I can't move!
Jong Kook!
Just get him.
Where's the cart?
(Jimin even rides on Kwang Soo's back.)
(Jimin marks Kwang Soo up close.)
Gosh, take this.
I am almost there.
(Out of breath)
(Every step Kwang Soo takes is extremely difficult.)
I want to take their boxes away!
I want to interrupt them!
(He wants to interrupt them.)
(Kwang Soo...)
(is well known to be a cheating expert.)
(But now, he desperately wants to...)
(freely interrupt BTS.)
(He wants to be free like a butterfly.)
(But he is caught by Jimin.)
Hey!
You're on your own.
(Kwang Soo, you'd better give up now.)
Hey! Stop them!
- Is it ours?
-  Yes.
I can't stand it any more.
(He can't stand it.)
That's it.
(Jong Kook is angry.)
(He holds Suga and Jung Kook at once.)
Hurry up, now!
Hey, get him now!
(The BTS members are knocked down.)
Please, stop.
- Gosh.
-  Jong Kook, help me.
Go on!
(Jong Kook separates Jimin from Kwang Soo with his hand.)
(Jong Kook ties down three boys on his own.)
- Good.
-  Go!
(He has taken care of 3 BTS members.)
- What's going on here?
-  What is this?
- What's happening here?
-  Gosh.
- Please, let me go.
-  I want to get out.
Please, let me go!
The Running Man team carried 62 boxes so far.
Let's go.
(Running Man member caught up to BTS.)
There's nothing on it. Why are you carrying it?
(Haha's interception)
(Running Man members are doing their best to get a puzzle piece.)
This is it. Stop them.
- Gary, please don't.
-  Let me have just one.
- If you win rock, paper, scissors.
-  Okay.
- Rock, paper...
-  Gary!
(Running away)
Gary! Gary!
Gary!
This is the last one.
(The Running Man team makes a final sprint.)
(The game is over.)
You did well.
- Good job.
-  Good work.
- You did well.
-  Great job.
- Good job.
-  Thanks.
Everyone did a good job.
(The 7 vs 300 Boxes game is over.)
This special is so hard.
Let me announce the result.
It's 157 boxes to 143 boxes.
(157 to 143)
(The Running Man team should beat BTS...)
(in order to obtain the puzzle needed for the final mission.)
(Who will be the winner?)
BTS won.
(BTS won!)
We made it!
(They failed to get a puzzle piece in this round.)
We were fired up!
As the Running Man members lost,
you should pay for another 300 boxes of ramyeon to donate.
- Sure.
-  Good.
Let's play the game of luck.
Again?
Do you want to play the game of luck?
- Divide the number of boxes.
-  Let's divide the number of boxes.
- Donation is a good thing.
-  It is...
- This...
-  It's good to be chosen.
It is a nice thing to be the one who pays for ramyeon.
We should smile happily.
- Let's make it 250 boxes.
-  That's a good idea.
(Someone must pay for 250 boxes.)
- It's a happy deed.
-  How much is 250 boxes of ramyeon?
- That wouldn't be that much.
-  It won't be expensive.
- Let's make it 250 boxes and...
-  Is it 500 dollars?
It's 5,000 dollars.
(5,000 dollars)
- 5,000 dollars for 250 boxes?
-  Really?
(Did you just say 5,000 dollars?)
What? 5,000 dollars?
- Really?
-  5,000 dollars?
- Let's make it 200 boxes then.
-  5,000 dollars!
- 5,000 dollars!
-  Let's make it 200 boxes.
- All right.
-  I'm nervous.
That's a lot of money.
How many boxes will we buy other than 250 boxes?
There will be 200, 50, 30, 15 and...
- Five. If you get none, you dance.
-  Five, and dance if you get none.
- That's right.
-  I'll be glad to dance.
- Let's step back.
-  Oh, please.
Then, BTS members will pick a random card...
- for us.
-  All right.
- I want Jungkook to pick mine.
-  Okay.
- Good.
- I want Rap Monster.
-  Okay.
(The random donation starts.)
- Let's do it together.
-  Go for it.
(Suga is the first to choose.)
- Okay.
-  Where's Jimin?
- Pick one with your own pose.
-  Give it to her right away.
- Do your own pose.
-  With your pose.
This is for you.
(How many boxes will Ji Hyo have to pay for?)
Next is Jin.
- Okay, Jin.
-  Dance for us.
Show us something before you give it to him.
- Great.
-  That's it.
- Good.
-  That's right.
Great.
Look at V. He's tired.
He looks like he doesn't want to do this.
- Please, just take it.
-  He's tired.
We didn't see enough of your dance.
- Gosh.
-  J-Hope is tired of waiting.
Next is J-Hope!
(What card will Haha have?)
- J-Hope!
-  You're good!
(Jumping)
(J-Hope delivers Jae Seok's card right away with Jae Seok's dance.)
Next.
- Rap Monster!
-  Yes!
- Who is it?
-  Gary.
- Gary.
-  You guys look alike.
(Rap Monster brings Gary a card.)
Let's go.
(Bang!)
(Jungkook gives a card to Jong Kook.)
Thank you. Thanks.
This is...
Jimin, you can do it!
(The last one is Jimin.)
Take it out from your back.
Kwang Soo, take the card.
- What if that's 200 boxes?
-  Now...
(Each member has a card for the donation.)
Let's find out what our cards say.
- Shall I go first?
-  Who should go first?
- Haha will go first.
-  Okay.
Please show us your card.
Oh, please.
- In 3, 2, 1.
-  200 boxes. 200 boxes.
(Will he have the honour of paying for 200 boxes?)
(What will Haha's card say?)
50 boxes.
(Haha gets 50 boxes.)
50 boxes is a vague number.
Congratulations.
- You get to donate.
-  Your donation is unnoticeable.
- Congratulations.
-  Congratulations.
But everybody,
that means one of you has to donate 200 boxes.
Gary's next.
- 200.
-  In 1, 2, 3.
(Dance!)
- "Dance".
-  "Dance".
Oh my goodness!
(Oh, no!)
Dance! With you!
That's amazing.
(Gary and Rap Monster share a strong chemistry.)
You're on fire!
- "Dance".
-  I'm envious.
Gary and Ji Hyo are so lucky.
- Ji Hyo.
-  Choose 200.
- 200.
-  You might get 200.
- Suga.
-  There might be a twist.
- Let's make it special.
-  It's about time.
(What will be Ji Hyo's fate?)
- Three.
-  It's about time.
(She gets 15 boxes.)
- 15.
-  It's not 200.
200 is still left.
It's you guys again.
- It's the unlucky ones again.
-  Jong Kook, do you want to switch?
- Should we switch?
-  Jong Kook.
- Do you want to go first?
-  Jong Kook!
- I'm getting hopeful.
-  He got shot earlier.
- You're born with bad luck.
-  It's the same even...
- if it was chosen by other people.
-  That's strange.
(There are 200, 30, 5 and 0 boxes left.)
- Let's go with Jong Kook first.
-  200.
We have bad luck, but he always picks the large numbers.
- Is that right?
-  I hope it's 200.
- It's for a good cause.
-  In 1, 2, 3.
(Will Jong Kook get 200 boxes?)
(Or will he be the lucky one to get 0 boxes?)
In 1, 2, 3.
(Wow!)
Two, three.
(He gets 0 boxes.)
- Why?
-  What is it?
- That's amazing.
-  Good job.
That's so amazing.
(Jong Kook gets 0 boxes.)
It's all or nothing now.
It's all or nothing, guys.
It's us again.
Do you want to switch like before?
- Do you want to?
-  I don't want to.
Do you want to see it and then switch?
- You can't react to it.
-  You can't.
You must not show any reactions.
- Let's open it up.
-  200 boxes!
Please give us music.
- In 1, 2, 3.
-  Two, three.
(They'll reveal their cards first.)
(Who has chosen 200 boxes?)
- Two, three.
-  Two, three.
(It is Kwang Soo.)
Close them.
Do you want to switch or not?
- Switch!
-  Dance, everybody.
- Let's go.
-  Dance.
- Come on.
-  Switch with whomever you want.
(They're looking for the right time to switch cards.)
- Are you on your own?
-  Switch now.
- Did you come on your own?
-  Yes.
- Would you like to switch?
-  No way.
No way.
Why aren't you switching with me?
Let's switch, Seok Jin.
- Let's switch.
-  Yes!
- Yes.
-  There you go.
(Seok Jin and Kwang Soo switch cards.)
- Shall we switch?
-  Should we reveal our cards?
- Should we reveal them?
-  Once again?
- Three.
-  Three.
(Seok Jin has 200 boxes.)
- Should we go again?
-  Let's go again.
Okay!
(Let's shake it up!)
Let's dance.
We can switch once we agree on it.
(They don't know what their future holds.)
Jae Seok, let's switch.
He wants to switch.
(He makes a gesture toward Jae Seok.)
(He takes the bait.)
- Would you like to switch with me?
-  Switch again.
(Shall I switch again?)
(This will change their destiny.)
(What will become of these two?)
(There you go!)
I have a good feeling.
(Jae Seok and Kwang Soo switch cards.)
(Kwang Soo is oblivious.)
That's it.
Whoever has 200 boxes, just dance along.
- This is exciting.
-  It's good.
This is fun.
Everybody, this is for a good cause.
- That's right.
-  Of course.
- This is for donation.
-  That's right.
We must send these off...
- willingly.
-  If you get picked,
you need to send these off with a smile.
If you get picked, how would you celebrate it?
- Pardon? I will passionately...
-  I will dance passionately.
- pour water over my head.
-  Me, too.
You have to act happy, okay?
(He's getting ready.)
- Get the water ready.
-  This will be interesting.
- Let's go.
-  One,
two, three.
(Congratulations, Kwang Soo!)
Can we see it?
(What's this?)
(Kwang Soo gets 200 boxes.)
(Flapping)
(He's full of joy.)
200 boxes, 200 boxes
5,000 dollars and 200 boxes
- Good job.
-  He's funny.
Good job, Kwang Soo.
You're the unluckiest person.
You're the most unlucky one.
- You're the most unlucky.
-  You're unbeatable.
- Who had it in the beginning?
-  I...
- Kwang Soo.
-  I switched with him in the end.
It was his from the beginning.
Was it his from the beginning? I switched with him in the end.
He took it back.
(Kwang Soo had 200 boxes in the beginning.)
(He gave it to Seok Jin, and it moved onto Jae Seok.)
(It went around and came back to him.)
I have a good feeling.
Jimin, why are you doing this to me all day?
I'm so envious. I should have kept the card.
- It's for a good cause.
-  Are you sure?
- This is for real.
-  You took it back.
- Sure.
-  I should have had it.
- Are you sad about it?
-  All right.
Shall we move on?
- Thank you for your hard work.
-  Thank you.
Thank you all.
- Good work.
-  Thank you.
(What's the next game that awaits them?)
- Thank you.
-  Good work. See you later.
We only got one puzzle piece.
We should have at least one more.
- We need one more.
-  We need another piece.
- We don't have enough.
-  The opponents were too strong.
- The cameramen were strong.
-  We can't beat them.
What will we do now? What do we have left?
- The box game, too.
-  Wouldn't it have...
something to do with 300 people?
We haven't had a game with 300 people yet.
- Ripping name tags.
-  We can't do that with 300 people.
- We'll be worn out.
-  Is there a game...
300 people can play?
- 300 people...
-  Whatever it may be,
- we can't win if it's 300 vs 7.
-  It's impossible.
- Whatever that might be.
-  What could it be?
- I think it'll be 300 people.
-  We can't do 300 versus 7.
We can't win if it's 300 versus 7.
We're near a university.
(It can't be 300 people, right?)
(Y University in Seodaemun-gu, Seoul)
(What awaits them here?)
(The atmosphere seems a bit unusual.)
- What's that?
-  What's going on?
- Are we starting right away?
-  Gosh, Kwang Soo.
(Noisy)
(As they approach the gymnasium, the noise gets louder.)
(What will be inside?)
(They exclaim as soon as they walk in.)
Look at this.
What's all this?
(What did they see?)
(Wow! They have goosebumps.)
(300 people stand in front of the Running Man members.)
This is...
(Overwhelmed)
There are actually 300 of them.
(300 university students)
(300 youths welcome Running Man.)
Wow, look.
(The gymnasium is getting heated up.)
(This is a very big-scale.)
Nice to meet you!
(Their hearts flutter for Running Man.)
This is too much.
- What do we do?
-  This is not possible.
We lost.
- This doesn't make any sense.
-  No way.
How do we beat this enthusiasm?
(They're stunned.)
(What game do they have to play?)
- This mission...
-  What is it?
(Please don't let it involve 300 people.)
It is 7 vs 300 people.
(Do the 7 of them have to beat 300 people?)
How could we go against 300?
- How's that possible?
-  We can't win.
- How can we win?
-  What do we do?
The only thing I have is that I'm older than them.
I can beat them with my age.
To start off,
the first person to face 300 people is...
(Please don't let it be me.)
- Yu Jae Seok.
-  Me?
(Jae Seok is chosen.)
Me? What do I do?
- Yu Jae Seok!
-  Yu Jae Seok!
This is the game Jae Seok is going to play.
- What is it?
-  The game you will play...
(This is the first game of their match.)
The game you will play is "Slap-Match".
I should have done this.
(Slap-Match)
Hold on.
How many people do I have to beat?
You'll place your game pieces on the floor,
- and Jae Seok will go first.
-  Maybe they're bad.
If it gets flipped, it's Jae Seok's win.
You have to get it in one try.
If I don't get it in one try, I'm in trouble.
- But there's a limit to that.
-  But I'm guessing these...
young students haven't played this game before.
- Have you played this before?
-  We have!
Have you?
(He didn't think they would have played it.)
Did you really?
(These young people have played slap-matches before.)
Gosh, I'm in trouble.
(Jae Seok is a strong player, but he has to face 300 people.)
(The 1st player appears.)
(He seems very relaxed.)
I will attack first.
(He's nervous.)
(300 people shout to support him.)
- Go, Player One!
-  Go, Jae Seok!
(And the 7 Running Man members start cheering loudly, too.)
(In front of 300 people, they rather look shabby.)
(We need to somehow forestall them.)
(Seok Jin pretends to give him a hug and rips his name tag.)
(This is Running Man!)
(Ripping)
(Don't you dare!)
(This is the spirit of youth.)
It hurts.
We can't beat them.
You should put yours down first.
They are unbelievable.
I have only one chance.
What if I lose immediately?
You will be fine. You won't lose immediately.
- Please beat at least one person.
-  He can do that.
Have you played this before?
- I played it when I was little.
-  How old were you?
I was in elementary school.
In elementary school?
- But even so...
-  Right.
That's the late 90s, right?
(He was in elementary school in the late 90s.)
- Right?
-  Right?
- Yes.
-  Was it in 2000s?
- Was it in the 2000s?
-  Yes.
It was already the 2000s when you were in elementary school?
- Yes. I was born in 1996.
-  Really?
- You were born in 1996?
-  In 1996?
You were born in 1996!
- 96...
-  Then...
- He was born in 1996.
1996?
I met my wife in 1997.
(If Seok Jin got married and had a son, his son would be his age.)
- You're okay, right?
-  Yes.
- Let's go!
-  Let's go!
- Beat him at once!
Go, Jae Seok!
- Go, Jae Seok!
-  Go, Player One!
(The 300 people's cheering is on a different scale.)
We are lovely from head to toe
(He sings Jong Kook's song.)
(What are you doing?)
What are you doing?
(He can dance to it, too.)
Jae Seok, please focus.
Here's the rule.
The game will continue until...
- Jae Seok loses.
-  You can do it.
- You are very good at it.
-  Yes.
It will get flipped no matter what.
(He never lost.)
(For the past 300 episodes, he's been the King of "Slap-Match".)
(He's the only man who can compete against 300 people.)
(Will he be able to create another legend today?)
It will get flipped no matter what.
- This is...
-  You get one chance.
It's so nerve-racking...
- to compete against 300 people.
-  Hey, you...
- They are all looking at me.
-  You are the king.
- I've never played it like this.
-  Jae Seok, you have...
to beat at least 50 people alone.
- You are the king.
-  You're good.
- You have to beat 50 people.
-  You can do it.
- This is not ridiculous.
-  You're the best player here.
You are the hero.
- You're the man.
-  You are the hero.
(He's pressured to compete against 300 people alone.)
(He will be in trouble if he fails on the first try.)
(He slaps the card...)
(with full power!)
(It flies...)
(but lands on the same side.)
(Jae Seok fails.)
(He's saved.)
It's Player One's turn now.
What do I do, Ji Hyo? I hit it too hard.
His name is Wan Seong.
(Using the interview as an excuse,)
(they step on the card to stop it from flipping easily.)
(They always think of ways to cheat.)
Gosh, you guys...
Hold on.
It will get flipped for sure.
Step back a little.
(They tease the young boy.)
We can't help it. We've been living like this our whole lives.
Anyway, we have to win.
Haha, step back.
- It's Wan Seong's turn.
-  Step back.
(He looks like a good player.)
You suck!
(You've played this before, haven't you?)
(Then it's time to play the mind games!)
Here we go.
(He slaps the card...)
(without any hesitation.)
(He's got power...)
(and perfect aiming!)
(The card flies in the air!)
(7 Running Men vs 300 university students)
(How will the competition end?)
(7 vs 300 Part 2)
We will be ripped and torn!
How can we beat them?
We lost.
(It's youth versus experience. They will bet everything they have.)
(A black cloud unfolded like an umbrella, and it was our turn.)
(Aren't you afraid? Every night, we were left alone. By Gi Hyeong Do)
(There is someone in this pitch darkness.)
Just tell us this.
Is it up there?
(People in the dark go after the Running Man members.)
(It's not over until it's over. Do not lose your guard.)
(300th Episode Special: 7 vs 300 Part 2)