- He's here.
-  It's Seung Joon.
He's my high school buddy, Lee Seung Joon.
Jae Seok had a girl that he dated for a long time.
She was tall and ugly.
- He's out of his mind.
-  He's Jae Seok's critic.
- Mother!
-  She's Jong Kook's mother.
- He's like a daughter.
-  Daughter?
He's the youngest son who is like a daughter.
He's like a daughter, isn't he?
(Witness Jong Kook acting cute.)
He's my role model.
(A disastrous audition takes place in front of the legendary singer.)
He gave me the dream of becoming a celebrity.
- Hello, Sir.
-  Hello.
Hurry up.
(A fierce race to find the Seven Loves begins now.)
Say, "Kwang Soo",
and Kwang Soo, please turn around while calling her name.
Kwang Soo!
(Hye Jin is Kwang Soo's first love. We will go meet her now.)
Several days ago,
we asked you guys about the unforgettable people in your life.
- Yes.
-  "I'm Sorry, I Love You" Special.
The second season is called Seven Loves.
(Seven Loves)
The person each of you chose is waiting for you somewhere.
You have to meet all seven of them within 12 hours,
complete a mission, take a picture and put it in the album...
in order to succeed.
- Hurry up!
-  Hello.
(Each member chose one person.)
(Find the Seven Loves)
(The mission begins.)
Gosh, it's been such a long time since I was here.
- Isn't your school around here?
-  It's Yongmoon High School.
Yongmoon High School is near Daehak-ro.
It's in Anam-dong.
Not much has changed around here.
- Really? Is it the same?
-  Yes.
It's almost the same. It hasn't changed much.
How long has it been since you last saw this person?
I'm not sure how long it has been exactly,
but it's almost 20 years after graduating high school.
- It must be so awkward.
-  It will be awkward.
But he's a celebrity, too. Why didn't you meet him?
I know. He just suddenly started coming out on TV.
You could contact him.
But at first, he appeared mostly on movies.
Just recently, I became convinced that it was really him.
(Who is Jae Seok's Love?)
He's really popular these days.
- Is that right?
-  Yes. I was really surprised.
I'm really curious about who he is.
We used to have a lot of fun together.
(Jae Seok.)
- It's not that I didn't like him.
-  You should come up with a story.
(Jae Seok, do you remember me?)
Hey!
(Hello, my friend.)
- Hey, Seung Joon!
-  Hello.
(Who is Jae Seok's best friend?)
- Hey, Seung Joon!
-  Hello.
You are Lee Seung Joon, right?
I am sorry. Are you okay?
You called me "brother" a while ago.
Did I?
Maybe I heard wrong.
If a pen stops working, you put saliva on it to make it work.
(The popular supporting actor, Lee Seung Joon, is here.)
I'll take this.
I just almost killed myself.
Dr Song, are you all right?
(Is he really Jae Seok's best friend?)
You are Seung Joon, right?
- Hey!
-  Welcome.
- Gosh...
-  He's in "Descendants of the Sun".
- He's in "Descendants of the Sun"!
-  Hello.
- You didn't know, right?
- Come here.
-  He's my buddy!
- Is he really your friend?
-  It's you, right?
But he's really awkward around you.
- Are you sure you're friends?
-  It's you, right?
You are Lee Seung Joon, my high school buddy.
- Buddy.
-  Hello, Jae Seok.
Did you hear his voice?
- It's so touching.
-  It's really touching.
See? Hey!
It's been such a long time. So it's really awkward.
- How long has it been?
-  About 20 years.
- About 20 years.
-  It's been 26 years.
We went to the same college, right?
I majored in theatre arts.
Right? And I majored in broadcasting and entertainment.
- It's you, right?
-  Did you graduate?
No, I didn't.
- He's really like a friend.
-  Then you are not alumni.
- That's what friends do to you.
-  We were thinking that...
the fact that you were so close but lost touch with each other...
- means that one of you did wrong.
-  Made a mistake.
- Did I upset you?
-  Or...
Even if they are awkward now, when time passes, they will...
- Right.
-  be like best friends again.
I don't know what it was. I don't remember, but...
are you still mad at me?
- It's been 26 years.
-  Let him speak!
He won't look at Jae Seok.
Please look at me. You're not looking at me.
- We were really close.
-  I feel so happy for them.
I always went to his place. Right?
We were close. He came to my place often.
When I first saw you on TV,
I doubted that it was you. But it was really you.
What's this?
- You will know when you open it.
-  Is it a report card?
They are report cards.
This is incredible. They brought all of these.
Seung Joon, this one is yours.
(He looks very smart. Was he a class president?)
- Oh, no.
-  Wait.
- You weren't a good student.
-  You had a C.
- I was really terrible at studying.
-  His grades were inconsistent.
- Let's check yours.
-  Wait.
- Gosh, my grades were...
-  How were your grades?
- I was 15th in my class.
-  You were okay.
- You were a good student.
-  Then you were really smart.
- He's a genius!
-  He was a genius.
- I'm not surprised.
-  Who did better than him?
He should be a member of Mensa.
In the first semester of sophomore year, I ranked 15th.
- Starting the second semester...
-  Your grades went down.
I ranked 46th in my class.
- You ranked 46th?
-  But you see,
I wasn't interested in studying, so I chose not to study.
But Jae Seok attended extra classes and studied hard.
He studied, but he still didn't do well.
He must've been with his girlfriend all the time.
- You used to go to Yonsei Academy.
-  How did you know that?
- Didn't you use to go there, too?
-  This is hilarious.
I didn't go there.
- He's like Jae Seok's critic.
-  He studied very hard.
- It's because...
-  And still, you were terrible.
Wait a minute.
(Jae Seok is flustered.)
- That's right.
-  He's funny, isn't he?
- I didn't have tutors either.
-  He's a critic.
- You changed a lot.
-  He's criticising Jae Seok.
He used to be very handsome.
- Seung Joon was...
-  He was very charming.
Seung Joon was like Park Ji Sung back in the days.
- There's an album, too.
-  I am here.
Why did you hang out with a person like him?
Jae Seok hasn't changed much.
- Yes, this is me.
-  How was Jae Seok in the past?
- He was really funny.
-  Was he funny?
- Is that right?
-  He was funny ever since.
He wasn't popular among girls, right?
- But he had good sense of humour.
-  Girls liked him at first...
- But did he obsess?
-  because he was funny.
But that's all.
- No, but...
-  I'm sure he didn't date back then.
- He dated girls.
-  Did he?
Jae Seok had a girl that he dated for a long time.
- We want to hear things like this.
-  We didn't know.
- We want to know everything.
-  This is it.
- Hey!
-  Stop it.
- Seung Joon.
-  We want to hear more.
- I am so curious.
-  No way.
- He's crazy.
-  Who was it?
We met again after 26 years.
I even remember her name and her school.
- Let's look for her.
-  Let's find her.
Don't say it. I will talk about your girlfriends, too.
- Was she pretty?
-  I will reveal your stories.
She was tall and ugly.
(Jae Seok's ideal type is a tall and ugly woman.)
- Hey.
-  She was just tall.
- But it's true.
-  He is...
- Hey.
-  She wasn't pretty.
He's unbelievable. Goodness.
Hey! Sure, she wasn't beautiful.
- She wasn't the prettiest, but...
-  His face turned red.
But she's still my ex-girlfriend.
- I'm sorry, but...
-  He called her "ugly".
He dated her for a long time.
He used to bring her with him when our friends hung out.
- I see.
-  I'm not surprised.
- How did he treat girls?
-  What was his style?
- Did he dress well?
-  I am really curious about that.
- Was he like Song Joong Ki?
-  She controlled him completely.
I knew it. He hasn't changed.
- It's always how we expected.
-  That's embarrassing.
That's why he sympathises with Kwang Soo.
- That's right. I feel like...
-  That's why he helps him.
you are a lot like me. That's why I tell you to confess your love.
- But I am not like the old you.
-  Hey!
I don't like tall and ugly women.
(Tall and ugly girls aren't my type.)
So he prefers...
- short women.
-  That is true.
I think he briefly dated a pretty girl...
- Really?
-  when he was in high school, no?
- You met a lot of girls.
-  Gosh.
- You're a playboy.
-  Goodness.
- I wasn't a playboy.
-  But his relationship...
didn't last a month.
I had a really hard time.
- After you broke up?
-  Yes.
Breaking up after one month is still painful.
Actually, although I dated her for a month,
I only met her once.
Are you sure you dated her?
That's not what we call a relationship.
You dated her alone.
Whenever I started seeing someone, I told all of my friends.
She just met you once and dumped you.
- We've all gone through dire times.
-  But I still don't...
- understand why she dumped me.
-  That's what he's been through.
- Seung Joon looks very handsome.
-  You're right.
Now I remember something.
- Were you like this as well?
-  Actually,
- Seung Joon...
-  No, I wasn't.
was adored a lot...
- amongst our friends.
-  Right.
We pinched your cheeks like this often.
We really did. Because he was cute.
What are you doing to him?
He is my friend!
(Seung Joon wipes his cheek.)
(Why are you doing this to me, Jae Seok?)
- You just hurt your friend.
-  Gosh.
- He didn't even...
-  Hey. He's my friend.
He didn't even appear on variety programmes before.
- It's his first time.
-  Is it?
- It is.
-  I see.
And you just pinched his cheek.
Because he was so cute. He was very cute at the time.
We met for the first time in 26 years, and you pinched my cheek.
(We met for the first time in 26 years.)
(Seung Joon is Jae Seok's critic.)
- Gosh.
-  We met...
- Hey, you're my old friend.
-  Here it is.
(It's my turn now.)
(You started this first.)
- Goodness.
-  How do you like that?
- Good job.
-  It feels so good.
(Seung Joon is like Jae Seok's enemy.)
(My friend, you are a talented entertainer.)
- I like it!
-  It's because they're friends.
- What a friendship.
-  Only friends can do such things.
I almost broke into tears.
- Why?
-  He always...
- Are you touched?
-  used to look at me like that...
when he was astounded. And I just saw that look.
- "How do you like that?"
-  "How do you like that?"
(Jae Seok is reminded of his old memories.)
Then why did you fight?
- This is so nice.
-  Goodness.
- Why did you fight, then?
-  You were so close.
Tell us why you fought.
It was on a weekend. We were at my place.
- I went to his house every weekend.
-  Please be quiet.
- I really...
-  I'm talking.
(He's lost for words.)
We went to my house after school.
(They were always together after school.)
- We were upset with each other.
-  Why?
- You don't remember why.
-  I don't remember the reason.
- So Jae Seok went home.
-  I see.
And a friend called me after two hours.
- He was one of our friends.
-  Okay.
(He received a phone call from one of their friends.)
He said, "Seung Joon, why are you home?"
So I said, "Why? What are you guys doing?"
He said, "We're all in Jongno. Why aren't you here?"
I told him that I didn't know about it.
And he said, "What are you talking about? Didn't Jae Seok tell you?
- So Jae Seok didn't tell you.
-  Really?
- Because he was upset.
-  He was mad at you.
- Jae Seok was upset.
-  So I got really mad.
(He was betrayed by Jae Seok.)
So I ran to Jongno.
- Did you run there?
-  I did.
- So he went to Jongno.
-  Gosh.
So he went to Jongno to see Jae Seok.
So I went there.
I was at a crosswalk, waiting for the green light.
- Will this be okay to talk about?
-  It's okay.
And I saw my friends across the street.
Immediately after the light changed colour, I ran toward them..
and gave a flying kick to Jae Seok.
Really?
- Really?
-  Did you hit me?
Goodness.
- You hit me.
-  It's too late, Jae Seok.
- It's been 26 years since then.
-  Gosh.
This is school violence!
This is school violence.
I'll kick you this time.
(It's my turn.)
The others were also very close friends.
- They tried to stop us.
-  Right, they did.
So, to be honest,
I've been feeling sorry to Jae Seok for 26 years.
You must've been.
What do you mean?
Then apologise to me.
I'm sorry.
I keep picturing Jae Seok getting kicked by Seung Joon.
I'm sure he reacted like this.
(Young Jae Seok would've reacted like a coward.)
And then he'd get hit.
So Seung Joon beat Jae Seok.
I'm sure I didn't stay quiet if he hit me.
(I probably didn't stay still.)
I must've hit him back.
- I hit him.
-  I'm sure you ran away.
- What did you do after you got hit?
-  Did he hit you...
or did he just stay quiet?
I don't remember getting hit by him.
Gosh.
That is ridiculous.
Don't you think you've gone too far?
Gosh, Seung Joon!
So Jae Seok ran away.
- That's just how I remember.
-  That is so funny.
- Gosh, this is ridiculous.
-  I think...
- he just stayed still.
-  So he didn't hit Seung Joon.
- Gosh, Seung Joon.
-  You were scared.
There was a friend of ours named Byung Soo.
I think I told you this before.
We screwed up our exams and...
went to Han River near the 63 Building.
And we decided to have some ice cream.
So Byung Soo went to buy ice cream.
And some older guys came to us...
and put their arms around us like this.
I know what kind of guys they are.
- Me, too.
-  Like friends?
- Yes, like close friends.
-  Okay.
- They told you to smile, right?
-  Like friends.
- I know.
-  They acted like friends.
I was excited to go to Yeouido that day,
so I wore expensive socks and shoes.
They told me to take my socks off.
- Your socks?
-  Yes. Then one of them...
said, "Wait."
"Those socks are mine."
(Wait, they are mine.)
- Why would they take your socks?
-  I know.
- They're my socks.
-  You had no say.
They were talking about what to do with my socks.
So what came to my mind was Byung Soo.
He wasn't with us.
So I thought he could call the police when he saw us.
So I looked back.
And I saw him walking toward us with ice cream.
(He was walking toward us with the ice cream.)
He started to walk away.
- Good.
-  So I thought it'd be over.
I thought he went to call the police.
- So I was relieved.
-  "He's calling the police."
So I waited for the police, thinking "You guys are dead!"
But few minutes later,
he came back with more ice cream.
(He returned with more ice cream.)
(He bought more ice cream for the new friends.)
This is so hilarious.
- So...
-  Is this true?
- This is funny.
-  He thought...
- more friends came.
-  Gosh.
- So he bought more.
-  This is so funny.
This is so hilarious.
- Did this really happen?
-  Did it?
- Yes.
-  It's a true story.
Gosh, that's unbelievable.
We were all bewildered.
(Jae Seok's high school friends are entertaining.)
- He bought more ice cream.
-  That was so funny.
So Byung Soo was of no help.
He was.
There was a friend named Dae Seong who lived near the school.
We went to his house and made a lot of prank calls.
Can I tell them what we did?
Yes, please.
- Please tell us.
-  Don't do it.
- Please.
-  Don't say it.
- Come on.
-  We have to meet other people, too!
- It is okay.
-  We have enough time.
- Please tell us.
-  Let's listen to him first.
- We made a prank call at 2am.
-  2am?
We said, "Hello, this is the SBS broadcasting station."
And we chose one of the SBS radio programmes.
- It was "The Starry Night".
-  And he said,
"This is Yoo Jae Seok, the programme's DJ."
And those who received our calls were half-asleep,
so they all believed what we were saying.
So we would ask where they lived and they would tell us.
They even sang songs if we asked them to.
That is harsh. Goodness.
I remember that.
- Gosh, you're unbelievable.
-  I did that, too.
So we'd all burst into laughter watching him do that.
He was a prankster.
I am so sorry. I was so young and immature.
My friends liked it so much and kept asking me to do it again.
- So you wanted to make them laugh.
-  Right.
No one ever revealed Jae Seok's school days like this before.
- You're right. No one has.
-  Right.
That was so authentic.
It's because my real friend is here.
But really, since then,
I'd see him from a distance on the college campus.
When we ran into each other, we felt awkward.
- That's right.
-  Because it's been a long time.
- After the incident.
-  So we'd just say hello.
- Just like that.
-  And...
our majors were different.
At that time, his classmates and mine...
- were in rivalry.
-  I see.
We didn't think of them as our rival.
It's like the movie, "Friend".
Hold on. What did you just say?
We didn't think of you guys as our rival at all.
Jae Seok, calm down.
(You're making me angry.)
Stop, Jae Seok!
- No, no.
-  Hey.
Gosh, get up.
- This is...
-  Please get up.
- My goodness.
-  Calm down.
What are you laughing at?
Gosh, then...
(Seung Joon knows how to fool with Jae Seok.)
- This is like "Friend".
-  Gosh, Seung Joon.
Now, we're...
- going to have a Reminiscent Quiz.
-  I see.
Here is the first question.
- You guys went to Jongno often.
-  We did.
What was the name of the music cafe you used to go?
You must have told them about this.
The answer is "The 11th Street".
I think he's wrong.
Actually, I don't remember exactly.
Isn't that an online shopping mall?
(That's the name of an online store.)
(This isn't an advertisement.)
You can just say you don't remember.
At the time, in the music cafe located in Jongno 2-ga,
although we can easily watch music videos through the internet and VOD,
- at that time, we had to go...
-  Right. They showed the videos.
there to watch the music videos of famous foreign singers.
- They had projectors for that.
-  What is the answer, then?
- The answer is "The 18th Street".
-  Right.
"The 18th Street".
- I said "The 11th Street".
-  It wasn't "The 11th Street".
But I got "Street" correct.
- You're still wrong.
-  Seung Joon and I...
- went there every weekend...
-  They went often.
- with our friends.
-  I think you guys were...
- Right.
-  very innocent at that time.
- I'll give you the next question.
-  It was "The 18th Street".
This is your photo.
- When was it taken?
-  I have this, too.
This is Seung Joon. And this is Hyeong Man, our close friend.
This was a good friend of ours.
We took this photo...
when we went on a Boy Scout trip.
You're correct.
(He's correct.)
- Gosh.
-  You look so...
- cute here.
-  Right.
He was very cute. So we called him a cutie.
- He looks so cute.
-  He is handsome.
- There are more photos.
-  He was chubby.
- Really?
-  I don't remember where this was.
We went to travel by ourselves.
This was Soyangho in Chuncheon.
Look at Jae Seok.
- Jae Seok looks...
-  You look like a prankster.
He looks like a mischievous boy.
- Jae Seok looks better now.
-  I had my hair cut short.
- We took it in early morning.
-  It's been about 18 years.
I remember what we did that night.
(The photo brought back memories of a night in Chuncheon.)
One of us brought a flickering lamp that was used in clubs.
We danced for two hours at night under that lamp.
Is that why you want...
- to dance with us so much?
-  Yes.
(Jae Seok always asks new guests to dance.)
- That's why he is good at dancing.
-  Right.
Finally,
what character does Lee Seung Joon play in "Descendants of the Sun"?
(What is his character's name in "Descendants of the Sun"?)
This is hard.
Did they call you by your full name in the drama?
That's enough.
(Did he lie about watching the drama?)
I'll take this.
Apparently, that pen is not just any pen. It's poisonous.
(He acted as Dr Song Sang Hyun.)
- He was called Dr something, right?
-  Then,
- Just the surname.
-  just his surname will do.
- Really? I know his surname.
-  Sure.
- In 1, 2, 3.
-  Dr Song.
Mission cleared.
(He's correct.)
- Good job.
-  We have a gift for you.
We've prepared a gold necklace.
You can put a photo in the necklace.
- It's real gold.
-  It's real.
- That's so nice.
-  Thank you.
You should give each other a hug.
Give each other a hug.
(I missed you, my friend.)
I hate that I have to leave.
(It's been 26 years, but it's as if they saw each other yesterday.)
(That's why they call each other friends.)
- I didn't know I'd see Seung Joon.
-  Seriously.
- I found my friend again.
-  You must have been so close.
- We were.
-  You were best friends.
You saw him in the picture. I used to pinch his cheeks a lot.
We already spent two hours speaking to Seung Joon.
- We couldn't cut it short, though.
-  I know.
- It was so much fun.
-  It was so good.
I asked him if you were one of the top five guys in blind dates.
He said you were bluffing. Why would you lie about it?
- Why would you lie about it?
-  Just be quiet.
- Why should I?
I only remembered after we finished shooting his part.
- I'm saying this now,
-  He said you were wrong.
but Seung Joon was no match for me.
- Hey.
-  Both of you came in last, right?
I told you. I was one of the top five guys.
- Should I give him a call?
-  You were probably the last.
How could he say my ex-girlfriend was tall and ugly?
- Oh, gosh.
-  Who are we going to meet now?
- It's Seok Jin's guest.
-  It's mine.
- When I was in middle school,
-  The school nurse?
I had a huge crush on the school nurse.
- You spoke about her before.
-  I used to show up on purpose.
I faked my illness.
She used to put her hand on my forehead. I loved it when she did.
If she was a school nurse back then, she's probably much older now.
I think she had just graduated from a university back then.
I think her name was Yeom Young Hee.
It's pretty here. This school looks so nice.
Look at them. Look at the students.
They look so young.
- It looks really nice.
-  Doesn't it?
- This is called freedom.
-  It's so nice here.
This is what a school campus is all about.
(He doesn't have much time to find the Second Love.)
Hello.
Building 102 is here.
Excuse me.
Hello.
(Will Seok Jin's guest be amongst the crowd?)
I'm getting a little bit nervous.
I don't remember her face.
In middle school,
- The school nurse?
-  I had a huge crush...
- on the school nurse.
-  Is that so?
I used to show up on purpose. I faked my illness.
She used to put her hand on my forehead. I loved it when she did.
(Are you Seok Jin's first love?)
Hello.
Is it you?
(It's been a long time, Seok Jin.)
Is it really her?
Is that really her?
- You're a professor now.
-  Yes, I am.
- Miss. I...
-  Were you the school nurse?
- Yes.
-  I had a huge crush on you.
I know.
(He finally confesses after a long time has passed.)
- Jee Seok Jin!
-  Jee Seok Jin!
-  I finally found you.
At that time, you were...
- Seok Jin's school nurse, right?
-  Yes.
I had a big crush on her.
- It was a one-sided love.
-  I used to...
fake illnesses and show up.
When she put her hand on my forehead, it healed everything.
(She even healed illnesses that he didn't have.)
I'm serious.
(Seok Jin, how's it now?)
- It was just like this.
-  Anyway,
- Like this.
(I'm healed already.)
- Excuse me, Ms Yeom.
-  That's it.
Professor, I have a question to ask.
- He said you wouldn't remember him.
-  Right.
- Because...
-  She wasn't my homeroom teacher.
you were a school nurse and not his homeroom teacher.
You saw him once in a while. But do you remember him?
Do you still remember him?
(What is her response to the long-awaited question?)
Be honest.
(He's hurt.)
- She probably doesn't know him.
-  This is how it's supposed to be.
- This is obvious.
-  I'm not 100 percent sure.
- I don't remember him clearly.
-  It'd be weird for her to remember.
When you were a school nurse, were there boys...
who used to fake illnesses to see you?
There were many.
- How could she say it herself?
-  She's very innocent.
Even if you look at her now,
she's very beautiful.
- We are here...
-  I was only 14 back then.
because Seok Jin said she was his favourite teacher.
But in reality, they are pretty much strangers.
- This is meaningless.
-  She has no recollection of him.
- She doesn't know him.
-  Miss Yeom,
it's fine as long as you are in my memory.
But I know our Seok Jin's song called, "I Know".
- Of course you do!
-  Though it's not very popular.
Miss Yeom, it was very awkward when you said "Our Seok Jin".
(They've just met but she calls him "Our Seok Jin".)
That sounded really awkward.
Somebody is holding up his name.
- Thank you.
-  But you know,
we have to ask her to do something to complete our mission.
- What does she have to do?
-  There's a mission.
Seok Jin, your mission is...
Don't call him that. Say, "Our Seok Jin".
- "Our Seok Jin".
-  "Our Seok Jin".
I'm back in my middle school days.
- He's in middle school.
-  I'm in middle school right now.
So "Our Seok Jin" has a mission.
First, he needs to buy...
everyone here lunch.
That sounds good.
Is this his mission?
- Wait.
-  Jee Seok Jin!
- Jee Seok Jin!
-  "Our Seok Jin"!
- Our...
-  Seok Jin!
- Our Seok Jin!
-  All right, then.
- Have you eaten?
-  No!
It's all on me today.
(Lunch is on Seok Jin!)
It's on me.
Seok Jin will pay for lunch as Ms Yeom's former student.
- They're burgers.
-  It's for lunch.
(This is Seok Jin's gift for her students.)
Please hand them out.
It's so nice to see you again.
Thanks for visiting me.
Don't mention it.
These are French fries.
- Enjoy your meal.
-  I will hand them out.
This is so heartwarming.
We would have prepared something better if we had more time.
- We don't have much time.
-  Take them.
Who didn't get one?
- Thank you.
-  The French fries...
We have something for you.
This is a necklace.
(This is a gift for the guest.)
- Doesn't it open?
-  It does.
This is the R mark for Running Man. It's gold.
(The necklace has a photo of Seok Jin and her.)
Ms Yeom, you can lose the photo, but don't lose the gold R mark.
(She can lose the picture but not the gold.)
Please be good to Ms Yeom.
- Okay!
-  Yes!
(Please be good to her like I was.)
- Goodness, "Our Seok Jin".
-  Can you take one for us?
- Our...
-  Seok Jin!
(Seven Loves)
Oksu-dong is the closest from here.
Let's go there, then. Who has to go there?
- It's Ji Hyo.
-  Yes, it's me.
Oh, it's you. Do you know whom you are expecting?
It's a friend who took acting lessons with me.
(It's someone who took acting classes with her.)
I took lessons from Kim Su Ro back then.
That's right.
He had a close friend...
who lived neared the mountaintop of Oksu-dong.
- I remember now.
-  I used to climb up the mountain...
to take lessons from him, but I often got hungry and tired.
So at his house,
I used to go through his fridge and eat his food.
I used to take naps there, too. That's what I recall.
- You slept then, too?
-  She used to take naps.
Then I would just read a page and finish my lesson.
- This is making me so nervous.
-  It does.
- It does make you nervous.
-  I wonder who it is.
I'm really curious.
(Ji Hyo's first love...)
(makes an appearance.)
- Oh, dear! Oh my, oh my!
-  It must be her friend.
(Everyone gets up.)
It's you, Young Sun!
- Oh, dear. How could this be?
-  She's beautiful.
-  Hello.
- She has a daughter.
- She was part of Redsox.
-  That's right!
I saw her when I was serving in the army.
You saw her?
- When did you get married?
-  That's amazing.
- Please, have a seat.
-  Hello.
- Your daughter is so pretty.
-  She is.
She's so pretty. I could have never imagined this.
- I think it's been...
-  15 years?
I think so. It's been 15 years.
Haven't we met each other on "X-Man"?
You're right.
- Was she on "X-Man"?
-  She was.
- We used to work together.
-  Right.
(Who is Chae Young In exactly?)
(She made her debut in 2005 as a member of Redsox.)
(Not only was she a singer, but she was also an actress.)
(She was in various dramas...)
(such as "Damo" and "Temptation of Wife".)
- She debuted earlier than I did.
-  Really?
You debuted on television a lot earlier than I did.
- And then...
-  Redsox was famous in the army.
- Both of us made our debut...
-  Really?
Really?
(Kwang Soo hums Redsox's song.)
- Which year was it?
-  That's "Sweet Dream".
- I remember that song.
-  Back then,
- I woke up listening her song.
-  Oh my goodness.
You were dressed in red in the music video.
I guess you were a big fan of mine...
among the Redsox members.
Well... That's...
- He must've been.
-  That's right.
I guess Young Sun is here...
not to see Ji Hyo, but to recollect memories.
Memories of the time when she was a member of Redsox.
- Was the name of the group, Redsox?
-  Yes.
- Yes, that's right.
-  Do you remember the choreography?
- Oh, my.
-  I guess you do.
(She shakes her head coyly.)
(This must've been her charm back then.)
- Look.
-  Can't you remember?
- I guess you do.
-  Me, too.
Even if you don't you do, once the music comes out,
- you'll remember.
-  Your body will remember.
- That's not true.
-  Let's see for ourselves.
(Let's play the music.)
(Oh, my.)
(Onto the stage, Young Sun.)
Redsox!
Let me summon Redsox...
from your memories.
(He still remembers the dance moves.)
- That's right!
-  It is?
(Kwang Soo is like a member of Redsox.)
This was how I danced.
(Shy)
(She begins singing and dancing.)
I don't know. I don't remember.
(The music makes her dance automatically.)
(Even if she doesn't remember, her body still does.)
(It has been 10 years,)
She still remembers.
(But she remembers it like it was yesterday.)
- There she goes.
-  That's it.
- Nice.
-  That's it!
- She remembers.
-  That's right.
- Redsox!
-  My memories are coming back!
(She is on point.)
(She dances just as great and lively as she did back then.)
Am I dancing correctly?
Give her a round of applause!
(She's still an amazing dancer.)
- Oh my goodness!
-  That was good.
- You still remember the moves.
-  That's right.
Do you have any special memories 15 years ago...
with Ji Hyo?
Back then, we didn't have...
serious conversations...
- Not about acting.
-  about acting.
- We were just young.
-  What did you talk about the most?
About men.
- I thought you had no interest?
-  She was interested in men!
- Look.
-  You said that your first love...
- You said it was a teacher.
-  She said she wasn't interested.
- Optimus Prime was your ideal guy.
-  Of course... Of course...
I had a boyfriend. I meant I wasn't interested in other men.
- You had a boyfriend since then?
-  Look.
- That's how I felt with Seung Joon.
-  He was really famous.
- Her ex-boyfriend was famous.
-  Was he?
(Ji Hyo was in a relationship with a celebrity 15 years ago.)
She heard about my history but never told me anything.
- I shouldn't have said that.
-  I can't believe it.
Let's look into Ji Hyo's past.
- Is he still famous?
-  This was before she debuted.
All of you may know him...
- if I say his name.
-  Really?
- Don't hide your past, Ji Hyo.
-  What's going on?
- So you were interested in men.
-  Gladly, she was.
- That's a relief.
-  All right. Young Sun is here now.
So what is their mission?
It's called "First Episode of the Temptation of Running Man."
(In 100 seconds, they have to read a script of "Temptation of Wife".)
(They need to shout loudly. It must be louder than 120dB.)
(Then, they have to tear off three post-its without using their hands.)
(Finally, two people must catch a ball in mid-air.)
- Are you ready?
-  Yes, I am.
Ready and go.
"Are you really going to go through with this marriage?"
"You borrowed my name and lived well."
"Aren't you too greedy?"
"I'm sorry, Young Sun. Please bless our wedding for him at least."
"What? Bless?"
"I don't think that'll be possible."
Cheon Seong Im!
(That was really loud.)
Can I see? That is beyond my expectation!
- It's over!
-  Is it?
(How loud was her screaming?)
- 137.
-  It's 137 dB.
That's amazing!
(She knows how to be loud.)
- "Please don't do this."
-  "Please let me go."
"I won't. You must suffer as much as I have suffered until now!"
- "Just let me go!"
-  That's good!
- You're doing well.
-  Keep the pace.
That's good.
- All right. Tear them off.
-  Hurry.
- One is stuck on your hair.
-  Good job.
"Ji Hyo, now we can be happy forever. I'll make that come true."
"Thank you, Kwang Soo."
That's it.
(Today, they have 12 hours to find 7 loves.)
(They need to complete their missions as quickly as they can.)
- That's it.
-  No!
- Pick up the ball.
-  Hurry up.
- Once again!
-  Hurry.
(They're running out of time. This is their last chance.)
(Second attempt)
- It's going to work.
-  They did it!
Well done. How long did it take?
- How long was it?
-  It took 1 minute and 28 seconds.
- Yes!
-  It's done!
(They have cleared their mission.)
That was amazing.
You're a great actress.
Your acting was so nice.
- Your scream was so loud.
-  I called out your real name.
- That was loud.
-  Seriously.
- She's really talented.
-  She is.
Again, we'd like to celebrate...
- the reunion of the two women.
-  Congratulations!
- That was great!
-  Let's take a photo together.
(Seven Loves)
(Next is Haha.)
- Who is your guest?
-  Honestly, I have no idea.
I really don't.
Haha wrote out so many names.
(Haha wrote out so many names.)
(Among them, who is his love?)
(Where are they?)
- Where is this place?
-  It's huge.
- Hey, Haha.
-  This is a stage.
(They are preparing for a rehearsal.)
I feel so nervous.
Maybe that person will make a musical entrance.
- I don't know.
-  I see.
- I really have no idea.
-  Every day
(Who is waiting for Haha?)
Stop it. Jae Seok.
- Isn't he Lee Moon Sae?
-  He is!
(It's Lee Moon Sae!)
He is!
- Isn't he Lee Moon Sae?
-  It really is him.
- You wrote his name.
-  Come over.
- Moon Sae.
-  Are you my love?
- Oh, my.
-  Really?
(Haha's love is the famous singer, Lee Moon Sae.)
(He has been a passionate singer for the past 39 years.)
(He is a famous and beloved singer in Korea.)
I heard that Haha was coming while I was preparing for a rehearsal.
- Did you say it's about influence?
-  Yes, that's right.
- When I heard he was coming,
-  I really mean it.
- I thought he was coming alone.
-  Did you?
Yes. And we've met last year.
- When I released my album.
-  That's right.
Haha appeared as a surprise guest at the showcase.
I was so thankful. It's hard to forget.
- Do you contact each other often?
-  Yes, I do call him.
Thanks to Haha,
I'm able to see you all today. I wanted to meet everyone.
It feels like a mission for myself is accomplished already.
We have a mission that needs to be accomplished for Haha to succeed.
This is Haha's mission.
Lee Moon Sae will choose a song and Haha must sing it.
Then, Haha needs to hear a specific comment from him.
It sounds really difficult.
Please choose a song.
- Among my songs?
-  There are so many of them.
- How about "Girl"?
-  "Girl" sounds good.
- Haha loves to sing "Girl".
-  Honestly,
- I sang "Girl" more than 500 times.
-  I sang 12,000 times.
No way. You didn't.
Even I haven't sung it that much.
- You don't have to lower the key.
-  I really enjoy this song.
- I won't lower the key.
-  Don't shout out too early.
- It's my favourite song.
-  It's my favourite.
- That looks nice.
-  I remember all the lyrics.
(The mission begins.)
(Haha is trying to sing and even look like Moon Sae.)
(Haha shouldn't fail the mission.)
I get it, he's mimicking.
- You get how he's mimicking, right?
-  Loneliness
(Haha is immersed in his singing.)
(He is worried.)
(That's not the "Girl" I used to listen to.)
(Jae Seok suddenly stands up...)
(and grabs the microphone.)
That's not how you sing the song.
(Jae Seok's singing is probably similar to Haha.)
Don't cry in loneliness
(Are you listening, Moon Sae?)
Oh my gosh, it's so great!
(Jae Seok is running out of patience.)
(Again, he takes the microphone away from Haha.)
(Seok Jin wants to sing the song, too.)
(Jae Seok unplugs the microphone.)
(Why isn't the microphone working?)
What is this?
(The stage has become a mess.)
This is my song. Lee Moon Sae told me.
That was funny.
- Wouldn't it be more difficult?
-  No.
- We need to listen to him sing?
-  Again?
- We'll sing "Old Love".
-  "Old Love" sounds really nice.
- It goes like this.
-  I'll begin my second mission.
(Haha begins without any music.)
- Hold on.
-  You need to pass the microphone.
(Haha doesn't listen and continues his mission.)
(It's your turn, Moon Sae.)
What is this?
That was too sudden.
Moon Sae, I know you are doing this intentionally.
I don't have much time. I want to stay, but...
You're here because you wanted to see him and now you don't have time.
- Do you have to go?
-  He's taking too much time.
- He's a busy man.
-  What are you doing?
It's been a year since I've appeared on television.
I'm finally on television again,
but you're going to leave after the mission?
- That's not it.
-  That's terrible.
- I have to watch your performance.
-  For this song,
- I will give you one tip.
-  Okay.
(He gives a tip so they can quickly succeed.)
- Don't try to mimic me.
-  Of course.
And don't worry about singing well.
Just think about how you will deliver the lyrics well.
- Right.
-  That's what you should do.
That's what I think when I sing this song.
- Me, too.
-  I always think like that.
It's my first time seeing Haha sweating like this.
- I know.
-  Right?
It's really embarrassing for me to sing a song I love in front of...
- a person whom I really admire.
-  Right.
- All right.
-  Cue.
(He gives the mission another try.)
(The time is passing quickly.)
(Will he be able to complete the mission with his role model?)
(Moon Sae continues naturally.)
(Haha succeeds.)
(The mission is over, but he wants to keep listening.)
It's nice.
(It's an overwhelming moment regardless of the mission.)
- That's it.
-  That's good.
- So...
-  The mission is cleared.
- What was the mission?
-  It was singing in relay.
Singing in relay.
That's so easy.
But I'm glad he did it.
- He has a concert coming up.
-  Right.
- He has to reserve his voice.
-  He shouldn't be singing.
By the way, have you ever seen Running Man?
- Of course.
-  Is that right?
I should rip someone's name tag one day.
(He wants to be on Running Man one day.)
The more we think about it,
the more we are touched by the lyrics and the song.
His songs have a special place in our memories, and we hope he will...
continue to sing great songs.
- Let's clap for him.
-  Thank you.
Thank you!
Thank you! It was an honour!
(Seven Loves)
Who's in here?
(There is a woman calmly waiting for the members.)
(Who is she?)
(He's the one and only love of Jong Kook.)
(Who can she be?)
Mother!
- Hello.
-  Goodness.
- She's Jong Kook's mother.
-  Hello.
It's been a long time.
- Mother.
-  It's Jong Kook's mother.
Yes, hello.
- Hello.
-  You all look very handsome.
Hello, Mother.
Why is my mother here?
- What's going on?
-  She's Jong Kook's mother.
- Mum!
-  Jong Kook.
- Hello.
-  She's Jong Kook's mum.
You look beautiful today.
- Where did you get your hair done?
-  I also thought...
- My hair is naturally like this.
-  It looks very nice.
Don't lie. I've seen your natural state.
(What kind of son is Jong Kook?)
I want to give this to other people.
I want to take it to my mother.
Usually, guys don't go to an arcade with their mother.
I often go to the movies with my mum.
- Right.
-  He's very caring of his mother.
- He's a good son.
-  Yes.
Jong Kook chose you as the person he loves the most.
Oh, dear.
- By the way, he always...
-  He should get married.
- thinks about you.
-  It's true.
- Is that right?
-  He always does.
- Jong Kook is such a good son.
-  Really.
I've never seen such a lovely son.
We know that you always cook him breakfast.
- Really.
-  We hear that...
he eats breakfast at 3am.
He has to eat breakfast.
(He has to eat breakfast, no matter what.)
So we always tell him...
- to stop torturing you.
-  I know.
- We tell him to get married.
-  Get married soon.
I know. I want him to get married soon.
What kind of woman would you like as a daughter-in-law?
The toughest condition is that...
she has to cook well.
Look at that.
- Right.
-  Goodness.
She has to be able to cook at three in the morning.
Because he has to eat breakfast every day.
What kind of son is he at home?
I am curious.
Since we don't have a daughter,
he's been like a daughter in our family.
Like a daughter.
Like a daughter?
- Is he adorable?
-  Is he really?
- Jong Kook?
-  Like a daughter?
I am the daughter in my family.
- Does he act cute?
-  I'm like a daughter.
- We'd never think of him like that.
-  He's like a daughter.
So you release the stress when you are outside.
So he's different when he's at home and when he's outside.
Does he ever act cute?
- He acts really cute with her.
-  At home?
One time, they were in a hotel room together.
And Jong Kook danced liked this in front of her.
- Really.
-  When did I do that?
- He really did that.
-  What are you talking about?
Did he cause a lot of trouble when he was in school?
No, he didn't cause much trouble.
- Because he's your son.
-  Gosh, mother.
- That means you've been lying.
-  Please don't do that.
We can help you to a certain point.
- The entire nation knows of him.
-  We all know how he is.
She's his mother for sure.
Since I was young,
I was a compassionate boy.
- He's right.
-  I was a really good kid.
He always asked me to pack two lunch boxes.
He gave one to his friend who couldn't bring one.
- Really?
-  Yes.
- I was a really compassionate boy.
-  He was a good boy.
(Jong Kook was compassionate and kind.)
It was just the bad people.
I only hated the bad people.
- I hated the bad people.
-  Gosh.
(I can't bear this.)
- He's right.
-  My goodness.
- It's really...
-  We don't know what to say.
- I'm so confused now.
-  Of course Jong Kook...
- is a compassionate person.
-  But it's true.
If his weak friend gets beaten by another kid,
he always sided with his friend and took revenge.
He sided with his weak friends.
- Right.
-  I wasn't...
someone who bullied weak people.
- Right.
-  I couldn't stand injustice.
You couldn't stand injustice.
The mission Jong Kook will clear with his mother is...
cooking for...
his mother.
He cooks well.
And he has to write a handwritten letter.
(He needs to write a letter.)
A handwritten letter?
(Manly Jong Kook must write a handwritten letter.)
My mother is flustered.
What do we do?
(He enters the kitchen.)
I need medicinal herbs.
(He checks the ingredients in the refrigerator.)
It's here.
(Checking)
There you go.
(What will he cook for his mother?)
Mother, Jong Kook has to get married now.
I know. If he can't get married,
I hope he will at least get me a grandchild first.
You are right.
- She'd like grandchildren.
-  I want a grandchild.
She wants to see her grandchildren acting cute.
- Right.
-  Yes.
- I'm getting old.
-  We always say...
that Jong Kook's mother is the best mother in the nation.
- Gosh, you're too kind.
-  Your first son is a surgeon.
- Gosh...
-  He's a plastic surgeon.
- And your second son is a star.
-  She has Jong Kook, too.
(She raised her sons well.)
- Really.
-  Aren't you happy?
(She must be happy just looking at her sons.)
Of course, I'm happy.
As long as you do your best with your work,
you are all number one daughters and sons.
Did you bring some photos?
I brought Jong Kook's childhood photos.
- You were big.
-  Goodness.
- That was from middle school.
-  Right.
That was my middle school graduation day.
- You went on an outing.
-  Mother, you were...
(She was always there for him.)
You were a beauty when you were young.
- She was beautiful.
-  Oh, dear.
Her eyes were big and pretty.
- And she is always smiling.
-  Right.
- She always smiles.
-  Whenever someone calls,
- Do you smile?
-  I always start with a laugh.
How? I will pretend to call you.
I always do that to everyone.
Hello.
(Bursting into laughter)
- Do you really do that?
-  Right away?
- Yes.
-  You just laugh.
I do.
- That's very nice.
-  She's amazing.
- It puts you in a good mood.
-  I laugh all day.
Whoever becomes Jong Kook's wife...
is going to be very happy.
- That's right.
-  She'll be a great mother-in-law.
(Meanwhile, Jong Kook is doing the mission in the kitchen.)
(Today's menu is samgyetang.)
I will add sticky rice.
(He won a cooking competition before.)
Don't I have to add things like chestnuts?
Garlic.
(He puts great effort into the dish for his mother.)
Do we have chestnuts?
Go inside.
Do we not have chestnuts?
(He stuffed the chicken nicely. Now, he must boil it.)
The chicken is too big.
(While the chicken is cooking in the pot,)
(Jong Kook writes a letter.)
(Because he's been busy, he hasn't written a letter for a long time.)
(With his large hands, he slowly fills the paper with his words.)
(Jong Kook's samgyetang is complete.)
(He tastes it.)
It's amazing.
How did it turn out so nicely?
I cook samgyetang really well.
Shall we bring it out?
Jong Kook's confident about his food.
- Gosh.
-  You must've tasted it before.
Jong Kook is a good cook.
- We will acknowledge it.
-  I...
- really...
-  He's a professional.
It looks just like the samgyetang he cooked before.
I...
- You cooked it well.
-  I really am...
- good at cooking samgyetang.
-  I know.
Is it good?
- Open it.
-  It's amazing.
You won't believe it.
- He'll make a great husband.
-  But really.
I cook samgyetang really well.
- Look at that!
-  I cooked it really well.
I think he cooked it well.
- She will...
-  I didn't add any salt.
- So it might be bland.
-  Please have a seat.
That looks amazing.
It's mouth-watering.
Goodness.
- You should serve it for her.
-  Like a queen.
Taste it.
(He worries that she will burn her tongue.)
It's hot. Blow on it.
He's sweet like this.
(Jong Kook's a sweetheart.)
(She doesn't forget to brag.)
Oh, dear.
She can't stop bragging about her son.
My goodness.
(She tries the samgyetang that Jong Kook cooked for her.)
- How is it?
-  It's really delicious.
It's rich.
- Is it good?
-  Yes.
- It's amazing, isn't it?
-  It's much better than mine.
- It's better than your samgyetang?
-  Yes.
What's for sure is that he cooks better than my mum does.
- Did you write the letter?
-  What?
The letter.
Now, you should write the letter.
- I wrote it.
-  She...
- When did you write it?
-  I saw him writing it.
- He wrote two pages.
-  Is it too bland?
I wrote a little more than a page.
Okay.
"Dear Mother".
"Mother, this is your youngest son, Jong Kook."
"I always try to be a good son,"
"but I've never given you a handwritten letter."
"When I was young, I used to be a troublemaker and make you worry."
"That's why I wanted to be a good son to you all the more."
"Father was so strict..."
"and frugal, so you had a difficult time."
"Watching you while growing up, I wanted to become successful..."
"so that I could give you everything good in this world."
"Whenever I told you this, you would be surprised."
"And you would laugh, saying that I won't be able to do it."
"But you always wanted to live with me and not my brother."
"You said your older son was too absorbed in his studies."
(Her eldest son wasn't very affectionate.)
"Mother, thank you for taking care..."
"of me to this age. I feel bad, but I'm very appreciative."
"I'm always trying to be a good son and a good person."
"I'll get married soon so that I can take care of you instead."
- That's right.
-  "Please be healthy."
"Be healthy for a long time and experience everything good."
"Let me be a good son to you as long as I can."
"I have a lot more to say, but I'll show you by being a good son."
"Thank you for everything and I love you. From your son, Jong Kook."
(Thank you for everything, Mum. I love you.)
Goodness, Mother.
- It's making me tear up.
-  I know, right?
While I was reading this, I got emotional.
- So I read it quickly.
-  You were tearing up.
- I know how he feels now.
-  It's a handwritten letter.
Thank you.
Be healthy, Mother.
(Be healthy, Mother.)
(Jong Kook is a lovable son.)
- Isn't he like a daughter?
-  Yes, he is.
- I'm so envious.
-  You should do the same for us.
- He rips our clothes.
-  He bites us.
He bites us, too. That's how he is.
There is no part of me that's unscathed.
He should do the same for you, too.
He should say that he loves us.
(The mother and son take a picture.)
In 1, 2, 3.
(Jong Kook completes his mission with his mother.)
(Seven Loves)
I got her number from my mum.
- Really?
-  Yes, she was my first girlfriend.
- We got it.
-  It was since kindergarten.
It might work.
- I have to find someone.
-  Gary, just...
- pick anybody.
-  Should I give her a call?
Try calling her.
- I'm getting worried.
-  How long has it been? 30 years?
I've never called her before.
And if I see her today,
- Is it 20 years?
-  it will be around 25 years.
Try calling her. Let's hear her voice.
He's calling her.
Just from the sound of the ringtone...
Hello?
(He hears her voice over the phone.)
(It's been 25 years since he spoke to his first love.)
- Hello?
-  Yes?
Is this Hye Jin, by any chance?
- Yes.
-  Oh, hi.
(It's a heart-fluttering moment.)
He said, "Hi".
My name is Lee Kwang Soo.
Oh, King Kong!
King Kong!
King Kong? He was the ugly one.
- He was tall and ugly.
-  Tall and ugly.
-  You must have been my girlfriend.
- Hello?
-  Yes.
- Hye Jin.
-  What?
- How have you been?
-  Good. Hi.
- I'm curious.
-  "Good. Hi".
According to Kwang Soo, you were his first girlfriend.
- Was I?
-  Yes, you were.
I think so.
Is he right?
Can we go see you in a bit?
- Sure.
-  As a prelude to our meeting,
can you tell us what kind of friend Kwang Soo was?
He was ugly.
(His first girlfriend confirms that he was ugly.)
You are so funny. See you later, Hye Jin.
- Sure.
-  Bye.
She's very blunt.
- She sounds funny.
-  Her voice hasn't changed.
- Really?
-  It's husky.
It's going to be fun. Remember what you said, Kwang Soo?
You said something good might happen today.
To be honest, I like women who are overpowering.
You never know what's going to happen today.
- Kwang Soo is single at the moment.
-  Right.
Everything about this situation is perfect.
- It's a perfect situation.
-  This is great, Kwang Soo.
- You must be excited.
-  When I spoke to her,
- She seemed candid.
-  she sounded very straightforward.
We are finally 1km away from meeting Hye Jin.
You must be really excited.
None of the other meetings felt like this today.
Kwang Soo must be nervous right now.
You should prepare what you're going to say.
- Let's practise it.
-  Practise in front of the mirror.
- Try it. Look at the mirror.
-  Hello, Hye Jin.
- Try another one.
-  That sounds awkward.
Try to sound cool.
- How have you been, Hye Jin?
-  Good one.
- It sounds weird, too.
-  It's awkward.
(Kwang Soo's first love)
- I'm curious.
-  I'm very curious.
(We will soon meet Kwang Soo's first love.)
It's Kwang Soo's...
first love, so I'm more curious than ever.
- Me, too.
-  I'm getting curious.
I'm very curious.
She sounds very easygoing and down-to-earth.
- I agree.
-  I'm so curious.
She seems to have a good personality.
- There she comes.
-  Is she coming?
- It must be her.
-  Kwang Soo.
- Can you close your eyes?
-  It's okay, Kwang Soo.
- The door opens
-  Close your eyes.
- She's coming in
-  Better yet, turn around.
At first sight
- Turn around.
-  I knew
-  It was love
- Get up.
-  When she came near me
- Goodness.
-  Doesn't she look like Ko So Young?
She wore a pink shirt.
(From childhood friends, they now meet each other as adults.)
(It's been 25 years, but they are still familiar with each other.)
(How has his first love changed?)
- Wow.
-  Hello.
Kwang Soo, now I know what you meant.
Hye Jin. Please, come here.
- Is this her?
-  You can guess her personality.
She does look very cute.
- She is.
-  She turned red.
- She's very pretty.
-  How long has it been?
- How long has it been?
-  It's the first time after...
- seeing him in second grade.
-  That's right.
You sound a lot different than when we spoke on the phone.
- Are you feeling shy?
-  Yes.
- You spoke aggressively before.
-  Your voice hasn't changed.
Kwang Soo...
- and...
-  Was he six years old?
It was until he was in second grade.
- She was Kwang Soo's girlfriend.
-  He was nine years old.
Please call his name. And Kwang Soo, call her name and turn around.
Kwang Soo.
- One more time.
-  Louder.
Can we do this one more time?
Be cute.
- Kwang Soo.
-  One more time, please.
Kwang Soo!
(She calls out his name after 25 years.)
(Do you remember our good times together?)
Kwang Soo!
(It's time to recall those memories.)
Look.
(Laughing)
Ta-da.
(He laughs as soon as he sees her.)
(Nodding)
(He can't stand the awkwardness.)
- You turned around and did this.
-  Hey!
What was that for?
- We practised before.
-  He practised his greeting.
- Try it.
-  Stroke her hair.
- How do you feel?
-  This is amazing.
"Hello". And then...
(He tries what he practised.)
I don't like it.
(Don't touch me.)
I told you I wouldn't do this.
- Do you not like it?
-  What did I tell you?
- I don't like physical contact.
-  Do you not like it?
- I told you not to do that.
-  Anyway...
You guys were young back then, but what kind of kid was Kwang Soo?
He was very quiet...
- Was he quiet?
-  and well-behaved.
I'm not used to him behaving like this.
- Really?
-  Yes.
(We have changed a lot, but we've met again.)
I was surprised that he still remembered me.
- Of course I do.
-  He kept on talking about you.
- Your sister was Hye Rim, right?
-  You're right.
- Was your sister Bo Ram?
-  And Sung Yoon.
- Yours was Bo Ram?
-  It was Sung Yoon, right?
- You're right.
-  Right.
- It's like they've met yesterday.
-  You lived on the second floor.
- Right, I did.
-  We lived on the 2nd and 3rd floor.
(She hits him.)
- She's a bit abusive.
-  Excuse me.
Didn't you say that you don't like physical contact?
- That's right.
-  She punched you. Are you okay?
- We lived on the 2nd and 3rd floor.
-  You're right.
He said you were very popular.
- I was very popular.
-  She was popular.
(She's so frank.)
- I was very popular.
-  That's what he said.
I thought he was going to be disappointed.
- Why?
-  I changed a lot.
- You're beautiful.
-  You're still beautiful.
- Was Kwang Soo popular as a child?
-  No, he wasn't.
(He wasn't popular.)
Did any girls like him?
- No, they didn't.
-  I was still young.
I heard Kwang Soo used to get beaten up a lot.
He did. I used to hit the kids who beat him up.
- Did I really get beaten up?
-  Don't you remember?
- Were you a nerd?
-  No way.
He calls everyone a nerd.
- He called me nerd, too.
-  How am I nerd?
He called me a nerd for getting kicked by Seung Joon.
- Goodness.
-  I remember this.
There was a small glass window in her house.
We were both staring out the window...
- In my house?
-  Yes.
- Did you kiss?
-  We were looking out the window,
- I remember she kissed my cheek.
-  Really?
(I remember her kissing me on the cheek.)
- Hye Jin did?
-  Yes.
(Do you remember that moment?)
No, he's wrong.
(Hitting)
- I didn't do it.
-  She doesn't like physical contact?
- Hye Jin.
-  I didn't do it.
Didn't you say you don't like physical contact?
- I didn't do it.
-  You punched him six times.
Are you two going out?
- You met yesterday, right?
-  No, we didn't.
- Hye Jin.
Do you have a boyfriend by any chance?
(Do you have a boyfriend?)
(Will they start dating after 25 years?)
- I am married.
-  What?
- Are you really?
-  Really?
(I'm married.)
(It's shocking news.)
- That's shocking.
-  Really?
It's shocking, shocking
- Did you get married?
-  You did?
- Do you have children?
-  No, I don't.
- You don't have children.
-  When did you get married?
I got married in 2014.
- I thought she said 14 years ago.
-  Me, too.
I thought she said 14 years ago.
You got married early.
- So that was two years ago?
-  Yes.
- I see.
-  Does your husband...
- know you are meeting Kwang Soo?
-  He does.
- What did he say?
-  He told me to get my hair done.
He wanted you to look nice.
- He wanted me to go shopping.
-  He's so nice.
How did you feel when she said she's married?
- Well, you know...
-  Answer me.
- What?
-  How did you feel?
I should congratulate her. What else could I do?
- He would congratulate her.
-  That's obvious.
- What is he supposed to do?
-  But he would have felt something.
- He would do the obvious.
-  She's still his first love.
He could have felt something when he heard that.
What do you think about Kwang Soo?
What type of a girlfriend do you think will suit him?
Who do you think will suit him?
She knows my entire family.
Someone who's good to his parents.
Why are you tearing up?
He could have been hers.
- He could have been hers.
-  She knows him the best.
Come on.
I can feel it.
- Is there...
-  That's too bad.
a mission for these two?
Hye Jin lives close by.
- It's late...
-  Will he walk her home?
- He'll take her to her husband...
-  Do I need to walk her home?
- safe and soundly.
-  That sounds good.
We're friends, anyway.
While they're doing that, we should move onto Gary.
I better find somebody.
- Let's discuss this.
-  Sure.
Look at the time. You should find somebody.
We only have an hour left.
I went back a little while ago.
- Have you gone there?
-  Everything was gone.
- My house was gone, too.
-  The video store was gone.
- It was gone.
-  That's gone, too.
What about the place that sells snacks?
- They used to sell this snack.
-  I used to love that place.
This feels weird.
I'm so glad to see you again,
but it still feels weird. It feels funny.
I could remember myself when I was younger.
I know, right? We used to go on trips together.
- I remember how my parents were.
-  I know.
- You should go now.
-  All right.
- This is her place.
-  I'll get going.
Keep in touch.
- Let me give you a hug.
-  Bye.
- Bye.
-  You, too.
It was so nice to see you again.
(From 1992 to 2016, they'll continue their memories.)
Look at the time. You should find somebody.
We only have an hour left.
- We can make it until 10:30pm.
-  We have to keep the time, right?
- It's until 10:30pm.
-  That's tight.
It's still tight.
- Kwang Soo should meet us there.
-  You're right.
- We have to get going.
-  Let's go.
All right. We're sorry to Kwang Soo,
- but he should come by a taxi.
-  We have to leave him.
- Tell him to go home.
-  This mission is important.
Just tell him to go home.
They left already.
Isn't this too much?
How am I supposed to go back?
Did they really leave?
Do I really need to take a taxi?
(They are going to complete the last mission.)
Hello.
We have to aim for 10:15pm.
(There are 40 minutes left.)
There's a lot of traffic.
We have to start the mission as soon as we get there.
As soon as we arrive, I'll take this camera.
Are you going to film it yourself?
(There are 32 minutes left.)
- Do we go straight?
-  Yes, keep going.
Do I keep going?
Is it this way?
(There are 20 minutes left.)
Where is it?
(Kwang Soo arrives first.)
We don't have much time.
Have they arrived yet?
Where is it?
Is no one here yet?
(The last guest is waiting for the members.)
(It's Yoon Gun.)
Who is it? Is no one here yet?
- Didn't they...
-  Yoon Gun is the last guest.
They're on their way.
- You should go say hi.
-  Where's Gary?
I know him.
Hello.
- Hello.
-  Hello, I got here first.
- Nice to meet you.
-  You're tall.
- Are you on your own?
-  Yes, I am.
But we have to finish the mission by 10:30pm.
We'll receive a penalty if we don't.
But we can only start when Gary gets here.
We only have 15 minutes left.
- Should I just walk there?
-  Where is it?
Wait. I'll just get off. It's on the right.
- Let's just walk there.
-  We should.
(Run for it!)
Let's go.
Gary, hurry up! We have no time!
We're here.
(The members arrive 15 minutes before time is up.)
- He's here.
-  Start the mission. Hello.
- Hello.
-  You are here.
- Start the mission.
-  We have no time.
- We have to finish by 10:30pm.
-  Go get the mission.
- Tell him what it is.
-  Hello.
- Hello.
-  Hi.
Yoon Gun will make coffee...
for all seven of you.
Meanwhile, Gary...
has to buy five items Gun asks for.
- Okay, hurry up.
-  What are they?
- We don't have time.
-  I want potato chips.
All right. I know which one it is.
- And hot dogs.
-  Hot dogs?
Are any hot dogs okay? They take long to make.
- Diet coke.
-  Diet coke?
- Can I request anything?
-  Just hurry up!
What about jelly?
- He wants the old ones.
-  Do they still sell them?
- They do still sell them.
-  And then?
- Ask for gum.
-  I want a lollipop.
That's candy.
Give me money.
- Where do I go?
-  Where can he go for hot dogs?
We have enough time.
I have 15 minutes. Where's the convenience store?
Okay.
(He finds a convenience store right away.)
Hello.
(His first target is the potato chips.)
(It's on his radar.)
I can't find the specific brand.
What's next?
What were they? Lollipops.
(He finds the lollipops.)
I got the lollipop. Do you sell hot dogs here?
Where are the hot dogs?
(He finds the hot dog.)
What's after the hot dog?
What was the next one? Here's the jelly.
(He finds the jelly.)
What was next?
I blanked out. I can't remember the next one.
I can't remember it at all.
We have 14 minutes left.
Please make seven cups of coffee...
in 14 minutes. That's all the time we have.
I can't remember one. This is driving me insane.
(Calm down, Gary!)
Hold on. What was it again?
It was diet coke!
(He finds the coke.)
Here's diet coke.
Don't you sell the potato chips?
Do you not sell it here?
Thank you.
(They don't sell the potato chips he was looking for.)
Where should I go? Where?
I have to go to a supermarket.
Let me find another convenience store.
He has to succeed. It's 10:18pm.
This is pretty close.
- Can you slow down a bit?
-  He's really good.
- I can finish them.
-  No, not yet.
How many did he make?
He made four so far.
- That's amazing.
-  You can't make them too fast.
You can't be too fast or too slow.
- We took so much time on the road.
-  The GPS didn't work well.
(There are 6 minutes and 25 seconds left.)
- I'm sorry.
-  You need to make them by 10:30pm.
(There are 6 minutes and 25 seconds left.)
(Gary finds another convenience store for the potato chips.)
Hello, do you sell the potato chips I'm looking for? Do you?
Where are they?
- Where are they?
-  They're here.
This is it. This is the original flavour, right?
I need to pay for it.
- He made six cups already.
-  Oh, my.
It's this way.
(He runs toward the coffee shop.)
If we don't succeed, we have to receive the penalty.
This is pretty close.
Where did he go?
We're in trouble.
You would hate this.
- It's the chocolate ice cream.
-  This is crazy.
(What is their fate?)
Is he back yet?
No, not yet.
- He's here.
-  He's here!
(Gary is back.)
- He's here.
-  He's here!
(Gary arrives before the seventh cup of coffee is made.)
- Let's see.
-  We just need the coffee.
(Their completion time is the most important.)
(If they go over the time, they will be penalised.)
(Did Gary arrive on time?)
Mission cleared!
- Yes!
-  We did it!
They didn't sell those potato chips.
The coffee is here.
- The coffee is out.
-  Just in time.
- That's perfect.
-  What time is it now?
Here you go.
In what ways did you help Gary, by the way?
I just made music with him. I don't know if I helped.
He made music with me. But to me,
he did much more. He would take his music...
- and let me rap in it.
-  He let you feature in it?
He got us involved.
So I earned 300 dollars. It was a lot for me at the time.
He provided me with work.
- He was like a mother bird.
-  He was.
I heard the story about "Ballerino", and I was really surprised.
This is how I came...
- to compose "Ballerino".
-  Really?
Gun visited my studio one day.
I asked him to show me something good...
because he is so good at playing the piano.
And immediately, he played this melody.
(As soon as he was asked to play something,)
(he composed an impromptu song, which has become "Ballerino".)
And...
he moved onto this part.
So my friend recorded him playing the melody.
While playing, I asked if it was okay.
But he already turned his recorder on.
- It was so good.
-  Really?
And he used that melody in his song.
Wow.
He even composed...
the piano part in "I'm Not Laughing".
I think most of the piano parts in Leessang's songs...
were made by Yoon Gun.
(He's a genius composer.)
He can make good melodies in three tries.
He's a genius composer.
He is.
(Gary and Yoon Gun have shared many ideas through music.)
They inserted their photo into the necklace.
This is for you.
- I'll put this on your neck.
-  Yes, please.
Let's give it up for Gun.
- Thank you.
-  Thank you.
(The Last Love: Cleared)
- Thank you.
-  Thank you.
We all cleared our missions today.
We'd like to say thank you to all the guests for being with us.
- Thank you!
-  Thank you!
Thank you and we love you!
I'm sorry, I love you!
Thank you, everyone. We all succeeded today.
- Thank you.
-  Thanks, guys.
- Thanks a lot.
-  Thanks.
You did a great job today.
(Each love completed our seven loves.)
(We root for your precious loves.)
I came Fukuoka to meet him.
I'm so nervous.
All right. Kyuhyun!
(You can watch the special Apology Service for Kyuhyun...)
(on our SBS website and various web portals.)
Have you ever thought about what you'd be doing if not a soldier?
What do you mean?
(Running Man Special)
("Descent of the Sun")
(Jin Goo and Ji Won wear training suits rather than uniforms.)
(Now they have name tags instead of ranking bars.)
(A dangerous invitation for Jin Goo and Kim Ji Won.)
(Next Sunday at 6:25pm)