Gather up your strength!
[Charismatic King overflowing with force]
[Running Man's clumsy challenges
that crumbles that charisma...]
[And a reverse turn...]
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Seoul Jongno-Gu, Changuimun]
It's really so beautiful!
[A place within the inner city
where the tradition remains alive]
Who's our guest today?
There are a lot of people
that live in this neighborhood.
-Ah! There's our guest!
-Where?
[Huh?  Guest?]
[Just Gary, who's late.]
Guest?
Gary's the guest!
[Not a guest but a Gae-st]
Now that Gary's here...
How many guests are we having today?
[Today's guests are people that suits
today's opening location]
Please come on out!
Is that them coming out now?
[Two people coming out while hiding their
identity with a hand fan]
[Just who are they...?]
-Who are they?
-Where do we need to go?
[Surprise]
[Korea's leading actors of Kings,
Im Ho and Lee Tae Kwon]
[The man whose specialty as a King
is overflowing with charisma]
[A forceful warrior, Lee Tae Kwon]
[Jewel of the Palace, Queen Hee Bin,
Queen Seon Duk etc...]
[The man who takes charge of all the
King's roles in historical dramas, Im Ho]
Sir... Your grip is no joke!
[His charisma is flowing even
with the introductions]
-He and Jong Kook...
-You have a great build!
Because of the project I'm working on,
I put on about 6 kg.
-Is your project all over now?
-Yes, it's all been wrapped now.
-Are the 2 of you actual friends?
-Of course!
Mr. Tae Kwon and I...
Seeing how you used the Mr. prefix,
you must not have seen him in awhile.
Normally, it would have just been Tae Kwon!
-It normally would've been...
-We used to fight a lot.
[Always the show of politeness
in front of strong men]
He's a man to be recognized...
[Can't even look at him in the eye...]
Can we take a look at your chest?
Why are you flexing when you don't
even have any muscles?
[Even his push sounds strong]
Why are you hitting my Jae Suk?!
[The Tiger leaps to Jae Suk's defense
as he is being pushed around]
It just came out of me because he kept
pushing Jae Suk around.
[Wow... This atmosphere is...?]
Why don't you two go at it?
[This really is... Full of anticipation]
[Anticipation filled match]
[Lee Tae Kwon vs. Mr. Capable]
The two kings can do rock-paper-scissors.
The two kings can play rock-paper-scissors
to pick 2 of their subjects.
Then once that's done,
there will be 3 people remaining.
Then the remaining 3 will become a nation...
The remaining 3 isn't a nation...
[Sense of unease?]
-That's not a nation.
-Please proceed with rock-paper-scissors.
['Ho' Nation and 'Kwon' Nation]
[Time to pick teams]
-Then the two of you...
-Yes.
Rock-paper-scissors!
['Ho' Nation picks first]
I think this has already been decided.
First... As the King that's
responsible for one nation...
Hurry up and pick.
[With one phrase from the young one,
he immediately becomes mute.]
-What?
-You're older than him!
This is how I've lived for the past year.
You really are like a part of the Running Man.
[Then... Who is his pick?]
-There's one person I've got my eye on.
-Who is it?
-You.
-Me?
[He chooses Mr. Capable]
-This really is going to be a match!
-This is going to be fun today!!
You have to protect me.
I think this is fate.
The way I see it... This nation is
going to have a different King soon.
[A scenario that everyone can picture?]
Even though Im Ho has played a lot
of roles as a King...
But usually, he's just eating lots
of delicious foods...
In about a 50-episode drama...
In about 20 of those episodes, I'm eating.
And in about 15 of the episodes,
I'm lying in bed being treated for an illness.
And the rest of the 5 episodes,
I'm usually playing dead from an illness.
['Kwon' Nation's selection]
[Makes the selection with a fierce stare]
I just saw your stare...
I stared at him very desperately...
Lee Tae Kwon... I have to create another
nation with my own subjects...
[He was dreaming a dream of
creating and leading his own nation]
You were dreaming of your own nation?
Stop dreaming!
I'm seriously about to go crazy.
I'm not the style that just goes
to be a subject under someone.
[Just how will the day go...]
We're going to be starting with
the Sejong era today.
[The 3 nations are complete]
-This is...!
-What are you talking about now?
[From the beginning,
the signs of change in regime]
It's a habit of mine...
I like to be on the outside!
He is the King, not you...
I will reveal your mission for the day.
It's a King's race where you have to
conquer the other nations.
[Complete the missions in 9 different lands]
[And the first team to win
takes over that land]
[Take hold of your own land
within that short period of time]
[Race to conquer the land... Start!]
Hey, Ji Hyo...
You want me to tell you a surprising story?
Lee Tae Kwon and Gary are the same age.
-What?  What did you say?
-He's the same age as Gary!
We should just treat him casually
and comfortably!
-I'm uncomfortable with that.
-He's younger than me and he's your friend!
-That's okay.  I like treating him as older.
-He's your friend, a friend.
-No way!  Really?
-Jong Kook is older than him.
We have to go to one of these
places on here, right?
So we have to get to these places quickly
and get things done quickly.
So we have to get to these 9 places quickly
and mark it as our own, right?
-Just look at the person next to you...
-Tae Kwon is younger than me.
-Really?
-That's right!
-How old are you?
-I'm 36.
-Really?
-Tae Kwon was born in 1977!
-Then we can be friends.
-Really?
-He's the same as Gary...
-You're right.  They're the same age.
[Same age as Gary and
1 year younger than Jong Kook]
He is pretty immature...
How shall we handle this?
Should we do it by order?
[His force is flowing out with each word]
-You should be sincere about it.
-Really?
-Just go this way!
-Where can we go?
[King Kwon's charisma is in full mode!]
Wow, our King is so charismatic!
[On the other hand...]
Please promise me not to get pissed
no matter what happens today.
[The King is listening at full attention]
Since we never know what could happen...
-Do you understand?
-Yes.
-Don't wave when you get out of the car.
-This neighborhood is really pretty.
-Right?
-The people I know around here...
-This is my first time here.
[A quiet atmosphere that's hard
to be seen in Seoul]
[Bu Ahm Dong neighborhood that invites people
into their cafes while out on their strolls]
We can conquer this place here...
[Even the way of his speech is King-like]
All he can think about is winning right now...
[All he can think of is to expand
the territory of his nation]
You want all of this right?
Tae Kwon, you want to conquer all this, right?
All of these 9 locations.
-Of course.  We have to conquer them all.
-See?
-We can give them these two.
-Ah, these two?
Your competitiveness is like Choi Min Soo.
Just your way of speech is different.
I'm a little more caring.
He says he's more caring...
He really is shameless.
-I... I really think that.
-So shameless.
-How do you think of yourself?
-That I'm really caring.
-This is the place, right?
-What's that?
['Ho' Nation arrives at
one of the mission locations]
[2 mission locations are side by side?]
-Which one shall we go to?
-Shall we go into the barber shop?
-Yeah, let's do that.
-Bookstores are always hard.
[Imagining the bookstore mission
to be difficult?]
[Interior of a classic style barber shop]
What's this?
[What's the mission here?]
We came here on a mission.
[Comb Wrestling]
[Stop the side parting to succeed]
You'll be having the showdown with me.
[The opponent they'll be having
the showdown with is none other than...]
[The youngest PD, Lee Hwa Jin?]
[A terrorizing member that made the
older brother's legs weak at the knees]
[Strong PD, who practices
mixed martial arts in real life]
[Stop his attack for 5 seconds]
[2 out of the 3 people has to stop him
in order to succeed this mission]
[Hmm...]
-He's our youngest PD.
-Really?
He's our youngest PD now, but he used to be
a mixed martial arts competitor.
[Big trouble... Those arms...]
-Where do we need to go?
-Over here, over here.
-The barber shop!  Barbershop!
-Hey, someone is already here...
[Mission start]
Hey.  Doesn't it seem like it's been a really
long time since there's been a barbershop?
-He doesn't like that.
-I'm sure he doesn't.
[Stop the attack of the combing
for 5 seconds!]
Ready!
[My hairstyle is my sense of pride]
[Will the giraffe be able to
protect his pride?]
Let's seriously do this.
Set... Go!
[Spray?!]
[The utterance of someone
who's used a lot of hairspray...]
You can't because of the hairspray!
I'm saying you can't because
of the hairspray!
[Kwang Soo fails...]
Fail?
Kim Mousse!
[Im Ho's turn]
-He's not that strong.
-It looks like it's going to hurt.
You shouldn't be saying stuff like that...
You're making him biased...
[Scaring his own teammate at his turn]
-You can do it!
-Im Ho, you can do it...
Don't think that you're going to lose.
[A King's pride]
[Did he succeed in stopping it?]
[Fail...]
Why do you all...!
[Finish off the styling?]
What do I do about my hair?
-It's okay, it's okay.
-It's not as bad as I thought.
Now!  The third man's turn!
[At last, it's Mr. Capable's turn]
-I'm really sensitive there.
-Why?
[Just who will be the winner between
the PD and Jong Kook?]
[Of course...]
[Flailing his arm around without mercy]
[Hulk is here]
[Jong Kook, success]
[Since 2 members per team needs to succeed,
Ho nation team fails]
Here. It's okay.
Do you understand how we feel now?
[Consoling the PD, whose pride
has been trampled on]
-I can see steam coming out of his ears.
-Good luck, Suk Jin.
[Is this the chance since
he's sapped of energy?]
[Not so much...]
[A very thorough styling]
Father...!  No...!
[Big nosed father is here]
[With a single hairstyle change,
he's turned into a father]
How many times did you comb through?
[Sorry]
You should've planted
the hair in first, father.
Please take good care of my hair, Mr. Barber.
You have to think about the mission!
Do you know this kind of a style?
Please do that style for me.
You can do it, Gary.
[Gary is surprisingly strong]
[Can he hold out?]
[Huh??]
[Gone in one stroke]
-NO!
-More!  More!!
[Retro style complete]
-That actually looks good on you?
-It looks okay?
[Gary's transformation to a flowering boy?]
[Kwon nation finally arrives
at their destination]
We're here.
Let's go inside and get our mission.
Since we're going to conquer it anyways,
shall we take a picture?
[What is the mission in this scenic cafe?]
[Come over here!]
[If Maroo the cat will come up on your lap,
the mission is a success]
Make the cat come up onto your lap?
There it is!
[The cafe's cat, Maroo]
[All 4 of Maroo's paws have to be on the lap
for the mission to be a success]
[An event that's actually ongoing at the cafe]
-Ah, really?
-Seriously?
[If our Maroo gets up on your lap,
everything is for free]
[If you force it onto your lap,
it doesn't count]
I know you were about to force it.
Maroo!
-Maroo.
-Maroo, come here.
Come here and get the grasshopper!
Cats don't eat grasshoppers...
-Maroo...
-Maroo, come here.
[Who keeps calling me?]
Maroo!  Come here...!
Come here, come here.
Maroo!
[Slapping his knees]
Over here, over here.
[Cafe's owner is amused]
Maroo... Maroo...
Let's talk for a minute.
-Calm down.  Calm down.
-I have something to talk to you about.
Maroo... Maroo?
Maroo?  Maroo...
Is this seriously our mission?
We need something that we can do with
our skills...
This doesn't require any skills...
This is just all about luck.
What if we have to spend all day here?
[Maroo isn't even coming near]
It seems like he's dreaming about
conquering the world.
Maroo... Maroo!
He doesn't...
He doesn't have any interest right now.
If he's too coy, then Tae Kwon will get mad.
[Worrying about Tae Kwon]
[I don't care if he gets angry]
-How stressed are you right now?
-Up to here.
-Get your hair down, Ji Hyo.
[Ji Hyo's turn]
[Special permission to use both hands]
Ready, set, go.
[Useless power]
[Fail...]
[Transformed into hair of chastity]
You look so pretty!
That's pretty!
[Nice and wet...]
[Song nation, fail]
Come on, part his hair!
Can't you do that?
[Mr. Capable and PD's rematch]
-You have to put the mousse on.
-Just a little... Suk Jin!
Will you let Suk Jin slide?
[Big nosed brother's surprise attack]
I didn't mean that, sorry.
Wipe it off of him.
Suk Jin, let's not be like this.
[A very serious rematch]
[Will he succeed this time in revenge?]
[What revenge...]
I can't beat this guy...
[The muscular Hulk wins again]
If one of you two can succeed,
then your nation conquers this land.
You can do it.
[Kwang Soo's rematch]
[Calling in his inner force]
Set.. Go!
[With the superpower of his hairspray
The giraffe holds out 7:3]
-He's holding it... Holding it!
-Success.
[Ho Nation succeeds]
[The giraffe benefits from
the superpower of his hairspray]
This land belongs to Ho Nation.
[Overtook the land under Ho Nation]
[Ho Nation conquers the barbershop]
[Ho Nation immediately uploads the
picture taken with the camera]
-Upload... It's being uploading.
-It's doing it?
[Doing this allows the whole world
to witness their conquers]
Maroo... Look at this.
Maroo... Maroo!
Just what is the King of a nation doing?
[Tae Kwon working hard to lure in the cat]
[Maroo seems to show some interest
as they bring out a toy]
He likes being played with.
[Huh?  Heading towards the boys?]
He's coming!
[Bring him up on your lap!]
[Chastises Jae Suk for not
stretching out his legs]
[Can't even fight back because
he's scared of the King...]
Maroo!  That's right, Maroo...!
[Now Maroo is really into the toy]
[An irritable reaction]
You seriously...
Hey... You could have said that with words...
[Tae Kwon's tunnel vision focus at
luring Maroo]
-That's right...
[Turning their chairs around to surround it?]
It's working!
[Maroo is completely absorbed in the toy]
[They may be able to get Maroo onto
their laps right about now...]
[Eliminating Jae Suk who just gets
in the way of the mission]
This is really hurting my pride...
[The time keeps on passing by...]
[Maroo is playing in a comfortable position]
In any given week, about how many times
does he get on a customer's lap?
If it happens a lot...
He'll do that about 6 times.
-What if he doesn't want to?
-Then he won't.
[It's all Maroo's decision]
He does get on a lap every evening...
-But not on a customer's lap...
-He knows that we're not a customer.
-We came here to work too.
-That's right.
I'm sorry, but we're trying to be honest.
[Tae Kwon's interest lies only in Maroo]
[Maroo... Come here]
[All 4 paws on their legs]
We did it!
That's it... we did it...
[Cafe mission is finally a success]
-Maroo, thanks.
-Maroo, we're alive thanks to you.
I'll take the picture now as evidence.
1, 2, 3.
[Kwon Nation conquers the cafe]
Jae Suk...
-All the other teams have conquered too.
-Where?
Jong Kook's team got the barbershop
and Song Ji Hyo's team got the bookstore.
[During that time,
Song Nation conquers the bookstore]
-Korean restaurant?
-Korean restaurant.
Upload that right now.  We don't have time.
Okay.  It's been uploaded.
We're all 1:1:1.
-Let's pick up the speed now.
-Okay.
Tae Kwon really worked hard.
[With Tae Kwon's dedication,
the cafe was conquered with effort]
Tae Kwon... You're hungry, aren't you?
[Suspicious of his persistence
to go to a Korean restaurant]
Look at the route...
It's easy getting there on our route.
But this other place is even closer...
You want to go to
the restaurant because you're hungry.
I don't like the store...
I feel like we have to search for something.
At times like this, we need to be energized...
-Want to do a fighting?
-Yeah, do a fighting for us.
[The King of historical drama,
Tae Kwon's fighting]
My men...!
Everyone... Gather up your strength!
-Gather up your strength!
-Yes!
-Say Kwon nation, fighting.
-Kwon Nation...!  Fighting!!
Fighting!!!
[Full of force]
You're full of energy...
Just full of energy!
[I'm the King of Kwon Nation...!]
[Mission location.  Korean restaurant]
Take a good look at this.
[Huh?  Song Nation?]
Come here.  Come here, Ji Hyo.
Take a good look.
[Abundant authentic Korean cuisine]
[Gujeolpan]
[ShinSunlo]
[The appearance of bright and neat
Chinese-like Cuisine]
[It tastes good]
[If you match the food correctly after
hearing the explanation, you succeed!]
[Only the team that wins can eat it]
-You can only describe by taste.
-By taste?
If you explain by color or the ingredients
then you fail.
-Really only through taste?
-Yes.
[Gary with his knowledge of food
steps up to the challenge]
Come on now...
-Hurry up and do it!
-I'm about to be hypnotized here.
There it is, there it is.
[Kwon Nation also arrives]
Jae Suk just got here!  Hurry!
[Song Nation all of a sudden is in a rush]
Hurry!
Hurry up!  What are you doing right now?!
[It will only slow down the process...]
Hurry!  Other team is here now!
Come on, let's do this.
[Beef tartar]
I'll get started.
-Make sure to explain it well.
-Yes.
-You can only describe the taste.
[Curious]
It's savory... and soft...
[The depiction drawn by the foodie, Gary]
This sweet taste...
-Cotton candy!
-Sweet wafers!
This is just melting on my tongue.
As it melts on my tongue
and glides down my throat...
Shaved ice with red beans!
This sweet and savory taste
is traveling all through my body.
-Is Gajisu the correct answer?
-Stop talking!
This fresh taste...
This fresh taste!
-3, 2, 1!
-Gujeolpan!
-No!  I said, this fresh taste!
-Come out here!
-What is it that you're saying is sweet?
Beef tartar is sweet and savory!
[Beef tartar is just plain delicious]
-You should have told us it's fresh!
-I did tell you that!
The two teams can compete separately
at the same time...
-But the team that completes it first...
-We understand, we got it.
-Suk Jin.  Give me one more chance.
-Okay, I got it.
[Kwon Nation is moving to an outdoor table]
Here's your next question.
[Toasted black sesame seed ball]
-I will get started.
-Please get started.
-Please listen carefully.
-Yes, we understand.
This chewy taste which is also very fragrant.
Something else comes forth from the inside
and is sweetening my tongue.
Ah... The fragrance of this thing...
really is astounding to me.
I feel like my stomach is getting full.
What is he describing?
It's a little difficulty swallowing this thing
which is very chewy and a little sticky.
This taste... That gets stuck to your teeth.
-3...2...
-Answer.
Miljeonbyeong
[Sesame seed ball]
[The correct answer is sesame seed ball]
Suk Jin, you want to give it a try?
[Kwon nation's food spread that's been
set up outdoors]
[The item to describe is mixed bamboo shoots]
What the heck is this?
-My men!
-Yes!
He really likes to command.
He's a command mania.
A command mania.
Start getting the whiff of this.
If you can't guess it correctly,
you won't be able to return alive.
He's a jokester.
[First trying it out]
Your Highness... Please describe it for us.
It's chewy...
And it'll be the best cure for a hangover.
And how else does it taste?
It's crunchy.
It's crunchy?
-Crunchy...
-Answer!
-Pancakes!
-You're wrong.
How are pancakes good for a hangover?!
Excuse me?
That's right.  Bamboo's are crunchy.
-Crispy and crunchy.
-Ah... He should've said crispy.
Crispy or crunchy...
Your Highness... Please forgive us!
-Your Highness...
-His Majesty, His Majesty.
Your Majesty...
Highness or Majesty...
They're all up there.
-If it's too hard, you can give up here.
-No, we're not doing that.
-The other team's doing it too...
-Hurry up and do it.
Now... Here's your next one.
They're talking about meat out there.
I can hear them.
It's sweet yet bitter.
Describe it more in detail.
The sweetness that rises
from deep within the earth!
-This sweet taste...
-More than one thing grows deep in the dirt!
-Don't interrupt me...
-Earth? Deep within the earth?
When it's combined with the sweet sauce...
Did you succeed?
We can hear you guys from in there...
But you can't describe the ingredient.
You can only describe the taste
like sweet and bitter.
-Saying the meat and what's on it...
-You can't describe the ingredients!
[Jae Suk is in the process of tattling]
What is this?!
Go away!
I think you can just keep doing
what you've been doing.
His Majesty told you to leave.
Calm down.
You guys were saying meat earlier...
-Tae Kwon...
-What do you mean, Tae Kwon?
- My older friend...
-Older friend... Don't be like that.
-Hey!  He's the same age as you!
That's why I called him my older friend!
Go away!
[With his older friend's command, they run.]
Suk Jin, hurry. Hurry!
-All of you opposers...!
-Go away!
If I were to describe it again,
The bitterness comes to me
from deep within the earth.
And just when my tongue is about to
be enveloped in this bitterness,
The sweetness, just....!
Answer.
1, 2, 3.  Grilled Codonopsis!
The correct answer is fresh ginger roots.
[Dang!]
-I'll go this time.
-Okay.  Let's do this quickly.
-Okay.  Let's do it quick.  We have no time.
-You know what's on the table, right?
-Hurry!  Do it quickly!  We know what's left.
-Answer it quickly and think!
-This is really too much.
-Okay!
-Are you ready?
-Okay.  Here I go.
-Hurry up and eat it.
Guys, this is so delicious!
Guys, this is so delicious.
[That's it?]
How can you just say that it's delicious?
[That's the whole explanation?]
It's so delicious, melts in your mouth,
sweet and also savory.
That's what we wanted...
[The name is NuhbiAni]
It's fine.  Just describe the taste.
I think I know what it is.
I think we know.
Here it is!!
[Grilled abalone in butter]
Hey, hurry it up!
NuhbiAni!
[Correct]
-Answer!
-Grilled abalone in butter!
That's the correct answer.
-Did they get it first?
-The other team got it first.
[Kwon Nation fails to conquer by mere seconds]
Let's hurry up and go.
We have no time to lose.  Let's go.
What are you doing?
I see you guys just got it.
We should have worked a little faster...
We seriously lost it by seconds.
Let's go.  As long as we bond together...
Then we can do it!
This isn't over yet.
That's correct!
[Ho Nation arrives at a gallery]
[Stand in a row with the writer and
have a relay drawing to succeed]
Hello.
Then we just have to take turns and draw?
[Writer Lee Mok Eul]
Everyone attention.  The most important thing
is to draw fast and simple.  Okay?
[Must get 3 right to pass]
[The eternal symbol of the King.  Dragon]
Whatever!  Here.
Here it is.  You can guess what it is, right?
Oh!  Nice!  Draw it just like that.
Hurry, Kwang Soo!
-Okay, okay...
-Draw it quickly!
[Wow... An admirable drawing skills]
You just need to draw it just like that.
That's fine, that's fine.
You'll know it once you see it!
[All of a sudden, it looks like a snake]
What is that?
-That's a dragon.  A dragon.
-Correct!
[Ink]
That's good!
The mousse totally...
My hair is all hard now.
This isn't the time to be worrying
about the hair now.
No, this isn't the time to do that.
[He seemed to have understood it's ink]
That's good!
I think he's going to know what it is.
[Kwang Soo is also drawing easily]
It's all done, all done.
A seal?
Ink, ink, ink!
[King Im Ho, who didn't understand the message
relayed by his subjects]
-What is it?
-Im Ho!  This one is easy!
[Ink stone]
This is easy!  We just did something like it!
The answer is this, not the other.
[Just need to tweak the previous
drawing a little]
-You drew one like it earlier.  The same.
-Think about the previous one!
[The giraffe trying to
draw it exactly the same]
What is it?
It was two but now just one?
-What is it?
-Ink.  Ink.
-I mean, ink stone!
-That's it!
-Ink stone.
-Yeah! You should've said that first!
Seriously!  Come on!
[Sorry...]
[Kwon nation arrives at the supermarket]
[Ice cream challenge]
[If you can throw the popsicle stick
in the trash can, you succeed]
-Ice cream.
-Ice cream?
[The King has to finish the ice cream and get
the stick in the garbage to succeed]
-Pick the smallest one.  Which one?
-Here it is.
This will be fine.
[What's the ice cream they're getting
for the price of one?]
How much is this?
-50 cents.
Where?  Where do we have to get it in?
Since we have to get it done before someone
else arrives, let's get it done.
-You have to eat it quickly.
-I think we need to eat both of them now.
-They're here already.
-It's him again!
Mr. Lee Tae Kwon!
Ready?  1, 2, 3.
[Distressed Kwon Nation]
Are you okay?
It's done.
Did you see him finish it in one bite?
[And succeed at first attempt?]
[Fail]
You see who's here, right?
[Have to eat another to get
another opportunity to toss]
My old friend!
Old friend, what are you doing here?
But you really do eat it fast.
[Finishing it in one bite]
He's already done?
[Sadly misses from the wind]
-Hurry, hurry!
-He's really upset by that.
[Retrieving the popsicles that
he left in someone's care]
Old friend... Old friend,
I'm afraid to even talk to you.
What?  You want us to get ice creams?
[Song Nation is also getting ice creams]
-Fighting!
[Tae Kwon is getting the ice chunks
off the outside of the ice cream]
-This part isn't ice cream.
-You're right. That's true.
-The twin popsicles.  That's right.
-Twin popsicles?
-How much is that?
-50 cents.
-Let's get you back up.
-1, 2, 3.
You really eat it so fast.
[Manly Tae Kwon finishing
his ice cream in one bite]
[He misses by a lot]
No.  He has to eat it like this.
[Even if it's a lot, he only needs 2 bites]
[Manly Tae Kwon who hates to lose]
[Huh?!]
[Ah... Too bad!]
No!
I thought it was going to go in!
Let's so.  We can do this.
[Unfortunately hits the rim and misses]
Twin popsicles are no longer allowed.
After this round, it's no longer allowed.
It's okay.  We can get it done.
Hey.  Get whatever you want to eat.
Look at this.  How about this one?
Don't feel too burdened by it.
-Don't eat too fast.  Take your time.
-We'll be careful and do it in one shot.
Just throw it well.
So cold... My teeth hurts.
Your teeth couldn't hurt already.
You're still too young.
Our King can do that well.
Your teeth shouldn't hurt already at your age.
[Working to melt it with his hands]
[Is this a King's wisdom?]
[The taste of death...]
Tae Kwon, what are you doing?
She's done, she's done.
We're ready.
Here I go.
Lightly, lightly.
No, no.  Eat the other one.
There's one more.
-It's our turn.
-No, it isn't.
Eat it right now.  Hurry up and eat it.
Just put it in your mouth!
-We don't have any time!
-What are you doing to your Queen?
You should be thinking about the
well being of your Queen!
Ji Hyo...!
What are you doing, Tae Kwon?
-He ate this in one bite?
-You really are smart... Smart!
[King's wisdom of melting
the ice cream under the sun]
-Look at our King.
-Our King is melting the ice cream in the sun.
Let's go!
Let's go.  Let's go!
Let's go!  1, 2...
[Unfortunately misses from the wind...]
Okay!  Our chance is here, Tae Kwon!
[King Kwon's another attempt]
One bite... Two bites...
[Always finishing it in 2 bites]
One bite... Two bites... That's right.
[Easily polishing it off]
-My old friend...
-No, you can't... Tae Kwon...
[Huh?]
[Bouncing off the rim again!]
[Song Nation was watching with ease]
They're not ready yet.  Let us go again.
-No, no, no... We're ready.  We bought one.
-You haven't paid for it.
-You have to pay for it.
-Tae Kwon.  Come here quickly!
[Another attempt due to Song Nation
not being prepared]
Gary, he's your friend.
-Suk Jin... Look at him.
-He's younger than me, but he seems older.
Tae Kwon.  You seem older than me.
The rush of his anger!
-That ice cream...
-Wow...
[Huh?  A goal?]
[Bounces off the rim again!]
My old friend, you look a little upset?
[Should've thrown it better!]
[Song Nation's Ji Hyo challenges again]
You can't eat it in several bites.
Just shove it all in there.
-Put it in there first...
-Get in all in there at once, Ji Hyo.
-You need to get it done.
-Why does your teeth hurt already?
[An unbearable pain of the cold]
[Back to buying]
[Ji Hyo's challenge all finished]
-Let's do this.  Let's win.
-Throw it hard.
[How can this be?  Success!]
[Wow... This is Ace Ji Hyo's skills]
[Dismay x 100]
[Eat...]
[And eat again...]
[Hold it under the sun]
[Threw it... And threw it again...]
[But the result is defeat...]
Song Ji Hyo!  Song Ji Hyo...!
[Defeat...]
[Victory cheers]
Seriously... Losing twice to the same team...
I know... Seriously...
[His blood pressure is rising]
Disturbing our peaceful slumber,
Gae-Ji-Jin...!
We will not let you get away with it!
Why those little...!
What is this?!
[The ending is always with King Kwon's drive]
This is it... This is the place.
[Another Running Man's flag just up the road]
[Guest house]
We're really going to win this one.
What if they follow behind us again?
Welcome to the guest house.
Come over this way.
[PD Dong Juan styled
as the owner of the boarding house]
Here is your mission.
You have to recite the times table 5 times
without making a mistake to succeed.
If you get it wrong in process,
you get a cold back wash as punishment.
-Backwash you say?
-They're here again.
We were just going to pass by...
But we saw the landmark.
Why do you keep following us?
We just saw it as we were passing by.
Since the other team is here,
the opposing team does the backwash.
That's right.  Let's do that, Suk Jin!
-Let's just do it with water slap!
-Okay! Water slaps!
-Backwash is too light.  Water slaps.
-What is that?
-You okay with that?  You're good?
-Yeah!  Let's do that.
-Are you okay with your glasses?
-I'm fine!
I'll make your face very smooth.
-This is a total war.
-Why are you bothering us so much?
-We just saw it on our way... We passed it.
-You could've just driven past it.
That's not how this should be...
King Kwon was working so hard
with his ice cream...
You have no idea how upset King Kwon is.
Let's pick the person too.
The person to recite the multiplication table.
-No, you're too good at it.
-You know you're good.
How about my old friend there?
Tae Kwon...
Tae Kwon.  You pick someone too.
We have to pick one too then.
We have to pick.
-We pick the blank head.
-The blank head.
[Kwon's Nation picks Miss Blank]
Is this it then?
Miss Blank is weak at stuff like this.
If you can recite the multiplication table
5 times within 30 seconds, you win.
They're going to give out the question,
and we have to get it right 5 times.
-In sequence?
-If you get it right, then it's over.
[Kwon nation first to challenge]
-8x8.
-64.
-8x6. -42.
[8x6=42?]
[Refreshing water slap to chase the heat away]
[Song Nation filled with glee]
-It's okay.  We can go again.
-You okay?
-9x6
-54.
-4x7?
-28.
[If there's a lapse in time,
an immediate water slap]
-5x8?
-40.
-7x9?
-63.
-9x2?
-18!
[Time lapse]
Why?  Wait!
[Water slap punishment]
-Let's just hold it in.
-Why don't we stop this?
How many times do we need to get hit
because of Ji Hyo now?
I'm really not good at this.
Ji Hyo can do it while sitting.
-She can sit?
-Of course.  We'll protect Ji Hyo.
-You're nice...
-Our aim are these two!
[King Kwon gripping the water bowl
with a stony expression]
Let's just see how it sounds.
Slap it down there.
[A forceful water slap]
Start.  7x9?
-7x9?
-What?  What did you say?
What did you say?
[Profusion of water slaps]
-4x8? -32!
-6x6? -36!
-5x3?
-What?
-That's so harsh!
-Is there something solid in there?
Is there something solid in the water?
I think there's something
solid in the water right now!
5x6=30!
[Time out]
-This really hurts!
-Ji Hyo, you can stay seated.
Thank you... Thank you.
[The gentlemen taking care of Ji Hyo]
Wait... Shall we switch out the person
to answer the multiplication questions?
[An appeal from the subjects
who are soaked to the bone]
[King Kwon coolly switching out his spot]
Tae Kwon's stance has become
very aggressive being on the show.
Did you see that?
He's ready to get soaked.
[Getting ready to get
forcefully water slapped]
You're actually quite scary.
[Getting rid of the hat
for the sake of laughter]
-Fighting!
-Fighting!  Kwon!  Kwon!
-4x8? -32!
-2x7? -14.
-2x7?
-14.
[Huh?]
[2x7=14 is correct...]
Why?  Why are you slapping?  It's right!
14 is right?
It's not 14?  Huh?
[Receiving a slap in return]
What's 2x7 then?
-Stop it... That's enough.
-Hey!
[Stop with the revenge...
Time is passing by....]
49!
-4x5?
-8!
[4x5=8?]
4x5=8?!
That's 4x5=20!
[Time out]
You guys be prepared.
You're dead.
[King Kwon's rage gauge is rising]
-You can't hit Ji Hyo.
-Grit your teeth.
-Careful...
[King Kwon biding his vengeance]
Set.. Go!
-7x7? -49.
-4x5? -20.
-8x7?
-...
6x3?
[6x3=36?]
-5x6?
-46.
-8x2?
-18.
-Do it!  Do it right!
-Ji Hyo, you're really awful!
Hey.  Whose side are you on?
Are you on their side?
[Ji Hyo's collapsed memory of
the multiplication table]
-Gary.
-Tae Kwon... Why not take the hat off?
[Tae Kwon refuses to take the hat off?]
Don't worry.  I'll take it off with the slap.
[Kwon nation's challenge]
Set, go!
-5x9? -45!
-4x7? -42!
[A strong slap!]
Sorry!  Sorry, old friend!
Old friend!  Forgive me!
[Let's take this to the end]
-3x5? -15.
-6x6? -36.
-4x8? -32!
-9x4? -36!
-4x7? -28!
[Success]
Okay!!
[Kwon Nation succeeds]
We won!
You guys have succeeded.
You guys got your share of
the water slaps today.
[Kwon Nations conquers the guest house!]
[Ho Nation succeeds
at anchovy noodle challenge]
Anchovy noodles...
This tastes unbelievable.
[The unbelievable taste]
I wonder what kind of anchovies they use?
Please stop doing things like that!
Let's go!
Im Ho... You should take off the ear muffs.
[This is how King Ho gets tormented
by his protector...]
[Anyways, the Ho Nations conquers
the anchovy noodle house]
[Now the only land left is the dry cleaners]
[Ho Nation heading off to the dry cleaners,
the last place remaining]
All the 3 flags are still out here.
No one's here yet.  No one's come yet.
No one's come through yet.
Here it is, here.
[Song Nation also arrives]
-Is no one here yet?
-No, someone's here.  There's the car.
[Kwon Nations follows right behind]
They're here already.
-What the heck?  Everyone's here?
-We're all here.
What is this?  What is the mission here?
Everyone come get one.
The King himself...
-We can get that for you.
-Aren't your subjects doing anything?
-We could've done it...
-Im Ho, Im Ho...!
Im Ho!  How many times have I told you
not to step out like that?
-Okay...!
-Don't do that and just stand still!
Why is this team like this?
You're the King...!
-You have to respect your King.
-He has no clue!
Our nation is doing very well.
Even though Kwon nation may only have
2 lands compared to you,
but we are all still bound together as one...
[Kwon Nation doesn't have
much to brag about...]
What did you guys end up like this?
Would you like to hear what
cavalier laughter sounds like?
-Let us hear it...
-Kwon Nation...
[The forceful sounding laughter of the King]
[Tae Kwon slyly does everything asked of him]
Let's look at the mission.
Right.  Since we were the first to arrive...
[His Majesty's jump rope]
[Two people jump the rope together and if the
King comes in and can jump 5, you succeed]
Im Ho.  This isn't difficult.
2 people can jump rope together...
And the King can come in and just jump 5.
We just need to do 5.
[If the Kings of each nation jump the rope
5 times while wearing a hat, it's a success]
The people handling the rope say
'Your Majesty, please jump higher'
And that's when you can jump in.
-Okay.
-Please jump higher?
Im Ho.  You just come in.
When you do, just grab him here.
And don't do anything else...
What do you mean, don't do anything else?
He's your King!  Your King!
-Just come in and then...!
-What's wrong with that nation?
Why is that nation in that shape?
Don't do anything else...
Wow...Seriously.
Just come in and just grab our waists!
I think we'll get it in the first try...
-We can just finish it in one try, right?
-Of course!
Let's go!
Your Majesty... Please jump higher!
[Subject giraffe's mistake...]
His foot is already caught.
[Nothing's going right
for Kwang Soo lately...]
Song Nation, I don't think this is for you...
-We can't jump short.  Jump high!
-There he goes again.
The King is being scolded,
and the giraffe is being scolded too.
You have to jump up really high!
-The way I see it...
-I'm sorry, but we're talking.
[Oh my...
Even the giraffe is disregarding the King]
[Song Nation's challenge]
-1... 2...
-Your Majesty... Please jump higher!
-1... 2... 3...
-She can't come in...
[Queen Ji Hyo not knowing what to do...]
-Your Highness!
-Why aren't you coming in, Your Highness?
[Ultimately, a failure...]
-Your Majesty... Please jump higher!
-It's scary...!
Let's do this well.
[Currently the Kwon Nation
has only conquered 2 lands]
Too tight.
The space for him to come in is too tight.
Hurry, hurry.  Say the words.
Your Majesty... Please jump higher!
[Fail]
[Subject Yoo's misstep]
-Higher... Higher...
-The timing... This is Yoo Jae Suk's fault.
You saw Tae Kwon coming in like the wind?
You have to come in like that.
Im Ho... Do you get that?
[Tae Kwon throwing out a gentle order]
-He's really warm.
-Of course, he is.
-He's even advising...
-Of course.
Just think that you can do it
and go in there.
-I can do it.
-Come in when we call you.
Don't think about anything else
and bend your legs.
-The things is...
-Pull up your legs.
[The endless rant of the Spartacus-Kook]
-I'm just getting his morals up.
-Looking at Im Ho's face...
Only his face is different,
but he's exactly like Jung Jae Hyung.
My nickname from my team is Koala.
Why are you bringing up something like that?
He really is a nice person.
There aren't many people that talk a lot
who isn't nice.
[Then Jae Suk must be the nicest person...]
Here we go!
Just get yourself ready.
Set, go!
Your Majesty... Please jump higher!
Now!
[Facing the rope head on?]
[Ho Nation, fail]
He's not getting it.  He's not...
He just ran in there...
[Frustrated yet laughing Hulk]
He was afraid of being scolded,
so he just ran in there at the command.
[My luck...]
It's our turn this time.
-No, Im Ho... Look at this...
-He's teaching again.  Another lesson...
You have to come in
right when you hear the thwack.
Thwack.  Thwack...
You have to come in on the thwack.
Hey!  Come in on the thwack!
On the thwack!
Come in on the thwack!
Thwack, thwack, come in on the thwack!
Okay, I got it.
No matter how we have to do it,
we have to win this one.
[Kwon Nation has plenty of chances
to win this round]
Here we go.
Set... Go!
-He's good...
-1...
[Before she can even go in on the thwack,
it's a failure...]
-What are you two doing?
-I was a little short.
-What are you doing right now?
-Jump rope!
-You saw it too!
-You can't jump rope like that!
We can do a better job next time.
They seem like old Hollywood couple now.
[Acting like an old Hollywood couple?]
Are the kids growing up well?
Just stop with your concerns!
[Cool Hyo-Mi Moore and Gae-Ruce Willis?]
[Has he constantly been
in the ready position?]
[He's like a football quarterback!]
[King Kwon thirsting for the win]
I'll come in at your words.
He actually does everything we ask of him.
It's true.  He does everything we ask of him.
My men...
You may begin!
[Forceful King Kwon that does everything
he's told to do]
He does everything we ask...
Say it, say it!
Your Highness... Please jump higher!
[Tae Kwon jumping in like lightning]
We did it!!
[Success]
[Kwon Nation succeeds!]
[Ho Nation feeling upset]
Let's try it one more time.
Our pride is staked on it, so let's do it.
[Challenging again
with their pride staked on the line]
When you hear the thwack,
come in from the front.
Thwack, and come in from the front.
[Just as Warrior Hulk orders...]
[Just what will happen to the Tiger's pride?]
Your Highness... Please jump higher!
[Oh?]
[King Ho jumping in there like lightning!]
[Success!]
[King Ho upholding his pride]
[Thanking his Warrior Hulk]
1... 2...!
[Kwon Nation conquers the dry cleaners]
Thank you... Thank you, Im Ho.
[All the lands have been divided 3 each]
I feel better now.
[Moving off to their next mission destination]
[Just what is the meaning behind
the land that they conquered?]
[Time to go up against one another with
the land they conquered in between]
[The last battle location]
[X-model house located in Hapjungdong]
This is the perfect location for a battle.
[The final battle]
[Steal the landmarks from other teams]
[Stick the landmarks that you've gained
on your name tags on your backs]
[Once the name tags are ripped off,
you can steal the landmarks beneath it]
Then you can steal the landmark
that the person has on them.
[Once you gained all the landmarks the
other teams have, you win the entire battle]
[Kwon Nation with 3 lands conquered
out of the 9 lands]
So we have to take one of these each...
How about 2 for him, and 1 or you?
Since mine will get ripped off no matter what.
The way I think is that...
They're going to think I have most of them.
And even if they did think that,
they wouldn't dare to come on to you.
We'll just have to stick it on me,
what else can we do?
[Reliable King Kwon, no matter what]
Tae Kwon, this doesn't feel good, does it?
No, it doesn't feel that great.
What does it feel like to rip it off?
How you do it is...
You grab this...
Watch.
[2 years know-how]
[There's a method to tearing off easily]
Rip it off by the end.
The middle doesn't rip it off well.
Put your arm out towards me.
[Quick as the wind]
[King Kwon teaching skills already?
Will he be able to unify the lands?]
[This is kind of thrilling]
[Tae Kwon leading the pack
to find the opponents]
Be careful of your back.
They wouldn't be hiding in places
like this, right?
[They can't hide inside the refrigerator...]
[Weak Song Nation
without a single strong warrior]
-Jae Suk?
-Where? Where?
[Discovered Jae Suk
of Kwon nation in the distance]
Suk Jin... Suk Jin... He saw us!
There they are, there they are!
[Jae Suk also discovered Song Nation]
Tae Kwon, Tae Kwon!
-Tae Kwon?
-Yeah?  Found someone?
[Running away for now out of fear of Tae Kwon]
[Battle of strength that preys
on the weak nation first]
Hurry up and close it.
Close it quickly!
Hurry up and close it!  Jae Suk!
Why are you being like this?
You're a little rough to a woman.
There is no such thing.
Rip it off even just one person.
[Ho Nation watching over the battle
between the other 2 nations]
They've met downstairs.
-Just surrender!
-Ji Hyo, hurry up and escape.  Get out!
You're so caring... So caring!
Ji Hyo!  Just hurry up and escape!
[Gary doing whatever he can to protect Ji Hyo]
[Song Nation's Ji Hyo succeeds at escaping]
[The reason for letting
Ji Hyo get escape like that?]
Actually... It's better for you to do it.
But if they get a hold of her,
it's all over.
[Because they've stuck all 3 locations
on Ji Hyo's back]
[If Ji Hyo's name tag gets torn...]
[They'll lose all the land that they have]
[The remaining Song Nation's Gary...]
[He can't escape from Tae Kwon...]
[That's no joke...]
[Tae Kwon, the King of strength]
[Song Nation's Gary-Out!]
[Who will beat his strength?]
[But there's nothing on Gary's name tag]
[Ji Hyo with all 3 land tags on her bag
just barely escapes]
Come this way.  Come this way for now.
Where did Suk Jin go?
First... Let's decide.
Using elevator as the center...
[For the sake of convenience,
using this location as their center]
-Then shall we do inside outside?
-Okay.  Inside outside.
[Wise King Im Ho?]
You really are a King.
I feel really good because...
Because I'm finally of use.
Let's constantly notify one another
of our location.
[Checking the walkie talkie
they're wisely using]
Save me.
[Even if it's practice,
why say such a thing...?]
I'm being chased right now.
[Ho Nation on their way to attack
the easy Song Nation?]
-I think Suk Jin is hiding somewhere.
-Right?
He always hides somewhere, right?
[However... There's a sense of unease about
Ho Nation unlike the Kwon Nation...]
[Will Im Ho pull it off?]
[On the other hand, Tae Kwon and his
subject Ha Ha hunting down their prey]
[In the emergency exit,
in the emergency exit]
-Emergency exit?
-There's someone in the emergency exit?
[Using the walkie talkies to communicate with
members while apart is a requirement]
Something feels strange...
Don't trust anyone...
Seriously.
[Why is he saying that all of a sudden?]
Do you understand?  Don't trust anyone.
[Anyways, wherever they're hiding,
Suk Jin and Ji Hyo are nowhere in sight]
We're on the third floor right now.
[Kwon Nation is spread out searching for
weak Song Nation]
Im Ho, out!
Im Ho's out?
Really?
Who ousted him?
[Blank...]
Did Suk Jin oust him by any chance?
[Why is Im Ho out?]
Im Ho, out!
What did he say?
[Im Ho being dragged away to jail]
[Why, and who did he get ousted by?
Just what happened?]
Hey.  Suk Jin and Ji Hyo ousted Im Ho?
When even Kwang Soo's still in the game?
Then are they going around with Kwang Soo?
-Kwang Soo probably ran away...
-Kwang Soo didn't betray him?
-Kwang Soo betrayed him?
-He has no reason to betray him.
[Uneasy Mr. Capable
after his King's been ousted]
Jae Suk.  Why did Im Ho get ousted?
[The mystery surrounding Im Ho's death]
Hurry... Hurry and get up there.  Hurry.
-Why?
-Just go up there for a minute.
-Let's talk.  Talk.
-Talk?
[Ho Nation's Kwang Soo also joining]
Hey... Why is Im Ho out?
Come here, come here.
Come here Kwang Soo.
Who... You guys tore it off?
-No.
-It wasn't us.
We separated from you?
No, but he wasn't even that far
away from me.
You were with Im Ho.
We were supposed to go around downstairs
and meet back up.
But while we were going around separately,
someone must've gotten to him.
Who could it be then?
Have you seen Suk Jin?
I haven't seen him.
What did this happen?
[Was it 2 against one between
Suk Jin-Ji Hyo vs. Im Ho?]
I heard Suk Jin was on the first floor.
Then it means he and Ji Hyo...
It means that he lost to Ji Hyo 1 on 1.
[Well... If it's Im Ho...]
-Ji Hyo isn't your average girl...
-I noticed that earlier.
[Then Ace Ji Hyo is the suspect?]
Let's go catch Ji Hyo first.
You really didn't tear it off of him?
Let's find out their whereabouts.
Since one of their
team member's been ousted...
[Everyone separates
with questions still unanswered]
[Just who's the real criminal
that killed Im Ho?]
[These 2 are the suspects for now...]
I thought you were one of our staff members...
You scared me!
-Did one of you kill Im Ho?
-We didn't kill him.
[It doesn't seem like a lie...]
We didn't kill him.
-We've been in hiding all this time.
-Im Ho?
-Let us go just once...
-Just once...
But in exchange,
once you take care of the red team...
We'll give you our backs.
We have to do what we can!
We're at his mercy here...
Can't you just close your eyes
and count to 10?
[Song Nation using their brains to survive]
-5 seconds.
-5 seconds?
[Coming after them
after giving them 5 second start]
How about we start from here?
Where should we go?
If you keep this up...
Then you'll really be in trouble later.
1... 2... 3!
[What 5 seconds?  Coming after them after 2]
Why are you being abandoned?
What are you doing?
[After Im Ho's been ousted,
Mr. Capable is being alert to Kwang Soo]
They're coming, they're coming!
-Grab them!
-It's Ji Hyo!!
-Kwang Soo!!
-It's Suk Jin!
[Tae Kwon corralling the Song Nation!]
[Song Nation being cornered within moments]
-What are you doing, what are you doing?
-You got Im Ho!
[Ha Ha and Kwon working together
to get Big nosed brother first]
[Kwang Soo eliminating Big nosed brother's
name tag with one swipe]
-Who ripped off Im Ho's?
-I don't know. You didn't do it?
-Did you get it?
-Ji Hyo!
You saw me tear it off, right?
There's nothing here.
She has all 3 on her!
Ji Hyo has all 3!
[Must rip Ji Hyo's off to gain all their land]
Calm down.
Tae Kwon... Just trust your instincts
and tear it off her back.
-It's all on her back...
-Go away.
Just grab one of her arms.
[But is Ji Hyo really the one
who got rid of Im Ho?]
Jong Kook, think about it carefully right now.
It'll be 3 against 2.
-Jong Kook.
-It'll be 3 against 2.
[If Ji Hyo is ousted,
then Song Nation collapses]
Kwang Soo!  Kwang Soo!
Don't rip it off.
Kwang Soo, don't rip it off.
[Tae Kwon gets rid of Ji Hyo's name tag]
-She had all 3!
-Yes!  It's ours. He got it, it's ours.
Let's see just how well you end up.
-Hey!
-I didn't rip it off!
You planned this whole thing, didn't you?
Let's see just how well you end up!
I didn't plan it, I just participated!
[All 3 of Song Nation's lands
now belong to Kwon Nation]
Hey... You planned this whole thing!
[Now that we think about it,
Kwang Soo today...]
[Kwang Soo's been really forward
about ripping the name tags off...]
[Wait...]
-Ji Hyo, you've worked hard.
-You've worked hard, Ji Hyo.
-Kwang Soo's being really strange...
-Kwang Soo is acting strange.
Did Kwang Soo rip yours off?
Kwang Soo... and Tae Kwon were flanking
both of my sides...
Tae Kwon did end up tearing it off,
but Kwang Soo...
[Kwang Soo has been especially aggressive
about ousting Suk Jin and Ji Hyo today...]
The way I see it...
[Huh?  Tae Kwon has something to say?]
Kwang Soo killed Im Ho.
[Kwang Soo eliminated Im Ho,
his own team member?]
-I did?
-Yeah.
Why would I kill him?
I asked Suk Jin earlier...
I did.
-Suk Jin said he didn't know what happened.
-I asked him...
He wasn't acting.  He was being sincere.
Why would I tear his off?
I'm sure he tore it off while Im Ho
was walking in front of him.
[Who's the owner of this hand that
got rid of Im Ho?]
[The truth behind that incident
is finally being revealed!]
Im Ho...
Was ousted by Kwang Soo.
[Lee Kwang Soo...
Just what is going on with him today?]
[2 hours before filming started this morning]
[A secret meeting with the Pd]
[This looks like the scene when something
is normally given to a spy...]
[Touched Kwang Soo tightly grabs
onto the PD's hand]
-It's been too long, right?
-It hasn't been long, it's the first time!
Yes!  I did it!
[In all the kingdoms of the history,
there are warriors and mistresses...]
[Spy Kwang Soo given the order to
oust all the members of Running Man]
[Im Ho, always have your back towards me.
I'll protect it from the back]
[Deciding the first person to oust
will be his own King]
[After tempting him to come to a place
where no one is around...]
[Coldly ousting his own member, Im Ho]
[Without even knowing the reason,
Im Ho is ousted just like that]
I'm sorry... I'm sorry.
I'll explain it all to you later!
[Just like this,
the spy's dream bloomed bigger...]
The way I see it...
Kwang Soo was the one who killed Im Ho.
I did?
-Why would I kill him?
-I'm sure he did while Im Ho was in front.
-Why would I?!
-I can smell it.
I didn't do that!  I didn't oust Im Ho!
[Tae Kwon's sharp senses]
We'll have to ask him about that.
Um... That's not...
You're not supposed to do that.
Why are you stuttering?
Are you going to abandon him?
Then give him to us.
-Wait... You'll be left alone then.
-Him?
If he's a traitor, then give him to us.
Wait a second... Wait.
I've really got a lot in my mind right now,
so give me a little time.
[If the atmosphere is like this,
Kwang Soo's going to be suspected more!]
-No.
-You're suspecting that I did it?
-Just a minute...
-It's Kwang Soo.
What have I done for you to suspect me?
-I didn't say that you did it.
-Why are you suspecting me?
Because I definitely saw you
walking away with Im Ho.
-I told you I was then separated...
-Are you a spy?
Come on now...
What's that, a spy?
What's a spy?
What's a spy?  What is that?  Huh?
Are there spies here?
One per team?
What if I'm not?
What are you going to do if I'm not?
If you're not?  Well then...
If you're not, then we'll have to
treat you to a nice meal.
[It's not like he's a kid, but make it up
to him by buying him something to eat...]
-Come on... Something to eat?
-I don't think it's Tae Kwon.  Not him.
I don't think it's Tae Kwon.
Go upstairs.  Go upstairs for now.
-Why are you sending me away?
-Just go upstairs for now.
-You should be helping me out!
-I need to...!
Kwang Soo, this is the best I can do for you
for now... This is my last act of love for you.
Go upstairs for now.
Give me some time to think.  Okay?
-Give me some time to think.
-Jong Kook...
-Give me some time to think first.
-This makes no sense...
Give me some time to think first.  Okay?
This is the best thing I can do for you.
Just go upstairs for now.
[He can't even argue to stay together
and is just going upstairs]
I'm still not even close...
Spy's road is long and dangerous.
I'm not right for this yet.
This wasn't the right time.
[Reflecting that he's not right to be
a spy just yet]
Please give me another chance in 2 years.
This wasn't the right time yet.
I rushed it, I'm sorry.
Ever since Im Ho's been ousted
the atmosphere has been really weird.
Even though we haven't had it
happen too often lately,
but when it comes to spies,
there could be 2...
Two people can...
-With me?
-Yeah.
It could be you two.
[Now the suspicion is being
flung to Ha Ha too?]
Why are you asking me all this right now then?
First...
Let's ask each other some questions first.
Everything we've all said and our behaviors...
Jong Kook is by himself on the first floor,
so go downstairs quickly.
Jong Kook is alone.
[Receiving the tip]
What did you say?
Jong Kook is by himself downstairs!
Hurry.  Jong Kook is alone downstairs.
Tae Kwon!
Tae Kwon... He's alone on the 1st floor now,
Tae Kwon...!
[Plans to use Tae Kwon to
eliminate Jong Kook early]
[It's not weird that he's getting
so antsy all of a sudden?]
I'm really going to go crazy...
Hurry, hurry, hurry!
[Tae Kwon, please come on down]
[Appearing out of nowhere all of a sudden
just like superman]
[Superman vs. Hulk?]
Tae Kwon...
[Since there's so much suspicion going around,
cease the pending attack for now]
My head hurts... Seriously!
My head is killing me now!
What's the point of ceasing?  Get rid of him
at this given chance, you dummies!!
[Ha Ha overreacting because he thinks
Jong Kook's suspicions are weird]
[Who's right here?]
What's this?
Then...
Then I'll stay out of it and the 3 of you
oust Kwang Soo out first and come to me.
-Then you're going to stay out of it?
-Yeah.  I'll stay out of it.
Then we can out him if he stays out.
That's a good thing.
There's a point to what I'm saying right?
The three of you go...
-And you can oust Kwang Soo.
-Okay.  You stay out of it then.
What Jong Kook said is right.
First, let's oust Kwang Soo first.
[Me? Me?]
I really don't think I can be a spy.
I can't do it anymore.
I'm just going to turn myself in.
[About to have a mental breakdown
from trying to be a spy]
[Everyone spreading out to capture
Kwang Soo for now]
What's going on here?
Why are you trusting someone else
instead of trusting your own teammate?
It's not about that,
but when Im Ho got ousted...
-Why are you trusting someone else?
-Im Ho got ousted all of a sudden!
-Just get him and oust him first.
-And you heard what Jong Kook said.
You keep staring at my back...
You hurt me when you suspected me...?
-Okay, it's not like that.
-So we're going to keep suspecting each other?
I have a feeling about Kwang Soo.
Im Ho isn't someone who'd just
be easily had like that...
Even if he were up against someone,
he's not someone that would lose easily...
He's pretty strong...
[Tae Kwon deciding that Kwang Soo
needs to be captured]
Are there any other floors?
Ah, there's also the garage.
That's right... We just keep going
to the same place over and over...
No one has been down there once.
-Kwang Soo...
-I'm really not a spy.
[Feeling of the hunting lion approaching]
Just give it a rest now.
I'm really not one.
-You're not?
-No, I'm not.
Then is Jong Kook the spy?
I haven't even heard that there is a spy.
I didn't even know that
there's such a thing as a spy.
Anyways, once you're out,
that's when the real fight is going to begin.
[Anyways, everyone is waiting
for him to get ousted]
Because we're all in this state
because of you.
-Ah... so because of me...
-That's right, because of you.
-So it doesn't matter what I say.
-We don't need it.  We're going to get you.
Jong Kook says to get you.
What if you tear it off and I'm not the spy?
-What if I'm not the spy?
-I told you, I'll buy you something to eat.
[Ultimately, the compensation is food]
[Tae Kwon is slowly going for
Kwang Soo's name tag]
[What!  Kwang Soo counterattacks
in the blink of an eye!]
[Attacking Tae Kwon as his opponent!]
[Total face-off!]
[They tore it off at the same time!]
[Tae Kwon's out too!
How can this be...?]
What the heck?
Lee Tae Kwon, Lee Kwang Soo, out.
I told you, I'm really not!
[Kwang Soo denying to the end
even though he's been ousted]
Hey, isn't this a spy tag?
Hey!
He is a spy!  Hey!
[Confirmed that Kwang Soo is a spy]
Where are you?
Jae Suk...!
Where are you?!
-Jae Suk!
-Get Ha Ha!  Hurry and get him.
[Once he's confirmed Kwang Soo is a spy,
he also suspects Ha Ha!]
-You're a spy, right?
-Me?
Why am I a spy?
Kwang Soo's a spy!
Then why am I the spy?
Jong Kook can be the spy!
[Causing distraction by accusing
Jong Kook of being the spy?]
Why can't you trust me?
If we can just oust him, we can win!
Jae Suk... If we can work together to tear
his name off, we can win!
-Kwang Soo.
-What's this?  What happened?
-What happened?
-All because of Kwang Soo.
-There's no way...
-We tore off each others.
Both of you?  Each other's?
[I'm sorry...]
-What the heck Kwang Soo?  Who are you?
-I'm a spy.
You're a spy?
He really does have long arms...
Even though I was pushing him away,
his arm was behind my back.
-Really?
-They're really long!
-You tore it off at the same time?
-At the same time.
There's a standard for being a spy.
How could he...
[The spy who brought down
the standards of a spy...]
-Then Jong Kook...
-There's only the 3 of them left now.
There's one more spy.
There's another one?!
Besides you?
[Just who is the other spy?]
If I hadn't seen Kwang Soo's,
I may not have known...
But how things are going about now...
It's not me...
-It's not me either, Jae Suk.
-Just a minute.
-It's one of you guys...
-Why isn't it you then?
-I'm not one.
-Why aren't you one?
-I'm not.
-Why?
-Is it you?  Is it you?
-Jae Suk...
Why would I be?!
Then why did you say you weren't going to
attach anything on your back?
Huh?  Attach what?
[Now that we think about it...
He tried not to attach landmarks on himself]
Because they're going to rip mine off
no matter what...
This is driving me crazy...
Jae Suk.  Jae Suk...
-Why didn't you attach anything?
-Because they always tear mine off!
For the sake of the team's win...!
If you promise me that you'll tear his off,
then I'll show you my back.
-Why are you saying that?
-I'm being serious!
Jae Suk, tear Jong Kook's off.
Then I'll tear mine off right after.
-Just promise me...
-If you do, then our team wins!
Tear his off...
[Jae Suk's head is about to explode]
Wait!  Just wait a second!
Our team... The power of green!
The one who calls on the power of green!
[Ha Ha trying to convince Jae Suk
to oust Jong Kook for their team to win]
[Jong Kook convinced that Ha Ha is a spy]
-Tear it off!  Tear it off!
-Tear it off!  I'll do it! Tear it off!
-Just tear mine off!  It's okay.
-You come here.
You're a spy, aren't you?
What are you going to do if I'm not and gone
once you tear mine off?
Then you're going to die, you fool!
You need to think about your wife and kids!
[Why is he bringing up the kids here?]
-Come here...
-Why do you keep suspecting me?
Tear it off.  Hurry up and tear his off!
Really?  Seriously?
I'm telling you to tear it off!
-Jae Suk!  Listen...!
-Wake up!  Come back to your senses!
-It's okay so just tear his off!
Wait... Just wait.
Come back to your senses.
I don't know, I don't know, I don't know...
-Why can't you trust me?
-You just stand still.
-Stand still.
-Jae Suk.  You really can't trust me?
Hurry up and tear it off!
If he tears mine off and there's nothing,
then he's going to eat you alive.
-Would you like that?
-No, no... Jae Suk...!
-Jae Suk...
-Jong Kook... Hurry up and tear it off!
-Hurry up and do it!
-Just wait.  Hey you!
Do you know who I am?
I am... I am... Someone important!
Let go!  I'm a spy!
I'm a spy!
How stupid and boring...!
[Confirmed Ha Ha is a spy]
You come here... Come here.
-You can't trust me?  Me?  Me?!
-You come here right now...
Hey!  Lee Kwang Soo!
You... You...
[At the time Kwang Soo was being excited
about becoming a spy this morning...]
You must be filming?
[Ha Ha, early in to work to receive
his secret orders]
-What are you...!  Giraffe!
-What the heck?
Traitor... The traitor, right?
[The reason for there being 2 spies today]
The two best traitors on Running Man...
[Go up against the Kings and oust
all the members of Running Man]
Crazy, crazy... I'm going to go crazy today!
-I'm going to go crazy!!  This is it!
-This is it!
[The 2 masters of betrayal,
this is how they became spies]
This is going to be really fun.
Because we're going to be betraying them...!
[It was a good opportunity of there being
a double spy for the first time in a while...]
You guys think you're total detectives...
[Ha Ha exploding at being revealed?]
You guys think you're Columbos!
You guys think you're Joseon detectives!
Why not solve all our country's problems?
[Because of Jong Kook,
he didn't get to play the spy at all...]
-What a good job you're doing...
-You, go away.
-Jae Suk... That was really difficult.
-We could've had big problems if not for you.
-You saved us... It could've been trouble.
-Jae Suk...
[But now... Going up against one another...]
This isn't really right...
That was an uncomfortable truth...
[The uncomfortable truth after
eliminating Ha Ha the spy]
This isn't right...
-He's here.  It's over.
-What the heck...?
-It's all over.
-Hey, Lee Kwang Soo...
[The 2 spies getting over-excited
as soon as they see each other]
Hey, you fool!  Do you know how this happened?
Think about it.
[Putting two masters of betrayals together...
Dumb and Dumber...]
Poker face isn't the problem...
But Jong Kook had you from the start!
I know that and that's why I said
we should get Jong Kook first!
-This is...
-Kwang Soo ruined everything.
It's not like that...
Can't we go out and watch?
[The scene that appeared to those
that went out to watch...]
[Yoo-Ruce Willis being toyed with]
What a nice scenery!
[A scenery they don't get to witness often]
-This really has been a while...
-They're all coming.  This is crazy.
Seriously what?  Seriously what?
[Yoo-Ruce Willis not being able to make a move]
[All the spectators beginning to arrive]
You dare to tear it off my back?
Little ones!  Don't watch!
Young Ones, don't watch.
Go wait inside.
[Getting treated more shamefully
than the spies themselves]
[Are they exercising?]
[After making sure he can't budge...]
[Spy or whatnot...
Jong Kook of Ho Nation unifies the lands!]
How about another round?
You can do it!
-Get up.
-What are you saying?
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Running Man's 99 races...]
[Landmark all over Korea
and all over the world...]
[Space to travel-Countless kilometers]
[Running Man's endless race]
[Enthusiastic welcome
by countless number of fans]
[And the studded list of guests
that's shone light on Running Man]
[However,
something that could surpass all this...]
[A new history is being written]
[Running Man... 100th special]