[Don't Walk, But Date!]
Subtitles by DramaFever
[August 2012, one summer day]
[SBS Running Man- Sabrina Hall]
[A press conference comparable to the Olympics]
[Then is this the location where
a new drama production will be announced?]
[Just what is this drama going to be?]
What is this?
- You don't want us to come up right now?
- Yes, you can just stand right there.
You want us to stop here?
- You'll come up as we announce your roles.
- Really?
I really hope that Kwang Soo is the main lead.
- Please let Kwang Soo be the lead for once.
- I'll take care of it.
He just started a drama,
but he has no scenes.
- What do you mean, I have no scenes?
- All you do is cry every day.
He plays Jun Ki's friend,
and Jun Ki's filming every day.
- What are you talking about?
- Just ask them to kill you off now.
We are going to announce the production
of a very special drama.
[Don't Walk, But Date]
Date?
There will be a male and a female lead.
And there will be 6
supporting characters surrounding them.
- 6 supporting characters?
- I will announce each of you now.
- I'll introduce the female lead first.
- Isn't it going to be Song Ji Hyo?
The Queen of romantic comedies...
- Gong Hyo Jin.
- What? What did he say?
Awesome!
[Could it really be Gong Hyo Jin?]
Gong Hyo Jin?
She's really here!
[Lovely girl, Gong Hyo Jin]
[The Queen of romantic comedies,
"National Lovely," "Gong-vely" Gong Hyo Jin]
[Overcoming Gu Ae Jung
in The Greatest Love]
[The woman that completes
the 577km Homeland Trek]
- Hello.
- What's going on?
Let's give her a round of applause!
[The female lead Gong Hyo Jin
of the drama 'Don't Walk, But Date']
Miss Gong Hyo Jin can go take a seat
in the female lead's spot.
- Miss Gong...
- Do you know her well too?
- Of course, I know her well!
- Just who don't you know?
- Gong Hyo Jin will be the female lead.
- This is awesome.
- Seriously...this is awesome.
- I will now announce the male lead.
The male lead is one
of the Running Man members.
- Really?
- Let Kwang Soo be it for once.
- Let Kwang Soo take the lead.
- Let Kwang Soo be one for once.
This wasn't decided by me,
but through a vote by the staff this morning.
The male lead for the drama,
'Don't Walk, But Date' is...
Let Kwang Soo be it for once,
that's the humane thing to do...
[Desperate plea...]
Seriously, let Kwang Soo be it for once.
It's Lee Kwang Soo!
- Kwang Soo!
- Wow... Kwang Soo!
- Kwang Soo! You're like the Ugly Duckling!
- You're the male lead!
- You've made it finally...
- And your partner is Gong Hyo Jin!
- Miss Gong...
- Am I on the same team with him?
Yes, please help him out.
[She doesn't seem too happy about her co-star.]
Look at how unhappy she is.
But he's not very good!
[Anyways, from everyone's well wishes,
a new drama couple is born.]
[Will this drama run smoothly?]
I'd like to thank everyone
for being here today.
Our male and female lead for the drama...
[Jae Suk- MC/Supporting character #4]
[Big Nose -#1: Kkuk - #2: Roro - #3
Blank Ji - #5: Lee Joon #6]
Now...our Gong Hyo Jin...
Please share something with us.
Are you laughing?
Are you laughing at us?
- So this is how you guys do it?
- Yes, this is how we do it.
First...I'd like to thank everyone for taking
the time out of their busy schedule to attend.
[Very distracting press conference]
I'm just trying to drink some water
because I'm thirsty!
- Seriously...
- I'm talking right now.
Are you happy with the male lead?
We'd like to hear your honest thoughts on it.
- First, I like his height.
- His height?
- How tall are you?
- 90.
[Gulliver?]
3m 90cm?
It's a joke.
I just thought that you were being too stiff.
Let's ask the male lead to.
This is your first starring role, isn't it?
- Yes, that's correct.
- I heard that you don't have many scenes.
The way I see it, you'll start this way,
but at the end, it's "What the heck is this?"
- "What kind of a male lead is this?"
- Jae Suk, come on...
- Why are you being like that?
- It's a 100% guarantee.
Isn't it a 100% guarantee?
Besides the leads, there are many others
that are here with us today. Lee Joon...
-  Yes?
- You recently started your first drama?
- Yes, that's right.
- What do you think of the drama? Is it fun?
Well since coming on...
Oh, do I need the mike?
No, I'm going to use it...
You can't do whatever you want!
What is the most memorable scene
that you were in?
The scene where I take the shot.
- So without any substance...
- I'm in the shot for about 2 seconds...
[If he's in the scene for more than 2 seconds,
then he counts them all to be his scenes.]
I hear that Song Ji Hyo here will be the other
factor in a love triangle story line.
This is your first time
acting with Lee Kwang Soo...
Are the feelings in acting
coming out well and naturally?
- It was very difficult.
- Really?
- But you haven't...
- You haven't even done any yet...
[Even just the thought of it makes her upset?]
I chose the role because I heard that
Gong Hyo Jin will be in the drama.
But with Kwang Soo being there too,
it did leave a bad feeling...
Ha Ha, what is your role?
My role is that of
Lee Kwang Soo's caretaker...
What are you talking about?
You know he's bed-ridden,
so my role takes care of him.
- That's your role?
- But since we're close in real life...
- Just thinking about it makes me tear up.
- Because you're really close to him?
I'm the third supporting role?
My role is to pull the plug
from his life support.
Why would you pull off my life support?
[Kwang Soo meeting his tragic death
by character #3?]
- It's been 3 years in the making...
- That's right...
[The romantic comedy, 'Don't Walk, But Date'
is leaning more towards a tragic story]
I'm sure all the viewers will be highly
anticipating this drama too...
Will you please say a word for the audience?
[With it being a fake drama,
all the questions are...]
You have to ask me a question
that's more detailed...
What can I say if you ask me to
say one more word to the audience?
Why do you keep asking her to say a word?
- What kind of a character do you play...
- Something more detailed.
I have no idea what this drama is about...
- What role do you play?
- Exactly, what role do I play?
I'll tell you. Yoo Jae Suk's role
is to be my father...
- I'm your father that opposes this marriage.
- Yes, you oppose it.
Because of your opposition, Kwang Soo
gets hurt and ends up in the hospital.
[No matter what,
Kwang Soo's always tragic...]
- Ah, so your father...
- That's right.
Kwang Soo's first starring role
in a drama with Gong Hyo Jin.
It's a daily drama.
It airs at three o'clock in the morning.
The fervor from the Olympics
hasn't died down yet.
Please wake up 3-4 hours before work,
and make sure to watch the show.
It's a 3am broadcast.
-'Don't Walk, But Date'... Fighting!
-Fighting!
Male and female lead will be one team.
Suk Jin, Jong Kook, and Ha Ha are one team.
Jae Suk, Ji Hyo and Jun will be one team,
totaling a number of 3 teams.
We will hand out
each team's uniforms out first.
[The benefits of being the male lead?
An extremely large name tag.]
What is this?
- Why is this thing so huge?
- Wait...
[What? More name tags underneath?]
What is this?
-There's more?
-What is this?
[Name tags that keep showing up no matter
how many layers they peel back, like an onion]
-Does it mean that he won't die?
-Is there more?
[More...!]
- What the...
- That's crazy!
- Do you only have one, Hyo Jin?
- Yes.
[Even the female lead,
Hyo Jin only has one...]
What's going on here?
[Kwang Soo has 7 name tags today!]
[Kwang Soo's name tag total - 7.
Thus he will encounter an unbelievable fate.]
You'll find out the meaning of the name tags
once you get to your final destination.
What is this?
Then Kwang Soo can't be ousted.
- How can we beat him?
- Seriously...
In the drama... I hope that you can be
how you usually are.
[No matter what the situation is,
the Giraffe keeps getting busted.]
I will explain the race to you.
It's a romantic comedy race.
[Today's mission - Romantic comedy mission]
Each team will move on their own
to shoot their scenes.
Every time that you succeed
a location shoot
2 people from the first team,
and 1 member from the second winning team
will be given a hint that will be
useful at the final location.
After you safely complete the mission
from the scenes
[If you shoot the ending scene at
the final location, then you win.]
The person that can shoot the ending scene
at the final location will be the winner.
['Don't Walk, But Date' - Starts filming!]
- Is all this going on air too?
- Yes.
[All the actors move on to the first shoot,
which is at Yanjaechun outdoor water park]
- There's an outdoor water park there?
- Let's get started.
The weather is really nice.
I think it's the perfect weather for a date.
- I'll do a really good job.
- You're serious, right?
Of all my friends who've been on Running Man
you were picked as the number one person
who's not to be trusted.
No matter what happens at the end,
don't forget that we're on the same team.
I would like for you to protect me.
- I'm really close with Ae Jin...
- Yes...
When I told her that
I'm coming on Running Man...
She told me that it would be difficult for me
because I'm not competitive.
And I told her that it would be
my concept on the show then...
But she told me that
the show wouldn't be fun then.
- So I'm not sure what to do.
- Already...you don't look very motivated.
It's not because of me, right?
[Does she really not have a
competitive streak in her?]
Oh! We're here.
We're here. This is the place.
[Discovers Running Man flag]
[A refreshing water park
in the heart of downtown]
[Lovers frolicking in the water is
a frequent scene in romantic comedies.]
[What will the mission be in this location?]
- We're the first ones to arrive?
- There's no way that can be.
- You are the first ones to arrive.
- Seriously?
[The actors will hold hands and retrieve the
colorful balloons that are underwater.]
[If you pop the balloons and correctly answer
the questions inside, then you're okay.]
[If you get it wrong, it's an NG.
Keep going until you answer it correctly.]
The balloons that you see underwater
hold a question inside.
Retrieve a balloon and pop the balloon by
squeezing it between your chest.
[We're...going to hug?]
And you have to get the question out,
and answer it correctly.
If you get it wrong,
you have to try again.
[The male lead feeling the moment on his own...]
Hello! Come on, Ji Hyo.
We're going to get started right away!
We're ready!
[Gong-vely feeling rushed as she sees
the other team arrive.]
- What...what is this?
- You have to pop the balloon between you two.
Why are you telling them that?
You should've kept quiet.
This may let you know what the hint is.
I get it, so let's just get started.
She says she gets it,
so just get started.
[Huh? Her competitiveness...?]
- One, two, three...
- 1st place! 1st place! Fighting!
[Male and female lead
parting through the water.]
[Wait for me!]
[Arriving at the balloon area]
-You're not going in the water?
-No, I'll go in.
- Go in and take a good look at the balloons.
- Go under and look at the balloons?
[Huh? With his eye open?]
I can't see! I can't see!
[Is it a question...or a dud?]
I don't think it's a dud.
Something's written on there.
[Going ashore for now...]
- I have to prepare...wait...
- Just pop the balloon!
[Under the lead of the impatient female lead,
the water balloon pops!]
- Open it up.
- Open it up and show it to me.
- Question #19!
- Okay, I'll ask you question #19.
Both of you have to say
the answer together at the same time.
The phenomenon of 2 trees that were close by
starting to grow together as one tree...
What do you call this symbol that correlates
to a married couple's growing relationship?
- You have 5 seconds.
- Is it a name of a tree?
- 5...4...
- Morning glory?
- Forever tree?
[Their answers differ from one another...]
1, 2, 3!
- The correct answer is...
- Why are you saying the Morning glory?
The correct answer is the forever tree.
I'm right! That's what I said!
That's what I said!
I said the forever tree first!
- Go back to the starting line.
- Put that down and talk.
- I said the forever tree first.
- Grab him by the throat!
Let him have it!
[Gong-vely stubbornly insisting...]
Why are you being like this
on such a nice day?
You made me upset!
It's not the morning glory?
[The Blue Team arrives in the meantime]
Why are you so wet already?
- Why are you already soaked?
- This guy really isn't listening.
I said the forever tree...
Let's not be like this.
[But this is how I work...]
When I told her that I was
coming on here...
[What? You said you're not competitive?]
- You seem really angry.
- I said the forever tree, but he keeps...
- She told him not to be like that.
- Oh, really?
- Did you two answer at the same time?
- We have to answer simultaneously?
- When you answer...
- Why didn't you tell me that?
You read the question together with me.
- But you were...
- Both of you need to answer the question.
Is the yellow team ready?
Yes!
[Fierce body fight
to disrupt their advancement.]
[Ballet major Lee Joon
quickly making his way.]
[From a body fight to a water fight!]
[Jae Suk vs. The Giraffe: The naval battle]
[Lee Joon with eyes of a hawk
discovers a balloon with a question?]
Disqualified.
The balloon is too weak!
- I seriously can't believe that.
- Hurry! Hurry!
The three of you need to pop the balloon
by squeezing it between your chests.
1, 2, 3.
- That's ours!
- Why are you taking that?
Hey!
[Ultimately,
getting revenge on the male lead.]
Hurry up and get up here.
[The female lead shares the same fate]
Our team is...our team is...
a well-mannered gentlemen team.
- I think there are duds too though.
- Did you push me?
Dud.
[It's war!]
- Well-mannered gentlemen, fighting!
- Fighting!
[Lee Joon,
very aggressive in procuring the balloon]
I really hope it's a question.
- Why are there so many?
- Why are there so many duds?
It's a dud because you chose it!
- Well-mannered gentlemen, fighting!
- Fighting!
[Let's just wait and see!]
Why are there so many duds?
[Throwing the question that far away?]
[What the...]
- This is nonsense!
- We're well-mannered gentlemen!
It's war!
[Giraffe, in the midst of tying his shoelace,
is forcefully submerged in the water.]
My shoelace is untied, Hyo Jin!
[Butterfly strokes...?]
[Athlete Jae Suk forcefully
making his progress]
[Skills enough to make even Michael Phelps
go home crying...]
This is faster.
- Well-mannered gentleman, fighting!
- Fighting!
[Second round of the naval fight]
Stop it and get up there quickly.
This is a dud.
We haven't gotten
a single question to answer yet.
- We need a question.
- 1, 2, 3.
- How did you get that?
- Like this...
[Jae Suk cleaning the name tag for him.]
You really are kind, Jae Suk.
Stop it now.
Jae Suk!
[Rinsing it out nice and well.]
- Give it to me!
- Don't do it!
[Passing it over to the well-mannered team.]
Question #14!
[Finally a question!]
During Joseon era,
when winter starts to thaw...
There was a tradition where people exchanged
this tree's seeds and relayed their love.
- What is the name of this tree?
- Jujube tree!
- When is that? Spring time?
- Everyone has to say it all together.
1, 2, 3!
- Forsythia!
- Jujube Tree.
[Correct answer: Gingko Tree]
That's what I was going to say earlier!
- That's what I was going to say...
- What do you mean, you were going to say that?
Please come forward,
and the blue team step aside.
Question #73.
- Helen, the Queen of Sparta...
- I know this one!
This one is really easy...
Escapes after falling in love with
Prince Paris of a neighboring country.
What is the name of the war
that resulted from this event?
- You know the one with the horse...
- 1, 2...
[Trojan...?]
Thirsty war!
[It's a Trojan...]
What is that?
- What was it? Horse something?
- The correct answer is the Trojan War.
[Submersion war]
[Male lead using force]
[Ballet Lee Joon
pushing his way forward as always]
Don't rip it! Don't rip it off!
[Searching for the balloon with the question
with eyes of a hawk.]
[Inside this balloon is?]
-Please...
-1, 2, 3.
It's a question!
[Lead character team with a question]
Question #64. Get out of the way!
[Tough female lead]
- She wants you to move out of the way.
- We were here first.
- It's a dud!
- Seriously...
Listen to the following notes,
and guess the name of the song.
Mi-rae-do-do-mi-mi-sol-sol-sol
do-do-si-si-si-sol-mi.
What is that? Say it again, please.
Mi-rae-do-do-mi-mi-sol-sol-sol
do-do-si-si-si-sol-mi.
-Mi-rae-do...Mi-rae-do?
-1, 2, 3!
Paturashu?
The correct answer is 'Lovely'.
- You said it was a dog's name...a dog!
- Is 'Lovely' a dog's name?
Notes...didn't you learn that in music class?
("Dog" and "Notes" sound the same)
Who names their dog 'Lovely'?
But it's spelled out differently.
[His pronunciation is Kangnam style...]
You should've said 'Gae'. 'Gae'!
[Blue team up to the challenge]
Question #38.
[Question #38!]
Okay. It's an easy question.
It's an easy one.
What is the name of Popeye's girlfriend?
1, 2, 3! Olive Oyl!
Her full name is...
[What is Popeye's girlfriend's full name?]
-1, 2, 3!
-Olive Popeye!
Olive Popeye!
- What the heck?
- How would we know her full name?
- What is Olive Oyl's full name then?
- All of Popeye's fans would know this.
[Olive Oyl's full name that all of
Popeye's fans would know is...]
The correct answer is Olive Oyl.
What you first had was correct.
What? Olive Oyl?
[It's true. Olive's full name is Olive Oyl]
- That's her full name. Olive Oyl.
- Really? Her full name?
You learned a good one today, right?
You're really making me angry!
Olive Oyl...
Tiger! Impala!
[Another question?]
Off! A question! #89!
[Question #89!]
Everyone shout it out together.
In Italian...with the meaning 'Night'...
What do you when a man sings
to his lover outside her window?
-Wait...we have to say it out loud.
-1, 2, 3!
Serenade!
[Correct answer]
- Yes!
- Yellow team, you may go on your way.
[Yellow team passes]
[Two members of the yellow team earns
a hint for winning]
[The hint that you need
at the final destination is...]
[...is in the prop room on the third floor]
For the next location...
You have to get in your car to find out.
[Leaving the fervent young fans behind]
[The Yellow Team moves on
to the next location!]
Question #100! I got a good feeling!
What is the jewel that's referred to as the
'Heart of the Ocean' in the movie, Titanic?
- The one that Grandmother throws?
- In the last scene?
The thing Grandmother throws...
- Okay. 1, 2, 3!
- Diamond!
Diamond!
[Correct answer]
[Male and female leads in ecstatic happiness]
[Passed second place -
Only one person can gain the hint]
The hint that you need
at the final destination...
is located in
the prop room on the third floor.
It's not very important.
Where do we need to go?
- Cafe in Seochodong.
- A cafe in Seochodong?
Let's just build up the momentum...
but if we keep winning, it usually...
gets reversed at the final location.
Here's to winning the next game.
Cheers.
Since you're the weakling,
you should drink some of this energy drink...
I'll show you. I'll really show you.
This is really hurting my pride.
[Can his words...really be trusted?]
I think this is it.
This way? Do we go up to the second floor?
[Yellow Team arrives at the cafe]
- What's this?
- Oh my...a tiger and a giraffe...
[Familiar stuffed animals...]
- What...what is this?
- It's a giraffe.
[Blue team arrives]
What is this?
What kind of parking was that?
[So happy to see...]
Giraffe!
[Stuffed tiger happy to see his tiger brother]
Oh my! The turtle is here.
- There you are.
- I'm the male lead.
She looks cold back there.
- Over there...sit over there.
- That's the seat for the main lead.
[Scene #2-Cafe: Female lead Hyo Jin
leisurely drinking her coffee.]
[And her opponent that shows up
out of nowhere!]
[His unexpected behavior sends
her heart a-flutter.]
Hyo Jin's heart is going to be set a-flutter?
If Gong Hyo Jin wants to win,
Kwang Soo needs to set her heart a-flutter.
Oh really?
Have they gotten close?
[Tenderness?]
For some reason,
I feel bad for you today, Hyo Jin.
Suk Jin, I'm the male lead.
- You look like you're being punished.
- We feel like you're suffering too much.
Gong Hyo Jin, please step outside.
Gong Hyo Jin's heart rate right now is
81-83.
[In worst condition?]
- Why?
- That has nothing to do with me.
Instead of the 'Greatest Love',
this is the 'Worst Love'.
- 'The Worst Love'
- Why are you saying that?
Our Lee Joon will get out there
and fix this situation right up.
[Prospect Lee Joon to start]
Joon! Don't be nervous.
[He looks extremely nervous.]
Just smile at her brightly!
[Oh! Her response is!]
Oh! It's going up! It's up!
- Hyo Jin, my name is Lee Joon.
- Yes.
It dropped back down to 81.
Great job, Hyo Jin.
Why is it dropping?
Your special skill...the wave.
Just start the wave.
[Launching the wave]
My name is Lee Joon.
I'm from MBlaq.
Do a turn. Show her your turn.
That's right...that's right.
[Blasting off a clean turn!]
[He's getting a response!]
[His motivation leads him
to excessive stretching.]
[The end of Lee Joon's challenge]
[Just what was Hyo Jin's highest heart rate?]
That was so funny.
[A love triangle? Blank Ji goes for it!]
- But since I'm a girl...
- But Ji Hyo's good at making people mad.
What? Jong Kook...
Do you think you can make one of the
singer's that you look up to angry?
- I'm already doing that.
- Who?
A man named Kim Jong Shin...
Don't worry about things like that
and just do it.
- Ah, first...
- Hyo Jin's her senior?
Of course...she's a senior that I look up to.
- But doesn't Ji Hyo look older?
- Yeah, she looks older.
Ji Hyo's not the one who needs
to get her heart rate up!
[Everyone raising up Ji Hyo's heart rate?]
- Ji Hyo! It's okay.
- I thought you were older than her.
Gong Hyo Jin's much taller,
but Ji Hyo's taller when you're sitting.
[Explosion]
What else was I supposed to say
when it's evident to the eyes?
- Ji Hyo...
- Ji Hyo, you can't get your heart rate up.
- Ji Hyo!
- Be quiet!
- Okay, I got it. I'm sorry.
- Ji Hyo is sitting further back, right?
[In shock]
[Ji Hyo-Knockdown??]
[Stopping before she can even say a word
from all the bombardment]
I don't think this is right.
I haven't even been able to say anything,
don't you think this is too much?
Just take a seat. That was too much.
Move over more, Ji Hyo.
Ji Hyo, you must have gotten really hurt.
- All at once...
- Ji Hyo, calm down.
Hyo Jin, don't think of it too weirdly
since this is all an act.
I can think of it as being weird.
[An extreme pre-block]
She said she may think it's weird.
It's not like that. Really...
[Jong Kook up to the challenge]
[Bragging about his strength without words]
For me, I...
[This is "Kkuk's style..."]
Do you think you're on X-Man or something?
- That's not it...
- Of course!
[Heart rate climbing up uncontrollably]
You want me to spin like this?
That will make her dizzy.
It's okay, Jong Kook.
It'll make my heart rate go up.
[Is Hyo Jin enjoying this situation?]
Are you doing it right, right now?
Seriously, what are you doing?
[Her heart rate keeps climbing up!]
Why are you holding on to him
so naturally like that?
Eun Hye, are you watching?
Why are you doing that?
- What are you doing?
- Eun Hye...
- Come on, Jae Suk...
You really seem to be liking that.
It's nice.
[Her honesty that's becoming
more and more attractive]
We won this.
[Kkuk's style...will it prove effective?]
- Thank you.
- We won, we won.
Why are you lifting her up like that
without any permission?
But I excused myself earlier.
Jae Suk...why don't you give it a try?
[This won't do...
Jae Suk taking the challenge?]
- You have to lift her right up.
- Okay.
[Just what will "Hyuk's" moves be?]
- You seem...to really like stuff like that.
- Yes.
[Her heart is fluttering with him
just sitting next to her?]
There's a flower that fell to the ground.
[Jae Suk's "behind" style]
Don't misunderstand!
There's a flower that dropped on the ground.
What are you doing? What are you doing?
Why? What did I do?
- Look at this!
- It fell on the ground!
[Is this his attack?]
- Don't misunderstand!
- Jae Suk! Here...hurry!
Oh my, here's another one!
Here's another one!
[His unstoppable attack of the behind]
Gong Hyo Jin, don't misunderstand!
Ji Hyo...it's because you
dropped the flower.
- Stop that!
- Joon! You come and pick this up too.
Hyo Jin...are there any places that
you'd like to go to?
[Her heartbeat finding its normal beat
when faced with his front side]
Do you have to pick it up again?
Here, Jae Suk.
[Falling into the lure of his behind again]
[Hyuk's style]
[His alluring attractive behind...]
[Her heart rate is revived!]
[The last shot]
[Did you see that?]
[This is Hyuk's behind style]
It dropped? You say that it dropped?
- Really?
- I was so out of breath...
- I really couldn't catch my breath.
- I know. It's because you couldn't breathe.
Because I made her short of her breath?
Hyo Jin...thanks. I'll see you later.
[Thought Behind-Yoo was being
well-mannered and saying his goodbyes...]
- It's because it's too tight over here!
- You can just walk the other way!
[His sitting style that's getting the blame]
Why are you walking by
sticking it up like that?
Okay. The Blue Team has another chance,
and it's Suk Jin.
[It's Blue Team's turn...
but it's Big nosed brother?]
[Predicting the worst heart rate to date?]
- You can even sit close next to her.
- I'm afraid of my heart rate spiking.
- Calm down.
- Hello.
It seems like you've been waiting a long time.
[Big nosed brother worrying about
his own heart rate]
But why is it...that you don't like me?
[An unshakable mental state]
- For now...you pass.
- Really?
[About to set the record for
her heart rate being the lowest]
Come on Hyo Jin...stand up.
Do you think our future is
over there, there, or there?
- Over there?
- Huh?
- Over there.
- Why there? That's the exit.
[The future of these two is the exit...]
That's the exit.
- Nice going!
This way...that good?
[No change in the heart rate...]
- Take care...
- Okay.
You're the one who should take care
of yourself, Suk Jin!
[Facing a parting from Suk Jin,
her heart rate is starting to rise?]
Hyo Jin's heart rate is climbing now that
you said goodbye to her.
And finally... it's Kwang Soo.
The lead. The male lead.
[The anticipated meeting of the two leads]
[In order to win this, Kwang Soo has to
make her heart beat faster than anyone else]
- Have you been waiting long?
- No.
Today's the 100th day
since we've started dating.
[Since it's been 100 days...
Her heart rate is at a decline?]
On their 100th day,
her heart rate is dropping like flies.
[Even with his touch,
her heart rate is still dropping]
Want to dance?
Follow me.
[His chaotic bendy dance]
It's dropping, what can I do about it?
[Rather than raising it higher than others,
dropping her rate to poverty line.]
I'll try it. You just sit still.
[The situation would be better if
Kwang Soo doesn't do anything?]
- Yeah, that could be better.
- You're making me nervous.
Or you can get on Hyo Jin's back.
- If Hyo Jin's having a hard time...
- Do you want to carry me on your back?
[The female lead wanting to get her
heart rate up no matter what it takes]
I...
Found someone else.
[What the heck is this now?]
At first,
it started with us just being friends.
- That's good acting. He's good.
- I'll introduce you to my new girlfriend.
[Who's Kwang Soo's new girlfriend
who'll get Hyo Jin's heart rate up?]
[Ji Hyo?]
Ji Hyo's accepting this...
Ji Hyo's helping out with this.
Sit Ji Hyo down on the chair.
- This is my new girlfriend.
- Ji Hyo's sitting back further, right?
- Ji Hyo!
- Ji Hyo! Don't pay attention!
[The new girlfriend barely
calming herself down]
I'm Kwang Soo's new girlfriend.
Is Ji Hyo really sitting down?
You're in a drama right now,
you're in a drama.
Please let Kwang Soo go.
She wants her to let Kwang Soo go.
Kwang Soo has a new girlfriend now.
You have to send him to her.
[What is this?
He has another new girlfriend?]
We're going to make makjang out of this now?
This is total makjang now.
[Makjang = over-melodramatic]
- Jong Soon! Jong Soon!
- Jong Soon...
[Kwang Soo's real new girlfriend, Jong Soon?]
You went for the short haircut?
You used to be prettier
when you had longer hair.
Sit down here.
[The new lover sitting in a tender pose]
This is my new girlfriend.
- This really is makjang.
- This is makjang drama!
You want me to make you even more jealous?
You'll die!
[Tiger girlfriend's true nature springs forth]
It's a little hot in here, isn't it?
[The male lead not knowing when to give up]
- Why? Is he going to undress?
- Kwang Soo...
[Even taking his clothes off
out of desperation?]
[Nudity!]
[Drawing in the lines with a pen]
Chicken...it's a chicken.
[Of all things, the t-shirt he's wearing
underneath is a chicken t-shirt]
[Serious again]
- Why are you asking things like that?
- What kind of things do you like?
Why are you...
[His hair getting stuck
to the gigantic name tag]
What the heck is this?
[God of entertainment not being able to
withstand Kwang Soo's earnestness]
- Wait! What is this?
- This is for real! It's real...
That hurts so bad!
[As always, in the end...
he will always be "Giraffe style"...]
Seriously...seriously!
Look at all his hair stuck on here.
The God of entertainment...
He hasn't abandoned you!
[Kwang Soo being favored
by the God of entertainment]
- It was so funny. It was really stuck.
- You've lost a ton of your hair.
How is it that...
[His chaotic hair thanks to the name tag...]
[The God of Performance
has helped out today as well...]
[Revealing the heart rate results]
Hyo Jin's heart rate with Lee Joon is 101.
- Ji Suk Jin...
- Yes.
98.
That's more than I expected.
Yoo Jae Suk...
120.
Lee Kwang Soo...
100...you didn't go over that.
[The giraffe not able to win his own
teammate's heart in the end]
92.
- His expression!
- You got 92.
- 92?
- Kim Jong Kook...
Hundred? Hundred...
116.
[Victory with Jae Suk's behind style]
[An explosion of her heart rate]
To the two members of the winning team,
I can give you the hint at the final location.
Why don't you and Joon go?
[Jae Suk and Joon to hear the hint]
[Another hint is
the call center on the 5th floor]
- Is that all?
- That's all.
It must not be anything too important, huh?
[Giving the same hint to Joon as well]
It doesn't seem like anything too special.
[The Blue Team that came in second can have
only one member hear the hint.]
Hey! You haven't even done anything!
Why would you go up there?
It should be either Suk Jin or I!
- It's either Suk Jin or I. Get back.
- Paper-rock-scissors!
Paper-rock-scissors! Paper-rock-scissors!
[Mr. Capable is disqualified]
Paper-rock-scissors!
Why is it so much longer than ours?
He's not getting what I'm saying very well.
I didn't get to hear the most important part.
Why don't you get a hearing aid, Suk Jin?
[Suk Jin also heard the same hint]
- Are you happy?
- You happy?
- You two make a nice picture.
- How long have you two been dating?
[The well-mannered team seems jealous
of the main lead couple team]
- It's a couple t-shirt that you're wearing!
- Yes, well...
- We got married pretty recently.
- Are you heading to the airport?
- Hyo Jin, good luck today.
- I was told not to trust anyone.
It's just Kwang Soo
you have to watch out for.
You were the second one in line.
All my friends told me
never to trust you, Ha Ha.
- Me? Why?
- Yes, you.
- He's first place, he is.
- We're 100% on your team, Hyo Jin.
We're your fans.
- What do we do at the last location?
- At the last location, there's usually a race.
You have to tear off the name...
If you're just going to tear off the name tag,
do we really need a hint?
But when you get the chance,
you have to rip Jong Kook's off first.
What could it be...
[The final location:
'N' shopping headquarters]
[ 'Don't Walk, But Date'...]
[Will the main leads for the drama
see a happy ending?]
Oh! There it is. Over there.
This is it.
This is the site of our final battle!
- We have arrived.
- Let's get out of the car.
[The last scene:
The lead characters vs. supporting characters]
Last scene: The battle of the cast
to rip off each other's name tag.
You have to rip off the name tags
off the supporting characters,
who are after you, and oust them.
Supporting characters who are after
the main leads?
- Then the two of us are...
- The main leads.
The supporting characters will be after you.
You'll have to try to oust them too.
- Then is it 2 against 6?
- 2 against 6?
What about me? This is dangerous for me.
- This seems unfair, right?
- Yes.
You two have a special edge.
First, you have a lot of name tags.
The other is that only once Lee Kwang Soo
has totally been ousted,
can they attack Gong Hyo Jin.
Thus, Gong Hyo Jin should
protect Lee Kwang Soo...
Don't leave my side even for a moment.
- Hey! You said you'd protect me!
- I'm being serious.
Please don't leave me even for a moment.
Please...I'm serious.
- What to do?
- There's one more thing.
Somewhere within the building...
if you find the writing duo, Go sisters...
You can get them to write the person
you want to oust off in the script.
[Find the Go sisters and get them to write off
the character they want to oust!]
The way you can get them
to rewrite the script...
You can get them to rewrite the script
however you want it.
[Have them rewrite the script however you want
and oust the person you want!]
So without having to rip it off,
just change the content of the script?
Then...can we only meet
with the writers once?
- It's not writers, it's only one person.
- You said it was sisters. Go sisters.
[Male lead seemed to have caught on to
Dong Wan PD's role as the "writers"]
- Gong!
- Kwang Cross!
How...
[It would be most advantageous for the
two leads to find the Go writer first...]
I was given a hint.
Can't I share that with him now?
- Since he and I are on the same team.
- What is that?
- I was told the prop room on the 3rd floor.
- Prop room on the 3rd floor?
- Let's go up there first.
- Since we're the only ones who know...
[Will something really be at that location?]
Does it mean...that we shouldn't go there?
[Everyone else arrives at the final scene]
Last scene: The battle of the cast
to rip off each other's name tag.
The supporting characters can't just rip off
the male lead character's name tag.
- What?
- There's something there then?
- You can't just rip it off.
- What then?
The supporting characters have to find the
death props hidden throughout the building
and act it out to be able to rip off
the male lead's name tag.
So we have to act out what it says...
Only once you oust the male character,
can you oust the female character.
[After getting rid of the male lead's
7 name tags can you then attack the female lead]
The name tags that Kwang Soo was
so happy about in the beginning
are nothing but devices for this game.
Kwang Soo isn't the main lead here.
Therefore, the person to remain alive to the
end to shoot the ending scene is the winner.
- Everyone, please hurry on your way.
- I understand.
Then can we rip it off
of our own team members?
[Thanks to the cooperation of all the
employees at 'N' shopping headquarters]
[...we were able to
complete the shooting safely]
Here it is.
- Is this the third floor?
- There was something here.
[The leads arrive at the prop room on the
3rd floor, according to the hint Hyo Jin heard]
What is it that we need to do after
finding it first?
[Kwang Soo, find the death devices that are
to be used to oust you and get rid of it]
I feel like I'm going to break something
with my big name tag.
I was told that the hint is very important.
[More than likely,
there will be an 'R' sticker on the hint...]
But when are the other members going to
start coming after us?
[Discovers an envelope
with 'R' sticker on it!]
- Hyo Jin, I found it! I found it!
- Where?
[Without a doubt, there will be a script
and a device to oust Kwang Soo in there!]
Is there something in there?
['Don't Walk, But Date' - The death script]
'Don't Walk, But Date' - The death script.
[Also discovers a pen like device
in the envelope too?]
Draw a mole on your face and scream out...
[Scream out
'I'll kill Lee Kwang Soo and go to hell'...]
[After shouting this out, rip off his name tag]
[2008 SBS drama, 'Temptation of a Wife']
After I kill Jung Gyo Bin and Shin Ae Ri...
I'll go to hell.
[The point is to draw the mole
with the included pen]
What does that mean?
[The device to eliminate Kwang Soo's name tag
using a scene from 'Temptation of a Wife']
- We have to make sure no one finds it.
- What are you doing? Can't we just rip it up?
It doesn't matter.
We should get rid of this whole thing.
[Hyo Jin ripping it to shreds and
getting rid of it without hesitation]
Since it says death script,
they'll get an idea.
[Main lead Kwang Soo suggesting that they
hide it so they can't even find the cover.]
Give it to me.
[That takes care of the death script...
but what about the death device, the pen?]
[The expert of destroying evidence,
Master Gong Hyo Jin]
[The two leads have crossed one hump,
but will they...?]
We have to search the 5th floor.
Ji Hyo, the 5th floor.
From the first clue that we heard earlier,
did it have anything to do with the 5th floor?
- So that's why we were told 5th floor...
- Oh my goodness!
[In order to eliminate all of Kwang Soo's
7 name tags...]
[...they have to find a lot
of death script-devices]
- Let's find it quickly.
- Someone else may be here already.
Wow! A call center is this big?
- Hello.
We have some things we have to find,
do you know what that could be?
[Blue supporting team searches
the call center to find the hint!]
R... R sticker.
R sticker...
[It seems like Ha Ha
definitely found something!]
[Discovers an 'R' envelope!]
[Just what is the content within
this death script?]
[Attach the mustache, and cover the face with
your hand and as you uncover your face...
[...shout out 'Recover!'
and rip off the name tag after]
- Cha Seung Won! Cha Seung Won!
- 'Recover'...
Recover...
[2011 MBC drama, 'Greatest Love']
Even though I thought my whole face would
disappear from humiliation, but - recover!
Recover...
[This is a way to oust Kwang Soo, using
Cha Seung Won's line from 'Greatest Love'.]
It's Jong Kook!
[An allergic reaction to the tiger!]
- I said, it's Jong Kook!
- I'll rip off his name tag!
Since he can't rip mine off, I can...
I can just rip his off from behind, can't I?
- I think it's on the 6th floor.
- There's someone there. Isn't it Kwang Soo?
- Is it Kwang Soo?
- It's Kwang Soo! Kwang Soo!
[Full speed escape]
[With the death script in their hands...
chase him down!]
- I think he ran in here.
- We have to get this done.
I wonder if Kwang Soo's in danger?
There's Gong Hyo Jin heading this way.
- It's Gong Hyo Jin.
- Gong Hyo Jin is coming.
What is it?
- I'm invincible right now. You can't oust me.
- That's correct.
[Until Kwang Soo's totally eliminated,
Hyo Jin is invincible!]
[Thus, she can be bold about her attacks!]
But there's still three of us here, Hyo Jin.
Hyo Jin, you're really scary.
[The power of invincibility!
The boldness that leaves the three men afraid!]
[Hyo Jin came...]
Kwang Soo!
- Yes?
- Come here.
- Are they gone?
- Yeah. They ran away.
[After verifying Kwang Soo's safety...]
[Attack!]
[Temporary invincibility.
Without hesitation, she attacks!]
[Her target for now is,
Impala Brother as her appetizer!]
[Hyo Jin, amazing!
Toying with Impala brother!]
- Hyo Jin!
- Why are you doing this?
As long as I ran into you guys,
I have to rip it off.
[If you're caught, you're dead!]
[Lioness Hyo Jin!]
She really is trying to eliminate us.
She's coming at us without hesitation.
What I'm curious about is, do they have to
recite the line from the death note
before they can rip off your name tag?
Wasn't this where they can rip off your
name tag if they got a hold of you?
[If that was the case,
I'd be dead 7 times over already...]
I can't trust you so I can't rely on you.
- I'm showing you my true side right now.
- You said you were going to protect me.
- But what the heck is this?
- I'm just going to cancel that statement.
Why are you suddenly
looking at me up and down?
Think about you and I having been together
all day today.
It's possible that all the supporting
characters could gather into one team.
Of course, they're all on the same team.
Are you just figuring that out?
[Even though two years have gone by,
the giraffe still can't figure it out]
Then shall we go separately on our own?
- I can go anywhere by myself.
- You can't be away from me even for a moment!
[Is this still a romantic comedy...?]
- I think someone took it.
- Someone already took it?
- Someone took it out of here.
- Where did you find it, Jae Suk?
- Maybe Kwang Soo...someone already took it.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- That's what Kwang Soo would do.
- Jae Suk.
- Yeah?
Hello.
(Jae Suk's voice)
[The supporting characters
are approaching right next to him!]
[Hiding quickly is a trademark
of all the Running Man members.]
- I'm sure they're going to check here too.
- Jae Suk's out there.
[Even though the giraffe has 7 name tags,
he still feels the same trepidation.]
[Catches the sound of Jae Suk leaving
through the emergency exit.]
[Invincible Hyo Jin attacks Yoo-ruce Willis!]
[The woman has no hesitation!]
[Totally real!
Yoo-ruce Willis not even able to budge!]
Miss Gong! Miss Gong! Miss Gong!
Hyo Jin! Hurry up and leave! Hurry!
[Her hand slips amidst all the chaos!]
[Yellow Team's reinforcement arrives!
Reinvigorated Yoo-ruce Willis!]
[Hyo Jin taking the giraffe
and escaping the site!]
What? What happened?
- That really scared me!
- Your name tag wasn't ripped off?
[That's the envelope that they
abandoned earlier...]
You should've left me to rip off his name tag.
I couldn't do it with you telling me to go!
I was afraid that I was going to
get my name tag ripped off.
- I think they took the content out.
- Seriously!
I didn't get his name tag
even though I had half of it ripped off!
There's nothing for you to be afraid of
as long as you're with me.
Thank you.
- I never knew you were so reliable.
- I'm invincible, that's why.
I seriously thought that I was going to die.
Until we can totally oust Kwang Soo,
we all have to work together.
She's seriously...a wild beast.
A total beast.
Even if I get ousted,
we have to eliminate Kwang Soo.
[The problem is Hyo Jin being invincible
until Kwang Soo is totally eliminated]
- I really don't think I can go near Hyo Jin.
- I really can't go near her either.
- One of you almost got caught recently, right?
- Yeah, that was me.
- That was me and Suk Jin.
- Her action is Choi Min Soo level.
[Hunter Choi Min Soo, who shot
2 action films on the show]
[Female warrior, Gong Hyo Jin,
who has nothing to lose to Min Soo!]
[Her dramatics is on par
with Min Soo, the hunter!]
[Possessed...by the hunter?]
[Yoo-ruce Willis who's been caught by
both of them is the surviving eye witness.]
This is really difficult.
It's not Gong Hyo Jin, but Po Hyo Jin.
(In this case, 'Po' means fear)
- For now, we need to all work together.
- Then let's all start searching.
- Let's all search one floor at a time.
- And gather together if anyone finds anything.
Let's search this floor first.
There could be another one
in here, right?
[The Yellow Team returns to the prop room
where an 'R' envelope was found.]
Either someone took it out...
or it was right here...
[Convinced there would be
evidence in the area somewhere!]
- There's nothing on the bottom.
- It's not here. Not here.
[Huh! That is...!]
- What is it?
- I found it!
[Lee Joon discovers the death script
that Hyo Jin had hidden!]
Where was it?
- Up there.
- That's unreal...
- What the heck is this?
- They got rid of it.
[The content of the death script that
Hyo Jin tore out of there earlier.]
You don't think they would've thrown out
the content they ripped out here somewhere?
Wow...this is...
[Discovers the ripped paper!]
- Did you find it?
- Is this the paper they threw out?
[If this is what's been done to
a piece of evidence...]
[It would be normal
not to be able to find this...]
[Throwing it away like this is funny enough,
but having found it is more unbelievable]
- Look at this. Face...face!
- Face?
[The ability to fish out clues like the CSI]
It says Lee Kwang something. Lee Kwang...
- Face? Lee Kwang...
- Wait a bit here...
- Like this...
- This is coming to life here...
- We can revive this.
- Ji Hyo, put this piece together. This one
Okay!
'I'll oust Lee Kwang Soo and go to hell'.
- 'I'll oust Lee Kwang Soo and go to hell'?
- 'I'll oust Lee Kwang Soo and go to hell'.
- Stick it on face and shout it out.
- What is that?
Jae Suk this is that line from
'Temptation of a wife'.
[Ace Ji Hyo even remembers the line perfectly.]
What do we do about the feelings?
That expression?
Hey...the line says,
'I'll oust Lee Kwang Soo and go to hell'.
'I'll oust Lee Kwang Soo and go to hell'...
- Since it says stick...
- Fork!
It's a mole! Temptation of a Wife.
- Really?
- Ah! Pencil! Pencil, pencil...
[Since the shred of the script was nearby,
the pencil device is surely nearby too!]
[Discovered?]
- What's wrong?
- I found it.
- How do you find things so well?
- Where did you find it?
It was up there.
[They thought no one would be able to find it
when she threw it up there...]
- They left this here too?
- Yes. They really are stupid.
- But are you sure you won't forget the line?
- Yes, that's fine, but...
[Anyways, through tenacity, the Yellow Team
has gains the device to oust the male lead!]
[On the other hand, the Blue Team is
going around to find another death script.]
- I'm convinced there's going to be one here.
- Ha Ha...
[Record room that may have something
hidden there]
Look! Look! The 'R'...
it has the 'R' stuck to it!
[It's really there!]
- I see it! I see it!
- How did you know that?
It's the record room...the record room.
- What if Kwang Soo is to find these?
- Then Kwang Soo will get rid of them.
[Put a picture of Kwang Soo within
your embrace and say...]
['You're in here...' and rip off his name tag]
[Ah...this line is from..]
[2004 SBS drama, 'Lovers in Paris']
You're...
In here.
[You're in here]
[Put a picture of Kwang Soo within
your embrace and say...]
['You're in here...' and rip off his name tag.]
[Ah...this line is from..]
[Inside of that is another
death script to kill off Kwang Soo?]
[While pouring the water on yourself,
say menacingly, 'I'm...going to crush you!']
[After saying the line, rip off his name tag.]
[1999 SBS drama, 'Trap of Youth']
I'm going to crush you.
I'm going to crush you...
[This seems like it will be
an easy act of emotion...]
[While scripts to eliminate Kwang Soo's
name tag are being discovered one by one...]
[The two main leads are yet
unaware of the danger that they're in]
[At last...ready to attack!]
[Apprehend the giraffe!]
[Now all the need to do is follow the script
and attack using the device!]
[Guardian Angel?
Invincible Hyo Jin blocks their path!]
- Let's grab her.
- Grab her...grab Hyo Jin.
[Ha Ha has somehow completely
transformed into Dokko Jin!]
[The plan to attack with 'Recovered'
from the death script!]
- I'm sorry.
- Go away!
[If he can recite the line exactly,
then he can eliminate a name tag!]
Recovered!
[Good! Acting and device passed!]
[Now possible to eliminate
one of Kwang Soo's name tag!]
Why are you being like that
over one, Kwang Soo?
- Hyo Jin!
- You can't!
[Ha Ha almost was had
by the invincible Hyo Jin!]
[Impala and the Tiger lock down on Hyo Jin!]
[Ha Ha goes to eliminate the first name tag!]
[Lee Kwang Soo, 1st out,
Lee Kwang Soo, 1st out.]
[Invincible Hyo Jin's wrathful counterattack!]
[Lead Giraffe, who lost one of his 7 name tags.]
[Still enraged Hyo Jin attacks Mr. Capable!]
Did you see her kicking with her foot?
- The glint in her eye...
- Why are you being like this to us?
[Even though she's smiling,
the glint in her eye is still fierce.]
- But you two are still alive...
- I didn't know Gong Hyo Jin was like this.
I thought she was delicate...
- I've been on the Homeland Trek.
- She's stronger than you.
- Really?
- Just because she's a woman...
The way you keep talking is
giving you an opportunity...
- Look at this! Why is she suddenly...
- Just stand still. Just need to stay still.
[Invincible Hyo Jin attacking the person
next to her out of embarrassment]
- If you're going to escape, then hurry up.
- Okay. We'll go downstairs.
- She just let you live.
- Thank you.
- Anyways, fighting!
- Homeland Trek, fighting!
[The lioness surprisingly weak to flattery]
- Fighting!
[The supporting cast being released after
eliminating one of the name tags.]
[She's just letting them go like that?]
What was I supposed to do when all
three of them were grabbing me like this?
You were totally grinning from ear to ear.
I really don't think I can handle you.
[Female lead refuses to shoot!]
[The male co-star really isn't to my liking.]
- So show it to me then.
- How much more can I protect you?
If the supporting cast shows up again,
just rip it off no matter what.
What am I supposed to do when it won't
rip off no matter how I try?
I'm just going to get hurt trying.
[Tough at one point and delicate at another...
Attractive Janus? (Goddess of change)]
Just look at my arms...
How can I with arms like these?
Just follow me.
You're really attractive like this, Hyo Jin...
[On the other hand...]
[The supporting cast is looking for
more death scripts.]
[At a place like that...an 'R' mark!]
There it is.
[Mr. Capable discovers a death script too!]
[Huh? A boxing glove?]
[Just what is in the script?]
How did you find that?
[With the glove on, throw a punch and say...
'Does it hurt? It hurts me too!']
[And after eliminate one of his name tags.]
[2003 MBC drama, 'Damo']
'Does it hurt? It hurts me too'.
You're dead.
I don't care if I succeed
in acting it out or not.
[Mr. Capable has no interest in
succeeding with the acting.]
This time, I have to say
'Does it hurt? It hurts me too'.
[Thinking of purposely getting NG's
so that he can keep on hitting him.]
I'm not going to eliminate him.
I'm going to keep getting NG's.
Have you seen anyone in a disguise?
[Go sisters]
- Is it okay for me to get a sip of water?
- Sure.
What have you done to need a drink of water?
[What have you done to need a drink of water!]
[I guess all he's done is run away,
asking her to protect him...]
What did you say? Hyo Jin...
Thank you. I appreciate the water.
Hyo Jin!
Why did you say that?
That was kind of disappointing.
Don't you have any sense? Any sense?
What would happen at a certain point?
Shouldn't you get feelings like that
after playing this game a few times?
Are you a spy?
- We're on the same team...
- You're not being any help to me at all.
Protecting me is a way of protecting yourself.
- You're hanging on my shoulders right now.
- How can you say something like that, Hyo Jin?
Just what is it that you can do?
All you do is run away.
I'll really do it.
I don't think I can take this any longer.
I'll rip it off.
- Let's go, Hyo Jin. Let's go.
- Why does he speak so seriously?
[A man definitely depends on the woman.
A different giraffe than the usual.]
I'll rip it off as soon as
I see any supporting cast.
I'll see about that.
[Encounters a supporting cast ally]
Kwang Soo...do you see this?
- What is that? Come on Jong kook...
- Huh?
It's only Hyo Jin and I,
but you guys all joined forces?
What did you say?
Even though it's just the two of you,
Hyo Jin's working like 7 people right now.
Hyo Jin...
With all the lives that he has...
[Hyo Jin slowly making her way to the
supporting cast members]
- I'll allow you to rip one off. Go ahead.
- I'm not going to rip one off.
- No, you can go ahead and rip one off.
- Shall I rip one off then?
- She can come up from behind. Watch out.
- No, it's okay.
- That glint in her eyes are back.
- Oh my goodness!
Hey, you have to eliminate one of
Kwang Soo's name tags.
['Damo' death script line]
[Punch one and say,
'Does it hurt? It hurts me too.']
Does it hurt? Because I'm happy.
NG!
Does it hurt?
I'm not hurt.
NG.
[Invincible Hyo Jin can no longer just watch,
so she starts to attack Mr. Capable.]
[All the allied troops
slowly making their way down.]
[Invincible Hyo Jin,
takes care of it with one swipe.]
- What the heck?
- Hyo Jin...
She's too scary.
- Does it hurt? Does it hurt?
- What are you guys doing?
Does it hurt?
[Wow! How can this be?
The giraffe's counterattack?]
[An enraged giraffe!
Looks as though he may bite the tiger!]
[Invincible Hyo Jin is trying to block
all of them by herself!]
[A total riot]
[Invincible Hyo Jin protects
Kwang Soo's back!]
[Giraffe... Mr. Capable's name tag?]
[How can this be!
Giraffe eliminates the Tiger's name tag!]
I can't believe he got my name tag!
Jong Kook out!
[Jong Kook-  Out!]
Hyo Jin! I ousted Kim Jong Kook!
[If someone were to see him,
they would think he won a medal.]
[Jong Kook - Out! Jong Kook - Out!]
Hyo Jin, come down here!
I can't believe...
[It's no fun to just leave...]
[Instinct to attack that never rests,
Invincible Hyo Jin!]
Hey...you really are awesome.
You're really awesome.
- This is just absurd...it's just absurd.
- How in the world is it that you...
- What happens to that then?
- I didn't think...
[Who could have ever imagined that
the giraffe would counterattack?]
I've been thinking the whole time that
he won't be able to attack me.
['Does it hurt? It hurts me too'
from Damo is no longer valid.]
[Should have just attacked
instead of playing around...]
First...I don't think going around
as a group is working.
- Then why don't we use the Go sisters now?
- Let's use them.
[Moving on from finding the death scripts
to finding the Go sisters.]
[If the script can be written well enough,
Kwang Soo can be ousted in one shot.]
You're right. Let's go find the Go sisters.
- Find the Go sisters quickly.
- We don't have Jong Kook.
Okay, let's go.
Let's hurry and get on our way.
Let's quickly find them and get him.
['Don't Walk, But Date'- 'Go Sister' writer]
[If they can be found and a request for their
script is made, then it shall be done.]
[An important existence to the victory for
both the leads and the supporting casts...]
[Being spurred on by
the urge to find the Go Sisters]
I bet he's dressed...
[Discovers a suspicious person!]
- It's a Go Sister!
- Go Sister!
[Ha Ha and Suk Jin discover
a Go Sisters' writer!]
Go Sister is coming that way!
He's heading that way!
Go Sister!
[Supporting cast allies
that hear the noise and gather around]
- 10th floor? Which way do we go?
- 10th floor!
[Knowing that this could be
their ticket to victory, chasing relentlessly.]
He's heading down.
[Where did he go?]
- He's not here?
- He's not here.
Where did he go?
I know that he came in here...
[There he is...]
[Since he will run if any noise is made,
first thing is to be cautious!]
[That's our Ace! Shutting the door first]
- Suk Jin! He's in here! Go Sister's in here!
- Where?
- Hurry! Hurry!
[Hiding underneath the desk]
- He's under there. Under.
- Hello, sir. We're sorry for this.
- I'm so sorry. Please excuse us.
- He's down there right now.
[I know that this could be trouble...]
- Hurry, hurry.
- We got him. Go in there.
[Finally entering the office that
Go Sister is hiding in]
- Good job on your hard work.
- Escort him out of here and write the script.
- We got him, we got him.
- Let us help you out.
I've been wondering if I should
kill Kwang Soo off or not.
Let's kill him off together.
Let's write it in an entertaining way.
We have to go find him quickly.
[Jae Suk and Ji Hyo off to find the other Go sister.]
[Without regards to whether it's
the lead or a supporting cast...]
[...they'll write the script as desired
and change the fate of anyone's life!]
[This story will start in 5 minutes.]
Out on the terrace on the 10th floor...
- Gong Hyo Jin slaps Kwang Soo's cheek...
- His left cheek.
- Screams out 'Let's break up!'
- And runs down to the 5th floor.
Runs down to the 5th floor.
And they break up for 20 minutes.
- And Kwang Soo kneels down in defeat...
- And rips off all his name tags...
- Kneels down in defeat and rips off all his...
- All his name tags!
He can only rip off one at a time.
[Even though it's the writer's script,
only 1 name tag at a time can be eliminated.]
- As he rips off one of his name tag...
- There's not enough space.
Then write smaller!
Don't leave so much space!
- It's the writer's pride.
- But you have too much space.
Then...as he slowly starts to sway,
he stops in his place.
- As he rips off a name tag...
- He stops for 20 minutes.
- You can't do it for 20 minutes.
- You just wrote in 20 minutes.
- Write in momentarily.
- Momentarily?
It's not "stadium," but "momentarily."
(Stadium and momentarily sounds very similar)
He stays frozen in the spot.
['Don't Walk, But Date'
The writer's script goes into effect!]
[At 5:05, this story starts]
Let's watch. This should be good.
Just let us know what the lines are.
- Let's break up!
- Let's break up?
- There's no time. We have to cue it.
- Let's break up.
[Shout out 'Let's break up'
as she slaps Kwang Soo's left cheek.]
[Since she burst out laughing, it's NG!]
He's shaking like a leaf right now.
[Scene retaken with feelings]
- Let's try this again with feelings.
- Quickly! Quickly!
[Shout out 'Let's break up'
as she slaps Kwang Soo's left cheek.]
[And screaming it out,
run down to the 5th floor.]
[Gathering of emotion]
You have to kneel down...
[The two break up for 20 minutes]
[In despair,
Kwang Soo rips off one of his name tags.]
[Lee Kwang Soo, 2nd out.
Lee Kang Soo, 2nd out]
[Kwang Soo frozen in his spot momentarily
according to the script.]
- You are...
- Wait! Wait!
[Timing! They have to rip off
one more with this opportunity!]
You are in here!
[Ha Ha, 'Lovers in Paris'-
Device and acting is a pass!]
- Hyo Jin, where are you?
- Grab him and rip it off!
- Grab him!
- Hyo Jin!
[This is the chance while he can't see
Invincible Hyo Jin for 20 minutes!]
Rip it off! Rip it off!
Ji Hyo!
[Ripping off Kwang Soo's third name tag!]
I love you!
[Lee Joon, following through with the line
from 'Love Fiction.']
Hey, you!
[Lee Joon - Out! Lee Joon - Out!]
Don't you know him yet?
[Line and device from 'Love Fiction'
no longer valid]
- I was holding onto him.
- Then how did he rip it off?
If you were holding onto him,
how could he have torn that off?
I even have the pencil here...
[Oh! The line and device from
'Temptation of a Wife' is also out!]
Hyo Jin...
[Just like the script, he escapes after
being frozen on the spot 'momentarily']
[Attacking him relentlessly since he is
apart from Invincible Hyo Jin for 20 minutes!]
- There you are. Where is he? Where is he?
- Hurry! We need to go!
I found 2 death scripts. Hurry!
He's on the 10th floor!
How did Joon get ousted?
I don't know!
[Male lead with a new glint in his eyes]
It's over if we can oust him
within that time!
There you are! Where is he?
[To the upper floor where voices are heard!]
Joon! Why did you get ousted?
Why are you out?
Where is he? Why are you out?
We weren't being cautious enough...
[Just then... Kwang Soo!]
What the!
Did he get you?
- Did he rip it off?
- Did your name get ripped off?
[Supporting character team in danger!
Hurry and find more death scripts!]
Awesome! Awesome!
[Discovers a box with the 'R' sticker!]
Awesome!
[Ring the bell and sweetly say, 'Yes, Chef!']
This is from Pasta...
- Chef... Chef...
- What are you doing?
[MBC drama, 'Pasta']
[The point is to say 'Chef' in a cute way
like Hyo Jin did.]
What do I do with this?
I have to say it in a cute way...
I don't know what to do with that.
[On the other hand,
Ha Ha heads to the kitchen area.]
Hey! I can't believe this!
I was just glancing in here!
I have to alert everyone to this right now!
- I found it. I found it!
- Where? Where are you?
- This is totally unbelievable.
- What is it?
[After licking on the lollipop,
offer it to the other person.]
[After doing so, rip off the name tag.]
[2009 drama, a scene from 'Iris']
[Do this candy kiss...to Kwang Soo...]
[The male and female lead who can't be
together for 20 minutes according to the script]
[Hyo Jin...where are you...]
Hyo Jin!
[Can only stare at each other from afar...]
Hyo Jin! I can't get close to you!
[A smoke blast]
[Now that we see it,
he's a specialist in pantomiming.]
I can't get close to you.
What's he doing?
Hyo Jin!
[You should act while being more
observant of the situation...]
[Finally realizing the situation, he escapes!]
[Kwang Soo, who can't be with Hyo Jin,
is about to meet his death!]
[Hiding himself in
preparation for counterattack!]
[Even though he's hiding,
his reflection can be seen...]
I'm going to crush you!
[Ji Hyo's line and the device from
'Trap of Youth' - Good!]
[Getting rid of one name tag first.]
Yes, Chef!
[Line and device from 'Pasta'- Good!]
[Save me...]
[The 5th name tag...]
How many are there left now?
[Now that we think about it,
the two can't be together yet.]
[Lee Kwang Soo - 5th out.
Lee Kwang Soo - 5th out]
[Male and female lead rendered helpless...]
[At this rate,
they'll be met with a tragedy...?]
[Another variable to victory,
another person's writer...]
Hyo Jin!
[Discovers flustered Kwang Soo!]
[Right outside the front door!]
Ha Ha!
Ha Ha! Hurry!
Hurry!
No, no!
[Seems as though Ha Ha is about to
do the candy kiss scene from 'Iris'!]
- Open your mouth! Hurry up and open it!
- I don't want to!
I said, open your mouth!
It's in there. It's in there!
[Candy kiss a success!]
That really hurts!
[Out of seven,
succeeds in eliminating the sixth one!]
Lee Kwang Soo - 6th out.
This shame...
I'll get my revenge.
I will destroy him!
The male lead for 'Don't Walk, But Date'
is Lee Kwang Soo!
[No wonder he became
the unexpected male lead...]
[We were still wondering about it
when Jae Suk was talking about it...]
What kind of a male role is this?
[Seriously...]
[...all sorts of humiliation...!]
[Just wait and see...
How is this a male starring role!]
[Still a little bit more time until she can
meet with Kwang Soo, the male lead...]
[That suspicious person is...the writer?]
Writer Go, come here. There you are.
[Slowed down
due to the uncomfortable clothing]
[That Go Sister writer
is the only way to save Kwang Soo!]
What the heck? Didn't I just catch him?
- Please sit down.
- Okay. Are we going to write here?
No, come this way.
Let's hide over here.
[Starting to write in a secret location!]
The recent...
Scenario...
Shall be deleted from the story...
[Delete the recent Go Sister script?]
The 3 people that have been
ousted will be acknowledged...
And the other actions will be invalidated...
[ 'Don't Walk, But Date'...
The strength of the script is once more...!]
What the heck?
- What is it?
- What's going on?
[Realizing that Go sisters'
script is in works]
- What is it?
- They must've used a death script!
[Just what is the content
of the changed script?]
[The recent script is a seamless story.
Ji Hyo, Ha Ha and Suk Jin acknowledges this.]
[And it's been decided
that everything is invalid.]
[The two leads not being able to meet
for 20 minutes is invalid.]
You wrote a nice script here.
Please acknowledge it willingly.
- Yes.
- Okay.
- So you acknowledge it?
- Yes.
[Thus...Ha Ha will slap Ji Suk Jin's cheek
until it resonates...]
Until it resonates...
[And Ji Suk Jin, who's just been slapped,
will rip off Song Ji Hyo's name tag.]
Why do I have to get slapped by him
and rip off her name tag?
This is what's written in the script.
Hey, why couldn't we have
written ours like that?
Wow...how could she have written it
so skillfully like that?
- Ours was a total mess.
- We can't do anything about her script.
We didn't know how to write ours.
Yours is written so cleanly...
I sat him down in the massage chair
and made him write it.
- Kwang Soo..
- Hyo Jin!
Kwang Soo, come here!
Come here. Everything is invalidated now,
you can come here.
- It's gone?
- We have to watch the slap.
- What happened?
- Just wait.
- Do it well.
- Okay.
[Thus Ha Ha will slap Suk Jin's cheek
until it resonates]
Action!
How did you control yourself?
Goodbye... Goodbye, Ji Hyo.
[Song Ji Hyo- Out! Song Ji Hyo- Out!]
[There aren't any more death scripts to
eliminate Kwang Soo's last name tag!]
[The return of invincible Hyo Jin!]
Ha Ha! Ha Ha!
[Impala brother on the run!]
Please! You can't!
Suk Jin! Suk Jin!
[Even though he came back to help...]
Ha Ha! I'm sorry!
[Really amazing!
Invincible Hyo Jin, right away to Suk Jin!]
[Ha Ha-Out!]
Pil-Chok-Cross!
[Attacking again after
shouting out their battle cry!]
Hyo Jin!
[She's coming...]
[What?]
How should I betray him?
- I didn't like you from the beginning.
- Please don't be like this, Hyo Jin.
- Hyo Jin...
- What have you done for me?
I know that you are famous for being
the icon of betrayal.
What kind of a sly move is this?
[Extreme conflict between the two leads
at the final scene?]
[Romantic comedy...
Changing to web of deceit at the end?]
[Just what will be the ending to this drama?]
There they come.
[A little while later...]
- She looks really at ease.
- Wait, Suk Jin...
Is Suk Jin dead?
[The last name tag still remains!]
[A little while ago...]
[Hyo Jin, please...]
[This was all a plan to distract Suk Jin!]
This is the winning trophy for
the male and female lead today.
[Effervescent]
[A trophy and a solid gold necklace
to the male and female lead]
[And for the ultimate ending, a hug scene]
[With the utmost emotion...]
[First meeting filled with nerves,
and their happy time together]
Let's break up.
[But there were obstacles
to break these two up...]
[Overcoming many adversities and hardship...
ultimately ending up together]
[Thus ultimately,
a happy ending for the two...]
[Huh?]
[The giraffe's betrayal DNA...]
[After protecting him all day...]
Wow...
you're really holding yourself back a lot.
I don't want to show
my violent side anymore.
If there's another chance in the future,
I really hope that Hyo Jin comes back.
We had no idea that she'd be like this.
[The queen of romantic comedies,
the ultimate female lead, Gong Hyo Jin]