I wonder what it is about me
they find uncomfortable?
[The burdensome Go Chang Suk]
[His ability to eat is a given,
ability to whine is an addition.]
Why is everything we do so hard?
[Grumbling Shin Jung Geun]
[The flower man Ace, Lee Jong Won]
[The Big brother, Im Ha Ryong,
overflowing with ease.]
[The adorable brother, Son Byung Ho]
[A day of the Flower man actors.]
This show is really challenging.
[Their day has been challenging?]
[The next morning...]
[The calm before the storm?
A peaceful morning in the ocean.]
[Agents raiding the dormitory.]
[Hm...]
[Being forced awake
without knowing the purpose.]
[The neighborhood actors being dragged
outside the dormitory.]
[So sleepy...]
Please keep quiet.
Pick one of the shirts and
get in the car.
[Jung Geun picks the color
of passion, red.]
Please pick one each.
[Who am I... where am I?]
Isn't this Running Man?
[Flower man Ace, Jong Won
is also being forced awake.]
[And...]
[Impala with the swollen face.]
[Suk Jin's also on the list of the
ones to be forced awake?]
Why am I here right now?
- I'm... I'm not...
- Maybe you've become a guest?
[Jung Geun's chic sharp tongue
bright and early in the morning.]
Don't you think the running wind
out there is too harsh?
This is Running Man.
[A refreshing morning gag.]
[Where are they going after each
choosing a t-shirt for themselves?]
Ha Ryong isn't here though...
[Ulsan Ulju-gun Nasari Village]
Everyone take a name tag for now,
but put your shirts on.
You can change into
your shirts when you arrive.
Do I have to keep this on?
The name tags are pretty large...
they're kind of big.
[Unhesitating flower men]
[Not even able to wake up fully.]
[Barely fitting into the tight-fitting shirt.]
Here, I'll stick it on your back.
[Second day on the show,
and already practicing ripping off the tag.]
Even though it was just a practice,
I didn't like the feeling of that.
- Okay, I'll see you later.
- Okay, brother.
Even though we all woke up
from our sleep the same...
how can our styles be so different?
[Could a hat be of any help?]
Even the hat is small on me.
That hat is big on me...
You all have to get up and go out
to the front lawn of the dorm.
[Blanking out first thing in the morning.]
[Giraffe rushing down the steps.]
First!
It's a great morning.
Did you all sleep well?
[All the same colored t-shirts that
the big brothers have already chosen.]
These t-shirts are for the couple race
that's going to take place in a little...
Couple?
[Ah... couple...]
Please pick a color.
- I'll take the orange.
- I'll take this one.
[Jae Suk - Blue; Kwang Soo - Orange]
During the couple race in a little bit,
you'll be with the person in the same color.
Couple? Ah... the big brothers?
I was really surprised earlier too
when he mentioned couple...
It's been a long time since
I've worn blue.
[Gary chooses white]
I have to find the person in the same color?
Why can't I understand it right away?
[Ha Ha chooses red.]
[Blank Ji rushes down to choose purple.]
What is this?
[Jong Kook gets green.]
[Find your partner in the same color shirt
within the next hour and a half...]
[and gather at Nasari Beach.]
Where are all the big brothers at?
Can we eat something?
This is the before.
Before I wash my face.
[Before washing up for the day.]
[Starting to wash his face]
[Just what will his image be like
after he's done washing his face?]
[Hm...]
[Before and after are the same?]
I'm done washing my face.
There's not much difference, is there?
I wonder if the older brothers
have eaten their breakfast?
[Everyone's taking it upon themselves
to eat their breakfasts well.]
- Is this what I think it is?
- Yes, it's Ah-sak.
Thank you for the breakfast.
[Even Chang Suk is enjoying
his mini cup ramen.]
[We were able to shoot this show thanks
to the cooperation of the villagers.]
[30 minutes to find
their big brother partners.]
I doubt they'll be at the entrance area...
[Where are the big brothers at?]
I'm looking for the
big brother in a white t-shirt.
If you tell me where he is,
I'll take a picture with you.
You will? Let me take a picture
of you first.
Really?
The one in the same shirt as mine?
- Yeah, I'll tell you.
- In the white shirt?
I can't see anything.
I don't know what Im doing.
Mother, I don't think you're doing it right.
Why don't I give it a try?
You just need to look right here.
One, two, three.
[Kindly taking a picture with her.]
- Wow, it turned out well.
- Thank you!
- Mother, where is he?
- I have no idea!
[Mother having attained her goal...
oh my goodness...]
- I don't know!
- Mother...
have a great day.
[But still coolly wishing her a good day.]
Hello, Elder.
[Jae Suk running into some elders
while looking for his blue-clad brother.]
- How are you?
- Yoo Jae Suk is here. Yoo Jae Suk!
- I'm looking for someone right now.
- You're here! Look who's here!
Hello.
- I knew something was going to happen today.
- Really?
- Isn't this Yoo Jae Suk?
- Ah, yes...
[An explosion of recognition.]
[Blank Ji on the search for
her purple-clad brother.]
Is anyone here by any chance?
No, I live here by myself.
[Where are the brothers?]
- Why are they hiding so well?
- That's what I'm saying!
[They're not hiding, but resting...]
Brother!
[In a serious game of Omok.]
Ugh, I lost!
Where are they hiding?
Seriously, these brothers...
Yes, it's 1,000 won.
How many are you taking?
[Did Chang Suk find a job?]
Do you need a bag?
[Servicing the customer comfortably
as if he's been doing this job for years.]
There you go.
Goodbye.
This cash business is fun in the country.
- You were a gym teacher?
- Yes, I used to be a national wrestler.
- There's a name tag ripping game.
- Ripping off the name tags?
- So that's why...
- What you should do then is...
When a person is hit, they automatically
bend down and put their hand up like this.
If that happens, you can grab it like this,
and twist yourself around...
[The teacher's quick leopard-like attack.]
If you grab them like this,
they can't move.
[A very realistic practice.]
Hello, Sir.
By any chance,
is there anyone in your home?
- I only have elders in my home.
- They're all elders.
Brother Jung Geun!
You startled me.
Hey, Jong Kook. What's going on?
[Discovers Jung Geun
in middle of his training.]
[The same red as Ha Ha.]
Seriously? Okay.
- Hey!
- Wow... wow!
He's wearing the same shirt as Ha Ha.
Jung Geun...
Jung Geun!
[Finally a team is born!]
[I found him... my partner.]
You're the same color as me.
Jung Geun!
- Did you sleep well?
- Yeah, I slept well.
You startled me!
I heard that this is what you're like.
You really did startle me.
[Starting to kid around
as soon as he sees Jung Geun.]
I'm so gullible that
I'll fall for things like this.
Jung Geun... just trust me.
- Trust me...
- I was told that I can't trust you.
We're a team. I was praying on my
way here that you'd be my partner.
[Even though it's not trustworthy,
Jung Geun and Ha Ha are a team.]
I heard that there was an elder in here?
[Byung Ho in midst of his morning nap.]
- Byung Ho!
- Yeah?
What are you doing over there?
How long have you been sleeping
there for?
Byung Ho... you're purple?
- Yeah, what are you?
- You were sleeping on a toilet paper roll?
[A middle aged man's great adaptability.
Some might see him and think it's his home.]
- Come on, buddy.
- Yeah, buddy.
- Don't be the first to get ousted today.
- I got it.
[Byung Ho is making sure to get his
rejuvenating rest for the game.]
[Blank Ji in her purple t-shirt.]
Jae Suk, did you find anyone?
You're purple... you're in purple.
- Did you see purple?
- Yeah.
- Where is he?
- You just need to go this way.
- I just need to go this way?
- Ji Hyo, I'll give you a hint.
He is like a cobra.
- Like a cobra?
- Go on.
You'll find out the reason why.
Ji Hyo, hurry up and go.
Like a cobra?
[Jae Suk desperately searching
for his blue brother.]
Is anyone here?
I think there's someone in here.
Oh my goodness!
[That's right! In this place...]
[Chang Suk, the supermarket employee.]
Oh my... you're in blue!
[The blue team is finally born!]
Chang Suk, come on out.
Wow... I was seriously so startled.
I thought you were the owner
of the supermarket.
- Wait... I have to write down what I sold.
- You sold something?
Yeah, shrimp crackers...
[Blank Ji searching for the Cobra Brother.]
Is anyone here?
[Cobra Brother having moved to the room
to take his morning nap.]
Who's this?
[I found him! The Cobra Brother!]
[Reunited with Cobra Brother
whom she so longed for!]
[Purple Team's meet is a success!]
- We have to hurry to the beach.
- We have to go right now?
I know these shoes!
I know these shoes...
[A brother with
familiar shoes in this location?]
Jong Won! Why have
you been in such deep hiding?
- I thought that's what I had to do.
- The hat suits you very well today.
- This is good... we have a chance.
- I understand, Jong Won.
I think there's some telepathy between us
following the events of yesterday.
[With the strength of
telepathy this time too?]
Am I the only one who hasn't
found my partner yet?
Just who the heck is it?
[Where is the orange clad brother?]
Just where...
What do I do?
Kwang Soo hasn't found his partner.
- Kwang Soo...
- Hello!
This is a great morning!
Did you all sleep well?
[The youngest Giraffe is showing
his respects to his older brothers first]
- It's Ha Ryong... Ha Ryong.
- I don't have a partner.
He's not here...
he seriously isn't anywhere.
As soon as Kwang Soo got here,
it's started to rain.
[Am I alone...]
- Hey, Kwang Soo...
- Where's Ha Ryong?
Where's Ha Ryong?
[Huh? Sound of music coming from
the ocean?]
[Twinkle?]
There's a boat heading this way.
There's a boat coming this way.
Hey, who sings this song?
Did Ha Ryong drink the flower tea?
- Hey!
- It's a girl... it's a girl!
How can you do this?
Hey, isn't that Tae Yeon?
That looks like Tae Yeon!
[You're right. It's me!]
[Girls Generation's Tae Yeon]
[What is she doing here?]
Change your shirt with me!
[Is everyone understanding the
situation now?]
- It's Tae Yeon!
- Switch me with!
- You must really be happy about this!
- She's my partner?
- Yeah, I think so.
- Are you sure that it's not Tiffany?
- Did Ha Ryong drink the flower tea?
- Yes.
[That's right... the flower tea.]
[That's how the big brother Ha Ryong
changed into Tae Yeon.]
Jung Geun,
hurry up and drink the flower tea!
Hurry... give him some flower tea.
Make him drink it.
Kwang Soo... look at Kwang Soo.
[The Giraffe breaks out into a gallop.]
[My partner?]
Hello!
- Tae Yeon!
- It's me, Tae Yeon!
[Automatically breaking out into a dance.]
[The bendy dance to welcome Tae Yeon.]
Tae Yeon, hurry up!
- Tae Yeon...
- Hi, Kwang Soo.
- How did this happen?
- It's nice to see you!
- Tae Yeon, have you been well?
- Yes.
[Giraffe thinking that he was
teamed with Ha Ryong...]
- Ta da!
- What's that?
- Is that the flower tea?
- It's the flower tea!
- Flower tea!
Flower tea!
Even if he were to change,
how could he have changed this much?
Ha Ryong changing to that...
Kwan Yeol... let's change our clothes.
Let's change our clothes.
[Ah... because his shirt is orange?]
Hey! Don't hold her hand!
Married man, stay out of this!
Stay out of this, married man!
You're here? Hey, Ppung-Soon!
- Jelly!
- It's been over two years, why bring that up?
- Hello.
- Welcome!
[Obstructing his handshake.]
[The countless number of hands
protecting Tae Yeon.]
Why are you being like this when I'm going
to greet an old friend of mine?
Hey, let's stand over here so that
we can see Tae Yeon's face.
[He wants to see Tae Yeon's face.]
Jong Won! I'm right here!
- Jong Won, I'm here!
- Jong Won, why are you being like that?
- Jung Geun moved where he's standing.
- This is my first time seeing SNSD.
He moved so he can see Tae Yeon.
I was afraid I wouldn't get to see her.
It's nice to meet you.
[A rare sight for such a brash brother!]
- This is the first time I've seen him...
- You're face is beet red right now.
- My face is red?
- Yes.
- Your face is the color of your shirt.
- Even the tips of your ears are red.
It's just because I'm glad to see her.
- Where are you going?
- What are you doing? Jong Won!
Why are you being like this?
[Unstoppable older brothers.]
Why don't you say hi to Tae Yeon,
Chang Suk?
- Tae Yeon, come say hi.
- Go say hi to her.
He said he saw her from far away
while shooting a movie once.
- I'm a fan of yours too. Hello.
- Don't touch her hand!
- Stand back. Get back to your place.
- You startled me!
- Jung Geun, your face is so red.
- Don't get close to Jung Geun!
- Jung Geun, come here.
- I don't want you touching me!
- Tae Yeon...
- Like this. He holds his out like this.
His face is really red!
Look at your face, it's so red!
[These two acknowledged as her
secret uncle fans.]
They're all so different with
Tae Yeon here.
I can't believe how different
the atmosphere is with Tae Yeon here.
Then what are we...
Now, we're going to start with the
preliminary game before the final location.
We're going to do a quiz right here.
The team that answers the question correctly
will take an egg and head to the final spot.
[These are the golden eggs.]
The last couple to remain alive will
take home all these eggs.
- Are you ready for the first question?
- Yes!
This is really tight!
[The team that pulls out the flag first at
the finish line gets to answer first.]
[Chang Suk's adorable attacks.]
Good job, you did good.
Today's quiz... is a song quiz.
[Preliminary mission - Song quiz]
One of the villagers that lives here
came up with this question.
[Correctly guess the song that the villagers
sing after they listen to the song.]
- Hello, Mother!
[Welcome]
Hello.
[Ah... she's going to sing along to a song
after listening to it on the headphones?]
- Mother, please...
- Please listen to the song before singing.
[Refined and adorable, Mother Lee Jung Sik.]
Set, go!
[Huh?]
Oh! I think it's a dance song!
[Can hear the sound of a recent
dance song flowing from the headphones.]
Her dancing...
Are you eating something, Mother?
Mother, is this a foreign song?
[A lively song?
Totally immersed in the rhythm.]
Sing it a little slower... slower.
I'm so confused with the dancing.
Her dancing is confusing me!
- Are you sure that it's a Korean song?
- Of course it is, it's a Seoul song.
[Just what could this Seoul song be?]
- The title is..
- The title of the Vietnam song is...
[Reminded of the Vietnamese role
that he played in a movie in the past.]
Chang Suk had to speak Vietnamese
in one of his movies.
[Is this what Mother's singing sounds like?]
- What was a word that you heard, Mother?
- No, you can't ask that.
- We don't know the title.
- The title... is a five letter word.
[A recent five letter word song.]
It's a recent song...
[Slightly thinking of something?]
[Just what could this song be?]
- Five letters...
- I wonder if this could be it?
I'm sorry, but I don't think I know.
Electric shock?
There's someone who mentioned this group
out of those of you who've been talking.
- Someone mentioned it?
- The correct answer is?
[Secret? KARA?]
Isn't there a time limit?
- Five, four, three...
- Wait a minute.
- Secret! Secret...
- Two...
- One!
- Secret garden?
It is not secret garden.
- You're saying it's a famous song?
- Is it this dance?
What is this?
Love is move...
[After hearing it, this part is similar...]
Isn't that Sistar?
No, no, it's Secret.
- Five, four, three...
- 'Sky ground, Star ground'.
What are you talking about?
[The song, 'Sky ground,
Star ground' from 15 year ago.]
[Suddenly reminded of the song.]
[This is hard...]
- The correct answer is?
- Love is...
[All the hints were already given.]
Is it Madonna, donna?
Five, four, three, two, one!
[Get it wrong, get it wrong!]
- Love move?
- I don't think so...
[Ma-don, Na-don-na. Ma-don, Na-don-na.]
- Love is on the move.
- Love is on the move?
- Love is on the move!
[The correct answer!]
- What was that?
- See? I was right!
[The identity of that song is this...]
[Singing with enthusiasm.]
Your moves match very well
to the beat of this song.
- Where?
- It's the same... it's the same.
It was Love is on the move?
- I thought it was just a move for a while.
- Thank you.
[The first ones to head over
to the final location.]
[Incredible scale - paper mill Factory.]
[The different set of eyes
that awaits them here.]
[Their every single move will be watched.]
[The result of the final mission?]
[The Blue team is the first to arrive again.]
Listen carefully to Mother's singing.
There's no way we can listen any better
to Mother's singing than we are already.
- She's so good.
- She does such a great job.
Is it the same one as earlier?
Secret's Love is on the move?
[Just what is she singing?]
You normally go around doing shows
like this, don't you?
[Perhaps singing because this is
what she usually does?]
Even the way she dances...
it's doesn't look like an amateur's move.
- Is this a recent song?
- This song came out about three years ago.
[A three to four year old song.]
- Five, four, three...
- Big Bang's 'Lies'.
How many letters is it?
I'm not going to tell you.
Why do you do this only when I come?
Let's listen to it one more time.
This sound...
[This sound if the voice that sings
all the popular songs.]
[The identity of this song is...]
[Is this song!]
[Son Dam Bi's 'Crazy']
[Currently singing it the right way.]
We got it!
Okay we got it...
we figured out what it sounds like.
You did a great job, Mother.
Then the correct answer is?
Ah, I think I'm going to go crazy...
Son Dan Bi's 'Crazy'!
He got it! He's got it.
I was crazy... I didn't like it...
I had fallen for it...
[Blue team having their win stolen.]
[Correct answer!]
- Great job, Mother!
- Mother, you did a great job!
This one really was the best.
[Thank you Mother,
for all your singing.]
[Second ones to pass through.]
[Heading straight to the final location.]
This time,
it's going to be a different Mother...
that will be singing for us.
Just as we're getting used to the singing,
you're switching up on us!
[Injured Gary gains the flag.]
- Are you okay?
- Hello.
- Hello, Mother!
- Mother, what is your name?
- Hello.
Hello, my name is Lee Bong Lae.
The subject this time...
is dancing!
Dance! Dance!
[Guess the correct song after seeing
the dance of a recent song.]
Mother, have fun with it!
[Huh?]
- She's not bad, look at her go.
- She's a good dancer.
- I think it's a girl group.
- It looks like a feminine sort of dancing.
I don't think it's one person's dance,
but several people dancing.
[The skills of a dancer.]
[Tae Yeon seems to have guessed?]
The correct answer is?
She did a really great job dancing it.
What is the correct answer?
Wonder girls... 'Tell me'.
[Exchanging glances with Mother?]
[Is this right?]
- Shin Shin... 'The world's in...'
- Wait a minute!
[A sudden answer from the Giraffe?]
No! That's not it!
I'll give you a final chance.
Tell me your wish...
[The correct original dance.]
- That's it... this is it.
- She broke out the move! She's got it!
That's right! This is it!
[Correct answer!]
[A joint performance with Mother.]
[Dancing skills that match Tae Yeon's.]
Thank you.
[Orange team, third to pass through.]
Is an 'R' written on it since it's an egg?
Being alone with you in Busan
in weather like this...
I feel a bit strange about it.
- This is Ulsan.
- What?
We're in Ulsan?
- Ulsan.
- We're not in Busan?
[You're in Ulsan...]
Oh, okay... I'm sorry.
But why did they...
- give these to us? Can we take it?
- These...
The winner will take all of these.
How much do you think they're worth?
[Whether young or old,
everyone loves prizes.]
[Could it be a Chinese song by any chance?]
I wonder if it's a song from Hong Kong?
I think I know this one.
[Vietnamese expert Chang Suk
guessing what it is again?]
[Blank Ji might've guessed what it is?]
[The dance automatically comes out!]
We thought it was only Mother who
knew how to do this...
- We thought it was only Mother...
- Why are you twisting your hair like that?
[A flamboyant dance in front of Gary
of all people.]
Why are you dancing like that?
Hey... why are you doing that?
Gary is trying to forget about you.
- I just can't seem to forget...
- Why are you doing that in front of Gary?
Memories, go away!
[Gary's memories are still strong?]
Girl's generation's 'Oh'?
- I think Gary has this one.
- Gary... Gary knows it.
Secret's 'Madonna'!
[Correct answer!]
[Extremely close.]
[Anyway...]
[The location where these eggs are headed...]
[is an extremely large factory.]
[This is today's battleground.
Ulsan's M paper mill factory]
Look at how the sides are built up.
[Just what awaits from them here?]
[Today's forecast...
Action of the largest scale?]
[Everyone, come with your anticipation!]
- Ugh, we're in big trouble!
- It's okay, it's okay.
This time, we have a Father helping.
It's a song.
[Only two teams left on the beach.]
Chang Suk is...
The song... set, go!
Are you okay?
[The lyrics are only 'Are you okay?']
[Fell over laughing.]
- Are you okay?
- No, I'm not okay.
[New lyrics?]
Correct answer!
2NE1?
- And the correct answer is?
- 'I Don't Care' by 2NE1.
[Correct answer!]
- Thank you.
- Thank you, Father.
- Crying like a baby...
- Father, thank you.
[But was able to bring out the point.]
[Ulsan's immense 'M' paper mill factory.]
[Suk Jin and Jong kook,
the first to arrive on site.]
[Pick a card of their choosing.]
- Number two and seven.
- Please show the camera.
[Jong Kook - seven, Suk Jin - two]
[Other members each choose a card
as well.]
Numbers five and ten.
Is it okay for us to know that
about each other?
- This...
- Aren't we on the same team?
We're on the same team.
[Everyone completes choosing a card!
Just what is the secret of today's mission?]
- You and I are pretty far apart.
- Yeah, we are. What is this?
[Huh? What is that large monitor for?]
So we can see everything that's going on.
We can see who's being hunted down.
[A total of 16 CCTV that have been
installed throughout the factory.]
- Look at this...
- Come see. It's what you like.
What the heck? This is what I totally love!
You can see everything.
[Not only can you see, but you can hear too!]
Come look at this... it's no joke.
Everyone's sitting in a spot
according to the number you picked.
[Everyone seated in number order
according to what they picked.]
[Time to announce today's game rules.]
In order of the number...
you will enter in five minute intervals
to start the name tag ripping game.
[In order of numbers, enter in five minute
intervals to start the name tag ripping game.]
The ones who have entered will
rip off each other's name tag
and the couple that remains alive
to the end are the final winners.
[The last person to remain alive and his mate
will be the final winners of today's game.]
Then I guess I'm over the minute I go in?
[Who knows? Hard to tell what will happen!]
Then... Ha Ha goes in first,
then I go in five minutes later?
Then Jong Won way down there
will come in after 60 minutes?
That's not a bad thing there.
[Now looking at it, all the team
members are sat very far apart.]
Rather it being advantageous for
the team members to be far apart
it's more advantageous for the team that
sticks close together. Just like you two.
The reason for that is as soon as you
get in there, the other team's after you.
Why do you analyze everything each time?
[Coach Kook's warning.]
I'm just saying that's how it is.
If he remains alive, as soon as his partner
goes in, then they're a team right away.
The way I see it...
As soon as Jong kook comes in,
we're all in danger.
[Anyways, as soon as Jong kook comes in,
everyone's lives are in danger.]
Suk Jin, you have to remain
alive until I get in.
Jung Geun... I'll try to remain alive until
you get in no matter what.
[Worrying from the far distance
they're sitting apart from each other.]
You have to remain alive, okay?
Then Gary and Jong Won
have the best advantage!
- Well, since the both of you...
- You're both far back, so it's better.
But anyways, it's not all that great either.
He's right after me.
Why do you only think that
mine will get ripped off?
Then Jong Won may be able to grant his
daughter's wish and remain alive for a while?
But Gary will be totally targeted.
Until Jong Won comes in,
he'll be totally targeted.
Until Jong Kook gets in, we shouldn't
oust each other in the arena.
If we don't pool all our strength together,
we'll all be victims of Jong Kook's.
- Stop doing that!
- I don't know what you're telling me to stop?
You don't understand?
When you're going off like that?
- I don't really understand.
- Really? I'll open up your ears for you then.
[So frightening...]
[Because it doesn't sound like
an empty promise, it's terrorizing.]
I'll open them up for you.
You just wait.
Please open up my frustrated
heart for me too.
My frustrated heart too.
Starting with number one,
we will get started.
- I understand. Jung Geun, fighting!
- Fighting!
- Ha Ha, you have to stay alive.
- Ha Ha, good luck, okay?
- Yes, Jong Kook. Fighting!
Number one. Ha Ha's entrance.
I think I'm going to die early today.
[An uneasy feeling...]
[Thanks to the cooperation of the factory,
we were able to shoot the episode safely.]
- There he is.
- He's going in... Ha Ha's going in.
[Clearly able to see the person
making their entrance.]
- I should really study the cameras.
- There are lot of blind spots.
[With the factory being so large,
there are many blind spots still.]
Wow, this is...
What do I do?
[Today's expansive battlefield.]
As long as we sit here,
we can see everything they're doing.
What do I do?
Today...
[Ha Ha's plan for today...]
There will be no moving around.
I'll stay hidden.
Today... if I move, then I die.
I'm going to stay hidden no matter what.
I'll stay hidden and get them when they come.
Stay hidden, and get them when they come.
Not enough time on air? If I get
ousted, there won't be any anyway!
That's why staying hidden is the best.
Just stay hidden.
[What he said isn't wrong.]
[On the other hand, everyone
in the planning stages in the room.]
[The greatest change to the plan
is Jong Kook's mission session point.]
- The thought of Jong Kook waiting for me...
- Jong Kook should've been the first.
That could've been better.
If Jong Kook had been number one...
it would be no different than throwing in
food to the beasts in Serengeti.
[Throwing in food to the Tiger
in five minute intervals?]
Tae Yeon, I'll come find you
as soon as I get in.
Okay.
Tae Yeon,
why are you being so insincere?
It's because she doesn't like you.
[You trust me, don't you?]
Does she have to tell you that herself?
No, she does like me.
We have an understanding.
- Just send him in already instead.
- It's not time yet.
He's about to have an anxiety attack.
Number two, you may enter now.
- Suk Jin, be careful!
- Jong Kook...
- I'll do my best to stay alive. Fighting!
- Fighting!
- Yay!
Good luck.
Don't worry about anything since
you've always been a target.
Okay.
[A different sense of nervousness
with the CCTV all over the place.]
Among all the beasts...
Number two, Ji Suk Jin's entrance.
I think I'm going to die early today.
I'm getting a bad feeling about this.
Why did I have to be number one of all things?
I'm seriously about to go crazy here.
[Ha Ha floundering all over the place.]
Ha Ha!
Suk Jin!
Hey, shouldn't we be
joining our forces together?
Hey, I'll talk to Jong Kook and
protect you.
We're as one!
I'll tell Jong Kook and protect you.
What did he just say?
Why is he speaking for me like that?
- Where are they?
- They're working together now.
Suk Jin and Ha Ha are working together.
There's no meaning to an alliance like that.
I don't know why Ha Ha is aligning
himself with Suk Jin. There are others.
An alliance like that...
as soon as one of them ousts someone,
it'll break off right away.
- It's so fragile and breaks easily.
- Something like that isn't even an alliance.
Thoughts like alliances aren't needed.
You have to go in and just rip them off.
That's how the game will keep going.
Hey, just go in there and go crazy
ripping everything off.
If they're somewhere where the camera
can't catch, then I'll drag them out...
- Hey...
- I'll bring them out to the camera.
- That's kind of scary...
- I'll drag them out in the open.
- That's what I'll do.
- Are you shooting a horror film?
I think I'm going to oust the
two of them first. They're just so loud.
- Byung Ho, fighting
- Fighting!
I will not be the first
to be eliminated today.
[Byung Ho had his name tag ripped
last week during his mission.]
[Therefore, he wasn't able to
chase anybody down.]
Don't worry.
I will wait for you to show.
[Byung Ho taking off with a firm
determination today.]
[For his daughters who will be
watching this from home today, please...]
This is frightening.
Wow... that machine is enormous.
I'm nervous and
having trouble breathing right now.
I've never done a race like this before.
I've never ripped off any name tags before.
But I'll make sure I'm not
the first to be eliminated today.
I'm going to make sure to remain alive.
Even if this factory breaks down in half...
[His vow that can be heard by everyone.]
[His vow and determination sound so cute!]
- Isn't this first for you too?
- It's my first time too.
[The quiet next player up.]
Chang Suk...
you look really serious right now.
It's because I'm nervous.
I went to rip Ha Ha's off yesterday,
but had mine torn off by Gary instead.
Ha Ha, and Suk Jin both...
they're the icons when it comes to betrayal.
They're icons of betrayals.
You can't trust them.
[Please last through it, Byung Ho.]
[Committing himself to the game...]
Why can't I hear Suk Jin at all?
- Where's Ha Ha?
- I'm afraid he's going to go after Suk Jin.
Ha Ha has to oust the others
before Kim Jong Kook arrives.
I have to oust Ha Ha first no matter what.
I think Ha Ha will be after me.
I was really shocked yesterday, Byung Ho.
These aren't that easy to rip off, right?
- Since the name tag is larger today...
- It's been five minutes.
- What? Five minutes?
- Since I have to wait for so long...
- Jong Won is counting.
- Chang Suk... good luck!
- Chang Suk, fighting!
[Stay alive!]
- I think he will be spotted easily.
- You think he'll be back soon?
[I'm coming!]
Chang Suk is surprisingly weak.
[Unlike the way he looks,
Chang Suk is more feminine than expected.]
[Number four, Go Chang Suk's entrance.
Number four, Go Chang Suk's entrance.]
Hurry, let's hurry.
Once Jae Suk comes in,
they're both going to be after me.
Before that happens...
I need to eliminate him.
His thought of attacking Jae Suk's team...
that's the right way of thinking right now.
How can you say that when I'm
sitting right next to you?
Until you get in there,
it's between them right now.
I'm getting scared.
The thing that Suk Jin needs to be doing is
to get next to Ha Ha and eliminate him.
- Yeah, he needs to eliminate him.
- What in the world is he doing instead?
[Ha Ha's my partner!]
- What is he doing? Ha Ha...
- He needs to eliminate Ha Ha!
Suk Jin, eliminate Ha Ha!
- And if Byung Ho or Chang Suk gets close...
- He needs to oust Byung Ho first.
- Number five, Tae Yeon...
- Get in there and...
- You have to destroy everyone in there.
- I understand.
[Will she be able to turn herself
into a giant player?]
[Be careful, Tae Yeon!]
[Even though she may look weak,
she has experience being on Running Man!]
[Pay attention to my shining self...]
Tae Yeon has to remain alive...
for us to have a chance at Jong Kook.
The only person Jong Kook will never be
able to eliminate is Tae Yeon.
[It's a camera.]
[Even though she's nervous,
camera fun time takes priority.]
- Tae Yeon is on number 14.
- There's Tae Yeon!
Just hold out for a little while.
I'll be in there soon.
I will protect you. Tae Yeon!
I think the viewer's anticipation will be
very high since Yoo Jae Suk is next.
Please don't say things like that.
The viewer's anticipation is growing.
Why? Because I go in after you.
Higher, higher, higher!
Higher, higher, higher...
their anticipation is getting so high. High!
Everything will turn into chaos
the moment he steps in there.
Higher, higher, higher!
- Yoo Jae Suk will enter in three minutes.
- Okay.
Somehow... I'll have to eliminate at least
one person within those five minutes.
- If you don't, it'll be dangerous.
- So there's a reason why you all work out...
- Why?
- I see why you guys all work out.
If we didn't work out,
there's no way we can stand this.
Chang Suk is in camera two range...
[Chang Suk keeping himself
well hidden for now.]
There he is, there he is.
- There he comes.
- Where? Where?
[Such Jin, Ha Ha, and Chang Suk
all have discovered each other.]
Here. Stay here,
and I swear I won't eliminate you.
[Suk Jin and Ha Ha seeming to team up
to eliminate Chang Suk of the Blue team.]
The stairs... he's by the stairs.
- Go Chang Suk... it's Chang Suk.
- Right?
[Heading off to attack his goal, Chang Suk!]
I think he's coming after me!
[Will Chang Suk be able to last until
his teammate Jae Suk arrives?]
- What if this doesn't make the cut?
- Chang Suk is already exhausted.
Please Suk Jin, please!
I have to oust two of them before
Kim Jong Kook steps into the arena!
Yoo Jae Suk, time to make your
entrance in one minute.
[His teammate Chang Suk is in danger!
Chang Suk has to stick through it somehow...]
[Ha Ha and Suk Jin surrounding Chang Suk.]
There's no time. Hurry!
[Ha Ha and Suk Jin corralling Chang Suk.]
Hurry up before someone else enters.
- If Jae Suk gets in...
- Not Jae Suk, we can't let that happen.
Not Jae Suk, we can't let that happen.
It's not that you can't let me come in...
[I need to get in and rescue Chang Suk!]
He should be eliminating Ha Ha...
I'm getting the feeling...
Number six, Yoo Jae Suk entering.
Hurry! Hurry!
Eliminate Chang Suk quickly!
Hurry up and oust Chang Suk!
[Yoo-ruce Willis rises!]
- If I eliminate you...
- It's Jae Suk! Hurry up and eliminate him!
- Jae Suk... Jae Suk's on his way. Hurry!
- I got it!
[It's that way!]
[Everyone's on their feet watching!]
Jae Suk's at a too big of a disadvantage.
How is he going to beat them?
- Hurry up before Jae Suk gets here!
- I got it!
[Wound up tight with nervousness
and not able to freely make a move.]
- Get in there and quickly...
- Suk Jin, you get in there.
- We have to quickly...
- Hurry, we're on the same team!
Who is that? It's Byung Ho...
[Oh... Ha Ha, you're not...]
[Ha Ha eliminate Ji Suk Jin
of the Green Team!]
Take a step back for now.
- I think Suk Jin's been eliminated!
- Suk Jin's been eliminated.
Wow... that Ha Ha... wow...
- You really are...
- I'm sorry!
[His sin is being on the same team
with Mr. Capable.]
Race start.
It's been a long time since
I've been able to say that.
[On the other hand, Yoo-ruce Willis
is heading off to save Chang Suk!]
- Where's Jae Suk?
- Why don't you sit down?
[Even though he's trying to calm down,
he keeps rising off his seat.]
Ha Ha's mine... Ha Ha's mine.
Chang Suk!
Jae Suk's on his way... he's coming.
Byung Ho...
Jae Suk's coming. Hurry.
- There's Tae Yeon on camera number seven!
- Chang Suk!
[Ha Ha fully attacking Chang Suk!]
Chang Suk!
[Ha Ha and Byung Ho concentrating
on attacking Chang Suk.]
Chang Suk!
Hurry! We have to eliminate him!
Jae Suk!
[Chang Suk eliminates Ha Ha and
Byung Ho eliminates Chang Suk!]
[Ha Ha and Chang Suk simultaneously
get eliminated!]
Who got eliminated?
[Due to the CCTV blind spot,
they were only able to hear the audio!]
Where are they? Where are they?
Come on Suk Jin...
you shouldn't have trusted Ha Ha!
Suk Jin...
you shouldn't have trusted Ha Ha.
- Did you see?
- We can hear everything in here.
This last spot is the first.
You're nothing but a target being out there.
- The ones who are in jail... please sit.
- I am in jail!
Hey, also... just eliminate whomever you see.
You can't trust Ha Ha.
Number seven,
Kim Jong Kook's entrance.
[Its opening... the gates to hell.]
It's starting... it's starting.
[Number seven, Kim Jong Kook's entrance.
Number seven, Kim Jong Kook's entrance.]
[There's no comparison to the
nervousness felt now.]
[Finally, Mr. Capable's entrance!]
[The Tiger's chase, an immense
competition with his entrance...]
Green!
- That's Jong Kook.
- Look at how much ease he has.
Wow with Jong Kook's entrance...
there's nowhere to go now.
[Jong Kook!]
It's Tae Yeon!
What's wrong?
Don't cry!
You have to stay hidden, you fool.
[Ten years shaved off her life.]
[But Mr. Capable isn't the only one
that she needs to be cautious of...]
I can't see Tae Yeon anywhere... Tae Yeon.
I know that she's got to be
around here somewhere.
I know she has to be...
Tae Yeon's not dead yet, right?
[Byung Ho has Tae Yeon in his target range!]
[Planning on ambushing her from afar.]
Number 16... number 16.
Wow! Byung Ho... he's creeping up on her.
She has to stay hidden.
Tae Yeon, Tae Yeon...
[She escaped here from Mr. Capable,
only to find Byung Ho closing in on her!]
Tae Yeon... Tae Yeon...
[With no one to help her,
escaping is her priority.]
Tae Yeon...
They've encountered each other.
Run, run, run!
I'm so scared.
Wow... what a waste. What a waste.
[Byung Ho just frightening her
without giving her the chase.]
Run, run, run!
Everyone that's in jail, please have a seat.
My legs feel cramped.
Aren't we the ones that started off the race?
Let us at least watch.
I'll keep my mouth closed.
[On the other hand, Yoo-ruce Willis
who wasn't able to save Chang Suk...]
[Number eight, Gary's entrance.
Number eight, Gary's entrance.]
Everything's so wide open here.
[Yoo-ruce Willis keeping his eye on Gary
and closing in on him.]
It's over! It's over for Gary
as soon as he makes his entrance!
You have to make a run for it!
Where is he? Where?
- Where is he?
- We can't see.
[Jail birds can't get a clear view
of the CCTV.]
Can't you turn it around a bit?
So that from jail...
Let us at least watch.
No, you can't.
Can't you turn it around a little?
[Gary not even dreaming of
Jae Suk's attack.]
[Will Gary be ousted within a minute
of him making an entrance?]
[There he goes!]
[Gary just had 10 years
shaved off of his life!]
[My partner Gary!]
You startled me!
[The ambush unfortunately gets foiled.]
We can't make any loud noises right now.
Then Jong Kook...
Later... watch your back.
He totally caught me off guard.
[Too bad...]
[But for some reason...
I'm getting a good feeling about today...]
[The more players entering the game,
the more competitive it gets...]
Ji Hyo, you can hear me, right?
I have made alliances and am keeping
an eye on things, so don't worry.
Okay?
Byung Ho is speaking to you, Ji Hyo.
- I'm keeping an eye on things...
- He's speaking to you.
- I mean to you, Ji Hyo.
- What did you say?
[Who's that?]
[Tae Yeon gathering her courage
to surprise attack Byung Ho!]
[But gets caught instead?]
[Byung Ho with his hands on
Tae Yeon's name tag!]
[Tae Yeon - Out!]
[Not even hesitating heartless killer!]
What the heck is this?
I heard someone's name tag
being ripped off.
Who was that?
Was it Tae Yeon?
Byung Ho eliminated her.
- Byung Ho got her.
- Tae Yeon's ousted?
- Why would he... isn't that too much?
- Byung Ho got her.
What the heck is this?
Tae Yeon's out?
Fighting! You have to show them
what you have!
Eun Ji's dad, fighting!
This is for Eun Ji!
You have to stay hidden!
[You have to stay alive for a long time
for your daughters watching at home...]
[Number nine, Shin Jung Geun's entrance.
Number nine, Shin Jung Geun's entrance.]
[All the father's weak to their daughters
slowly making their entrance one by one.]
I was totally caught off guard.
I thought that she was going to
get my name tag.
It was fortunate that she was a girl.
Tae Yeon, I'm really sorry.
I let you live,
but why did you attack me?
[A video message to Tae Yeon this time.]
Tae Yeon, I'm sorry.
But I have to protect Ji Hyo.
No matter what, I have to remain alive
until Ji Hyo gets here.
I'm going to make sure to survive today.
I have to protect Ji Hyo.
I have to stay alive no matter what.
[Eun Ji's dad is climbing up the machine
in order to survive for a long time.]
Jung Geun!
[Of all places, why does Mr. Capable...]
[Orange team's Tae Yeon walking into jail.]
Kwang Soo!
- Tae Yeon...
You fool!
I told you to be careful and
just stay hidden!
I seriously was staying hidden...
- Who eliminated you?
- Mr. Son Byung Ho...
- Really?
- I guess he had no qualms.
Then you can get out there
and eliminate Byung Ho.
I'll eliminate him for you.
If nothing else, I'll go and avenge you.
[The Giraffe finally makes his entrance
after guaranteeing Tae Yeon's revenge.]
[Number ten, Lee Kwang Soo's entrance.
Number ten, Lee Kwang Soo's entrance.]
[It's Giraffe, the traitor!]
[Both of them going after their enemy,
traitor Giraffe first.]
Jong Kook, don't get me.
I just got here.
I just got here!
[At this rate, forget Tae Yeon's revenge...]
Jong Kook...
let me face off with Jae Suk once.
- What?
- Just once...
Jong Kook...
He's already caught?
- There's no need for him to try then.
- Jong Kook caught him?
[Giraffe's lifespan... there's not much left.]
- They're following him.
- Kwang Soo is over then.
- Jong Kook and...
- Tae Yeon's been ousted...
- Tae Yeon's been ousted.
- Tae Yeon's been ousted?
Yes, Son Byung Ho got her.
I told her that I'd avenge her.
Jong Kook, you know you can
eliminate me at any time.
Just let me avenge Tae Yeon first.
Really?
What kind of revenge?
[Worth using until he can eliminate
Byung Ho?]
- You promised, okay?
- Yes, Jong Kook. Just until I get him.
- Go eliminate him then.
- I'll be on my way then.
[Whew... I survived... for now.]
[Starting the hunt after leaving
Byung Ho to Kwang Soo.]
Stand still, stand still!
Stand still! Move back, move back.
[He's not Mr. Capable for nothing..]
- Jong Kook!
- Gary!
- That's not what I meant!
- Jong Kook... that's not what I meant.
- Gary!
[Giraffe Kwang Soo runs over
after hearing all the noise.]
Kwang Soo, rip his name off!
Kwang Soo, you have to think
carefully about this!
[Yoo-ruce Willis undoubtedly
heads over this way too!]
[The goal is...
Gary with the highest risk factor!]
[Even before White Team's
Jong Won has entered.]
[Gary - Out!]
[Running Man members stopping Gary
and Jong Won from uniting.]
Gary's been eliminated.
- Gary's been eliminated?
- Yes.
[If he had lasted 10 more minutes,
they could've met up.]
If you and Gary had been together...
- Hey, Byung Ho...
- Let's go get Byung Ho.
[Next target is Byung Ho before
Ji Hyo makes her entrance.]
- Hurry up and find Byung Ho.
- Yes, I will.
[Until Ji Hyo gets here...]
[Where is he? Byung Ho...]
- Good luck, Ji Hyo.
- Ji Hyo, fighting!
- Fighting!
- Wow, there's a team with both members now?
[Purple team is the only team with both
Byung Ho and Ji Hyo still alive.]
[Number 11, Song Ji Hyo's entrance.
Number 11, Song Ji Hyo's entrance.]
[Ace Ji Hyo needs to quickly
meet with her teammate, Byung Ho...]
Number 11, Song Ji Hyo's entrance.
I want to eliminate Jong Kook,
but I can't think of a way.
[His plot to betray making its' appearance.]
I should've just ripped it off then,
but I got caught.
[The tiger can hear everything you say...]
[Tiger having heard the traitorous Giraffe
talking to himself...]
[Awfully unlucky traitorous Giraffe.]
[You scoundrel... you won't be forgiven!]
- Kwang Soo, I shouldn't have let you live.
- No, no!
Kim Jong Kook, let's fight!
Please eliminate Kim Jong Kook!
[All this time, I've let him live and live...]
[I let you live, and you betray me.
I let you go, and you betray me.]
[I make an alliance with you,
and you betray me.]
[I be nice to you, and you betray me...]
[Because of you, all the kids thinks that
Giraffes are traitorous animals lately.]
[That's why today...
it's your turn to be had!]
[Tiger succeeds in hunting down
the Giraffe!]
[Kwang Soo - Out!]
[The result of betraying is
an even bigger betrayal - Running Man]
- Is Kwang Soo ousted?
- Huh?
Is Kwang Soo ousted?
Did you eliminate him?
Since Jung Geun is still alive too,
let's start after we oust one more person.
[Huh? Why are these two being
cordial all of a sudden?]
I'm just heading this way.
[Just passing by?]
- Wait... that was a little strange.
- I'm just heading this way.
Don't misunderstand.
I'm just heading this way.
That was really strange.
Wasn't that really weird?
Hey! Don't misunderstand what
I was doing.
[His ambush has been thwarted for now.]
I have to oust Kim Jong Kook...
[Pretending to be in alliance...
but both eyeing for a chance.]
[Catching each other in the act.]
- I thought you were heading that way?
- Why did you turn around?
[Both arguing that they were
each heading in that direction.]
What? Jae Suk...
I'm just jogging.
[At some time, they're going to have to
start hunting one another down...]
[The two circling around each other...
just who will get the last laugh?]
Just somebody win.
That's right, I still have Jung Geun!
Shin Jung Geun!
- I'll be back.
- Fighting!
- Gary, I'll be back.
- Yes, Jong Won. Fighting!
[At last, the entrance of the final player.
White Team's Lee Jong Won's entrance!]
[Will he be the one to start the final battle
that everyone is circling around?]
[Traitorous Giraffe lonely walking.]
[Returning right away without
having done anything.]
Pil! Chok... Soo!
What happened?
You're much better at returning
than when you were heading out.
Why did you come back so quickly?
- Who eliminated you?
- Kim Jong Kook!
- That was the first time being stabbed...
- Kim Jong Kook, fighting!
You did good, Kim Jong Kook!
You came back way too quickly...
[Orange team, Tae Yeon and Kwang Soo
first to be out of the game.]
Chang Suk feels better now after
being given Tae Yeon's name tag.
- Does anyone have a pen?
- Tae Yeon is better than gold.
I'm going to get her to autograph it too!
- My daughter's name is Yae Won.
- Yae Won?
[Chang Suk is also whipped by his daughter
asking Tae Yeon for her autograph.]
Are you that happy even though
you're dead?
- Why are you so happy?
- Tae Yeon over the gold.
Everyone... come join us in jail!
Byung Ho!
Byung Ho, where are you?
Staying alive for me like this...
Ji Hyo!
[Finally!]
[Purple team's Byung Ho and Ji Hyo unite!]
- You remained alive!
- I did remain alive.
- When Tae Yeon attacked me earlier...
- That was seriously no joke!
- I did good, right?
- You seriously did great!
- We're the only ones left alive right now.
- Our team's the only one remaining, right?
- We are the only ones right now...
- I think I saw Jung Geun.
[Will they be able to take the win?]
Come this way.
- Lee Jong Won is heading this way.
- I know.
[Even though he's alone,
capable Jong Won is heading this way...]
[And now even though strength is strength,
a strategic fight is more important!]
I bet Jong Kook is over there.
- Hello. I came to say hi.
- Oh, really?
Have a nice jog.
[Checking out each other's resolve for now.]
I have to get them.
[Jung Geun planning on ridding
the Purple team's two members.]
We have to eliminate one of them, Jong Won.
- We should eliminate one of them.
- Should we form an alliance?
Just one of them...
Just because you guys are alone...
I'm going to get you instead though.
Hey, hey...
Why are you coming in my direction?
[The moment any one of them leaves their
guard down, they're headed to jail!]
- One of the guests has to remain alive.
- I know.
- Right now, I...
- Let's send Ji Hyo away.
[Alliance formed. Start the attack!]
I'm sorry.
She's quick!
Come on, don't...
[Purple team's Byung Ho in danger!]
You almost had him!
Be careful, Ji Hyo.
This seriously isn't the time
to be attacking us!
Let's all survive for a while...
as guests...
[Another alliance...
for all the dad's to remain alive.]
- Let's all promise each other.
- This is for real.
[Including Ji Hyo...
All the guest daddy's to unite and align.]
Let's end them away one by one.
[Until Yoo-ruce Willis and Mr. Capable are
eliminated, not to touch one another.]
[This is big trouble...
how do I beat all four?]
- Jae Suk... Jae Suk.
- What?
[The middle-aged man passing by again.]
What's wrong with you?
You're so sensitive today.
[Arguing again... even in the midst of danger,
here they are at it again.]
- Hurry up and leave.
- I'm seeing where I can go.
- Are going to be like this?
- Come on...
[They need to join their forces if they're
to go up against the four dads.]
[Okay... in that case!]
[Dad alliance discovers
Mr. Capable's location!]
[Agreeing that Mr. Capable
should be their first target.]
Jong Kook, come here. Let's do this.
[Yoo-ruce Willis joining in
from the opposite side.]
Jae Suk's here too.
We can do it all in one.
[Blue team's Jae Suk and
Green team's Jong Kook vs. Dad alliance.]
There they are. It's starting.
[This is the moment of battle...]
[No matter who gets ousted,
a big change is about to come...]
- They're all there. They're going at it.
- This is really entertaining.
[Mr. Capable attacks Jong Won first!]
[Yoo-ruce Willis and Mr. Capable on
the same team for once in a long time!]
[Jong Won starts his counterattack!]
[Jong Won vs. Jae Suk. A nice match!]
[If Yoo-ruce Willis gets pushed back,
it's the end for him!]
[Jong Kook!]
[Go away, Jung Geun!]
[Mr. Capable on his way!]
[Jong Kook... come here!]
[Yoo-ruce Willis and Mr. Capable's
awesome sync!]
[Easily sidestepping Jung Geun's attack!]
[The two powerhouses of Running Man...
who knew they had such good teamwork?]
[This is Running Man style!]
[Jong Kook - Out!]
Jong Kook... I'm so sorry.
[At a loss for words...]
[Betrayed him... he betrayed Jong Kook!]
[This is the Running Man betrayal
they've all only heard about.]
I had a feeling!
The card that I was going to play myself...
It's Jong Kook! Jong Kook!
- Good! I'm glad!
- Jong Kook?
What a sight...
you need a taste of your own medicine!
[A full out celebration with the exception
of his teammate, Suk Jin.]
I was wondering how long
you were going to survive...
then you die right away!
You deserve it. You deserve it!
- It's sweeter than candy!
- Let's have a party tonight!
Kim Jong Kook... come join us in jail!
Let's all prepare a welcome dance.
[Holding an immediate dance party.]
One, two, three, four!
Two people! Two people!
[Oh my goodness...]
[Falling over...]
[Ball of nerves after hugging Tae Yeon.]
- It was just a game! Why so nervous?
- Ha Ha! You said two people!
- What about it?
- I'm going to step out for a moment.
Ugh... that made me so nervous.
[Yoo-ruce Willis vs. Daddy alliance.]
What do I do about this?
It's four against one.
[After all the physical exertion,
at the point of exhaustion]
[On top of that, the heavy pressure of
a battle against tightly knit daddy alliance.]
No matter how,
I'm going to have to win this.
[The legend of Yoo-ruce Willis
that started two years ago on Chu-Suk.]
[His legendary skills that always
win against extreme conditions.]
[His amazing skills that have become
an icon in Running Man!]
[Today...
Yoo-ruce Willis has been awakened again!]
Oh my God.
[The four members of Daddy alliance
that are searching through the area.]
[Ambush]
[He's not Yoo-ruce Willis
to be had so easily!]
Jae Suk's really fast...
I could've stopped him!
Where should we hide?
[It's blocked...]
So here's my thought.
Once Jae Suk's been eliminated,
only one of us has to remain alive.
Then we'll win. So either you
or I just need to stay alive.
We need to eliminate Jae Suk
first though.
Is there a way to go or not?
There isn't?
I think he went down
from the opposite direction!
- He's not up there?
- He went down?
No, he came down.
Seriously... I seriously feel like death.
After eliminating Kim Jong Kook...
such a huge obstacle...
I had no idea there would be
such a huge obstacle like this.
[What to do... What do I do?]
- Jong Kook's here.
- Let's start the partying.
[The party is still going on in jail.]
Hey, he's my teammate.
[Only Suk Jin is not joining in
on the party.]
[Three times!]
[The party's guest of honor
makes his appearance.]
- Do you know what they're doing right now?
- What?
- Jong Kook... you know what they're doing?
- A little louder!
Are they celebrating my elimination?
- They are, aren't they?
- Yeah, they are.
This is your elimination party,
and he started it.
[Anyways, victory is a burst bubble
for the Green team as well.]
[Yoo-ruce Willis penetrating deep
into the battlefield once again.]
[Discovers Ji Hyo!]
Jae Suk's over here!
- Why of all places...
- Grab Jae Suk real quick!
I think they got him!
At least two of them have to be
ousted right now.
Nice... nice!
[Jae Suk!]
- He's right up front!
- Be careful!
[No matter where he goes,
enemies are all over the place!]
[Yoo-ruce Willis surrounded!]
[Just then! Jung Geun goes for
Byung Ho's name tag!]
[Daddy alliance's collapse?
Using the opportunity!]
[Shin Jung Geun - Out!]
[In an attempt at a revolt,
being ousted instead.]
What? What happened?
- He's caught... he got caught.
- He's caught.
He's eliminated.
Who? Who?
Jung Geun's been eliminated.
Jung Geun's the one eliminated.
[Yoo-ruce Willis vs.
Byung Ho, Jong Won and Ji Hyo.]
You're level of betrayal is too much.
I couldn't believe it.
- I have no choice if I want to survive.
- Okay, I got it.
[Jong Won heading up to get
Yoo-ruce Willis.]
- Why are you coming up here?
- Let's fight.
[Yoo-ruce Willis in extreme danger!]
[Just then! Jong Won going after Byung Ho!]
[Just then! Ji Hyo!]
[Song Ji Hyo - Out!]
[Daddy alliance is formally over!]
[Now the real battle... just who
will be the last one left standing?]
Jung Geun!
[Point of exhaustion.]
- You did great...
- What a loss...
- I didn't even get to betray anyone.
- Did you take a shower?
Who were you trying to eliminate
when you got eliminated?
I think Byung Ho got me.
[So chaotic that he doesn't even know
who he was ousted by.]
- Byung Ho's on a rampage today.
- Jae Suk, Ji Hyo, Jong Won...
- Byung Ho.
- And Byung Ho. Four left.
- There she is!
- Ji Hyo's out.
Jung Geun...
don't you think you were too much?
- How could you have done that?
- Why?
I didn't eliminate you.
How could you have betrayed us like that
when we were in an alliance?
- I can't believe...
- You did it! You betrayed her!
- You betrayed her, right?
- It wasn't a betrayal...
[Being congratulated by
the experts in betrayal.]
Jung Geun,
congratulations on your first betrayal!
- First betrayal...
- I didn't betray...
[The excitement of first betrayal.]
If you come on Running Man,
you learn how to betray.
- What's that sound?
- What's going on?
- They're going at it! They're at it!
- Are they going at it?
Look! they're going at it!
[The three parties going around in a frenzy!]
[The last man standing out of the three
will be the ultimate winner today!]
[Simultaneously?]
[Yoo-ruce Willis rips off
Jong Won's name tag first!]
Jae Suk ripped his off first.
Jae Suk did it first, Jae Suk.
Jae Suk ripped it off first.
So Jong Won is out?
Wow... this program is entertaining!
This is unbelievable!
It keeps switching over.
This is the new weekend program.
The CCTV program.
[The new weekend variety, CCTV!]
[The motivation of the guests driven
by the need as a father...]
- That's why at home...
- There he is!
[White team's annihilation.]
There they go.
They're going up against each other.
[The face-off... has come this far.]
[The two that were on the same
team as of last week.]
[Yoo-ruce Willis vs. Son Byung Ho]
[No matter who wins,
they've both given their best.]
- I bet she'll be very happy.
- You understand, right?
It's all thanks to you. Thanks.
[But the final glory...]
[Can only belong to one person!]
[An unforgiving battle between men.]
This is scary.
Fighting!
[Nerve-wrecking jail viewing room.]
No, they just tugged at it.
I'm so sweaty and slippery...
[Fine...]
[My final attack!]
[The screen and audio that went blank
at the sound of ripping.]
If Jae Suk's to win, I even have this too...
[Getting Tae Yeon's signature and a win?]
There's no need to work so hard at it.
[Without knowing if he's won,
eating his cake first!]
Everyone, be good to your
daughters at home...
[But just what happened at the end?]
- How did it end?
- What happened?
- Who won?
[Just who is the ultimate winner?]
Die Hard... It was Yoo-ruce Willis II.
[It was Yoo-ruce Willis II?]
[In that case...]
[Jae Suk going in for his final attack
after making a firm determination.]
[Byung Ho had Jae Suk's name tag
in his grip too.]
[By a split second difference,
Jae Suk was first!]
[The final winner,
Yoo-ruce Willis' Blue team!]
[Chang Suk and Jae Suk's Blue team
is the ultimate winner!]
Please give a round of applause for
Yoo-ruce Willis!
[Congratulations to the return
of beloved Yoo-ruce Willis!]
[Wins 12 golden eggs as a prize.]
Subtitles by DramaFever
Flip over this Ddak-ji.
I can't flip this over!
[Running Man's King of Ddak-ji, Jae Suk!]
[The birth of new challenger, Jong Kook!]
[That unrequited face-off
is being unfolded in this episode!]
I will pass down my inheritance to the team
that can flip over this Ddak-ji.
This family is strong!
- When it comes to Ddak-ji, it's me.
- What a joke!
[Just who will become the legendary
King of Ddak-ji turn this over?]
[Next week on Running Man,
Absolute Ddak-ji!]