[The cost for looking into the future...]
Just what is it that you've seen?
[Must be paid.]
[Running Man... face your future.]
[If your future changes...]
[We can't guarantee your present.]
- Why is he here?
- The one who sees into the future!
[The one who sees into the future...
tumbling into chaos.]
[The one who sees into the future]
[Falling deeper into fall.]
[Iksan Station]
[Giraffe is the first to arrive.]
Is no one here yet?
Here comes someone.
Good morning, Sir!
[Jae Suk's arrival]
Hello.
Are we going to get on the train?
Then do you think we're going to
get on the bus at a train station?
It's really quiet this morning.
What happened to the other members?
They're on their way here right now.
And there's a train coming in right now
with your guests for the day.
That train is going to arrive at 11:24.
Exactly in eight minutes.
In eight minutes?
[In eight minutes... they will arrive.]
[The strong masculine scent?]
- There's a great race happening today.
- What?
- Really?
- No way...
- What?
The last time we had guests come in on
the train, Min Soo came out of it.
[Memories of the Hunter coming back
whenever a train race is mentioned.]
When it comes to trains,
you're the first to go, then me.
Gary... where's Gary?
I feel nervous when I don't see Gary.
I seriously feel nervous
when I don't see Gary.
- Don't worry about it.
- Gary's coming, right?
- He's the trouble maker lately.
- Gary!
- You scared me!
- I was scared that you weren't coming!
- Why do you have to scare us like this?
- You have no idea how worried I was!
- I was... I was just getting ready.
- That's never going to happen again.
- Don't scare us like that again!
Gary, don't ever leave our sight.
How many guests are there going
to be today?
[Time for the train to arrive at any moment.]
They're going to be getting off
by that post.
It's coming, it's coming!
This is an unusual meeting.
[An unusual platform meeting.]
- It's coming!
- It's coming in!
[Full of anticipation]
I'm nervous, I'm nervous.
- I'm seriously really nervous.
- There is a sense of romanticism.
This is...
[Where will they be getting off?]
This way, this way, this way...
- Over this way.
- I think it's going to be this way.
[What? These people?]
Ji Sung!
[Ji Sung]
[Song Chang Ui]
[Ji Jin Hee]
[Drama 'The Great Seers'
three males actors.]
What the heck?
[Greeting their friends in joy.]
[Testing out the name tags as
soon as they arrive.]
[Welcome!]
Remember when he was on the show last?
Flying his duck feathers everywhere?
[Memories of Ji Jin Hee leaving
with duck feathers flying in the air.]
[In a previous chase with
the scent of masculinity flying in the air.]
[With the scene of his flying duck feathers.]
With the duck feathers flying...
it's been a long time seeing Ji Sung too.
Ji Sung was on the show before
and worked really hard too.
- That's right...
- I think it's been a year.
And I don't think I've seen him
since Family Outing.
What took you so long to get
on the show?
I know... are these three going to be
on the show today?
I will tell you about today's mission.
[Today's race is...
The one who sees the future.]
Even though all of you are
just normal people right now...
Once you get on the seven train
from this platform in a little bit
you will receive the power
to look into the future.
He says we can gain that ability.
Okay, we'll just go along with it.
[Those who can see into the future...]
[Look into the future by using
the Future Ddak-Ji.]
[The fantasy chase for those
that can travel through time.]
I saw the future!
What the heck is the 'Future Ddak-Ji'?
We're going to see the future?
Every time the trains stops at a station,
you'll all get off the train.
The person eliminated will be left behind
and the rest of you will board the train.
Kwang Soo and I are always the first ones
to get eliminated in this race.
But this has nothing to do with luck,
it's all based on your skills.
So those that remain alive to the end...
[Just on time, the speaker starts
playing befitting 'Hometown Station'.]
[A song of the romantic past.]
- This song really is a work of art.
- It is a work of art.
[The song and the timing
are both works of art.]
So the person who's left remaining to
the final terminal gets the future Ddak-Ji.
- Ddak-Ji?
- The future Ddak-Ji.
Are you talking about this kind of Ddak-Ji?
Ah, the Ddak-Ji that you hit?
[The new King of Ddak-Ji
brightening up at the idea.]
You need to have that future Ddak-Ji
for you to be able to see into the future.
[Only the person who uses the future
Ddak-Ji can see into the future.]
[The person who remains alive to the end with
the future Ddak-Ji is the ultimate winner.]
[Guests' strong sense of competitiveness
they've already experienced in the past.]
His competitive streak is no joke!
A lot of it has dissipated.
- Are you serious?
- Yes, most of it is gone.
- You don't seem to be in good condition.
- You look like you just woke up.
[The truth is, he's still a bit groggy.]
Those of you that gets
eliminated along the way...
can board the elimination train
and come to the final location.
- The elimination train?
- We can get eliminated early?
There are a total of six stops
along the way.
Where is the first station
that someone can be eliminated?
It's in Samrae Station
Kwang Soo, you can tell your Manager to
go wait for you at Samrae Station.
How can you say that?
[Is Jae Suk looking into the future already?]
The train is going to arrive
precisely at 12:07.
To be honest... I don't
think Chang Ui is very competitive.
No, he's not very good.
Why do you think that?
- I came on the show with a firm resolve.
- Chang Ui and I...
Let's you and I work hard together.
Why don't you go stand next to
Kwang Soo?
- Kwang Soo... come shake his hand.
- It's nice to meet you.
[Getting the sense he will be getting
chummy with the Easy Brothers...]
Chang Ui is the type where he has the desire,
but he's always one step too late.
Kwang Soo, I think
you've got yourself a match today.
It really is lonely if you're
the first one to get eliminated.
It's really lonely...
Kwang Soo,
why don't you tell him more about it?
You're better than I to tell him about
what that's like.
I think you're going to be
eliminated early too.
[Chang Ui likely to be eliminated
early on in the game too?]
[The train finally arrives]
[Only the survivors of the race
will safely arrive in Sooncheon.]
[Boarding the train with nervous anticipation.]
Wow... it really has been a long time
since we've boarded this train.
Are we not going to eat any
snacks onboard?
- Hard boiled eggs and cider.
- We have to eat something.
[Without knowing what
the future has in store for them...]
[Just smiling and giggling away.]
[Following the beautiful scenery
towards Sooncheon]
Everyone's introduced themselves, right?
- Yes.
- Why do you keep enforcing that?
- Asking why we've introduced ourselves...
- Since you may not be seeing them again soon.
[Since they may be saying farewell
to one another within moments.]
Jin Hee and Chang Ui both are really
nervous about being eliminated right away.
We have to get to know each other first.
[The first destination to decide who
will be eliminated first is Samrae Station.]
- Kwang Soo...
- It's really not going to be me.
You've got four minutes remaining now.
While we're making our way to Samrae Station,
we're going to decide the order of the game.
The first game we'll be playing...
is to steal the walnut cookie,
the King of all snacks on train rides.
[Steal the walnut cookie!]
You each will pick one,
which will have a number on it.
And as soon as you pick one,
you have to eat the cookie.
Everyone, take one.
We will start with Ji Sung.
You've never been in this situation before...
but first to be out can be very lonely.
Please show everyone.
One, two, three!
- Number six... number six?
- No, it's number nine.
[And our exhausted Jin Hee?]
I think he's going to get a good number.
Can I eat this?
- You can eat it later.
- One, two, three!
[Jin Hee picks number seven.]
Seven... the lucky number seven.
[Chang Ui who came on the show today
with a firm resolve.]
[Number two...]
Chang Ui, I knew it...
One, two, three! Number four!
[Kwang Soo, number four.]
[A little ominous?]
One, two, three! Number three!
[Jong Kook, number three.]
[Safe number? Ji Hyo, eight.]
[Number one hasn't made an
appearance yet.]
[Suk Jin, number five.]
- One, two, three!
- Number six!
[Ha Ha, number six. Which means...]
Number one is still left!
[The only ones left are number one
and ten.]
- One, two, three!
- Number one!
[Gary, number one.]
It's number one?
Why did I get number one?
[Ah... I'm number one.]
-How did Gary pick number one?
- How did Gary number one?
- Gary...
- Read it out loud.
[If you flip the coin on top of the book by
hitting it with your hand, you pass!]
[If you don't flip it,
you're immediately eliminated.]
[Hitting the book means...]
[A game where you have to hit
the book to flip the coin over.]
If number one is eliminated,
then the rest of us get to go on?
[By going in order, as soon as someone is
eliminated, the rest gets to go on.]
Numbers one through four are in danger.
[Jin Hee who's commented he's not feeling
competitive today is reacting strongly.]
[I'm number seven. So happy...]
Number ten... number ten...
Days like this can happen to me too.
We're going to go out and
get some fresh air.
If you hit it too hard,
it can flip over twice.
We don't have much time left...
so if he's eliminated, get back on the train.
Don't follow the rest of us
back into the train and just go.
Let's all be cool and
say our goodbyes then.
[The first destination, Samrae Station.]
[Number one, Gary, full of nervousness.]
No, it's okay Gary. It won't happen.
If he's eliminated, he's left behind alone?
- Yes, he's left alone.
- Then you'll just have to flip it over.
It's so lonely to be left behind alone.
He'd need some knitting or
cross-stitching stuff.
He'll have a lot of time on his hands.
[The mission table coming into view.]
[Exactly one minute during the stop.]
Quickly!
[Starting with number one, Gary.]
Here I go!
[Just one chance! Will the coin flip over?]
[Nervous number two, Chang Ui]
[It flipped over!]
[Number one, Gary, succeeds!]
[The chance goes over to
number two, Chang Ui!]
One, two, three!
[Fail...]
[Flipping over twice
and landing on the same side.]
[The guest car full of cheer.]
- Gary... you did great.
- I did it... I did it!
[Unpredictable Gary who shows
how capable he can be at times.]
Didn't I tell you? Chang Ui...
[It's been so long since
he's been on the show...]
This is unbelievable... unbelievable.
Let's just say our farewells to him now.
- Just wave bye.
- Say bye to him.
See? These kind of premonitions that
I have are never wrong...
[Chang Ui's elimination they
were all nervous about...]
[Could Jong Kook's premonition
have been right on target?]
[Wait... but Big nosed Brother said that
the coin could flip over twice...]
[The future he predicted for himself?]
[Darn...]
Have a nice trip.
[And so, Chang Ui's eliminated.]
Why did it have to flip over twice?
I had a bad feeling about it from the start.
[Bad premonition from the beginning.]
Things keep going the way the guys are
saying. It's almost like magic.
[Does being on the train really allow them to
gain the ability to see into the future?]
[Unbelievable number one, Gary]
The two of you are really cold-hearted.
[The two members of 'The Great Seer' who
appeared happiest with Chang Ui's elimination.]
- But they all came on the show together...
- Are you seriously sleepy?
I'm sleepy... I'm seriously sleepy.
There used to be a head here,
and now it's gone.
Chang Ui used to be in this seat.
I think Chang Ui has all the looks when
it comes to someone being eliminated.
If you look at his face,
he has very sad looking eyes.
- His eyes are very sad.
- As if he was up crying all night.
[Move over deer...
I'm the new doe-eyed kid in town...]
I wonder what Chang Ui's doing?
[Sad eyed Chang Ui is...]
I seriously had no idea that I would
be the first one to be eliminated.
Because I wanted to win so badly,
I think just the opposite has happened.
I hope they enjoy themselves...
And I hope the other two survive.
[Such a sad way of saying things...]
- Chang Ui...
- Did you see how he did it?
The number has a lot to do with it...
Jeonjoo Station is the next stop to
determine who'll be eliminated next.
- You have two minutes at the stop.
- The person to be left is... this person?
Why are you saying that it's me?
- This person!
- The person who sees into the future!
As we did the last time, we'll
determine the order with a walnut cookie.
[More nervous energy than the
last time.]
[Starting with Gary this time around.]
One, two, three!
[Whew... Gary picks number five.]
[Wow! Number nine!]
[Overtly happy about his pick?]
- One, two, three!
- Number one!
Number three...
[Kwang Soo, number three]
- Number three can be nerve wrecking.
- No one's picked number one yet.
Number one hasn't been picked yet.
Please... number one...
[There it is! Number one.]
[Big nosed brother, number one.]
Jeonjoo station... this person!
Ji Hyo?
One, two, three!
Number four!
[Ji Hyo, number four]
One, two, three!
[Ha Ha, number six]
- Number seven!
- Number eight!
[That means...
Jae Suk has number two!]
- I can't believe I got number one.
- This is making me nervous...
[Pick a ball and depending on what it says,
Board or Elimination]
- This is good!
- I'm good! This is okay then.
- First ones to go is better.
- Going first is actually better.
This will be over by the fourth person.
By the fourth one, it'll be over.
If Suk Jin picks the elimination ball,
then the rest of us are safe?
[Whomever picks the elimination ball first
is eliminated and the rest are safe.]
[Second stop - Jeonjoo Station]
I know we're getting ready to get off...
but the three people standing up here are
the three who always lose at this.
It's going to be over right now.
[Full of nervous energy.]
[Two minutes at the stop.]
[Draw either a PASS, or ELIMINATED ball]
Please... please!
[Desperately wishing for the
elimination ball.]
One, two, three!
[Eliminated...]
[Chosen - Eliminated]
[Survivors disappearing
like a bolt of thunder.]
Awesome... that was awesome.
This is so unbelievable...
[Guest car overflowing with cheer.]
Perfect... that was perfect.
[Number two, Jae Suk,
gains 10 years to his life.]
He got eliminated before me.
Wow... how could this...
But... remember how I pointed to him
and said, 'This person' earlier?
Jae Suk,
be careful with that hand of yours.
Don't be rash and point that at anyone.
What are you writing?
Wow, Jin Hee is really hateful...
[Being hateful and writing 'Bye']
You really are hateful... seriously...
Bye?
He wrote, 'bye'.
That's what he wrote.
But isn't he really exciting when someone
gets eliminated early on?
Without even knowing...
When I think about it from Suk Jin's shoes,
I shouldn't be getting this excited...
But I can't help but be happy about it.
He's already forgotten us and isn't
even saying bye to us as we're leaving.
He's in his own little world.
[The second person to be eliminated,
Ji Suk Jin.]
Seriously...
how does this make any sense?
This is seriously making me nervous now.
[Eight people remaining out of
the original ten.]
[Giraffe still remains alive.]
Everyone that's likely to be eliminated
is being eliminated right now.
That means that it's going along
as predicted.
[Time to pick the order for the
next round.]
- Let's all do this!
- Jae Suk.
One, two, three!
[Jae Suk, picks number two again!]
[Oh... Giraffe, number six.]
I'm set!
One, two, three!
[Ji Hyo, number five.]
- Ji Hyo picks really good numbers.
- One, two, three!
[Gary, number eight.]
Why isn't number one coming out yet?
One, two, three!
[Ha Ha, number seven.]
I thought I was going to get
number one.
Is he going to get number one?
[Jin Hee, number three.]
Number four!
[Ji Sung, number four. That means...]
Jong Kook!
[Kkuk, number one.]
[A celebration]
It's okay, it's okay.
You won't be eliminated.
Here's your next mission.
[The next mission is...]
[Play 'Cham, cham, cham' with an expert.
Win, you pass. Lose, you're eliminated.]
[Play a match of 'Cham, cham, cham' with
Dong Wan PD lying in wait at the next stop.]
[If you lose, immediate elimination.]
I'm not good at that game...
One, two, three. Cham, cham, cham!
[Showing us the skills that he may be
eliminated right away.]
Cham, cham, cham!
[Jae Suk's no different.]
[Number one and two full of
nervous energy.]
[Putting number six at ease.]
If Jong Kook passes,
it's all up in the air.
If Jae Suk passes, then the rest...
Who's number three?
- It's Jin Hee, Jin Hee...
- No way...
I would actually be really nice if
Jin Hee's eliminated during this round.
- Number two... no way...
- Jin Hee, you should be eliminated.
We're here! We're here!
[Numbers one and two with their
nervous expressions.]
I'll be back.
As a guarantee that I'll be returning,
I'll leave my jacket here.
[Leaving his jacket behind as a
guarantee that he'll return to the train?]
I'll leave my jacket behind.
The jacket won't come off.
[Ultimately heading towards the exit
with the jacket still on.]
Please... just this once.
Please... please,
let Jong Kook be the one.
[Everyone desperately wishing that
Jong Kook be the one to be eliminated.]
[The third stop, Imsil Station]
- I can't be eliminated here.
- I have to get the Ddak-Ji... I have to!
- I have to get back on the train.
- Let's go, we've got one minute!
[Time at the stop, one minute]
To the left... it's to the left.
[Cham, cham, cham-
In order starting with Jong Kook]
Cham, cham, cham!
[Jong Kook succeeds!]
[Jae Suk also succeeds?]
Cham, cham, cham!
[Ji Jin Hee fails...]
Goodbye, Jin Hee!
How could this have happened?
[Numbers one and two
recovering within moments.]
I had no idea that it would come
down to me.
All the guests are getting the shaft today.
[I can't believe I'm eliminated...]
Cham, cham, cham...
This way, that way... it should've been that.
How can you go this way twice?
[The truth that he still can't accept...]
Bye...
Sad... this is really sad.
- He looks so sad all of a sudden.
- Yeah, he looks so down all of a sudden.
His mood goes up and down a lot.
Look at him. He looks really pissed off.
[Seriously pissed off?]
[I'm leaving...]
- This is surprising.
- Thank goodness I'm not a guest.
[You just wait...]
It would be so nice if Jin Hee's eliminated.
[Jin Hee's eliminated just as
Ha Ha had predicted?]
[Was this written into his future?]
[Still upset]
It should've gone the opposite way,
but he went back to the same side.
If you think about it...
number two was eliminated
at the first mission.
[During the first stop,
number two, Chang Ui was eliminated.]
And during the second mission,
number one was eliminated.
[Second stop,
number one, Suk Jin was eliminated.]
And since number three was eliminated
during the third mission...
[Third stop, number three,
Jin Hee's eliminated.]
So during the fourth mission,
I wonder if number four will be eliminated?
[For the fourth mission,
number four will be eliminated?]
[Could... could it?]
Ji Sung is the only one left out of
the guests that are here today.
[Ji Sung, the sole survivor out of
'The Great Seer' team.]
[Choosing the order for the next mission.]
One, two, three!
[Jong Kook, number six.]
- One, two, three!
- Number two!
[Number two again?]
Number two for the third time in a row!
Seriously...
One, two, three!
[Ji Sung, number four!]
[Hm... number four that Jin Hee
predicted...]
[Ji Sung is chosen.]
- It's a relief that you're not number one.
- One, two, three!
[Ji Hyo, number five!]
One, two, three!
Number one! What the heck is this?
Why am I number one? Why? Why!
[Kwang Soo, number three]
I thought I was going to get number one.
Why are you putting me through
this ordeal?
[If you get the right answer to the
multiplication question, you pass.]
[If you don't, you fail.]
I'm really bad at this!
This is something that we can all pass!
- 7 times 7?
- 49.
- 7 times 8?
- 56.
- 6 times 7?
- 42!
He's good.
[This game can go to the latter numbers too?]
- 9 times 8?
- 72.
Jae Suk is really good...
- 9 times 9?
- 81.
What do you mean, I'm good?
As soon as I answered 9 times 8 right...
Ji Hyo says, 'Jae Suk is so good....'
- I'm not very good at being quick like that.
- Multiplication table isn't about quickness.
We're here, we're here!
[The fourth station, Osu Station]
- This isn't about how much you know...
- You can pass this.
[Time given during the stop,
one minute!]
- Get in line!
- Hurry! Hurry!
- 6 times 6?
- 36!
[Correct answer]
- 7 times 4?
- 28!
[Correct answer]
- 8 times 6?
- 42!
[8 times 6= 42?]
[Kwang Soo, eliminated!]
What?
[Huh?]
Bye!
[8 times 6 isn't 42?]
- Lee Kwang Soo...
- How is that 42?
- How is that 42? Seriously...
- 'How is that about quickness?'
I'm seriously so upset by this...
Kwang Soo...
He was just asking how
it's about quickness...
Multiplication table is all about
being quick.
being quick on your feet.
I can't believe this...
Also... we've never been wrong once
about the predictions that we've made.
I knew it was going to be him.
There is goes again, there it goes...
[All of a sudden,
reciting the multiplication table...]
[8 times 6= 42?]
Ah, 8 times 6 is 48...
[The fourth person to be eliminated,
Lee Kwang Soo.]
[The three eliminated members who've
been reunited during some time.]
Then are the three of us teamed together
to rip off their name tags?
We don't know about that.
We'll have to wait to see what happens.
You know what the worst is?
When you watch the show broadcasted at home
and finally realize then what was going on.
Wondering during filming,
'What the heck is going on?'
[ Ah... I see...]
That's seriously happened to me before.
- Seriously?
- Yeah.
Jin Hee's usually on the serious side,
but he seems to like coming on Running Man.
Yes, it's fun. It's so much fun.
That's why I keep wanting to come on the show.
And the recent thing that happened with Gary?
I thought that it was my chance
to come on the show permanently.
- Even though I felt bad towards Gary...
- Even though you felt bad?
I thought that it would be the perfect
spot for me to become a member
so I suddenly thought that it was my chance
and that I should give the writers a call.
- I seriously thought that.
- Really?
I really thought that I could do it.
Geun Young was on the show last week
and asked if she could become a member.
Even though that wouldn't be bad...
I think I would be better than her.
[What nice things to say...]
I'm not interested in other ones...
but I do have an interest in Running Man.
But what is the deal with this?
The nameplate isn't on there completely
like usual and it looks easy to tear off.
- This is how they are lately.
- So they rip off easily?
The new ones are like this now.
- This is new...
- It must be the new style.
They're coming out now so that it's
much easier to tear off than the old ones.
Who knows what the 2013 models
will be like?
[The name tags are always evolving...]
Ji Hyo, Ji Hyo...
[Everyone starts hoola hooping simultaneously,
and the first one to drop it is eliminated.]
I'm horrible with the hoola hoop.
The order isn't important with this one
so grab one and start hoola hooping
the moment you get off the train.
You have to keep going until someone
drops their hoola hoop first.
But...
The time you have for the stop
at the next station is five minutes.
[Five minutes at the next station?]
If I can keep going to the very end...
do I get the Ddak-Ji?
If you're left standing to the end,
then you'll get to have your own Ddak-Ji.
I need to become a Tosa
who sees into the future.
Since it's a Tosa who's good
at hitting with the Ddak-Ji...
A Tosa who's good at wrestling,
or a Tosa who's good with Ddak-Ji...
[This humiliating insult...]
[The fifth station, Namwon Station]
[Practicing before getting off.]
I don't know about this...
I really am bad at this.
I'll be the first one who drops it.
I really am bad with hoola hoops.
[Opening the door...]
Okay, everyone grab one!
Let's all each grab one.
Here you go.
[Everyone grabbing a hoola hoop.]
I seriously am so bad at this...
[Everyone stand and simultaneously...]
Ready... set... go!
[Everyone doing rather well...]
[Oh no... Kkuk fails]
[The remaining starts celebrating.]
I don't know the trick to do this...
I just didn't know...
Jong Kook!
We did it...
Kim Jong Kook was eliminated.
[Starting to analyze the issue
right away.]
Everyone, come look.
Come look at something funny.
It's especially fun watching him do it
in his yellow shorts.
It's so much funnier in his shorts.
[The man in the yellow shorts
who's just not getting the concept.]
Isn't it so funny?
He really is horrible at it!
I'm usually so good at this kind of thing!
[His damaged pride.]
Look... look... look at him!
[Spinning it with all his might.]
See? He's hoola hooping with
his strength...
He really is bad... so bad...
He really is horrible at it!
Why couldn't I do this earlier?
He figured it out so quickly...
I bet he's upset...
What a loss he must feel...
This is actually pretty easy.
[Mr. Capable becoming an expert at
hoola hooping within moments.]
I'm good at it now...
You were talking about how badly
you wanted to become a Tosa...
You've now become a hoola hoop Tosa!
I really should've been a Tosa today...
[Fifth person to be eliminated, Kkuk.]
[Alright!]
Next game...
[Finally, the last station!]
[Everyone shout out a number in order and
the last person to shout it out is eliminated.]
[If a number is duplicated,
then you start over with that number.]
[Quick to notice game.]
As soon as this game starts,
I'm going to shout out one.
I don't care whether it's duplicated or not,
but that's the number I'm saying.
Then it'll be duplicated since it means
the game will start over. It's a good thing!
I'm unconditionally going to say one.
When it starts, I'm going to shout out, one!
Let's not exhaust each other, okay?
I'm going to duplicate it,
so just be aware of that.
Don't annoy me with this, okay?
As soon as the game starts,
I'm going to shout out, one!
- I'm going to do it too.
- Let's see it then.
If anyone wants to duplicate me...
let's see you try.
[Then jumping into practice...]
- Start!
- One!
[Everyone with the same plan]
- Let's all go down together!
- Okay... we got it!
Let's see where this goes then.
Then go ahead, let's duplicate it.
It's not about seeing if it's duplicated,
but I'm purposely going to duplicate it.
[I guess...]
If we keep getting duplicates but the train
starts to pull out, we have to get back on?
That's not a bad idea...
that could be the answer.
I'm going to purposely duplicate others.
We're here, we're here.
You have one minute at the stop.
- Let's go.
- Let's get off.
[Sixth station, Gosung Station]
I think once someone shouts out, one,
we're all going to stand up.
- It's war.
- We've arrived at the battlefield.
Let's go.
- I told you what I was going to do...
- I've made myself very clear too.
I made myself clear first.
I'm jumping up as soon as it starts.
[Everyone getting in formation.]
Ready... set... go!
[Quick to notice game, start!]
One!
[Ha Ha's big trick.]
[Even though Ji Hyo hesitated,
she didn't shout anything out]
What are you doing? Come here.
[All properly fooled by Ha Ha.]
[Ha Ha and Ji Hyo passes!]
- Ready... set... go!
- One!
[Ji Sung barely passes from
not having shouted anything out.]
Why did you shout it out?
Why are you making it complicated?
We could've just ended this!
One!
- Ready... set... go!
- One!
[Looking as though they're going to keep
duplicating each other to the end.]
- Ready... set... go!
- One!
What are you doing?
- What is going on?
[The train is getting ready to leave...]
One!
Just do Paper-rock-scissors!
- Just get on... get back on.
- Get back on the train?
[Ultimately ending in a tie.]
[The Quick notice game
ultimately ending in a tie.]
[So ultimately, everyone
is headed to the final station?]
Wait... do you all know that
we've been tricked by Ha Ha?
- Gary...
- His betrayal is never-ending.
You're the best.
You have to know how to survive...
and he has surviving skills.
Originally, one more person was supposed
to have been eliminated
and the rest of you were supposed
to be on your way to the final station...
But luckily, there is one more station
which we weren't going to be getting off at.
It's Gurae Station...
we're going to stop there.
- I'll tell you the game when we get off.
- You can tell us what it is now.
No, I'll tell you when we get off.
Everyone will be participating.
[Everyone has to participate again.]
That's not fair!
- We have a totally different game prepared...
- No way!
That's not fair!
[Gurae Station]
Ready... set... go!
[The final game is, 'Round and Round'.]
Two people!
[Ha Ha eliminated...]
Serves you right!
Wow... I'm about to break down
in tears.
- That was awesome.
- That was such a great game.
He totally deserved it.
- How deserving for Ha Ha to get eliminated.
- That was a very fitting game!
I noticed how you guys
just latched onto each other.
There was only one person
that I needed to turn to.
At times like this,
we really do seem to be in sync.
- Ji Sung and I...
- I think it was very fair this time.
- Seriously...
- That Ha Ha was eliminated...
I think this game was very just.
[Sixth person to be eliminated, Ha Ha]
Then does it mean...
I'm a Tosa who can see into the future?
Yes. As I have told you all before...
These are the future Ddak-Ji's that I'm giving
to you all for remaining to the end.
You may open them now.
What is this?
[This is... the future Ddak-Ji?]
[If you throw down the Ddak-Ji
in the future...
while screaming out,
'The one who sees the future'
you can return to the present]
Why do we have to shout it out loud?
That is so embarrassing...
- The one who sees into the future?
- I've always wanted to do this.
You're asking Ji Sung to do that?
[The one who sees into the future?]
[This future Ddak-Ji is going to
lead me into the future?]
[And the consequences that follows
after taking a peek into the future is?]
You don't see the future when you
throw it down.
But you throw it down when you want to
return to the present after seeing the future.
This is too difficult for me.
Can I return it?
Present now is a difficult concept for me.
How are you saying
that we can see into the future?
[Your present is more difficult
than the future...]
[You're saying we can see into the future?]
[Just what is the future that they see?]
[The battle scene where Running Man
will be tearing off each other's name tags!]
[The ultimate filming location situated
in Jeollado Sooncheon!]
[Old streets, Shantytown, and the
streets of the poor have been reproduced.]
[The four Tosas who arrived on the train
are the first to enter.]
Isn't it amazing how they made all this stuff?
[Feeling as though they're walking through
an old town from back in old times.]
- This is...
- Oops!
[Everyone is on their own from now on,
so need to be weary of one another...]
I was just trying it out.
[The ones who've been eliminated at the
train stations also enter the set.]
Let's go... I like the Shantytown.
I need to go to the bathroom.
[Discovers Giraffe running in on his own!]
I don't know if I should tear his off
the moment he enters or not...
- Kwang Soo!
- No way! No way!
- I have nothing...
- I know.
If I wanted to oust you,
I would've done it already.
You really startled me.
[Deciding to let him live out of pity
since he doesn't even have a Ddak-Ji.]
I'm sure they've already
looked through all this?
[Huh? Now that we're looking, the eliminated
ones seem to be searching for something?]
If you search around on set, future Ddak-Ji's
are hidden throughout the set.
[Future Ddak-Ji's are hidden
throughout this large set!]
[If they find the future Ddak-Ji, the special
skills the Tosas possess' will be theirs too!]
- So the more we have, the better?
- You can look as many Ddak-Ji's as you have.
[More Ddak-Ji's they find,
the more advantageous it is to them.]
I wonder where the Ddak-Ji's are...
where could they be?
[Huh? That is...]
[A future Ddak-Ji in one of the two boxes?]
I'm going to open the other one.
[Danger?]
What the heck does that mean?
What is that? What the heck?
[What? A security personnel is on his tail?]
[If the 'Danger' box is opened,
your location is discovered.]
[If you're caught,
you're frozen on the spot.]
What the heck...
[Chang Ui also opens the Danger box!]
[Sweating profusely as soon as
they arrive on set.]
I've seen Chang Ui twice today,
and this time, he's on the run.
- Is that Chang Ui?
- It's my second time seeing him and look.
I've seen him twice today...
The first time, he was eliminated
and the second time, he's on the run.
That is so funny.
[50% chance. If it's not Danger,
then it's the future Ddak-Ji.]
[Huh?]
[Ha Ha discovers the future Ddak-Ji!]
If you shout out, 'The one sees the future',
you can return to the present.
I think I got it...
[Now he has the ability to see into
the future like all the Tosas!]
I feel like I've just died and
gone to heaven.
Race... start!
[Anyways...
it's still a peaceful street for now.]
[But just then...]
What is that?
[A loud clashing sound out of the blue...]
[Suddenly, all these women...]
[Clueless as to what's going on!]
[Without even having the chance to be
shocked, escaping is their main priority!]
What is this? What the heck is this!
What is this?
[Why are these ladies suddenly...
who are they after?]
What is going on?
What is this?
What's going on?
What the heck?
- What is this?
- What?
I don't know!
That totally scared me.
What is it, Jae Suk?
[Unknown reason for the attack by
the ladies.]
[Just what is going on in this town?]
I should get up to a high point
and take a look at everything first.
[Jin Hee searching through Shantytown.]
Let's slowly take a look.
I found it!
[The one he picks without hesitation
has the future Ddak-Ji inside it!]
Wow... who knew how reassuring
that would make me feel?
This is what it's like.
[It's Jin Hee...]
- Did you find something?
- No.
But the thing is...
you already have one.
- Right?
- Yes, I have one.
Will you give me one?
If you already have two?
You have two, don't you?
- Hey! You have two, right?
- Where did you find yours?
I haven't found one yet.
I'm searching for it right now.
- This is what I have...
- That's what it looks like?
- You only have one?
- Well, but...
Come on... give me one.
Come on, we're going to be shooting a drama
together for the next three months...
But I only have one... only one...
- You only have one?
- Yes.
Then let's do it like this...
since we're here together...
if you find two, then you give me one.
I'll think about it.
- I really think that you have two.
- I'll think about it.
- I'm going to get going, okay?
- Okay.
[Yeah... the more Ddak-Ji's I have,
more advantage I'm going to have...]
[Giraffe seeming to have been
waiting for Jae Suk to come around?]
[What? Ha Ha's waiting too?]
Yes... what are the two of you
planning on doing here?
What do you think we'll be doing?
[Could they be after Yoo-ruce Willis'
future Ddak-Ji?]
[Sensing danger! Let's first escape!]
Jong Kook!
[Yoo-ruce Willis making an immediate
U-turn to get out of there!]
That's that Tosas special skill!
Jong Kook! Jong Kook!
- Get him!
- Jong Kook! We're chasing after him!
Jong Kook!
- Chang Ui...
- Catch him!
Are you really going to be like this?
How many Ddak-Ji's do you have?
- I asked you how many Ddak-Ji's you have.
- I only have one Ddak-Ji.
Hey... I trusted him last week,
and had to pay for it.
Let's just get rid of him.
- We are...
- Be-tray-al Cross!
Do you have to get a taste of this
for the two of you to wake up?
Tearing off the name tag isn't the only way
that you can be ousted.
Everyone Tosa has a different skill!
We all have different skills!
I'm saying, we all have different skills!
[Yoo-ruce Willis using a bluff to get
him out of his dangerous situation.]
I don't care if I get ousted...
I just need to touch someone,
and we're both ousted.
Calm down.
If you need only one person...
I nominate this one.
- Pick him, not me.
- You two decide.
- I nominate him.
- I just need one of you.
[Just then!]
[Assassin Jin Hee approaching from
behind!]
Nice job!
The one who sees into the future!
[Jae Suk uses his future Ddak-Ji!]
[Yes... I saw it!]
[I saw the future of Jin Hee
tearing off my name tag!]
[I saw it... my own future!]
If you only need one person,
then I nominate this one!
No! I'm on your side!
[That's right... this is the future I saw!]
This is when you came up
from behind me, Jin Hee!
Jin Hee... he came up from behind me...
[Predicting what's about to happen
from having seen the future!]
How did you know that?
[This is what
the future Ddak-Ji is capable of!]
It means that if I hadn't seen the future,
Jin Hee would've ousted me.
- He would've come up from behind me!
- How do you know that?
I would never do that...
I would've never done that.
The one who sees into the future!
Hurry up and get him!
What are you all doing?
[And just so... the future was changed]
[However...]
[You have to pay the price...
for looking into the future...]
[What is this going on all of a sudden?]
[Covering them up with a blindfold?]
What is this? What's going on?
What is going on? Where are we going?
[To all the Running Man scattered about...]
What? What is this?
No! No! Don't do this! You can't do this!
You can't...
What is this?
[Why are they blindfolding them,
and where are they being taken to?]
[Huh? Why are they all gathered
in front of the theater?]
[Everyone is being lined up!
Just what...]
[Enemies all around!]
[As soon as the blindfold comes off...
actively attacking one another!]
[Total chaos!]
[This is the karma of Yoo-ruce Willis
having seen into the future!]
- What is this?
- Grab him! Grab him!
[Ji Sung going after Ha Ha who has
his hands on Jae Suk!]
[Fine... you tore off my name tag?]
[The future Ddak-Ji that he just found!]
The one who sees the future!
[Ha Ha uses his Ddak-Ji!]
[I saw it... I saw it!
In midst of all the chaos...]
[I saw the future of Ji Sung
tearing off my name tag!]
Everyone back to the previous situation.
- What the heck is this?
- Let's not do this!
[Everyone back to their spots
when they were standing blindfolded.]
just before the chaos ensued.]
Everyone back to their spots.
[Everyone to go through the same thing as
done previously with the exception of Ha Ha!]
We're supposed to pretend
none of this happened?
This is seriously so frustrating.
[Other than Ha Ha, no one else saw
the chaos that ensued earlier.]
Okay, everyone... everyone stand there.
Sung Yong... Hey! Sung Yong!
Get down here!
Get down here and get ready.
I'm going to escape that way.
[Letting his personal VJ, Song Yong know
of the route he's going to use to escape.]
These people don't know which way
I'm going to escape to.
I'm going to go that way.
I said, come down!
Come down here!
- I have to get the full shot.
- Who cares about the full shot?
Come down here.
[Planning his future in detail.]
Okay, everyone stand a little further apart.
[Finally coming back to the present!]
[As soon as the gong sounds, Ha Ha...]
[This is Ha Ha changing the future.]
[In the changed future, instead
of chaos, everyone's a spectator.]
[Everyone getting as far away from
one another as possible for now.]
This is crazy... what the heck is this?
[Whew... I escaped.]
[However...]
[Have you noticed?
That he hasn't been seen anywhere?]
[Why is Big nosed brother in jail
by himself?]
Suk Jin... you're not affected by
the change?
- I was ousted even though I had a Ddak-Ji.
- Seriously?
[Shortly after he entered this place...]
Pick one or the other?
I bet one is good, and the other bad?
[Big nosed brother, who found the
future Ddak-Ji faster than anyone else.]
[And shortly thereafter...]
Just show me the Ddak-Ji once,
just so I know what it looks like.
[Suk Jin showing Chang Ui the Ddak-Ji
upon his request.]
- You can't tell anyone, okay?
- I won't tell anyone.
As you slam this down...
You shout out,
'The one who sees into the future!'
[Oh my... he used it.]
[Just from wanting to show off,
he used the Ddak-Ji to see into the future.]
- Suk Jin...
- What?
I'm sorry...
but can you show me your Ddak-Ji?
Hey...
where do you think I have one?
I just wasted my Ddak-Ji from
having shown it to you!
[My future is having used the Ddak-Ji
after listening to his request...]
Seriously...
[And the karma that followed his action...]
Seriously... that is so absurd.
[The attack by the army of ladies earlier
was from the result of Suk Jin's actions.]
[Chasing Suk Jin to the ends of the earth.]
What are you planning on doing to me?
[Just then...
Ji Hyo starts heading his way!]
Ji Hyo... Ji Hyo, help me!
[So, Ace Ji Hyo...]
[Easily eliminated Big nosed brother!]
[The time is now over, lady army dissipates.]
Ladies... am I out?
- Out!
- What did you say?
This is the time when I need my Ddak-Ji...
[This is how...]
[He ended up here.]
[The use of future Ddak-Ji is key
to winning this battle.]
Let's quickly oust the ones
that have Ddak-Ji on them.
Let's just oust him...
[Targeting Ji Sung who's
guaranteed to have a Ddak-Ji...]
Why me? Why are you targeting me?
Why are you all after me?
- Okay, then I...
- Do you have one?
- You have one, don't you?
- Me?
- Do you have a Ddak-Ji?
- No, I don't have one.
- No, I don't have one...
- I'm coming after you!
What are you doing?
[Ji Sung in extreme danger!]
What's going on? What's going on?
What sin have I committed
by having one of these?
Kwang Soo... do you have a Ddak-Ji?
A Ddak-Ji?
- Do you have a Ddak-Ji?
- No, I don't have one.
We have to go find them.
Jong Kook... Jong Kook...
- Jong Kook has  Ddak-Ji?
- He doesn't have it, but let's eliminate him.
[Ji Sung ultimately being caught
by Mr. Capable!]
[Just what will Ji Sung do?]
[Startles Chang Ui...
backs up into Jong Kook's personal VJ.]
- He has one! He has a Ddak-Ji!
- Why are you so startled?
[Chang Ui eliminates Jae Suk's name tag!]
Chang Ui ousted Jae Suk!
[Yoo Jae Suk, out!
Yoo Jae Suk, out!]
- We have to out Ji Sung! Ji Sung...
- Ji Sung?
- Ji Sung has a Ddak-Ji!
- Why are you doing this to me?
[This is our chance..]
I told you, Ji Sung has a Ddak-Ji.
[Will Ha Ha and Jin Hee use this opportunity
to eliminate Mr. Capable?]
[Even Chang Ui is joining in!
Their target is Mr. Capable!]
[Chaos!]
[Kwang Soo caught in a dilemma!]
Who am I supposed to eliminate?
[Kwang Soo, attacking Ji Sung first!]
[Ji Sung, Jong Kook...
who will get ousted first?]
Kwang Soo, hurry!
[Giraffe eliminates Ji Sung's name tag!]
[Ji Sung, ultimately getting out
his future Ddak-Ji!]
The one who sees into the future!
[Ji Sung uses his future Ddak-Ji!]
[He saw it...]
[I saw the future where Jae Suk
and my name tags are eliminated!]
Ki Jin, are you okay?
Chang Ui, you weren't after me, right?
[The same situation as earlier!]
This is strange!
[But... it's a different future
than seen earlier?]
[The price of seeing into the future...
must be paid!]
What am I doing here?
[Changing the future]
[The consequences for it is coming!]
[The Ladies Army called into attack!]
[The most fearful consequence!]
[The most fearful time in this town.]
[Having to go through it again,
they're not as strong as they were earlier.]
[Ladies overflowing with tons of energy!]
Ha Ha, head up. Head up!
[No matter where you go,
they'll come after you!]
[Nowhere to run to!]
[Yoo-ruce Willis caught with
nowhere to escape.]
[At a quick glance,
it looks like it could be a fan meeting...]
[Time over. End of consequences!]
[Just then!]
[Ace Ji Hyo sneaking up out of nowhere
to eliminate Jae Suk's name tag!]
[Jae Suk ousted once again.]
[Ultimately, the future doesn't change.]
Shouldn't we... shouldn't we do something
with the ones who have a Ddak-Ji?
- Then we should...
- Jin Hee, you don't have one, do you?
Of course, I don't.
I haven't even seen one yet.
I was the last one to get to the set.
[Jin Hee not admitting that he
has found a future Ddak-Ji to anyone!]
I came with Chang Ui.
Chang Ui, Suk Jin and I arrived together.
We were the first ones to get ousted,
and we all came in together.
I think you have one because
you keep saying weird things.
- What are you talking about?
- I can tell that you have one.
- Hey... I don't have one.
- You have at least one, I'm sure of it.
That's why you kept asking me
about it, right?
I'm sorry,
but I'm going to check your shoe.
[Caught!]
[Since he's caught having it hidden
in his shoe, he's on the run!]
- We have to get anyone who has a Ddak-Ji!
- He has one!
Yeah, he has one...
[Jin Hee, you're really in trouble now...]
I can't believe that he lied to us!
Just like you said...
let's make them use their Ddak-Ji's.
If those guys... work together, I'm dead.
I need to go and hide.
- Wait... you don't have one?
- I already used mine.
- But you could have two.
- As far as I know...
There's a person amongst you
who has a Ddak-Ji too!
[Starting to inspect each other after
one parting phrase from Jin Hee.]
- Seriously... I don't have anything.
- Search Kwang Soo quickly.
I haven't found anything.
[Come on... would he really have hidden it
inside his pants?]
See? He has it. There it is.
- See? I just saw it. It's right here.
- Where?
[He hid it inside his underwear!]
What is this?
[Without even asking any further questions,
starts the attack on Kwang Soo!]
[Succeeds in eliminating Kwang Soo's
name tag!]
What the heck was that?
Hey... how can you lie like that?
You can throw that away.
That's disgusting.
[I went through so much trouble
just to find this...]
[Who ever knew I'd have to use it
like this?]
The one who sees into the future!
[Kwang Soo uses his future Ddak-Ji!]
This Ddak-Ji wasn't meant to use like this...
- I really don't have it.
- You really don't have it?
I really don't have it.
Are you sure you don't have it?
- I really don't have it!
- Okay then, search him.
- You really don't have it?
- I really don't have it.
- You really don't have it.
I told you, I don't have it.
[A safer future with the use
of his future Ddak-Ji.]
[However... there are still consequences.]
[Huh? What's going to happen this time?]
[What? Their name tags...
are being switched?]
Until one of those two are ousted,
their name tags will remain swapped.
Excuse me?
Please rip it off my back...
please rip it off my back!
- Wait... just wait a second.
- Why?
- I like this...
- Jong Kook...
Jong Kook, come on...
Out! Dong Hoon, out!
Dong Hoon, out!
[Kwang Soo assisting Jong Kook
so it's easy to rip off Ha Ha's name tag!]
Ha Dong Hoon, out!
[Ha Ha, out! Ha Ha, out!]
The one who sees the future!
Let's do this again... just one more time.
I'll buy someone's future Ddak-Ji
off of them!
What a cheat...
I guess they can't shoot the dramas
unless they build sets like this one here.
[The streets that only remains in our memories
that can only be seen on a filming set.]
Who's that? Ji Hyo, you...
[The culprit who's responsible for
putting both Suk Jin and Jae Suk away.]
Do you see the expression on her face?
Her expression says,
'What? You've never ousted me before?'
[Serves you right...]
Seriously... that Blank Ji Hyo.
- Saw that you went to a club in Busan!
- Yes, I did. I went to a club. So what?
I went and danced all night! So what?
Hey... when Gangnam Style came on,
she just went crazy.
[Internet search -
Song Ji Hyo's horse dance in Busan Club]
I have no idea what's going on right now.
Here it is...
[50% chance...]
I think it's going to be this one.
[At last... Chang Ui
discovers a future Ddak-Ji!]
Let's do something...
Let's work together until
all Ddak-Ji's are gone.
- The weak ones have to work together.
- Then we're working together right now?
How can those words
even come out of your mouth?
Let's not betray each other.
[These three working together
to eliminate anyone with a Ddak-Ji!]
- Let's go.
- Why is he here?
What do we do with him?
[Of all places... why come here?]
Let's talk to him first.
- Where's Jin Hee?
- Do you have a Ddak-Ji or not?
As of right now... Jin Hee and Gary have one.
Really?
Are you pretending not to have one
when you actually do have one?
- I really don't have one.
- We have to get rid of them first.
- Come here.
- You're acting strange.
[Like a thief tripping over his own foot.]
- I seriously don't have one!
- Calm down!
Grab him... just grab him!
[Very... easily eliminates Chang Ui's
name tag.]
[He just barely found his Ddak-Ji...]
- Do you have a Ddak-Ji or not?
- Do you have one?
[I'll show you... Ta da!]
[Chang Ui showing off his future Ddak-Ji!]
Where are they all getting them from?
The one who sees the future!
[Chang Ui uses his future Ddak-Ji!]
[I saw it...
I saw the future where I'm eliminated!]
- Chang Ui...
- Wait! Wait!
You're going to grab me
and rip my name off, aren't you?
I saw it! I saw the future!
- What would you like to do?
- Work together...
- Let's all get Jin Hee first.
- Right?
Right now... there are three Tosas left.
- We have to do whatever to get...
- Don't rip it off!
While there are still a few of us left.
[The consequences of seeing
into the future must be paid!]
Let's make them use their Ddak-Ji's.
- What are you doing?
- They're swapping it out again.
[This time... Jong Kook and Chang Ui's
names are being swapped?]
[The strongest and the weakest
players names were swapped!]
What do we do now?
- Chang Ui...
- Hold still! I said, hold still!
- You have to protect it, okay?
- I'll protect it.
Do you understand?
You understand?
[Subconsciously,
his hand goes to Jong Kook's name...]
We have to work together.
We all have to work together.
- No, I'm okay.
- You're okay if I do this.
[Jong Kook and Chang Ui have to
protect each other's backs.]
[But will the alliance between
these four last long?]
I think they're coming to get us
right now.
- I think they're coming for us.
- They're coming to eliminate us.
[It won't be easy
to handle all four of them...]
- But we have to work together.
- Should we?
All three of them over there have
Ddak-Ji's.
[The three people guaranteed of
their future.]
Jong Kook... you take Jin Hee.
Wait. Stop!
Do we have to stop just because
he tells us to stop?
Why would we stop?
Wait... something doesn't feel right.
- What are you doing, Jin Hee?
- No, something doesn't feel right.
Why are you running away?
What do we do right now?
You have to use your Ddak-Ji...
you have to use it!
[Jong Kook's saying he'll let them live
if they use their future Ddak-Ji's...]
[Arguing back and forth as to
who should use their Ddak-Ji's first.]
- Let's decide by playing Rock-paper-scissors.
- Fine, just one round.
- Rock-paper-scissors.
- Okay, the loser has to use it then.
- Rock-paper-scissors!
[Gary's hand straying to Jin Hee's back!]
[Gary rids Jin Hee of his name tag!]
[Ultimately having to drag out the
future Ddak-Ji hidden in his sock...]
The one who sees the future!
[Jin Hee uses his future Ddak-Ji!]
[Jin Hee ultimately takes a look
into his future!]
[Returning to the scene right before
they play Rock-paper-scissors.]
Rock...
wait, I think you're going to betray me.
Why would I betray you?
How can you say that?
You can feel it, can't you?
- The loser has to use it, okay?
- Okay.
- Rock-paper-scissors!
- Rock-paper-scissors.
You're acting really strange.
It's because I'm getting a weird feeling.
- Rock-paper-scissors.
[Jin Hee loses all on his own!]
[This is how Jin Hee changed the future
and remained alive!]
[Another consequence
for looking into the future!]
What is it? What is it?
What are you doing? What's this for?
[Being blindfolded again...
What is it this time?]
You want me to go in?
[Separating them from one another
far away from each other.]
Is someone next to me again
like before in front of the theater?
Why isn't anyone else around?
Jong Kook!
Chang Ui!
Yeah?
Is Chang Ui next to me?
[Everyone is on their own...
far away from one another!]
[Off with their blindfolds!]
Chang Ui... Chang Ui!
[I have to protect my name tag
on Chang Ui's back!]
Jin Hee! Jin Hee!
Jin Hee!
If I don't eliminate Jong Kook's name tag now,
there aren't any other chances to do it!
It's now or never!
[Kwang Soo heading off towards Chang Ui
with Jong Kook's name tag on his back!]
Why would I tear it off?
We have to work together...
Chang Ui, we have to work together!
Why? What's going on?
Chang Ui!
[Kwang Soo in the meantime reassuring
Chang Ui to get closer to him!]
Jong Kook!
Chang Ui, come here!
[No... I can't lose this chance!]
Why? Why are you doing this?
[Kwang Soo attacks Jong Kook's name tag!]
Chang Ui! Chang Ui! Chang Ui!
No, Chang Ui!
- Chang Ui! No! No!
- Why are you doing this?
Chang Ui! Chang Ui!
[Jong Kook's name tag eliminated!]
Chang Ui! Chang Ui...
Kim Jong Kook, out!
- You're out.
- Why did you do that?
- Why did you...
- This was the only chance to do it.
[Kim Jong Kook, out!
Kim Jong Kook, out!]
[Chang Ui's name tag on Jong Kook's back
goes back to Chang Ui.]
- That Lee Kwang Soo...
- Why did you do that?
In that situation...
this was the only chance I had to rid of him.
Jong Kook!
[While he was too busy bragging...]
[That's right!]
Jong Kook! I got him!
Good job! Chang Ui!
I was in the midst of talking!
[Lee Kwang Soo, out!
Lee Kwang Soo, out!]
Someone is being scolded on their
way here.
Isn't it Jong Kook's voice?
Then it must be Kwang Soo.
This isn't anything new.
This is what always happens.
Suk Jin, hurry up and eat the chocolates.
He's going to say something
about the chocolates.
[Rushing so they don't get scolded
by their younger Brother, Jong Kook]
Do we really have to live like this?
This is not right...
Nothing goes well with him around.
Seriously...
- What now?
- Lee Kwang Soo, seriously...
What are you angry about now?
What did he do wrong now?
I think he has some sort of a sickness.
[Name of the sickness:
Eliminate Jong Kook syndrome.]
[Symptoms: His whole purpose in life
is to rip off Jong Kook's name tag.]
- I really love it when you're ousted.
- Is eliminating me your own personal win?
- I really love it.
- It's like that for you, isn't it, Kwang Soo?
It's not like that for you?
To be honest, everyone that's here...
You're worse! You're worse!
[Displaying similar symptoms.]
Let's really try hard
to work together tomorrow.
Come on, don't be like that.
If you console him like that,
he's the type to believe it too.
He's over it already.
Jong Kook's already over it.
- We're like brothers!
- I'm a little dense...
Yeah...
[A man with a soft heart]
[Not many survivors left remaining.]
[Easily frightened male survivors.]
You startled me!
Why does it feel like we're on the same side
even though I was startled to see you?
Who is it? Is someone back there?
Ji Hyo!
There's no one here. No one here.
Ji Sung...
- Ji Sung...
- Oh! There's Ji Sung!
Oh! There's Ji Sung.
[It looks as though they've made
a pact to attack Ji Hyo.]
[Then Ji Sung will attack Ji Hyo?]
[Ji Sung eliminates Gary's name tag!]
- Okay, I did it.
- The one who sees the future!
[Gary uses his future Ddak-Ji!]
[How will his future change?]
I knew this would happen!
I knew you'd do this!
[Figured out Ji Sung would attack
from behind from having seen the future!]
- I knew you'd sneak up from behind!
- It's a misunderstanding!
[Everyone heading in their direction!]
- What is this?
- The ladies! The ladies are coming!
[The consequences for having
seen the future is starting!]
Ladies?
Ladies, ladies!
[The Lady Army attacks!]
[The ladies moving even faster than before!]
[Gary in extreme danger!]
[Gary caught in their vise-like grip!]
[If they're to eliminate Gary's name tag,
now is the chance!]
If not now,
we don't have another chance!
[The time for consequence is over.]
[Gary's breaking away!
I have to eliminate him quickly!]
[Gary endured his consequence!]
Did anyone get ousted?
No one got ousted. If they had,
I'm sure it would've been announced.
Those ladies are the scariest.
[Survivors:
Gary, Ji Hyo, Jin Hee, Chang Ui, Ji Sung]
Ji Hyo... you're the only one with
a Ddak-Ji left, right?
- Why don't we go after Ji Hyo then?
- Shall we?
If we get rid of her Ddak-Ji,
then we can all start over.
Okay then... then let's go.
[Ji Hyo proposes a one on one
against Chang Ui.]
With me? Why don't you do it?
You have to do it since you suggested it.
[I may lose...]
[Just then...]
[From behind!]
[Ji Sung attacks Ji Hyo!]
[A racket breaks out within moments.]
[The three guests start their attack
on the Monday Couple!]
[Jin Hee rids Gary of his name tag!]
[Fine...]
[Ace Ji Hyo, at last...]
The one who sees the future!
[Her future... how will it change?]
[I saw it... I saw my future!]
Something... something is going to happen.
I saw it all.
Gary... are you going to be catty...
[Right about this time... is when
Ji Sung attacked me from behind...]
[Appearing just as she had seen
in her future.]
The bell rang.
[Why are the guards grabbing
Ji Sung and Ji Hyo?]
[This is!]
[Ji Sung and Ji Hyo name tag change?]
Ji Hyo, come here.
[Wait...]
[The name tag on Ji Hyo's back...]
[Eliminates Ji Sung's name tag
on Ji Hyo's back!]
[What! In the meantime!]
[Jin Hee follows behind
without hesitation...]
[Even before Ji Hyo's name tag is returned
to her, her name tag is eliminated!]
[Ji Sung, out! Ji Sung, out!]
I was going to show you...
[Song Ji Hyo, out!
Song Ji Hyo, out!]
[Blank...]
[The last three remaining-
Gary, Jin Hee, Chang Ui.]
- Instead of standing around like this...
- No, we just need to get you.
Why would you get me?
[The two guests targeting Gary again!]
We have no other chances to get you.
[Gary is the first to attack!]
[By the split of a hair!
Gary eliminates it first!]
[Gary's lightning fast moves!]
See? I told you that he was good.
[Now the final battle!
Gary vs. Jin Hee.]
That was too bad...
[Song Chang Ui, out!
Song Chang Ui, out!]
- Chang Ui's out?
- Then Gary and Jin Hee are left.
What happened?
Even though he's fast, Gary's pretty good.
I think everyone just goes crazy
as soon as they see the name tags.
- So it's one against one.
- It's no joke out there.
[A battle that they can't avoid.]
[Assassin Jin Hee vs. Know-how Gary]
Jin Hee...
- It's been... it's been fun.
- It's been very fun.
[A mental battle going on between
the two.]
My pride balances on eliminating
your name tag.
Jin Hee, to rid me of my name tag
is ridding me of my pride!
[Gary's polished avoidance technique.]
[Ah! Jin Hee's name tag!]
[Gary... did it!]
I won! Me! I won this game!
I won this battle of Ddak-Ji!
Jin Hee...
The one who sees the future...
[What the...]
[Then Jin Hee had more than one?]
[Not long after he found his
first future Ddak-Ji...]
[He gains another future Ddak-Ji!]
[Using his brain!
Hiding one so others won't suspect!]
[That's... how it happened]
The one who sees the future... is me!
[Jin Hee uses another future Ddak-Ji!]
[I saw it...]
[My future where my name tag was
ripped off my back in the end...]
[I will change it!]
To rid me of my name tag is to
rid me of my pride.
[Returning to the point
right before the battle!]
- He had two Ddak-Ji's?
- Wow... so he had two?
- That makes sense...
- Of course, if he found two...
- I'm positive that I won...
- I'm positive I lost...
[Earlier was only a future that Jin Hee saw,
this is the only present that matters!]
[With his teeth!]
[The final battle where
means no longer matters!]
[The two who will never
concede their victory!]
[Just what...]
- That's Gary's voice.
- They're going at it.
A part of me thinks Jin Hee may win
because he's wants it so badly
but Gary tends to have strong
motivations too.
[Jin Hee taking a chance from a defensive
position to counterattack!]
[Jin Hee's repeat attack on
Gary's name tag!]
I know that I won!
How did this happen?
The one who sees the future!
I actually won initially...
[An outburst of accusations]
- After joining our alliance...
- Why were you working so hard at it?
- Because of us...
- Yes, thank you.
What is this?
[Saying thanks to almost everyone
standing there?]
All of us were in an alliance.
How big was your alliance?
- They all each came to me asking for it.
- Seriously?
What the heck is this?
You really are the ultimate traitor.
I'm the 'Or'
You're 'Tra', he's 'it' and I'm 'or'.
[Taking a role in the three part 'Traitor'.]
[The winning prize is given to
Jin Hee alone.]
What is it?
[Gold hourglass]
Is it real gold?
It's okay, I love it!
[An honest reaction from Jin Hee.]
The one who sees into the future
today is, Ji Jin Hee!
Subtitles by DramaFever
[The early next morning
in a hotel in Gwangju...]
[The shadows that snuck up on
the members...]
[Who is it?]
[Ta da!]
[Miss A's Suzy, who hails from Gwangju]
[And Wonder Girls' Yoobin]
[The mystery theater in Gwangju,
The riddle race!]
[The one and only ultimate riddle!
Throw your whole body into finding the hint!]
[The ultimate challenge
in history of Running Man!]
[Next week - The Riddle Race]