Is the money yours?
Return it to me.
I became a gisaeng just like this.
Im Soo Hyang from 'New Gisaeng Story'.
Thank you.
'Baek Hyo Min, congratulations,
-It's cold. -Hello.
Ah unnie, you were all watching.
Today we're Charlie's Angels.
Have you had breakfast?
Not yet.
Oh..really?
Ah I. prepared this. Do you know this?
Thank you.
I just opened this one, I only have two.
Unnie, how old are you?
I'm an early 90er.
I'm just a 90er.
I'm an 89er, so that means I'm the eldest.
Let's talk informally, since our ages are similar.
Yes, yes.
Please help look after us. I'm really not good at this, unnie.
Good morning, Angels,
You are here today because of a secret  mission.
Infiltrate Running Men as Spies, and eliminate all Running Men.
One of you must survive till the end for the Charlie's Angels to win.
Later you will start the race together with the Running Men.
If you don't want your identifies as Spies to be exposed, you have to prevent the Running Men from obtaining the hints.
You have to prevent the Running Men from obtaining the hints.
Then I wish the Charlie's Angels good luck.
I'm really not good at this.
Unnie has to take the lead.
My heart's beating very fast.
My face is all red.
So. we have to hinder the Running Men from carrying out the mission.
-We... - So we have to prevent them from getting the hints, us?
If we're not quick, the Running Men will finish the mission first and get the hints. Right?
-Right. So we have to be quick. -That's why we have to be quick.
We're acting...?
But Charlie is not allowed to reveal that he is Charlie
Charlie is someone from our Running Man members.
One person knows our identities?
They do know indeed.
But Charlie is not allowed to reveal that who is Charlie.
Then we have to find Charlie ourselves?
Oh no!
Then that means we still have to know who Charlie is.
-How do we know who Charlie is? -We have to find Charlie.
Plus Charlie can't die.
We have to protect Charlie and get all the Running Men out.
-Then are there any hints, about Charlie? -No.
-Oh. so how do we locate him? - It's really very tough.
Seems like it will be very difficult to find him.
-It's really very tough. -It really is.
-What if we end up doing well after this talk? -It fully depends on our acting.
I'll just depend on both of you.
The junior has to make even more effort.
Do you understand?
Why am I first... huh?
Why is there bread and milk?
Are we having a meeting*?
Oh. seems like a meeting today!
I'm seriously...
Hyung.
-We're not going skiing? -Hyung.
My shoulders look very broad right?
The fat bellied friend is here.
What's this again?
Nice to see you.
Oh. hey.
Hey, what does this atmosphere look like?
Right? Right?
Ji Hyo!
You're pretty.
-Wow. she's no joke. -She's so pretty.
Pink, pink.
Hey Ji Hyo, you applied hot pink on your lips?
Oh, what's with him?
Hey. isn't that Kim Won Hyo, Kim Won Hyo?
-Oh. what's that? -Hey.
It's not a joke...
Running Man's fastest ageing kid.
Jeez, hyung.
Really, Gwang Soo.
Don't you think he's aged completely?
Oh, why is he like this?
Why do you look so old?
Suk Jin hyung's here.
Suit Jin hyung...
-What's that?%-Isn't that his own self? His normal style.
Why are you wearing a neck pillow?
Hey, it's cold.
Over here hyung, hyung.
-Oh. -What does this atmosphere seem like?
Why, what is it?
Hyung!
The clothes are very matching.
Hey, Ji Hyo's sitting over there now.
Who is it, today? I'm going crazy.
Today it's a Retro Meeting Race.
This is it!
How many are there?
Today. the meeting participants, are stars to watch for in 2012.
See.
Done!
I'm going crazy!
-Please sit down -Ah, yes.
What are you doing?
Hey.
-Oppa, now... - hope it's someone I like.
The thing is that there are only four milk cartons here.
-Oh! -That's right.
Two people here will be excluded.
-Then it will Suk Jin hyung and... -Feel, touch, cross!
Hey, why is it me?
-Hey, Gwang Soo. -Feel, feel!
Hey. why?
What's 'Feel, feel'?
It's not 'Feel, touch'.
It might be you being on your own!
And Ji Hyo, you put too much rouge, don't do this.
-Oppa, this is excessive. -Hey.
-One thing to note, it's not two people eliminated today but three -It's you. you, you.
Hey, you're included too, you.
Ok, we'll...
Let's turn our heads away.
Without further ado. will the first beauty, please come out!
Is it all right if I like her?
-I'm going to close my eyes. -Hey Gary, can I be at ease?
She's young, she's young.
She's petite, she's petite. She's petite.
Who is it. who?
Oh, who is it?
Who is it?
She's pretty, she's pretty.
She's pretty! She's pretty!
Im Soo Hyang.
Do you know her, Gwang Soo?
You know her too?
How do you know her?
Im Soo Hyang was in 'New Gisaeng Story'.
Ah, 'New Gisaeng Story'.
-You came all this way? -Nice to meet you!
Soo Hyang!
She mentioned us at the Entertainment Awards.
I like Running Man a lot.
You have to invite me.
Eat as you wish.
-Oh, Soo Hyang also sat in front of the strawberry milk. -Ah, yes.
Switch, switch.
Then the next person after Soo Hyang.
The next person, please come out!
Looks a little familiar.
Wow, Hyo Min!
Roly, Roly!
Nice to meet you, Hyo Min.
Hello.
They did a drama together!
-It's been such a long time! -Unnie is so pretty.
Sit down, sit down.
This is refreshing.
Jae Suk oppa keeps pulling his pants up Ills waist.
This Is high waist.
Ji Hyo, this is high waist.
Hey, seriously. We're really with Hyo Min and Soo Hyang.
Hey, don't keep staring at them. Why are you like this?
I can't stand Gwang Soo's look.
Don't be afraid. You're surprised because of Gwang Soo's wide. forehead right?
What are you saying?
You're sitting in the centre and your forehead is reflecting light.
I combed it back on purpose like this.
Right, your wrinkles are all coming out.
Why are you looking like this?
-It's really very wide. -You'd do well to get rid of it.
-There's still one more, still one more. -One more, the last person!
Ok, please come out!
Who is it, who is it?
Go A Ra!
Oh my god.
Oppa. hello.
A Ra! A Ra!
Aigoo. Go A Ra.
Oh. seriously.
She's really mine.
I know her!
What, what?
He likes Lee Yeon Hee. Lee Yeon Hee.
Really.
-Here by the window, this person likes IU a lot. -Yes. I saw.
He likes IU a lot.
-I saw that confession. -I like IU as a dongsaeng.
This side likes Yoon Eun Hye a lot.
Isn't that right?
Ah, isn't that right?
What did you say?
Isn't that so?
Don't say it!
-That was a long time ago. -Stop it. stop.
Stop it.
I'm seriously going crazy.
-We're deciding on the partners now. -Yes.
The method is by picking their personal items.
Oh, this was done in the past?
The ladies, will put out their own personal item.
The men will pick.
-But, there are six men. - Six of us.
Yes, you'll find out.
Ah. for real?
Just like this, you'll be partners with the owner of the personal item!
-Moon Sook noona won't be here again right? - Will the men please turn and face the window?
Ok. now you can turn around and go back to your original seats.
Oh, what?
Do we just pick?
-There are six... -So why are there six?
Among them, two are the staff's items.
The two males who pick the staffs items. as you know, they'll become a male-male couple.
Let's begin!
-You lose if you don't put. something out. -Rock, paper, scissors!
Rock, paper, scissors!
Paper! Paper!
Hang on.
I'm nervous.
Now we're all thinking alike.
Threes, split into threes.
Rock, paper, scissors!
Ok!
Ah. last!
Rock, paper, scissors.
Yeah!
-You lose if you don't put something out. -Rock, paper, scissors!
Yes!
Rock, paper, scissors!
Did you see this side?
When Suk Jin hyung was 1st, she's a bit...
Jee2, don't worry.
Don't worry.
For me. I choose this.
-Lip balm. -Lip balm!
-Hyung. -Yes?
-It could belong to the staff. -No.
Soo Hyang, look at Soo Hyang.
-Soo Hyang, really? -She went like this.
-Lip balm. -This is it, it's really correct!
Soo Hyang went...
Her face became red.
Soo Hyang's face is so red.
No.
-Your face is so red. -Doesn't seem like it. Doesn't seem like it.
Me, me.
-You said you believe in fate. -Is this fate?
How can you call this fate?
No, no.
You can only pinch once.
I got it, I got it.
Five, four, three, two, one!
Ah, it's Ji Hyo's, it's Jl Hyo's.
No.
-Kim Jong Kook, Kim Jong Kook. -Me? Me?
Why are you booing me?
Boo, be together with a guy, boo.
It won't be the sunglasses. Because most girls have very long hair, they bring hair tie.
What do I pick?
Hyung, it's fate.
I choose this.
-This is becoming nerve-wracking. -Of course.
Ah, what? Which should I pick?
There seems to be two people here who still haven't been picked.
Shall I pick the wig? -
-Wig is too obvious. I have to pick from these two.
Oh, he picked, he picked!
-He picked this, he picked this. - It's over, it's over.
-It's over, it's over. -It's the end, it's over.
Hurry up!
You can only pick once.
-You already picked. -Jeez, you already picked, hyung.
-Ah. this part touched... -Ehh, it didn't.
I'm seriously going crazy.
Anyone can see that it's a prop.
No, no. No!
Ah, I'm really going crazy.
Gary hyung.
The wig is not bad.
The wig is too obvious.
-Take the wig. -Gary, the mobile phone.
The mobile phone seems like it.
I, feel it's the mobile phone.
I pick the wig.
-I already said it's the mobile phone. -Hyung!
I chose what hyung left behind!
This is reverse psychology.
-People don't usually put down their mobile phones -Exactly!
They wouldn't do it.
I wanted to take the mobile phone!
One by one, you ii ask for the owners of the items.
If it belongs to the ladies, the ladies will confirm it.
Ah, great.
-Who is the owner of this soft wig? -It's definitely one of the four of them.
Who is the owner of the wig?
The one who will be my couple today.
Ah, see! It's Hyo Min.
The hair colour is the same as Homing's.
Our writers don't wear these.
Then oppa will call you 'Min' today.
No, the staff should really have prepared more.
I really have the desire today.
That won't do. it really won't do.
Who is the owner of this lip balm?
-Ok. one! -Soo Hyang, Soo Hyang.
Two!
Three!
It's mine.
Hey, why do you carry around a lip balm?
Why are you carrying around women's lip balm?
This is the law of the universe.
Ah, this really doesn't make sense!
-Hey, this is seriously the law of the universe. -This is fate.
Ah, it's really yours?
Wow. Why do use female stuff?
My lips are very precious.
You use the same one I do.
Ah. it really doesn't make sense.
Ah, they're going one by one.
Ah, I'm really unlucky, really!
Suk Jin hyung, please stand over here.
-Wow, l'm seriously unlucky, out of the six. - Who told you to pick that?
Ah, I'm seriously...
Although, it looks like Suk Jin hyung's extremely unlucky but it's very lucky for Running Man as a whole.
This is just great.
This should be a woman's right?
Jong Kookie!
-The owner of this hair tie, who is it? -Ok.
The owner of the hair tie.
Oh, maybe Eun Hye is coming?
Ah really, didn't I tell you not to say it?
It is possible. You throw it away?
Don't talk about it.
I got it, I got it.
-I just won't say it then. -All, seriously.
Ok, Kim Jong Kook will begin.
Ok, one!
Two!
Three!
Really?
For real?
Hey, really?
Daebak.
Did everyone know?
Really!
It doesn't make sense.
-Is this real? -Is it for real?
Yes.
Really, is it really Miss A Ra's?
It's really yours?
It's mine.
This is why queen and king can't meet.
That's why the kings are all lonely.
Now there are two girls and three men left.
Ok.
This side is heaven!
Yes.
That side is hell,
his here is paradise.
-Even his clothes are red. -It's so amazing.
The owner of this cactus tonic, who is it?
Ah Haha, do it coolly.
'This tonic, who is the owner?'
The controller of tonic!
It's me.
What?
Hey! If you are not feeling well then go back. Don't try too hard.
-It's to give you strength!&-Ji Hyo. it's alright.
For Gwang Soo and I, one will go to heaven while the others goes to hell.
Take turns to ask, "is this right?" and then wait.
The dazzling...
What are you doing?
What are you going to say?
The dazzling person..
Oh, so frustrating.
Sorry.
Oh. this is so frustrating.
The dazzling person!
When I turned on the phone and took a look.
There is a very cute cat, just like you.
The camera director likes cats very much.
I believe in fate.
I'll be waiting.
Please please please? 1,2,3.
3!
What's the matter between you and me!
I said it in the beginning right! Fee/, feel, cross!
I said it right! Feel, feel, cross!
-Really? -How can this happen?
Yes. this is mine.
-It's yours? -Yes.
But how die! it really end up like that?
I originally intended to take that.
What is it?
You match each other well.
The current team will last till the end without any changes.
There won't be any changes?
No changes at all? it will be more interesting with some changes!
These two people cannot stay together, it's awkward.
Hyung, when we linked arms he kept moving his hand like this.
Why?
Today is a Meeting Race.
Go to every mission location and complete the couple games,
The top 3 couples will receive a piece of information useful for the final mission through a phone call.
Where to? Is it there?
This way.
They must be really happy.
-The first mission for the Meeting Race. -Yes, yes.
Cross the stone bridge from here.
When you find the Running Man banner, you will receive more instructions.
-Got it. -It's better if you set-off quickly.
Move aside!
Can't we go slower today?
Hey! You two have to hold hands!
Hyo Min, this way.
It doesn't seem like it's this way. It doesn't seem like it.
It's here! It's here!
Quickly!
Be careful.
Camera!
Kwon Ryol!
Run faster, Kwon Ryol!
Catch up quickly, Kwon Ryol!
Ah! It's really tiring!
Soo Hyang, you're good at running.
We're first.
Soo Hyang, well done,
Barefooted youth. Couples please search for the question papers while barefooted.
Hey, what should we do about this?
Totally barefooted?
Barefooted?"
What? Even the socks?
There will be question papers inside. After you have . found it, you just need to answer the question.
I am going crazy! Do I have to-remove the socks too?
Yes.
In-consideration of your partner. we will allow piggyback rides.
Ok! Set off!
Huh, jeez!
Barefooted!
Please say something reasonable!
Soo Hyan, come up.
Ah! It's cold!
Ah. it's really cold.
Soo Hyang.
Ah, it's cold! Wait a moment.
Soo Hyang. wait. Wait a sec.
I have to carry you. We have to find it quickly.
Ah! It's prickly! It's prickly
It's cold and prickly!
Ah! It hurts!
It's cold and prickly! It's cold and prickly!
Ah! So heavy!
Sorry sorry!
Ah! So light!
They are catching up! Soo Hyang, hurry!
Ah! It's so cold!
Can you walk like this, should I just walk?
Ah! Ji Hyo, it's too cold! Look!
My feet are freezing.
There's snow, snow!
Really,
Let's go somewhere else.
Ah. my feet are freezing, my feet are freezing.
I'm really sorry.
Sorry, we need to take a look.
Where is it? Let's search the soy jars platform.
Oppa, there's ice here.
Really, there's ice here. Where is it? Look for it.
What are you doing? Soo Hyang. what are you doing?
What does it look like?
You can't open it here after finding the question -paper. If you open It. it is considered a fail.
Yes.
Oh. I'm alright.
Ah! Who is it?
Paper, what does the question paper look like?
I found It!
-Where is it? -Between the blankets! Between the blankets!
Feel!
Cross!
Today something big will happen!
Ah! it's cold! Prickly!
-Both of you need to answer the question correctly -Both of us?
Yes
Feel!
Cross!
Gwang Soo, please turn around. It is a movement related question,
Do you still remember the pioneer dance idol star Park Nam Jeong's XX dance in the 80s?
Yes.
Please say the title of the song while doing the dance.
Why am I missing you so much.
Why am I like this?
-Please go to the back -Why me.
Then, Gwang Soo.
Do you still remember the pioneer dance idol star.
Park Nam Jeong's XX dance in the 8Os?
Yes.
Please say cite title of the song while doing the dance.
Ah, I really know this.
If I close my eyes.
Park Nam Jeong sunbaenim if you close your eyes'.
I get it. Please go to the back.
I know all the lyrics!
1.2,3.
Why am I missing you so much.
Guang Soo, please do it once.
If I close my eyes.
I can see you brightly smiling.
A happy expression.
Park Nam Jeong's ‘Missing You'.
Gwang Soo sang Lee Myeon Woo's 'Dream'
Ah, it's 'Dream'.
Come over here!
Hyo Min, I'm sorry!
-No? -You are suffering because you didn't get a better partner.
Today's groupings won't change, right?
Why are you like this?
We just started.
Why must we stay till the end?
-There isn't any here. I've searched everywhere -Is that so?
I've searched everywhere.
Oh, what a shock!
What's wrong?
That scared me!
Where is it?
What's wrong?
That scared me!
-Did you find ft? -No.
Oh, because of this?
-You must have been frightened. -Sorry.
It's fine.
It was too scary.
Oh, I thought you had found it.
Oppa, where is it?
Oh!
-Where? -it's here!
-Where? -Here.
How do you expect us to find this?!
This is too hard.
Oppa is useful right?
Oppa, then are you good at quizzes?
Quiz?
I'm sorry.
Please wait for a while.
Yeah.
Oppa will go first.
All right.
What is the 1988.Summer Olympics
Yeah.
Official mascot's name?
Oh my god.
Did you think I would say Gaedori?
-Hyo Min. this is definite. -Hyo Min.
Is it easy?
Very easy.
Ah, our Hyodori.
-In Korea's 1988 Olympic Summer games, -Ah, our Hyodori.
What is the name of the official mascot?
Haha, I got it.
I can't go back and say it right? I have to say it here?
Say it softly here.
Podori.
Please go back.
-Do you know? -I almost didn't know it.
Had I been born later...
Yeah, you were born in '88 right?
Although I was born in '89. but it was talked about then. too.
You knew right?
Then we'll go now.
Hyo Min. please say it first.
1. 2 .3.
Podori!
Hey. you Hyodol!
Hodori, it's Hodori!
What did I say? Podori?
It's because...
It's because the weather is too cold today so her lips were stuck together.
it's too cold.
So it's like that.
No, her lips were stuck because of the cold.
Korea's 1960 family planning slogan,
"If you blindly reproduce" iv fiats the next line?
Smoothly, smoothly, the child will grow...
What should I do...
What's wrong? Who bullied you?
He did? All right I'll take care of this.
-I don't know about the 1960s. -I'll say the front line and please tell me the end.
If you blindly reproduce.
You will have an endless number of babies.
That's not it?
And Hyo Min?
Smoothly, smoothly, the child will grow.
That saying didn't exist in the 60s!
You won't escape becoming a beggar!
Notebook!
Rogue.
The correct answer is Rouge.
Can't do that?
Over there.
Soo Hyang, over there.
Ah, I'm going crazy.
Soo Hyang, come over here.
Step on the rocks.
Who is going first?
-Oppa can go first. -I'll go first.
We'll start now.
This, which is becoming popular again since the 80s, is a dance where one switches feet am I drags them on the ground.
What dance is this?
Shuffle.
Shuffle dance.
Please go Bach.
It's my turn?
Soo Hyang, it's not hard.
Fighting, Soo Hyang!
Soo Hyang. you can do it!
The name of the dance where one switches feet and drags them on the ground?
-Where do I answer? -At the camera.
Shuffle dance.
Please go back.
Soo Hyang is incorrect right?
Please say out the answers when I say 1,2,3.
1. 2. 3
Shuffle dance.
Correct.
We did it.
We did it! It's the shuffle!
-Try the shuffle dance. -Why should I?
You just did anyway!
Where do we go?
The first who pass gets 30 seconds of the phone call hint.
Please go to the telephone booth.
Yeah.
That oppa is the best.
We're the first.
Soo Hyang, you listen.
Every time the mission ends, obstruct the Running Men from the hint.
The fast mission of the meeting race is the battle of the strongest couple.
Rip off each other's name tags, even if one person is left, the team still wins.
Are there any questions?
Every time the mission ends, obstruct the Running Men from the hint.
Where do we go. now?
I'll repeat the next location when we get off the phone.
Really? We can just go out from here?
Yes just go out from here.
What did he say?
Battle of the strongest... They hung up.
What?
It's the battle of the strongest.
So,
This Running Man is...
-Everyone? -Yeah, everyone.
-Battle of strengths? -Yes, correct.
Oppa, I'll go.
The fast mission of the meeting race is the battle of the strongest couple.
Tear off each other's name tags, even if one person is left the team still wins.
We have to tear off all the name tags?
Yes.
We...
-You and I together. -Yes.
We're a couple so we must fight the others.
-You and I together? -Yeah.
Head to the observatory beside Jang Yeong Sil Science Museum and find the Running Man banner.
All right.
This is oppa's personal VJ?
-He went missing just now. -Didn't see you just now.
I see you on TV often.
I'm your fan!
You got it right?
You still haven't found one?
Hyo Min, I thought that was your house.
We only found one.
We only found one!
-Hyo Min, you still haven't been able to go? -You just need to find one.
Soo Hyang. what die! they say just now?
They said to tear off name tags?
Yes. that's right.
For the last race.
Nothing else?
Yes.
The mission usually isn't that simple.
It can't be just ripping name tags.
There should be a spy.
It's a spy game?
A Ra, you aren't the spy, right?
Don't they usually tell spies beforehand?
If you're here for the first time, they tell you beforehand.
The spy?
From your facial expression...
I don't think you are!
You look like you really don't know anything.
-I really don't know anything. - You really don't know anything.
Then what is it today? There's obviously something...
Oh, we arrived.
Over there.
Where?
-Just go in from the entrance there. -Yes, yes.
We're the first.
There isn't anyone else right?
What?
Excuse me.
I'll take your temperature.
36.2 degrees.
It's normal right?
36.0 degrees.
Please walk straight ahead.
Oh, this...
I don't Clare to look down.
Dong Wan, why are you here?
What's this?
Do we start now?
This is no joke.
London Night.
Oppa's dancing is good.
Ah. it's really tacky.
Ah. really tacky.
Wow!
Yoo Jae Suk, Yoo Jae Suk.
Dance with me. Soo Hyang.
We have to dance like this.
What is it?
36.2 degrees.
36.0 degrees.
I was dancing excitedly yet it fell.
Music, start!
Let go of me. Let go!
Hey, Jl Hyo! Let go of me!
-Ok. you have to dance, dance. -This is dancing.
This isn't dance, you have to dance all the way.
Ah, it's hot! Ah, it's hot!
You have to dance, dance.
Ok.
We did it all.
36.0 degrees.
36.1 degrees.
But oppa, you really looks like someone coming out of some 70s catalogue.
It's not a joke.
It's not a joke, oppa!
This confidence is seriously not a joke.
No. he's someone who always think he's popular.
Oppa. there was this one.
-What? -This, this.
This is Jong Kook's right?
-Hey, this... -Jong Kook.
They're here, they're here.
Hyung, look. A Ra. look down.
Wow!
-What, she's not scared? -It's jjang!
A Ra, how is it, A Ra?
Oh, very good!
It's very good, A Ra?
Soo Hyang says she dances the Roly Poly dance very well.
-Soo Hyang, Soo Hyang. -It starts now, it starts now.
What?
Soo Hyang, how old did you say you are this year?
Why, why?
She's born in 1990.
She has a retro style.
She looks like someone from the past.
There's nothing else.
Look below, take a look.
Should we do 'Friends Forever'?
Fighting.
How can we raise our temperature with this?
She's similar to me, seems similar.
Wow, this is it.
A Ra, show your dance!
I'm starting!
Go A Ra!
Heat it up!
Heat it!
Oh. you can't do this, you can't do this.
-Hey, you guys stop it. -Oppa, heat it up like this.
Ok.
Heat it up!
We have to pump it up.
Heat it up7 heat it!
Heat it up!
Yeah, Go A Ra!
A happy heart.
Being happy, being happy.
Hey, it's tiring, it's tiring.
Yeah.
-Hurry, hurry. -It's really daebak.
Hey, check it out.
-Seems like it went up. -Hurry.
Go A Ra's the best.
-Measure it quickly before it goes down -How much will it increase?
Soo Hyang...
Soo Hyang is not sure if she's caught.
When Go A Ra was dancing at first, Soo Hyang said, "it's similar to mine."
A little later after watching, "She's dancing for real."
"She's similar to me."
A Ra is a good dancer, Soo Hyang,
What are we doing?
What are you doing?
36.1 degrees.
I'm having a fever?
Aigoo, come quickly.
They're here, they're here.
Look there, took there.
Why, why?
What's this?
Done, you've passed the first round!
Why, why?
You have to raise your temperature.
No...
We have to raise our temperature by 1 degree.
If it raises by 1 degree, would I have to go to the hospital?
Just come!
Why are you whining the whole time?
Ah, this kid's whining isn't a joke!
-It's not a joke. -Why are you like this?
It's abnormal.
Hyung, the Olympic mascot is Podori, Podori.
What, is it the police?
It's the police's Podori!
Aigoo.
Good, it's interesting, it's fun.
The sky became dark while we danced.
Feet, feet. Lift your feet, lift your feet.
Hey, there's no time to do this!
Now isn't the time to do this dance!
Hyo Min!
A bit more, more! Hyo Min!
Pump it, pump it up!
You can't stop, you can't!
Hyo-dol, now's not the time to be like this!
Homing's no joke.
- She 's truly Hyo Min. - Hey, let''s wrap this up!
What are you doing?
Let's finish it up in one go. one go!
-I don't know, I don't know. - Hyung, hyung.
- I'm going to go crazy! - Let's jump.
Our hearts seemed to have stopped?
How much will it truly increase?
36.2 degrees.
He wore a hat to dance so why didn't it rise?
36.1 degrees.
Mr Gary's body temperature didn't increase.
Miss Homing's body temperature increased by 0.1 degrees.
So how much more exactly do we have to do? Why again..
Do you want to know how much. Hyo Min?
if you want to know how much, watch the show.
Watch how much we did it.
- We danced, danced so vigorously now. - It's not a joke.
Ah, shall we see Soo Hyang's sexy dance?
The sexy dance her boss tried to prevent at all costs.
The anticipated sexy dance.
Oh. sexy!
Soo Hyang, be sexy.
That's right, Soo Hyang!
What's this?
A bit more!
Isn't this sexy?
Im Soo Hyang!
How is this sexy?
Soo Hyang, more!
Hey!
- Ah, how is that sexy? - What sort of moves are those now?
That's just a delicate dance.
Ah. I'm seriously going crazy, really.
Comparing it to food, her dance is like the bean paste soup.
36.4 degrees.
I had to learn traditional dance when I acted in 'New Gisaeng Story'.
Oh, this my first time seeing such a tacky dance.
Didn't you learn how to dance?
36.5 degrees.
I really haven't danced much!
- My clothes, that's why my clothes... - We'll reveal the results!
Yoo Jae Suh hod an increase of 0.2 degrees after dancing.
Im Soo Hyang has a whole 0.5 degree increase.
I got it.
It increased because you were embarrassed.
It's because you were embarrassed!
You felt embarrassed right?
Soo Hyang, get up quickly, that's it.
Soo Hyang, come quickly, that's it.
Soo Hyang, it's because you were embarrassed.
Every Night?
Hyung, enjoy it as much as possible!
Ah man, so tiring!
You have to see it to know,
aise it.
Ah, what to do?
Measure it quickly, quickly.
36.8 degrees.
Oh!
Wow!
-Do they pass? -Huh?
36.7 degrees!
Oh!
Do they pass?
Did we succeed?
-A total Increase of 1.2 degrees -Wow!
Wow! Wow, today's really...
May the world know that the Easy Brothers' time has come!
-Ah, it's our time! -Feel!
Feel!
Cross!
Let's dance together.
Together, together.
Let's do it together.
Ji Hyo.
Now... earlier...
-Ah. I'm going to cry! I'm going to cry! -That was a glorious moment, a really glorious moment.
We have to do this, the shuffle.
Faster, faster!
Oppa, do it faster, faster.
-Ah, I know, I know that. -Faster.
Good!
Great, Jong Kook!
What's this?
Good!
Jong Kook!
Kim Jong Kook, Kim Jong Kook!
Ah. it's so tiring.
It 's the first time I'm forcing myself to play.
We're forcing ourselves.
Hey, let's form a trio, a trio.
Hyo Min, get up, Hyo Min.
Hey, what are you doing?
To our viewers, are you having a good time?
-We are now with Go A Ra, Im Soo Hyang... -Pump it up.
-Hyo Min and Ji Hyo. -Pump it up.
Do stay with us till the end.
We have to pump it up.
There's the phone.
0h?
-Yes hello, this is Running Man.-Yes.
This is the Easy Brothers in first place.
Yes, congratulations.
- Yes. -The final mission is 'the strongest couple'.
Yes.
Just one person, from the last couple has to survive.
Get rid of all the remaining couple's tags.
Do you have any queries?
No, how do we get rid of them?
-Just tear the tags? -Yes. just tear them all off.
Where do we go?
To the final mission location.
Gwang Soo has something to ask. Hang on.
-Hello? -Your time is up.
Huh?
Hello?
- Oh. - We're the first, we're the first.
Ok, you've already gotten, the entire mission.
-Yes, we've got it. -If you, win in the end. you con take all of these rewards.
-Hyung. no one's even here yet. -Hey, this...
Wow, we have to go in and take a look.
Ah, let's just grab them, really.
Shall we hide here and ambush them?
Oh?
What is it?
No. what's this?
What's all this?
Hey. let's...
Feel!
Cross!
Hey, close your mouth.
Hello.
Hey, come here.
Hey, don't run off!
Over there, Jong Kook hyung's here.
Jong Kook hyung, Jong Kook hyung on the left, on the left, Jong Kook hyung.
What, are they holding hands?
-Those guys... -The Easy Brothers right?
Good Morning, Angels.
The reason for gathering you here today is to give you a secret mission.
Become Spies and infiltrate the Running Men and get them all out.
We have to get them all out?
One of you just has to survive to win.
Let's pray for luck.
-Charlie, we have to find him. -How do we know who Charlie is?
And Charlie can't be taken out, we have to protect him and get the other Running Men out.
It's like the real Charlie's Angels.
We've arrived?
Soo Hyang.
Can you talk if you're in Jail?
Huh?
Yes. Come here, come here.
Two girls are coming this way, stay cool.
You're here together?
What's your room number?
Our tactic's a success.
I've been working hard... I've been looking for you.
What's the deal, what's the deal?
- Look, I've always been behind you protecting you - Oppa, are you throwing me aside and escaping by yourself?
No, I'm not escaping.
I'm not escaping.
I'm here ready to help you if you got hurt.
But why are you here?
Ah, 1 really saw you.
I was there, why are you here?
Hey, I saw you there earlier.
You really have to believe me, believe me, really.
But why are there so many of them?
-What's all this? -Why are these people here?
Hey, why mus we tear name tags off here?
Ah, hey.
I got a shock.
- Hello. - Oh, A Ra.
Oppa. hello.
Hey, what are you doing?
Just the mission.
What mission?
Isn't it the to be the best couple?
Ah. is that so?
Why is oppa hiding here?
Ah hey. hey.
Don't move!
Yes.
Unnie.
Hey. this place is just right. Oh?
Oh, how can I stay here?
Ah, it's so cold!
- Is it very cold? - It's very hot, it's very hot.
Hey, let's lie in ambush like this for awhile outside.
Come on in. it's not cold.
- Come in quickly! - Oppa, is it warm?
It's warm!
- Believe me. It's warm! - Believe you?
-Take one step and you're in. - Really, it's really not cold?
Right, aren't I in the water?
Ah, how do I go in, really?
It's very warm, come in quickly!
- It's very warm right? - Yes.
Told you it's very warm.
Because there's fog here, those over there can't see us.
Go this way.
Where does this, where does the water come from?
Seems like it's a spa.
The water source.
It seems like this place is the end.
It's so cold here.
Aigoo, stop whining!
What do I do if my skin shrivels up?
If you shrivel, you shrivel!
Does the fog here come from the water?
I beg you, can't you stop asking questions?
But I still have so many things I'm curious about.
It's Jae Suk, be careful of your back.
Hyung.
Yes.
I feel that the game will start when Gwang Soo and hyung's name tags is ripped.
We re thinking along those lines, hyung.
Hey.
We're not easy pickings.
Jong Kook, where are you going?
- Be careful. - Hyung.
Jeez, you're seriously...
I'm really itching to tear something off.
Aigoo, seriously.
This is too odd, the mission's too easy.
We didn't catch that last^part of the hint.
Could there be, more?
Maybe we have to find something?
Hey, come here.
The Jail has ten chairs, hyung.
Is it torn off?
So, you're out?
What's this?
What?
She got me?
It's not like that.
I didn't see anyone else's but oppa's.
No, I don't know.
Oppa, I'm sorry!
I really like oppa a lot!
It's not my real intention.
Hey. the timing's really the fastest ever. You're out.
Ah, I can't stick it back?
- Are you out? Really? - No...
No. Soo Hyang...
No, I was also... hey.
The shortest time.
- No, Soo Hyang... - The shortest time in Running Man.
Hey kids, stand back, she's very scary.
No...
Ah, I never even thought A Ra would...
Ah. it's too hot here.
Because this is a sauna.
How did you do it?
-I can tear them all off, right? We didn't lose right? -Of course.
That's the mission now.
Right?
I feel somewhat uneasy.
Hey, I was so shocked.
You rushed out like the wind.
Ah, I saw it so I just did that.
Oh, when you were tore it off, how could you be that fast?
-'Rip', while we were all frozen and you went just like that -Jae Suk oppa. I'm sorry.
This is my heart.
It's really good here.
-Right, it's the best right? -Yeah.
They can't see anything from outside.
If we meet Gwang Soo and Suk Jin hyung. we have to get rid of them, got it?
Then, who will do it?
I catch them, you tear it off.
Ah. tear it off when you catch them.
How do you catch them?
Just catch hold of them.
Oppa, then whose will you tear off?
Why are you curious about so many things?
-They'll be hapless once we get them out anyway! -It's my first time.
Hyodol!
Oppa, no one knows we're hiding here right?
No one even knows.
There's nothing special, right?
There's nothing else right?
But. we still don't know.
-Hyung, if there are guests... -But, I'm very curious.
Who tore off Jae Suk oppa's?
-I tore it off. -A Ra.
No, we were all together
We were all In the same place, together.
We remained as two teams.
But I happened to see Jae Suk oppa's back so I just tried tore it off and ran.
But, if you tried to tear it of, of course it will be torn.
But it was torn easily.
"Rip", just like that.
I didn't know I'd tear his off.
I thought it wouldn't tear easily. I didn't intend to do it.
-I really didn't. I was simply curious. -Charlie's Angel.
Charlie's Angels.
-Jeez, I'm not that. -How about me?
You're not an Angel, you're a pretty boy.
She's an Angel, a real beauty.
Jl Hyo Unnie's a total blossoming flower.
-She's too pretty. -The most handsome among members.
Hyung, this.,.
A Ra?
Wouldn't I told him?
Charlie's Angels.
No. I just tore off a name tag, why am I being suspected.
I just wanted to tear it off!
Absolutely cute!
You try it.
Loyalty!
Oppa, what do I do about this?
My partner...
See, look at this.
Huh, look at this.
I'm really going crazy.
I feel safe because you're around, Ji Hyo.
Thank you, Ji Hyo.
Oh, oh, oppa... oh. oh.
Over there.
Jong Kook oppa, Jong Kook oppa.
He's scary.
Omo. omo.
Oh, don't film me.
Don't film me.
Let me off this once, let me off... hello.
Hello.
-Totally... save me. -Let you off?
-Where's Gary? Gary. -Huh?
-He's escaped. -Gary oppa.
Gary should have brought you along?
Oppa escaped first.
Really, he left you here?
He left you behind and escaped?
Gary oppa, he should be hiding here somewhere.
Oh oh!
-Wow, daebak! -How did you know I was here?
Hyung, hang on.
Hang on, hyung.
-Catch hold of his hands. -No, hang on.
-So you were here. -It's too early, hyung.
Ah, this is too early, hyung.
You outlasted Jae Suk oppa.
Why?
He's already out.
Really?
-It's not a good place here. -Gary oppa's here.
Tear it off. oppa.
Tear it off.
No!
What's this?
Hey, what are you doing?
Hang on.
Hey A Ra.
Hey, A Ra tore his off.
Go A Ra. Go A Ra!
This is what you do in this game, right?
Ah. that's right.
Oppa.
Hey. how can you leave a girl behind and escape?
Ah, what escape? I wanted us to hide together.
Go A Ra, Go A Ra!
-It's a game where you tear it off. -Go A Ra!
Everyone's suspecting me because of this.
Oppa!
-Oh? -Hey, Gary.
-What did he say? -Ah.
I don't know, I don't know.
I'm not doing it.
Hey Hyo Min, didn't you not do anything?
How?
They are suspecting me because I tore it off.
But it isn't me.
-I was just working hard. -It's just Miss A Ra at 100%, she was just working hard.
Ah. don't we tear them off?
We should tear them off right?
That's right. That's the game.
Right?
We were too weak because of our affections.
You helped us and I'm very grateful actually.
Because you tore it off so quickly.
I'm so sorry.
No. Ah really, don't be.
You did well, you did well.
A Ra.
Yes?
It's better that the females tear the females' tags off.
-The females do it first? -It's better if the females...
But I also feel affection towards them...
Because we're females,
-It's usually females tearing off the female tags. -I feel sorry about it.
We were all like this.
-Is that so? -Yes.
-Because it's not ideal for men to tear off the females' tags.
Yes, I don't think I can do it to Ji Hyo Unnie. -No, for Ji Hyo...
-Earlier I was about to tore Hyo Min's but because she's a girl...
-So oppa, tear them.
Yes, I don't think I can do it to Ji Hyo Unnie. -No, for Ji Hyo...
-Earlier I was about to tore Hyo Min's but because she's a girl...
-So oppa, tear them.
-Oppa should do it. -Don't view Ji Hyo as a real woman.
Yes, I don't think I can do it to Ji Hyo Unnie. -No, for Ji Hyo...
-Really. -No.
Absolutely not.
-It can't be me! -Hey.
Let's go out.
Hey I'm. I'm going into the water!
Oppa. I can't go into the water.
Hey, what's this here?
Let's go in there.
If they enter it will be so hot that they'll die.
Lock the door.
Hide me.
Go tear them off quickly.
What?
You go then!
You're better at fighting than I am.
You're good at it too.
You fool, God has given you strength so use it quick.
What about you? What about you?
I have my shortness.
I was born short.
That's how I live.
Be quiet.
What do I do without strength?
Why are you like this?
I don't even have any strength!
We're partners!
Because it seems like you'll abandon me.
You idiot.
Jong Kook oppa, might be Charlie.
Omo, Jong Kook oppa?
Jong Kook oppa.
-Or Ji Hyo Unnie. -Ji Hyo Unnie.
It's Ji Hyo Unnie, more so because she's a female.
-She may be Charlie. -Maybe, she's Charlie.
-And Charlie may not necessarily be a man. -But JI Hyo Unnie hasn't even helped us once.
Shall we let A Ra try testing him out? Jong Kook oppa.
Like this, shall we ask "Oppa, do you have a puppy"?
-After asking this... -After asking this, we'll say our puppy's name is Charlie!
Oh! My puppy is cute, my puppy's name is also Charlie!
After that we'll look at his expression together.
We must quickly convey this to A Ra.
Oh!
Rather than tearing guys' name tags, it's better if you could tear the girls'.
-Tear off the girls' name tags? -It's not good for me to tear off the girls' name tags.
-But I also have feelings for the girls, as we are all girls. -Girls should tear the other girls' name tags.
Is that so?
Why! Why! Why! Why! Why! A Ra. why are you like this!
Oppa!
Where are you going? Quickly, catch him!
I almost got him!
-Stay here first. He thinks only A Ra is suspicious. -No, it's all of us.
-All of us? -We cannot let him tell the rest!
-Quickly, catch him! -What do we do?
-Ah!! Really!! What do we do? -You should have given us a wink just now!
I was giving you both side glances the whole time!
Oh, that was scary. Oh, that was scary!
Hey what is this?
Hey, I will die.
So you both should act like you are not spies!
-Wait... Even if we act like we're not, this won't do. -Also both of you. don't make it seem so obvious.
-If that doesn't work. I'll sacrifice myself. -No. Tear off one more person's before you die!
-I already have no chance of survival. -Seems like Jong Kook oppa is Charlie.
Charlie? No way.
Just try confirming it once again.
Just say "Oppa, Charlie Charlie!" to him.
Ok, I understand.
I feel that Jong Kook oppa is Charlie.
Go for it! No matter what we must win!
Where is it?
Let's go out to take a look.
Seems like something happened to Jong Kook hyung.
As long as we have this, we will survive.
Get some more.
-More? -Take more...
Jong Kook hyung!
Hey, What?
Hey!
Good morning angels.
Today your mission is to eliminate all of the Running Man members except Charlie.
Charlie is one of the Running Man members.
-So one of them knows of our existence. -We have to find Charlie?
Nobody would guess that I am Charlie even in their dreams, right?
Although everyone will be very happy when they hear there will be beautiful guests.
Wait till they suffer this time.
Hey, What?
Hey!
Turn Off the lights! Quick, turn off the lights!
Hey, Dong Hoon!
Dong Hoon! Dong Hoon!
Dong Hoon! Were you tricked?
Dong Hoon!
The 4 girls are culprits.
You didn't know, right?
The 3 girls are the culprits.
The 3 girls are culprits! Dong Hoon!
Something big happened! What should I do?
What?
You only survived this far because you used me as a shield.
Didn't you promise to protect me?
You should have been nice to me.
-I knew something was fishy about you! -Be quiet!
How can you use me as a shield for the whole day?
Do you know how much I trusted you?
-You trusted me? Trusted me? -That's right.
Because you trust me so you left me alone in the jungle and ran off?
Is it a jungle? It's a swimming pool?!
Let go!! can walk out with my own legs.
You!
You just go.
Me? You?
Just go!
He's really noisy!
Oh, who's that over there?
Who is that? The one at the back.
It's Haha oppa! Haha oppa is dead!
Haha oppa died... Ji Hyo unnie did this!
-Ji Hyo unnie is outside. -It's Ji Hyo unnie.
-It 's Ji Hyo unnie who helped us. -We have to go and meet her once.
This is what makes a good game! Now is the climax, now!
There is no need to hide anymore!
What are you two doing?
-Oppa! Oppa! -Why?
It's not! Oppa, don't run away!
-Oppa, don't run away! Oppa, wait awhile! -Why wait?
-Have you seen A Ra? -You both are together, you both.
-What? -There's only the two of you?
-Yes. -Have you seen A Ra?
You should know (A Ra) where A Ra is.
Oh? What's that. Hey! A Ra!
-oppa! -Why are you like that?
I am really sorry.
-We have to tear off Jong Kook oppa's now! -Now Jong Kook oppa...
-Hey, you really... -Oppa, I am really sorry, although you are my partner...
Our puppy's name is Charlie.
Our cat's name is Charlie.
You all didn't know between yourselves?
So you all didn't know between yourselves!
Wa, really!
-Oppa, tear it off! Tear it off! -What is this?
What is this?
You all really didn't know?
What you said just now was great!
-We have to find out who is Charlie, -Us, us.
-Yes, only the 3 of us. -Charlie's Angels?
-He mentioned it earlier. -And then there's our Charlie.
That's the situation for now.
-What? Jong Kook hyung is also tricked? -What are you?
Why didn't you come out when I called you earlier?
-Hyung, you're too scary. -What's so scary about me?
-Didn't you hear my desperate call earlier? -Hyung, you are very scary now.
Hey! I called you like this "Dong Hoon. where are .you?" Do I call you like this when I want to catch you?
-Then when I was shouting "Jong Kook hyung" I got caught from the back. -Hey, A Ra definitely has something up her sleeve.
It's not just A Ra. What you said before was right.
-All? All? -The girls?
How many beauties are there amongst the girls today?
- What is 'Mineo'? - Beautiful girls.
- Charlie's Angels! - There are 3 beauties, right?
- No. Ji Hyo tore Haha's name tag. - Ji Hyo is Charlie.
Yes. the guy. the guy.
-In Charlie's Angels, there's a guy called Charlie. - There's Charlie.
Ji Hyo is helping them.
See, what 1 said was correct.
Where is Jong Kook hyung?
Jong Kook hyung!
A Ra, A Ra, A Ra!
- A Ra, you... - Oppa, it's not what you think. Where are you going, oppa?
No, no, no. Gwang Soo!
Ah! Really scary!
What happened? What happened?
Why are all of you here?
Come here, come here!
Hey Gwang Soo!
- What happened to Jong Kook hyung? - Don't!
Don't!
Hey! Don't do anything dangerous!
Don't do anything dangerous! Don't do anything. dangerous!
Wait!
- Catch him. catch him! - Hey, hey, hey!
- Don't hurt yourself! - Hey!
- Think of your family! - No, wait, no!
It's not like that, kids...
- Kids! Kids! - Tear it!
You all... You all! Gwang Soo! Hey! Wait!
Wait, wait!
Hey! Hey!
It's all torn off from the back.
- Sorry oppa. -What is this?
- Don't attack me! - I'm not!
- Really? -I said I'm not.
- Where is Suk Jin hyung? - Where are you going?
Hey, where did you go?
-Are you a spy, or not? Tell me quickly! - I am not a spy.
- Then why did you run? - They...
- What happened? - What happened?
You will die.
-Why will I die? - You will die.
- Why? - Your life is doomed.
- What happened? - What happened?
You will die.
-Why will I die? - You will die.
- Why? - Your life is doomed.
We tore it, we tore it!
You are a spy?
Oh? What is this.
Soo Hyang, what happened, Hyo Min?
What happened? Who is Charlie?
Ah, Ji Hyo!
- We were totally right. Charlie's Angels. - We were totally fooled.
- What is Soo Hyang? - 010...
- And there's 4 and 5... - What's that? Someone's phone number?
- Is that your number? - No.
If you called the number, I'd have told you that today's Charlie was Song Ji Hyo.
You just need to eliminate Song Ji Hyo.
And the remaining Running Man members would win.
I keep wanting to tear off Ji Hyo's.
What a pity.
Take this and share it with your family.
- What is this? -1, 2, 3.
Tada!
Wow!
- It's gold! - It's real!
It's really a gold ring!
How much gold have you got already?
Wow. Daebak!
Congratulations to our Charlie's Angels and Song Ji Hyo!
Running Man!