[One day in April]
[Running Man headquarters in Incheon Chinatown]
Subtitles by DramaFever
I wanted to start the day
today without clapping.
Let's go with the atmosphere if you can.
It's been 2 years now.
It sounds like you're talking to me.
Seriously...
it's shooting me straight in the heart.
-No, I didn't mean...
-Thank you...thank you.
Do you know what he just said right now?
- Hello! (in Chinese)
- Ah, yes...
-Come on, Suk Jin...
-Why? Hyung's drinking first. (Older brother)
Seriously...I can't even drink my tea?
-What? I'm asking if I can't even drink tea?
-Wow...you seem very cool right now.
It's not just for today anymore,
but I'm going to be like this all the time.
You're all dead now...
Let's get up to the roof.
-You're sounding real tough right now.
-You're a tough guy.
Get your hair done like how Kim Moo Soo
used to do in the past.
So that it holds up nice outside too.
Kwang Soo.
Did you see the broadcast yesterday?
-Yes, I saw it.
-Seriously...
Because I was teamed up with you...
I wasn't on the screen very much.
How is that my fault?!
You know I did my best!
Since he's not on the screen much,
you can just give him to me.
You're really territorial over
Kwang Soo lately.
I have some uses for him lately.
-See? That means I'm doing well.
-After that...
You have to get my permission first.
He's mine.
-What's wrong?  What's wrong?
-Hey, hey, hey!
-What are you doing?
-Because she's like family...
-What are you doing right now?
-How am I your family?
Ji Hyo...sorry, Ji Hyo.
Then...why are we dressed like this today?
Don't you think we're going
to have a guest today? Guest of sorts?
I wonder if it's a guest that's
related to China somehow?
We are in Chinatown.
Who's coming out today?
Our guest for the day is already here,
and is waiting.
-Oh really?
-Why?
If you look off to your side,
you're going to see some screen doors.
You each pick a door and stand
in front of the screen to select the guest.
-Hyung...forget it.
-Why?
Couple of weeks ago, we had Lee Deok Hwa,
and the other two guys as guests.
-Last week, it was just us.
-We didn't have any last week.
This time, it's the Idols' turn.
Unconditionally! I swear to it!
Once I say go, you have to stand in front
of the door that you choose.
I'll take my time going.
I was comfortable with the hyungnims.
(His older mentors)
-Why is that?
-The reason why is...
-Even though those guys were nice...now...
-Suzy, isn't it time for you to be on the show?
Suzy...or Sistar's Bora.
Hey, I'll use Kwang Soo today.
-Guest...come on out!
-Jessica!
-Please...! Idol! Come on out!
-Please!
[Dong Wan FD wins!]
(FD = assistant producer)
-There you go!
-I knew this was going to happen.
[Disappointed]
I knew it was going to be like this...
seriously.
-We are!
-It's going to be us, no doubt...
Seeing how Gary and I
are together like this today...
Today, we're going to get a beautiful guest.
Who shall we call out?
-Beauty.
-Should we try calling out for Suzy Q?
-Sure, Suzy Q sounds nice.
Believing that Suzy Q will come out,
we'll call out for Suzy's name.
-1, 2, 3...
-Suzy Q!
[Man with the boyish smile,
Actor Chun Jung Myung!]
[Surprised!]
I was surprised because he's good looking.
Seriously...this isn't right,
but he is so pretty for a man!
He's so pretty for a man!
-Hello...
-I was so surprised.
[Yoo Hyuk - Gary - Jung Myung: one team]
-It's Jung Myung?
-Total A class.
Jung Myung is a very close dongsaeng.
(Younger brother/friend0
He's my dongsaeng from my neighborhood.
[Showing off his friendship]
The two of you look really ugly standing
next to him right now!
We're in big trouble today!
Hurry up and call out for Suzy.
Should I pretend to be a girl?
You don't have any girl costumes?
A face mask that looks like Suzy...
We're going to see what we have over here.
-1, 2, 3...
-Please come out!
[J.Y.P. Park Jin Young]
[Cold ice?]
J.Y.P...J.Y.P!
-Seriously? J.Y.P?
-With a live broadcast coming up...
What are you going to do about your broadcast
for you to come out on this?
With Kwang Soo there...I think you're going
to be very disappointed with those 2...
-We are...
-We're the best!
Since earlier, you thought it was a girl,
and then it turned out not to be,
and with the second one, you said it's okay
even though it's a man because he's handsome,
but since I'm neither, I got so nervous!
When I first opened the door,
he smiled and said "I'm sorry".
Then have the teams been decided?
Jung Myung, Gary and myself like this?
-That's how it is right now.
-I guess it's 3 per team?
Today's broadcast of K-Pop star
is their last show.
-We will...
-It will be revealed after a moment!
Learn how to gauge the atmosphere,
if you've been on the show for 2 years.
Did the two of you shoot
a movie together recently?
No, no...Jin Young is going to be
making a comeback soon...
Jin Young, let us hear something.
-Shall we?
-Why don't you sing something for us?
[A taste of JYP's new song, 'Only You']
What's wrong with me today?
-I was a little too nervous...
-It's okay!
It should have been half oxygen
and half voice.
Since all you did was sing without oxygen,
of course, your voice was going to crack.
JYP!  JYP!
From the beginning, the breathing that
flows in and out,
half oxygen, and half voice
that I stressed about more than anything...
Half oxygen and half voice...
What's wrong with me today?
JYP...instead of judging what others do,
you yourself should have used
half oxygen and half voice...
The oxygen...with the voice...
It's because there was
no oxygen within your voice...in your voice.
If you work that way,
it's not getting much of anything.
This is what I mean...when you're nervous,
the oxygen is depleted from your voice.
Human...JYP.
Even JYP is human!
-I can see it now...
-You can tell how much oxygen is needed now?
It's because there was no oxygen,
even JYP ended up like that.
For too long of a time...
all we've done was talk about him.
You're right, you're right.
-Chun Jung Myung! Chun Jung Myung!
-He's got cold feet...
-Don't do that.
-Why?
Back in the day, when Jung Myung and I
used to do "X-Man" together,
his nickname was Mr. Freeze.
He has some stiffness about him.
Earlier too,
when the filming was stopped for awhile,
and we kept telling him not to worry
because we were joking around,
he said 'I know...
it should've been a girl group that came out'.
It really isn't like that...
Seriously!  We're excited about you here!
-You have no idea how happy we are.
-You need to pay more attention to him.
Why are you still talking about that
when that nickname was from years ago?
How many years ago was that?
-2004.
-2004. You remembered.
[Remembered exactly...
Nicknames are not to be forgotten!]
So...since we're teamed up with Jung Myung,
are we starting off right away or not?
I will reveal your mission for the day.
Today's mission...is black bean noodle race.
Take the phone order that comes in
for Running Man,
and the team that delivers to
the right spot first is the winner.
-This is it!
-We're here!
And to the winner...
the prize is golden chopsticks.
Just look at these black bean noodles.
Jae Suk really likes noodles.
Jae Suk, when you're eating noodles,
you really look ugly.
Even though I do know
that I'm not good looking...
[So...? Next week - viewers' picks will
be revealed!]
This is really good.
-I'm nervous.
-Why isn't anything happening?
[Perhaps... the mission is under the table,
or seat?]
[Just inhaling in one breath...]
Guys!
There's a phone order at the
first floor counter!
You have to come and take the order!
Come get the phone!
-Jung Myung!
-JYP!
-Jung Myung! Jung Myung! Jung Myung!
-JYP!!
Jung Myung!  Grab it!
-I thought you said you couldn't do it.
-Hello. This is Running Man Restaurant.
This is...
Where?
-... (Inaudible)
-Excuse me?
-He can't understand what the guy is saying.
-Just look at his expression.
Guhmoondo?
-Guhmoondo, Guhmoondo.
I'm in town next to Moouido.
What did you say?
Past Moouido in Somoodo.
Bring me a bowl of black bean noodles quickly.
Let's go.
-We're going now?
-A bowl of black bean noodles please.
Are we going right now?
There's only one bowl of
real black bean noodles in front of you.
-You have to choose.
-JYP, you choose.
[He chooses a bowl with black rubber].
You can wrap it up with saran wrap,
and take it with you right now.
[Beginning the journey of delivering black rubber...]
How can you choose the bowl with
the black rubber?
[If this is black rubber noodles...]
[Then one of these two must
be the real black bean noodles!]
Suk Jin.  Do you remember?
-Moo...I think he said Souido.
-Is it Soraedo?
It's because he has long legs.
JYP was the first after we teased him
about always being last.
I was the first one to rise from the chair...
Guys!  There's a phone call at the
second floor counter!
-There's a phone call!
-Hurry up!
Jung Myung!  Hurry!
-Which one?  Is this it?
-The phone's still ringing.
Where is it?  Where is it?
-Seriously...
-Where is it?  Where is it?
-Hello?
-Yes, yes. You've got the right number.
This is Somoouido.
-Moouido?
-Bring me a bowl of black bean noodles.
It's Moouido, right?  Moouido?
Yes, I understand.
-Let's write it down.
-Write it, write it.
[Somoouido].
-We have to choose the right one?
-The one on the left?
Open it.
-They're not both real.
-Just shut it for now.
[Blue team: Package and deliver the
real black bean noodle]
The whole thing?
Yes, hello?
Yes.
A reservation?  Please go on.
We have to answer this one.
12...just a moment please,
I'll put the owner on the phone.
I answered their regular line.
-I answered their regular line...
-Yes...
-This is Somoouido.  Somoouido.
-Where?
It's Somoouido past Moouido.
-So...Woo?
-It's Somoouido.
These guys haven't left yet.
-Somoouido...
-Bring me a bowl of black bean noodles.
Yes, I understand.
Yes.  He says he's calling from Souido.
Write it down here for now.
-What are you doing?
You scared me.
I guess I shouldn't let my guard down?
I guess this is how it feels.
Jung Myung.  This is no time to be laughing.
Somoouido.
-[Somoouido]
He said he's in Somoouido.
Pil Chok Cross is the most scary thing.
What's that?
It's Running Man's most popular phrase.
I'll show it to you.
Pil-Chok-Cross!!
Why are you Pil?
[The best mantra (?) is described step by step]
You do something.
-Speed.
-Speed?
-Pil Chok Speed?
-Let's try it.
-Pil.  Chok!
-Speed.
Why is your voice cracking like that?
My voice has been off all morning.
-Speed!
-Put some air in there. Oxygen!
Put some oxygen in
your throat when you're talking.
Did you really learn Jujitsu for work?
-No.
-What's Jujitsu like?
It's fun. It's so fun!
My personality is originally...
very competitive.
You know how you shake hands
after the match is over?
Well, I wasn't shaking my opponent's hands.
Your competitiveness was that strong?
Because I got so angry...
Wow...that's a really strong streak.
They always shake hands.
Before they start and when it ends.
The meaning of that handshake I realized
is very important.
Why didn't you act like that when you
went to answer the phone earlier?
Jung Myung...
when you went to answer the phone earlier,
I saw you shoving Ha Ha out of the way.
You egged me on.
'Jung Myung! Jung Myung! Keep it up!'
-Kept saying, Jung Myung!
-That's how the skinship started.
-That's why he is Chun Jung Myung.
-That's why.
And what if he and Jong Kook
get pitted up against each other later?
-That's going to be something.
-I think it's going to be fun.
-Wait, wait...I think he's got it.
-No, his leg is caught.
[Who will win this match?]
-Our black bean noodles right now...
-Yeah.
-This is the real black bean noodles.
-Really?!
-Really?
-Then the others are all fake?
-Then the other teams have fakes...
-They could be fakes, or...
Or they could be something else entirely.
Like ramen or something.
Wait...sorry.
It's a call from Running Man Restaurant.
Hello?
-Yes, this is the President.
-Yes, President?
We just got a call from the customer that
ordered the black bean noodles.
And he wants to make sure you bring him
a pair of wooden chopsticks.
-Wooden Chopsticks?
-We didn't bring any wooden chopsticks.
-Wooden Chopsticks? We don't have any.
-What did he say?
-You didn't bring any chopsticks?
-Yes.
That's a given when you're making a delivery!
What should we do?
You should've told us that sooner.
Since it's late,
don't come back to the restaurant.
When you get to Jamjindo,
you'll find a Running Man's mark.
You can go there
and get the wooden chopsticks.
-Jamjindo?
-Yes, I understand.
Wooden chopsticks?
That doesn't even make any sense.
How can this even make any sense?
They said they have chopsticks
ready at Jamjindo spot.
Seriously...they could just bring
the chopsticks themselves.
That's what I'm saying.
-Jamjindo?
-Yes.
[Find chopsticks at Jamjindo~]
-This is...
-I think it's to the right.
There it is!  It's here.
[Yellow Team
Finds Running Man Flag]
It's the ocean!
[The mission to get the chopsticks is here?]
We're here to get the chopsticks.
[Guess the items in the metal bin].
I guess we have to match up the items
to get the chopsticks.
-So...we have to guess the items in that bin?
-Isn't that too far?
-We have to guess it from here?
-Can we even see that from here?
-Isn't this where we stand?
-Stand by the yellow mark please.
This is yellow over here.
I wasn't sure.
Please stand in line.
-Yes.
-What are you doing?
Take your sunglasses off!
-Would you like some help?
-Yes.
Aren't these pedometers?
Please put the pedometers on.
The music is going to be playing.
If you dance until the music stops,
then each pace on the pedometer will count
as 1 mm and you can step forward that amount.
-1 mm?
-1 mm.
-If it's 100 times, it's 100mm..
-100mm?  You mean, 10 cm?
Pil!  Chul!  Speed!  Cross!
Speed!  Cross!
You have to guess the item in this metal bin.
We have to stand over here.
You want us to guess that?!
-What the heck?
-You saw it, right?
See what?
One more time.  1, 2, 3.
Sweet pickled radish!
-You're wrong.
-Why are you doing it by yourself?
You have to discuss it with us first
before you shout it out.
Is it rice cake?  That's what it looked like.
[It's ramen].
You guys are dressed like little chicks.
-They're already doing it.
-JYP!
-JYP, what are you doing?
We're trying to guess what's inside
that metal carrying bin.
-Red team...
-We'll have a go.
Look at the item that's inside the metal bin.
-Oh, that?
-His arms are really long.
Why are your arms so long?
-I saw it, I saw it.
-Again.  Do it one more time.
I saw, it, I saw it.
-What the heck...
-What is that?
Blue team can start with the guess.
1, 2, 3.
-Doshirak! (Bento Box)
-You've got it wrong.
Red team.  1, 2, 3.
-Rice cake!
-I guess everyone's guessing that.
Yellow Team.  1, 2, 3.
-Rice cake.
-Yellow team, you're wrong.
Us?
You got it wrong because
you didn't answer within 3 seconds.
-You didn't even call us!  No!
-What?  No way!
-We were discussing!  Discussing!
-How can you do this?!
You're wrong.
-Hey!
-That...that...
Hey.  Just stick it in there.
Kwang Soo got so flustered that he
doesn't even know how to stick it in.
I'll play you some music.
[Chance to advance with pedometer]
["Elevator" - 1995, by Park Jin Young]
[Jung Myung-ah!
You have to dance!]
[Exciting dance at the beach]
[Dance God that's bothering Ha Ha].
You can't up the numbers.
Blue Team.
-One person at a time.  Just one.
-294.
-462.
-Okay, 462.
-462?  Wow...
-151.
You can move up 907 mm.
Res Team, your turn.
I've got 222.
224.
235.
You can move up 681 mm.
70 cm?
This is unfair...the reason why is...
You have to dance to the beat,
how can you not dance to the beat?
JYP, this is not being judged or anything.
-How...
-I've got 208.
130.
If it's more than this, it means
they weren't keeping to the beat at all.
36.
Why are you only 36?
I think I was keeping to the beat too well.
-Seriously!
-Move up 374 mm.
If we're to make it all the way up there,
we're going to be up all night.
Let's just finish it this time.
Are you okay, Kwang Soo?
I'll show it to you again.
It's a real zoo!
You guys are like the real zoo.
I'll show it to you now.
What the heck is that?
[We told you, it's ramen].
-What's that?
-What is that?
Does it have anything to do with Running Man?
-You're having way too much fun!
-Hey!!
Hey!  Which school did you go to?!
Hey.  Come back.
I told you to just come back.
It's something all of you see a lot of.
Give me the correct answer.
It's something we see a lot?
Jung Myung's chance.
Jung Myung's going to say it by himself.
What are you saying all of a sudden?
-Jung Myung...
-1, 2, 3!
Fermented soybean paste soup.
-Come on...seriously?
-That was too much.
You're wrong.
The music is going to start again.
["That Girl is Pretty" - 1996, by Park Jin Young]
That girl...was so pretty!
[The dancing giraffe]
[Creating a scene all by himself]
[A solo dance for the seagull]
Hey!
I wonder what that is?
I'll show it to you one more time.
Tell me your correct answer.
Let's do this one more time.
Grab his hands.
I think I got it.
-What is that?
-I think I got it.
-We've got the answer!
-1, 2, 3.
-Ramen!
Ramen!
Correct answer.
It's ramen! That's ramen!!
Awesome.
The team that got it right can come this way.
How did you see that?
You can choose one of the three here.
We have to do this right.
-Chun Jung Myung's chance!
-Is this it?
-You can check it.
Wow...you guys look happy.
[Find the Running Man's mark at the
only beach in Moouido].
-We're leaving!  Good luck!
-We're leaving now!
-How can you take the chopstick?
-We're late. We're going to go.
See you later.
[Running Man Restaurant
that delivers anywhere].
Friends...we'll be leaving first!
Wait...even though we got the chopsticks...
who got the black bean noodles?
Yes, President.
Did you get the chopsticks?
We got the chopsticks in the metal carrier.
We got another call from the customer
that ordered the black bean noodles...
-Yes?
-He wants lots of sweet pickled radish.
He wants lots of sweet pickled radish now?
Okay, okay.
If you ride the boat into Moouido,
there's a beach area called Hanagae beach.
Hanagae beach.
Yeah, Hanagae beach.
You need to stop by there
and get the sweet pickled radish.
Yes, President.
I think we're supposed to get on that.
[Moouido Ferry]
This is where we were that one time...
Moouido.
[Crossing the sea to Moouido does
not stop the delivery~]
[The Running Man Restaurant will go anywhere!]
[Even if only to advance 1mm]
We have a new item now.
-Correct answer!
Coal briquettes!
Correct answer.
[A World Cup semifinals reaction]
[The one thing Speed JYP did]
First time!  Got it at the first try!
Pil-Chok-Speed-Cross!!
Pick, pick...gotta pick.
Since we picked the middle one last time,
let's just stick with it.
1, 2, 3!
[Fake broken chopsticks]
-From now on, when it comes to picking...
-Don't pick.
[Find the Running Man's mark at the
only beach in Moouido].
Correct answer.
Disposable camera?
You've got the correct answer.
-Be a little happy.
- Be happy!  I guessed it right!
It's chopsticks.
Ah...no, it's not.
We got here so quick.
We're in Moouido.  We're in Moouido.
I hope no difficult competition
starts in Moouido.
We have to think of this as an honor.
-He's a world renowned producer.
-No, I'm not...
Can you...sing us an Easy Bother's song?
-I like things like that.
-Really?
We're not easy like the Easy Brothers.
Suk Jin...what kind of a comment is that,
we're not easy like them?
That's coming out right away.
-We can do it this way.
-How?
Here I go again.
We are easy...easy...we're not easy...
-Hey.  You want to shoot a music video?
-That's really nice.
-1, 2, 3...
-We are easy...not...we are not easy...
Kwang Soo, you're not bad at singing.
We are easy...not...we are not easy...
We're going to win today...
Here it is, here it is.
Running Man!
Let's go!
[What is the mission to obtain the radish?]
Look at the fog.
-It's fog.
-I thought it was sandy wind.
It's gloomy. It's weird here.
What kind of a mission is this?
What's that?
There's something up there.
Why is it so difficult to deliver
one bowl of black bean noodles?
It would've been so nice if you gave us
the sweet pickled radish earlier too.
What is with this water?
[Memory Game]
[To go find the same item].
Do you see the bungalows behind you?
There are 50 bungalows.
There is one item each in every one
of those bungalows.
What do you mean, yeah?
We have to discuss this with him, Jung Myung!
You can't be this accepting!
You are just too nice!
While one person has
their face dunked in the water,
The other 2...
See?  I told you this isn't the time
to be so agreeable!
While one person has their face submerged,
the other 2 go around with a joint bracelet.
And the two will go around and bring back
2 pairs of anything.
-Of the same thing?
-How do we find it out of the 50 bungalows?
[Each bungalow has a hidden item]
[Remember what each room has
to find the two items!]
[Only, one team member must last
while keeping his face in the water tank.]
[Then, they will get the radish.]
-Gary?
-Yes?
-Are you ready?
-Yes.  I'm ready.
Okay.  Then we're going to start.
Jae Suk.  You have to endure it even if
you have to drink the water.
Ready, set, go!
Basket and sunglasses.
-Basket and sunglasses.
-Basket and sunglasses!
Basket and sunglasses.
-Is it here?
-The basket!
Nice!  I'll carry it.  Let's go!
Sunglasses?
Basket and sunglasses.
Sunglasses!
I think he's done.
Basket and sunglasses.
Sunglasses!
I think he's done.
Director...I can't help but laugh.
-I was surprised...
-We did it!
I totally forgot to take a deep breath
before I dunked my face in.
Jae Suk...what happened?
We almost had a pair.
I was supposed to take a deep breath,
but I was in a rush and just went in.
Jae Suk!
Anyone who ordered black bean noodles?
-Is this the right place?
-Anyone who ordered black bean noodles?
There it is!
There it is.  They're doing something.
You have to take the biggest breath you can
before you dunk your head in!
I don't know if I was too rushed,
but I just went in.
-Jae Suk!
-Gary. Do a good job!
We have JYP who can hold
his breath a really long time.
I know he's really good at swimming too.
And JYP...your expression is
a bit different than this morning.
The reason for that is because he made
us a song called 'Easy Brothers'.
-Really?
-Yeah.
1, 2, 3.
We are easy...not...We are not easy...
It's going to be out on album soon,
please wait for it.
We are easy...not...We are not easy...
Since JYP is holding the song,
just you two try singing it.
Just you two.  Without JYP carrying the tune,
just the two of you do it.
We are easy...not...We are not easy...
Did you see?
Who are you trying to kid?
Look at that team.  Just look at their mood.
They're already angry.
-Just look at them.
-They're totally pissy.
-What are you doing right now?
-What's going on?
-With Jong Kook and JYP...
-JYP is a pro at submersion.
Watermelon and bamboo torch.
Why aren't you dunking your head in?
JYP...Yang Jang Pi.
Yang Jang Pi.
Choi Myung Pi!
JYP!  Chul Bi Pi!
Jung Myung, that was exquisite.
Endure it just a little bit longer!
Open it.
If it's not in there, just go.
Open it.  Open it.
-Open it..open it.  Not there.
-Open it.
Not there?  Open it.
No there?
Take a picture from the side.
It looks like a pod...
The thing on Star King that makes
the head looks bigger, right?
-It looks like that.
-That's what it looks like.
He's really under the water for a long time.
Where in the world is it?
-Not in here.
-Seriously...where is it?
-Not here.
-JYP!
-Yang Jang...Pi!
Yang Jang Pi...that was difficult.
How can you continue to keep making me laugh?
Didn't you see earlier?
You were in there a really long time.
You can't do it as long as
I thought you could.
Hey!
You try it.
The oxygen is totally gone from his voice.
Now...we'll show you how it's done.
Here he comes.  This guy is out now.
Jong Kook.  Drink the water.
If you can't do it, drink some of the water.
-Banana and toilet paper.
-Okay!
-Get on the water, Jong Kook.
-They're already back.
-They're already back, Jong Kook.
The moment his face lifts, it's over.
[The Tiger is bulging]
[An urgent Ha Ha and Ji Hyo]
Hey, your mouth looks like Jae Suk's.
Where?  Where is it?
Kwang Soo.  Say something.
Jong Kook.
Kim Jong Kook.
Jong Kook?
[The Tiger resurfaces from the water]
You heard that?
You heard?  You had your ears plugged.
I think he came out because he got mad.
I think I could've stayed another minute,
but came out because I got angry.
-What are you guys doing?
-There was almost a fight.
I have no idea where the sunglasses are.
JYP!  JYP!  JYP!
Pil-Chok-Speed-Cross!
If you don't want to do it, tell us.
Do it with some more vigor.
Can't you do it more vigorously?
What is this?
You guys ready?
-Wait...
-Ready, go!
Wait...the bracelet.
Basket and a plastic bowl.
What are they doing?
How do we do this here?
What is this?
Mr. Jin Suk Jin...that diamond in the rough..
The diamond we found after 2 years.
-It took too long, right?
-Yes.
I apologize to our viewers.
At least we found it.
-Hey.
-My shoulder.
How are we supposed to do this?
Just come this way...this way.
If we were on the same team with JYP,
we would've already found it.
-Straighten the arm out a little bit.
-Just come this way.
-It's the bamboo.
-Weren't we to get the plastic bowl?
-Isn't it a plastic bowl?
-Is that what we're supposed to find?
It's basket, and plastic bowl.
There's the plastic bowl.
The plastic bowl.
Suk Jin...my hand.
You should've grabbed my left hand.
He's out, he's out.
Can you do this?
Can you alert me at each 10 second interval?
10 seconds...10, 20..like that.
In counts of 10.
Jung Myung. You're the Ace in our team.
You're all we've got.
Doll and plastic bowl.
-You have to let me know, okay?
-Come on, get in.
Let me catch my breath.
-Come on!  Get in there!
-Hurry up!
-I have to get ready!
-Hurry!  1, 2, 3.
[Yoo Hyuk & Gary find one pair of dolls]
We just need the plastic bowls!
Jung Myung is going around in circles.
-What the heck is this?
-22 seconds.
One more.  Just one more!
Where do you think?
50 seconds.
-What the heck is this?
-His face!  It's out of the water!!
No!  That's not right!
His face came out of the water.
-His mouth came out of the water.
-You can't use this.
This makes no sense.
-Come on Jung Myung...seriously...
-This isn't right.
-This...wow...his mouth was out of the water.
-No, no...you pulled me out.
So I had no choice in getting pulled.
Let me make a request...
don't interrupt this time.
We're not going to do it.
-Go in there slowly.
-You can live under the water, Jong Kook.
Doll and plastic bowl.
Get in there, Jong Kook!
Where do you think you're going?
You can't go in there!
Come out of there. You can't...
there's nothing in there.
-Come on...
-I said, go away!
[Ji Hyo and Ha Ha have found one pair of dolls]
Come up here, Ji Hyo.
Run, run.
Ha Ha!  Over there!
-Hey!
-We got it!  We got all of them!
-Go away!
-Don't do it!
-Got it!  We did it!
-It's over!
Why are you acting like you're in a movie?
We thought about how you could come out
looking cool, didn't you?
I really thought I was going to die.
I'm not kidding!
You saw how I helped, right?
You're lying on my foot.  It hurts!
You were lying on her foot.
Just look at her foot!
We did it.
You succeeded within a minute.
-Awesome.
-You two really are the best.
As before, the sweet pickled radish
is one of these three dishes.
You have to carefully pick one.
1, 2, 3.
Open it.
If you go to a black bean noodle shop,
you usually get a sticker, right?
Yes, a coupon.
It's a coupon sticker.
If you don't collect 3 coupon stickers,
the customer isn't going to pay you.
So we're going to have to fight
no matter what, right?
Inside the car...
You have to put it on the back of
one of you inside the car.
Should we just put it on you since
anyone would be expecting that?
Make it obvious?
Or...you want to stick it on me,
and I can hide?
No matter, I think it would be best
to stick it on you.
But you fight better than me.
-It's been a minute and 30 seconds...
-Just a little bit longer.  Here it is!
Here it is!  we found it!
-We found it, we found it.
-Where's the other one?
A little bit longer! We found it!
-We found it!
-JYP!  We found it!
-Success!
Pil-Chok-Speed-Cross!
Speed-Cross!!
Look at what they're making the one
who's out of breath do.
-JYP...nice job.
-JYP.
Now the choosing...you do it, Kwang Soo.
Why not pick the middle on again?
We shouldn't change now.
[Yellow confetti!]
My eyes must be getting bad.
I thought it was the real thing.
While you're driving in the car,
put it on one of your backs.
I think only 1 person is going to
put it on their backs.
-What do you think we should do?
-If you put it on my back,
-I'm confident I won't have it ripped off.
-Really?
-You're strong.
-What do you think?
-He's name is Him Jin Young. (Strength)
-No matter what, put it on JYP's back.
I played American Football in school.
-Oh my God!
-JYP!
I played the running back.
Running back is running around with the ball
making sure it doesn't get taken away.
Sunglasses, and plastic bowl!
The easy one first.  Number 11!
Where was the plastic bowl?
Plastic bowl...plastic bowl was here.
What the heck is this?
Over there then.
Over there.  That way.
Was it on the other side?
Here's one.
There it is.
Jung Myung!  We got them all!
We got them all!
Jung Myung...!
-Jung Myung!
You should've said something on your way!
-When you were almost here...
-Jung Myung!
Jung Myung!
We told you we were almost there.
Why now of all time?
You should've said you were right here.
I thought you were way back there.
We were almost there like in the movies...
Let's do it again.  Again.
-Just give us the credit now.
-Give us the credit now?
Did I...save this one?
Yeah, you did save one.
You saved a jewel-like one.
But we should get going too now.
Even though it would be nice to save it here,
we have to get going too.
Doll and basket.
It's so hard to hold my breath...
Basket is in number 13.
This is too hard!
-Jung Myung!
-Endure it!
-It's in the back.
-The back?
Jung Myung!  We're almost there!
I think I got 50 seconds...
I only got 50 seconds.
I'm really sorry.
All we had to do was get back.
All we had to do was bring those back.
I endured 10 more seconds than the last time.
-This is something...
-I could've endured longer, but it was funny.
What was so funny?
I just imagined you guys running back.
You guys running back like this.
You laughed while imagining that?
Fighting, fighting.
We were the very first to arrive here.
I think you've forgotten that, Jung Myung.
I understand.
-We will...
-Doll and plastic bowl.
Which one first?
The closer ones or the further ones?
[Jung Myung just can't dunk his head in.]
You have to dunk your head in.
Hurry up and grab it.
Right next to it! Right here.
Right here.  The doll's here!
Plastic bowl.
-Plastic bowl!  Plastic bowl.
-Plastic bowl.
-One more.
-Where is the plastic bowl?
-In the third one!
Here.  Over here.
Jung Myung!  We got it!
Don't come up!
Jung Myung!  Jung Myung!
Jung Myung!  Please!
Jung Myung!
Did we get it?  Did we get it?
Got it...we got it.
Even if we're last, I have no regrets.
Gary, good job.
Chun Jung Myung!  Chance!
Change.
Let it change to sweet pickled radish!
Lemon.
-This isn't pickled radish...
-This is my favorite.
[Blue Team]
[Real noodles, and real radish].
[Red Team]
[Real Chopsticks].
[Yellow Team]
[Nothing].
[Which team will be the one
to deliver the complete set?]
I want to ride the 4-wheeler.
Shall we ride the 4-wheeler?
[First team on the 4-wheel motorbike]
Awesome!
Over that bridge is Somoouido.
-We're awesome.
-Let's go!
[Now for the waiting grandfather's
black bean noodles...]
[Special delivery, authorized to use
4-wheel motorbikes to Somoouido]
-Is it too hard?  Are you okay?
-Yes, I'm okay.
First...we need to hide it.
Hiding it would be best.
What about this supermarket?
Hello, elder.
By any chance...
We have to hide this here...
We'll put it up there, but if Jae Suk comes,
If he asks for it,
I'll tell him 'I don't know'...
Of course!
-I don't know...
-Your senses are amazing!
-What are you talking about?
-I have no idea what you're talking about.
Then we'll just leave it in here, mother.
-If we put it up here...
-Nice, it's totally perfect.
[Hiding it in the box placed up there]
There's no way he'd know.
He'll have no idea!
-There's no way he'd know!
-Thank you so much, mother.
-Mother...but...
-I'm not stupid.
Thank you.
[Meanwhile, the red team with the real chopsticks]
-Aren't you Yoo Jae Suk?  I'm a fan!
-Yes, I am.
I was about to go out on a delivery.
This is nice...it's really picturesque.
[The red team walks over to Somoouido]
What is it?  Let's share!
We're not that tight anymore now.
I feel like you hid it somewhere around here.
Where did you hide it?
3, 4!
Ah, number 34?
-How can you tell them that?
-Such an easy hint like that?
How can you tell them that?
If by chance...if 3 teams go at it,
we can't go against one another.
You can't trust the other guys.
But he keeps his words.
You know who the biggest traitor is here?
It's him.
He's on the same team as us.
Let's get friendly for right now.
First, at least let's all meet up
and talk and have a conversation.
Isn't it possible for those 2 teams
to work together?
Yes, they could.
They usually work together with the team
that we're on.
Team with the weakest link in it.
That team has the chopsticks.
-Chopstick team.
-What are you guys doing over there?!
The other team is on the other side.
They're on the either side.
There they are...this is uncomfortable.
-Kwang Soo is over there!
Kwang Soo.
Hey, Kwang Soo!
Kwang Soo!
I don't have it, Jae Suk.
You're trying to ambush us,
but it backfired!
-Jae Suk! We can't get Kwang Soo yet!
-Why?
Wait, wait.
-You can't get him yet.
-Let's make an exchange.
-You can't get him yet!
-We want Kwang Soo!
-Wait, wait!
-Jae Suk, no!
-Don't worry about me!
[But why does the red team look more worried?]
Should I put it on my back?
-I'm...a little scared.
-Let's exchange.
Let's make the exchange.
Send him on the count of 3.
-1, 2, 3.
-Really?
Why were you standing over there?
I was just going my way.
I came along the side.
-Wow...that could've been big trouble.
-That was something.
We almost had the 'R' ripped off.
They got it?
You think JYP will make a move?
How do we solve this problem?
-Yoo Jae Suk, fighting!
-Ah yes, hello. Hello.
It's the grasshopper. The grasshopper.
He's good looking.  Are you serious?
There's Gary.  Gary is here too.
They're both here.
Just look at you and the way you're dressed...
You're a handsome boy.
-Is it Gary?
-Yes! You're right, father!
I'll do my best!
-Gary is here!
-Thank you, father.
You're a total handsome boy
that looks casual too!
-Handsome boy!  Thank you, father.
-You look like you're 20 years old.
Goodbye, elders.
Please, stay healthy!
I'm really torn here.
Let's have a discussion.
If we were to go one on one,
who would we have a better chance against?
We have to think this carefully.
I think we should team up with the red team,
and get rid of Jong Kook.
If we were to get rid of Jong Kook,
then it would help us greatly.
You know how Jong Kook thinks
we're working together with him right now?
Then this is the chance to tear
the tag off his back right now.
This is the only chance we have.
It means we have to
get rid of the biggest one.
Hey, hey!  This way!
This way!  Come this way!
This way guys!
Here! They're here!
They're here!
We got them cornered!
[Jung Myung, in Jujitsu form!]
-Are you two team working together?
-We're not working together.
Your form is out now. It's out.
[Ingrained in his mind is the
basic Jujitsu form.]
[Ha Ha, in an exorcism position]
[Jae Suk's Grasshopper Tactic]
[Finally...Jong Kook vs. Jung Myung!]
[Confrontation between Jujitsu black belt
and the Commander!]
Help Jung Myung.  Help Jung Myung!
[Clashing of Red Team and Blue Team]
-Jong Kook!
-What's this?
-You're going to regret this later.
-Whose name should I tear off?
What are you doing?
[Jin Young decides to go after Jong Kook!]
[Except...!]
I got Suk Jin.
-Who tore it off?
-He did!
Without even realizing it...
I got excited.
Race has started now.
Race has finally started.
Now everyone...the race has started!
(Joke=When Suk Jin's out, the race stars)
Suk Jin is definitely cool.
His name was torn off.
Because of the yellow team,
it's so confusing.
For the first time in Running Man,
my leg was tripped.
Jung Myung tried to trip my leg.
You can't do that.
You can't use your legs.
I understand.
JYP.  Work together.
Work together for right now.
Where are you, Suk Jin?
Seeing from afar, I can see better.
Work together with them.
From the clouds...
from the clouds up in the sky...
[Hear my words...]
JYP, work together with them for right now.
And get rid of Yoo Jae Suk.
Seek my vengeance and get rid of Jae Suk.
Since there's a girl,
it's 2 against 2 right now.
I'll tell you...I'll tell you.
Until they're gone, I won't go against you.
The reason why is, since the red team
took Suk Jin, I want to get rid of them.
-Okay.
-You guys get rid of Yoo Jae Suk!
I told you I can see it well
from afar here.
-Where did they hide the delivery box?
-I know. I'd feel better once we find that.
That's what I'm saying.
-Jung Myung.  Just stay still!
-What are you doing?
You want to have a go right now?
-No.
-I want to go up against them right now.
I'm itching to do it!
["There you are, Red Team! Then..."]
[As far back as possible before the take down...]
Where am I right now?
I'm lost.
It's really windy out here.
[On the other side looking for Jae Suk - Yellow Team]
["I'll be there!"]
["Where's the remainder of the red team?"]
Is it Jung Myung or Gary that's
hiding behind that wall?
-Where?
-Over there next to you.
Over here?
Come out here...come out here.
You have a long shadow!
It's not Jung Myung or Gary.
What did you say?
[Actually Kwang Soo, Jae Suk is purposely
trying to get rid of the smoke!]
I feel really trapped in this tight alleyway.
Kwang Soo...
-I'm going crazy here...
-I don't know what to do.
What are you doing?
What's going on?
Up there.  He's going up there.
[Ha Ha and Kwang Soo aim for Jae Suk!]
[Gary's attack on Kwang Soo fails with the wind]
[Each of them have too many close calls]
Who did you get?
Who were you trying to get?
You were trying to get me!
Gary!  That slum...!
-JYP!
-Awesome!
-Jung Myung's in here.
-Jung Myung!
[Outside, the door is locked!]
-Gary!  Gary!
-No!  You can't!
-You can't!
-Jung Myung!  Jung Myung!
-You can't!  You can't!
-Get him!
-There's Jung Myung!
-You're both out?
Because Jung Myung wasn't here,
things went well like this.
We totally failed.
Jung Myung...you have no choice
but to team up with us now.
Should I?  Want to do it together?
-You guys are switching too easily.
-3 against 3.
He says it's 3 against 3.
When we have a girl here.
-This is really...
-But we're not sneaky about it.
Come here, Kwang Soo.
The most important thing is,
get rid of Jong Kook first.
So you have to block the other 2.
If you block Ha Ha, and Ji Hyo,
as long as you can block them,
I think we could get Jong Kook.
This meeting...let's call this an Ace meeting.
A-C-E-Cross!
Jung Myung's coming.  Jung Myung's coming.
JYP!  Fighting!
Wow...this is really hard.
There are 3 guys over there...
With 3 guys there...
Hyungnim!  Let's not be that way!
Kwang Soo!
Where did Kwang Soo go?
You have to be careful of Kwang Soo.
["Where did he go...?!"]
JYP!  JYP!
Ji Hyo!  Ji Hyo!
How do we do this?
Wait...wait a minute...
Come on...wait.
Kwang Soo!
What are you doing?  What are you doing?
Come here Kwang Soo.  Come here.
No, Kwang Soo!
Don't do it!
[They combined forces to get the strongest
one out, but it wasn't enough...]
Kwang Soo!
-Kwang Soo!  Kwang Soo!
-Awesome.  Awesome!
You have to be careful of the giraffe!
Watch out for the giraffe!
Where did he go?
Kwang Soo's not someone
who can just sit still.
Kwang Soo.  Rip Jung Myung's name off.
That is your job.
Hey, what are you doing?
Are you playing with me?
Chun Jung Myung, out.
-Lee Kwang Soo...seriously...
-Giraffe...seriously!
I'm sorry!
I know you're lying.
You just wait 'til next week.
JYP.  You're going to regret it now.
Why did he do that?
I can't understand this kid.
How fun would it have been if he worked
together and got Ha Ha together?
I think he may really be dumb...
There could have been so many
different scenarios.
I knew he would do something like this.
Jung Myung's really angry right now.
Jung Myung said right now, 'There could've
been so many different scenarios'
Kwang Soo.  In your heart...
I'm sure you're going to have the thought
to rip off my name tag here and there...
But you have to
think that carefully, Kwang Soo.
I don't betray my own team member.
But thoughts like that could
flit across your mind.
-You have to endure it.
-I understand.
When you see my name tag,
you have to think about it carefully.
Can you see the tiger's skin there?
It wouldn't be good if only
your skin remained either, right?
-I gave you a break this time.
-Thank you, Jong Kook.
Where are you going?
-Jong Kook.
-Yes?
Let's go up one against one.
How about Ha Ha against Kwang Soo?
Let me discuss this with him.
Don't you think this is too silly?
But if you're that afraid of Kwang Soo,
then forget it.
Get out here, Ha Ha!
This is going to be very curious!
Hey...Running Man's viewers
are really going to be curious about it.
Seriously...I can't believe this is happening.
Chok-Speed-Cross!
Come here...lift your head...
Come here.  Turn around.
Wake up.
Look at me!  Come here!
[Haroro vs. Giraffe!]
-Wait a minute...
-Maybe I should do it.  I'm so nervous!
Ha Ha.  If you lose this,
you're Running Man's weakest link.
-Stand.
-I'm going to pick some pebbles first.
-There's glass here too.
You're not going to fall...
-I'll give you one more chance.
-Nice, nice.
Kwang Soo...
I promised myself that I wouldn't get rough...
I'm sorry, mother.
For the last time,
I'm going to be a little rough.
Hey, are you ready?
[Man vs. Man
A symbol of strength, hand-to-hand combat!]
[Clearly these two are doing
absolutely everything they can.]
[These two men are quite serious]
If they keep that up,
will they become windmills?
What are they doing right now?
That hurts!
He's biting me!
Hey!
[Oh? Kwang Soo uses force?]
[The weakest link is determined!]
[Now the Final Showdown!]
Did you get it?
I lost!  I lost to the giraffe!
Customer who ordered the black bean noodles!
Black bean noodles is here.
-Hello.
-Hello, sir.
It took too long, didn't it?
-This is what I have to pay you.
-Thank you!
[Golden Chopsticks]
Thank you for delivering it.
Father, enjoy it, and let us know if you
need more delivered.  We'll bring it again.
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Next Week-6 o'clock].
[10 hour non-stop chase].
[The toughest race in Running Man history].
The member that you want to eliminate...
[And...]
[Those girls identities are...]
[The definitiveness of
conspiracy and betrayal]
[We welcome you to Running Man's
survivor game].