[The questionable man with his eyes
on Running Man...]
[His identity is...]
Today you are...
A beast with his eyes set on the Princess.
[Beast Yoo Joon Sang]
[Remotely out?]
[The beast is on the move]
Subtitles by DramaFever
[On the other hand, at Seogang Bridge]
Everyone look at the camera.
[Right before the filming started]
[The youngest Giraffe's slate]
1, 2, 3...!
[It's the funniest when the Giraffe is scared]
-I think there's something going on today.
-I will tell you about today's race.
-Is Ji Hyo not here today?
-Today's race is 'The Princess Race'.
[The Princess race]
If you look at the parasol's over there...
Underneath it are your princesses.
[Only once the princess chosen accepts them,
can they succeed this mission]
Start!
[Jae Suk-Kwang Soo, Jong Kook-Suk Jin,
Ha Ha-Gary, off to escort their princess!]
-There are so many parasols!
-There are so many of them!
Our mission this time...
[Behind the first parasol...]
[Behind the first parasol is... The writer]
What are you doing?
Seriously, what are you guys doing?
[Princess, where are you?]
-He Young... Work... Just go back to work.
-Isn't that your stylist?
[Ha Ha's stylist escaping the sun?]
[This person is...?]
[Older sister No Sa Yeon?!]
[Passing right away?]
Oh my goodness... We got the wrong one!
-There's no one here... Where is she?
-Oh my... It's really hot out today!
-Just where is the Princess?  Where is she?
-Hey!!
Why did they just walk pass me?
[Just moving on without even glancing back]
I don't even believe it...
I thought the concept today was Princess...
[Huh...?]
[Lee-Yoo brothers discover a princess?]
[A real Princess, Shin Se Kyung]
[Shocked]
What is this?
-You're here!
-Se Kyung... When did you get here?
How can this be?
Hey! Se Kyung is here! Se Kyung!
-It's Se Kyung!
[Two very excited children]
Who did you say?
Do it with us!  Be on our team!
Let's go somewhere else.  We can't.
[The Tiger and Impala give up right away]
[Starting to woo her]
Se Kyung!  Look at how sexy we are!
-Look at us!
-Kwang Soo!  Show her!
[Giraffe busting out his jerky dance moves]
[Displeased]
Se Kyung... Give us your hand.
-I just saw Sa Yeon on my way down here.
-You did?
-Jae Suk... Jae Suk...
-No way!
-Really?  Sa Yeon is here?
-Someone is going to have to team up with her.
-So we pretended not to see her.
-We came down and acted like we never saw her.
[Those little...]
[The 2 teams desperate for her selection]
-If you've ever felt disappointed...
-What are you doing?
[The humiliating rebuff]
Hey, Kwang Soo!
-I thought you two were close!
-Come on...
[Ice Princess Se Kyung with her eye on victory.
Just who will her selection be?]
Se Kyung...
[Chooses the 2 kids, Ha Ha and Gary!]
-Hurry up and get to Sa Yeon!
-Se Kyung, thank you...
Thank you so much... Seriously...!
[Ha Ha, Gary, Se Kyung-One team]
-Ah hello...
[So ultimately...]
What's wrong with you guys...
-Why are you acting so uncomfortable?
-No, not at all!
-Why aren't you acting glad to see me?
-No, it's not like that at all!
-What happened to the others? Where's Ha Ha?
-Ha Ha already has his team.
[Kiddie subjects enamored with their princess]
-I shouldn't have come on today.
-Don't say that.  Please be a team with us.
-Please will you be on our team?
-It's been 2 years since I've seen you.
-Will you please be on our team?
-What are you going to do for me if I do?
-Are you going to feed me until I'm full?
-I've brought $30 today.
[The goal is more than food?]
-You remember the throne, right?
-You know who won that, right?
-I was the one who won that.
-I'll become your adorable dog!
-Like your very own poodle...
-Why do you look so sad?
I'm going to go with these guys.
[Princess Sa Yeon chooses Yoo-Lee]
It's because of Gary!
[Why Gary?]
-Wait...
-I'm not Gary.  I'm Kwang Soo!
Kwang Soo... That's what I meant.  Kwang Soo.
[Jae Suk-Kwang Soo-Sa Yeon.
Anyways, they're now team Princess Sa Yeon]
-Where are we running to?
-Over here.
-Everyone has their Princess now...
-Yes.
We will now start the princess race
with your respective princess.
Each of the 2 males subjects on each team...
Will have to pass each course while
escorting your princess.
The team to come in last on the mission...
You'll have to choose one of the cases
which has one person's name tag in it
Please pick one of those and give it to us.
The last team to have arrived is
Princess Song Ji Hyo's team.
[Team Song Ji Hyo's who were the last to
gather their team is to pick]
-Come on...
-We don't even know whose name is in it?
You won't know what it is until later...
-Just give him whatever... This one.
-That one?
-Then bring it to me please.
-I'll give it to him.
-Just stand down... Stand down.
-Who do you think you are?
We'll take this one... This one.
[The case selection is up to the princess...]
-We don't have to do it... We arrived second.
-We'll take a look and see.
[Just whose name tag will be in there?]
It would be really funny
if it was Ji Hyo's name.
[Song Ji Hyo]
[Oh my! Princess Ji Hyo's name tag!]
-It would be really funny if it was Ji Hyo.
-I know.  It would be funny if it's me.
[How will this chosen name tag be used later?]
-We can't find out who it is?
-Of course not. You definitely can't.
-Then what happens to that name tag?
-You'll find that out later.
-Then watch the broadcast later!
-Why are you so curious about everything?
-They'll keep that name tag a secret for now...
-I told you to just go along with the flow...!
It's been 2 years! 2 years!
Princess No Sa Yeon... Do you understand?
Huh?
Well... I did hear what he said...
It's not that hard.  We'll be fine
as long as we don't come in last.
[Bingo! All they have to do is
make sure they're not last!]
...Please change into your
team uniforms and we'll get started.
[Off to the Princess Race's first location!]
You have to leave those...
[Put those down...]
Please just leave those... Leave those.
Take them?
[They'll gradually start to get it... Right?]
[Princess race... Start!]
It's an honor to see you after all this time.
It's an honor.
Kwang Soo... You pulled the chair up
so much that your knees are up to your chin.
I'm fine.  I'm comfortable.
-That's the least that you could do...
-Princess... They want us to come to Hongdae.
-What?
-Hongdae.
[Escort the Princess to Hongdae
and find the Running Man's landmark]
This is the first time we've worked together,
right Kwang Soo?
[Team Princess Sa Yeon's first time
teaming up with the giraffe]
Anyways, what is your IQ?
-How tall are you? 190 cm?
-Yes, I'm 190 cm tall.
I may not know correctly, but I think you
can assume his IQ to be half his height.
Come on... Then you're saying my IQ is 80?
What do you mean 80?  How is that 80?
-How is that 80?
-Oh my... seriously...
What you weren't able to do
on the Queen Bee Race last time...
I'll make sure that it happens today.
Yeah, that was too waste of a loss...
And also... I don't know what the
winner's prize is today, but gold...
-Gold?
-Yes.
[Prize as of late is gold...]
[Now this is starting to sound great!]
-Real gold is...
-Yes, it is.
-The purity is 99.9%
-Yes.
-Gold with 99.9% purity.
-Real gold.
We have to... No matter what happens...
Even if the world comes to an end,
I'm going to take that gold home.
You got it?  Jae Suk you have to help...
And you help too.  Got it?
Yes, I understand.
Se Kyung... Did you shoot a movie?
Yes.  It's a movie that I shot last year.
I shot the movie with Rain...
But since he went off to the army...
No matter... Welcome.
-Thank you.
-Welcome to the Flower Boy team.
Anyway, Se Kyung...
Let's get first place today!
-Yes.
-Okay.  Let's all say 'Fighting!'
-Since Se Kyung is competitive...
-I think I need to be cautious about that.
-Why?
-I watched the one when I was on last...
-And I looked like a crazy wildcat...
-No...
So that's why Se Kyung
is being so quiet today!
A little, yes...
Even though you think otherwise...
You can't help but be
competitive on Running Man.
-Right?
-Yeah.  That's just a given.
-There's nothing I can do about that...
-Of course...
Actually, we've been coming in first
since the beginning of today.
-That's right, that's right...
-We have to keep that going.
[Not having any other choice than to
revert back to the wildcat to win...]
[But... You know that you're
going the wrong way, right?]
Huh?  This is the place.
-Oh!  There it is!
-Where?
-Running Man.
-Here it is, here it is!
[Discovers the Running Man landmark]
Princess...
Excuse me?  Ah... Princess?
We're going to change your name tag.
[Switching out the Princess' name tag
that befits her status]
Please be gentle...
So that he doesn't get hurt.
The crown suits you.
-You remember the Queen Bee race, don't you?
-Yes.
This is the Princess Race that's
an upgraded version of the Queen Bee race.
That's why...
We're going to do the Princess marble.
Princess marble?
-Do you see the start mark here?
-Yes.
Inside the street is the finish mark.
There are different points
in between the lines.
If you finish your missions at those points
and get to the finish line, you succeed.
[Pass all the points]
-It's like a game then.
-Yeah, it is.
-Fighting.
-Fighting!
[Tour the eateries with the Princess]
[But if the Princess' feet touch
the ground on the way, you fail]
-We have to carry them around?
-This game was made for you...
Her feet can't touch the ground!
-Her feet can't touch the ground...
-Her feet really can't touch the ground?
-This reminds me of the race last year...
-We already did this last year!
But you have a different partner this time.
If the Princess' feet touch the
ground on the way, we fail.
[Chaotic mission starting line]
[Anyways, off to 'R1'... Go!]
Sa Yeon... Don't worry.
I'll make sure your feet definitely
doesn't touch the ground!
-We'll do out absolute best!
Sa Yeon... Sit down here.
-Oh... Here?
-You can just sit down here.
[Princess Sa Yeon's grandeur that
can be felt with their whole body]
-Okay?
-Wait...
[Giving up the throne?]
I'll give it up!
What are you giving up already!
-What are you saying you're giving up?
-I'm sorry.
Sa Yeon... I think piggyback would be better.
[Ultimately, a piggyback ride?]
My feet can't touch the ground...
You two can switch off.
Since we have to get going quickly...
Hold onto my hand... Hold onto my hand!
-Wait...
-Hold onto my hand, Jae Suk.
Sa Yeon...
You've gotten much lighter than a year ago.
-Your face is totally beet red!
-No, no...
[Off to 'R1' with the Princess]
Sa Yeon is really light.
-I'm light, right?
-Yes.
1, 2, 3.  Jump on.
-Let's go.
-She is so light!
I feel like I have a backpack on.
A light backpack!
[This one is...]
It's here... This is it...
-Sa Yeon, it's here.
-Jae Suk, the first round...
-Jae Suk!
-Here it is.
Jae Suk!
Ji Hyo feels like a backpack on my back.
You just keep quiet!
Jae Suk!
If you let her down,
you're disqualified immediately.
-Really?
-You'll each...
Just wait, Jae Suk...
Get him some water!
-I wasn't going to laugh...
-You're much lighter than you were last year.
I'm really hurt right now...
Sa Yeon... You're much lighter now!
You really have gotten lighter...
There are total of 8 points to finish.
-You'll be okay, right?
-Yes... I'm fine.
Wipe up his sweat for him.
Can't you hurry up and give us the mission?
It's because I...
Want to get the game going quickly!
Give it to me quickly.
[A collision accident]
Sa Yeon... Your butt's in my way!
-How dare you speak that way to a Princess!
-Because she was in the way!
Her butt hit Jong Kook's face!
I saw that myself.
I'm a witness to that...
Let's sue them!
I'm the witness.
-To a Princess...
-She backed into me!
Out of these three...
Please pick one of them.
[Pick one out of these three]
-This will tell you which point you can go to.
-Really?!
[There's a note contained with each dish that
will alert you to which point to go to]
-Once you all of it, it'll tell you where.
-Okay, I understand.
-Princess, please pick one.
-One of those three.
-This one...
-Yes, we'll take that one.
[Princess Sa Yeon's selection is the
bean paste stew to the far left]
-That one.
-This one?  We'll take this one please.
[Princess Ji Hyo's selection is the
bean paste stew to the right]
-Go ahead...
-Just eat it?
-We can eat it too, right?
-We have to eat it quickly.
[Even though they don't know the information
that is hidden in the food...]
[The mission can wait until after the food]
Ah... This is so nice
since I didn't even get to eat breakfast.
How are you guys doing?
Is it good?
Sa Yeon!  There's something here!
[Huh?  On the bottom of the stew bowl?]
[+1 number!]
-Plus 1!
-This is 'R1', right?
-Yes.
-Then it means, you can go to 'R2'.
But then... Isn't this the worst there is?
-That means there are more...
-So it means that you're moving up one spot.
-One spot...
-Do you think we don't already know that?
Seriously, you are...
[General Kook with his teachings...]
Jong Kook, there's something here.
[Princess Se Kyung's team finally arrives]
What to do?!
-If the feet touches the ground...
-Well... Se Kyung's light as a feather, right?
Since the day she was born,
our Se Kyung had a nice figure...
-Even without exercising...
-She has no fat...
I have a lot of fat!
Since she doesn't gain weight
even when she eats a lot
she'll be very light.
But her personality is that of a wildcat.
Yes.  A sensitive and crazy wildcat!
[Princess Sa Yeon's procession]
[A Princess' procession that draws
a sigh from the crowd gathered around]
-The weather today is so nice and cool...
-A little bit more... Just a little bit...
-Just like this...
-Wow... It's so far away.
I think I'm going to throw up...
I think I'm going to throw up, Jae Suk.
[Vomit inducing lady chair]
Want to ride the motorcycle for a bit?
[As long as her feet doesn't touch the ground,
everything else counts as her bench]
-I don't know whose it is, but...
-I'm sorry... Just for a bit.
-You look so cool...
-It really suits you.
It really...
-Looks good.
-Wait...
[A motorcycle rest for the royal photo shoot?]
It's because...our wrists are a little weak.
We're really strong everywhere else,
it's just our wrists.
-I don't know who the owner of this bike is...
-Thank you...
-Just for a bit, our princess...
-Without a choice...
It's a photo shoot to commemorate...
So please understand.
1, 2, 3... Yes, we've got it.
-Since my feet can't touch the ground...
-Of course, not.
All we did was to come around the corner
from over there...
The sweat is pouring down your face...!
[Scared that the Princess may get hurt]
I've got the back of it now.
-Is anyone here?
-Get a good spot... Get a good spot, Suk Jin.
Hey, I bet there's another one
on the bottom again.
-I think that spot would be good.
-Over there?  Okay.  Let's take that one.
['R2's food is a rich spaghetti carbonara]
I bet Ji Hyo gets the Princess treatment
everywhere she goes.
Why don't you make me a bite
and feed it to me?
-You can feed yourself.
-If you don't, I'm putting my foot down here.
-Here, here, here... Eat it.
-I'm putting my foot down.
[Obeying as soon as she threatens]
I'm envious of you.
-Since our arm hurts, shall we piggyback her?
-Should we?
[Princess Sa Yeon's team with their weak arms
is getting ready to take off]
[Giraffe with Princess Sa Yeon on his back]
Please move!  Everyone, please move!
[Giraffe racing off to 'R2']
We're here.
[Finally arriving at 'R2']
Just where did Se Kyung's team go?
Hey.  Why is your face so red?
-Because I feel so bashful...
-Look at the sweat on your nose!
It's because I got a little sun burned.
We're all done!
[Princess Ji Hyo's team completes their food]
[Moving right onto 'R4' after picking +2]
[On the other hand,
Princess Sa Yeon's team is...]
Why are you shaking like a leaf like that?
I keep seeing the number!
I keep seeing bits and pieces of the number!
[The dish that keeps hinting at the number]
There's no way that it could be -1, right?
It's not like this is a joke...
[The more they eat, the more nervous they are
wondering if they'll have to retreat]
If this is a minus, you have to
tell them forcefully that you'll walk.
-You can't just sit back and do nothing.
-Throttle them or something.
-But it is pretty delicious.
-Yeah, it's delicious.
-Ha Ha's team is just passing by.
-What?  Why?
They ate a dish with +2 at the first stop.
R3?  Do we just go to R3?
[Princess Se Kyung's team finds +2 at 'R1']
-We can't do the whole plus thing.
-Why?
We have to go one by one.
-It's really tough on you, right?
-No, it's okay.
-It's not a problem.
-You're light.
Where in the world is R3?
There it is!  R3!
We found it!
[Arriving at the octopus restaurant]
-Just a little bit more!
-We're here!
-It does taste good.
-We're done.
-Here
-It's minus one.
-You have to go back to R1.
-What?
Please stop eating...
Thank you for the food!
[Back to R1...]
[Ji Hyo arrives at R3 after picking minus 1]
[This is the sweet and spicy
baby octopus specialty shop]
-Hurry up and come on...
-I can't eat very spicy things.
You think that I can handle that?
[Princess Ji Hyo doling out food
without hesitation]
Hey, it's spicy.
-It's spicy?
-Yeah.  It's really good, but spicy.
[Getting hotter by the second]
I really can't handle spicy food!
Princess!
[The princess keeps doling out the spicy dish]
You have to eat it too.
Please don't put too much
sauce on it, Princess.
-I'm going to have to eat that with rice.
-I get the hiccups when I eat spicy food.
-Here  Eat another to stop your hiccups.
-I'm not done with this bite yet.
-I'm not done yet!
-Hurry up and eat it.
-Wow... That's spicy.
-I feel it now.
[Automatic dance time
thanks to the baby octopus]
[Princess Sa Yeon's team arrives at R3]
Hey!  Wow... This is seriously...
-You're here!
-Wait...
-Isn't there any water?  Water?
-It must be really spicy.
-Wow... This really is good...
-It's really good... But so spicy!
Do we just eat this now?
It's spicy.
But that's the attraction of this dish.
It's good.  It's good, but...
-Isn't it good?
-It really is delicious!
Eat the seaweed... Eat lots of seaweed.
[Giraffe falling into stupor...]
Here, drink this.
[What?  The spicy sauce?]
[About to cry...]
Jong Kook... Do you see the fire coming out?
[The dance time that comes
after eating the baby octopus]
You feel it... You feel it, right?
Me too... I kept walking around too!
But you keep wanting to eat it, right?
[So hot!!]
-Can you please give us some water?
-There's water over there.
Just a little bit...
You have two bottles of water.
[One belongs to the giraffe on fire]
[Barely finishing off the baby octopus]
-What does it say?
-Plus one.
We're finished too.
It's plus one.
[Ji Hyo's team also gets plus one]
Off to R4!
Thank you for the meal.
-Wow... So hot!
-Sa Yeon... Don't worry.
Let's go!
-Jae Suk... Gather your strength.
-I've build up some resilience now.
You've built up resilience.
-Now that we've found a way...
-It's not too bad now, right?
-Gather your strength!  Your strength!
-Yes.
[Princess Ji Hyo's team on the chase]
Jae Suk.  Jong Kook is behind us.
Jong Kook?  Get up your strength!
-Move!
-Let's go this way.
[Keep advancing in that direction?]
There it is!  There's R5!
[R5?]
Jae Suk!  Over there!  There!
We passed R4!
[Difficult to go back in reverse
on resilience alone]
Sa Yeon... You want to try riding this?
Try to pick a good one...
-You have to pick the right one...
-We can end up eating the octopus again!
[R4's dish is shaved ice with red beans]
Just no baby octopus...
[Princess Sa Yeon's team that barely
doubled it back]
You're weak going up the stairs...
You're weak when it comes to that.
It's shaved ice with red beans!
Don't you think
the smallest one would be best?
The biggest one?
[Team Ji Hyo's choice is...
The one to the furthest right]
-You're confident about this one, right?
-I'm confident this time.  Let's eat it!
-Princess...
-Wait... This one?  Let's pick this one.
[After the selection of the dish...
[The cherry goes straight
into Sa Yeon's mouth]
Sa Yeon...
I'll plant this in the front yard at my house.
This cherry will be the cherry of labor...
Hurry up and eat it.
[The icy sweet taste of shaved ice
that chases away the heat]
-I think we're almost done...
-I can see something!
I can that it's one of some kind...
Hurry up and drink it...
Hurry up and drink it!
[Advance one!]
-You guys are going to be minus...
-You're going to be minus!
[How do they know?]
I just have a feeling that it is.
-How would you know to say that?
-Just that the chances of it are high.
You want those to be your dying words?
Please forgive us.  We're sorry.
-Shall we get going then?
-Let's get going.
We really got lucky...
[Ji Hyo's team advancing to final R5!]
-The last one...
-I'll finish it up.
[Sa Yeon's team left to check the number]
It can't...possibly be, right?
-There's no way that it can be.
-No... No, it won't be.
-Jae Suk!
-Hey!
[Sees something?]
[Still as a statue?]
I haven't looked yet.
Can we eat one more?
Why is our team...
It's minus one again?!
[Sa Yeon's team... Minus one reverse!]
-We have to go back and...
-The spicy...?!
The spicy...?!
[Princess Se Kyung's teams experiencing
spicy baby octopus for the second time]
Is it raining in here right now?
It's so spicy!
[Ha Ha acting all cute]
[Handing over a piece of seaweed
to Princess Se Kyung as well...]
Audience, will this actually be possible?
[Will it be possible to advance this time?]
We're almost done.  Eat it quickly.
Oh!  I can see something.
We're finished eating it.
Nice and clean, right?
[Princess Se Kyung's team
advance 2 spots!]
-Thank you for the meal!
-Thank you!
Wow!  They got a minus!  A minus!
[Princess Sa Yeon's procession
going back in reverse]
-We're here.
-This is the last one...
[The finish line is right
in front of their nose!]
-This is...
-It's doshirak!  Wait...
From here...
-Are you just giving this to us?
-You have to choose one.
We can't get minus 2 here.
If that happens,
we have to go back to the baby octopus.
[Princess Se Kyung's team also arrives]
I thought I was going to die with that one.
-Wasn't that baby octopus so spicy?
-Okay... We're here!
-Pick one, Ji Hyo.
-This one?
-I don't know... You pick it.
-Okay.  We've picked one.
[Princess Ji Hyo's team completes
choosing their doshirak]
I just hope that we don't get a minus!
Eenie-meenie-miney-mo!
-Which one shall I pick?
-This is the last stop of Princess marble.
[Princess Se Kyung taking R5 very seriously]
-They're both the same!
-What is your phone number?
010...?
[Phone number?]
My number is 010...
And yours is?
-Hurry up and punch your number.
-I'll go with this one.
Punch in your number.
It's a minus...
[Ji Hyo's team is already done eating?]
[Ah...]
I guess you can come back
after cleansing off your palate.
How many times do we need to
cleanse our palate?
How many times do we need to eat
shaved ice in one day?
-Eat and dessert, eat and dessert...
-How many times do we need to eat dessert?
[Sa Yeon's team in the process of
eating the spicy baby octopus]
[No longer even saying anything...]
It's a plus. A plus.
[Oh!  Advancing 2 spots!]
[Princess Se Yeon's team heading off
to final R5 spot!]
There it is!  We'll finish this!
One, two... Keep heading onward!
But why is it that... When we pass by...
All the bystanders are clapping for us?
Why do you think that is?
I mean there are other teams too...
But why only when our team passes by...
-Is it plus 2?
-Did you get plus 2?
We got plus 2!
[Princess Sa Yeon's team finally enters R5]
Paper-rock-scissors!
-Yes!
-Paper-rock-scissors!
Paper-rock-scissors!
[Princess Se Kyung's team
with one last bite remaining]
Jae Suk, are you okay?
Have you been off hiking somewhere?
You look like you've been hiking...
[Butler Jae Suk left in a pant]
[Finishing off the last bite]
Plus!
You pass in first place!
[Princess Se Kyung passes the round!]
[So excited!]
[Even Princess Se Kyung is shaking her hips]
-I'm so full...
-Finished!
-We finished it!  We finished it!
-I knew this would happen, but still...
[Escort the princess to the swimming pool
by Han River and find Running Man's landmark]
-Okay!  To the pool!
-Okay.
-But... What do we do at the swimming pool?
-Swim.
Let's go!
There's a plus one and minus one left.
[Only minus one and plus 1 left at R5]
[The team that picks minus 1
automatically comes in last]
[The last team will have to
pick a name case here]
-We get to pick one first, right?  Princess?
-Of course.
Which one would you like to pick?
As long as we don't get minus one here...
-It's the same thing as placing first.
-This one?
[Princess Sa Yeon choosing one
with conviction]
I'll trust your luck on this one.
-We trust you.
-Please let this be plus one.
[Princess marble's last meal...
Just who will be the losing team?]
Hey... I can see the number one,
but I don't know if it's minus or a plus.
-We now only have the middle part left.
-Yes... We covered it with the egg.
[Would it be plus one?  Or minus one?]
We did the same thing... Should we see?
1... 2... 3...!
[Just which one of the team will be plus one?]
Sa Yeon... You did great...
You definitely had the eye for it...
[Light shining down on
Princess Sa Yeon's luck]
[Crying?]
Then do we have to pick again?
[Princess Ji Hyo's team having to
pick again twice in a row]
But the team won't dissipate
if we keep going like this, right?
-Which one shall we pick?
-Why are there so many?
-I guess those two are ours.
Princess, please pick.
We've been in this situation
for not having picked the left one...
-So why don't we pick the one to the left?
-Okay.  Let's do that.
Let's go with that one.
-We have to give it to you?
-Please give it to us.
Then we only have 1 left?
Just a moment...
We're going to look for ourselves.
[That name is... Ji Suk Jin!]
You'll find out in a little bit what role
this will be playing.
I'm sure it'll be something bad.
Jae Suk!!
[The beast with his eyes on the Princess]
[His unknown attack]
[What is their fate?]
Everyone... Look at me.
[90's Idol style?]
Foreign exchange student hairstyle?
I'm going to act as if I used to live in LA.
Hey... That's a total Jikiri style.
It's Jikiri hair!
[Singing casually after placing first place]
[Tiger JK's song seems perfect
for the situation?]
Don't you know hip-hop?
I'll try to learn.
Start from the beginning again.
-Come back to my world, yo!  Everybody...!
-Come on!
-Everybody...!
[Cutie hip-hop?]
So cute.
But why aren't you guys saying anything?
-Us?
-Yeah, you two.
We don't usually talk too much
while we're in the car.
-Really?
-Of course.
I'm really full... It's no joke.
[A rare moment of silence]
But why aren't there any responses
after saying something?
-It's weird... I think you guys are lying.
-We're not...
Of course, we're not.
We're here!  There's the landmark!
Se Kyung!
We have to keep being in first place, okay?
[A refreshing Han River swimming pool]
You have succeeded the first round
as the first place winners.
[Ceremony of happiness?]
What about me?
[So much fun!]
Hey, Se Kyung! Come in!
You just need to go in.
[Capping off their suffering
with a combination dance]
Se Kyung just did this move!
This is the second relay of the Princess Race.
[Cross the pool with the Princess on your back]
[Succeed once each person carries her on their backs]
Do you see what's over there?
[An extremely long water balance beam]
[This is the Princess Race's second relay]
[Huh?  Princess Ji Hyo's team's arrival?]
-Hurry, hurry, hurry!
-Did you get in second place?
-Second place is not bad.
-Hello!
-What's going on here?
-What is this?
-Hey!
-I'm Kang Ta from H.O.T!
That's totally H.O.T style!
So that I can fly freely...!
-Did you pass as second place?
-No.  We're in third place.
-Third place.
-But we arrived first.
-But the second place got lost on their way...
-They got lost.  There they are now.
[Looks as though they may have
gotten lost on their way?]
-Where do we go?
-Hello.
I think we can go this way.
[Princess Se Kyung's team
taking the challenge!]
You've got 30 seconds to do this!
Okay... We're going to start...
Get ready... Set...!
[Very unstable water balance beam]
[Huh?  But still doing pretty well...!]
[Arriving at the opposite end]
[They have to quickly get back
within 8 seconds...]
[Even though the time is over,
going to the end for next time]
[Even though he's slow,
he's slowly getting used to the walk]
40 seconds!
[With tiny little steps,
arriving at the starting line again]
[Princess Se Kyung's team fails to
complete within the allotted time]
How disappointing!
Jong Kook... Don't fall in!
[High anticipation for Mr. Capable and Ace]
[I'll show you all...!]
-You've got 30 seconds to complete it!
-Yes, we understand!
How did you cross this?
[The divine King of Games is Mr. Capable...!]
-How are you going to cross?
-How did you get across this?
If you're being like that,
how are we supposed to do it?
I don't think I can do it!
[Time is running out!]
What's wrong with him?
Are you sure that's Jong Kook?
-What's going on there?
-What the heck is he doing?
[Mr. Capable that used to
dominate Running Man...]
[Kneels down on the water balance beam...]
The way I see it, the yellow team
is about to lose all their name tags.
[Princess Ji Hyo's team in danger!]
-Kwang Soo... Fighting.
-I don't think I can cross it.
-Lee-Yoo!
-We miss you!
-If we fall off here, it's over for us.
-Think of it as a vat of boiling water.
Think of it as a pool of lava.
[Can't ever fall into it...]
-Fighting!
I guarantee...
You'll fall off within 10 seconds!
-You have no idea how light Sa Yeon is!
-I'm light!
-I swear... Keep your head on straight.
-I'm light!  I'm not heavy!
I'm much lighter than I look!
-Don't waste your energy on him.
-You're right.  I know I'm light.
[Princess Sa Yeon's team
taking up the challenge]
-Kwang Soo!
-Keep your head on straight!
-Keep your mind sharp!  We have to win!
-We're going to win this unconditionally!
You've got 30 seconds to complete it!
Get ready...!
[Butler Jae Suk showing fierce concentration]
[So far so good!]
[Arriving at the opposite end!]
Kwang Soo's going to fall in the water
within 3 seconds.
[Long legged giraffe's turn to cross]
[Ultimately falling in together...]
[Ha Ha right on the money!]
[You brat...]
[Princess Se Kyung's team's re-challenge!]
You've got 30 seconds.
Get ready...
[Gary showing off his skills at
crossing the water balancing beam]
[This unpredictable man that shows
surprising skills once in awhile]
[Switching off at a fast speed]
I came all the way here!
[Princess Sa Yeon team's re-challenge]
[Yoo-ruce Willis showing incredible speed
on the water balancing beam]
[Switching off at a lightning speed!]
Kwang Soo!!
[Will they win this way?]
[Huh?]
[Even though he's fallen in the water,
carrying Princess Sa Yeon to safety...]
[Just like Princess turtle getting
piggy-backed by a giraffe...]
[The way you hoist her up is a little...]
Is Sa Yeon a tuna or something?
[Princess Sa Yeon being hoisted up
as if she's tuna...]
I asked you if you think Sa Yeon's tuna!
[Do you think this is Noryanjin?]
Are you seriously going to be like this?
I'm sorry... Sa Yeon...!
This is all... Young Kwang Soo's fault.
[All of this is young Kwang Soo's fault...]
[Princess Sa Yeon regretting
having picked Kwang Soo]
I'll piggyback you across the beam.
[The Princess offering to piggyback
from not being able to stand anymore!]
[Re-challenge after switching up their roles]
Sa Yeon!  What are you doing?
Ready!  Get ready!!
Just go!  Just go!
[Throwing him in?]
[Falling in herself after a bit]
She just threw him in...
She just threw him in there...!
Okay... Here comes the tuna.
[Second harvesting of tuna]
[Even more difficult than last time
from being soaked to the bone this time?]
[The tuna that was caught with difficulty
by so many people...]
What are you doing hoisting her up like that?
[Ah... Goddess of laughter...]
You've only one chance left.
[State of crisis.
Ji Hyo team's re-challenge]
[Mr. Capable having shown a side of him
that's very unlike him]
[Is he used to it this time?]
You got it... You can do it.
[Charging at full speed to the other side]
[Big nosed brother going at a fast pace!]
[He's good!]
[Is this... Big nosed brother's miracle?]
[Only 5 seconds left!]
[Ah... The legs are feeling weak...]
[Over paced himself?
Big nosed brother's legs gave out]
-You were doing so well...
-Suk Jin...
Suk Jin... That's the funniest thing you've
ever done since starting on Running Man!
[Princess Ji Hyo's team fails]
[Princess Se Kyung's re-challenge]
Ready...!
[Tiny little penguin steps with
Princess on his back]
Good job!  You're doing great, Ha Ha!
Great job, Ha Ha!
Nice!
[Swiftly switching off]
[Balance beam expert, Kang Gary]
[I'm... A man... Who runs across water]
Take it easy!  Go slow!
[The finish line is right in front!]
[Will they succeed like this?]
[Success!]
Great job!!
We did it... We did it!
[Princess Se Kyung's team...
Passes the second relay]
We have to determine the losing team.
-You do it first.
-35 seconds.
-Are you ready?
-Yes.
[Ji Hyo's team, who's getting used to it
is going up for another challenge]
[Big nosed brother with the strength
in his legs recharged!]
[One step after another towards Mr. Capable!]
We can do it... We can do it!
[Big nosed brother completes it quickly
without losing strength in his legs!]
[Now if only Mr. Capable
can safely cross all the way!]
You can do it!
-You have to do it!
-You can do it!
[This time...
There's no way I'll come in last again!]
[Will he succeed within 35 seconds?]
[Success!]
We did it!
[Loser Princess Sa Yeon team
who's happy at not having to do it again]
Since you came in last... Please choose one.
I don't know what it's for...
But it would be nice if you picked Kwang Soo's.
I think this one would be good.
-I'll go with this one.
-Okay.  This one.
We'll check it for ourselves.
[Just whose name tag will it be?]
[Jae Suk's name tag!]
-You may get going now.
-Princess... Let's go.
Let's do another fighting!
[Without knowing what those
name tags are for...]
[Just like that, they're off to
the final destination with vigor]
[But no one knew...]
[Just what would happen to the Princesses
and Running Man...]
[Yoo Joon Sang]
[Why is he here?]
Today you are...
A beast who has his eyes set on a princess.
[Beast with his eyes set on
the beautiful princess?]
Furthermore, it is a given
that you have to oust Running Man...
And you also have to oust all the Princesses.
Oust the Princesses...?
None of the Running Man and the Princesses
has any idea of your beast's existence.
Because within the Princess' name tag,
there's a hint regarding your identity...
Once the Princesses' name tags are ripped off,
your identity will be revealed.
But... If I get mine ripped off first,
I'm going to jail, right?
What floor is the jail on?
-Jail is on the second floor.
-Second floor?
[At this final place, there are 3 cases
where the members' names are hidden]
[If he finds the cases
and pulls out the name tags...]
[Those people are automatically ousted]
If you pull out those name tags, even if
you don't pull it off their back directly...
They're automatically ousted right away.
[If he finds the case and pulls out
the name tag, they're automatically ousted!]
I just found out that Running Man
will enter the building in 3 minutes.
It would be to your best advantage if you
get started now and find those cases.
They are on 18th, 15th and 12th floor.
You look really nervous!
I'm extremely nervous.
Oh and my clothes...
Can't I just keep this on?
[Trying to use the jacket to his advantage
since he's outnumbered 9 to 1]
[Wherever there's the beauty...
Beast is sure to follow!]
[Joon Sang gets his beast name tag!]
I understand.
[Beast Joon Sang shoots out of there
even though the camera's aren't even ready!]
[Whether the camera follows or not...!]
-I have to go find those cases.
-Let's get you getting on the elevator.
-Shoot you getting on the elevator.
-No, just take the shot with me already on it.
Why are you making things so difficult for me?
[Already seeing
the Beast's rough attractiveness!]
Hello.
If by any chance...
Someone asks, say you never saw me.
By any chance...
Have you seen a case...?
[By canvassing the area,
discovers one of the cases!]
[But it's a fully loaded fake case...]
There's nothing in here.
[Where are the real 3 cases,
with the name tags in it?]
Pretend that you didn't see me...
And have you seen any cases like this one?
[Without a doubt,
they said one was on the 12th floor...]
[Discovers another case!]
In a place that I never would have
even imagined...
[Ji Suk Jin]
[Big nosed brother's case]
[The case Princess Ji Hyo picked when
they came in last in Hongdae!]
[Beast Joon Sang, takes one of the offerings!]
[Rushing to find the remaining 2
before Running Man enters the building!]
[This one is also a fake!]
[All you Running Man...
Did you have a good time with the Princesses?]
[This beast is going to shred
your memories to pieces!]
[Song Ji Hyo]
[Song Ji Hyo's case that was first chosen!]
[Song Ji Hyo's life
being offered to the beast...]
[Beast Yoo Joon Sang vs.
The Princesses and Running Man]
[Start!]
-Yes, we're the team that placed first.
-Hello.
[Entering without a clue
about the beast's existence]
You're right.
We didn't lose a single name tag!
That's right.
[Handing over the final mission]
Will you read it out loud and clear?
[The final relay]
[Catch the beast who has
his eyes set on the Princess!]
[The team that ousts the beast
is the ultimate winner]
[But the hint leading to the beast
is underneath the Princess' name tag!]
Catch the beast who has
his eyes set on the Princess?
The team that ousts the beast
is the ultimate winner
But the hint leading to the beast
is underneath the Princess' name tag!
The team that ousts the beast
is the ultimate winner...
But the hint leading to the beast
is underneath the Princess' name tag...
Then we just need to catch the other Princess?
Like Princess Se Kyung... And Princess Ji Hyo?
I really want to catch the other Princess'...
The Princess that Ha Ha and Gary has
is pretty fierce...
-It won't be easy to rip hers off...
-Ji Hyo's not very easy either.
Let's go.
[First, entering the arena]
The way I see it, the beast...
Does it mean that
there's a beast in each team?
Tell me again.  Explain to me...
I just pretended to understand
because there were people standing there.
[Slowly explaining everything
from the beginning...]
...The identity of the beast can only be learned
once we take off a Princess' name tag.
But since the other teams are also going to
eye an opportunity to get our Princess...
-That's right...
-We have to get a Princess' name tag.
If we find out the beast's name after
taking off other Princess' name tag...
We win once we take off the beast's name tag?
Wow... Seriously...
But if we're going to get to the Princess,
we have to get the 2 subjects first...
This is really bringing down
my coolness factor...
[Beast Joon Sang has acquired Ji Suk Jin
and Song Ji Hyo's case out of the 3...]
[Where is the last one?]
[To disrupt them,
there are many others dressed alike...]
The way I see it,
these people know something...
-Why don't we tempt them...
-Huh?
-What's wrong?
-I thought that it moved...
-Did it really move?
-It moved?
[Just in case that this is the beast...]
-It's not it?
-Are you going to keep lying like this?
-Oh my goodness! See?  It moves!
-It just moved!
[Of course it moves
when there's a person in there...]
-I bet it's hot in there.
-Are you a man or a woman?
Anyways... We kept having to pick our cases
since the race started...
Let's first find those cases.
But we can get attacked while
searching for those cases.
Why are there so many people in here today?
I wonder what they're here for?
[Jong Kook discovers a case!]
[A fake case...]
-What the heck is this?
-There must be fake cases hidden too...
[Princess Se Kyung's team
seems to have found something!]
We found one!
[This is also a fake case]
Oh my!  You scared me!
Goodness! You scared me!
-You just tried tearing mine off!
-No, we didn't.  You did that by yourself.
[The Princess scared herself when
her name tag got snagged on the wall]
I thought you tried tearing mine off.
It really scared me.
Sa Yeon, search closely around here...
I found it!
[Huh?!]
[That's my briefcase...]
I'm sorry.
She mistook your briefcase...
I'm seriously so sorry.
[The employee taking it all in with a smile]
-That's not the right bag...
-It's not?
-I'm sorry.
-You just made a silly mistake.
[Wasn't that what the cases looked like?]
[Beast Joon Sang
still hasn't found the last case]
[A case in a likely place...!]
So this is what it's like...
This is seriously...
[Offering discovered!
Yoo Jae Suk's name tag!]
[Beast Joon Sang,
takes all three of the name tag offerings!]
[But the Running Man are nearby!
Must use caution...]
-Just what is this beast thing?
-Right?
What's that?
[The beast in danger of being discovered!]
Someone was running with cases in hand!
Look over there!
-What's going on?
-What's wrong?
-Someone's running away!
-Who is?!
-Someone dressed in a black suit.
-What the heck?
Who is it?
Jae Suk!
Jae Suk!!
-Jae Suk!
-What?!
What, what, what?!
Where?  Where is he?
-Kwang Soo... Where did Kwang Soo go?
-Where did he go?
Kwang Soo!
Where are you?
What the heck?
[After looking around the place...
Discovers that they're all scattered about!]
Kwang Soo!
What the heck?
[Sa Yeon's team each left on their own]
[Where did everyone scatter off to?]
What the heck... What the heck?
[Beast Joon Sang!]
[With Jae Suk wandering alone...
Attacking without delay!]
What the heck?
Oh...!  Joon Sang!
-Hi.
-Joon Sang...!
What are you doing...?
-Can I just not do this?
-Why?
You... You're the beast!
You're the beast...
-Aren't you going around with silver cases?
-No... No, I'm not.
Since there's no one around...
Since I helped you out,
you can't tear mine off...
Yes...
I won't do that.
You're going to tear mine off?
You can't tear mine off.
How did this happen?
How this all happened is...
Sit down, have a seat.
-I know you must be busy...
-I didn't want to go this far either...
I had no idea that it was this hard.
-What...?
-Why do I have to keep running like this?
[But your existence is that of a beast...!]
When did you get here?
None of us knew that you were on the show!
First, I don't have a name tag.
Then what?
What about your name tag?
Let me see.
-See?  I don't have one.
-Oh!  You don't have one.
But you have a shirt on under the jacket.
I can tell the name tag is on your shirt.
I said, I don't have one.
[You weren't going to
show it to him anyways...]
-You don't believe me?
-I can see your name tag.
Then I guess I have no choice
but to tear yours off.
What do you mean, you have to tear mine off?
-You don't believe me right now?
-No, I believe you.
-I said, I don't have a name tag.
-Okay... I got it.
-I guarantee that I don't have one.
-But I can see that you have one...
I can see the square tag on your back.
So what is going on then?
What's going on today?
I'm asking what your mission is.
-Are you curious about that?
-Then you don't think I'd be curious?
You shocked me by being on here...
What do you think?
Can't you just tell by seeing me on here?
I'm telling you that I don't know...
I have your name tag right now...
You do?  So what?
If I were to take your name tag out right now,
you'll be ousted right away.
-Me?
-That's right.
-If you took out my name tag, I'm out?
-You could be ousted immediately.
That's the mission I have been given.
So what I want to know is,
why are you going around by yourself?
Show me that name tag.
-Show me my name tag.
-He really can't believe anything I say...
We can't trust anyone.
We don't even trust each other.
You really don't believe me right now?
I'll believe you once you show me my name tag.
[What kind of an offering is this...?]
The one that I locked eyes with on
the stairs was you, right?
[He almost had his identity revealed earlier]
Then where are the rest
of your team members right now?
[Beast Joon Sang taking Jae Suk
to his secret hideout...]
[Bringing out the offering case directly...]
-Don't come close to me.
-Yes, Joon Sang.
If I were to right now...
[Can't stand the ripping sound...]
-You wouldn't believe me.
-I'm sorry.
-You... Didn't believe me...
-If you rip that, I'm ousted?
You'll be over then... Just over.
-Joon Sang...
-I'll show you since you kept disbelieving me.
Please... Calm down a bit.
Then right now...
If I ripped this off, you're ousted.
If you go out there right now...
And don't rip someone else's name off
within 5 minutes, I'm going to rip this off.
[And don't rip someone else's name off
within 5 minutes, I'm going to rip this off]
-But that's...
-What minute do you have right now?
[Using the name tag as bait to
order Jae Suk to do the hunting]
It's... 10:30 right now,
so you have until 10:40.
-Come on... Joon Sang...
-10 minutes.  I'll give you 5 extra minutes.
Don't you think you're being too much?
If you don't get someone within 10 minutes,
then you'll be automatically ousted.
Just think of it as a relief
that I didn't order you to get 2 people.
I understand.
You've got 10 minutes to oust someone,
and 15 minutes to return to me.
If you're not back within 15 minutes...
Joon Sang, this is the kind of thing
bad guys do in a movie!
If by any chance...
You do get someone within 10 minutes,
but don't return to me within 5 minutes...
-Then you're immediately ousted.
-Joon Sang...
My nickname is Yoo-ruce Willis...
-And this is like 'Diamonds Are Forever...'
-Get ready!
I wish you the best of luck.
-The time right now is 10:30.
-You really are acting so different...
-You really are being so different!
-Wait... What did you say?  Wait.
-I got it... Come on, Joon Sang.  I'm going.
-What did you say?  Wait...
Joon Sang, I'll be back.
I'm seriously about to go crazy...
Just why...?
[Hm...]
[Of all things...
Why is my name tag in that case...]
[Yoo Jae Suk]
[He seriously is... Unbelievably unlucky...]
This is like a total remote time bomb...
There's no time... There's no time.
There's just no time.
Why did my name tag have to be picked
out of all things?
[I wish you luck, Jae Suk...]
[What is he doing?]
[I have to get one person...]
[But why are you of all people showing up?]
-What have you got?
-I think I found something.  Got something.
I bet there's nothing in there.
But... I've been wandering around myself...
Do you know where Sa Yeon is?
-How would I know that?
-You don't know?
No, I don't.
[Why is he behaving this way?]
-Well, let's just keep looking for now.
-Jae Suk... What's wrong with you?
[Yoo-ruce Willis making it very obvious
that he is flustered]
Jae Suk...
-You're acting a little strange.
-What do you mean, strange?
Why are you so busy by yourself?
When have I ever been
not busy on Running Man?
Whomever is very busy on Running Man
is the one to be suspicious of.
You should be walking around slower,
but your steps are way too rushed.
Since I'm dead anyways, just tear it off.
What's wrong with you all of a sudden?
So just leave me to go on my own way
since I'm busy!
-Jae Suk...
-Just let me be on my way.
-This is...
-I'm a dead person anyways, so...
It's all over for me today.  Tear it off.
Here's my back.  It's all over for me today.
It's all over for me.  So...
-I'm really busy, so let's talk later.
-Your behavior is really strange.
I told you earlier.  So...
You look like someone whose goal
is very different from mine.
[Definitely acting like
he has a different goal]
-What's wrong with you?
-I don't have time to chitchat right now.
[Strange...!
Why is he seriously acting like that?]
[On the other hand,
Yoo-ruce Willis quickly needs to find someone]
-Kwang Soo... Have you found anything?
-No.
-Where's Sa Yeon?
-She's resting in the room right now.
-Kwang Soo, let's go.
-Where are you going?
-We have to get going.
-Do you know something?
No, I don't.
He has a slight tendency
to go around cluelessly.
Jae Suk, what do you think?
You think we'll need this?
-What?
-You think we'll need this?
Well... Let's just carry it around for now.
Right now, I...
[What's wrong with Jae Suk?]
Is something going on?
[Looks as though he's planning on getting rid
of Kwang Soo at a quiet remote place]
-You're not the beast, right?
-I'm not.
-Aren't we taking the Princess with us?
-Where's the Princess?
-She's on the second floor.
-Second floor?
[Giraffe wanting to bring the princess along
after Jae Suk barely got him alone]
-I'll go get her.
-Don't you think it'd be better to leave her?
What?
If she's in some room,
I doubt someone will do something to her.
We have to protect her.
I'm concerned that she's tired...
So I want her to rest.
What?
[Awkward]
-Are you being suspicious of me right now?
-Jae Suk...
[After Gary,
the second worst liar of the bunch]
-Se Kyung, have a seat.
-This is so strange...
-Have you seen Jae Suk?
-I haven't seen him once.
-Jae Suk is seriously so busy going around!
-Is he the beast?
-Really?
-So I asked Jae Suk...
Why he's so busy going around like he is?
To which he kept on telling me that
he's a dead person anyways...
-Why?
-What does he mean, he's a dead person?
Then he kept saying that he's a dead person,
so if I want, to rip his name tag off!
After saying that,
he went back to going around on his own.
[There's isn't...
Much time left, Jae Suk...]
-Jae Suk, by any chance...
-Oh my!  What...?!
You scared me!
Why it is that I dislike him so much?
Since the last time... He scares me.
-I've just been with Se Kyung's team.
-Where?
Jae Suk... Those name tags...
I think those name tags...
I think someone has those name tags and
is able to control our lives.
[Mr. Capable accurately being able to
solve the situation]
-That's what I think.
-That's why we have to oust them quickly.
-The ones with the name tags...
-Oust the red team quickly.
-If we don't, then both our teams are dead.
-That's right...
-So quickly...!  We don't have the time.
-Your judgment is right.
-There's no time.
-Why were you acting so flustered, Jae Suk?
Whenever I run into you...
When it's just one on one, it's nerve wracking!
[But the real reason why
Jae Suk was flustered...]
Let's go quickly.  Where are they?
What floor are they on?
-What floor?  Let's go up there quickly.
-18th floor?
[Yoo-Ruce Willis becoming
more rushed by the moment]
I bet this is it...
You know those cases with the name tags?
If the name tag gets ripped from the case,
I bet that person gets ousted.
[You're...disappointing me, Jae Suk!]
Let's get this over with.
[A sudden announcement?]
[There's one minute left...
There's one minute left]
To what?
[Less than 1 minute left for Yoo-ruce Willis!]
What's that all about?
What has less than a minute left?
[Time left... 1 minute!]
Listen to me... What I'm saying is...
What I thought was weird earlier is that
you said you were a dead person.
So what I think is...
That person has been threatening you
with your name tag.
Everyone get off right now.
[The person in most danger, Yoo-ruce Willis!]
[If he doesn't get rid of someone,
then he's dead!]
Jae Suk!
[Discovers Ha Ha!]
Stop right there.  Stop right there!
Don't come here, don't come here.
What has only a minute left?  What is it?
I'm going to die soon...
[In order to preserve his life,
desperately begging Mr. Capable]
-What's going on?!
-Come here... Come here!
Come here, come here!
[Ha Ha-Out.  Ha Ha-Out]
In that case...
[Starts again]
[Will acknowledge if he returns within 5 min!]
At which point, I'll resume my actions.
[Mr. Capable ousting Ha Ha after receiving
the desperate request from Jae Suk]
Feel better now?
[Thanks to him,
Yoo-ruce Willis retains his life]
So where did you meet the beast?
-I met him while I was walking around.
-You met him, right?  He threatened you?
-He did threaten me.
-So this was all the beast's doing?
Then just tell us what happens
in that situation.
If I get ousted...
1 of you 3 will soon get to meet him too.
Listen to me.
Go and get rid of the red team quickly.
I'm going to be ousted soon...
You can get rid of me.
Whether I get mine torn off here or there,
it's the same difference to me.
I think Jae Suk is really scared of the beast!
I bet though...
You bought yourself some time right now.
You bought yourself some time?
I bought you some time?
-In the fairy tales...
-Did I buy you some more time?
[This is a scene from a movie...]
I'm Yoo-ruce Willis,
and this is like Diamond is Forever.
-This is Diamond is Forever...
-Then did I...
Anyway, I have to get going.
Seriously... What have I been reduced to?
I really do like Joon Sang personally, but...
Oh my... I just said his name
without even realizing it.
I'm over here.
4 minutes and 25 seconds.
-I'll let you live.
-That's not exactly right...
But you're really being too much here...
Thank you.
Then who are the other 2?
I can't tell you that.
Starting now...
-I'm sorry, but...
-There's no need to tell you honestly.
I'm not the type to go in
and work for someone...
My style is to work alone
and go around freely by myself.
My style isn't to work for someone.
You're really stressing me out!
All those other guys realize what's going on.
If you don't oust someone within 15 minutes...
[If he doesn't oust anyone with 15 minutes,
then he is killed!]
15 minutes.
I don't think you have the time
do be doing this right now.
-Joon Sang...
-15 minutes.
But, we both...
[Soul of a beast]
Precisely...
Okay...
This isn't the time to be laughing right now.
Joon Sang right now...
It isn't my style to go work for someone...
-Seriously...
-He seems really cool...
-Who's cool?
-Yoo Joon Sang.
[Heading off to somewhere
with all 3 offering cases]
-Gary, what are you doing?
-Ah! You scared me!
Who is it?
Se Kyung, come here.
I have nothing to do with winning today.
Then what are your intentions right now?
Me?
Just to go around for a bit,
then getting ousted.
Jae Suk is...already a dead person.
[Through Jae Suk's actions earlier,
they were able to discover a lot]
-He has been threatened by the beast.
-He is, in another words, the beast's hostage.
[Huh?  He opened someone's case?]
[He is not by any chance planning on
remotely ousting someone?]
[I don't really know...
He is not your average beast]
You met the beast?
I met the beast...
-Good luck dying.
-Okay.  I'll die well.
[The surprising announcement.
Is it by any chance...?!]
[Song Ji Hyo-Out.  Song Ji Hyo-Out]
[Just what is the beast's reasoning
for ousting Ace Ji Hyo first?]
[The terror creeping up on everyone]
What the heck?
[Yoo-ruce Willis feeling more burdened
with Ace Ji Hyo being ousted]
There's not much time left...
There's not much time left to my life.
[Ace Ji Hyo remotely ousted!]
[Left out at a place
where others can easily find!]
So cruel... He's frightening.
Jong Kook... Then one of two are going to
get ousted without any effort at all too.
But he can use us... We can be used.
The way I see it, Suk Jin...
If it were mine...
He would've just ousted me unconditionally.
I would have just been ousted.
Don't go... We're just being toyed with.
We're just being toyed with.
Don't go...!
What is it?!
What is it?  What's wrong?!
-What is it?  What is it?!
-Who is it?
[Discovered someone suspicious.
Is it the beast?]
What's wrong?
Don't go after him!  Don't go after him!
It's dangerous!
Who is it?
[Beast Joon Sang discovered!]
[Easy Brothers going after him
into the bathroom out of bewilderment]
[Beast Joon Sang,
getting them totally confused first...]
Joon Sang...
-Have you been well?
-Hello.
[Ji Suk Jin]
You saw it, didn't you?
-You saw it, didn't you?
-I saw it.
You saw it, didn't you?
[In this case...]
[Big nosed brother
ripping off Kwang Soo's name tag...]
[A man with determination, Ji Suk Jin]
-I took it upon myself.
-You got that?
-I know what I need to do.
-You get it, right?
I'm sorry, Kwang Soo.
Then I'm still left alive, right?
-Then... Will you be on my side?
-Of course.
-I already ripped his off...
-Am I out then?
[Easy brothers turning their backs on
each other at decisive moments]
-Thank you.
-I had a reason for saving you...
What's the reason for it?
Because you're always
getting ousted so early...
[The beast bringing up
pitiful big nosed brother's pride]
[You just wait and see Suk Jin...]
[Lee Kwang Soo-Out, Lee Kwang Soo-out]
What's going on here?
Just stay close to my side for now.
The way I see it...
I think someone is on the move right now.
Jae Suk... If I tear off your name now,
will you be ousted?
Of course, I'll be ousted then.
Don't tear it off.
[Sadly making an appeal...]
Sa Yeon, I'm going to be ousted anyways...
You know this, don't you?
You and he are total enemies right now.
-Really?
-Yes, you need to be aware of that.
What do you mean, enemies?
She's unsure of things,
and doesn't know the flow of things.
-Sa Yeon...
-But we're both wearing the color blue.
[The untimely color dispute?]
-Sa Yeon says she's really tired right now...
-Yeah, I'm tired.
-He and my son are very close... Oh my!
-Sa Yeon, what's wrong with you?
[Scared from Jong Kook's elbow
touching her name tag]
Why are you being like that?
She's the one who touched me,
and she's the one getting scared!
She gets scared when she bumps into
something while walking around.
-That really scared me.
-Just think about the situation, Sa Yeon.
[Big nosed brother, who's become the
beast's ally is heading towards them]
[He survived alone after chasing
the beast together with Kwang Soo?]
Suk Jin's headed this way?
[Have to get rid of at least
one of the beast's hostages!]
[Mr. Capable gets rid of
Yoo-ruce Willis' name tag!]
Jae Suk!  I don't want to see you being
used and dragged around this way!
-Thanks!  I'm grateful to you!
-That's right!
-Make sure to catch the beast!
-I'll get him!
-You have to make sure to catch the beast!
[Yoo Jae Suk-Out.  Yoo Jae Suk-Out]
What the heck?
What is this?
[With the slightest move from the beast,
the subjects start to scurry...]
Where are you going?
Hey... Hello?
[Gary... You said we should stick together...]
When I see the face...
This is the feeling that I get
when I look at the face...
My gut feeling tells me that
the beast's accomplice today is...
I think it's Jong Kook.
-Jong Kook just knows too much...
-Why is she like that with me?
-No, I think it's Jong Kook.
-There's someone over there.
[Beast Joon Sang!]
Oh my!  Oh my!
Oh my!  Oh my!!
[Princess Sa Yeon feeling truly surprised!]
[Beast Joon Sang vs. Mr. Capable Jong Kook]
Wait, wait, wait...
I was mistaken... I made a mistake.
-Wait, wait...
-That man... Get him!
-I made a mistake.  Let's meet again later.
-That guy...!
-Hello, Sa Yeon.  Have you been well?
-Yeah, I've been good.
Yeah, yeah... Yoo... Yoo Joon Sang!
Isn't it!  Wow!  He's so cool!
The time we have left is 3 minutes.
[Beast's hostage,
Big nosed brother attacks Princess Sa Yeon!]
Sa Yeon!  I'm sorry!  I'm sorry!
I'm sorry!
[Suk Jin succeeds at
getting rid of Sa Yeon's name]
Sa Yeon, I'm sorry.
I didn't want to do this...!
I've been found out now.
-Why are you so late with your timing?
-Why?
Where have you been? Where's Se Kyung?
If you had come just 30 seconds earlier,
the game would be over!
-What?  What happened?
-Yoo Joon Sang is the beast.
What?!
-Yoo Joon Sang?!
-That's right!
The nation's leading husband!
There's Suk Jin.  We have to get him.
He's the beast's minion.
-We have to get him!
-Jong Kook, Se Kyung...!
-Se Kyung!  Se Kyung!
-Let's go... I'll go this way!
[Se Kyung, who's been left
on her own is in danger]
What do we do about Se Kyung?!
Se Kyung!
-Do you not see her?
-You scared me!
[Stupids!]
-Why don't we go this way?
-Se Kyung!  I left Se Kyung on her own!
It's too scary being on my own.
Have you seen Shin Se Kyung?
She didn't come here?
Has Shin Se Kyung been here?
Se Kyung!
Shin Se Kyung!
-Hey... Did you find her?
-I haven't found her.
-I have no idea where she went!
-Hey... Come here...
There's Joon Sang, and there's Suk Jin.
Suk Jin is weak...
Even though Suk Jin is weak, you can be
in danger if he teams up with the beast!
You got that?
Hurry up and find her!
-I have no idea where she went!
-Which floor did you first lose her at?
-I don't remember...
-Seriously!
[The eraser within my head...]
Just what is going on here?
Explain it to me.
Please?
You can't?
Don't come close.
Joon Sang, don't come close!
Se Kyung!
Shin Se Kyung!
[Discovers the beast's hostage,
Big nosed brother!]
What floor?  What floor?!
[Mr. Capable Jong Kook on the move!]
11th floor!  11th floor!  I'm going to chase him.
We're heading down right now!
He's on his way down!
He could be luring us too!
I'll go to the 9th floor... 9th floor.
Hey!
[There's Se Kyung...?]
[But her expression seems nervous...]
What are you doing there?
What are you doing over there?
I'm just hot.  Gary...
Gary, wait!  Gary, you know...
Gary!
[Gary, no!]
-Wait...
-Joon Sang!  Hello.  My name is Kang Gary.
[Since this is their first meeting,
politely greeting him first]
This is a really different side of you
that I'm seeing on this show.
[Se Kyung became bait after being
caught by the beast earlier]
-Se Kyung!  Don't come here!
-What are you doing?
What...  Joon Sang, wait...
You can't be doing this.
-Joon Sang!  Joon Sang!
-That's not it...
[Beast Joon Sang starts to attack
Gary's name tag!]
[Even though she feels bad,
she's using the time to escape!]
Wait!  Wait!!  Se Kyung!!
[Calling Mr. Capable to report the situation!]
Jong Kook!
[Gary in danger!]
Why aren't you answering?!
Jong Kook, why aren't you answering!
[Press 1 to leave a voicemail...]
Jong Kook!  Why aren't you answering!
[Gary-Out!]
[Big nosed brother is here!]
-Be careful of Gary...
-Why?
[Princess Se Kyung not yet aware that
Suk Jin has become the beast's hostage]
-There's no way that can be!
-I'm serious.
I'm telling you they're working together.
[In this situation...
Princess Se Kyung is in danger!]
[Ah ha!  Se Kyung doesn't know anything!]
[Warning]
Why are you being like this?
[Gary-Out.  Gary-Out]
So who's left?
Us 2 and Kim Jong Kook...
Just the 3 of us?
-Are you going to help me tear his off?
-I'll help you tear it off.
-Liar!
-I'm serious.
-Jong Kook...
-Suk Jin.
Oh my God!
-Oh my God!
-What's wrong?
I'm going to tear hers off!
I'm tearing hers off!
If you come any closer,
I'm tearing her name off.
If you come any closer, I'm tearing hers off.
-Shin Se Kyung's...
-Go ahead!
[How dare...
Who do you take Mr. Capable for?]
[Beast's hostage, Suk Jin-Out!]
[Luckily still intact
thanks to her tight hold on it]
[Ji Suk Jin-Out.  Ji Suk Jin-Out]
Now I'm...on my way to meet him.
[It looks like it's time
for the beast to end things]
There you are.
-Hello.
[Mr. Capable & Princess Se Kyung
vs. Beast Joon Sang]
Se Kyung... You shouldn't stay here.
-How can there be such a thing?
-Does it mean you want me to go to jail?
-After using my own teammates like that...
-It's nice to see you, first of all.
After using my teammates like that...!
With your nice image and all...
The nation's leading husband image...
Why did you do that?
Why don't you at least tell me that?
Actually...
I have nothing to say about that either.
If I don't do the mission
I've been given today...
When my kid watches it...
My kid told me to do my best on the show...
So I had no other choice... And I was also
told to come and get a picture of you.
I even met Gary...
But left them all with a bad impression...
I had no choice.
Se Kyung, why are you coming this way?!
Joon Sang... We just...
Don't have any other choice.
[The one to tear off the beast's name tag
is the day's ultimate winner!]
-Since we're here...
-The way I see it, Se Kyung...
-You should just win this.
-That's what I'm planning on.
You can tear off Jong Kook's,
and I'll tear mine off.
How can you say such a thing?
That makes absolutely no sense!
[A stand-up competition.
The winner will be revealed naturally]
-Let's just do an arm tug standing here.
-Why?  You want to do that?
You must do this a lot
seeing how confident you are.
No, I used to do stuff like this
in high school.
Do it.
-I'm actually not very good at this.
-Go!
No!
[Beast Joon Sang brings down
Mr. Capable in one pull!]
[Thus leading into the attack!]
[Mr. Capable extremely flustered!]
-No!
-Se Kyung!  Tear it off!  Tear his off!
You really are like a beast!
-Jong Kook... Can you grab his arms?
-Wait, wait...
Why are you hitting me?
What have I done?
He's really scary... So scary!
Wait a minute!
Joon Sang...!
[Mr. Capable starts his counterattack!]
[Whomever tears off
the beast's name tag is the winner!]
His shirt, his shirt!
[Turning into a real beast
when his shirt becomes ripped!]
[Mr. Capable finally gets his hand
on the name tag!]
[There's no way!]
[Se Kyung-Jong Kook, just who will?]
[Mr. Capable does it!]
[Beast Yoo Joon Sang-Out!]
Joon Sang!
-What do we do about your shirt?
-Since you've ripped off plenty...
Look over here, Joon Sang.
You've really become a beast!
[Instead of a beast, perhaps a hulk?]
[Too bad...!]
Joon Sang, are you just abandoning us
after using us like this?
I got someone for you...
I ousted 2 people for you.
-You're really good...
-You look really great in person.
Sa Yeon, why are you being like that?
Sa Yeon... He's really dashing, isn't he?
Joon Sang is dashing.
-This, I'm going to...
-What?
Jong Kook!  You're so totally cool!
[Handing the beast's name tag to his Princess]
You're so cool!
[A gold ring for Princess Ji Hyo]
-Sa Yeon, don't even look at it.
-What have you guys been doing?!
[2012 Running Man Olympics]
[The magnificent event will be opening]
[Will it be veteran experts Running Man...]
[Or will it be the young
and ambitious Idol team?]
[Run towards the gold medal!]
[The pride of each team is on the line!]
[Running Man vs. Idols]
[And the terrorizing bell race
that's come back after an upgrade]
[Until everyone's been ousted! The bell race!]
[The breathless chase!]
[Highest level of suspense]
Subtitles by DramaFever