Faceoff combat
Let's compete...real fresh
We're here
Where are you?
Where?
No
No way
What do I do?
yeah...wow
yah yah yah
wohoh
Hey! You over there!
Oh it's cold
It's really cold
Ah nice
Make some noises!
No we..
Hey be careful, you can get hurt.
Watch out
It's high! It's high!
You are definitely on top of my palms
Why are you like that...really
Today is combat
What?!
Combat, combat!
The guests will be arriving
They'll be coming here.
Are they taking a boat?
Are they taking a helicopter?
No way...
There's a landing spot over there.
They must be coming in a helicopter then.
Really?
Eyy no way!
I think they really are
Awesome! Awesome! Wow!
It's coming towards us.
Wind ah wind!
I was right!
Seung Ri! Seuring!
There's Tae Yang
Awesome!
GD, and there's Dae Sung! Dae Sung ah!
It's really BIG BANG!
How long has it been, guys?
Hello
'They look cool.
How are you?
Stop it!
I mean!
Just take a picture of the sun (Tae Yang)
What is this? What is this? Really?!
It shouldn't be like this. No...
We look like we got dressed up
If you knew BIG BANG brothers were coming you should've told us!
I have special attire I saved to wear when I see these guys
Green leather jacket?
No no
Anyway BIG BANG is here. BIG BANG!
Did you know?
Did you know that?
HAHA is planning a faceoff with you guys.
He has a new album. His album gets released on the same day
HAHA come here.
You guys will win. But...
You guys will win, definitely. But...
I need to live too.
I need to survive
You look really pitiful.
you guys release on the 29th, right?
Yes.
Mine releases on the 28th.
Let's battle for ranking
Okay. Let's battle. With me.
Mine comes out on the 27th.
You come to KangNam station
I will on the 27th.
Yah!
You're too old-fashioned!
Go away!
Hey TOP why do you have sores here?
Oh I've been getting ready these days so I haven't slept in 2 days.
Oh really?
Dae Sung I haven't seen you hair like that for a while. Dyed.
It's the first time.
You feel awkward, don't you! I can tell!
Your face is too tan.
Dae Sung is just like that.
I saw him in the countryside a lot so
We have a country boy here too
Dye your hair too
He did.
He did that.
My hair is dyed now!
Oh I didn't know.
Why not!
I will give out the mission card
Hey giraffe!
And this team G-Dragon
What's today's mission?
Let's see.
Divide the teams into defence and offence.
Each member in one team has bells, and needs to take the other team's members out.
Frontal Victory?
No this isn't it.
So we take turns one by one?
That's correct
Also in the latter game. Only the team with the bells can rip off name tags.
So if ripped off all the name tags, that team wins.
Running man team has 2 more persons so we will give them a handicap.
I will go there.
No me.
Choose two members from running man team,
and those two will walk together with a bracelet.
If the bracelet is broken then both are out.
Please choose two.
-Feel, choke! -Easy brothers
When are you gonna stop doing feel chok?
Who would you like to have the bracelets?
Let's go with BIG BANG deciding?
Hmm...
Oh you're handsome.
He's handsome even with that strand of hair.
Should I try growing that too?
We want Jong Kook and Gwang Soo.
Okay. BIG BANG said Jong Kook and Gwang Soo.
No way! Seriously.
You're the best.
Tiger and giraffe again!
Oh I mean! It's not like we're in Serengeti.
And before we start the game,
I'll give a new weapon to one of the teams.
Teams can choose through a simple game now.
They're name tags.
Oh It's name tags.
Yeah they are.
Who wants to go first?
BIG BANG will go first.
Seung Ri hasn't changed.
He knows how to say what he wants right away.
It's TOP.
His mouth is open.
Oh I thought I was getting one.
I thought I rolled one so..
I've never seen TOP that happy
I thought I rolled one.
It's a three, not six.
Let's throw once more.
This time our team goes first
The man who rules time!
The man who does nothing right
BIG BANG come choose one first and then running man team can choose next.
It's okay, it's okay.
GD, what is that?
Gary choose one!
-Me? I'll choose this one. -Of course!
These weapons have never been used in Running Man so no one knows what they are.
Really?
From now on the combat race has started!
The team that sets off first has advantages.
What's with Tae Yang?
He left just now.
He said it's advantageous to leave first so...
We have to learn from them.
Are you kidding? We're normal.
From our team, Gary will be in charge of Tae Yang.
Oh really?
Dae Sung and Jong Kook.
Please call us Gae Yang.
Gae Yang
Seung Ri (victory) and loss
TOP and...
me
No! Gwang Soo Gwang Soo
Why!
-You're too short. Gwang Soo is the top between us. -Height wise.
GD...
I think GD and Jihyp
Am I their manager?
Not manager.
I'm on to you!
Ah, I mean, TOP.
yah
Where are we going?
It says SukDae Moon Museum.
Natural history museum?
We have two sheets
Small one first
Oh it's nothing
I knew it.
They have it.
They shall be placed inside the name tag like spy tags.
If your name tag is ripped off, the person who ripped it is also out.
Do we do it secretly?
We decide between ourselves and stick it.
But if Jong Kook rips it, he has a bracelet so we get two out.
With Suk Jin hyung or something we can't die.
-Song Ji Hyo sister. -Ji Hyo or Jong Kook.
Jae Suk hyung is good too. He's quite strong as well.
I don't get this game yet.
Do we have bells?
We don't know. We'll find out there.
Either case we take turns.
With the bells,
we chase them around. When we don't have bells we hide and run.
What would the weapon be?
They said it's never been on the show.
I don't think it's anything so good.
Yeah but I think one or two people will get out with the weapon.
Suk Jin or Gwang Soo.
If Gwang Soo gets out then you get out too.
-Oh right. Really. I'm gonna die. -I'll just break the bracelet.
Jong Kook whether you want or not you have to protect Gwang Soo.
-I think we have to get off here. -Hurry, hurry!
Okay. Let's go.
Can we go in?
Yes.
Hey you, that!
Oh right.
Wow dinosaur!
Big Bang enters! Big Bang enters!
I only saw this on tv.
It's here, isn't it?
What is this?
Take the bells if you want to be the offence team in the first term.
Or enter without the bells if you want to offend in the second term.
Oh we can choose!
They must have not arrived yet.
Let's hide first so it's relaxed.
How is it relaxing? Is it?
I think it's better if we chase first.
I agree with Seung Ri.
No it's better to hide and analyse and then attack in the latter half.
Cause we have these bombs too.
Oh you are right.
We'll hide.
Avoiding the team with bells, and find 5 running man cards.
So we should start looking?
Wait who's going to have the bombs?
We have to get caught by Jong Kook, Gwang Soo, or Ji Hyo.
At least avoid Suk Jin hyung.
Okay we'll go. Fighting.
First we have to familiarize with the location.
Can I stay with you?
For now ok.
How do we determine the mapping?
Look for emergency exits and we have to be careful cause we have bright hair.
Life Cycle room
Oh I found one! As soon as we started.
It's a good start, good start.
What is Run Kwang Man?
It looks like this!
We have one here too.
There're lots of fake ones.
They found one too.
There are too many.
Ah it's Run Kwang Man.
Hyung, there are a lot of cards but all Kwang.
Hyung we don't have time to look at the animals.
Really its glass. There's no way it would be in there.
Hyung stop looking at the animals.
We don't have time for that. I know cause I tried it.
You can't throw these out.
-Why? -So they don't know we've been here?
Yeah we can't leave traces. There's no blood or tears here.
It's here. You tease me about my small eyes,
but I can see better than you. -Haha okay.
You have to find it and scratch it in 1 second.
If it's nothing then you have to run.
you need this swiftness.
I have to find it quickly.
It's here. it's here.
-We are here. -There's the panel! There's the panel hyung.
Did we beat them?
I think we're just starting.
Running Man enters.
-This is really scary. -Since our hairs stand out so much we have to be really careful. Fighting!
Yah what is this?
Seems like they're already here.
It's like the museum is alive.
Did BIG BANG already come?
It seems like they have.
Oh so we have to get it first?
hey you guys, here!
Oh do I have to hold hands with him?
Wow I haven't heard this sound in so long
The bell's sound is really loud.
being here all together feels good.
It must be really scary.
With these bells on, I fee so invincible.
There are only three floors.
Guys, where are you?
This place is kind of small, isn't it?
You guys don't even have anywhere to go.
GD come out.
GD
Dae Sung ah
I feel old already...
I feel like they're going to be around here.
I know how the mind works for people who are hiding.
Kids, where are you?
Kids
This is the second floor right?
-No, the first. -First?
Really?
GD where are you going? GD Where are you?
Gd Where are you?
GD where are you going? GD! Where are you?
Oh my gosh, this place is too small.
Ji Yong ah, where are you?
Where did he go?
Ji Yong ah. Where did he go?
Ji Hyo, where did Ji Yong go?
Where is Ji Yong?
Where is Ji Yong? Have you seen Ji Yong by any chance?
No, I'm not sure.
Where is Ji Yong? Where is he?
Where is Ji Yong, Ji Hyo?
Where is he?
This is so hard
I feel like there's something here.
Why are you shaking so much tough?
Are you nervous?
-Stop shaking so much I feel like I'm holding a girls hand. -I'm shaky.
They are not here.
We can't find them.
Dong-hyun
hyung, where are they?
Let's just drink this.
Sorry, it' s because it was a little bit high.
Why are you guys here
We decided to come here.
Please.
Kwang Kwang
Because it's too obvious, this place.
Nothing.
I found so much but none of them are real.
grasshoppers
Running Man!
I found Running Man!
Mission 20 % complete
Oh? They're doing a mission!
Figure out what's the mission, hurry!
We have to know it.
Gary hyung, look at this
Gary hyung, look at this.
What is it?
We're on the same team.
Oh?! What's this?
Really?
Why are you wearing this?
-Oh it's only you? -The rules of the spy changed.
They said there's no spy today?
-Was it not? -Of course they would say there's no spy. They would say there isn't any when there is.
You're right , I think the same thing.
Wait, are you the only one wearing this?
That's what I'm saying, I'm the spy.
Gwang Soo and Jong Kook are together, right?
Yeah.
The members can't know, seriously! Don't say anything.
Alright, you're not saying some nonsense right?
I don't get fooled easily.
-You can't fool me anymore.-Of course!
Alright
You have to be secretive about it.
I just saw Seung Ri and he's wearing a bell.
hey stay there! Stay there!
Wait, what is this?
-My brain's not really good right now. So you can go confirm it. -Go back! Go back!! I'll be right back.
-Gary. -Yes.
-There's someone here, come down come down.
Did you not hear?
No I didn't hear anything...
Wait, wait, why?
So in running man,
There are seven people and Jong Kook and Gwang Soo are spies from the seven but for Running man, I'm the spy.
What?
I'm running men's spy.
Hey. Really though why are you wearing a bell?
Jong Kook and Gwang Soo are spies and I'm running man's spy.
They said there's no spy today.
Of course they'll say there isn't one when there really is!
Do you really think I'd lie?
Tell Jong Kook and Gwang Soo to come here then.
Hide the bell. What are you doing!
Wait, hold on! Don't get close!
Wait, you're wearing a bell?
Wait, what's going on?
he's wearing a bell?
Don't get close.
Why are there so many bells here?
What is this?
You put this on yourself!
No I didn't!
Look at all these bells.
You didn't see this bag of bells before?
He said Jong Kook was the spy.
He is the spy.
Come here. Come here!
Then you're going to lose!
I'm the spy!
Seung Ri out.
Hey hey. Look at all these bells. Take them!
Gary hyung was here first and was like "really?!"
You know what Gary said? He said "our bells are silver but Seung Ri's is gold coloured!"
This is hard, hard!
It's already hard enough to run around like this,
and we have to find this card. It just make it more difficult.
Oh sorry.
RUNNING MAN!
Mission 60% complete.
How did they get 60%?
We should be running around, we have no time to be doing this.
Did someone get caught?
It's T.O.P!
Hey T.O.P! TOP! I'm going to run.
Where is he? Where?
T.O.P I'm coming! Get him!
TOP! Grab him! TOP!
I'm sorry.
Let's end this once and for all.
Why do you run like this, you should be running faster.
Oh! They got him!
You should've been running faster.
Just tell me what the mission is.
-I know what the mission is. -You know?
They're coupon cards.
oppa!
What is going on right now?
Why is TOP just sitting there and not running away?
Yah! They had the secret weapon. Do you think that's a retaliate?
What is this?
What is in there?
Bang?
At least avoid Suk Jin hyung.
What is in there?
Bang?
Ji Suk Jin out!
Yah! You should've properly ran away!
TOP out.
Oh we're out together, together.
We have to get them.
They should've been there, we were supposed to have found them by now.
Are they hiding somewhere?
But look here.
Oppa!
Dong-hyun, ah!
They finished a lot of missions on the top so they have to be on the second or first floor?
These are the only exits here and there and even the elevators.
There's one on the elephant's nose!
He's right there.
oppa over there!
Hurry! Come here!
Hey Dae Sung!
Dae Sung, come here, come here!
Dae Sung ah!
Dae Sung!
Why did you take this off!
They've probably been here?
Dae Sung out
Dae Sung out.
It's usually on the floor.
Yah, GD, what are you doing?
-Hyung I was looking for you. -I was looking for you too.
I was looking for GD too.
Oh really?
But GD wouldn't appear anywhere.
Ji Yong, have you seen GD or not?
Oh he was over there.
Oh really, over there?
yeah he went over there on the second floor. I think he went to the roof top.
Ohh yeah I couldn't find him anywhere.
I'm supposed to go straight on BIG BANG but what am I worried about? The fans won't understand?
-Ji Yong ah. -Hyung.
GD, have you seen GD?
-He's right there. -Where? Where is he?
Right there, hyung.
I heard he met with you earlier.
Really?
Yes. He went to that side.
-That side? I see. -Yes.
Alright
What should I do?
I can't think straight now.
Oh, what is it?
It's Ji Yong. Yah!
It's Ji Yong. I should've caught him.
Ah, it's all because of HAHA hyung.
We are here!
If you meet with HAHA hyung...
What should I do now?
-Have you seen HAHA hyung? -He's right there! Right there!
He's over there?
Well, Suk Jin hyung is already out now, right?
Hey, Ji Yong ah!
Ji Yong ah! Ji Yong!
Ji Yong ah!
You should go together with your VJ.
Come here. Gather around!
Ji Yong, Ji Yong ah...
-Ahh.. -Ji Yong ah.
Ji Yong ah, Ji Yong ah...Ji Yong
GD!
Come here!
Hyung, rip off the tag.
Yoo Jae Suk out! Yoo Jae Suk out!
Yah, he made you out too..
What is that?
Running man is too tiring!
I'm sorry.
SOL! Where are you?
It's me....Gae Yang!
Tae Yang ah! It's me Gae Yang!
Tae Yang.
-How come we can't find him? -He must be hiding in somewhere.
Go inside, maybe he's hiding in there.
Hyung, I heard the door is closed, over there.
Here is right.
There's someone inside. There's someone inside.
Just stay there!
I wanna hear too.
I just told you! Don't do that!
Stay still. Stay still.
Don't do that!
He could find out, Gwang Soo.
Just stay here..
I...so, I just stay still like this?
Oh, okay.
What are you doing? Give it to me!
Why did you do that?! Why?!
Let's have some talk.
No, I just want to try once, rip off your name tag.
But why tear off my name tag?
Hyung, I came here...without saying a word, just followed you.
But why did you do that?
-I didn't even say a word, just followed you. -Even though.
I can't listen, I can't eat, I can't even walk as my wish.
I don't know. You didn't have to do that though.
I've been holding it in all this time.
WHAT?
Wait, wait!
Lee Gwang Soo, what should I do with you.
Hyung....Don't joke with me.
-What is going on? What is this all about? -What are you doing?
It didn't get ripped!
What's all this?!
I thought you were a spy, because you teared Jong Kook hyung's name tag.
-So, why did you tear it off? -I thought you were a spy.
-No, it's not like that. -Let me look, are you spy or not.
Why would I?
Hyung...
-What? I really thought you were a spy. -Doesn't he need some time to cool himself, hyung?
Ah, wait, hyung...what should I do then.
Gwang Soo, why did you do that?
Don't come here. Just stay there.
Gwang Soo, come here.
You must don't know that you are in the afternoon section.
I just knew before.
You made him out.
Today, you won't come out on tv.
You won't come out on this show.
You'll see.
He's inside.
-You scared me. -What are you doing, Tae Yang?
Tae Yang is inside.
Turn around. You were hiding silently in here, I see.
How did you find out that he was hiding in here oppa?
I heard something before, it turned out that he's hiding here.
Let's decide who tears off his name tag.
-Yah! -Hey!!
Ahhhh. What the hell are you doing?
Why you...?
SOL
I'm in front of the elevator.
Why you...?
SOL
I'm in front of the elevator.
-Yah -Hey!!
Tae Yang, give up.
Now it's the end for you
-Okay, after I say 1 2 3, let's tear off the name tag. -Ah, I can't run anymore.
Right.
One, two, three.
Tae Yang, I'm sorry.
Finally.
It can't be right. It can't be right.
We lost.
Somehow, I feel that I was insulted.
We didn't do anything...
I feel ashamed.
I was even played (?) by HAHA hyung.
Be ready and get nervous?!
I was insulted
If you see HAHA hyung, let me know.
God, it's driving me crazy.
We were defeated in round 1, you know.
Let's stick together!
Catch him!
Don't shoot me.
Wahhhhh! Wait a second!
NOOO
This is our power.
Wow, we even have a power now.
Tae Yang
GD
Seung Ri
Dae Sung
TOP
Joined forces of five ring.
Dominate the space.
Yeah!!
This is the first time I do this kind of thing since I was in elementary school.