Hi. I'm Han Ga In. Let’s be friends.
My first love...
Actually. I wanted to go out with you...
I think my memory is slowly coming back.
Is it not me, really?
You're her first love...
No more!
Become my last love.
Today, we're at a school. A school.
Ah, who will come out today?
-Since we're at a school... -I am really curious about the guest.
At this rate, we'll have Johnny Depp appear!
-Eh?! -Johnny Depp!
-Why would Mr. Johnny Depp come on this show? -Why not?! He could!
-How would he come here? -He could, really!
There’s a chance we could have a Hollywood star as a guest!
Fine, let's say Mr. Johnny Depp comes. 4 to 5 of us won't go 011 air that episode.
If Johnny Depp comes, it means 4-5 of us won’t be on air.
-We'll have to st ck by him. -Of course.
-And keep talking to him. -Like a ghost.
-The guest is about to come out. -Oh really?
-Is it Johnny Depp? -Today's guest, please come out!
It looks like it's a too heavy.
Who could it be that they're...
Ah, they're too far away!
-You should have started them out closer! -You haven't tried carrying a Gama, right? It’s incredibly heavy!
Isn't this too much on them?
-It‘s way too far! -It's too mean!
-Those people must be... -There must be three people in them...
Ah, truly. Rest a bit my friends!
-Put it down! Put it down! -It's too much!
It's a guy, a guy.
Is it that heavy?
Ah, everyone...
This is heavy, See. Come this way.
Ah, it's a flowered gama!
A princess must be riding in it.
The guest is in one of these flowered gamas. Please choose one and stand In front of it.
-Ah?! -I knew you would do this.
-Yon become a team with the guest that comes out of the gama. -I heard a male voice on this side.
When they put it down, he went "Oh! Oh!"
This side did seem incredibly heavy.
-No, this side was heavier. -They looked like they were holding something very heavy.
-Are you sure? -You heard something?
What do I do?
This is maddening.
Suk Jin hyung, it's definitely this side.
Hey!
Hyung! Let me go!
-You can't go anywhere. -Suk Jin hyung, come to this side.
-Yes, go to that side. Suk Jin hyug! -No, I don’t want to!
You have to be a brand name, together with me.
But like this, the number of people is too small on that side.
-It didn't seem like a guy... -Starting with this side...
-Please ask for your person to come out. -Starting with us?
Ah, this is not good.
-We got it wrong? -Can we change now?
We must have gotten it wrong.
We don't know who it is. but please, two female idols, please come out!
Isn't that Dong Wan?
Ah, really!
Hey, what are you doing?!
-Gary! -Please come out!
Hello!
-Oh! Ga in! -Hello!
Yeon Woo!
-Whoa, wait... -What! Yeon Woo...!
-Yeon Woo... Yeon Woo.,.! -It's Han Ga In?!
Hello-!
-But you must be... -Han Ga In!
No. she's maiden Yeon Woo!
Because I was so shocked...
Hey, Gary hyung shrunk.
And as I've said, in a circumstance such as Ga In’s...
-Hey! How is it Just "Ga In"?! -Oppa. again!
-Don't do that! -But, really..!
-No one believes me! I even officiated her wedding! -It's true.
We even did comedic skits together!
-Well, at that time she must have been friends with Hwi Jae hyung! -True...
With Hwi Jae... But Han Ga In, here...
You usually don't come out on variety shows.
I'm incredibly scared right now. Are there usually this many cameras around?
-I was completely surprised. -We're here, why be nervous?
Yes, that’s true.
I couldn't sleep last night because I was so nervous.
So the teams are split like this?
We should split teams like this, but because the teams are 3 vs 5,
it's a bit disadvantageous.
Ms. Han Ga In can choose one person from tills side.
Ah, hey!
Hey, how could to do that Ga In!
Ah, what is that?!
Hey, is this something someone should do?!
Hey. don't do that.
-Hey! -Okay.
Because my family was historically servants.
We do things like this well.
Who should I pick?
-Mr. Gary, I could you move a bit closer... -I can't get closer.
Just let me stay here!
If you can’t get closer, get out!
Why!?
I don’t want to!
I... Mr. Gwang Soo...
-What did you say? -Mr. Gwang Soo.
Mr. Giraffe!
Ah, giraffe!
Yes!
Giraffe!
Giraffe? Me?
It was a gut reaction.
He's my sacrificing shaman!
In Running Man.
Why should I be sacrificing?!
-He's mine. -Why do I need to be sacrificing?
-Why do I have to be sacrificing? -What do I do if he leaves?
Then, unavoidably, hyung-nim, you will have to be the sacrificing person.
Today's mission is to find your first love.
All of you have lost your memories.
We have to act?!
-You want to create a drama now. -Were superpowers not enough?!
You can't remember right now, but
as the missions progress, you will find clues for help you recall your first Jove.
Through the race that starts now, you have to find the clues to find your memory's first love.
Yeon Woo!
-You're her first love. -Hey!
Actually, I want to go out with you..
Be my last love.
It's’here,
But, where are going?
Why have we suddenly gotten onto a bus? It's weird.
It’s Budang.
Ah, over there!
-The Running Man banner, -Where? Where?
In front here.
-Let's get off. -Go out. go out.
Where do we go?
-The team that arrives first will do the mission first. Please go downstairs. -Hyung, come quickly!
It's a team competition!
We all have to go? But where's the flag?
-Which way? -Which way?!
Where are we going?
We have to get there first!
My body can't move, hyung.
What's this?
Hula hoop?
The Blue Team arrived first?
-I got here first. -No. we did.
Our whole team got here.
This mission is a hint obtaining game.
The name of this game is "the Moon that Pierces the Sun".
-What did you say? -Seriously?
The missing moon, the piercing moon...
How could you, in front of Ga In. so embarrassing.
So it's Sun Piercing Moon? Sun Piercing Moon.
We have to pierce the sun?
-The Moon that Pierces the Sun... -Show us how to succeed!
How is this "The Moon that Pierces the Sun"?
-But who will throw? -But this is incredibly hard.
-You have to do it all at once, right? -How do you throw that
I can do this without jumping.
Really?
Try it.
Without jumping.
Oh, how funny!
Stand there.
Gwang Soo, it was funny!
Ga In, have you done something like this before? You probably haven't done games like this...
-When was the last time you... -During elementary school?
So it's been more than 15 years?
-Try rolling once... -Should l try to roll?
To the front?
-She does it really well, -Wouldn't it be easier to the side?
But this game is too much!
-It hurts a lot, doesn't it? -Ms. Ga In, don't use your head, just roll to the side.
-To the side? -Yes. because if you use your head...
-Ga In, tie your hair well. You might be mistaken -for an understudy of a criminal.
Fighting!
One. two, three.
Oh, Gwang Soo passed through?
It's just too hard.
Ah, come on people.
Okay, if you just roll, it will be right on top of your heads.
-You just have to go through. -That had better be true!
Yeah! Get ready! One. two...!
Okay. three!
-Oh, it spread out well. -See, I told you!
See, I told you!
Why doesn't it come toward me?
Just roll comfortably!
When you get up... it won't be over your heads.
Gary!
Should I roll to the side, instead of like this?
Is this faster?
-Okay! -Is this faster?
Ga In, what are you doing by yourself?
Did I see incorrectly?
What are you doing by yourself?
It looked like you just rolled sideways?
I'm practising rolling...
Ms. Ga In. it depends on your left or right leg. If you use your right leg, do this.
Then just do this. Put your hand down like this, and roll just like this.
How could Ga In roll like you do?
See. she just did! It's gotten a lot better!
-How can she roll like you? -She just did this!
No, that's not it!
Just push yourself straight. Without using your head.
-Using your shoulder. -Look at her hair!
I'm sorry.
Yang Myeong-gun!
Yang Myeong-gun.
How could you make the guest's hair like this?
You're making it more...
You're creating static!
We called over a top star and...!
Stop it!
Let's do a cheer!
-Yes, hyung! -Since Ga In is here and all.
-Our cheer is ready, right? -Yes!
Two three! Han Ga In Is a star that does one thing!
Han Ga In isn't, Han Ga In isn't a idle star
Pierce the sun and run! Sun piercing moon! Sun piercing moon!
It's so embarrassing. I can't bear it!
So embarrassing!
Ga In, it was because I hadn't seen you so long and I was so happy...
Okay, I'm going!
One!
Two!
Three!
It was all for Han Ga In.
She's the only one.
By herself!
We'll show you what a real cheer is!
Let's do this elegantly. Elegantly,
Commander! Big Nose! Ace Haroro!
We four have gathered to p erce the sun! Sun Piercing Moon!
Sun Piercing Moon!
And what's this...
Why don't you just pierce my frustration.
Don't pierce the sun. just pierce my frustration.
Hey!
One, two three!
Two, three!
Can't Jong Kook hyung throw for us. too?
They just need to sit still.
Ah. it was so close.
I wore white pants for nothing.
You should have let us know earlier.
My white pants have become stained with grass and are now green.
Hey! If it's green, you can give it to Jae Suk hyung.
-Hey! Not all green stuff is mine! -That's what you can do!
Let's switch these, too.
Hey!
It might be because of that.
Do it with the power of green, hyung!
Okay. Gwang Soo, you have to come toward the middle.
One.
Two.
Three!
Lease become a couple with me!
You must play like this at home usually.
Is that something you say to someone?
How could you say that she plays like this at home usually?
Because she's so good at it.
-How could she do this with Mr, Jeong Hun? -The two of them could.
And with Mr. Kyu Jin!
How could they do this at home?
-Hey, apologize! -Gwang Soo, apologize.
I'm sorry.
Look at maiden Yeon Woo.
-She's become an understudy for a criminal. -Exactly.
Ah. this is really...
Wash your hair in the stream.
Is that something you should say?!
How could you say to maiden Yeon Woo to wash her hair in the stream?!
Because her hair is like that. I felt sorry for her.
The most important thing is
rolling quickly, looking for it, and following it.
-Ji Hyo, so leave the last one for me. -Okay.
Promise me!
Okay, I’m going. One, two. three!
Oh. success!
Success!
Big Nose! Ace! Haroro! Commander!
We four gathered... sun... Yah!
But this time, like Jong Kook said, this time. they rolled and it was right on top of them.
How did that work?
-This time, it was true. They lift ed their heads, and it was right there. -How does he do that...
The succeeding team, please come here.
You can take the bus you arrived on and go to the final location comfortably.
And there's a hint here.
You will find clues about your first love if you look for 'picture diaries'.
Gary, let's do this well this time!
One, two, three!
Three!
Success!
-You have to see this as passed. -Pass it through your head. quickly!
-Immediately! -We did it!
-It went right in. -They just succeeded!
-No way. How? -They did?
Please give us the mission.
Because you lost, at the next location
you won't get a hint.
Only the winning team gets that.
And, you can't use that bus we used before. You must go on your own somehow.
-Go! -Can we use something? Like a cellphone?
-Can we use our ce p ones -You're going to ride there on your cellphone?
-No..! -Sure, why not!
I'll ride it there!
Oppa. I think I understand why you do that now.
You see now, don't you?
-Ga In, you see, don't you? -But that's not...
Why we're like this.
Hey, heyThey!
Let's go. let's go, let's go!
Oppa.
Search for a picture diary?
A picture diary?
Wasn't there something called a picture diary, a book, in the past?
-During elementary school... -When we were young, during elementary school!
-It's the thing where you draw on top and write on the bottom. -Yeah, the one where you write.
Ah. we're going back to our childhood. But what is this first love?
Oppa, over there! There's the Running Man banner.
H-hey. I think it's here. We must be going to this building.
Thank you.
-Ah, where is this? -It's this way.
A job world!
-Oh. Running Man..! -It says Running Man!
Let's go in. oppa!
Oh, it does.
What's this?
Are we having a race here?
Hey, there's something here.
Will you be giving us something again?
Yes. this is Job World.
It's an individual competition.
Individual competition?
-But we came in so friendly... -Individual competition isn't good...
But you have a very Important hint.
There must be someone!
This is your childhood. The one yon can't remember very well.
-Who is this? -Gary's too pretty!
Why is Gary so pretty?
From now, it's an individual competition.
Individual competition?
Because you lost, you do not get the hinf.
As I said in the morning,
there's something about this.
Hey. hey. hey. Quiet. Go to your seats.
Quickly, to your seats.
Song JI Hyo. shush.
Attention.
Hey kids, today we'll have a new friend transferring in from Seoul.
Shall we call our friend?
Hey, Ga In! Come in!
Here. here. Ga In. How pretty you are.
Isn't Ga In pretty?
Han Ga In, become my last love.
Hey! Hey! Hey!
Ga In, greet everyone.
Hi, nice to meet you. I'nrHan Ga In. Let's be friends.
Do you happen to know Kim Soo Hyun?
She looks familiar. I've seen her often before.
Now, who would like to sit with Ga In?
-Me. me. me. me. -Hey!
Today's Monday!
Oh my god.
Stress.
-The seat next to me is empty. Do you want to sit here? -Ga In, that seat is empty.
Go sit over there.
Now, everyone, face forward.
We need to start class.
Now, let's start class!
Shall we take attendance to see if everyone is here?
-Song Ji Hyo! -Here!
-You've come. Next, Kim Jong Kook! -Here!
-Yoo Jae Suk! -Here!
-HaHa! -Here!
Lee Gwang Soo?
Hey kid, you're Lee Gwang Soo!
-Here! -Good!
Ji Suk Jin!
Ah, really? First love?
Not meeting your first love is best.
You're not supposed to meet your first love.
I need to find picture diaries.
Let's search for clues.
Finding that is the most important.
Perhaps Gary hyung and Ji Hyo... Maybe Monday Couple are first loves?
It couldn’t be, right?
That's right!
It's like finding a needle in a haystack. How do they want us to find this without anything?
In this wide place.
Go Quickly.
Heey.
Ms. Harr Ga In.
Acfually. you're the protagonist of this first love story.
Because you and the other members have amnesia.
No oneknows vvho loved who.
But there definitely was someone yon loved in your past.
Within these members.
Because you lost in the game, we can't tell you what you should be searching for.
But if you gather those hints and order them chronologically.
You will find who your first love was.
Chronologically?
You must first find your first love before the other members do.
Yes.
Then. if you find your first love, with your first love,
tear off the name tags of the remaining five members and go to the final location.
And those hints are... in here?
They are hidden in various places.
-Hey. Gwang Soo! -Hyung!
You're just walking around without knowing anything, too, right?
Yes.
Hyung, you know it's defin tely in places like this, right?
Oh? Wow.
But what's the hint? What does it look like?
Wow!
Wow, this place is amazing.
Can we sit here?
Hey, Gwang Soo.
Wow, this is no joke.
Wow, it really looks like this? Whoa.
Co-pilot!
Can't I be the captain?
-Wow, you can hear it, too! -You do this.
Passengers, Running Air is taking off.
All passengers are toiplease put on their seat belts.
Now?
-I've always wanted to say this. -Put your mic up first.
But you shouldn't have put that in my mouth still!
We pologize.
There will be some turbulence.
There will be more turbulence than anticipated.
No matter what anyone says. Korea's yeonjigonji is the best.
There was something like this too. Hiding.
Fly! Fly!
She was so pretty-
Ji Suk Jin, out! Ji Suk Jin, out!
We will end the news here.
Ah, really.
The picture diary is...
What is this?
Somewhere like this...
Somewhere like this is a good hiding place!
Wow, here...
I should bring my child... Oh?!
Oh?!
Didn't I find this too quickly?
Huh?
I finally found one.
"During the talent show, everyone danced together."
"♥♥ danced the best. He was like a celebrity." He dances well...
When I grow up, I'm going to become a legendary dancer!
Ah Definitely. Yoo Hyuk is the best at dancing!
Hey, who do you think is the coolest?
Me?
Um. I... I... Him!
He dances well?
I can't dance well...
Who dances well?
Yoo Hyuk?
Is it Yoo Hyuk?
Jong Kook dances well, too...
HaHa, too. Gary.
Ah, so frustrating.
I have to find something?
What do I have to find?
-Ga In, did you mind something? -No.
They won't tell me.
-You haven't found anything yet? -Yes.
-Did you find something, oppa? -No, I haven't.
Oh, it seems like you found something.
Your gaze is wavering.
I was only taking this out.
No, I think there's something strange.
No, there's not!
-You know something, don't you? -No. I don't.
I really don’t! You think I would do this, Ga In?
-If I knew, I'd tell you. -Then why'd you ask if I had found something?
Ga In, you're...
I think I have to keep searching.
Where are you going?
I think I have to find something.
I think he knows something. Slightly.
Did he find a hint?
Is he my first love?
Is Jae Suk oppa my first love?
My first love within Running Man...
Oh, it might not be me, right.
I can't recall!
Is there some amazing hint hidden within here?
Could my first love be Gary hyung?
You think it's me?
You're my first love?
Hyung, are. you my first love?
Truly?
Could it be?
Because I have amnesia, I don’t remember very well.
Are you OK?
-HaHa. are you OK? -I think I remember!
Who is it?! Who's your first love?
Here.
-Who is it?! -Oh my head! The person had double eyelids!
Like this?
-Oh! My first love! -Is it not me?
I think it's you. hyung!
Hyung!
Am I out?
Hey. you startled me.
We could be first loves later, so when we are, let's deeply...
Sure.
Show that.
Your colour is looking good today.
I think my first love just passed by.
I must have seen incorrectly.
See you later, my love.
Where are you going?
-I’m just looking around, hyung. -You look like you have a mission.
-Eh? -You look like you have a mission.
I don't have one.
I think I'll play on the slide.
-If you get on that, where do you go? -Down there.
-Get on. -I'll go first!
I'll go first!
My love! Are you all right? My love?
I Just looked at the slide and when I Just looked it was just there just stuck to the roof.
See!
Han Ga In!
The name is Han Ga In!
"He was very han some. He looked like a fairytale prince. I'm going to grow up and marry him."
Boys play like that, I guess.
No! You're out!
Hey! Gary!
You're out!
Hey, I think Gary likes me.
Do you have someone you like?
What about you?
I... I... I...
Since we're both embarrassed, let's just point in one shot!
One, two, three!
Him!
Ah, green!
Ah, he's wearing green.
It's Yoo Jae Suk.
The face looks like Yoo Jae Suk, too. His face is longish.
Green is...
definitely Jae Suk hyung.
-Really? -Oh. go down this way.
It's usually somewhere here. When you're going down the slide.
Then I'll go down first.
Is here something there? Look carefully.
Hey! Wait! Hey!! Wait!!
Hey! You. really! I'll...!
-I will..! -Is there something there?
I will seriously not let you get off easily!
I will...! This time, I will...!
- not let you get so easily... -That's not-it...
-Someone had to check! -I will seriously...
-Hyung! -You truly...
-Is there something there? -Oh!
What is it??
Hyung!
No, it's OK now Gwang Soo.
-Did you find something? -I'm here!
No... Hyung...
-I'm here!! -No, that’s...!
You want to know what's here? I'm here!
You made me let go? Over there?
That's not it...
I think it would be somewhere like this.
Oh, no, no, no!
-No, it's not time yet! Hyung! -What is?
-It's not time yet! You're not supposed to! Hyung! -Hmm?
-What isn't? -Hyung!
Were you then supposed to tear of my name tag when you ripped it off?
No, I wasn't but...
Ahh, hyung! Hyung!
Please! Stop! Stop!
Please!
Get your act together.
-Don't do that anymore. -Yes, sir.
We might be first loves, Gwang Soo.
Always remember.
That we may be first loves.
Us...?
-Oppa, what's the hint? -Excuse me?
What's the hint?
-Ah... maiden Veon Woo. -You know, don't you?
-You can't come suddenly like this. -What's the hint?
The hint?
Do you not know what we're supposed to find?
No, now...
There's something... like this...
-Is there? -You can't tell anyone.
There...
What we wrote in when we were younger...
the picture diaries, you know?
That’s what we’re looking for.
-I'm just especially telling you. -Did you find one?
So you can't tell anyone. Anyone. This is an individual competition.
-If I find one, I'll call you. -Yes. Please.
-Hyung! -What?
You really can't tell anyone!
She's maiden Yeon Woo...
I wanted to become Yang Myeong-gun.
I wanted to become Yang Myeong-gun!
This is a present from me.
If I can't be her first love, at least if I could be Yang Myeong-gun.
-Do not come close! -Oppa.
Do not come close!
And do not stray far...
Are you threatening me because you’re the guest?!
-Are you threatening me?! -This is not a threat.
You... you're not?
I thought it was a threat.
Daebak!
Do not come close! Do not come close!
Why did you not choose me?
If we had been on the same side, I could have worked harder for you.
I want to turn back time!
Can we not turn back time.
Where are you going?
I thought there was something under here
so I lifted it and there was a memo, so I went "What is it?!" but it only says, "Be careful of the glass".
Oh? Oh, it's not...
Here... There's even a shovel.
Can I go... can I go in?
Oh my!
I think this child was my first love.
"He pulled my hair so I cried. Why does he only do this to me?"
It is. If this is me, this is the child.
Is it this child?
He has to be here.
When Cinderella was young,
she lost both her parents.
From her stepmother and...
Ow!
Who is it?!
Eh, whatever.
If I catch you, you’re dead!
♫ Submeigeti in longing ♫
♫ that gefs thicker as time passes ♫
♫ Can we not turn back time? ♫
♫ If you hugged me as you did bach then ♫
♫ I would feel better now ♫
Hyung, where did you find this?
-Over there. -Oh. down there? You didn't find it here?
I don't really understand it actually.
Oh, it looks like this.
Ah.
"During the talent show, everyone danced together, dances really well. He was like a celebrity." So...
Ah. but there has to be a name.
-Oh! Han Ga In! -Han Ga In!
-There was a name in the back! -That's what I was looking for!
So In the front, I thought there should be a name, but there's no name. That's right! The name!
-If this is truly Han Ga In... -Yeah.
Then it could be him. He's holding a mic.
He's not wearing glasses. Hyung,look. We only have a little information, so let’s solve it like this.
-It could be you. -Me or...
Me, Gwang Soo and Gary. It's one of us.
-It's one of you or... -Let's think broadly. It could also be Song Ji Hyo, right?
Han Ga In's previous love.
-Hyung, you can keep this well hidden, right? -Of course.
-It makes me uneasy. -Do you want to take it then?
Hyung, but if you're eliminated, what...
Could I not hold onto it?
-If you get caught later... -Fine. You keep it. If you find another one. show me.
Of course!
I promise. We need to go around quickly during this time.
-Hold it. -All right.
It seems it's Han Ga In and someone else who are the first loves.
Oh, Ga In-ssi. Why are you...
-Excuse me? -Have you found something?
No. I haven't, but...
-You found something, didn't you? -You haven't found anything, Ga In-ssi?
-I did slightly find something... -Oh, you did?
-Really? -Yes.
But, I can't make sense of it.
You can't make sense of it? Why not?
-It's insufficient. -Really?
Then, shall we both... look at them...?
-Shall we? -And analyse them?
-But this is... -Yes?
Look at Jong Kook hyung's poison at work.
Okay.
-Oppa, what’s the name on yours? -Whose is it?
-Mine is mine. -Han Ga In?
-Oppa. yours in mine, too. right? -This one is also Han Ga In.
-He's a troublemaker. He pulled my hair. That's not it. See, we have to analyse the photo.
There are kids with glasses and kids without, within the boys.
-He's not wearing glasses here, too. -He's not, see.
-Then firstly, it's not the ones with glasses. -Then taking out the ones with glasses...
Gwang Soo and Gary.
And me. But he's holding a mic here.
So we thought, perhaps it could be a singer?
Then it's either Gary or me.
-But... -Yes?
He's definitely a singer.
"My dream is becoming a singer."
- "...danced together... dances really well. He was like a celebrity." -Wait...
Could it be me?
It sounds like "My Childhood Dream". "My Childhood Dream". Turbo's "My Childhood Dream".
It seems like Jong Kook oppa...
I'll keep it and I'll hide it well.
If perhaps...
That diary... is a haeuseok that I'm giving to you. Ga In-ssi.
- I've completely become a an o your drama. - Yang Myeong-gun...
Lord Yang Myeong...
-Please, go first. -Yes.. I will.
But... what is really sad about Yang Myeorig-gun'is...
he dies in the last episode.
-He dies in the last episode. -What did you say?
He dies?
Yang Myeong-gun dies in the end!
Wow, this is ominous.
This is ominous...
It’s one of these three...
He dances well, and he pulled my hair...
It seems like Jong Kook oppa...
There's no way to confirm this...
Oh?!
This way. I can't open this anywhere.
No, because there's no information for me!
"Today..." "Today is picture day."
"He wore glasses today to look handsome. He looks better with glasses."
One, two, three...
-You have a hint, don't you? -Show us.
I do have a hint, but...
-Dong Hoon! -Yes...?
-Can't you just show us? -No, but what were you two doing together?
Can't you just show us?
-I will show you. but what were you doing? -Before, we got together...
- to see what we had to do with the photo. -I really don't know what to do so I asked him.
To ask what I had to do.
-So there's something... -Do not come close.
-I am trying to do something... -Do you have something?
"He was very handsome..He looked like a fairytale prince."
"I'm going to grow up and marry him."
"He was very handsome"? Handsome?
So we can definitely say that it's not Gary hyung. Gwang Soo or Suk Jin hyung.
But do you know what the most important hint is?
The colour green!
Jae Suk hyung.
Jae Suk oppa likes green.
Green-dori.
-Come out this way. -Okay, okay. It's quiet.
-Green. Green clothes. -Exactly.
Because Yoo Hyuk is dance.
Right! Dance!
"He wore glasses today to look handsome."
At the back, "Han Ga In".
-You didn't know, did you? -No.
-It's Han Ga In's picture diary -Really?
-So we’re trying to find the person Han Ga In liked. -I'll show you mine.
" danced the best. He was like a celebrity."
-Dance? Yoo Hyuk? -Yoo Hyuk! Dance!
So it’s Jae Suk.
-He's coming. -Jae Suk!
-We have something to say to you. -What is it?
-No. -Come here.
I'm saying the truth.
-We have something to tell you. -We found your first love.
Hey.
-Your first love... -Why?
-The clues we found show that you're the first love. -Me and you, hyung?
-No. You're the first love. -Me and who?
Whose first love?
-Hyung. you’re just the first love. -You're today's first love protagonist.
Why? What's the clue?
-Ga In-ssi. -There's something.
Have you found something?
What did you find?
-You're the first love! -Why?! Why am I the first love?
-Jae Suk hyung! -Jae Suk hyung!
-I think your memory should be returning. -Of what?
-What did you say? -Are your memories of your first love not returning?
I have no clue.
-Hyung, I'll tell you but, it's not you. -It's not me?
Yeah, I'm...
Gary, you're not it. If it were, they would have called you out especially.
Usually they make you wear green, but they didn't this time.
Exactly.
Hey Then is it me?
Was it me?
-They didn't call you out separately? -No.
Hyung, can't you just tell us what you know?
Yeah! You should tell us!
-I know for sure. -How are you so sure?
Because I'm me!
H-hey! That was cool!
Hey. Jong Kook is really cool. He's the coolest!
"Because I'm me!" how cool is that?
But where is Gwang Soo?
Where is Gwang Soo-ssi?
"Today we held a party for the August birthdays."
"I gave ♥♥a kiss as a present."
Happy birthday to you!
Happy birthday, dear August birthday friends!
August birthdays? Jae Suk hyung has an August birthday.
Ji Hyo nuna is also in August.
This is Ga In nuna's?
Nuna!
Do you have something?
-Did you find something? -I...
Do you know? Who?
It said they had a birthday party.
What day?
Ah, but...
You have it, right? You didn't hide it?
-I hid it. -Where is it?
Gan I tell you? It's my first time finding something like this.
I'm not sure what I should do.
This is my first time finding something like this.
-I'm not sure what to do. -Just show it to me once. Just once.
What did it say? Just the drawing, so I can see what it is about.
Ah, show me. Ah, so frustrating. So frustrating.
-Are you angry...? -No
where Is it?
I hid it... in the VJ's backpack.
I hid it in hyung's backpack.
Let's hide here.
What is this?
This is so strange.
This... is our secret place.
-"We held a party..." "I gave ♥♥ a ki..." -But they're both wearing glasses.
-Yeah. They're wearing glasses.
It's HaHa hyung or Jae Suk hyung or Suk Jin hyung.
I'll go hide Th is.
Back into that bag.
-I'm telling you without asking for anything in return. -Thank you.
When’s his birthday?
It’s August 20th.
-August 20th? Then he's wearing glasses... -Jong Kook hyung, Jong Kook hyung.
I'll try to... first...
What are you doing, Gwang Soo?
Yes?
-Wait! -Have you found something?
-Have you found something? -No I haven't.
Ga in-ssi, do you really not know?
I don't. How do you know?
Do you really not know?
This is so pitiful!
Ah, Yeon Woo!
Your memory has to return! Your memories!
-Gwang! -Your memory has to return, your memories!
-You have to do this and 'Ga'. -Ga.
-Gwang! -Ga!
Cross!
Don't follow him. Ga In-ssi!
-Just please understand my feelings. -No, he's just..!
-We were the same team! -Ga In-ssi, he's really no good.
Then I'll ask you something oppa. If you have something.
-If you know something. -Truly...
-What are you talking about?! -But...
-We haven't even shared anything! -He's really...!
-We haven't shared anything! -He's really...!
-But I gave you my all! -Ga In-ssi!
He's really... You, you know...
You always... Let's say you're not the first love.
Then, if you had the chance, who would you eliminate first?
You, hyung!
-But I wouldn't. -Why not?
Because I should stay until the end with hyung.
Even if I trust everyone. I can't trust you!
Kook!
Soo! Cross!
Cross!
Lee Gwang Soo, out! Lee Gwang Soo. out!
So he's eliminated?
-Yes. -Why?
Why?
-Because I ripped it off. -Oh really? You know something, don't you?
-Do you really not know? -I don't.
Give me a hint! It's my first appearance, and how could you not even give me one hint? It’s so merciless here!
Gwang Soo!
Where is Gwang Soo?
Hey!
She's so pitiful...
Truly... Truly... Wol's memory must return.
Wol needs to get better.
Hey, Kim Jong Kook! Did you eliminate him?
Did you eliminate him?
If I'm not her first love. then...
-Isn't it that? -What?
What is he saying today?!
Dong Hoon!
Watch out, watch out.
-You two are... not that right? -Are what?
-What are you talking about, hyung! -What would we do to you?
We were reasoning.
Reasoning what?
-It's right, right? I don't think there's anyone else but him. -It's 100%!
They went in that way. I pushed the two of them together on purpose that way.
But Wol's memory is completely not returning.
Then Han Ga In tore off Gwang Soo's name tag?
-No, I ripped it off! -Why did you?
Because Gwang Soo is nothing!
What's with that?
Then this hyung is also nothing!
Hyung! I didn't rip it off! I didn't!
Ji Suk Jin, out! Ji Suft Jin, out!
Hang on...
Is it truly me and Ga In?
In the past, Ga In and I were in a skit.
I think they're referring to that.
-Oppa. -Hyung, hyung.
Hyung.
-Hyung, let's go to the prep room or now. -Why?
-Do you know who is it? -I have no clue.
-We know for sure. -Who is it?
-It's Jong Kook oppa, -Why?
-Let's go that way first. -The prep room.
I thought it was you, hyung.
I also... I... I thought maybe it was me... It's not me?
-It's not you, oppa. -Why not?
It's not me?
-Did you eliminate Suk Jin oppa? -Because I haven't found anything...
Oppa, oppa, see.
Jong Kook oppa guided you somewhere.
-Yeah, he... -So everyone thought it was you.
-Oh! -See this!
In the picture diary... "Today Is picture day. He wore his glasses today to look handsome."
"He looks better with glasses." So glasses means that you...
So it's not me. It's someone who doesn't wear glasses.
So. the people who are wearing glasses since they were younger Is Ji Suk Jin oppa and HaHa oppa. It's one of you three.
-So Gwang Soo is already eliminated and I'm... -Yeah.
But. the scarier thing is. when Gwang Soo was eliminated, I witnessed the scene.
-But? -Jong Kook oppa was with Han Ga In-ssi.
Really?
-So.. -It's not me.
Oppa, oppa. you thought you were the protagonist, didn't you...
-But Oppa, see, what's more important is. -Wait, Kwon Ryul...
Ah hyung! You had something!
Hyung. how could you be like this?
Well, I tricked people, too.
-What did you find? -What I showed you earlier. That one.
-What about you? -I haven't found anything.
You... didn't find anything, but how do you know everything...?
But I witnessed the scene with my own two eyes, oppa.
If the first loves meet, after they gather 5 name tags, they can open the time capsule, oppa.
We need to ally and rip off the name tag of either Jong Kook oppa or Han Ga In-ssi.
-Hyung, let's try to win against the guest! -Let's do that!
Hey. this looks like where a picture diary...
It opens...
This is crazy, this is crazy, this is crazy, this is crazy.
My gosh.
Hey. wow. my gosh!
"Today we went to a friend's house for snacks."
"It tasted really bad. Ugh,."
It tasted bad...?
It's tastier than my mom’s cooking.
Could you teach my mom...?
Wah, it looks delicious!
Kids, eat well.
Yes, thank you!
Oh., ugh!
Oh my god. Stress.
Why don't you like it? It's tasty.
Glasses don't matter... Because he takes the on and off...
An August birthday... and he dances well...
First, he needs to be a singer...
If he's a singer, it's Jong Kook oppa, Gary oppa. and..
HaHa. these three.
But they had a birthday party in August.
She looks like my mom.
These days l've been focusing on fusion dishes-
The people with birthdays in August are...
Ga In.I'm sorry. Actually, it was because I liked you.
-Hey, who do you think is the coolest? -Me?
Um. I... I... Him!
-Happy birthday. -Thanks!
Ga In...
It's HaHa oppa.
I remember,
I finally remember!
It's me... I'm this week's protagonist...
Protagonist...!
Do not come close! But also do not stray far.
Ah, you startled me!
I'm an August birthday...
'During the talent show, everyone danced together." I dance really well!
"He was very handsome." You know how handsome I am!
My first love!
You know my mom. This looks exactly like my mom!
You have to stay on this side to be filmed properly.
You must find these hints quickly.
- Chronologically? - and stack them chronologically.
You will then know who your first love is.
Ah, if you put them together...
Windbreaker!
Windbreaker! Windbreaker, windbreaker.
But what if it's not me?
Ah, it makes me cry.
-Why? Why? -This is really sad.
-This is really sad. -Why, what's there?
I think I may be too absorbed in this drama.
I like you.
Will you be my first love?
Since you can't be my last love.
Has your memory returned?
Are you alone?
-Are you alone? -No, HaHa oppa Is ins de.
-HaHa's inside? -I think he came to check something.
-What? -Oppa, have you found any picture diaries?
Do you still not know anything?
Nothing?!
-But... -How is this so similar to 'Moon that Embraces the Sun'?
Oppa! Is it you, oppa?
No, I told you. I'm...
I'm Yang Myeong-gun...
You two., what...
What are you two doing?
-It's really we Rd. -What did you hear from Hwon?
-Oppa, the Hwon I know is different. -What?
-Younthoughts are totally open, Hwon-ie! -The Hwon I know is different.
Hey Gary, come here!
Yang Myeong-gun!
-I'm Yang Myeong-gun! Today my role is Yang Myeong-gun! -He’s Yang Myeong-gun!
Yang Maeng-
-What are you two doing? -Hyung!
-I'm Just... I felt sorry for Ga In-ssi who doesn't understand this game. -Then who has the name tag?
-Gwang Soo's and Suk Jin oppa's. -Yeah!
-Why do you have that? -And Suk Jin oppa's?
-Ji Hyo, are you doubting me? -Yes.
You make me crazy.
Yang Myeong-gun.
-What?! -Yeon Woo!
-Yeon Woo! -There's no need to pretend!
I already figured it out!
Why is he Yang Myeong-gun?!
Do you have both sides?
-For now, let's separate, -Let's separate.
Ga In-ssi, if I told you his much, retrieve your memory and...
-Ga In, I think you're the most important! -Please find your love!
Quickly...
-What was written there? -What was written on yours?
On yours, oppa.
-What about your drawing? -I hid it over there.
-Where? -In there.
Where?
Where did you hide it?
-I've hidden a few. -You saw a few?!
Really? How many?
Ga In! Ga In!
Hey, wait! Wait!
Yoo Jae Suk, out! Yoo Jae Suk, out!
-I think it's me. -It's not you!
-Rest, it's not you. -Yoo Jae Suk. out!
Oh my God.
What did it say?
Yoo Jae Suk is eliminated?
Who ripped it off? Ga In-ssi?
-Oppa, then doesn't that mean that Han Ga In-ssi is hiding something? -Hyung!
Hyung!
Did Ga In-ssi understand incorrectly...?
Why are you down there?
Eh? Just thinking. About who's on my side.
-Has your memory still not returned? -I don't know who it is.
-It's not that...! -I also...
But in the drawing, the feet were big. Because it was green, I said it was Jae Suk hyung.
Hobbit!
Hyung! His feet alone are 280!
-And also, the stuff here... -Exactly...
-It's HaHa. -HaHa. he takes. his glasses on and off.
-That's right.7-Yeah.
And his feet are just big.
It’s really not me?
Ignoring that, I'd be very happy if it were me...
Dong Hoon-
How is it that...
Has your memory returned?
I...
I really don't know who it's.
I told you. Today I am Yang Myeong.
There's no way that it is me.
-It's not you, oppa? -Because I was Yang Myeong from the very beginning.
-Then who is it? -I am working to get your memory back.
Then...
-Shall we see the notebooks again...? -Shall we?’
I hid them really well.
Where did you hide them?
I hid them within the plane...
You hid them within the plane? Really?
Where inside the plane is there a hiding spot...?
If it's inside the plane, we need to go that way.
Ga In-ssi, do you really not know?
-I'm Yang Myeong-gun! Today my role is Yang Myeong-gun! -He's Yang Myeong-gun!
Yang Maeng-
Ah Yeon Woo. Your memory has to return! Your memory!
Maiden Yeon Woo... you have to take this, too...
Maiden Yeon Woo, you have to take this, too. so you can have five.
Maiden Yeon Woo, you have to take this, too.
He's coming, he's coming.
Who ripped your tag off?
Hyung! I got mine ripped off my Ga In-ssi!
-Hyung! -As it should be.
-I'm Yang Myeong. -What?
I'm Yang Myeong-gun.
You're not Yang Myeong-gun. You're fool-gun.
-Hyung! I know. I figured everything out. -Hey, you...! OK...
I deduced it amazingly once again.
-It s HaHa isn't it. -I figured out it was HaHa.
Why is your mouth so alive in jail?
After ripping mine off for no reason, you're doing well, doing well-
You're just condiments, condiments!
He wasn't wearing glasses and he was wearing green.
-He dances well. -Green!
He was holding a mic.
-I'm also green.. -It's one of you two.
I'll go look at them.
-I hid them. -Where? The plane? Tell me where. I'll go look at them by myself.
Inside the plane, there are a lot seats. I hid them beneath the seats.
Where are they?
What?!
Hey, what are you doing?!
Hyung, I'm sorry. I'm her first love.
No way! It's me!
I tell you. it's me!
It's me! See this!
It's not. I'm sorry.
-It's me! -You're not, hyung. Ask Ga In.
-I'm sorry, oppa, -I tell you, it's me!
-It’s not! -Hey, glasses! Sunglasses!
Please!
We're sorry.
Gary. out! Gary. out!
There's no need for you to lip sync that, is there?
How long will we continue this?
My dear says her legs hurt-!
Ah, you scared me!
Hey, you all...
Ahh, so scary... Ah, Ga I n-ssi.
This is embarrassing as your first love.
You're showing us many sides of you.
Ga In-ssi!
Please protect me!
Ah Who's this?
Ah, have you finally come?
-So? -Ga In-ssi! Ga In-ssi!
Quickly, quickly, quickly, quickly! Qu ckly tear it off!
Ga In-ssi! Ga in-ssl! She's...!
Oh, so scary! So scary! Please tear it off quickly!
Ga In-ssi! Please tear it off! You don't understand how scary she is!
Please help! Oh, you've nearly gotten it! We've won, we've won! Come on Ji Hyo, please!
Oh, she's scary! She's hitting me! See. see! She’s kicking me!
No, this can't continue, ack!
How dare you...!
Ah. so scary!
Hey! Hey! Hey!
Sorry that I cannot be your first love!
She protected me!
My first love protected me!
-What's this? -Oh, what's this here?
I think we have to go there?
What's this?
Shall we rip it off? Do we have to?
Ah! This!
Because they told us to find five.
Jong Kook oppa here, because he helped us the most.
One, two, three!
What's that?
Because they told us to find five.
Jong Kook oppa here, because he helped us the most.
One, two, three!
What's that?
What's this?
Let's hide everything! Because It's ours!
-What's that? -It's here! It’s here!
-There's something here. -What is that?
-That's that thing! -A vitamin container.
Back then, we did a lot of stuff like this in that container.
-What's this? -I remember! I remember!
I really remember!
-What do you remember? -Actually, I wanted to sit with you. Let's be good friends. From Ga In.
-No way, no way! I wrote that! -I remember this! 1 remember this!
-That's the real thing, the real thing! -Gold!
Good job!
Here, you take one. and I take one.
-Is this real gold? -It's real gold. Real.
-It’s real gold. -Real gold?
You really like it!
Since my first love gave this to me...
-You., have it all. -You're manly!
Manly! Manly!
Hey, why are you crying?! Why are you crying after giving her the gold?!
Why are you crying?!
The forgotten memory. First Love. Han Ga In. HaHa!
This Is more nerve wracking than live TV.
This, this is the code.
Is this a Western alphabet?
How'd you find that?
Suk Jin hyung!
It's within this radlus?
Gwang Soo!