Subtitles by DramaFever
[Busan - A city of Romance by the ocean]
[A place full of sightseeing,
food and things to do.]
[A city of vacation
lifting everyone's spirits up.]
We're in Busan!
It really has been a long time
since we've been to Busan.
Seeing those flowers...
does it mean that the five guests...
There are seven of us here
including Ji Hyo...
Is one of us going to be left on our own?
Maybe Ji Hyo will have one,
and the rest of us will be in pairs.
- Could it be?
- Is that how it's going to be?
[In that case,
will today be a couple race?]
Although I don't know who will be on today,
today will be another...
- Beautiful memories.
- I do have some anticipation.
We're in Busan,
we should go with a romantic theme.
All the flowers bordering the way...
[In the midst of all their anticipation,
who will be their first guest?]
[Huh?]
It's a man.
Ji Hyo, this must make you feel good.
[Even at the briefest glance,
it's a 100% male silhouette.]
- Who could it be?
- Min Soo?
[Could it be... the hunter?]
[The founder of flower boys,
Lee Jong Won.]
Oh! The last game?
[The lead actor of all the 1990's hit
dramas, Lee Jong Won.]
[Especially the 1994 drama, The Last Game
that ignited Korea's passion for basketball.]
Ji Hyo... you can be Ji Hyo's partner
for today's couple games.
[Just like he used to act with the
lead actress of the time, Shim Eun Ha.]
[Today's with Snail-Ji Hyo?]
She's much more beautiful than when
Eun Ha used to be really popular.
Please don't say things like that,
it's going to go to her head.
[My little Junior is pretty...]
We will anticipate the cool pairing of
our snail and dashing Lee Jong Won.
Our next guest, please step out!
[Huh?]
No way!
[Could it be... Psy?]
- That's not Psy.
- He's a horrible dancer!
[A total chaotic dancing style.]
- He is not a very good dancer.
- Who is it?
[The jolly actor, Son Byung Ho.]
[Byung Ho's joking around that makes
others cringe in embarrassment.]
- Hello.
- Hello, it's good to see you.
- Our anticipation is starting to...
- It's starting to crumble.
Even though we're glad to
see you on here...
To introduce the next guest...
As for the Gangnam Style dance, this is...
[This is Son Byung Ho's style.]
[Three flower decorated doors still remain.]
[Is it finally, Girl's Generation?]
Oh... that's more like it!
- That's it!
- That's it.
[What the heck?]
[Clumsy dancing unbefitting
of Girl's Generation.]
[This person is?]
[A powerful visual actor, Go Chang Suk.]
[Entering with shy steps.]
- Seriously...
- It's Chang Suk.
Chang Suk... this is the first time
I've seen dancing like that.
- How old are you?
- I was born in 1970.
You're four years younger than me.
[Younger by four years than
the Big-nosed brother.]
[The remaining two guests are?]
With each guest,
my anticipating is building.
I'm starting to build up my anticipation now.
My anticipation has changed now.
What is this music?
-Wow... that's a nice pose!
- He's slim!
- He's slim.
- I think it's a young person.
[The confident, actor Shin Jung Geun.]
[The strength of these older brothers,
who cringes laughter with each appearance.]
- Hello!
- What brings you on here?
I just came.
Just... he just came.
Seriously... I have seen all of them
on TV so often.
This is awesome.
I don't know what it may be like today,
but the moment the four of you appeared
I think I'm pretty sure of the direction
that we'll be taking today.
I think I know where the writer is headed.
We really are grateful to all of you.
We really are full of anticipation
for your action today...
[Wait! There's still one more guest!]
What era is this song from?
This song is from the seventies, isn't it?
[The profoundness of next actor can be
guessed at just by the music alone.]
- I think I know who that may be!
- I know that vibe!
[By any chance,
is it Suk Jin and Jae Suk's Senior?]
I think that's our Senior!
[The legendary comedian, Im Ha Ryong!]
[This is the legendary diamond step!]
[The Junior's affectionate dance response.]
- It's good to see you.
- It's so great to see you.
[Overcoming the comedy to become
the legendary top notch actor]
- Without a doubt...
- It's our Senior, Ha Ryong.
Our brother!
[With the appearance of the big brother,
all the other brothers become calmer.]
This is really embarrassing.
[A famous phrase, 'This is embarrassing'.]
I went through a lot of trouble
to borrow this outfit.
On such a hot day like this,
all of you came out in suits.
So, you are the oldest one here, right?
- Second, third, fourth...
- He's a bit older too...
- And this is...
-I'm the youngest!
I'm the youngest!
[The youngest.]
[Baby Chang Suk - Born in 70.
Older brother, Jong Won- Born in 69]
At first, I used formal speech with him
thinking that he was older.
If he was born in 1970...
he is the same age with all of them.
This is... this is the first time we've been
pushed aside by a character.
The doorways that they stepped out of
are decorated with flowers as you see.
Today is a special episode with our
flower middle age men.
Flower middle aged men?
I will announce the team's first,
and we will start the race.
First...
- Lee Jong Won...
- Ah, Jong Won... he's the Ace.
And Gary.
- Jong Won... it's an honor!
- I'm glad to hear it.
And the next one is... Ha Ha.
[And the groom to be, Ha Ha.]
[The two kids excited at meeting
the CF star of back in the day.]
Song Ji Hyo.
- The snail... Ji Hyo, the snail.
- What the heck is this?
- The snail too?
- So this is one team?
- Then who's going to be Ji Chang?
- With your hair, you're Ji Chang.
[Haroro as the character, Son Ji Chang and
Snail Blank-Ji as the role of Shim Eun Ha.]
Gary has no choice to take the role
of Jang Dong Gun.
- That's how it should be.
- You're right... I see it!
- He's pretty good looking.
- Thank you, Jong Won!
- So that's 'The Last Game' Team.
- I will announce the next team.
- Im Ha Ryong...
- Ah... Ha Ryong!
All your faces look pretty disappointed.
- No, not at all!
- What are you talking about?
My weak joints are
driving me crazy these days!
The next person is...
Yoo Jae Suk.
[Jae Suk paying his respects to
his Senior.]
- Wow... seriously...
- I have a feeling about the next person.
Son Byung Ho.
[The next teammate is Son Byung Ho.]
- Wow... Byung Ho!
- This is a good pairing.
These are the two oldest guests
we have on here today!
Then why don't we go around to all
the nice places in Busan...
And the last member is Ji Suk Jin.
[The last remaining member is,
Big-nosed brother.]
[Jae Suk to be the youngest.]
How can you stick Suk Jin in there too?
- But that's your team...
- How can this...
[The remaining Jung Geun, Chang Suk,
Jong Kook and Kwang Soo to be a team.]
If you combine all four of you,
it's more than 200 years in age.
How can I be the youngest one here
when I was born in 1972?
It's been awhile since
you've been the youngest, right?
Ah, yes...
[Jae Suk born in '72 as the youngest.]
We're the youngest team here.
- Why do you have your arms around them?
- What's wrong with it?
- It's because I like them so much!
- Stand more comfortably!
It's not awkward in the least with
Jong Kook's arms around us.
Seriously... I love these guys.
Chang Suk looks like the scientist in
Atom Boy with his suit on.
[With the suit, his face becomes that of
a familiar scientist from Atom Boy.]
[Today's race is Busan Vacation
Diamond Step race.]
- I think we've got an advantage here.
- The title is nice.
[A special title in
celebration of his wedding.]
I bet you'll be singing that song
quite a bit today.
- Congratulations, Ha Ha.
- Congratulations.
I will show each team a board with all
of Busan's attractions written on it.
You have to toss the die and
move to wherever it points to
and complete the mission
and come back to the home base.
The chances of winning the final race goes up
tremendously for the team that returns first
so it's best to complete them quickly
and return as soon as possible.
[Busan vacation race - Start!]
Before we start the Busan Vacation Race,
you have to toss the die.
So I guess we start here and goes to
wherever it points to.
[The Big Brother Team 'Go' one spot.]
[Atom Boy Scientist Team 'Jump' two spots.]
[The Last Game Team also 'Go' one spot.]
- Then, we're going to head out.
- I'm putting my trust in Jae Suk.
- Secretary Ji...
- Yes, sir?
- Make sure to pay attention.
- Secretary Ji...
Secretary Ji, Driver Yoo and the Chairman.
- Director Son...
- Yes, sir...
I understand.
Wow... look at all that.
This is great.
[Forgetting about the mission,
the Chairman is drinking in the view.]
Isn't that the site for the ending scene
in the 'Chaser?'
When I look at you through the
rearview mirror
you really look like
you're just sightseeing.
Sightseeing with my guides.
[Missions are no different than
leisure sightseeing for us.]
What are we going to do right now?
We're right now...
have you ever watched the show?
- I have watched the show.
- He really likes Running Man.
- First... we got to jump two spots...
- We are ahead of everyone right now.
We have to go to the spot and do a mission.
None of know what the mission is though.
Is it something scary?
I really don't like amusement parks.
[Something a little fast is waiting for you.]
Why are we doing something so difficult?
[The coziness of the final
'The Last Game' Team.]
- Number one, Snail.
- Yes.
- Number two, Lee Jong Won.
- Yeah.
Number three, Son Ji Chang!
Number four, Jang Dong Gun!
- How did we get such a good team like this?
- Running Man's all about the visual.
[Snail - Original Lee Jong Won -
Jang Dong... Kang Hee Gun]
[Self-proclaimed best visual team.]
Since we've been into this team,
we should get first place.
We have to show them
what we're made of, right?
I heard that your daughter
really likes Running Man.
No matter what's going on,
she always turns it on when it's on.
Did your daughter tell you anything about it?
[His daughter's advice
for coming on the show?]
She says we could be picking something,
and for me to never be the one to pick it.
Why? Why did she say that?
That's the main point of this show.
[Will he go along with
his daughter's warnings?]
- Here it is, here it is.
- Where?
- We're here, we're here.
- Running Man?
- Jong Won, let's get out.
- Let's get out.
[Discovers the Running Man flag.]
[Busan Nampodong, 'A' market.
Busan's infamous market.]
[This place even made an appearance
in the movie, 'Friend'.]
[A mecca of outdoor food stalls,
and street food vendors.]
This one... read this one.
[Bring back the cards after dividing up into
two teams and eating the food.]
[The shape within the two cards has to
match in order to succeed the mission.]
[Team work and luck has to
work together...]
- This is just... This is luck.
- This is all about luck.
- No, it's about telepathy.
- Telepathy... we don't have telepathy!
You should practice then.
[Ah... practice...]
[And they have to move through the
market in a tube with their partner.]
- Okay.
- Let's practice.
- A number. Tell us a number between 1- 10.
- One, two, three!
- One!
- Three!
What did you say?
I said, three, and Ji Hyo said three too...
[You said three too?]
[Telepathy practice. These two
shout out three simultaneously.]
[This is... Answer me 2011?]
[In that case...]
What... what is it between you two?
Are you not over me?
Are you still not over me?
[A strange coincidence that
makes them think of their past.]
What's with you guys?
[Now deciding on the two menus
by selecting two pieces of paper.]
Why don't you step up, Jong Won?
Look at Jong Won flexing his
fist right now.
[His fist flexing on his own.]
[Just like the buzzer beater
in 'The Last Game'.]
[The taste of the time back then...]
[The market food vendor that
the Green Team will be visiting is?]
Chive pancakes?
[Chive pancakes - Stall Number 69]
[Green Team chooses Chive pancakes
and Patbingsoo stalls.]
[The Big Brother Team arrives.]
- Someone's already here?
- They're already here.
- There you are!
- You guys are already here?
Chairman... this way.
Have you come here to sightsee?
You must be here on a filial vacation?
He's here on a business trip.
We're going to get going.
[The Green Team heads out.]
- Make sure to receive my telepathy message.
- Make sure to pick the right card.
- Pick the right card, okay?
- I'll be sending you a message.
[Heading into the busy market.]
[All the food vendors catching their eye.]
Patbingsoo! Where's the place that sells
Patbingsoo around here?
- Patbingsoo!
- Where is the Patbingsoo place?
There are too many signs around here.
- Secretary Ji, make sure to escort him well.
- Yes, I understand, Sir.
We can't fit.
- Ha Ryong... you have to lose some weight.
- This is...
[Chairman and Secretary Ji
getting off to a difficult start.]
Where do they sell the chive pancakes?
[Their destination is
the chive pancake vendor.]
Where's stall number 69?
Where's 69?
-Impala!
- Impala!
- Wow... Impala's still alive.
- Impala, fighting!
[Everywhere they go, they're met with
welcome and cheer from the citizens.]
Jong Shin!
[Jong Shin... Yoon?]
[Mistaking Big-nosed brother
for Yong Shin Yoon.]
I heard about your son...
Jong Shin... she said, Jong Shin!
I'm not Yoon Jong Shin!
[Busan Kwanganri, 'D' amusement park]
- Hello, hello there.
- Jong Kook, you're so handsome!
Thank you! Busan is full of life!
- It's full of life...
- Hi!
- What is Diving Coaster?
- What is that?
[The exciting rides that await them!]
[Busan Vacation Diamond Step]
[Roller coaster karaoke room]
[If you score above 90 points while singing
karaoke on a roller coaster, you pass!]
They want us to ride this and sing?
You have to ride this...
But they should ask if we have a phobia or
if we're an invalid or something.
You don't have to go far as
saying invalid!
- Can you get above 90 points on this?
- Of course, you can.
- If we don't get it, we have to keep riding?
- That's correct.
- It's going to be two people at a time.
- I see.
You're really competitive.
If we succeed,
you have to excuse me for the insults.
Why are you afraid of being insulted?
Who in the world likes to be insulted?
- What... what do you want to sing?
- Something we can shout.
[Discomfort?]
I'm sorry... but is this shut?
- This is... this is really tight.
- But it's not...
But you can fit like three fists
in front of Kwang Soo.
Do I have to be insulted over this too?
[Chooses the song, 'Come back to Busan'.]
Okay... here we go!
[Getting flustered as soon as
the roller coaster starts moving.]
This is really scary!
[The time has come...]
[Extremely nervous.]
[With both eyes tightly shut.]
[The starting point is the most
terrifying point of any rollercoaster.]
[Arriving at the summit.]
This is...
[A nose-dive.]
[Starting to sing again after coming
back to their senses... impossible.]
[Extremely funny to the people watching.]
[Screams]
It's falling again... it's falling again!
[Feels like death.]
[Even in their dreams,
they can't sing in this situation.]
[Sincerely screaming out loud.]
[Arrives at the finish line.]
[A round on the rollercoaster has
turned these two docile.]
The score...
[Needs above 90 points.
Just what will their score be?]
Please...
[81 points]
You've scored 81 points.
[Fail - But a fairly high score.]
[Is it my turn now then...]
We are Running Man.
- Patbingsoo, Patbingsoo...
- Here it is. Here it is!
[Finally discovers it.]
- Patbingsoo!
- Here, this is the place.
- This is it.
- We're here. This is the place.
[Refreshingly cool and delicious Patbingsoo.]
We have to choose it well.
[A piece of paper for them to take
under each dish.]
- Make sure to do a good job. Pick well.
- Our telepathy has to work!
- I think it's up there.
- I think it's up there too.
We have to choose well...
otherwise we'll be in trouble.
- Here it is.
- There it is!
- We found it, we found it!
- Okay, okay, okay!
- Let's take the middle one.
- Let's go with the middle one.
Which one should we go with,
Jong Won?
- Let's try our telepathy...
- Let's check it.
[Using the telepathy...]
Everyone... please help us send
the telepathic message to our team.
List your hands above your heads!
One, two, three!
[Receive our message!]
[Receive our telepathy!]
- One, two, three... one!
- Three!
- Let's do it again. Two!
- One, two, three... two!
Okay, okay...
[Oh? Jong Won and Snail
also picks the middle one?]
[However, just because the placement is the
same, it doesn't mean it's the same card!]
- Enjoy it.
- It's delicious.
- Did you pick the middle one?
- Yes, we chose the middle one.
[Ha Ha and Gary also
enjoying their delicious treat.]
[Would telepathy really have worked?]
You have to take the card and return
without looking at it.
- Jong Won... I love you.
- Thank you.
[Still as popular as ever.]
Thank you for the meal, Mother.
- For some reason, I think we got it.
- If we get this in one try, we really are...
I don't know how long we've
been walking for.
I'm going to go crazy here.
Hello, hello... here it is!
Oh, there it is.
There it is... hang on.
[The market staple,
seeded sweet hotcakes.]
[The lure of its' sweetness and crispness.]
- Eenie, meenie, minie-mo...
Eenie, meenie, minie-mo...
Which one should we eat?
We have to choose one of these three...
[Each of the cards contain a
different shape.]
- The middle one... okay.
- I'll take the card.
- We have to use our telepathy.
- Let's take the one that she just made.
[Ha Ryong and Suk Jin choose the one
that was just made.]
Ha Ryong... you look so young.
It's not that I'm young,
but that I'm still childish.
I'm not that old.
Wow, this is delicious.
It's so good!
- Wow... this looks delicious!
- It does look really good.
[Byung Ho and Jae Suk also biting
into their delicious treat.]
This is way too good.
[The heavenly taste.]
- We picked the one in the middle.
- Seriously?
You picked the middle one too?
If you did, that makes me a little nervous...
- Now, your cards...
- Please! Wait, wait, wait...
Our energy... let's gather our energy.
One, two, three.
One, two, three!
[Huh?]
[Match]
[Wow! Succeeds in just one try!]
[Explosion of their joy.]
- Wow, we really...
- This is a match.
Can I take that as a memorabilia?
I want to show it to my daughter.
[The Green Team passes their
first mission in one shot.]
Telepathy.
One, two, three!
- Those guys...
- I bet they didn't get it.
Jong Won, since you're in a good mood,
why don't you show us your move?
Come on, show it to us.
- Is it okay?
- Sir, can we use the chair for a moment?
- Yes, you can use it.
- Let's see this. It's been a long time.
Let's see this.
You guys got it in one shot?
Congratulations.
- We got it in one try.
- Just a minute... wait...
[During that brief time,
a chair has been prepped.]
[The commercial that's the topic
of the conversation...]
[That main lead, Lee Jong Won.]
[The moment for the perfect reenactment.]
[A perfect reenactment!]
[He still has it!]
- Jong Won, you were so quiet at first...
- This is fun.
- And now he's wanting to throw it himself...
- And earlier, he was screaming too!
He said he wasn't going to do anything,
but he's doing everything.
I guess his competitiveness is still alive.
I'm going to spin the die now.
- I hope you guys get 'Back'.
- Go!
[Moves up one spot]
It's the amusement park.
[Byung Ho and Jae Suk making
their way back.]
- You guys did good, did good...
- This hotcake is so good!
- Why didn't you eat it?
- We did. We had one.
We're going to finish what we
brought back.
[Byung Ho and Jae Suk bringing back
something for the Chairman too.]
Don't look at each other's.
One, two, three!
[No match.]
It was the middle one.
The middle one.
It's the shape of a star...
[Feeling happy just from seeing
the picture of a star.]
- I wasn't going to take it, but it's so good!
- This is really good.
Wow... can't we just go there
just once more?
- We should pick Ddukpokki...
- Just one more round...
- That is just too good.
- Mission or not, we're just going to eat.
That is seriously way too good!
[The Green Team heads off
for the amusement park!]
Let's give ourselves a round of applause.
- How is it we got it in one shot?
- No kidding!
- Winning really feels good.
- Jong Won...
You were really getting excited
back there.
[Unlike the advice given by his daughter,
Jong Won engaging in all aspects of mission.]
I kept thinking about the past with
our name being 'The Last Game'...
The other team just can't follow
us when it comes to our team spirit.
I wonder what the team that went
to the amusement park did?
I bet it has something to do
with riding the rides.
[Bingo]
[The Red Team making their
fourth attempt.]
[About to start crying.]
[The people not on the rides
seem happy.]
[Rollercoaster of terrors.]
[Can't do anything else other
than laugh...]
[The Red Team returning
from their fourth attempt.]
I have never seen such
passionate singing like that.
Great job... you did a great job.
Look at the thing exploding.
Confetti exploding.
[69 points.]
- You should've sang a little harder...
- You should've done better...
Just stop it already.
[Mental departure.]
Let's get off for now,
and have them get in.
- Number one?
- Number one...
- Hello!
- Hello... hello.
- Here it is, here it is...
- Hello!
That looks delicious!
[Delicious looking sweet red bean porridge]
- You pick it.
- No matter what we pick...
[Eating is their higher priority
rather than the mission.]
That's good... that's really good.
- The blue flag... hello!
- Hello!
Iced coffee...
pick whichever one you'd like.
Okay.
Go ahead. You drink it first.
- This is it... this is it.
- Are you finished eating?
- Then you can go back.
- Can I take this to the Chairman?
[Wanting to take the red bean porridge
for the Chairman...]
- We can't take the bowl, right?
- You have to get permission.
- Can we take this to our Chairman?
- Yes, take it to him.
- Pour it all in there.
- It's because this is so good...
- I don't want to waste it.
- It's too good to throw out.
- Thank you so much. Hope you sell a lot.
- Good luck with selling!
One, two, one, two...
[Being careful not to spill any]
[Chairman and Secretary Ji
also arrive.]
We're here too.
Why don't you try this red bean porridge?
It's really good.
This is unbelievable.
We brought it back for
our Chairman and Secretary Ji.
This dduk is gooey like cheese.
- Here, try it.
- That's really good.
- What did you have?
- Iced coffee.
- Was it refreshing?
- It was good.
Shall we try it again then?
We can look at it, right?
[With the meal finished,
it's time to check the cards.]
One, two, three!
[Match]
[Purple Team passes the mission.]
[The result of throwing the die is...
Jump!]
- The sushi house. Let's go!
- Let's keep on eating!
- No way... we're headed there right now.
- No... we can't!
- Diving coaster?
- I'm getting a bad feeling about this.
[The Red Team on their
seventh attempt.]
[They seem to be riding pretty well now?]
[Rollercoaster plunging into a nose-dive
while they sing at the top of their lungs.]
[But still holding on tightly to their mikes.]
[The final curve.]
[Arrival...]
[Singing right up to the moment
they have to get off.]
[Screaming right up to the end.]
Please! Let it be this time!
[Above 90 points.
Just what will their score be this time?]
You got above 90 points.
[Red Team succeeds with 95 points!]
[Fierce hugging similar to an athlete
who's won a gold medal.]
- 95 points! 95 points!
- We did it!
Look at Go Chang Suk's face...
he's about to collapse.
This is...
- Let's try for the sushi house.
- Yeah, let's do that.
- Yeah, let's go to the sushi house.
- be cautious how you throw it.
If you can, try to get 'Go'.
- One, two, three!
- Sushi! Sushi!
- Go! Go!
- Jump! Jump!
It's the baseball field.
How long are they going to go
without feeding us any food?
[Crap...]
If you're hungry,
you can get something to eat on the way.
It doesn't matter.
But it'll delay you.
- Let's just go to the baseball field.
- Let's just go then.
Why do I have to get insulted for
getting the 'Jump'?
- No, you did good.
- Let's go to the baseball field!
- Baseball field!
- They sell chicken and beer at the field.
Chicken and beer...
I'd really like to eat something.
Let's get a hot dog... a hot dog.
If we get a hot dog, the team that's
at the sushi place will soon follow...
I didn't say we should stop for ramen,
I'm saying let's get a hot dog for the road.
Right? We can eat on the way?
- What is this?
- Is this all they have?
- Sausage...
- One sausage? Okay.
I want a hot dog and... an ice cream.
Dipping dots ice cream?
- You like Dipping Dots ice cream?
- Yeah.
- Those are usually what kids...
- You like what little kid's like?
- Your taste buds must be like a little kid...
- No... adults like these too, right?
- This is ice cream?
- Yeah.
A drink for everyone...
Grab a drink for each of us.
- Is it good?
- Yes, it's good.
Ah... I feel like I can finally live now.
I'll open it for you.
[Double-fisting with food]
- You've got both hands full with food...
- This is so refreshing.
You're dripping it all over your hand.
You really are like a little kid.
Who knew you'd be so high maintenance?
[Green Team attempting
the amusement park challenge.]
[Nose-dive]
[Even dancing?]
[Jong Won working hard at everything.]
[Compared to the Red Team,
they're riding the coaster like pros.]
[Approaching the terrifying curve.]
[Nose-dive!]
Mommy!
[Arriving at the finish line.]
Keep going! Keep going!
[Snail and Jong Won riding the
roller coaster like couple of pros.]
- Good job... you did good.
- How many points did we get?
94 points!
[Passes with 94 points!]
No way!
[Green Team succeeding in
just one try again!]
[Sweeping the missions.]
[Jong Won throwing the die
this round too.]
[Jump]
Jump!
[To the baseball field!]
You really eat well, don't you?
[Chang Suk finding peace in food...]
There are napkins up front.
Your hand is covered in mustard.
[Taking a nap?]
Are you sleeping right now, Jung Geun?
- What are you doing right now?
- My eyes were just stinging a bit.
- We just finished our first mission...
- You can't sleep during our mission!
- You seemed out of it just now.
- No, I'm not sleeping!
- But you looked like you were.
- My eyes were just hurting.
- Why would your eyes hurt?
- Why are your eyes hurting suddenly?
So this is how you treat people?
I'm sorry.
My daughter told me to kill you first.
- Kill him...
- She said rip your name off first.
The name tag, Jung Geun.
[After the gorging, his digestion...]
I really think
I'm going to go crazy right now.
Did you try the chive pancake?
Isn't it good?
Pork soup and rice used to be
famous in the Oceanside towns.
- Pork soup rice is pretty famous.
- That stuff is delicious.
I don't think you've once thought about
or worried about our mission.
Well, since he's the Chairman...
- I've been part of an auction recently.
- Auction?
There was a nice house up for auction,
but I couldn't get it.
[A wide generation gap in the speech
between the older brothers.]
- Well, since it's the truth...
- Why don't we talk about the next mission?
Instead of an auction,
it'll be inherited now...
[Carrying on with the conversation without
a hitch no matter what the topic is.]
What was our battle cry again?
- Live thin and long.
- Live thin and long!
We don't need a battle cry.
When you get older, shouting out
a battle cry doesn't give you strength.
Rest is what gives you strength.
When it comes to chatting,
we can't seem to beat you...
With these two legendary chatterers...
Those words that are
rarely heard or used in recent times...
Assets, Inheritance, Lien, Auction...
- Wow... seriously...
- Well, the ingredients...
That conversation is still going?
That talk still wasn't over?
In midst of all that talking,
we're here already.
Shall we go on ahead with the
mission then?
- Now that we're here...
- You saw, right? Our older brothers...
They don't ask things like,
'What's our next mission' or things like that.
They haven't asked anything
about our mission today.
[The older brothers going on
as if they're out for a light walk.]
- Here's to our Driver Yoo.
- Thin and long!
[Even the water tastes good.]
- What is this?
[This is the baseball field!]
[Surprised upon seeing
the large crowd of students.]
Lee Kwang Soo! Lee Kwang Soo!
[The Giraffe's ever growing popularity
with the growth of his betrayal.]
[Answering them with a dance.]
[Star of their adoration!]
What is this?
Are we playing baseball or something?
This mission...
is called the terrifying alien
baseball team.
It's a baseball related mission in a city
where baseball is much loved.
A person of your choosing will hit
the ball and shout out 'Homerun.'
And the remaining three needs to run
with one straddled in their arms between them
while the hitter is
still shouting out Homerun.
So you have to shout it out
loud and long.
- This isn't going to work.
- Homerun...
We have to complete it before
he's done shouting it out.
- How can we do it before he's done shouting?
- It has to be someone who has good stamina.
- Have you done a simulation of it?
- Of course.
Is this Running Man or
Mission Impossible?
- One, two, three.
- I'm telling you, I'm light.
[Chang Suk to shout it out,
and the rest to round the bases.]
- Let's go.
- Fighting!
Fighting!
Here we go!
[Oh my...]
- That was a strike.
- Come on now.
Go Chang Suk... Go Chang Suk...
That's much more burdensome.
Here I go again.
[Successful in hitting the ball.]
[And...]
Homerun...
[Quickly getting on the way right away.]
- We got the wrong mission.
- This is no joke.
You really think that this is feasible?
You have to keep going!
[This is not Pavarotti.]
- A little bit longer!
- Wow, Chang Suk can really hold it out.
[Fail]
No way...
- This is...
- It's not like he's Pavarotti.
Wow...
how are we going to do this?
I'll give it a try.
[Giraffe taking the challenge.]
Fighting!
Lee Kwang Soo, fighting!
[He's got momentum here.]
Here I go!
[Oops!]
Homerun...
[Pretty fast speed!]
[Fails after rounding the second base.]
[Thunderous chanting.]
Song Ji Hyo! Song Ji Hyo!
[A place filled with male students.]
[Blank Ji's absolute popularity.]
Ha Ha... Ha Ha... Ha Ha!
Byul! Byul! Byul!
[Not forgetting to cheer on
their new sister-in-law as well.]
[Their sensibility is alive and kicking.]
[Battery being discharged in a flash.]
Chang Suk, get up.
Why do you keep laying down?
Chang Suk... we've only done it twice now.
[Green Team taking the challenge.]
Here I go!
Let's go.
Homerun...
They're going to be finished by the time
they hit second base.
[Until this point, The Last Game Team
has been sweeping all their missions.]
Hurry! Go quicker!
[Fail]
[Rapid down. Small lung capacity.]
[A mouth-watering feast.]
[A feast of fresh ocean's creatures.]
- Please have a seat.
- Have a seat, have a seat.
[Ultimately, eating again.]
Your face has to show.
These guys don't care about
stuff like that.
I'm telling you,
they're just here to sightsee today.
[Big brothers' world of
leisure and relaxation.]
If we get Jump, it's 40 steps.
Jump.
[The next location is 40 steps.]
- We need to get it over with now.
- Let's get going.
- Should we all say our battle cry?
- Let's say our battle cry.
- How about we just get going quickly?
- We should say it first real quick.
- One, two, three!
- Thin...
- You guys are...
- It's taking longer because of you. Hurry up.
- Let's just say it.
- One, two, three! Live long and thin!
After saying 'Live long and thin',
they're all moving in a very slow pace.
Take your time. We need to learn
this level of ease from you guys.
Thank you.
Say 'home' and 'run' separately.
Really?
- Home...
- And then say run...
Okay, let's give it a try.
- I think that may work.
- I think that's going to work.
[Chang Suk looking confident.]
Since he made it halfway with his one breath,
we can come the other half with his next.
- I think it's going to work...
- What?
- Okay, okay, okay...
- Fighting!
- Let's do this. Fighting!
[Will the Red Team succeed this time?]
We need to get a tighter grip this time.
Have a seat.
Home...
[Quickly rounding the first base.]
He's not finished with home yet...
he's not finished saying home.
[Pavarotti's unending 'home'.]
Run...
[The three men in a more urgent rush.]
A little bit more!
We're almost done!
[Just need to get to the home plate!]
Just a little bit longer!
[A success?]
[Success!]
[The moment they're given the chance to
say it in two syllables, they succeed!]
Thank you!
Go... Go one spot.
But if we get 'Go 2',
we have to go that way.
But I'm getting really nervous about
that 40 steps over this way.
That's good!
Go 2.
Why do we keep going to
all the difficult spots?
[The Red Team headed to the 40 steps.]
Seriously...
Go Chang Suk and Shin Jung Geun aren't
doing a hidden camera by any chance, right?
We're not at that level...
- With all the big brothers here.
- I'm getting suspicious of everything.
- We're here.
- Okay... thanks for your hard work.
Everyone clap first.
- So funny.
- This is nice.
There's quite an atmosphere about
this place.
[40 steps - Busan Jung-gu]
[40 steps featured in the film,
'No need for Mercy'.]
[Busan's tourist attraction with lingering
scents of Korean War refugees.]
- Isn't that amazing?
- The 40 steps are very cool.
- What is that?
- There's a certain ambiance to it.
There's an atmosphere around here.
The corridor and the store up here
have a certain atmosphere to them.
That statue is so pretty.
Don't you think it kind of looks like me?
[Feels as though Ha Ryong is
sitting up there.]
More than the mission,
we're talking about the ambiance of the place.
- The atmosphere...
- You're not here to sightsee.
- We should take a picture over there.
- Yeah, let's take one.
[Taking a commemorative photo.]
Live thin and long!
- Okay, okay... did it turn out well?
- Let's see.
- That came out well.
- It did come out well.
Another round of applause.
[Applauding whenever there's a chance.]
- Whenever there's a chance...
- What's our mission?
[Finally asking about the mission.]
[40 steps - Shoe throwing]
[If you can kick off your shoe and have it
land on the step chosen, you succeed.]
- You're going all the way up there?
- That's way too far!
- How can we kick it up that far?
- We can't get it up there.
It's very easy.
People in this neighborhood enjoy it...
Ugh... seriously...
- Oh! Here it is.
- Where? There it is.
- Who is it?
- The Purple Team is here.
- There's the Red Team!
- There they come.
You guys are here?
- Where have you been?
- Where have you guys been?
Why do the two of you look
so exhausted?
When we bought Chang Suk dipping dots
ice cream earlier, he quieted down.
[If you want to calm him down,
dipping dots ice cream...]
[Flaunting his Homerun...
shouting abilities.]
I think there's a side effect of that.
- Has anyone succeeded yet?
- No, we haven't yet.
-Let's do it quickly.
- If two people succeed, you pass.
[Red Team taking the challenge
first with Jong Kook.]
[The citizens' enthusiastic cheer.]
- Do a good job.
- Okay!
I'll do a good job, Mother.
Fighting!
[Too bad... it goes over by two steps.]
- Wow... what a loss.
- He's good.
You're good.
Can you hold onto my hand?
- You can't hold on too tight.
- Fighting!
Shin Jung Geun!
[The shoe flying off at lightning speed.]
[Oh no... a mere one step difference.]
- Wow... just a one-step difference.
- That is really too bad.
- It's just one step.
- So this is how it's going to keep going.
[Purple Team taking the challenge.]
[The goal being lowered two steps.]
- Challenge!
- Ha Ryong, fighting!
Ha Ryong, fighting!
[Oh! Right in the vicinity!]
[Did he just succeed?]
[Success!]
[People of the upper steps cheering him on!]
[The big brother does it!]
[If just one more person from the Purple
Team succeeds, then they pass]
You have to aim a little higher
then you're thinking.
You look like you can pull it off.
- One...
- Fighting!
[Fail...]
That was a fail.
Applaud!
Ji Suk Jin! Ji Suk Jin!
[A female student with a loud voice.]
- Ji  Suk Jin!
- Ji Suk Jin!
You have a nice tone.
- Fighting. You can do it, you can do it!
- I think I can do it.
[Will it?]
[Shoe falling towards the goal line.]
[Success]
[Purple Team succeeds!]
[The leisurely Purple Team
rapidly completes their mission.]
I can't believe we got it done like that.
Young lady, thanks!
[All due to the fervent cheering
from the young student?]
- Fighting!
[The Big-nosed brother
ultimately getting shunned.]
[Grateful to all the citizens
that cheered them on.]
Thank you!
One... two!
- We got a 'Go'.
- Go.
- Things are going really well.
- We're no joke right now.
At this rate, we can win right now!
- How can this be?
- We're in first place right now.
The young lady that cheered us on earlier...
her energy...
[Could it be all thanks to the
energetic cheering of the young lady?]
That girls energy really was...
Okay, I'm going to go for it.
[Practicing?]
[Taking the time out for tricks
and stunts.]
[Seriously high maintenance...]
There's Kwang Soo to help you out...
Just sit still, Chang Suk.
He can reach it.
[Giraffe's very handy long arms.]
- His arms are so long.
- Whenever I kick, it just goes up.
You want to give it a try?
[Drafting the young lady from earlier.]
- Since she has slippers on...
- Slippers would be good for this.
What's your name?
Go Tae Hyun, fighting!
I think it'll be okay for you to
do it hard.
- Do I just need to kick?
- Just kick and throw it.
[Huh?]
[Hitting the fourth floor.]
[Amazing.
Definitely overflowing with energy.]
You did good. You're very strong.
This isn't easy.
[Fails by three steps.]
[Jung Geun making another attempt.]
Jung Geun, fighting!
Fighting!
- Fighting!
- He got it.
[Kicking the shoe this time
without so much force behind it.]
[Wow! A success!]
You still got it!
- How...
- He still has it!
[One of the two remaining has to succeed
in order for them to pass.]
Chang Suk... kick it, kick it.
It's almost there, he almost got it.
[Kwang Soo has to make sure to
succeed in this situation.]
Lee Kwang Soo! Lee Kwang Soo!
[Cheering himself on]
[Huh?]
Traitor, traitor, traitor...
[The Traitor Song is being sung loud
and clear at the top of the steps.]
Lee Kwang Soo, fighting!
Will this scene be on TV?
[Are you watching?]
- Thank you!
- Fighting!
[Taking the energy from the citizens.]
[Success!]
[The Red Team succeeds!]
It's because of me!
- Lee Kwang Soo, fighting!
- I'll work harder to betray more from now on!
[The young lady with overflowing bundle
of energy throwing the die for them.]
Jump!
[Definitely a girl who brings luck?]
Thank you.
- Thank you!
What is Jae Suk and his team doing
right now?
- Beach?
- They're at the beach.
But I think those guys are
really lucky right now.
All they've done is throw a shoe
after having gotten to eat twice.
And now, they're at the beach.
I guess they've been really lucky.
And I can't stand it when the PD smiles.
[Hates to see the writer smiling.]
He just keeps smiling.
You're right.
There's no need for a person
to be so overly bright.
- Don't you think so?
- You're right... you're so right.
I'm not going to be so bright whenever
someone else is having a hard time from now on.
[Jung Geun taking life lessons
from the missions.]
[The Last Chance Team
focused on their mission.]
We're the only team
heading toward the village.
If we succeed at the village here...
we can go straight to home base.
We were lucky throwing the die.
[Green Team taking
the shortcut to the village.]
[What mission awaits them here?]
[Village - Mission impossible]
[Find the hidden Running Man mission container
in the village and come to the finish location.]
If you find that hidden container,
you'll find the finish location written on it.
[Head to the finish line after finding the
mission container hidden within the village.]
Be careful on your way...
[Huh? Be cautious on our way?]
There must be something along the way.
We have to be careful of our name tags...
first and foremost, be cautious of that.
Let's go.
Should we cover our own name tags
with our hands?
We have to constantly watch our backs.
Jong Won, be careful.
Be careful and watch your back.
[Getting the feeling that someone is
keeping their eyes on our backs...]
We have to find that container.
Hello.
Have you seen someone carrying around a
thing that looks like a thermos around here?
You don't think there's a spy
amongst us, do you?
No way.
[It's a water gun!]
It's Running Man!
[The lady scurrying out carrying
a water gun.]
[Over there too!]
Run! Run for it!
What do we do? What do we do?
[That's right. In this village...]
[Everyone in this village are
water gun snipers.]
[If your name tag is hit by the water gun,
then you're ousted!]
[Will they be able to safely escape
this terrifying village?]
People that cheer us on here
are actually more of a danger.
[All the students and ladies
that cheer them on are all dangerous.]
You don't have a water gun,
do you, Mother?
- You don't have a water gun?
- I don't have one.
I don't have it, I don't have it.
[Discovers a sniper Mother!]
- Ha Ha! Be careful!
- Why? What is it?
- Escape!
- Be careful!
[The ladies' well hidden and
well attacking water gun units.]
- Mother...
- Gary!
[Since I'm already discovered,
attacking straight ahead.]
[Scary ladies who ambushes,
attacks and raids.]
All these ladies are just
waiting to attack.
Wow... they're all waiting in ambush.
They're all lying in ambush,
and they're scary.
- Mother, have you seen a thermos like thing?
- Wow... you're so pretty!
- Let's go up there.
- It's Gary!
Look at this guy, this guy!
- Be careful...
- Mother, we have to go back to recording.
Even though we know how you
feel right now...
[For the time being this place has turned
into Lee Jong Won's fan meeting site.]
[Green Team catching a brief spite
thanks to Jong Won's fans.]
Can I have a glass of water, please?
It's all over.
It's over.
- It's over?
- Yes.
[Deceiving them into thinking that
the mission is already over.]
- Water?
- Thanks for you hard work, Mother.
[Lady fans believing
whatever Jong Won tells them.]
We've been waiting all day
for you guys.
Oh my... I'm so sorry.
We should've came sooner,
but we just got done.
But it's all over.
- I don't think so...
- It's over.
- See? You can ask him too.
- Is it true?
- I don't think so...
- He can't talk during the show.
- Really?
- Yes.
I'm going to get going, Mother.
Thank you for the water.
If other weird people show up later,
just shoot them without mercy.
- No! It's you, right?
- No, thanks for the water!
[Operation deception a success!]
Mother, have you seen
a thermos looking like thing?
- You don't have a bottle?
- We don't know...
- Huh?
- I don't know.
Elder, have you by any chance
seen a thermos?
- I haven't seen a thermos.
- Ah, yes.
[If a person opens up their home,
it is possible to search through them.]
[Pretty sure it's hidden
in one of these homes.]
Hello, Grandmother.
By any chance, have you seen
a thermos looking thing?
I haven't seen any.
You haven't seen one? Can I check real quick?
[A suspicious giggle?]
Mother, your expression
is a little suspicious.
Seeing how nice and tidy your
house is too...
I have a weird feeling about this
right now.
- Mother...
- Let me shake your hand once.
- Mother... you have it, right?
- I have it.
- Where is it?
- She says she has it!
She says she has it!
- Where is it, Mother?
- I found the bottle!
- This is the thermos!
- No, it's not!
It's not this?
[It's an ingredient.]
- Should I look for it?
- Sure, look for it.
- Where could it be...
- Mother...
[Fount it!
Running Man mission container!]
[Once they open that,
they can find out the finish location!]
Mother... you should've told us sooner.
- Mother, thank you...
- Mother, thank you!
Always be healthy, Mother.
We found it.
[Thanking Mother for hiding it in her home.]
[Good job finding it.]
Since you were able to complete the mission,
you are going to be given this.
- What is it?
- Please take it.
Is it something that'll help us?
What is this? It's a key?
There's a key in there?
- It's a key.
- It's a key, right?
[A mysterious key inside the envelope.]
You are going to definitely need that key
when you get back to your home base.
[A key that'll be needed back at
home base.]
[Just what is the identity of this key?]
[Three keys hidden amongst
three different mission locations.]
[Just what will happen when they
arrive at the home base in a little bit?]
[This is the clean
and beautiful Song-do beach!]
Wow... it's so picturesque!
Look at the mountain in the clouds.
I think we can even go swimming.
[But... what is this?]
Please read it out loud, Ha Ryong.
[Song-do Beach -
Eat dried persimmons together.]
[If you eat the hanging dried
persimmon, you pass.]
[The person who can't finish eating in
the allotted time is ousted.]
Eat dried persimmons together?
The important thing about this mission is
the person who doesn't finish eating
within allotted time is ousted right away.
Then they can't go on to the next mission?
[Not able to participate in the
next mission.]
But it's okay if we write our own name
with a pen and still play, right?
Write out our own name tag...
- We just need to find a way.
- Ha Ryong has many different methods.
You have no idea all the experiences
that he has.
He doesn't care about stuff like that.
- What do we do with the hats?
- We have to wear them.
- I'm getting scared now.
- I'm starting to feel afraid.
- I'm nervous!
- I'm getting nervous!
This is really making me nervous!
- The allotted time is one minute.
- I don't think... one minute?
- One minute? Eat it all in one minute?
- Yes. Ready... set... go!
[Start]
Wait...
Is this even feasible?
I feel like this is going to fall off!
[Maybe, maybe not...
maybe, maybe not...]
[Wake me up if they succeed...]
[At this rate,
will all four of them be ousted?]
[Wait! Ha Ryong!]
[Calmly...]
[Ha Ryong succeeds in
eating the dried persimmon!]
Who succeeded?
I'm the only one that succeeded.
[There really isn't much time left!]
[Jae Suk succeeds!
And then Suk Jin too!]
[Byung Ho's the only person left!]
[Not even ten seconds left on the clock!]
Byung Ho, please!
[Come on... please!]
[Time over.]
[Son Byung Ho - Out!]
[Purple Team's unable to
participate in further missions.]
Byung Ho's daughter begged him
not to get ousted early...
[Even though his daughter
desperately begged him not to...]
Ji Oh... the thing is...
sooner or later, they'll all be ousted.
Who are you talking to?
Your daughter?
Don't worry.
There's still tomorrow.
In war,
victory always goes back and forth.
That's what life is about, understand?
You're putting your life on the line
just to eat some dried persimmon?
[Cool dad, Son Byung Ho...
putting his life on the line for everything.]
This bus terminal mission is
to defend the name tag.
Huh? defend?
[For three minutes, defend your name tag by
escaping blind-folded Dong Wan in the bus.]
Inside the bus?
If your name tag gets ripped off
by lady PD Dong Wan...
then you'll be ousted immediately.
You can't participate in the mission further.
- Out for good?
- Out for good.
Totally done for the day?
- You can't attack.
- But we can defend, right?
You have to keep avoiding him.
When the three minutes pass,
a bell will sound
and you can escape through the
backdoor which we will then open.
Then we can just go in our t-shirts?
I feel like I'm getting drunker with
each explanation I hear.
Just go in your t-shirt instead.
The reason being is that he can
grab onto your long sleeve.
- Just like this?
- Yes, that's better.
[Re-attaching the name tag
so it's easy to tear off.]
- We have to be careful.
- That's too easy to rip off.
[Red Team getting on the bus.]
[Will they be able to last the three
minutes inside this tight bus?]
Someone can go in here...
I'm going to lie down here.
- In case he comes over here...
- Oh, that's a good spot. That's good.
- That's good!
- You look rather adorable in there!
But you won't be able to move once
you get in there.
I'm going to get started!
[Red Team rushing to find their spots.]
[Start!]
[Defend your name tag from lady
PD Dong Wan with his eyes blind-folded!]
[Oh no! Heading towards Chang Suk!]
[Discovers Chang Suk!]
I can't reach his back!
[Ultimately giving up on Chang Suk
who's sticking like a rock.]
[Causing disturbance by singing.]
[Mr. Capable safely escaping
behind him.]
[Lady PD Dong Wan catches
Shin Jung Geun!]
[Oh no! It's trouble!]
[Shin Jung Geun - Out!]
[Unable to participate in the next mission.]
[Oh no...]
[Approaching in
Jong Kook's direction this time.]
[The man actively defending himself.]
Stop touching me.
[There's not much time left...]
[Still in the same place and position...]
[Giraffe using a good plan.]
There's no one here...
[Ten seconds left!]
[The bell will sound soon,
and they just have to escape!]
The three minutes are up!
You have to ring the bell now!
[Now they can escape!]
[The bus door opens.]
[Go Chang Suk,
the first to succeed in escaping!]
[Hurry up and get out!]
[Kwang Soo and Jong Kook all succeed
in escaping the bus safely!]
Wow... that was hard.
[One unfortunate person...]
Why were you going around singing?
Did you guys get a jump?
When did you get here?
- We got a jump.
- Ah... you guys jumped.
- Where is Jung Geun going?
- I'm eliminated.
[Shin Jung Geun - Out!]
There's something you didn't receive when
you succeeded in your mission at the beach.
What is this?
- Can we look at it?
- No, don't look at it now.
You guys were the first to pass this mission.
Therefore, I have something for your team too.
[Handing over a key to the Red Team.]
- We can't look at it now?
- No, don't look at it now.
The way I see it,
two people will be eliminated here.
[Predicting two members of the
Purple Team to be eliminated.]
- I can vouch Suk Jin getting eliminated.
- Is it hard?
Suk Jin... it's not easy.
It really isn't easy.
[Red Team to toss the die.]
['Go' would mean moving forward to home,
'Back' would mean going to the beach.]
Back, back, back...
Go!
[Lands on Go!]
- They should've gotten 'Back'...
- You didn't get the right face on the die!
[The divine touch of Shin Jung Geun.]
[On the other hand, Green Team,
who were the first to arrive at home base.]
[What's the mission that awaits them
at the Maritime Museum?]
[Find and open the hidden
treasure chest.]
[Hidden somewhere in here is a treasure
chest filled with a gift for the winning team.]
The final victor is the team that finds
that chest first and opens it.
- You were given a key earlier...
- Yes, we have it.
You have to attach that key under one
of your team member's name tag.
You can use the key to
open the treasure chest when you find it.
[Green Team putting their key under
Jong Won's name tag...]
Could it be?
[Some ease when it comes to finding the
treasure chest since they're first to arrive.]
[Large conference room.]
[There's something in there!]
[The treasure chest!]
[There are two padlocks on it?]
[Two keys are needed!]
[Have to steal the key one
of the other team possesses!]
[All the other teams are meeting up
at the home base!]
Is this game even going to work?
We're at a disadvantage here.
It's more than just being at a disadvantage.
If our name tag gets torn off,
our key then goes to that other team.
- So what we should think is...
- We should just accept being eliminated.
Put in on my back
and I'll try to talk to them.
I'll try to talk to them...
- But this is...
- We were told to put it under, right?
I put in under your name tag
in the middle.
- Who are you calling?
- I wanted to see my granddaughter.
[Grandfather wanting to brag about
his granddaughter no matter where he is.]
Is she tap dancing right now?
Can't all the kids do this level
of tap dancing though?
- No, they can't...
- Really? Is it different?
Look at this.
Her steps are... they're advanced.
- This is...
- You have to protect the key.
[The two teams facing each other as soon
as the Purple Team arrives at the museum.]
- Why isn't anyone else here?
- Why don't you give them a hug?
- In the spirit of them being your Juniors...
- With trust in one another...
This is... this is nice.
[Jae Suk eliminates Green Team
Ha Ha's name tag!]
[Ha Ha, out. Ha Ha, out]
[Yoo-ruce Willis' surprise attack!]
- Jae Suk, that was too much.
- Get him, get him!
It's total chaos down there!
Chang Suk, it's total chaos.
It's chaos... it's chaos.
Don't do it! Don't do it.
Let's just forget about Ha Ha.
[A guerrilla attack.
Escaping after ousting Ha Ha.]
Wow... Jae Suk, you...
- I told you earlier...
- I was totally shocked.
There are no eternal enemies,
or eternal allies either.
If we had left Ha Ha,
he definitely would've...
And we're too outnumbered too.
Jong Won... why don't we go to the area
where the treasure chest is for now?
We can't let it be found since it's
a secret that only we know about.
Should we guess who has the key?
- You guys definitely have a key.
- Chang Suk has the key.
Chang Suk has it, 100% guaranteed.
The reason being...
The word key is written on his face.
- See? No one's denying...
- I told you that it would be too obvious.
I told you that I'm too obvious.
[Bingo.
Stabbing himself in his own foot.]
What are you doing right now?
[Gullible Chang Suk...]
We were right?
- Chang Suk... what are you doing?
- It's true.
[Chang Suk has the key?]
[Can we switch out a player?
Switch me out...]
Kwang Soo, let's talk.
[Ace Ji Hyo with her eyes on
Chang Suk.]
[Kwang Soo initiates an attack on Ji Hyo!]
[Green Team vs. Red Team face-off!]
[An unavoidable face-off.]
[Gary attacking Chang Suk,
who has the key!]
[It's been ripped!]
[Gary gains Chang Suk's key!]
[Go Chang Suk, out!]
[A battle between the two teams!]
[Yoo-ruce Willis seeing his opportunity!]
[Gary eliminates Kwang Soo's name tag!]
[And just then!]
[Jong kook eliminates Jong Won's name
tag and gains Green Team's key!]
[Purple Team's goal is Gary,
who has Chang Suk's key!]
Jae Suk!
You can't rip mine off... Jae Suk!
Ha Ryong!
What are you doing to me?
Don't tear my name tag off!
[Jae Suk succeeds in eliminating Gary!]
- Aren't you going to get Jong Kook?
- No... Gary, are you okay?
[Most chaotic battle in Running Man history!]
- Lee Kwang Soo, come this way.
- You're not eliminated?
My name hasn't been ripped off?
[Ace is Ace...]
Ji Hyo really is something else...
You weren't eliminated in this chaos?
I really thought that I was eliminated.
Lee Kwang Soo, Lee Jong Won,
and Gary... out.
[A pile of ousted players.]
Should we just go and see where it is?
- I don't want to.
- Why?
- I don't want to...
- Why? Why?
Why don't you want to?
[She knows something...]
- Why don't you want to?
- What?
- Why? I just don't want to!
- Tell me why you don't want to.
- Tell me why?
- I just don't want to!
It's weird that you don't want to.
Something isn't right here.
You can show me the chest,
couldn't you?
Jong Kook, I honestly don't know
where it is either.
I heard that it's around here,
but I don't know the exact location.
I'm being honest.
Before Gary could show me exactly where
it is, everyone got ousted.
You just know that it's around here?
- I just heard it's around here.
- What's your plan?
[Key-less Ji Hyo's plan?]
Do you have any hope or not?
I always have hope when I'm on
Running Man.
Do you think there's any hope
for you or not?
To be honest,
even though I want to work with you
without a doubt, you'll eliminate me
if push comes to shove.
[Bingo!]
So... are you saying that
you're going to eliminate me now?
I think it would break my heart
to have you do that to me.
I think it's right that I get you
when I have the chance right now.
What kind of a windfall is this?
Jong Kook is saying
that he'll eliminate Ji Hyo.
Why are you seriously being like this?
You think you can beat the two of them?
Yeah, I know I can.
[What an absurd thing to even ask...]
[Mr. Capable planning on eliminating Ji Hyo,
then taking down the Purple Team!]
Don't bite me! Ji Hyo...
[Purple Team now knows what to do...]
Ji Hyo, Ji Hyo...
[First saving Ji Hyo from danger!]
We're the ones that saved you...
we saved you.
Kim Jong Kook, you...
- Ji Hyo... want to end it?
- What's your plan for the day?
I'm going to eliminate Kim Jong Kook
and die myself!
[Explosive statement]
Ji Hyo... I won't make this long.
You're trying to strong arm me
like a man?
Would you have eliminated me if you
had to or not?
I would've eliminated you,
of course, I would've!
Why would I not have?
Yeah, that's a given.
- Anyone in that situation would do that.
- Why are you agreeing?
[Jong Kook standing ground on his own.]
[Yoo-ruce Willis avoiding with agility.]
You don't think I know your attack style
after doing this with you for two years?
[Learning Mr. Capable's attack style
after two years together.]
[We can see Mr. Capable's
attack style now!]
Even though you've always gotten me
before, it won't be like that anymore.
- What if Ji Hyo comes for us?
- What?
- What if Ji Hyo...
- Ji Hyo wouldn't do that.
Ji Hyo is extremely angry
at Jong Kook right now.
I don't know,
a woman's heart is so fickle.
You have no idea when and how
it'll change.
What is this?
Are you going for him?
[Fickle Ace!]
[Ever-unpredictable woman's heart!]
See? I knew it...
You definitely...
you definitely know show business.
[Now it really is an unpredictable battle!]
Press down on him using your strength!
[Ji Hyo takes this opportunity
to attack!]
Don't do that...
Ji Hyo, you shouldn't do that!
[In the midst of rough battle of the men,
protecting a woman is...]
[Song Ji Hyo, out!]
Ha Ryong! Ha Ryong!
[The remaining three men's final battle!]
[Purple Team's last chance at victory!]
Ha Ryong, we have to eliminate him here!
This is our only chance!
Ha Ryong!
[Docile...]
How did this happen?
Ha Ryong...
I told you, that you could get hurt.
This good-for-nothing cheater...
You, go away!
[Jae Suk, out!]
- What's going on out there?
- It looks like fun out there.
- It sounds like they're having fun.
- Why don't we just start laughing too?
You're a fool!
- Jae Suk... it's Jae Suk.
- Jae Suk's ousted too.
Who eliminated you?
- Kim Jong Kook!
- I'm glad!
[A very full jail cell.]
Ha Ryong should have ripped off Jong Kook
when we had the chance...
- So you didn't get to do it...
- Kim Jong Kook just isn't normal.
Chang Suk must not have any strength.
He's only smiling with his expression.
- Chang Suk... can I use casual speech?
- Yes, of course.
Yes, please use casual speech with me.
The way I see it,
Suk Jin won't be able to do that.
He'll feel uncomfortable.
He's younger than you.
I wonder what makes him uncomfortable?
Coming... someone's coming.
[Ha Ryong and Jong Kook coming
after completing the final battle?]
[Huh? How did the battle end?]
You won, didn't you?
You lost, didn't you?
- Did you win?
- Jong Kook...
[Chairman's thirst for victory surfaced
as soon as he sees the treasure chest.]
[Chairman's hidden competitive streak!]
[Amazing defense mechanism!
Mr. Capable eliminates the Chairman first!]
- Should I show you the prize first?
- Yes.
A two night three day travel voucher
in Busan for a family of four.
Since Ha Ryong is such a respected
elder amongst us...
[Winner Jong Kook conceding his prize
to the Big Brother.]
[That's a man!]
Show us your diamond steps, Ha Ryong!
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Next week on Running Man]
[And the next day...
the descent of a fairy]
[Even the flower middle aged men's jaws
goes slack at the sight of Tae Yeon from SNSD.]
[And 'my daughter's watching!'
A battle between the fathers.]
[In this place, every
move you make is being watched.]
- This is a bloody battle.
- You have to eliminate him!
[Battle between the father's to
get their hands on the golden egg!]
[Father and the golden egg!]