-Because I love her.
-I love you.
-I like you.
-Have you been well?
What about you?
[Or will it be fake love?]
-Jae Suk.
-I'm about to go crazy.
Ji Min!  It's me!
[Find clues that'll
lead you to your true love]
[Lightning speed interference from
fake loves for the win]
[Finding true love-Start]
[A bright morning in Jeju Island]
[In front of the dormitory the next morning -
7 a.m.]
[Wow! Ji Min's the first one to wake up!]
Did you sleep well?
I can't believe that I have to do it again.
[Extreme fatigue
from the fight the day before]
[A mission table?]
Why isn't anyone else here?
It's making me nervous.
You're the first one here.
-Seriously?
-Yes.
You have a mission first thing this morning.
[Solution... And water guns?]
Please go ahead and read it.
[Curious]
[Find the unidentified person who has the
clues needed for your first mission]
[The person to get the solution on that
person's name tag first gets the clue!]
I have no idea what that means.
-Please select a solution first.
-Okay.
And after that, choose a water gun.
And once you put that solution into your
water gun, that becomes your color.
Is this really a water gun?
Is this how you work it?
[Ji Min cautiously choosing her weapon]
This one?
I'll take this one.
-Yes.
-And you can put this in there...
-Put it in now?
Put it in there now, and the allotted time
from that point is 10 minutes.
So the person who comes out here
later is more at a disadvantage.
-What are you talking about?
-You see them coming out now?
[Running Man members finally starting to
come out one by one]
-It'll be better for you to go quickly.
-Go where?
[First, let's run!]
[Without even knowing the purpose,
starting to sprint as soon as they're awake]
What the heck?
[Where do I go?]
[Everyone making a U-turn]
-10 minutes as soon as you pour that in.
-And I start to shoot whomever?
I have no idea what you're saying.
-There's someone hiding out there.
-Okay.
Ah... An unidentified person?
You have to shoot that person's name tag.
The person that shoots that person's
name tag first...
I think this is going to be too big.
I'm not going to take this one.
[Heading over to the mission table
after floundering]
-Did you sleep well?
-Ji Min...!
What's this?
Yes!  I got here first!
-Get in line... In the order you came.
-I was first.
[Concentration]
From the moment Han Ji Min gets started,
that's when the race starts.
-What?
-What?!
So the person who got here later is
at that much more of a disadvantage.
-Wait... Wait...
-Ji Min, shouldn't you at least say hi?
Did you sleep well, Gary?
You're concentrating way too hard here.
[Her evident competitiveness]
[Pledging to today's win again?]
Last time, Shin Se Kyung said
that she was like a wild cat...
I can now understand
how she must have felt then.
-You were a champ yesterday.
-Thank you.
-I don't think I worked hard enough...
-You're working extremely hard right now.
Who would ever think that you're not
working very hard right now?
Okay... With Han Ji Min getting started,
the race will now start.
[Morning water gun mission]
[Time allotted: 10 minutes]
Find the unidentified person.
The person to get the solution on that
person's name tag first gets the clue.
Choose a solution and a water gun quickly.
You have to pour the solution in quickly,
and get started.  The clock is ticking.
So it's water guns again?
Isn't that the gun Jae Suk really likes?
This is...!
[The water gun Jae Suk treasures...]
-How do I get this off?
-I should be the one to use that...
Why are you getting jealous over a water gun?
That's so childish...
One minute has already passed.
If the other person lasts another 9 minutes,
then that person is going to win.
-Really?
-Get going... Hurry up.
I need to choose one quickly.
[Ji Min testing out her water gun on the way]
Where do I find the person?
[There's a guest
in this wide open space somewhere?]
Do you know how far the parameters go?
It's this whole place, right?
[Searching for likely hiding places]
She said that she wasn't going to work hard...
We really don't have much time.
When it comes to water guns, I'm the one...
This one is leaking.
They're making us run as soon as we get up.
[Running Men that slept in
are also starting their search]
[Where is the guest in this big place that is
to be shot down first thing in the morning?]
I can't be seen... I can't be seen.
I don't think they'll see me here.
[A familiar back
hiding behind the big boulder]
[This is the guest...
That everyone's desperately searching for]
[Actress' best friend professionally
Kim Jae Dong]
[An hour earlier]
Hello.
-Welcome to Jeju Island.
-Yes, nice to meet you.
What... What is it that I'm to do?
Why am I here?
-You're here for a special mission.
-Yes.
Do you know what your mission is today?
Once the members get out here,
they have 10 minutes...
And you have to protect your name tag
from these members' water guns.
[Save the name tag from
Running Man members' water guns for 10 minutes]
You have to avoid them.
-I can't be shot?
-No, you can't be shot.
What is this?
This is a USB that contains a hint
that you'll need at the final mission.
If you protect your name tag from being
shot by water guns for 10 minutes...
-You can take that hint with you.
-Okay.
You're saying that I need to protect this?
[Just what is the important hint
contained in the USB?]
There's no place to hide around here.
Where can I hide in this wide open space?
You can see everything out here.
Do you have a shovel?
[Why?  Are you going to dig a bunker?]
Can anyone see me if I stay down here?
[We can see you very well]
[That's why after all the worrying,
decided to hide by the boulder...]
Isn't there a female guest on today?
Ah, Ji Min?
Ji Min's following me around even
outside of the studios...
Where do I find this person?
They don't know it's me, right?
If they knew,
they're going to try to shoot me in the face.
This gathering is full of people
who doesn't like my face.
Especially Jae Suk.
He really doesn't like my face.
He told me that I look like an intersection
that's missing its traffic light.
[God of water gun out searching for
'The intersection without traffic light']
I wonder if the person
is in these bushes somewhere?
Someone's  here!
Who's that in the orange?
[Gary is in the vicinity!]
This is making me nervous.
Oh my goodness!
[Ji Min walking around the ridge...]
[Discovers Jae Dong behind the boulder!]
There's someone there!
[It seems like everyone
is starting to take notice]
Ji Min, where are you going?
Wait a minute...
[Encircling the area]
[Still unaware?  Defenseless?]
What's going on?
[The first person to shoot
the name tag wins!]
[Just who will...?]
[Fighter Ji Min!]
Yes!  I found him!
[Defeated defenseless...]
[Victim of a shootout
without the ability to resist]
Hey...!
I'm hit, right?
You're totally hit!
[Soaked?]
Huh?  Why is Jae Dong here?!
[Stupid... Ousted in less than 3 minutes!]
What? It's already over?
Jae Dong...!
How can you get caught so quickly?!
-Is it over already?
-It's already over!
[Mission over with Ji Min's one shot]
[Speechless]
Ji Min...
You said you weren't going to work very hard.
She used to follow me around a lot too
when we used to MC together...
-You guys used to work together?
-Yes, yes...
-You used to work with Ji Min?
-Of course.
I kept following his lead
without even realizing it myself.
She used to hold my hand under the table.
No way!
-Tell me more stories like this.
-I'm serious!
There's no way...!
Someone kept throwing stones at my window
while I was sleeping.
It was me... That was me.
I'm saying that it was me.
It was Jong Kook...
Jong Kook told me last night that he wasn't
going to leave you and Kwang Soo alone.
I thought I was going to die
while trying to stop him.
[Don't you remember...
What happened yesterday?]
Hurry!  Hurry!
[Kwang Soo joining alliances with the white
team to betray his own teammate, Jong Kook]
[The Tiger's vengeance]
Anyways... I'll show you something today.
[We're dead...]
What happens now?
You have the hint.
-Yes, yes...
-Ah, Ji Min gets it first?
[Passing over the USB containing the hint
to the winner, Ji Min]
-It's a USB?!
-Seriously?
If you have this,
it'll help you at the final mission.
[USB to play a very important role
at the final mission!]
I feel like we're filming the drama, Ghost.
Just as Kim Jong Kook had wanted,
everyone's on their own all day today.
-What?!
-Individual?
Why do you want that, Jong Kook?
[Just what he wanted...]
Individually...
Move on to the location contained in that
envelope and complete the mission.
After hearing what the final mission is,
you can move on to that site.
And you can all meet up over there.
Han Ji Min can pick first.
-So we don't know where we'll be going...
-She likes me...
Why am I on this show with someone like him?
[Unsatisfied with the guest
she's on the show with?]
She said a person like him...
A person like him...!
Since I placed first, I'll take #1.
[Ji Min chooses #1]
I'm...going to pick lucky number 7.
[As each individual leaves,
they check their mission]
Number 6.
This one!
I'll see you later.
I'll take number 2.
[Just what is the mission that awaits them?]
[A mission hidden behind a veil-Start!]
Hello.
[Checking the mission]
[The beach?]
Please take me there.
Just where would I be going...?
Supermarket? Just any supermarket?
[Just go to any supermarket?]
Where do I find the stone statue?
[Jae Suk just got a stone statue...]
There's no address.
Field?!
This is it.  I'm to go to a field?
Equestrian center?
[To meet Giraffe's friend, the horse?]
A sea view deck...
Please take me to the bus terminal.
Mr. Driver... Please take me to the school.
Mr. Driver... Is there a ladies' diver house?
Please take me there quickly.
A ladies' diver house?
Is it a restaurant?
[Everyone making their move
to their own suspicious place...]
[I wonder what the mission is?]
I was like a wildcat yesterday too, wasn't I?
[No, you weren't.
You were just pretty eager...]
I can't really remember
what I was like at the end...
[Do you remember now?]
You were really bad!  A really bad man!
[You were just a bit too eager...]
[Wildcat embracing her wildness...]
[But anyways...
What's the hint contained in this USB?]
Ah... Seriously...
I can't believe I got caught like that.
[Jae Dong getting shot down
without even making his stand]
My mom said this after seeing it...
Hey... Why do you get killed off every time?
(Jae Don's mom's comment after
his last appearance on Running Man)
I'm sure she's going to say the same thing
after seeing this one too.
No matter what the mission is today...
Jong Kook isn't going to leave
Kwang Soo and Ha Ha alone....
[Kwang Soo and Ha Ha marked for death
by Mr. Capable Jong Kook?]
I'm going to work really hard today...
And put an end to this lonely fight.
[Enter one of the involved parties]
Kwang Soo?
Yes, Ha Ha.
You're the first...
-You're the second, right?
-I'm the second...!
[Confirming the Tiger's killing order]
Let's not go around together.
Even if we see each other,
let's not say anything.
Let's just...grit our teeth...
And even if we tear up...
Let's just ignore each other.
[And even if we tear up...
Let's just ignore each other...]
Ha Ha...
-I understand, Ha Ha.
-Kwang Soo, I love you!
-I love you, Ha Ha!
-I'll see you in jail, Kwang Soo.
I'll wait for you in jail.
[I'll wait for you in jail, Ha Ha...]
It's Jong Kook!
[A call from the Tiger!]
Hello, Sir!
Kwang Soo...
Yes, Jong Kook?
You know the mission we have to do
before the final mission?
Yes, Jong Kook.
Work hard at it.
I understand, Jong Kook. Thank you.
I'll do my absolute best!
Since anyways...
Only this mission is going to
get broadcast...
[Declaration of war
on hunting down the Giraffe]
Hope you understand.
In that case...
Before I go into the race,
I'll take a calming medication.
Yeah.  You should take some.
-Yes, Jong Kook.
-I'll see you later.
[I shouldn't have betrayed him...]
So this is the stone statue village?
[Jae Suk arrives at the stone statue]
What the heck?
[A table and flag...?]
-Yoo Jae Suk...
-This is...?
[Once you give out 30 signatures to
local residents, you succeed!]
[But excessive soliciting is prohibited]
[Passing out more than one
to the same person is prohibited]
How can I do a fan signing when
there's no one even around here?
It's only 8 o'clock in the morning right now.
Who would be out at this time...?
[Ji Min arrives at the beach]
Do you see the table over there?
Yes.
What is this?
[Fan signing event!]
[Kwang Soo arrives at the equestrian center]
[Fan signing event]
[Once you give out 30 signatures to
local residents, you succeed!]
Excessive soliciting is prohibited.
Passing out more than one
to the same person is prohibited.
This is not feasible...!
This is...
What kind of signing event can I have here?
[That's why it's an abnormal signing event...]
It's not like I can give out signatures
to a cactus...
Do a fan signing?
It's not horseback riding or something?
[Why would I give you a ride?]
I'm sure all the members have
the same mission as this...
[Waving the flag with all her might...]
Are you sure people
actually come around here?
I don't think anyone will be coming
with the low tide...
[Using the signing papers as a sign]
Wow... Now that I'm doing this,
this is really embarrassing.
It's way too embarrassing.
[How to get 30 signatures out...?]
[Gary in front of a supermarket]
Not a single person is passing by.
Over here!
Oh my...!
[Caught speechless]
I shouldn't be doing that when they're driving.
[There's no obvious method...]
[Distressed?]
Save me!
[Blank-Ji put in distress from
having come to do the signing event]
What the heck am I doing here...
[Laughing at the absurdity of it all]
[Anyways... Slowly starting to get set up]
[Not even the flags
are helping out the Giraffe]
[The setting is...]
[Why is he taking out his anger on the flags?]
[What the heck is this...?]
Ah... Seriously...
-There's not a single person passing by...
-There are tons of cars around.
This is still very early in the morning.
Yes, yes...
Mr. Hyung Taek?
[PD??]
[Attempting to present
his signature to the PD's]
-No... Please don't be embarrassed.
-I can't accept it like that.
Don't be embarrassed.
-I'll write, 'Study hard'.
-Study?
Why?
It is bad for me to tell you to study hard?
This is the most popular memo that I write
among the parents.
Kwon Yeol... I should give you one too.
-I'm fine.
-You're fine?  What do you mean, you're fine?
I'm signing it for you!  Seriously...
Please don't order anything too expensive.
Hey, ant... You want my signature?
[Starting to have conversation with an ant]
Where are you going?
Hey... Why do you keep running away?
[Impala going back to nature within
30 minutes of being out in the field]
You're the only one I have... Ant...
What's your name?  Is it 'Ant Kim?'
Or is it 'Ant Choi?'
Why don't you call your friends over too?
Only about 30 of them.
[Impala's hopeless signing event]
Do you want my signature?
[Forcing his signature upon the horse]
[Approaching from afar out of fear]
[Is it mad?]
[Same herbivore.
Seems upset at Giraffe's appearance].
-A signature is for someone who wants it.
-It wanted it.
The horse wanted it... It did.
[What?  You said, I wanted it?]
Sign it for me... Sign it for me...!
[Is that a gag?]
If I don't at least do this,
how can I give out 30 signatures?
There's no one here... There's no one.
Hello...
[Advertising her sign]
[Here! Here!]
[The first time she has acted like this
as a Hallyu star in her life]
She's not coming...
There aren't even any cars driving by.
[Jae Suk's current number of signatures: 0]
Hey!  What do you find so funny
about a car driving by?
What's so funny about a car going by?
[Taking his anger out
on Kwon Yeol for no reason]
[Chae-Reung Elementary School]
If you were going to pick a school,
we should've come earlier.
Can I move my spot?
Wait... Hi!!
[2 students showing up just at the right time]
Hi, kids!
Here... Read this.
What do you think I'm doing here?
-A signing event.
-Yeah, a signing event.
How about a signature...
-Sign it for me please.
-Okay, kids!
[At last, someone who wants a signature!]
Hee Kyung?  Oh, Hee Hyun...
[After the long wait, signing event starts!]
Hello!
Is it the same lady from before?
Please don't go...!
Just once...
Just once, please!
[Abnormal signing event
that's garnering a crowd]
Hi!
-Thank you so much for coming!
-Oh my gosh!  I can't believe it!
[Ji Min's signing event
also goes off to a start]
Thank you so much!
Oh my goodness!!
Oh my goodness... Hello!
[All the ladies dashing out
from the next building]
Please come this way.
[Jae Suk also gets his signing event
off to a start]
[More than 1 signature
per person isn't allowed]
Why are you being so abrupt to these
fans who came out here this morning?
[Finally people have appeared
to start off his signing event...]
-My son's name is Seung Won.
-Seung Won?
[But at the equestrian center...]
Look at that!  He's going to the signature!
[The horse seems to show an interest
at Kwang Soo's signature]
See?  He's looking at it.
[What is this? Is it food?]
He's looking at it.
See?  The horse is looking at my signature.
[It can't just look at the signature,
it has to accept it...]
It looked at my signature.  Like this...
Look at it shaking its tail out of happiness.
[When did I do that?!]
I was shocked thinking
you guys were on vacation.
-Today's the start of our vacation.
-Really?
[All of a sudden, Jong Kook's
signing event is a success!]
Do you know how worried I was?
-That's why we ran over here.
-Thanks.
Bye!
Hi!  You should bring your sister too!
You have to bring her with you.
[Gary convincing her
to bring her sister along]
-She said she doesn't want one.
-You have to bring your sister.
You have to bring your sister...
That's the only way you can get yours.
Even if you don't want it, come take it!
[Impala is also getting started]
Please come stand in line.
Thank you for your support.
Here.
[Ji Hyo's on her way too]
-Hello.  And thank you.
-Hello.
-You're saving me right now.
-I'm saving you?
-Thank you.
-We love you.
[But...]
[Giraffe moving his signing event location]
Don't go!!
Don't go!
[Is he going to Seoul with that table?]
Thanks!
Eun Ah...
What do you want to be when you grow up?
I want to be a Running Man member.
-You want to be a Running Man?
-Yes.
Bye, Eun Ah... Thanks.
See?  Look at her run!
[Already showing her potential]
-Can I give you a hug?
-Thanks!
[Taking him by surprise
and ripping off his name tag]
[Jae Dong's name tag turning into a mess]
They're more fascinated by this than me.
Hey!!
Hey!
-I want to rip it off once.
-I'm going to get ousted then!
Hey!
You can't do that!
[Ripping off Mr. Capable's name tag off,
which only happens a few times a year]
If you guys keep ripping it off like that,
it'll only get easier to rip off.
[Ha Ha at the ladies' diving house working too]
Hello.
Let's hold this and stand in line.
1, 2, 3, 4...
To the right... To the left...
Top... Bottom... Top... Bottom...
Top... Bottom... Hurry!  Hurry!
To the right... To the left...
Nice...Nice!
See?  It's working.
[A rush of visitors from the tour bus!]
-How many of you are there?
-There are 18 of us.
18 people!  Awesome!!
Everyone, scream!!
Scream out, signing event!
[Most festive here!]
[Ji Min with 22 signatures complete]
[A lone child approaching timidly]
How nice of you to come see me by yourself.
-You want my signature?
-No.
What did you say?
[Coolly declining her signature]
You won't take it if I gave you one?
[Please listen carefully to the story
I'm about to tell you now]
[A message in the sketchbook?]
[Pretty sister... I have a favor to ask]
[A favor to ask of Ji Min?]
[You can't turn around.  Promise?]
[I can't turn around and look behind me?]
[The reason why is...]
What's that?
[The reason for asking her
not to turn around is...]
[Is it because of these men that are
approaching her from afar?]
[These men approaching Ji Min
in a heart formation]
[These unidentified men...]
[Just who are these men...?]
You're not going to tell me?
Why?  Why?  I can't see!
Why?  Why?  What is it?
[There's a bashful person who wants to
confess his love to you]
[Behind me...]
[There's someone who wants to confess
his love to me?]
[A bouquet of flowers?]
[Who is it... That's doing this?]
What is it?!
[And... A note?]
[What is written on the note...]
What is that?!
All these men in suits...!
[These mysterious men disappearing behind
a splash of rainbow hued umbrellas]
[Who... Who is it?]
Hey!
Take my signature before you go!
What is this?
They've disappeared!
[Who could it be?
The one who gave me the flowers and the note?]
Dear Ji Min... I like you.
Please find me.
From, your true love.
[From your true love...]
What is this?
Is someone else coming on this show?
Is this Jae Dong?
That's so annoying...
[Suspecting Jae Dong without
much hesitation?]
I have to finish this before
I can start searching for him, right?
Yes, of course.
You'll find everything out once you
get to the final mission location.
This is related to the final mission.
Ah, really...
Even though I don't know who this is...
Even though it was a part of the mission...
It was very touching.
Was he in the middle of the group?
-He was in the middle.
-Seriously?!
So that's why I was told not to turn around...
[Ji Min's true love... Just who could it be?]
[Gary completes his 30 signatures!]
Bye, Ae Young...
No, I'll do it.
[A few more for the fans]
I'm done with my mission.
-You're really handsome!
-Ah... Thank you so much.
Do you know that you look
really unattractive on TV?
[Soothing their hearts
after seeing him in person]
Thank you!
[Jae Suk also completes his 30 signatures]
Thanks to you, I've completed my quota.
Thank you.
[Mr. Capable, taking a commemorative picture
after completing his signing event]
Bye... Okay.  I got it.
-Go get the Giraffe!
-Okay!  I'll go get the Giraffe!
[Okay, don't worry.
I'll make sure to hunt down the Giraffe...!]
[Kwang Soo still short a few signatures]
You're done?
Kwang Soo!
You think a signing event is that easy?
-You're already done?
-Yeah.
[Putting in much care into his last signature]
He's going to make sure to stay healthy,
and make sure to be happy on his own...
Come on, Gary... Thank you.
Thank you!  Thank you!
-Are you done now?
-I'm done!
[The Giraffe is also finished]
[Handing over the final mission location]
[Final location]
[Building 'D' in Jeju's Yeong-pyung-dong]
We're at the final mission already?
[That means... It's the end of the deal?]
Dear audience...
It was nice seeing you.
Let's meet again next week.
Mom...
And Kwang Soo's mother and father...
We're not going to be on TV much today...
[Feeling like he's crawling
into the Tiger's den]
I'll work harder next week...
Then... Goodbye...!
[On the other hand...]
[Impala not making any headway
after his initial 3 people]
[Fighting!]
Thank you!
[Ah... It's a sad fan signing event]
[Soon arriving at
Jeju's 'D' Portal Headquarters]
[Ji Min's the first to arrive on location]
This?
[If she places the object
on top of the screen...]
[Find Han Ji Min's true love!]
Am I looking for that person from earlier?
-The one from the beach?
-That's right.
There's just one person who has confessed
his true love to Han Ji Min.
The rest are fakes that has to
pretend to be her real love.
[There's only one chance!]
[She has to step on the decision podium
with her true love to win!]
[If by any chance, a fake tricks Ji Min
and gets on the podium with her...]
[Han Ji Min will lose,
and the fake will win alone!]
[Han Ji Min will lose the race and the
fake standing on the podium will win alone!]
If by any chance the person you go
up there with is a fake...
Then that fake person will win alone.
Which means that the fake love will win
all the prize and you get nothing.
-What's the prize?
-It's a gold ring.
What?!
-It's me.  Lee Kwang Soo!
-Mission clear.
I'm first love mania!
There are hints about her first love
hidden throughout the building.
-It's hidden throughout?
-Yes.
Can I rip the name tag off?
-Of course, you can rip it off.
-Thank you.
That's all I need.
In that case... What if her true love gets
his name torn off and is ousted?
Then her true love can't win.
Can I get started then?
Then what happens if
Han Ji Min goes up there alone?
-Then what happens?
-Seriously...!
[So frustrating!
Of course, she can't go up there alone!]
She can't go up there alone.
Why is he walking around unarmed?
-Huh?
-Why are you unarmed?
Because I'm her true love.
What are you talking about?
Jae Suk, seriously...
Okay, I understand...
This is harder than a blind date.
[Starting off to find her true love]
[That bashful person who handed over
flowers and a note to her...]
[Who is her true love...?]
[Ah!  It's Ji Min!]
Oh my goodness!
Do you keep the note?
Did you keep the note?
What note?
[Dear Ji Min... I like you.
Please find me.  From: Your true love]
I'm just telling you to hold on to it.
Don't show it to anyone.
[All the members already know about
the note and how the proposal happened]
You're really good at this acting...
-You should try acting in a drama!
-This isn't acting...
[Ha Ha, definitely has a talent for acting
seeing how he is even though he's a fake]
Is it okay for me to rip off the name tag
when I don't think he's the one?
And this is a sign of my affection.
Put your hand on my shoulder just once.
[The feeling of that hand that briefly touched
my shoulder while passing me the note...]
[I'll be able to tell who that is
just by how it felt!]
Up here on my shoulder.
[Could Ha Ha be the one who confessed
his true love to her?]
-I'll see you later.
-Okay.
Don't trust anyone, Ji Min.
Don't trust anyone!
[Ha Ha seems to be telling the truth...]
Juliet!
[Isn't this the scene from
'Romeo and Juliet'?]
[Bittersweet]
[And he was doing so well...]
Even though she may have taken me
for a joke until now...
She's going to be really shocked
when she finds out I'm her true love...
We have to find the hints first.
[If they're the true love,
hide their identity!]
[If they're fake,
they need to get rid of the true love!]
I think there's something there?
[Huh?  There's something...?]
Oh my goodness...
[Big nosed brother... What in the world?
He really discovers a hint right away?]
I found a hint!
[Huh?  It's a picture...]
What's this picture?
Suk Jin!
I'm ousted anyways.
I don't need anything.
Jong Kook said he's going to oust me first.
-Jong Kook's coming after me first.
-Are you first?
[Giraffe's desperate look]
It's the Giraffe.
The Giraffe...
-It's Jong Kook!  Hide!  Here!
-He saw me... He already saw me!
Giraffe... Giraffe!  Giraffe...!
It's the Giraffe...
[Escaping away to the furthest place]
Quickly!
[There's no place for him to go...]
From now...
This is where we need to be for 3 hours.
[Mr. Capable's Giraffe hunt down complete!]
[None other than the Grim Reaper...]
I'll just... I'll just stay right here.
[Frigid]
Can you not...hear what I'm saying right now?
Please don't make any expressions like that!
Please don't make any expressions like that...
[Do you remember why...
Mr. Capable is after Kwang Soo like this?]
[Last week...]
[Mastermind behind the coup that brought down
Mr. Capable... Kwang Soo the Giraffe]
[The one who declared a ruthless
revenge on Kwang Soo the Giraffe]
[Today is that day...]
-Jong Kook... Wait... Wait.
-Why?
-Giraffe, is it you?
-No.
No, I'm not him.
[Disguising himself]
I saw him upstairs earlier.
[A knack for acting out multiple personalities]
-Aren't you Lee Kwang Soo?
-No.  I saw him upstairs earlier.
I saw Lee Kwang Soo upstairs earlier.
I got his signature.
[Taking full advantage of the character
seen in the movies]
No, I'm not him.
Wait...
-Kwang Soo...!
-No, that's not me.
Please just stop!  Rip it off!
I'd rather you just rip it off!
It's not me!  Please, Jong Kook!
It's not me!
I'll just stay here...
I'll think of this as my home and stay here.
[Revenge reincarnate Mr. Capable
who has no intention of ending this easily]
[What is the older Easy Brother,
Big nosed brother doing here?]
-Jong Kook...
-Why are you asking for Kwang Soo!
-I really have something to say.
-What do you have to say?
I'll give you a hint...
So let Kwang Soo go just once.
[Big nosed brother looking out for Kwang Soo]
Pil-Chok-Cross!
Here... Here it is.
[Showing the picture clue in exchange
for Kwang Soo's life]
-Hand it over quickly.
-I'll give this to you.
It's the grand award...
It's in the picture here...
-If it's the grand award...
-If it's a grand prize...
Only Jae Suk and Jong Kook's
ever received one.
Jong Kook's received it 3 times.
Do you know how long it's been
since I've received mine?
[If the grand trophy in the picture is a clue,
then is it really Jae Suk or Jong Kook?]
Anyways... Let Kwang Soo go just once.
-I'm giving that to you.
-Okay... You stay in there for now.
Were you just trying to lock the door?
I don't think this door locks.
[The grand trophy is in the middle...]
[And on either side are current employees,
Kim Kwang Soo and Lee Dong Hoon?]
Kwang Soo... I succeeded in trading you.
It's okay.
You look like you're being released
from prison.
[Looks as though he's being
released from a foul place...]
[Giraffe cheating death and escaping]
-I don't know how to thank...
-Jong Kook, we'll see you later!
Jong Kook, thank... Thank you!!
I'll live the rest of my life being kind!
[Giraffe being saved by Big nosed brother
paying his bond]
[There's nothing like a brother
when you're in trouble...]
[As soon as he's released,
his treachery DNA comes into play]
Hey!!
[That horrible habit...]
I seriously won't do it again!
[The notorious icon of betrayal]
-I'm sorry, Su Jin...
-This is the real you... Jong Kook!!
Jong Kook!  Jong kook...!
What I did was wrong!
It wasn't me, it was my left hand!
This isn't going to work. Jong Kook!
Come and rip off his name tag!
You're not going to do it, right?
You didn't even know you were doing it, right?
I really won't do it.  Pil!
-I can't trust you... Chok!
-Cross!
If he loves me, then I'll be able to tell.
Ji Min!  What are you doing?
Long time no see.
I won't make this long.
I just want you to remember how
it felt when I touched your shoulder.
But there's no way it can be Kwang Soo.
There's something I have to tell you.
He would have stuck out in the
middle of all those people.
[With his height,
Kwang Soo would've been obvious]
It's something really important...
When it comes to Running Man...
It's always the least likely person
that's the right answer.
But I still don't think it's you.
[The one person who really doesn't seem
to be her true love?]
[What it felt to have touched you...
I still remember it]
Your fourth finger and my second finger
grazed each other.
But I grabbed the note like this.
-You grabbed it like...
-Its Jong Kook!  It's Jong Kook!
Where is he?
What's wrong with you?
If Kwang Soo truly is my real love...
I'm going to have to
protect you from Jong Kook.
I don't care if I get ousted,
but I keep running away because of that.
If you're my true love and get caught...
Put your hand on my shoulder.
[Kwang Soo, the man facing danger...
Could he possibly be...]
[Is the Kim 'Kwang Soo'
in the picture a clue about Kwang Soo?]
[And...]
[The exciting touch
of a hand on her shoulder...]
[Tenderly...]
Please remember.
[A similar feeling... To earlier?]
Stand up and try it again...!
If someone this huge had come,
I would've noticed.
-Someone this huge...
-See?  I told you...
Anyways Ji Min... The least likely person
is the one on Running Man.
Just keep that in mind.  Let's go.
You do seem like you would be
the least likely...
Me?  You would think that, right?
[Hmm... Big nosed brother...]
[Seeing how frustrated you are...
Perhaps are you the real true love?]
There's no way you'd know...
But I...
I hope that you'll see how I really feel.
Jong Kook's coming!  Jong Kook!
[More than love or compatibility...
It's the scary Mr. Capable]
He's just pitiful... Just pitiful.
I hope you realize the reason for me
trying to survive this badly.
[Kwang Soo's reason for trying to survive...
Is it because he's her true love?]
-Jae Dong...
-What?
I'm sorry for earlier this morning,
and I hope you get a lot of airtime on here.
What are you talking about?
Well... Since you've come so far...
It must hurt your feelings
if you don't get enough airtime.
There's no need for me to get airtime.
I don't need to be shown on this show.
All it matters is that you're shown.
Anyways, how have you been?
What do you mean, how have I been?
When you already call me once in awhile.
You haven't found a boyfriend yet?
Strange...
The style of that bouquet was
just your style earlier...
[The bouquet of flowers that she received
earlier was Jae Dong's style of choice?]
[Red, yellow, and green...
Are primary colors Jae Dong's style?]
[And now facing Gary too...]
Ji Min!
-Where have you been?
-Why?
You remember me, don't you?
I couldn't really tell you earlier
because of all the people there.
Did you read the note?
I seriously read it carefully.
-You only have one chance...
-Just like earlier...
I want you to give me strength
like you did earlier.
How... This?
Ah, you want me to do this?
Did you just send me a kiss right now, Ji Min?
-Hey!  Han Ji Mong!
-Han Ji Mong?
-Han Ji Ming!
-Why, Gary-Ang?
I asked you, if you remember?
-Remember...
-Remember...!
Okay?  There's only one chance, Ji Min.
What?!  What are you doing?
Ji Min-Ang!
There's only one chance.
You need to think carefully.
-Okay.
-Hey!
[The sweet lover-like atmosphere...
Is Gary... Her true love?]
[Who is her true love?]
[On the other hand...]
[These two who keep running into each other]
-I'm just walking around.
-It can't be you, right?!
How could I be the one?
It's not you, right?
It's me.
But you really finished quickly...
You can't be it.  You're a married man.
You're a married man.
[What does that have to do with the game?]
What does that have to do with it?
But you still can't do that...
It's not like I'm looking at
Ji Min as my real true love.
This is only just a game.
But still...
We're looking for the suspect
that gave her the bouquet of flowers.
But you have a family.
You can't be giving her flowers.
It's like I gave it to her secretly.
-I didn't give it to her secretly.
-But it was given to her secretly!
I gave it to her out in the open.
That's allowed.
Who was watching when you gave it to her?
The camera.
I gave her the flowers where
all the viewers were watching.
So it's okay.
You have some very strange morals!
What does that have to do with my morals?
-You're asking for trouble!
-That has nothing to do with this!
Hurry up and apologize.
But why?
Why would I have to?
What have I done by giving her flowers
for a mission?
Did you give it to her?
-Ah...
-You gave it to her.
[Fell for his leading questions?]
[If this is the case...
Is Jae Suk the one who confessed his love?]
But that can't be it.  I gave it to her.
Come on...
There's no way it's you.
You don't have the looks to pull
something like this off.
[Lacking looks for love?]
Even though it's only a nickname
between us, you're 'Shin-kkuh-Sa'.
[Intersection without traffic lights]
[A chaotic face...?]
Even though I know I'm ugly too, but still...!
I'm still better than you!
[Jae Suk with countless number of
less attractive underlings]
You guys can fight amongst yourselves
and climb up here.
Pick the best out of yourselves
at the end of the year.
Pick the best looking amongst yourselves
and then you can join my ranks.
No matter the case...
I have to get up on the podium with Ji Min
because I'm her true love
that gave her the flowers.
-So Shin-kkuh-Sa...
-I have to get up there too.
I'm going to get going.
[The 'Looks Brothers'
showing off their competitive streak]
Jae Suk!
-Jae Suk!
-Yeah?
Ji Min!
It's getting close to the time that you
have to get on that podium with me.
Are you okay?
Did you find out who it is?
-How can I find him... How can I find him?
-Huh?
I love you...!
I said, I love you.
What did he say?  Did he say he loved you?
Ji Min...
There's not much time left...
You have to choose soon and get up there.
I really have no idea.
Don't be fooled, Ji Min.
Don't be fooled.
I really know.
[Every person she runs into tells her
that he's her true love...]
I really can't say too much right now.
But later, I promise...
If others find out it's me,
they're going to rip my name tag off.
-Did you find any clues?
-I haven't found a single one.
-Have you found any clues?
-On the fifth floor...
Fifth floor...?
The room at the end with the chalkboard
on the fifth floor...
There's a 'J' written on there.  'J'...
[A little earlier...]
J?
[Discovers the clue, 'J'!]
The room at the end with the chalkboard
on the fifth floor...
There's a 'J' written on there.  'J'...
Jae Suk!
[Is the 'J' an initial for a name?]
Jae Suk!!
Jae Dong?!
[A different 'J'?]
-Jong Kook...!
-It's not him, Ji Min...!
What the heck?  That looks really natural.
-Looking at you guys...
-Do we look good together?
-No...
-What is he doing?
[Aggressively showing off his affection]
[What is he doing with all the
countless employees watching?]
It makes even less sense that
you're allowing him to do that right now.
Just bolt out of your seat
and slap him in the face!
What are you guys doing?
What are you guys doing?!
-He does this all the time...
-You can't allow him to keep doing that!
I think he's really tired right now
so he needs to get his rest.
No... But I'm sure when they broadcast this
they're going to make it
seem like he dreamed it, right?
Because whenever I open my eyes,
there's only a pillow left behind.
-Ji Min... Seriously...
-Did you find any clues?
-I'm being more serious about this.
Clues?  If I find any, I'll give it to you.
-I'll give it to you when I find any.
-Ji Min...
I'll go find another hint and tell you
just to make things more clear to you.
Ji Min, I'm being serious.
Go up to the fifth floor.
I'm seriously about to go crazy!
Ji Min... There's no need for you to go crazy.
Because I'm the one that loves you.
Why does she keep laughing at me?
Is this funny?
[What do you think
when you look at it, Jae Dong?]
I have something to say to you, Ji Min.
I'm so confused right now that I think I'll be
even more confused if you say anything.
The way I see it...
I think it's Gary.  What do you think?
[Gary?]
Think about it carefully.
-It could be Gary.
-Why?
The way I see it...
I'm so confused.
[Ji Hyo bringing Ji Min to Gary...]
-What do you think, Gary?
-About what?
You don't think so?
-Me?
-Her true love?
Me?  Why me?
I should only be telling Ji Min...
[Only the one who made the confession
knows the truth about her real love]
I know myself, so I know.
-Then who's your true love?
-You!
You!
I just heard you, Gary.
Ji Min!  That's a misunderstanding.
It's a misunderstanding.
He was just joking around.
[I guess it's not Gary!]
I heard you, Gary.
Get your head on straight!
Today, you love Han Ji Min!
-You love Han Ji Min!
-But you...
[Is Gary expressing
his residual feelings again?]
[Is Gary just doing a good job of
hiding his true love... Or not?...?]
I don't think it's Kwang Soo...
It's not Kwang Soo.
Ji Suk Jin...
No, he's not it.
I don't think it's Ha Ha either...
There's no one.
Are you her true love?
As I'm sure you already know...
I'm a love maniac.
A first love maniac...
What about you?
Let's talk about this in front of Ji Min.
I'm fine with that.
[Huh?  The Giraffe is heading this way?]
[If he stays here, we may be able to see
the Tiger catching the Giraffe for his meal]
-Hey...
-Ha Ha...
Oh!  Ji Min...
Ji Min... Have you been somewhere?
I've been around here.
-Were you looking for me?
-Did you like the flowers?
-Yes.
I was the one who gave it...
[That bashfulness...
It could really be Jong Kook...]
Oh my... Mr. First to be out is here.
-Mr. Second, I've heard a lot about you.
-Yes, it's nice to meet you.
-I heard that you're going to die soon.
-I have a little bit more time.
I gave him a clue...
You can't die if
you're my true love, Kwang Soo.
Kwang Soo! Come here.
[Individual movements not allowed]
-This one is a total scammer.
-He's a real scammer.
-Ji Min!
-Yes?
Be careful going around.
The reason why is...
The fake ones...
If they trick you and you get up there,
then you lose.
Then you'll fail.
Ji Min, get your head on straight!
Everyone else other than me are fakes!
Don't die, Kwang Soo, okay?
But I have a feeling
that you're going to die soon.
No, I won't, Ji Min.
Can I go in here?
[Jae Suk heads into the gym to find a clue]
[Discovers the marker for a clue!]
What is this?
[Shin-Kkuh-Sa Jae Dong also arrives
following behind Jae Suk's footsteps]
-What are you doing here?
-I wanted to get a workout in.
Did you find a clue?
[Baseball]
What?
Baseball?
Did you see it?
[A baseball fan amongst them would definitely
be either Jae Suk or Jae Dong]
[Are they both nervous because the clue
indicates to themselves?]
[How can he argue that he's Ji Min's true love
when he's behaving that way?]
Jae Dong has a really nice form.
See how he's swinging now?
But do you know how he hits on the plate?
'Oops!  I missed that a little'.
I saw him a while ago when we used to play
on the celebrity baseball league.
His form was so horrible back then...
This is a total shocker for me right now.
Is it you?
Don't you know how disappointed
Ji Min's going to be?
[If Shin-Kkuh-Sa was her true love...]
Ji Min... What's Ji Min going to do?
I feel so bad for Ji Min!
Jae Suk...
I could not be it either.
If it's 'J' and baseball, that would be you.
What?
J?
You just don't know anything, do you?
What have you been going around doing?
There was a 'J' too?
Inside my head right now...
I'm pondering if I should oust you or not.
Your self-confidence keeps on
taking a hit, isn't it?
Jae Suk... Aren't you THE Yoo Jae Suk?
Jae Suk... Wait...
Jae Suk.
But you're THE Yoo Jae Suk.
[The 2 people with a real high probability
with 'J', baseball, and the grand prize]
[Think about this carefully too...]
There's a famous baseball player
named Kim Jong Kook.
He plays for KIA.
It means that I may not be the one.
Jae Suk...
-Jae Suk.
-Yeah.
But you know it could also
very well be me, right?
[You know it could also very well be me?]
Ji Min!
Ji Min...!
[Kwang Soo has found a clue!]
-What is this?
-Something that can reveal the truth...
[A weight scale?]
[Kwang Soo, the one who discovered it
is going up on the scale]
[Huh?  The arrow mark and Kwang Soo's
weight is matching up?]
[Kwang Soo matches perfectly to
the weight scale mark!]
[Then does this mean Kwang Soo
is her real true love?]
I wasn't going to go this far...
It's real...!
[Finally Kwang Soo has become
a strong true love candidate]
To be honest, I didn't know there
would be a clue like this.
[Kwang Soo... Is it you?]
[After hearing the news, everyone
heads over to get on the scale]
[Disqualified.  Ha Ha is below the mark]
Disqualified.
[Of course, Gary would be below the mark]
Jae Dong.  You just need to get on it.
[Then Jae Dong...is definitely below the mark]
[For now the only person that matches
is Kwang Soo only!]
[Then let's hurry up and get out of here!]
[Ah... A lover's escape... Huh?]
If they go, Kwang Soo could win as a fake.
We can't let that happen!
[Ji Min believes that Kwang Soo
is the one at the moment]
[Only one chance to get up on the podium!
Have to stop others from getting on it!]
-Since we ran away...
-They're coming!
Ji Min...!
How much do you weigh?
-How much do you weigh?
-Ji Min...
[Since it looks as though everyone will
be gathered, it's time to convince her]
Ji Min...
-Did you find any clues?
-How much do you weigh?
-It's not Kwang Soo.
-Why?
-Did you look up on the fifth floor?
-No, I haven't seen it.
Ji Min, Kwang Soo...
-It's Jong Kook!
-Run away for now.
-Ji Min... You can't be fooled!
-What?
Ji Min, running away right now...
Is like a lover's escape!
-Just go Kwang Soo... Run!
-I love you!
-Ji Min!
-How can you be that simple?
-With just that one clue?  Open the door.
-Ji Min...
-Think about this carefully...
-Don't be so simple.
If by any chance, it's not Kwang Soo...
-Then Kwang Soo is going to win.
-Kwang Soo wins then.
The name for this escape right now...
Is a lovers' escape!
This feeling right now...!
Don't ever forget it!
Ji Min... It's not Kwang Soo.
I don't know...
I haven't found a single clue yet.
According to the information that
I have gathered...
You all need to know this.
It's not Ha Ha, Suk Jin, Kwang Soo or Gary.
-Why?
-Then is it one of you two?
Wait a minute...
-It's not Ji Hyo either.
-No, not Ji Hyo.
[Ji Hyo's definitely not a suspect either]
[Then the only suspects remaining would be
Jae Suk, Jong Kook and Jae Dong]
[The 'J' and baseball that Jae Suk has found
adds to the reasoning]
[If paying attention to what the weight scale
says, then the interpretation says otherwise]
Ji Min,
why don't you step outside for a minute?
-Yeah.  Let us talk this out.
-She needs to stay with us.
-I'll take Ji Min and stand outside the door.
-Okay. Do that.
-Let us talk for a bit.
-Your hand when we were running earlier...
-...it felt really warm.
-You'll remember yesterday, right Ji Min?
Who do you think it is?
I...did think that it was Jae Dong...
But Kwang Soo matched
the weight marker so perfectly...!
But the fact that it
matches so perfectly is weird.
-Just think about it.
-Is that what you think?
Do you still think that it's Gary?
I think it's Gary.
I'm thinking about you
and helping you find your true love.
[Getting even more confusing with
each hint that they find...]
The person who says they're the one,
please raise their hands.
-The ones who aren't?
-No, the ones who are.
-He's really being shameless.
-I'm the real one.
[An outcry from all the young men]
I'm sorry to interrupt your conversation...
But have you seen Han Ji Min?
-We saw her.
-Where is she?
Jae Dong...also is a possibility.
-Really?
-I could be the one. Where is she?
The possibility is there according
to the information that I've gathered.
-Where is Ji Min?
-No, he can't be the one.
-Let me just say this.
-He can't be the one.
'J'... There's a 'J' in the name.
'J'?  What about Ji Suk Jin?
[Jong Kook-Jae Dong-Jae Suk-Suk Jin]
Jae Suk... My name is actually Jelly.
-It's not Gary, but Jelly?
-My real name is Jelly.
My name is Ja Ja.
And my name is Jang Soo!
Think about something else.
-Jong Kook...
-It was fine up to Jelly and Ja Ja...
Then my name is Kwang Joo.
Think about it one more time.
Can I say one thing before I go since you
guys dismissed me so harshly?
-Is Jae Suk up there?
-Yeah.
In my opinion,
there's a 90% chance that it's Jae Suk.
-Why?  Why do you think that?
-According to the clue I found.
[Jae Dong believes Jae Suk is the true love]
Jae Suk weighs exactly 76 kg.
[The marker on the weight scale earlier
was also 76k!]
[If the fakes are to take advantage,
they have to oust the true love!]
[If one insists on being the true one here,
they could definitely get taken out!]
It's me!  Kang Jelly!
-Wait... Wait a minute.
-And after that...
Listen to me... Listen to me first.
-The information that I've gathered.
-Who is it then?
-Baseball.
-Wait.  Don't listen to him!
-Baseball?
-Baseball.
[R-Clue: Baseball. J. Grand Prize]
-Baseball...
-There's a 'J' in there...
-And he also received the award.
-The award...
-Jae Suk...
Then that would be you.
[He deeply digs his own grave]
[A total ambush]
Wait a minute!
[But if you think about it,
Baseball. J. Award... Jae Dong also qualifies]
-Jae Suk...
-But I received it too.
Ah, that's right.
[Baseball. J. Award...
Is it really one of these 3?]
You only looked at the weight scale...
There was something written on
the weight scale...
So I came back to take a look,
and it says 'Duet'.
[Now that we look at it again... Duet?]
Who would be in a duet?
Leessang!  Kang Gary!
[But Ji Hyo...
Why do you keep insisting on Gary?]
In my opinion... I think it's Gary.
What do you think?
It could be Gary.
-You still think it's Gary?
-I think it's Gary.
[Earlier... After signing mission was over]
[A secret mission only she received]
[Today's final mission is
'Find Han Ji Min's true love']
[All the men will be trying to be selected
by Han Ji Min as her one true love]
[However!]
[If the man that you choose becomes
Han Ji Min's selection, then you win]
[Whether it's real or fake, if the man that
Ji Hyo picks gets on the podium, Ji Hyo wins!]
I...pick Gary.
[Ji Hyo picks Gary!]
[This is why Ji Hyo keeps going around
insisting that it's Gary]
Get up there and crouch down.
Everyone was only looking at the weight.
But beneath the weight arrow...
Diet!
[Duet...!]
Gary... Duet!
-Gary!
-Leessang!
-That's right!
-I'm in a duet group!
That's right!
It's a perfect clue, isn't it?
Ha Ha...
Jong Kook!  Turbo!
We're all in a duet!
[Going crazy...]
Think about...the people in a duet right now.
Recently... Jae Suk and Lee Juk
put out a duet song.
[J. Baseball. Grand award. Duet...
Are all these clues to Jae Suk?]
He even received the grand award...
And he used to play baseball...
[The real one is Jae Suk...?
In that case...!!]
[Who is her true love?]
You know how long I've like you, right?
[Showing Ji Min the baseball hint,
and convincing her it's themselves]
Who is 'J' and baseball?
Huh?  Who is 'J' and baseball, Ji Min?
Ji Min... Think about when we used to work...
Don't you remember?
Ji Min... Listen to me.
[That's right!]
[She finally remembers!
The USB clue from this morning!]
-I think I need to look at this.
-Ji Min!
-I have to check...
[The two men getting desperate]
-It's 'J' and baseball...
-Think about it.
[Ji Min starting to look as though she's
slowly starting to narrow down her candidates]
Ji Min!  I won't say anything anymore.
You just need to choose when you go up.
Ji Min!  Ji Min!
[Everyone gathering in the gym to
check out the baseball clue]
-Did you see the baseball clue?
-What?
Yeah, I saw the baseball.
-What's this?
-It's baseball.
-But I have nothing to do with baseball.
-Jae Dong really loves baseball.
-He used to play baseball.
-You used to play baseball too, Jae Suk!
-Yeah, I used to play.
-You used to play baseball too.
-And you even took home the award!
-And he has a big possibility too.
To be honest... If we were frank about it...
You have the highest possibility right now.
Jae Suk... The thing everyone
has wrong right now...
Did you see the word that was written
beneath the number on the scale?
-What?
-On the scale?
-Everyone only saw the number, right?
-Yeah...
I was suspicious of it and there was an arrow
underneath it so I went and took a look...
If you add that in...
-There's one person who's guaranteed.
-What did the arrow point to?
Who is it?
-He's next to you, isn't he?
-Yeah...
-What did the arrow point to?
-Is it Jae Suk?
Duet.
That's right... You did one with
Lee Juk recently.
What are you doing?
What are you all doing?
-'J' and baseball...
-How did you propose?
[If Jae Suk really is the true love,
then he's totally screwed]
[Ji Hyo trying to get rid of Jae Suk
to put her chosen one, Gary up on the podium]
Song Ji Hyo!!
Where is she going?
Ha Ha!  Ha Ha!!
Hey!  Hey!!
[Jae Suk-Out!]
I swear, he was the one.
If he really is the one,
this would be awesome.
[Yoo Jae Suk-Out!  Yoo Jae Suk-Out!]
Who killed you, Jae Suk?
[No matter who killed him...]
[If he was her true love,
Ji Min's chance of winning is out the window]
-Are you in a duet?  Have you ever done one?
-What?
Where's Gary?
Gary was just running around looking for you.
Does Gary like baseball?
Of course, he does.
Who doesn't like baseball?
Ji Min!  It's me!
[Everyone is now actively courting her]
-It's really me!
-There's no time!
You don't know that there's a 'J'
in the name, do you?
How do you know it's a part of a name or not?
-It's a part of a name...
-And the weight scale...
Think carefully about whether or not
'J' is part of a name.  It could not be.
The scale isn't about the weight.
It's not about the weight.
-Duet... I come from a duet.
-Are you part of a duet?
-I am too!
-Turbo?
[Ha Ha has a duet out with Skull currently]
[K HQ Entertainment Weekly]
[She used to MC with Jae Dong as a duet]
Think about different types of duet.
[Divided opinion]
Who do you think it is?  Just tell us that.
-It isn't the weight...
-I'm confused between Gary...
-And Kwang Soo?
-No, not him. Jae Dong.
No, I don't think it's Kwang Soo.
Something's off like Ji Hyo says.
Ji Min!  Who was the one that always talked
about baseball while you used to guest MC?
But why does he keep running away?
Is he really the one?
Where in the heck is Kang Gary right now?
Be reasonable about your true love.
My father is Ha Il Sung,
the baseball commentator...
[Huh?  Where has Giraffe been
to show up now...?]
[He's handing her something...
Could it be a clue?]
Could he have made this himself?
Could he have made this up?
[LKS?]
[LKS?  Lee Kwang Soo?]
[Did he seriously make this himself?]
It's too obvious of a hint...!
I'm sorry...
But is it possible to print something out?
Print it out with L.K.S...
[Completes printing out his initials!]
[Forcing the 'R' sticker on top!]
[That's how he succeeded in completing
his own clue!]
-Ji Min, that's...!
-Hey... You want to die?
[Giraffe's tricks to have Ji Min
believe that he's her true love]
-Let me see it.
-That makes no sense...
[Decisive Dog-nosed brother takes care of it!]
-He was mine... That was mine...
-I did it for you.
-Kwang Soo... This is continue next week.
-Why did you do that, Suk Jin?
You can take this with you.
Lee Kwang Soo-Out.  Lee Kwang Soo-Out.
[Big-nosed brother is also out!]
Wow... This is no joke.
[And now he's off to attack Jae Dong,
who has the strong potential to be the one!]
Hey!  It's not me...!
Suk Jin... How could you...
[Jae Dong cornered at a dead end!]
Wait... Don't come any closer!
[No, you can't!
Jae Dong could be my true love!]
The truth is... Whether it's you or not,
we have to oust you.
-Why?
-We have to take out the competition.
-But so suddenly like this?
-No matter, we have to rid the competition.
You don't think I had any
opportunity to oust you?
-Me?
-I could have ousted you.
[Ji Min gets rid of Ha Ha's name tag!]
Ji Min, it's me...!
Ji Min,
do you know what you're doing right now?
[Ji Min ousts Ha Ha
for not being a likely suspect]
[Was Ha Ha really a fake love?]
[Awhile later...]
[The decisive clue!
Ji Min goes to check the USB!]
Really?  Where do I plug in the USB?
Thank you.
[There's a video file...]
[X Man??]
Here is the most buzzed about
phrases of 2005!
Of course!
Tell me that you love me.
Everything else is great about you.
But your problem is... You're too forward!
[Cupid of love, Ha Ha can be seen...]
You're the only one in my eyes.
[Jae Dong is on screen too...]
[Jong Kook too...!]
You're the only one in his eyes!
Ha Ha... Kim Jong Kook...
What do I do?!
What is this?
Baseball...
I think it's Jae Dong.
[Ji Min confirms her belief that
her true love is Jae Dong!]
I have to go find him!  Thank you!
Duet!  Yeah... He's a duet
because he and I MC'd together.
It definitely wasn't Kwang Soo!
[Ji Min rushing to get on
the podium with Jae Dong!]
[It's Jae Dong!]
-It's really not Jae Dong.
-Let's oust him right now.
Jae Dong knows it too.
See?  He's running away right now.
[Even though it was confusing,
finally have confirmed he's her true love...]
[Now...]
[Uh Oh!]
[Jong Kook gets rid of Jae Dong's name tag!]
Jae Dong, what is this?
What is this fighting?
-What is this?
-Is something back there?
[How can this be... No!!]
[I'm sure Jae Dong is my true love
that confessed his love to me...]
-Why do you think I came on this program?
-Why?
I came on here because of Ji Min.
[Listening to what he has to say...
It really was Jae Dong...!]
That wasn't right!
-Jong Kook!  That really wasn't right!
-Jae Dong... Then I really apologize!
-You're apologizing now?
-I really am sorry.
What do I do now?
We'll go stand out there now,
and you can decide.
We've decided to concede.
It's the truth bell...!
It's really been a long time since
we've seen that Truth Bell.
And now, for Han Ji Min's selection?
[How long has this been...?]
If you get up there holding
one of their hand...
If you go up there with the right one,
there will be confetti flying down...
If it's the wrong one,
there will be a water shower.
You know which one it is, don't you Ji Min?
[Just whose hand will Ji Min grab?]
I think I know.
Please grab a hand and stand up there.
One...
[Jong Kook?]
[Gary?]
[Time to get up on the podium!]
[Take Gary up there!]
[Her selection is...?]
-It's me, right?
-Hey!  I'm Kang Hee Jin!
And I was in a duet...
And good at baseball...
-Kang Hee Jin, just come here.
-Okay, I'm coming.
It's not me!
The two of you have gotten really close
again here on Jeju Island.
Seriously...
Did you do all this because you
redeveloped your feelings for me again?
My position was actually very difficult
because I'm a girl...
I actually thought about...
Who the real one would be,
and went to bat for him.
[Just a means for batting for someone?]
Then you didn't believe in me?!
You were just trying to win it for yourself?!
I really thought it was weird myself...
-Song Ji...
-Gary, seriously...
This was the first time you've talked to me
so much while we've filmed Running Man.
[A day full of conversing with Gary]
Wait, I think I may be getting
showered on.
[Returning the mike in preparation
of being showered on with water]
[Self-despair?]
Right now... Ji Min is getting ready
to get soaked to the bone.
[Right now, Ji Min's belief in Jong Kook
that she's stepped up with is...?]
-Who is the person that you thought it was?
-Jae Dong.
-You thought it was him from the final clue?
-You thought it was Jae Dong?
-I thought all along that it may be him...
-He's crying right now.
-I just wanted to confirm it.
Let's get started!
Are you ready?
-I'm seriously so nervous!
-The Bell of Truth!
[The Bell of Truth!  Ring it!]
[Jong Kook... Are you my true love?]
[The flowers and the note that was
handed to me on the back this morning...]
[Who was the one that was
behind those umbrellas?]
Those flowers were totally your style.
Yellow and red...
-It was really yellow and red...
-What?
[Vague mutterings...
And forward confessions...]
[And his video impression...!]
[That's why she was sure
that it was Jae Dong...!]
[But he's already been ousted!]
[And Jong Kook that's made it up]
-Did you like the flowers?
-Yes.
[The bashful conversations...
Concerned gazes...]
Why is it like this?
They have put the people who has
deepest relationship with Running Man on here.
Ah... I'm so confused right now.
Then did you really think that
it wasn't me all this time?
[She has stepped up on the podium with
the one who only confused her...]
Bell of Truth!
Ring it!!
[Next week!]
I don't trust people.
If I don't trust them
there's nothing for me to lose either.
-Open the door!
-I need to go to the bathroom!
I'm not going to give up!!
[Next week's Running Man!
Tracker's abduction!]
[After all the countless interference...
With Mr. Capable...]
Ring the Bell of Truth!
[Ji Min's true love... Kim Jong Kook!]
See? I'm the one!
You really didn't know when you
brought me up here?
[Even though Ji Min didn't see...]
[Flowers and the note...
He was the one who gave it to her!]
Out of all those people...
[Mr. Capable's quality...
This is how you confess...]
[The truth is, there was a decisive moment
that he could remain alive to the end...]
[He discovers an 'R' sticker in the library!]
Spartacus.
[If someone else had discovered this,
his fate would've had him be ousted]
Ji Min had gone up there to get soaked!
I seriously... I'm so sorry, Jong Kook!
Ji Min... Are you disappointed that
you didn't get soaked?
If I hadn't ousted Jae Dong,
you would have been in big trouble!
Today's winners are...
Han Ji Min and Kim Jong Kook!
[True love's winning couple...
Han Ji Min and Kim Jong Kook!]
Subtitles by DramaFever