Absurd disqualification!
[Psychic power truly exists?]
[Power of adherence that's been shown
all over the place in London]
The one who stops time!
[Even the appearance of the strongest
can stop time]
[And that's how a week, that felt like
a mere second, passed on]
[Running Man's comeback race]
(Subtitles by DramaFever
[Gold medal won in London!]
[Laughter is won in Running Man!
The grand race befitting the Olympics]
[The same passion and ardor as the Olympics!]
[Jeju Island's bloody holiday]
[Running Man feverishly cheering on
Republic of Korea!]
[Summer, the season of vacation]
[Jeju Island International Airport]
[Even through the heat wave,
the Running Man go on their MT]
-Look at the clouds. It's supposed to be hot!
-But still, we're in Jeju Island.
[Even in the intense heat,
Jeju Island is full of joy]
Where are we going?
-Wow!
-What's this?
[Arriving at MT location?]
-Kwang Soo, let's get off!
-Yes, Jae Suk.
[Running High School's 'R' class
brimming over with excitement]
-Welcome.
-Let's go.
[Queen Ji Hyo leading the way]
-A man should be carrying that for her.
-It suits Ji Hyo the best.
-Look over there!  I think that's it!
-Is that our dorm?
[A picturesque cafe
in the middle of peaceful woods?]
[Is this where the MT is taking place?]
-Why don't you carry that for her?
-Why am I the oldest one, to carry it?
-You want me to carry it for you?
-Ji Hyo, it really does suit you well though.
-You look like some sort of a delegate.
-A delegate?
-Let's all go inside.
-Let's go in everyone.
-It's really nice in here.
-Wow...!
-Let's get a drink or something.
-Have a seat, Raid Queen, Ji Hyo.
-Now that we're all here...
-Does that say 'Queen'?
Who do you think you're pointing
your finger at?
[Queen Ji Hyo's force receiving protection
from all the male students]
Queen or whatever...
Why don't you guys pay more attention
to fashion and how you dress?
Why don't you pay more attention to your hair?
This style right now is really...
Come here... With your hair like that,
you really look so much like your mother.
[His own mother's doppelganger]
-It's totally his mother! His mother!
-Mother, hello!
Are you here in Ha Ha's place today?
I really thought that it was her...!
[Mother and son look so much alike!]
Anyways, are we on this MT by ourselves today?
Ji Hyo can't be
the only pretty girl here today, right?
There's no difference or separation.
Difference is separation.
-Where's everyone else?
-I'm sorry, but we're in the middle of filming...
It's me!
[Ah... So it's not Michael...?]
-It's me!  What are you guys asking?
-I'm so sorry!  Kwang Soo, it's you!
We really thought you were someone else
sitting there looking like that!
I really thought you were someone else
sitting over there.
[It really is most fun to tease the giraffe]
I'm really sorry, Kwang Soo.
It's because we didn't recognize you.
But isn't Kwang Soo really ugly?
-What?  I've gotten much better looking!
-No... You're really unattractive.
[Did the giraffe just spit?]
[The giraffe at times can't seem to
control his reasoning]
I'm sorry, Ha Ha!
Then since I'm the Queen today...
I have the authority to sit with
whomever I want to sit with, right?
No!
Why do you go against everything I say?
Don't think about all the feelings
that you still have left!
Hey!  Don't think about things like that!
-Those feelings...!
-I shouldn't think about it?
[Suspicious of any residual feelings
left between the two]
-This is so frustrating!
-You still have some feelings left!
No, I don't!  She's just misunderstanding!
She's still disillusioned!
You still have some feelings left!
We'll cut it off here for the broadcast.
[Ex-Monday Boyfriend.
Residual feelings have been discovered]
-Ah, seriously...
-Tell me though, is something going on today?
I came here with a friend.
[Shooting out of their seats]
[The news of a friend
that has everyone rising off their seats]
Hey... What's with your arms doing that?
A friend... She brought her friend!
-Ji Hyo... How...
-Should I introduce my friend?
Hey, do you have any friends that
look like Yang Jung Ah?
[Still single-mindedly wanting Miss Il Sook]
My friend is really pretty...
And she has very pale skin...
[Queen's friend introduction]
[The beautiful woman with pale skin]
She has a great personality...
and she's really pretty.
[On top of that, a great personality...]
[The perfect woman]
My friend...!
Friend, you can come on in now.
[Friend of the Queen...
Just who could it be?]
[Curious]
-Oh, my my... She's really pale.
-She really is pale!
[The woman approaching them shyly...]
[Surprised]
[Goddess of Purity-Han Ji Min]
[A string of successful projects]
[The woman crowned as
the representative of a Hallyu actress]
[Flabbergasted]
Ji Min!
It's Han Ji Min!
I almost didn't recognize her
because she is so beautiful!
[Her blinding beauty that robs
the men of their ability to speak]
-This is my friend.
-No way that can be...
-You all know my friend, Han Ji Min?
-Of course, we know her!
[Ji Hyo's famous friend, Ji Min,
that everyone knows]
I'm a...
[Huh...?]
[Ha Ha's freestyle greeting getting blocked]
-What are you doing when she just got here?
-Hey...!
Everyone stop doing that... Come on...
How do you know Ji Hyo...?
There you go starting again, Jae Suk...!
[Welcome, Queen of Purity, Han Ji Min]
-I'm not busy at all.
-You just finished a drama recently.
Yes, I had nothing else going on,
that's why I came on the show.
[Recently wrapped up the drama,
Rooftop Prince]
-You're totally fit in here.
-What was your major?
I was a French major.
[Legendary French major Goddess, Ji Min]
My initial major was French too!
Sit down!  Why do you keep standing up?
What is your name?
I told you, I knew some French!
[Jae Suk's strong French skills!]
You will be divided into 2 teams between
Song Ji Hyo and Han Ji Min's team.
I think the teams are very well divided.
I have something to give to each of you today.
You can find your picture when you
open up these wallets.
[Passing out an 'R' wallet to every member]
This is the most money we've ever received!
[A fat cash stuffed wallet?]
$220?!
The survey results after interviewing a total
of a thousand people...
As 2012 vacation spending money,
everyone is given $220 per person.
Thus, everyone is given $220 per person.
The race that you'll be doing on Jeju Island
today is the vacation money race.
[Today's mission-Vacation money race]
[A race that's no different than a vacation
on the beautiful Jeju Island]
Use your own spending cash for any expenses
related to the race today.
[Any race related expenses
to be taken cared of themselves]
[Plan your vacation within the limits
given by the vacation allowance]
The one person that wins the most races
can win all the vacation allowance given out.
[However, only 1 ultimate winner can take
all the vacation money given out]
[The competition to take all the vacation
allowance that's been saved frugally]
[Vacation allowance race-Start!]
[Find the Running Man landmark
at Wal-Jung-Ri Beach]
To be honest, I've been a huge fan
of the Running Man from the beginning.
But I don't really get the chance to
watch any TV while shooting a drama...
-We're really popular.
-That much, I know.
[Mix of formal and informal speech?]
Ji Min, have you had dinner?
(Spoken in mix of formal and informal speech)
Ji Min, make yourself comfortable.
Speak in informal speech with us.
-You can just call me Gary.
-Yes, Gary.
Anyways, since when were you so pretty?
You can tell us honestly.
-Honestly?
-Of course, Hee Sun did the same thing!
-She said that she's always been.
-She said she was born pretty.
I've been pretty since I was in
my mom's stomach.
[Coolly acknowledging she's been
pretty since she was in the womb]
You win. You beat Hee Sun.
-You beat Hee Sun!  You beat her!
-You're the prettiest.
I'm sure Hee Sun is going to be shocked!
There's nothing she can do
about you being pretty since in the womb.
With Ji Min in the car,
it really does feel like an MT.
-That's right!
-This is what a true MT is like!
This really feels like an MT!
It's not an MT if you go with
the people that you see every day!
-I'm really grateful to Ji Hyo.
-Of course, we should be grateful to Ji Hyo.
I'm sure they don't even have anything
to talk about amongst themselves.
What could they have to talk about
when they see each other all the time?
I'm sure they're saying stuff like this...
-Instead of making things fun, let's win...
-I'm sure that's what they're talking about.
-Since we're in this situation...
-Let's win!
Let's at least win.
-Jong Kook... Let's win.
-Jong Kook...
I would like for you to remember
that we're on the same team today.
[Expecting a hit?]
Since we have vacation allowance today,
let's buy whatever we want to eat.
If there's anything you want to eat
on the way, just tell us what it is Ji Min.
-We'll take care of you.
-This is Jeju Island.
There are so many delicious things here.
Aren't we going to eat
sea urchin seaweed soup?
Of course, we're going to eat it.
-What about abalone?
-Of course, we're going to eat it!
-I'm drooling over here.
-Me too.
-Here it is... This is it.
-Look at the color of the ocean!
Wow... That's awesome.
[Blinding emerald green ocean]
[Clear blue sky and clear blue ocean]
[Herbivores feeling the danger
and starting to run]
Ji Hyo's the tamer of the pack.
[Tamer Queen Ji Hyo leading
the Tiger, Giraffe, and the Impala]
-I feel like we're in another country.
-This is truly like another country.
How can the water be so clear?
[Clear blue water in Jeju]
Dong Wan supermarket?
[Huh...?]
-Dong Wan, how many jobs do you have?
-How can they do this?
I seriously have forgotten
what you really look like.
[God of disguise, Dong Wan]
A refreshing water gun is $2.00.
What is all this?
[So many different items]
[Even full of refreshing snacks and beverages]
What is all this?
Look at this...
They make it so that we can't not spend money!
-What the heck?
-Look at all this!
-Look at the watermelon!
-Can we eat the watermelon?
That melon looks really good.
Can I have one of the melons?
-Hey guys... I'll buy.
-Do it later...!
[Tiger and Ace reprimanding him right away]
Can I have one too?
[If Queen Ji Min is requesting...]
[Then, of course]
Ah, yes...
-What are you going to have?
-The watermelon.
-Just yours though.
-I'm going to have 2.
Ah, you're going to have 2?
Buy some for us too!
Why don't you buy something
for your own teammate?
[The Queen from each team to use the men as
stepping stones to go across]
[If they fall in the water, then it's a fail]
[The Queen has to get to this spot
for the mission to be a success]
What is this 'Supplemental teammate' for $150?
It's a part time worker.
-Wow... Who would that be?
-If you buy it, then you'll find out.
Then do we need all this stuff?
-We'll just try it then.
-Let's just do it for now...
-Going for the challenge on your own first...
-Let's do the challenge as is first!
-We can save it for some other time.
-We have to be wise about our spending!
[Human Stepping Stone-Start!]
This is just like Maldives!
[Emerald green ocean that could compare
to Maldives' surrounding sea]
That's so cold! So cold!
The moment that I blow the whistle,
you can start forming yourselves.
And the Queen can go across on the
stepping stones so that they don't get wet.
I really hate getting my underwear wet!
-We're selling underwear too.
-Seriously...!
Don't you seriously think that
you're being too much?!
We're not buying it!
We sell everything, so please don't worry.
Okay. Get ready for the whistle blow.
Your time limit is 1 minute!
Here we go!
[White Team-Start!]
[The key is to move quickly]
Hurry!  Gary!  Gary!!
[She has barely moved 4 steps now]
Ugh!  That's so cold!!
[Ah... It's getting deeper and deeper]
Salty!  It's so salty!
[The saltiness of the ocean
that they're getting to taste]
-I'm so sorry!
-It's okay.
Quickly... I'll move quicker.
[Floods Gary]
Gary!  Gary!
[If the Queen falls into the water,
they have to start over from their spot]
[Struggling not to taste the salty water]
Salty!  Salty!  It's salty!
[Queen Ji Min working hard to withstand
the crumbling stepping stone]
Hey, let's go buy something!
[White Team-Fail]
Is there any water?
We're also selling water at the stand.
-How much?
-It's $2.00.
[Refreshing ice water for $2.00.]
-We'll take 2 bottles then.
-The supermarket is that way.
-We have to go and get it?
-Yes.
[No deliveries at Dong Wan supermarket]
I'm going to go buy us some water.
You have to step on the middle of our backs.
[Time for Coach Kook's lessons]
[I said, I got it!]
[Red Team going to challenge!]
[[The Giraffe's legs crumble underneath him]
- Hey!  Do it right!
-Why can't you do it right?!
[Fighting within the family
whenever there's a chance]
We have to start from here.
[Stepping onto inadequate
Giraffe stepping stone]
[Even more inadequate Impala stepping stone]
See? That wasn't me this time!
[Poor inadequacies all over the place]
[Queen Ji Hyo getting soaked
to the bone from the start]
What the heck?  Suk Jin!
-Hey...
-Father!
[Synonymous with inadequacy...
Big nosed father]
[His desperate battle with the ocean]
Don't make Suk Jin do things like this!
[Big nosed stepping stone that crumbles
as soon as it's stepped on...]
-What the heck?
-What's wrong with you?
[Red Team-Fail]
And about Dong Wan...
When I went to his supermarket, he saw that
I was really wet and gave me a towel...
And I thought he was just giving it to me,
but he charged me for the towel too!
He's marketing himself right now!
Jae Suk, should we try the horse style?
Try it.  Try everything we can try first.
It's not the water...
I'm not afraid of the water, but...
It's okay!
[Is it really okay?]
This is... More than anything else...
It really doesn't make me feel very good.
[His biggest problem is that it doesn't
make him feel very good]
-Jae Suk... Why don't we all try the horse?
-Okay... That sounds better.
JI Min... You have to be quick about it, okay?
[Doing the challenge with the 3-men horse]
I'll hold your hand, Ji Min.
-Hey, she's on the other team...
-Thank you.
[Taking off with Giraffe's gallant gesture]
[The Queen's advance looking rather swift]
[But this position...]
I can't hold my breath!
[The plan this time
requires a strong set of lungs]
Oh my gosh...!
[Utters of pain all over the place]
Hurry up!
[Is he diving right now?]
Ji Min!
When are you going to get here, Ji Min?!
Ji Min..!
Let's just go buy whatever!
The way I see it, this game can't be won
without having to buy something.
[How did he know?]
Let's go. We were tricked.
We were tricked big time!
[Whirlwind shopping spree complete?]
[Water goggles-$15.00.  Towel-$2.00]
[White Team loaded with new items]
[Straw hat-$5.00]
[Water goggles-$15.00; Towel-$2.00
Straw Hat-$5.00]
You bought a mask?  How much was that?
-$15.00.
-What?  $15.00?
-Suk Jin... Just go spend the money.
-You look so weird right now!
[With the water goggles, his confidence is up.
His looks crash and burn]
[Alien life form discovered at Jeju beach]
-Your time limit is 1 minute.
-Okay.
Get ready!
[White team armed with
the expensive water goggles]
[Freedom to dive]
[Huh?!]
[Tiger disrupting the breathing]
Stop it!
[The sea water?]
Hey, Lee Kwang Soo, don't do it!
[Jae Suk coolly spitting out the seawater]
-I think we can do it this time.
-Good, good!
[The strength of the equipment?
Going forward with ease]
We're almost there.
[The finish line is within their sight!]
Quickly!  Quickly!
[Are they seeing the benefits
of their expensive equipment?]
Oh my goodness!  Hurry!
-Just a little bit more!
-Little bit more!  Just a little bit more!
[Now, just two more steps!]
[5 seconds left!]
[Queen Ji Min stepping forward
with all her might!]
No way!!
-You've gotten much better!
-Really?
How disappointing...
But you've gotten so much better.
You were almost there. Nice teamwork!
-Maybe we should buy the part-timer.
-Let's go buy one.
-Let's just buy one!
-Let's buy one.
-What's the point of being stingy?
-Let's just buy one!
-We can just earn more money later!
-Seriously!
Why don't you treat, Jae Suk.
[Red Team taking up the challenge again
without any equipment on their own]
Are you guys just trying to do it on your own?
We have an unbelievable plan right now.
We don't spend our money easily.
We'll really show it to you.
You guys are going to be surprised.
[Impala stepping stone
is proving to be inadequate again]
Is that you showing us?
Just go spend some money!
Seriously... These guys...!
Hey, hey...!
[Red Team's goal is to save their allowance]
[Taking the challenge with drastic measures
with just their bare bodies]
[Fail]
Suk Jin...!
You have to move quicker!
[All the blame falling on the Impala]
Suk Jin, let's go spend some money.
I need something to boost up my energy.
Let's go eat something.
-You guys are frustrating.
-Go spend some money!
You should spend some money since you're out
with the family for the first time in so long.
[Red Team sharing energy drinks
amongst themselves]
It's so much cheaper elsewhere!
[Fluctuating prices at Dong Wan market]
-Why are we only spending my money?
-Suk Jin, we're family!
Your money is my money,
and my money is your money!
We should buy these too!
[$10.00 for a T-shirt with their name tags]
Jong Kook... Should we buy the other team's
T-shirts with our money right now?
[Planning on purchasing all the shirts,
and profiteering from them later]
That's a great idea.
-Let's just buy them.
-Buy them and sell them at twice the cost.
-Okay!
-It's $10.00 per shirt.
-If it's $10.00 each... We'll take them all.
-That'll be $80.00 altogether.
Just give us all of them.
They bought even all our t-shirts?
-They bought them all.
-Even ours?
Did they buy their own shirts too?
-Yes, they bought them all.
-It's okay.  Our shirts are nice and cool now.
Let's just get a part timer
for ourselves then.
-They got themselves another team member.
-Really?
[White Team making the investment to win
the mission without scrimping their money]
Jae Suk, you really are a big spender.
Give it a try then.
[Will the investment pay off?]
Ready!
[White Team-Start!]
Okay, okay... Nice!
It's so nice having 3 people!
-Hurry...
-Quicker... Quicker!
Okay, okay... Hurry.  Hurry.
Part timer, quicker.
-Wait1  I'm scared I'm going to fall!
-It's okay, you won't fall.
[Advancing with a quick speed]
Come on... Move it quickly!
-That's too far!
-It's okay, it's okay.
[Queen Ji Min showing her concentration]
Part timer, quickly.
Nice, nice, nice.
[So close to the finish line!]
-A little closer!
-Get a little closer.
[Just 3 more steps!]
Okay... Jump!
[One last step?]
[The final jump!]
[Arriving at the finish line!]
[Success]
Success!!
[White Team's investment pays off!  Success!]
-We should've done this sooner!
-We should've done it sooner!
[Investment well worth it!]
The supermarket is selling clothes.
-For those of you that want to buy...
-We're just going to stay like this.
-You guys need to get it done quickly.
-We understand.
[Red Team going up for the challenge
on their own without any equipment]
Good luck!
-See you later!
-Let's not use anything.
-Let's save our money.
-You can lead her, Suk Jin.
[Coach Kook's lesson time]
Then you stand up and grab her.
-Okay, okay...
-The next person can keep going.
I just want to do it.
[Frugal Red Team-Start!]
-But this isn't very stable.
-Hurry!  We have to go quickly!
[Oh... The Red Team changing their method!]
Nice, nice!
[Will they succeed with their plan alone
without any investments?]
That's right... That feels better.
This is how it should be!
[Even the unstable Impala stepping stone
has become more stable?]
-We're almost there!
-We're there!  We're there!
[Red Team moving at lightning speed]
[The final step]
[Arrives at the finish line!]
Success.
[The workers succeed without any investments]
Don't you think we spent too much money?
It's a good thing we got it first.
No matter, we got through it first.
Why spend the money?
Congratulations.
Forget it, forget it.
[Smart customer, not falling for it twice]
Do we have to pay for the pension too?
It's $100 for 4 people.
If it's $100, everyone pitch in $20, and
Suk Jin pay extra $20 since you're oldest.
Why am I the only one that keeps paying?!
Isn't the oldest brother supposed to
do things like that?
Does he really think that
I'm made of money of something...?
Let's not be so obsessed about money!
They keep asking me to...
There are a total of 4 rooms in the pension.
And it's one person per room.
You guys aren't doing it?
You guys aren't buying the pension?
-You're not buying the pension?
-I have a friend that lives here.
-No, we're not...
-What wrong has Ji Min done?
You guys should buy the pension for her!
[The Red Team being courteous
to the guest, Ji Min.
You really aren't going for the pension?
I told you, we're not.
-And you're not going to buy clothes?
-Why would I buy clothes?
[Not falling for the Red Team's
money making scheme]
Ji Min... Aren't you going to buy a shirt?
-How much is it for the shirt?
-The shirt?
It's only $40.  Just $40.
[The Giraffe trying to sell them off for $40
when they originally cost $10]
-$40 is too much.
-For Ji Min, we'll do it for $20.
-Only $20.
-Don't buy it.  Just keep what you have on.
You can wash it and wring it dry!
[She does want to change after
falling in the salty seawater...]
[She's the Queen!
The team members should buy it for her!]
-We're not buying it.  Hey...
-You can each chip in $5 for her...
[Then the White Team is going to
keep their wet shirt on to the end...?]
[You're really not going to buy?]
-Let's go! I said, we're not buying!
-You're not buying the shirts?  Please buy it!
-I said, we're not buying it!
-You're not going to buy it?
-I can just wring it dry like this.
I can just wring it dry like this.
-I'll buy it if it's $5.
-No, we can't take $5 for it... Not $5.
-Why don't we let her just have it?
-What are you talking about?  We can't do that.
[Queen Ji Min reminding them
of Queen Jung Woo]
-$6...!
-Let's just go, Jong Kook.
Let's go.  Ji Min, you can take these.
[Continuing to convince the weak
Impala brother]
How can we not?  It's Han Ji Min...!
-I'm not asking for anything else...
-Then you can pay for the difference.
Fine!  I'll make up the difference!
Since we were going to sell it for $40,
just give me the $30 for it.
[But having to make up the $30 difference?]
[I got the shirt at a wholesale price!]
-Just give me $30 for it.
-Why would I pay that?!
I have a degree in Business Administration...
If I buy it for $10, then sell it for $7,
and pay extra $30 difference
then what does that make me?
[A business with a negative profit?]
Give me the money!
[Impala brother not living up to his major]
Since we told her $20 earlier,
let's do it for $20.
-$17... I'll make up that difference.
-Just pay $30 for it!
-Give me $7.
-You said $6 earlier.
[The deal was definitely for $6]
[Very precise Queen Ji Min]
We need to get going to the next stop,
so everyone move quickly.
[Ultimately, moving on after acquiring
Ji Min's shirt for $6]
We don't even have any clothes to change into.
[The white team needs to wash up,
but they don't even have any clean clothes]
It's a relief that at least
Ji Min got to buy clean clothes.
We should get there first...
Since they already got the pension ready...
Let's go there and quickly get cleaned up.
-Let's go, Jae Suk.
-Let's go.
[Anyways, they have 3 useless shirts left
of the opposing team's...]
-You don't think we'll be stuck with these?
-I'm sure they won't not buy these...
[Arrives at the pension!]
[Red Team and Ji Min looking to get
cleaned up and change into fresh clothes]
What floor is that?
[Just then!]
[Jae Suk, Gary, and Ha Ha, infiltrating
into the interior of the pension!]
[Going into Impala Brother's room?]
[Eyeing the free shower]
Let's go in.
[Checking to make sure
that the Tiger isn't here]
[First, getting undressed]
[Attack]
[Shocked]
What the heck?!
Hurry up and shower!
What the heck is this?
What are you guys doing?
Hey, two people can stay here...
And the other goes downstairs
to Kwang Soo's room.
[Jae Suk, heading out to find
Kwang Soo's room]
Kwang Soo, let's shower together!
[Flustered]
Jae Suk, what are you doing?!
I'm sorry!
-I'm sorry, Kwang Soo.
-Jae Suk, what are you... Jae Suk!
Sorry... I'm just going to shower.
[The tiger running in
after hearing the Giraffe's scream]
What are you doing?!
-We're showering together.
-What are you doing?!
-Kwang Soo's butt naked right now.
-What the... Wait...!
[You've got 5 minutes left to shower]
-This is...
-What the heck is this?!
I'll leave after washing up real quick!
We don't have any time.  What else can I do?
[Butt naked Giraffe not able to do anything]
Get out!  All of you, get out of here!
[His fate not allowing him to do anything else
but to hide behind the door]
Kwang Soo, thanks for the shower.
Come on!  Shut the door!
Don't just open the door like that!
Hurry up and get out!
Everyone, get out!
Anyways, I'm sorry.  I don't have the time,
so I'm just leaving after washing my face.
Everybody, get out!
Don't torment me anymore...!
-Kwang Soo... Kwang Soo, thank you.
-Please just get out!
I'm going to head out first.
Thanks Kwang Soo!
That was nice...
Wow... That was a nice use of the shower!
All I have to do is to dry my hair outside.
Wow... What a nice use of the shower!
-Those guys just barged in...
-I heard!  Don't you think that's a problem?
Of course, that makes no sense.
We paid a lot of money for it,
and they just barged in.
You can't do everything
so casually like this!
You have to be more firm about it.
We paid $100 for this...
And they just barged in...!
-Suk Jin, this is why we can't ever...
-We can't give them their shirts.
[Reaffirming that they will get
paid their price for the shirts]
I don't think I can wear this shirt.
I'm going to have to buy one.
-I'm going to buy it.
-I'm going to buy it too.  I can't take this.
[The team shirts that fell in the sea water
feels too dirty for them to wear again]
-Kwang Soo, I'll buy the shirt.
-I'm going to buy mine too.
-How much?
-They're going to buy the t-shirts!
The reason why you guys have to pay $20
is because you took a free shower,
so you guys have to pay $20.
$20, $20...
[Tiger not backing down from not accepting
anything less than $20]
You took a free shower.
-But how can you charge $20?
-Let's go... Let's just go.
They said they're going to buy the shirts.
[Reporting the situation
to Queen Ji Hyo in the car]
-They said $15, but I told them $20.
-They can't do that.
-Then I'll keep saying $20.
-If they won't do $20, then take $17.
-Charge them $20.
-Yeah, we have to charge them $20.
We'll buy the t-shirts.
Please sell us the t-shirts.
You can't wear those, can you?
-Then, hurry up and give me the money.
-Hand over the money quickly.
And you even took a shower...
We were going to charge you $30,
but are giving you a break and charging you $20.
Hurry up and hand over the $20.
Let's go... Forget it, and just let's go.
[Pondering]
You bought them originally for $10.
-You even took a shower...
-Yeah, hurry it up.
There's the delivery charge
for delivering it to here also...
-Can you take $15 for it?
-Just forget it.
-Ha Ha... Then $17.
-Okay, $17.
[Final agreed upon price is $17]
Gary, hurry up!
[Wholesale t-shirts being sold for $17]
He bought his shirt.
[Gary walking up to buy his shirt too]
How much for the shirt?
$20.
[Rising price of the t-shirt]
You guys are really being too much.
-Okay, good...
-Suk Jin, you're being too much!
The price of the shower
is included in this price too!
-We should buy Jae Suk's shirt...
-Wait!
-Why?
-Give us Jae Suk's shirt too.
-$20.
-Okay, $20.
[Buying Jae Suk's shirt for $20 too]
[Gary and Ha Ha each chipping in $10
to buy Jae Suk's t-shirt]
Bye, White Team.  Bye.
[Ultimately selling off all the t-shirts!]
Who took the $20 earlier?  Kwang Soo?
-Then we just need to split this then.
-Okay, good!
I made $10!
So did we make $22 off of it?
See?  This is how you do business, Suk Jin.
-Then Suk Jin... Yeah, you did great.
-I did good, didn't I?
-I have $170.
-Why is it I only have $130?
Jae Suk, you can just give us $30 for it.
[Buying a shirt for $20
and trying to sell it for $30]
We really did buy it for $30.
[The cold truth of trying to profiteer
off their own team member]
-Just give me the shirt first...
-Give us the $30 first.
-Come on... Let's just do it for $20.
-Hurry and pay up.
-I can't go then.
-I'm not going either then.
We have to get going quickly.
Come on, let's get going.
This will be over if you pay up another $10!
Jae Suk... You're really being too cheap.
Tell me the address,
I'll go put it in the navigation.
Would you be happy to see me sadly putting
this wet and cold shirt back on?
-So just give us another $10.
-Give me a break and let's go with $20.
[Putting in the next destination
without wasting any time]
-Jae Suk...
-Let's just do $20 for it.
-I told you, I'll take care of you!
-Let's just go on with the game!
-There's nothing left for us...!
-Honest, there's nothing left for us.
[Without any other choice, paying the $30]
Thanks.  I have a $5 bill.
[Dividing up the $10
between themselves immediately]
Fine... You think I'm just going to take that?
Did you make $5 each?
-Hey...
-Doesn't it feel good now with a clean shirt?
Both of you, hand over $10 each
for the transportation fee.
-$10 each for the transportation fee.
-What?
[$10 for the transportation fee?]
If you don't, we can't go anywhere!
-Then I'll drive.
-No.  You just stay there.
[Ji Min getting frustrated]
If you don't, then we can't go.
Hurry up and give me $10 each.
-Just give me $10 each.
-What $10 are you talking about?
I'm going in reverse then.  Going in reverse!
I'm going to go back in reverse!
[He's really going in reverse...]
Ji Min, hurry up and tell them
to give me $10 each.
Let's hurry up and get going!
What are you doing right now?
[Frustrated Ji Min ultimately hands over $10]
-Are you really giving him the $10?
-Can't I just earn it back?
-Are they really far ahead of us?
-Yes.
[Find the Running Man landmark at M Maze park]
[Dong Wan supermarket is the first to arrive]
[Over the mountain, and across the ocean...
Wherever the Running Man are...]
[Arriving at M land!]
I'm really worried about this one too.
[This game is at
the largest maze park in Jeju Island]
There it is!  Dong Wan supermarket!
[Undoubtedly,
Dong Wan supermarket is open for business]
Escape the maze.  Time limit is 3 minutes.
[After the 3 minutes, you will be deducted
$5 for each additional 10 seconds]
For 3 minutes... 3 of you will go in the maze.
You have to pick either 'R1' or 'R2'...
And find the corresponding
'R' flag inside the maze
and come out the other side
where the 'R' finish flag is.
If you go in the 'R' start line and come out
the opposite 'R' finish line, you succeed.
You have to make sure
to come out within the time.
-Then 3 people go in at the same time?
-You all go in at the same time.
Then what about the remaining person?
The remaining person will go up
to the observatory over there.
That person can guide the others from
the observatory up there.
-Ah... You can guide them where to go...
-The person with the loudest voice should go.
There's no second chances with this game.
-Since the penalty comes with the timing...
-So it's all in one shot.
Until the very last person is out, the clock
is going to keep on ticking past the 3 minutes.
This is the map to the inside of the maze.
And it costs $30.
-$30?
-And this is the map with the route.
And this one costs $200.
There's even a map with the route?
We'll take one of these.
Let's get this for $30,
and get some water...
Why do you keep buying water?
Buy it with your own money!
-Buy it with your own money!
-Use your money!
-Why are you all yelling?
-You're seriously so strange!
[Frugal Red Team just buying a map for $30]
[Investment heavy White Team
is buying a walkie-talkie and the map]
I'm totally broke now.
-How much do you have?
-I don't have much.
Ji Min, don't worry.  We're your team.
We wouldn't...
-Of course.  You have to trust us.
-I was told not to trust anyone on this show.
-You can trust us.
-I was told that I can't ever trust anyone.
-But Ha Ha hasn't spent any money.
-Yeah, that's a little strange.
-Wow... That's driving me crazy.
-Especially, I was told not to trust Ha Ha.
[Purchased a walkie-talkie and a map
for $50 and $30 each]
When I took a look, you just need to keep
to the edge and you'll be able to get out.
No matter what, keep to the side.
To the outer perimeter.
[Queen Ji Min's surprising improvisation?]
First, just think about it.
This isn't going to be very easy.
[White Team's path]
[Red Team's path]
[Gary and Jong Kook up at the observatory]
Should I have given them the map?
Suk Jin!  I think we're going to win this.
Suk Jin, the White Team...
Gary brought the map up here.
But we can't figure the map out from here.
-We can't see anything from up here.
-Why did you take that up there?
I don't why either...
[Both teams off on their way]
-This way?
-No, this isn't the right way.
[Coach Kook directing his team]
-No, no, no...
-Is this the way?
[A very confusing maze]
[White Team running along the outer walls]
Wait... Wait... Stop for a minute.
-Go to the right.
-Right?  This way?
To the right.  To that break right there.
To the right... To the right!
Go around that way.  That's right.
Go that way.
Wait... Wait for a minute...
[You want us to wait?]
[Hm...]
[It's so confusing...]
[Have no idea what's what...]
-Here?
-Is it here?
It's right.  Go forward.
Just keep going forward.
Run.  Run.
[A fiery showdown?]
We're going the right way?
Is this right?
Is this the right way?
-Weren't we just here?
-Isn't this the same spot?
[Feeling as though
they're spinning around in a circle]
You're doing good.  You're doing good.
Isn't this the same spot as earlier?
-I feel like it's the same spot.
-Isn't this the same spot?
[No matter how far they go...]
[Strangely feeling like
they're going around in circles]
This is just too big.
How are we supposed to
get out within 3 minutes?
Look at the map!
Jong Kook!  Where are we supposed to go?
Look at the map and go!
-So where are we supposed to go?
-How can you tell us now to look at the map?
[Just running all over the place
within the vast maze...]
[Huh?  A tangent?]
-Hey!  Hey!
-What?
-Jae Suk!  How do we get there?
-Hey!
How do we get out there?
Wait there for a minute... Just wait...
Just go straight for now.
-Left or right?
-Go straight to the right.
[Just going where they're supposed to go
without a map]
-Straight?
-Straight?  Okay.
Just go for now.  I don't know either!
Where the heck are they right now?
Where did I tell them to go?
[Gary in a state of panic
up at the observatory]
[3 minutes are up!]
3 minutes are up already.  Hurry.
[From this point, $5 gets deducted
for every 10 seconds that passes]
-Oh!  I can see something!
-You see it?
[Giant giraffe,
the optimal player in this game?]
[Like a giraffe galloping around the prairie]
-Kwang Soo... He's like an Impala!
-He really looks like a giraffe!
-I can really see something.
-Take a good look, and don't make a mistake.
-Do you see the flag?
-Yes...
-Suk Jin, this is the right spot.
-Kwang Soo's being really useful today.
[Kwang Soo proving himself to be useful
for the first time in a long time?]
Suk Jin!  Hurry!  Come quickly!
-Did you see ours too?
-Excuse me?
-Did you see our flag?
-No, I didn't see yours.
This way... I think it's this way.
-It's blocked that way.
-This way's blocked?
-Kwang Soo, you're awesome...!
-This way... This way!
Hey!  The flag!
[Discovers the flag!]
They found their flag.
-Where?
-We found it!
-Wait...
-Kwang Soo...!
-We just need to get out now.
-Kwang Soo... You're seriously the best!
[Jumping giraffe looking for the way out]
Run!  Run!
[The White Team is still lost]
-I think they put it at a dead end.
-We can't find the flag.
-There's no flag...
-I think they put it at a dead end.
[The flag should be around here somewhere...]
Here it is, here it is!
[Did he discover it?]
[The 'R1' flag!]
Is it over there?
-Wait a second...
-Come quickly!
Come here!
[Now the 2 teams just need to
get to the finish point]
Wait.  Where are you right now?
-Jae Suk, we have to run!
-Run quickly!
4 minutes and 30 seconds!
Faster!  Faster!
[Time is gold!  For every 10 seconds,
they're deducted $5!]
[Which one of the teams will cross
the finish line first?]
-Not that way... Just keep straight!
-Keep going!
-Keep turning!
-Where is it?
Stop talking and keep going!
[The 2 teams at neck and neck]
[Measuring their time by the last person
to make it out of the maze]
Where's the 'R2' flag?  Here it is!
[Red Team arrives at the finish line!]
[The white team
also arrives at the finish line]
Who wins?
[Fighting over who the winner is]
Pil-Chok-Cross!
-There was a 2 second difference.
-Seriously?  2 seconds?!
[The judging was made
from the 2 second difference]
[Just which one of the teams was first?]
The Red Team...
[Reading the video feed to judge fairly]
[The first for all 3 members to cross]
[The rest of the White Team members
crosses 2 seconds later]
Red Team-5 minutes and 49 seconds.
And the White Team-5 minutes 51 seconds.
[The Red Team wins with a nick of time]
Since it was $5 for every 10 seconds,
it's $80 for the Red Team.
And $85 for the White Team.
That team is very lucky.
What a waste...
-But things can turn over again.
-Don't worry about it.
-Fighting!  Fighting!
-Let's finish this.
[Find the Running Man landmark
at Jeju black pork restaurant]
I can do very well at this.
Ji Min says she likes to eat.
Hello.
This place looks delicious.
I wonder what this is going to be about now.
-The last time we ate like this...
-Just order whatever you want and eat.
-We just eat?
-We have to pay for it, right?
[Being suspicious is their nature]
Remember having to pay for it all
when Ji Sung was on the show awhile ago?
-Anyways...
-We're spending the money anyways...
No matter what, we can't follow
this team with money anyways.
Let's just eat whatever!
The grilled pork belly.  Let's have that
with the kimchi stew.
We'll order the pork belly.
We'll do the pork belly too
with the kimchi stew.
We'll do 4 orders of the pork belly,
1 kimchi stew and 1 kimchi casserole.
-Please give us 4 bowls of rice.
-We'll take 4 bowls of rice too.
It's just one casserole, right?
This table isn't ordering one?
-Not them.  We don't know these people.
-They're not with us.  They're separate.
Ma'am!
Gwon Yeol...!
[The VJ's are starting their meals too]
Why are you guys sitting down
all of a sudden?
-Just order a little bit.
-Do you have just plain white rice for them?
[Will they have to pay for their tab too
like the last time?]
-Ki Jin... The kimchi stew here is famous.
-Yes?
[Recommending a simple and cheap kimchi stew?]
Please give us each 4 orders of the beef ribs.
[What?  Beef ribs?!]
-Did you just order beef ribs?
-What's with 4 orders of beef ribs?
[The army of VJ's that can inhale
a table full of food]
When we're only eating pork belly...
Don't you think that you're being too much?
Can't you see us eating just the pork belly?
I'm sure there's something today.
It can't be the same as the last time.
[Just what will it be?]
How did you make the kimchi stew
so delicious?
-Please enjoy your meal...!
-Everyone, enjoy!
[The pork belly is sizzling away...]
-This is so delicious!
-Should we turn the heat down a bit?
-How can this be so good?
-I love this!
[These are the delicacies to be
enjoyed on a vacation]
I was told to be suspicious
even when I'm eating...
[The one who's warning her correctly...
Just who are you...?]
-This is seriously so delicious!
-How's the beef?
It's very tender.
Ki Jin... Eat as much as
the person sitting next to you.
[Hardworking VJ's are enjoying
their delicious meal too...]
Sitting down and eating like this...
It really does feel like we're on vacation.
-Doesn't it feel like we're on a group trip?
-I know.
-Do you want some beef too?
-Just eat what we have here, Suk Jin.
You have a very peaceful household there.
But he's not allowing you to order any beef.
[No thanks to the harsh son,
father Impala can't eat any beef]
This pork is really delicious!
[Completion of the meal]
-Did you enjoy your meal?
-Yes!
It was really delicious!
Here are the bills for your meals.
The bill for Song Ji Hyo's team is $88.
Han Ji Min's team is also $88.
As for the VJ's meals...
I'm sure that Gwon Yeol ate quite a bit.
-That has nothing to do with this game.
-What?  Really?!
[A test of love for their VJ's?]
I was nervous for nothing then!
See?  I told you to order expensive stuff!
Eat as much as you want!
-You have to pay for your meals now.
-Yes.
-How do we pay for it?
-It's a very simple game.
Out of the 8 wallets that you all have...
Whose ever the owner picks will have to
pay for both teams meals with their money.
[The person picked has to pay for
both the tabs!]
-The total bill is $160...
-The total tab is $176.
What happens if he doesn't
have that much in his wallet?
Then she'll have to pick again.
We're good!  We're going to be okay!
-No, that's not it... It's after yours is in...
-After all your money is spent...
[It means that if you're short,
then another person is chosen to chip in]
And look at him thinking that
he was going to get away from not paying.
-It's after you put in all your money first.
-Everyone put your wallets on here.
[They're about to lose all their vacation
allowance they worked so hard to keep]
-Everyone... Don't save your money.
Just spend it all.
[Putting in his utmost care
to mix it up thoroughly...]
This makes no sense...
Ma'am... Ma'am...
[The lady to decide their fate enters]
-It was really delicious!
-It nearly brought tears to my eyes.
-Please...!
-Thank you very much.
[Completes choosing the wallet]
-This is really light.
-It's light?
-I think it's one of their wallets.
-He says it's light.
[It looks like it belongs to someone
who spent a lot of their money already?]
That's...mine, I think...
Whose is it?
-Whose is it?
-Yoo Jae Suk!
[Paying the meal tab in full]
But you don't have a lot of money.
But how...?
Yoo Jae Suk, you have $70.
[His reaming $70 goes towards the meal tab]
Thanks for the meal.
Now there's $106 left to pay.
This is the most nervous
I've ever seen Jae Suk.
-Be comfortable, and don't look too hard...
-Just go with your feelings... Your instinct.
Just grab whatever your gut tells you to.
That's right!
[If it's thin,
it probably belongs to the White Team?]
Ma'am... I think you picked a good one again.
You can't feel it around like that.
You're not supposed to do that.
[Just who could it be this time?]
[Gary is chosen!]
-Why are you so broke?
-Do I look like I'd have money?
[After wiping Gary out clean too,
the tab is now all paid up]
Then I guess I'm the head of this team now.
-We can no longer...
-Thanks for the hard work.
[Rich Ha Ha handing out
$1 to those less fortunate]
Thanks for your hard work too.
He takes it too...!
[Find the Running Man landmark at
the aquarium at Seogwi City]
[Inputting it into the navigation right away]
I found this stuck up here.
Right now... Gary and I have no money.
-This is what you call free traveling.
-We will not become one with the nature.
How could that have happened?
[Vacation allowance left]
[The final battleground for vacation funds-
Jeju A-Aquarium!]
Walk with strength.  With strength.
Had we known it was going to be like this,
should we have spent some of the money?
[What is the mission here?]
[Tear off the opposing team's name tag.
Only those left alive can take the money]
[If your name tag is ripped off,
then you forfeit your money]
[And find the hidden bonus card]
If your name tag is ripped off,
then you forfeit your money
-And find the hidden bonus card.
-Huh?  What's the bonus card?
There are bonus cards hidden
in various different places.
The bonus card can change the amount
of the money you have...
-Then it can double it...
-Or wipe it out or multiply it?
It can become advantageous
or disadvantageous to you.
So no matter what,
it's tearing off the name tag.
What do we do about Jong Kook?
-That Kim Jong Kook...
-Can't you take Jong Kook out of these things?
I seriously feel like I'm going to go crazy.
-Let's go around together.
-Okay.
[Mr. Capable and Ace going around together?]
[Not really caring what happens
to the Easy Brothers...]
-What about us?
-Don't abandon us...!
To be honest... If Ji Min were to show up,
you know that I won't be able to do anything.
Jong Kook, I can grab Ji Min by her hair.
Really?
I'll pull Ji Min's name tag off.
He can tear it off
whether it's a woman or a star.
[Easy Brothers filled with motivation today]
[Will things go as well as they think?]
[Under the sea world that's
happening in right front of their eyes]
This is just an aquarium...
[This is an undersea paradise]
That's so amazing!
Look at this one.  Look at him go through.
Did you see that?
-This is seriously no joke.
This is no joke!
-What is this?
-That looks good.
[That's not something you say
at an aquarium...]
It's me... Me!
[Adorable and sweet penguins
languidly swimming about]
-But I don't see any walruses...
-Oh my goodness!
I was just saying that there aren't
any walruses around, and there it is!
Look at it when it's going up.
He looks like a well-built brother of ours.
-Wow... That's so fascinating.
-See?  It looks human almost!
[Almost human like in form?
Like a well-built older brother of theirs!]
He's just a well-built brother of ours!
This is just so cool...
[Forgetting the mission for a moment...]
[Losing themselves to the welcome
given by their sea creature friends]
[This time coming to see a walrus show]
Please allow us to say hello.
This is Balryah, the walrus.
Didn't we see that earlier?
Balryah is a sweet 7 year old female.
She says she has a wish...
Her wish is to find herself
a boyfriend this year.
-Here's Kwang Soo over here!
-What about Kwang Soo?
[Recommending Giraffe Kwang Soo
as her boyfriend]
What do you think
is your attractive trait for the men?
What?  You say you're sexy?
Just what about you is sexy?
-No way!
-Sexy...!
-Any volunteers out there?
-Yes.
Why don't you go out there since
you've been showing an interest?
Kwang Soo... Let Kwang Soo go.
[Kwang Soo going out to meet the walrus]
Would you like to kiss her?
Kiss her!  Kiss her!
Did you brush your teeth this morning?
How can a girl not do that?
Then let's at least gargle first.
[Gargling before the kiss]
Kiss...
Kiss.
[Rejected]
[Giraffe Kwang Soo
getting rejected by the walrus]
[Balryah...]
[You're not my style]
[Putting his hurt aside,
trying for another kiss]
How do you feel after the kiss?
[Summer 2012...
Kwang Soo's girlfriend is a walrus]
Don't you think that we're too
into sightseeing right now?
[Slowly starting to
search for the bonus cards]
[Did Mr. Capable find something?]
Hey, look across the water...
Don't they look like they're in the water?
[Pil-chok-cross]
[Looking at them this way makes them
seem like they're in the water]
-Seriously... We can just do this.
-I can really do it.
-You're actually pretty strong, aren't you?
-I've been working out lately.
I'll tear Han Ji Min's off.
I don't think anyone can tear Ji Min's off.
So I'll tear hers off.
I'll get Ji Hyo then...
[Who are you saying you're going to tear off
when you're so clumsy like that...]
[Anyways, the Easy Brothers are being
greedy for the win today!]
Even though we're all on the same team now,
there can only be one winner.
To be honest, we have to tear
Jong Kook's off when we get the chance.
[For now,
searching for the bonus cards first!]
Hey, that's quick!
What is it?
Did you find something?
[Kwang Soo discovers a bonus card!]
Pil-Chok-Cross!
Quiet... Be quiet.
It's times 2!
[Kwang Soo's amount- $126 X 2=$252]
You'll be in danger
if people find out about this.
This is actually pretty dangerous right now.
Someone's coming.
-Let's go.
-They'll be suspicious if we just go.
I think that's why I make things obvious.
-What's that?
-Suk Jin...
What?
Why did they two of you shout out
pil-chok with such fervor?
Huh?
-Why did you shout it out like that?
-We just do it no for reason a lot...
-Suk Jin...
Just as I mentioned earlier...
Amongst ourselves...
You have to think that we're a team...
We're all the same color.  Of course!
-Just think about what we've done today...
-I think the card is somewhere around here.
Somewhere around here...
[Ace Ji Hyo discovers a bonus card!]
What is it?
[Lee Kwang Soo, times 2.
Lee Kwang Soo, times 2]
[He purposely didn't say anything
to hide the fact that he found a card...]
[Who knew that it'd be broadcast...
I'm dead now...]
[Ji Hyo's amount- $137 X 0=$0]
I think the other team found something and
it was 'Lee Kwang Soo times 2'!
Ah... I guess there are cards like that too!
[Able to survive thanks to
Mr. Capable's wrong deduction]
I think the other team found something,
and mine got multiplied by two!
-So that's what happened...
-There are such things...!
[Anyways, hiding it from Mr. Capable
hasn't been detected]
-Then you have the most money right now.
-Don't be so happy.  You're not most targeted.
[Easy brothers acting as if
they're just finding this out themselves]
But how can you be announcing stuff like this?
[For now... I survived...]
[Haroro and Yoo-ruce Willis
searching for the cards too]
[Huh?  Dong Wan supermarket is here too?]
[Little stuffed toys with name tags
attached at the store?]
-Welcome.
-Hi.  What's this?
It's name tags that's worth someone's life.
How much is it?
-Here's the price.
-$100?
Then I'm going to buy one.
-You can only buy one.
-Yes.
-I only have a dollar...
-Then go earn some money.
-Think about it!
-What?
You need to do this after you find a card
that says times 2 or something...
[Jae Suk telling Ha Ha to wait until he finds
a bonus card to double his money first.]
No, that won't happen...
If I get 'x 0' card, then I'm going to lose
all my money, and not be able to buy this.
-There are 'x 2'...
-I'll just tear it off anyways.
[Jae Suk wanting Ha Ha to double his money
first so that he can buy one for him too]
-How much do you have?
-$1...
-You gave me $100.
-Yes.
Seriously... This is bad for my pride.
[Feeling the shame from watching Ha Ha buy
something expensive in front of him]
[Bitter]
[Ha Ha completes adding another life
for himself for $100]
Should we tear Kwang Soo's name tag off?
Jae Suk, let's hide here.
-Let's oust Kwang Soo.
-But Kwang Soo isn't alone, he's with others.
[All the members of the Red Team
making their way over]
These are the type of places
where we usually hide.
Are you selling something?
[The Red Team also discovers
Dong Wan's supermarket]
-You can buy an extra life here.
-An extra life?
-How much is it?
-It's $100.
Buy one.
-Not many people know that it's here.
-I have a $1 left.
[Easy Brothers each purchase
an extra life for themselves]
[Since buying an extra life isn't being
announced, it is to remain their secret]
Even Ji Hyo and Jong Kook came with him.
-What's this?
-They're selling an extra life here.
-You can buy an extra life here.
-What did you say?
-You can buy only one.
-I already bought one.
[Easy Brothers' with their extra life
are feeling more at ease]
I'm going to buy one too...
The reason for it is...
You have another one.
He scared me...!
Someone who doesn't even have any money...!
Why are you being jealous of someone who has
money just because you don't have any?
[It's been exactly 30 seconds since
he bought the extra life...]
Give me back my $100!
I said, give me back my $100!
[Losing out on
precious $100 within 30 seconds]
What are you doing?!
I feel like I just dropped an ice cream cone
right after I bought it!
-Kwang Soo...!  I'm sorry.
-Wait...!
[It's not as though he can even
buy an extra life either...]
[The giraffe's anger
that won't dissipate easily]
[But just then!]
[Mr. Capable Jong Kook also completes
purchasing himself an extra life]
Kwang Soo... At least you have a
lot of money. I'm sorry.
Do you have $30 I can borrow?
Do you seriously want to get slapped?
Let's go.  I think I need to get out of here.
-Are you just leaving after what you did?
-What else can I do?  You're still alive.
How could you have wasted something that
you just bought for a $100?
[About to collapse]
The big problem is, Jong Kook has 2 name tags.
-What if we tear them off at once together?
-I don't know if that'll work.
As long as he has 2 name tags,
we have to ask the other team for help.
[Easy Brothers not considering whose team
they're on in order to win it]
But no matter what...
No matter what, I'm with our team to the end.
[Getting extremely flustered with
Mr. Capable close by]
No matter what, I'm with our team to the end.
[Did he hear our conversation by any chance?]
Why are you saying that all of a sudden?
What were you just saying?
-What were you talking about over here?
-I was talking about my name tag...
[Luckily, Mr. Capable didn't seem to have
heard their plans to revolt against him]
He's totally unstoppable now...
He has 2 name tags.
Suk Jin...
Let the 3 of us take this to the end.
[Just what will happen with
the Easy Brothers' plan to revolt?]
I feel like there's one in here...
-Gary!
-What?  What?
[Ji Min discovers a bonus card]
[Just what will the bonus card say?]
[Ji Min's amount-$95 x 3= $285]
[Rule: But be aware!]
[If you're ousted, you forfeit your money]
That's so awesome...
Suk Jin...
[Kwang Soo discovers Ji Min]
[Han Ji Min times 3.  Han Ji Min times 3]
-I just saw Ji Min and Gary running by.
-Han Ji Min times 3?
[If they oust Ji Min, it's big money for them]
Han Ji Min times 3.
-Where?
-Come this way, Jong Kook.
[Red chase team, closing in on her]
Since we don't know what'll happen,
go to the back.
Go back there.
[In order to create a diversion,
Gary bravely steps outside]
-This is locked!
-Where?
-I bet they're in here.
-They have to be in there.
-I think someone's holding the knob.
-Gary's out here.
[Gary pretending not to notice anything,
and coming out to disperse the group]
-Really?  Is there something in there?
-You're being serious?
[Holding tightly with her hands]
It's not locked.
She's really strong, Jong Kook!
Ji Min could get hurt if we bust the door
because she's light enough to get pulled.
-Why is she so strong?
-The door's not locked!
[Strong Queen Ji Min holding on
with the strength of her hands]
I told you, no one's in there.
Ji Min, we won't tear off your tag.
Let us just see your face.
-We'll just take a look at you.
-Would you like to come out for a moment then?
[A useless body guard]
-Just come out for a moment so we can see you.
-How are you so strong for a girl?
-How could she have held onto that by herself?
-Were you holding onto the doorknob?
-Ji Min... How are your hands so strong?
-Since you saw my face, we're all set.
[Visiting hours are over]
-We have to talk a little too!
-This is all you get.
-Let's get out of here for now.
-Let's go.
-Be careful of Gary.
-I have to talk to Ji Min for a minute.
Ji Min... Ji Min..
I can't open the door...
Ji Min, it's me.  Can you open the door?
Ji Min... I can't open it
because my nails are too short.
Ji Min... It's me.  Open the door.
Do you not want to... I got it.
Don't you want to see me?
She's not here?
[His client has disappeared!]
She's not here!
Where did she go?
I don't think they detected anything, right?
Did they see me?
[Abandoning a useless bodyguard,
and fleeing on her own]
[Flustered]
Where did she go?
She's going around on her own without me?
-Jong Kook!  Ji Min's gone!
-Who's that?
-She's gone?
-She's disappeared!
[What kind of a bodyguard says that...?]
She's disappeared!
Where the heck did she go?
[Ji Min, with the largest vacation allowance]
[Will she be able to protect it to the end?]
[On the other hand...]
[The Red Team continuing to search for Ji Min]
[Huh?  Kwang Soo seems to have
seen someone...?]
[Discovers Haroro walking around by himself]
[Being surrounded immediately]
I couldn't believe you attacked our team
when we were all standing there earlier.
-Was I the one who attacked you?
-You stood there watching Jae Suk do it.
[The sin of just standing by and laughing
as Jae Suk attacked Kwang Soo]
Since he has 2 name tags,
hurry up and tear one of his off.
-Hurry, hurry...
-Come on...
[Big nosed brother, a man with determination]
[One of Ha Ha's name tag is ousted!]
Even grabbing their wrists with
one of your hands...
[Haroro ousts
one of Big nosed brother's name tag]
[An eye for an eye!]
-Seriously... I'm so pissed!
-Hurry up and get him!
-You, come here!
-They should've grabbed him.
[Haroro making his escape at a leisurely pace]
[Both of the Easy Brothers have had
their extra name tags taken away]
[At this rate, ousting Jong Kook
with 2 name tags...]
-We have to gather...
-Kwang Soo, come here.
Kwang Soo, come here.
[Just then, Jae Suk is heading their way]
Jae Suk, come here...
-Hurry up and come here.
-To the left... Go to the left...!
[Being cautious in case Jong Kook shows up]
Go back a little bit more!
And don't look back!
[Why are they being so loud
about a secret meeting?]
-It's 2 against one right now...
-Putting everything aside...
Can we seriously count on you for help?
-Okay.
-Let's oust Jong Kook right now.
-He has 2 name tags, so...
-But...
-But if we make a mistake, then we're...
-Rip his name tag off and escape.
[Jae Suk takes care of one name tag,
and the other taken cared of by Easy Brothers]
We'll be right by you...
[Winning is almost impossible
without ousting Mr. Capable first]
-We have no other choice right now.
-Jong Kook is the only one with 2 name tags.
-Jong Kook has the most money too, right?
-Yes...
He has the most money, and has 2 name tags.
We're in big trouble.
What else can we do?  He's like God!
You guys stay here for now.
I'll go get some more people...
Let's do it this way then.
Bring everyone and get Jong Kook...
[Everyone attack to oust both of
Jong Kook's name tags]
[The decision to attack Mr. Capable together]
-Ha Ha!
-Jae Suk!
-I just made a deal with Kwang Soo and Suk Jin.
-What kind of a deal?
To oust Jong Kook.
You think we can do that by ourselves?
-For now... We have to try it.
-Let's do it.  Let's go right now.
-Jae Suk, is this a sure deal?
-Yeah, of course, it is.
[Just like this,
Ha Ha becomes an ally against Mr. Capable]
[On the other hand...]
Ji Min!
Where did she go?
I think they like each other.
[Totally immersed in watching the dolphins,
with the mission forgotten]
I think they like each other...!
-Anyways... We should do something.
-Let's rip Ha Ha's name tag off.
Let's get Ha Ha.
He went that way, so let's go find him.
[The rebels gathering nearby in the area]
Let's go find him and oust him first...
Let's go get him.
[Mr. Capable not having detected
anything by the others]
Even if we try, he has 2 name tags...
Since Ha Ha and Jae Suk are together...
[Their plan at a coup
that can't have any margin for error]
-Let's go turn this around.
-Okay, let's go do it.
[Mr. Capable is heading this way!]
[At this rate,
everything will go up in smoke!]
[No other choice.  In that case...!]
[Yoo-ruce Willis purposely
tempting Mr. Capable!]
-Get him!
If we make a mistake
and Jong Kook attacks us...
Jae Suk's running away...!
[Out of confusion, Easy Brother's follows!]
-Jong Kook saw us!
-Hurry up and run!
[A total chaos]
Why?  What?  What's going on?
Why are you running away?
You have to catch them, not run with them!
[Hiding for now to wait
for the next opportunity]
-Why is he running away with them?
-I don't know.
[Have to avoid a confrontation at all cost]
[Yoo-ruce Willis working together
with the 2 kids]
Jae Suk... Let's do a surprise attack on him.
-He's coming... He's coming.
-Why are you backing off?
Just why are you running away?
[The rebels being afraid of Mr. Capable]
If you run,
he's going to run after us even more.
[Finally discovers Ji Min
that he's been looking for]
[She hasn't been seen for awhile...
What has she been doing?]
Jae Suk!
Don't shout so loudly!
[Easy Brothers starting to bicker again]
We're in a tunnel right now.
Everything echoes in here!
-At this rate, we can get ousted first.
-We can get taken out.
Jae Suk!
Hey!  Jong Kook can hear you!
-You seriously are...
-This is my whispering voice.
[Mr. Capable and Ace being more cautious]
[The coalition against Mr. Capable is waiting
to ambush him around the corner]
[Mr. Capable and Ace in danger!]
Wow... You really scared me.
I thought you guys were part of the wall.
[White Team moving in
before the Easy Brothers]
Now there's a definite cause for me to attack.
Are you trying to oust me right now?
They're for sure trying to oust me right now.
[A nerve wracking confrontation]
Hurry up and do something.
[Giving up]
Let's go.
[Even though there are 3 of them,
it's too hard against Mr. Capable and Ace]
Come on.  I can take you guys on.
I think I can oust at least 2 of you.
-Come on...
-That's not what we were trying to do.
[It looked as though they were
calmly backing away...]
[Full of fear]
[Filled with resolve and speed
when they're running away]
Why are we such cowards...?
-Let's try the surprise attack one more time.
-Let's do it here.
[What's going to change
with another surprise attack?]
It was no joke with the 3 of them trying to
spring a surprise attack on me just now.
We just need to capture
and oust them right now.  Let's go.
-They went that way?
-Yeah.
Coming... He's coming.
There... They're over there.
They're hiding over there.
They saw us.
-They saw all four of us?
-Yeah, they saw all of us.
Be careful... Be careful.
[Even though it looks as though Easy Brothers
are bravely approaching Mr. Capable...]
[But the truth is...]
[They've gone to confer...]
Is Jong Kook over there?
[All the rebels are gathered here!]
Jong Kook... I can't see them!
-Are you by yourself?
-The guys are behind me.
We have to quickly oust Jong Kook
and Ji Hyo first.
[Just then!]
[Mr. Capable approaches!]
Hey!  Hey!
[Mr. Capable Jong Kook!]
[An ambush from behind for a take down!]
[But just then...!]
[Mr. Capable falls to the ground!]
[A total chaos]
Hurry up and tear it off!
[Jae Suk ousts one of Jong Kook's name tag!]
[Yoo-ruce Willis finally does it!]
[But just then!]
[Ace Ji Hyo, gets rid of Jae Suk's name tag!]
[What?  Did Jae Suk also get
Jong Kook's second name tag?]
What are you doing right now? Hurry.
Ji Hyo ripped yours off first.
[Without a choice, the name tag goes back on]
No...
[Who was that??]
No, his was off first.
[As soon as it's put back on, Kwang Soo...]
[The plans to revolt succeeds!]
-Jong Kook... We ousted Jong Kook.
-Pil-Chok-Cross!
[A miracle]
I ripped it off... I did it.
Is this the path to jail?
Help me so I don't have to face Jong Kook.
I'm so nervous right now.
[Okay... Kwang Soo...]
[If the tiger disappears from the forest...]
[All the animals...]
[Appears thinking...]
[Thinking that they're the new king]
[Therefore...]
[One must stay cautious]
[A time now to determine the new king
through a true battle]
[Giraffe Kwang Soo discovers Haroro,
and starts to attack!]
Suk Jin!
[With 3 of them attacking Ha Ha...]
[Gary and Ji Min attack from behind!]
[There's no escape!
There's no concession in this fight!]
[Ji Min gets Big-nosed brother on his own]
[And here... Ji Hyo has Ha Ha...]
[And Gary has Ji Hyo...!]
[A total entangled situation!]
[Gary and Ji Hyo's name tags
ousted in one shot]
[An action without concession that
happened in the blink of an eye]
[Song Ji Hyo out.  Gary out]
[White Team's Ha Ha and Ji Min vs.
Red Team's Easy Brothers]
Ji Min...
Give me your money and go.
[Greedy for the win.
Thinking about money even in this situation]
Wait... Let's rest for 5 minutes.
[Rest, my butt.  Attacking immediately!]
[Ha Ha marks Big-nosed brother as his prey!]
[Ji Min attacks Giraffe Kwang Soo]
Come here, come here!  Tear his off!
[Ha Ha and Ji Min gathering in defense]
Hurry up and tear his off!
[A neck and neck battle without
any indication of the outcome!]
[Ji Min showing off her aggressive side]
[Kwang Soo has his hand on Ha Ha's name tag!]
[Kwang Soo succeeds in getting rid
of ha Ha's name tag!]
[Now Ji Min's the only one left!]
You're bad!  Get away from me!
I'm just a girl...!
[Suk Jin grabs Ji Min's name tag...!]
[Big-nosed brother gets rid of
Ji Min's name tag!]
[And he succeeds in saving his own name tag!]
You're so mean!
You're seriously so bad!
-I got Ha Ha!
-You got him?
I got it... I got it!
-Really?
-We won.
You really are so bad!
Kwang Soo...
It wasn't right for you to do that.
Seriously... I can't even...
Let me tear it off too
since I came on the show.
We won!!
[What?!  Ji Min has another name tag?!]
What the heck?
I can't believe it!
How could that plan have worked?
[Totally confused...]
-What the... She has another name tag!
-We won!
[Ah... In that case!]
[While she had disappeared for awhile
after having escaped...]
-What is this?
-I'm selling name tags.
If you buy your own name tag,
then you get an extra life.
[She purchased an extra life
without the other team knowing!]
-You didn't tear off both the tags?
-You said you tore hers off.
I tore one off,
but I thought you said you got everything else.
You were shouting at me that you got her!
-'I got it, I got it!'
-See?  I did get it!
Then what did it mean
when you said you got it?
If you got it, then why is there another one?
If I said, 'I got it, I got it',
does it mean that I tore 2 off?
Who says such a thing exists?
[The endless fight]
What the heck is this?
[This is how they usually are...]
I thought we ousted everyone,
because he said we got everything.
And... I was celebrating that we won...
Wow... She's something else.
'Let me try tearing it off too!'
She started tearing off the tags
because she said she's never torn it off
and come to find out,
she has another name tag.
Seriously?!  Seriously?!
[Even her own teammates
didn't know her surprise plan]
[Her true victory]
Today's winner is the White Team.
However, only Han Ji Min gets the money.
-You can take the name tag.
-Yes, thank you.
[Han Ji Min's winnings has been
donated to help out the needy]
You should treat us out.
How can you ask her to treat you
after tearing off her name tag?
I can't believe that she fooled us.
Kwang Soo... I was in jail with Jong Kook...
Jong Kook's pretty mad right now.
Kwang Soo... Kwang Soo...
I really loved you and was really grateful...
-Really?
-Why?
I think the next time I rip off your name tag,
I'm going to tear it off like a mosaic.
Kwang Soo, do you know what that means?
At first I didn't understand it,
then I thought I was going to die of fear.
[Next week's preview]
What is this?
[A refreshing Jeju Oceanside...]
[The most romantic proposal in the world]
[One man's secret mission for this woman]
Sincerely, your true love.
[The man of mystery that leaves after
leaving that piece of paper...]
[Find your true love!]
[Subtle psychological game by the fake loves
to get their true love]
[Find the hidden words to
find your true love!]
[A shocking ending that surrounds
the identity of true love!]
[On the next Running Man...
Find your true love]