Secret Agents... have you been well?
Aim!
[Last week's 007 Water Sniper]
He's getting away! Stop right there!
[All the Agents everywhere, gather around.]
[Unbelievable testing to pick
the ultimate Secret Agent.]
[Determine who the ultimate Secret Agent
is through a water gun fight.]
[To the ultimate Secret Agent,
a license to oust will be given.]
[The ultimate victory for
the Agent test goes to Team Seung Gi.]
Good work, everyone.
To the first and second placed team
a smart PC and a smart phone which will come
in handy for your mission will be given.
And unfortunately,
to the team that came in last
only a cell phone will be given out.
Don't despair and work harder to
show me what you're capable of tomorrow.
What are we supposed to use this PC for?
Yes, even if Jae Suk has it,
he doesn't know how to use it.
How would I be able to use this?
That's a relief, because I
wouldn't know how to use it either.
Wait right there.
Did you know that the License to Oust is
given out to the individual
who's shown me their skills
without regards to how their team placed?
We didn't know that.
I've kept a close eye on how
all of you carried out your mission today
and have been grading
your skills individually.
The who one qualified
for the License to Oust...
[Qualifier for License to Oust is...]
At exactly 9 a.m. tomorrow morning...
[Will be notified on their cell phone
tomorrow morning.]
[The next day]
[8:55 a.m.]
[Heading out to work with the case which was
given out to him containing useful gadgets.]
I see that you're hard at work
already this morning.
[Working on his fitness early
in the morning...]
[Each waiting for their phone call from M.]
Yesterday seriously was...
the first time since my middle school days
that I've fought so hard at
winning in a water gun fight game.
I had so much fun from playing
so hard yesterday
that I passed out as soon as
I got home.
There's one minute left.
I know that they're really prompt.
But what if I don't get the call?
It's finally come...
Hello?
[Everyone receives their cellphone call...]
I'm not even sure how to answer this.
Why can't I answer the phone?
Ah, I have to slide it open.
Hello?
Everyone worked very hard to
receive their training.
Good morning, M.
A License to Oust has been
issued to you.
[At last... License to Oust has
been issued!]
[Also everyone is granted their
individual code name.]
- Your code name is 007.
- Okay.
[007 is Lee Seung Gi]
You cannot reveal your
code name to anyone.
I will give out a mission to you since
you've become an official Secret Agent.]
[Today's mission]
I will give out a mission to you
since you're now an official Secret Agent.]
I've been informed that someone is trying
to blow up the gold vault in Prism Tower
in their effort to dominate
the worldwide gold industry.
[With intention to dominate
the gold market in the nation...]
[Gold vault in Prism Tower is being targeted!]
Go to the determined meeting place to
secure the information needed
and stop the bomb at Prism Tower
from exploding by two o'clock this afternoon.
I understand. Don't you
know that I'm Yoo-ames Bond?
You cannot reveal your
identity to anyone.
I understand.
I'll keep my identity hidden.
Now even the national gold market
is being protected by Running Man.
[Huh? A delivery?]
Can I open it?
[A package is delivered to
each of the Secret Agents.]
- Is it just a delivery?
- Yes.
Don't lie to me!
Tell me the truth!
It really is just a delivery.
I'm sorry.
[An immediate apology]
[He's completely immersed in
playing his Secret Agent role...]
[Agent items are given out to
each individual agents.]
Why is this so light?
Why is the watch... why is it so light?
What is this 30,000 won for?
It's your money for your activities.
Don't you think it's too little for that?
I'm a Secret Agent.
[To remain competitive,
must be frugal with your money...]
Shoes...
Even at a first glance here...
I really like my costume.
This is perfect for our jobs.
A notepad to jot down notes.
There's even a map in here.
Then... shall we get started?
Let's go!
No one.. no one can see this!
[A little while later...]
[Transforming into a Secret Agent]
[Addicted to being a Secret Agent]
After gathering your information
by going to a location I direct you to
stop the bomb from exploding at
Prism Tower by Two o'clock this afternoon.
Let's go to Sang Ahm.
That's number one on my list.
Since I'm 001... hello.
I'm Agent 001.
Hello.
I think I'm going to go
to the nearest place first.
Seogyo... I'm going to head over
to Seogyo.
When I'm caught in a quandary,
always head to the Chinese restaurant.
I'm going to head over to
the Chinese restaurant first.
I bet everyone is going to choose either the
Chinese restaurant or the loach soup place?
Since I'm sure they'll all be hungry.
However I'm... not going to do that.
I'm... going to head over to
the steps in Hongdae.
[Agent Gary's selection is
the steps in Hongdae.]
[A loud take-off ceremony]
The person walking behind me...
is my ally.
Have you been well?
I hope that you're being diligent
with your secret activities.
There's a taxi over there.
Hello, Sir.
Welcome.
- Where can I take you?
- To the market in Mangwon.
- Have you been well?
- Yes.
- It's really been a long time.
He's a Secret Agent who used to
work with me in the past.
- Senior, do you remember?
- Yes, I remember.
Do you remember what happened
in Russia?
[During the special op in Russia where his
life and death hung on balance everyday.]
[And this is the person who
saved his life?]
- Thank you for saving my life.
- It's all in a day's work.
[His sense is fitting of a
Special Op Agent.]
I never realized how difficult it was
to be talking to the camera by myself.
I thought I'd be good at talking to myself.
[A rather lonely life of Secret Agents.]
It's a really nice day to be a Secret Agent.
The weather was just like this
on that day too.
Whenever I think back to that day...
[Agent Giraffe whose specialty is
talking to himself.]
And my Father... Father?
I miss you.
My Grandfather was an Agent too.
[He sure talks a lot...]
[Special Code name, 007 Seung Gi]
I'm a  Secret Agent...
and I've been selected to be a spy
amongst the rest of the agents.
Hello?
Your code name is 007.
And you seem to be the most skilled and
talented out of all the other agents.
That's why you've been chosen
as the best agent of all the agents
and have been given the honor of being
given the code name, 007.
You will be given top secret information
only you will be privy to.
The enemy that I've told you about
is actually one of the other agents.
[An enemy amongst the agents?]
Remain natural and carry out the mission
by working with the other agents
and you must find out who the enemy
is and oust that enemy.
[Don't trust anyone...]
[Just who could the enemy be?]
You can stop right here.
Yes, thank you.
Thank you.
[Agent Jong Kook arrives in Sang Ahm.]
[There's another agent here already?]
Go to the location and meet
another agent who is your informant.
If you go to the end of this road,
you can meet your informant!
[If he makes it safely
to the end of this road...]
[Information which will aid him in
today's mission can be found!]
Thank you.
What are you doing here?
[Agent Jae Suk also arrives]
- Why are you wearing sunglasses?
- What's with the hat?
- What are you, the Terminator?
- What's with your hat?
- Can't you tell?
- Why is an agent wearing a hat?
- Then why are you wearing sunglasses?
- Agents wear sunglasses.
Seriously... what the heck?
What time is it?
[Each showing off their
secret agent watch.]
Where are you going?
- I just stopped by for something.
- Stopped by where?
I'm just stopping by here for a minute.
- Why?
- Why are you asking?
I had some business here.
Go about your business then.
Where is he going?
[Rushing to get his information!]
This is the same intersection where we had
the water gun fight with MBLAQ previously.
I'm 001.
Thank you for all your hard work.
I see that your hands are really chapped.
I think you need some lotion on your hands.
[If you go to the end of this road,
you'll be able to meet your informant!]
So Jong Kook's already seen this.
Thank you and good luck.
Kim Jong Kook...
[Upping his speed with Jae Suk
soon to be following him.]
Before Yoo Jae Suk catches up to me...
[Attack of the ladies!]
[That's right... it's not a
road to get through so easily...]
[Grabbing his face from the joy
of seeing him.]
What is this?
- Where are you going?
- Why are you going back?
- What? I have something to take care of...
- Why are you leaving?
- Wait... where are you going?
- I have to do something...
[The truth of the streets that he's been
made aware of thanks to Agent Kkuk.]
- How do I get there?
- You can go this way.
- Down that way?
- Yes.
[Only way is to go through the street...]
Why do you keep following me around?
When the ladies have their hands on him,
I'll use that moment to sneak through.
I have a feeling... he'll take the moment
to sneak by when I'm caught.
I'm going to run by them like the wind.
Look at him up there...
Look at the way he's walking.
Even the way he walks...
[Nearing where the ladies are
lying in wait.]
Wait, wait...
[I'm to get to the end of this
street, right?]
I think Jae Suk...
[Agent Jae Suk making a move]
[But ultimately...]
[Jae Suk allowing his face to
be grabbed.]
Kim Jong Kook, Kim Jong Kook!
Mother, Kim Jong Kook!
[Using the moment to run by
like the wind!]
But I don't know what else
could be up there.
[Second obstacle:
Men dressed in athletic gear!]
[Agent Kkuk caught with nowhere to run.]
Mother, Kim Jong Kook...
[My road... will I able to get through it?]
Thank you. Have a great day.
[Agent Blank Ji arriving at the market.]
There it is, there it is!
Hello.
I made it.
[A mission card given out to agents.]
Find the seven agents hidden around
here and put together the words
to gain your information needed.
The secret code is...
[Approach the informant by
using the secret code.]
[Agent Blank Ji entering the market.]
By any chance...
[Could this person be the informant?]
I'm sorry.
Ma'am, by any chance...
- Have a great day.
- Can I shake your hand?
A hand shake? Sure, thank you.
[Agent Big-nose arriving at the market.]
Find the seven agents hidden around
here and put together the words
to gain the information needed.
[Having turned into a completely
different secret code...]
[Spouting out a different code as soon
as he approaches anyone.]
[This doesn't sound right...]
Ma'am, by any chance...
[An informant has been found!]
Thank you!
[The first letter found is 'Da'?]
Have a great day!
[Yeon Hee Dong in Seoul]
[007 arriving at the Chinese Restaurant]
[Cards... and a mysterious man?]
Hello.
[Why is PD Myuk here?]
Remove your case.
[Beat your informant! Competition
event is a card matching game!]
There are 10 pairs of cards here.
If you win this game against me
by gathering the most cards
you'll gain your hint.
However one pair in this bunch,
is a pair that shouldn't come up...
[Still groggy from being early
in the morning.]
There's a pair that shouldn't come up.
If that pair comes up, the
opportunity will go to that other person.
[That pair will not be permissible.]
You look like you've aged a lot
since yesterday.
I think that water gun fight aged you.
You're not very good at this.
It's because I haven't
played this game very much.
If I catch you trying to trick me...
I'm better than that.
Paper, rock, scissors!
- It's just a single round?
- I'm going first.
[PD Myuk goes first]
If this person come up,
then your turn is skipped.
[Ah... the hunter!]
Kang Woo Sung?
That's Kang Woo Sung.
Oh! It's Choi Min Soo!
Song Ji Hyo...
Son Yae Jin.
Suzy, Moon Geun Young.
Moon Geun Young, Moon Geun Young!
[007 Seung Gi succeeds in
matching his first pair!]
Son Yae Jin.
[PD Myuk succeeds in getting a pair.]
Yoon Ah...
Shin Se Kyung.
I think I'm going to win this game.
Shin Se Kyung, Shin Se Kyung.
[PD Myuk with two pairs!]
Song Ji Hyo, Song Ji Hyo!
It's not over yet!
It's not over yet...
Ha Ji Won, Go Ah Ra.
Suzy?
I know I saw it...
[Where was it...]
[We definitely saw it earlier...]
[An important match!
Will he remember?]
Suzy!
- I see that you're nervous.
- Not at all.
It's because I'm hot in this thing.
Go Ah Ra... Go Ah Ra.
[007 Seung Gi succeeds in getting
four pairs!]
[Ah! The hunter!]
Min Soo!
Sulli...
Sulli!
- I think...
- You won.
[007 Seung Gi beating his informant,
PD Myuk.]
Thanks.
But there's nothing in here.
[There are a total of four hints
in the Prism Tower.]
hidden in the Prism Tower.]
[Since I have the information...]
I'll be leaving now.
Ugh, a headache.
I've got a headache all of a sudden.
Do you have any chocolates?
I think I need some sugar.
- You have your money.
- I have to use this for chocolate too?
How do I go about being the spy?
[But anyways, who is the enemy?]
Going by my instinct...
If I was the villain, I wouldn't
want to appear weak, right?
I'd try to make other look like the villain,
so that I can keep on with my attack...
[Or is that not right?]
Hello.
[Agent Shin Hye arrives at steps
of Hongdae!]
What is this?
[Information is hidden somewhere around
here! Find the information yourself!]
[There's information to be gathered on
the steps or in the nearby area.]
Somewhere around here...
is the information?
Seriously, I...
With my blood type,
I'll probably rip all these off.
Hi!
Okay... hi.
Are you a hint too?
[Could the information be hidden
on the dogs in the area?]
Hello.
[Shin Hye being suspicious of
all the dogs in the area]
You're so cute!
I feel like you're a hint too.
Do you have anything?
- What's the dog's name?
- Gary.
Gary...
Gary, stand up.
Oh my goodness!
[Being startled by real Gary's prank.]
What are you doing here?
- Did you find anything?
- Did you find it?
No, I haven't found anything yet.
Paw.
It's not the time right now for you
to be playing with dogs.
But he could be the hint.
Oh, really?
Let's see... shake.
[Concentrating on searching the dogs...]
Come here.
Okay.
Don't be like this because you look like
Jolie in 'You're Beautiful'.
[A phone number written on a tag
on the dogs collar!]
Did you find something?
- Wait...
- Why?
[Agent Shin Hye having found
a phone number for the hint!]
Should we call?
Let's call with your phone.
[Agent Gary sidling up to naive Shin Hye
in order to gain the information.]
I won't forget this favor.
If... if I get a hint.
- What the heck?
- Why?
It was a dud.
[That was a dud?]
Then it really must be on
the collar of one of the dogs.
Maybe?
[I didn't call...]
[Wow! Agent Shin Hye only
pretended to call!]
- Gary, I'm going to search down below.
- Okay.
[Shin Hye heading down below
to avoid Gary to make her call.]
[Making the real phone call.]
It's ringing...
[The number worked!]
Hello?
Yes.
Agent 007 has something important.
Agent 007 has something important?
[Agent 007?]
I understand. Thank you.
[Agent Shin Hye succeeds in gaining
the information at Hongdae Steps.]
Are you hiding something?
Say ah... is it in your mouth?
Why are you being like this?
We're both Gary's.
Stop being coy and tell me what it is.
[Shin Hye walking way down below
to avoid Gary's watchful eyes.]
I think that Agent 007...
has an important piece of information.
[Who is Agent 007? And what
is the important something?]
Who is Agent 007?
[It's this guy...]
[He's said to have something important...]
[Ah, so sleepy...]
[Agent 007 has something important.]
This isn't going to be easy.
We're in big trouble.
- Then...
- Yes?
- Jong Kook...
Let's work together.
We can share the information.
One person can be the bait...
and the other person can get
the information and we can share it.
[I got you...]
[Rushing in on bicycles!]
- We're in trouble.
[Steeper than they had imagined.]
[The ladies' lair]
[When did they get past us?]
We have to be prepared.
[Second obstacle. Where
the men in athletic gear awaits.]
This isn't going to work.
[If they slow down at all,
they'll be caught!]
[Mr. Capable and Jae Suk having bypassed
both obstacles at lightening speed!]
[However...]
[This is... the third obstacle,
a mob of young girls!]
[Ultimately getting surrounded by
a mob of girls and the group of men...]
[Will this be the end of their attempt?]
[Agent Kkuk, rushing in head first!]
The flag!
Where's the flag?
[Please succeed...]
[A flag on top of the flower pot!]
[Agent Kkuk succeeds in obtaining the flag!]
Kim Jong Kook, Kim Jong Kook...
Kim Jong Kook, go get him.
[Meeting the informant at last.]
Thank you.
[Being handed the information.]
That was exhausting...
The answer is hidden inside the word.
This is it? This is all there is?
[The answer is hidden inside
the word.]
[The answer is hidden inside the word.]
- Did you find it?
- I thought I was going to die.
- I'm serious.
- Tell me what it is.
- What did you say?
- You have to tell me what it is.
Share the information?
You were able to get it only because
I allowed myself to get caught.
- You're saying you sacrificed yourself?
- Of course.
- I was chased down too.
- I threw myself in the crowd.
- When did you do that?
- I threw myself in there!
Like a moth that flies towards the flame,
I threw myself in that chaos.
- That's the only reason you succeeded.
- You really have a way of twisting the truth.
Fine then. I'll have to go on my own
to find out the information.
Hey... in that case...
I'll tell you what it is,
but give me your bike.
Okay. Let's cooperate here.
The answer... is within the word.
- What's that supposed to mean?
- That's what I'm saying.
- What does 'Answer is within a word' mean?
- That's why I'm really mad right now too!
Can't you see that I'm mad right now?
- But you're always angry!
- I'm more angry than usual right now.
That's not the complete hint.
What is the word then?
- That's all it said! How would I know?
- What's the word then?
How do I know what the word is?
That's all I was told.
- What kind of information is that?
- What did you say?
- What kind of an information?
- That's no information!
That's the information I was given!
Thank you.
[007 Seung Gi arrives]
- We had a cup of tea.
- Jae Suk...
- Seung Gi!
- Hello.
- He came here?
We're in trouble.
- What? What we're you two just scheming?
- We didn't scheme anything.
You just schemed something, didn't you?
[Not being coherent with his words
once he sees Seung Gi...]
- Good luck.
- Did you have any breakfast?
- Excuse me? Breakfast?
- Did you not have any breakfast?
- No, I didn't have any breakfast.
- Then have yourself a nice warm cup of tea.
- What's going on?
- Will you be alright?
- What...
- Just get going.
[Feeling sorry for him from knowing
what's about to head his way...]
- Is something going to happen in there?
- No, it's not like that.
Just order yourself something
nice and warm.
I'm sorry for making you suffer so much when
I haven't seen you so long on a variety show.
- Why are you apologizing to me already?
- No, no...
Just go have a cup of tea, Seung Gi.
Did you find any information?
So you have.
[Agent Seung Gi being a little
too obvious...]
- Can't fool you.
- Seung Gi...
- Seung Gi, we're heading out.
- Yes, I'll see you later.
What do we do about him?
- I feel so bad for Seung Gi.
- He needs to go through the experience.
[Pitying the little brother who's
about to face some big trouble.]
Down to the end of the street?
[Seung Gi with the mission in hand.]
End where? Where is the end?
[To the end of that street?]
- But anyways, Seung Gi...
- I can hear the sound.
[Trouble is already well under way...]
[Making an escape for now!]
I'm sure he's really shocked, right?
At least we've experienced it before.
And I noticed that a few of those ladies
really likes to stroke the face.
[Stroking his face to heart's content...]
[So this is why they were
so worried...]
I should've had a nice warm cup of tea
before I started running.
[Gary also arriving at the same place.]
- Did you find anything?
- What?
- Gary... are you in good condition today?
Why?
You have to be
physically fit for this mission.
- If you go down to the end...
- It's chaos?
[Will the secrets of this place
be revealed so easily?]
- Amazing prize is waiting for you.
- Really?
- You're really going to be surprised.
- Were you the first one here?
Yes, I'm the first.
- Really?
I want to cheer you on, so...
- Seung Gi...
I don't know what may happen,
so I'll follow behind you.
- Is it that crazy?
- Just in case...
- You just have to be fit.
- Fit?
- Both your legs and upper body is healthy?
- Yes.
Then you're fine. Go.
- If you need anything, just call for me.
- Okay, Seung Gi. I'll be back.
Thanks, Seung Gi!
He's seriously going to be shocked.
Hello.
Ladies! Wait!
[Gary being attacked by the ladies
without any notice.]
[They've got him!]
Gary! Gary, fighting!
[Seung Gi passing by using this opportunity!]
Hey! Lee Seung Gi!
[Huh? Gary escaped?]
How could you do this to me?
[Men in athletic gear are heading
their way!]
[Seung Gi making a break for it!]
[007 Seung Gi lucking out and
passing through the second obstacle!]
[But there's one more
that he's not aware of...]
Later...
[The mob of girls... are about to attack!]
Hey! Hey!
I'm going to get the information!
What the heck is this now?
What is this?
[Mob of girls on their way!]
[Seung Gi being surrounded with
nowhere to escape to!]
No, no!
[Gary succeeds in getting away
by using this break?]
You deserve it!
You deserve it, Lee Seung Gi!
[Now all he needs to do is get the flag!]
[Huh? He's just passing by it?]
[Why does Gary have to revert to
being by himself again at this time?]
[He sure is... going far.]
Enough...
Gary!
Where is it?
I've been totally had.
I've been totally had...
Hello.
[The flag is still...]
Isn't this the flag?
This is the flag, isn't it?
Didn't Gary already pass by here?
[He passed by quite a while ago...]
[With flag in hand,
he enters to meet the informant.]
- Hello.
- Oh my! Hello.
- Did Kang Gary stop by here?
- We haven't seen him.
He beat me here though...
[Where is the flag?]
[007 Seung Gi succeeds
in getting the information.]
[Agent Gary one step too late.]
I know you have another one!
Give it to me too!
- I'll see you later.
- What do you mean, see you later?
Hey! Lee Seung Gi!
[Lucky to gain the hint thanks to
Gary's tendency to go blindly forward.]
The answer is within the word...
[The answer is within the word.]
The hint in Sang Ahm is sold out...
[But I haven't gotten a single
piece of information yet...]
[Agent Shin Hye arriving at
the loach soup restaurant.]
This is exhausting!
I can smell something delicious in here!
[Rescue Jenny from being a captive in
the car! There's only one real car key!]
[A car parked in front of the restaurant.]
[An informant is captured inside the car!]
[Open the car door
and rescue the genie!]
Where's the key?
- Can I open it?
- Yes.
[Countless number of loaches
inside the tank.]
[And inside are countless number of keys!]
- With my bare hands?
- Yes.
Please don't do this to me...
[Agent Shin Hye acting very
frightened...]
[She got one!]
[Checking to see if it's the real car key!]
Is this not the car?
Are you sure this is the one?
[It's not opening]
This isn't the one!
[The terror having already disappeared
with the mission in front of her.]
This one isn't even going in.
Seriously...
[Going back and forth
countless number of times...]
Seriously!
You guys have to stop doing this to me.
Thank you!
[Agent Blank Ji gathering
the words one by one.]
Thank you! Thank you!
- You're so pretty!
- Thank you!
I just need to find one more...
Come on in.
I found it! Thank you!
Thank you!
I've been looking all over for this!
[Last letter has been found!]
[Agent Blank Ji moving on
to the next location.]
Hello, Sir.
[Laying out all the letters she found...]
[The enemy is within.]
The enemy is within...
[Who's the enemy within?]
What do I do?
It's about time I find it...
[Agent Shin Hye pulling out the keys
without hesitation now.]
[It opened!]
Jenny!
[The identity of Jenny...
is this stuffed teddy bear!]
[An 'R' sticker is stuck to the hint.]
[Sharing the information-
Kkuk and Jae Suk on the same team?]
Let's just share our information.
What is all this for?
First our mission is to stop the bomb.
- That's right.
- Can't we stop it by all working together?
[But... that's true...
They could all just work together...]
[Jae Suk and Jong Kook having
arrived at the loach soup restaurant.]
- Isn't he an agent?
- Are you an agent?
- Thank you for your hard work.
- Thank you.
[Rescue Jenny, who's held captive in the
car! There is only one real car key!]
- Jenny!
- Jenny?
- There's Jenny. That's it.
- Jenny!
That's Jenny.
What is this?
Can we take a look?
Do loaches bite?
It's people that eat the loaches,
but the loaches don't bite.
Let's see...
[Agent Jae Suk rising up to the challenge.]
- It feels weird, doesn't it?
- Yeah, it's no joke.
We have to be quick about this!
[A single key that he manages to grab...]
- Get out of the way.
- I can do this if I don't look at them.
[Could it be the right key?]
[The wrong key!]
It opened!
[It opened?]
[I'm sure it would've been
nice if it opened...]
I'll make it quick.
- It opened!
- What a lie...
It opened!
[Keeps opening only in words...]
[Having fun with it now...]
It opened!
[It really opened!]
Why are you shutting the door?
- We have to share it together!
- I know... but let me check it first.
- You said we should share the info.
- Okay, okay...
- Share... share!
- I said, okay!
[Don't you dare not share it with me...]
[An 'R' sticker is stuck to the hint.]
That's it?
Seriously...
- Hey! Hey...
- What? What!
- Why do you keep hounding me?
- What was it?
It's telling me that an 'R' sticker is on
the hint which is just a given.
Are you telling me the truth?
You don't trust me?
[Agent Blank Ji arriving
at the loach soup restaurant.]
You'll live about 200 years
with your crazy healthy habits.
- Jae Suk, Jong Kook...
- Hi!
[Getting his nutrition after
gaining the information?]
- This is a mission.
- What is this?
What is this?
It's all wet, and I bet it's scary.
No, it's not.
You're scared of things like that?
Ji Hyo, you're not like that, are you?
This is crazy...
Hi... loaches.
This one just stared at me.
There are some nice ones in there,
who'll get you the right key.
Really?
- Ji Hyo...
- Yes?
Or we can just all share our
information.
I'm going to try to find the key.
See? I told you, she won't go for it.
She never wants to work together on things.
Move!
See? We can just all share the
information.
We can just share...
I touched a loach!
[Blank Ji in a total state of terror.]
Wow...
- Hey, Song Ji Hyo...
- Let's just exchange information.
- We can just exchange information.
- That's a good solution.
[The wrong key...]
Oh my God!
Ji Hyo, we're telling you there's no
need for you to be doing that.
[No desire to exchange information,
but still scared of the task at hand.]
- We can work together to stop the bomb.
- We all have the same goals!
Okay. Let me just try one more.
Wait.
- She never listens to us!
- She's at awful at listening to us.
Wait... wait, guys.
Wait, guys. Let me just get one.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry...
what I did was wrong.
[Apologizing to the loaches...]
Hey, Song Ji Hyo...
I feel like we're watching
a drama while we eat.
- Do you feel like you're watching a show?
- I feel like we're watching a drama.
Here's the TV right here.
It's pretty funny, isn't it?
Song Ji Hyo is a good actress.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
What I did was wrong.
Don't do it! Don't kiss my hand!
- Wait, guys... just one!
- Oh... she got one.
I feel so dizzy...
[Will it be the right key?]
It's the wrong one...
it's the wrong one!
I'm sorry, Jenny... it's the wrong one!
It's not right... Jenny, it's not working!
I don't think I can do it.
I don't think I can work with
these guys.
Ji Hyo, come here.
[Giving up on gaining the hint?]
[The code that should be quiet is
all of a sudden being sung out loudly.]
This is so frustrating.
[Agent Big-nose finally getting it?]
This is it... this is it.
[Calling from earlier...]
[Correct at last.]
- Bang!
- What?
[Succeeds in getting one right away!]
[The letter he gains is 'Ae']
Should we?
Should we try to match it up?
Of course! We're not
stupid, why get all separately?
- Within... a spy...
- There's an enemy within!
- This is a great...
- This is an amazing piece of information.
Who could it be?
[Suk Jin and Ha Ha gain the information,
'There's an enemy from within']
This is amazing.
Suk Jin, let's do this today.
- Yeah, let's do this.
- It really was disappointing yesterday.
You should've won.
Suk Jin, the thing is...
Let's one of us win today.
- Seriously... and leave Kwang Soo out!
- Seriously...
- I already counted him out.
- I'm being serious.
What? The market information
is sold out?
There's no other place for
me to go then...
[The long awaited mission location.
Prism Tower in Sang Ahm Dong!]
[Someone is targeting the gold vault.]
[M16 agents foray into stopping that
attempt!]
Lee Kwang Soo,
you need to hurry in there.
Everyone's already here?
[Their individual secret agent code name
is being placed behind their name tag.]
I'm 003.
[To Seung Gi who placed first
in the previous test mission...]
[The code of honor, 007!]
[007 Seung Gi having received a mission
from M earlier that morning.]
I'm going to give top secret
information to you only.
The enemy is actually one
of the agents.
[007 having found out then that
the enemy is within since earlier.]
This is for your ears only.
[M ordering for him to covertly
find out who the enemy is.]
Make sure not to trust anyone.
No one can know that you're 007.
And no one can find out that you
are aware of this truth either.
Carry out the mission by integrating
yourself within the group
and find out the identity of the enemy,
and oust that member.
[007 secret mission: Stop the
bomb and oust the enemy within!]
I can't trust anyone...
[Changing into the agent outfit
that M had sent him...]
[Now the real 007 mission is
about to begin.]
Who could it be?
When a person starts to get suspicious
there's no end to that suspicion.
[Enemy within... who could it be?]
You don't have a PC, right?
- Do you have a laptop?
- No, I don't have one.
- I didn't think that you did.
- Do you even know how to use that?
That's not it!
That's not the power button!
- Just leave it!
- You are so ignorant!
Just look on the side... on the side!
You think I pressed this because
I thought this was the power?
- Then why did you press it?
- Come on, seriously...
I was going to pull this off.
You didn't know this, did you?
Of course, I know.
Come on, you didn't know.
Turn on.
[Agent 001's weakness:
Not knowledgeable with unknown devices]
This is seriously so frustrating.
- Jae Suk, that's not how you do it.
- It is how you do it.
- You have to stick them together!
- Just leave it alone.
[The agents are immersed in a game.]
- Seung Gi...
- Seung Gi.
[Let's see... could
one of them be the enemy?]
[It's impossible to tell
by their expression...]
- Hey, let's not be like that. Seung Gi...
- Yes?
What did you get from the
loach restaurant?
What does it mean,
find something within what?
It said there's an answer within
something.
So what is the answer within?
- If I tell you that...
- You can tell us that.
Why did you say something at the
restaurant, but not here?
I didn't say anything at the restaurant.
Did you by any chance, get it at...
With the ladies earlier...
then the answer is within the word.
You really are...
Seung Gi really is a bubble head.
I thought it was something
really top secret...
I thought it would be big trouble
if all of us knew that...
[Let's see...
Jae Suk doesn't seem to be it...]
- We have to stop the bomb from exploding.
- Are you an agent?
Of course!
I've been an agent since I was a kid.
[Just as his nickname states,
he is the Giraffe of betrayals.]
[Kwang Soo... definitely
have to be cautious of him...]
[On the other hand, there are
these also looking for the enemy.]
- We seriously have to...
- This is no joke.
[Suk Jin and Ha Ha having found out
that there's an enemy within at the market.]
- Our information is high quality.
- This is the best piece of information.
This is the best...
Out story today is...
There's a villain who's trying to
blow this thing up today.
The problem is they're going to
try to rid us of our name tags.
But I don't think it's just one person.
- I think Ji Hyo's definitely one of them.
- Why Ji Hyo?
[All three of them earned the information
about there being an enemy within...]
[Big-nosed Brother tried to glean
what information that she gained...]
[Ji Hyo's lies about there being a hint within
instead of there being an enemy within.]
She lied about there being a
hint within...
[Did Ji Hyo give false information to the
agents because she's the enemy within?]
I think I know who the other villain is.
Hear me out.
- Enemy?
- Enemy. The villain.
If you hear this, you'll be shocked
and it'll really scare you.
- It's Kim Jong Kook, isn't it?
- Yeah.
- Hi, Jong Kook.
- Hey... did you find something or not?
I haven't found anything.
I don't have anything.
- There's really nothing here?
- No.
- What about down below?
- I haven't been down there yet.
We need to search the stage.
[A stage being busy getting set up
for the 'Go Show'.]
[Trying to pretend to be the
guest on the show?]
Let's pretend that you and I are being
introduced together to enter the stage.
It's Kim Jong Kook and Lee Kwang Soo!
Let's get out there!
[Why is Mr. Capable all of a sudden
ripping off Kwang Soo's name tag?]
[Could... he be?]
Come here.
I said, come here. Stay still.
Stay here.
You can't be seen by others.
Stay here. Don't move.
[Lee Kwang Soo, out!
Lee Kwang Soo, out!]
Lee Kwang Soo, out?
See? It's already begun.
You and I've been together,
and neither one of us did it.
I'm not the villain!
[The enemy within... is Kim Jong Kook!]
[How is it that he became the
enemy within?]
[Earlier this morning]
Great job yesterday.
But unfortunately, you didn't pass the
mission for the License to Oust.
It's because you received the
lowest score during the mission.
Though I'm disappointed that
we won't do work together...
the world of secret agents
is a cruel one.
I'm sorry. Goodbye.
[Mr. Capable wasn't able to become
a 00 agent.]
[Just then...]
[A special delivery was made
even to him...]
[A mysterious letter was sent to him...]
How does it feel to have been
disqualified?
I will now give you a chance to get your
revenge on MI6 for disqualifying you.
[A chance to get revenge?]
[In an attempt to get monopoly on
the gold market...]
[someone is planning on setting off
a bomb in the gold vault at the Prism Tower.]
[MI6 agents will be sent to
stop the attempt at the attack...]
[Infiltrate the group of agents by
wearing the uniform that's been sent to you.]
[After stopping the attack on the gold vault,
steal the gold bars in secret!]
It would be an advantage to you
to do better than the last time.
I have all my faith in you.
Just who in the world sent this to me?
If it wasn't M...
then there's someone else?
Anyway...
you're going to come to regret...
disqualifying me.
M... you just wait.
[This is how he became the villain
that we were unaware of.]
[In order to get to the gold bars first...]
[He must find the hints to dismantle
the bombs before the agents!]
[And...]
[Just who is the one that
handed me the evil mission?]
[This is...]
[A time bomb!]
[This is the explosive device that's
posing a threat to the gold vault!]
[In order to get to the bomb...]
[This lock needs to be unlocked!]
[I don't care if it blows up or not...]
[Mom, Jong Kook tore my name tag
off again...]
I feel like it's in here somewhere.
[Agent 001 working hard to
find the clues.]
This place is huge.
Quiet, quiet, quiet...
Look around the surroundings.
Gwon Yeol...
Take a good look around.
Is anyone here? Anyone watching me?
[After taking a look around to
make sure that no one is watching...]
[Agent 001 discovers a box
containing a clue!]
[A car looking thing inside the box...]
[This is a USB storage device!]
[An extremely cautious Agent 001.]
What the heck... this is nerve wrecking.
[Finally getting it connected to
the computer.]
Hint!
[Giraffe?]
Giraffe!
But Kwang Soo's been ousted.
[Now that he thinks about it, the
answer is supposedly inside the word...]
[Just what could it mean?]
[Right around the same time...]
[007 Seung Gi also discovers a USB!]
It's telling me I need to use
my computer...
Water sniper?
[They said the answer is within
the word...]
[Gary also discovers the USB hint!]
It fits...
It says hint right here...
Look at the whole picture.
Spread out the seeds wide.
007 has something very important...
That's the only hint I have.
The color of the seventh letter...
is red.
Does it have anything to do with 007?
You have no desire to
rip off my name tag, right?
- No, I don't.
- I have no desire to either.
- Suk Jin!
- No... I'm holding myself in check.
Jong Kook really is dangerous.
- I told you, I'm positive it's Jong Kook.
- I'm sure of it.
- You didn't oust Kwang Soo, did you?
- No, it seriously wasn't me.
- It's Jong Kook.
- Right? It's Jong Kook, isn't it?
Hey, who are you? Tell us quickly.
Are you 007?
If you're not 007, what are you?
Are you a spy? Are you the enemy?
I'm asking just what it is that
you're supposed to be doing today.
The way I see it, from the way you speak,
I don't think you're the villain.
Why would I be the villain?
I'm scared to death right now.
- You're an agent, right?
- Of course, I'm an agent!
- May I reveal it to you then.
- Who are you?
- What is your identity?
- I'm telling you, I'm 007!
- I'm 007...
- If you're the villain, we're over!
I'm seriously not the villain!
You're the one who sang
'Will you marry me' with an innocent face.
You're the one who sang to my wife
with that sweet expression.
If you're lying,
I'm never going to talk to you again.
- I'm serious.
- Tell me... tell me why it's you.
[Suk Jin and Ha Ha giving Seung Gi
the benefit of the doubt that he's 007.]
I'm sure there's some kind of a sign.
You're saying there could be
more than one villain?
- Of course!
- There way I see it, there's about two.
There's about three of them!
No, hear me out!
- The villain... is Jong Kook...
- Jong Kook must be the head.
There's one head villain, and the women...
there has to be at least one woman.
Whenever you watch 007 movies,
there's always a woman spy!
- Bond girl! Bond girl!
- That's what I'm saying!
- Shin Hye... and Ji Hyo...
- Shin Hye and Ji Hyo, get rid of them.
- Jong Kook is 100% the villain.
- Jong Kook is for sure.
Let's get rid of Jong Kook first.
- Did you see it?
- What?
- You didn't see the bomb?
- I saw it.
- Ah... the timer?
- Yeah.
Shin Hye and Ji Hyo are both
really good at acting.
[Ji Hyo and Shin Hye's reactions
are both so lively.]
I feel like I'm watching a drama.
- Shin Hye, have you found anything?
- I heard that Kwang Soo's been ousted?
Suk Jin told me that you're
the one who did it.
Why does he always do that?
- He said that you...
- He told me that you did it too.
When did Kwang Soo and I
ride in the elevator together?
- Wait, I have to go to the bathroom.
- We rode it together a long time ago.
When we were all going our
separate way earlier.
That's such an absurd thing to say!
Jong Kook... did you find any hints?
No, I haven't found any.
[Ah... Shin Hye's about to pass on some
information to Mr. Capable, the villain.]
There's a 007...
[Shin Hye reveals that 007 has
something very important!]
The person who's 007 has
an important hint.
[Shin Hye passing on that important
information to Mr. Capable!]
[Is this without knowing he's the villain?
Or could she be..?]
To be honest, Jae Suk is the one
who gained the most points yesterday.
And Seung Gi got first place.
He and Seung Gi were on the same team.
[Shin Hye convinced that 007 needs to be
found in order to gain the hint.]
So 007 doesn't know that he
has the hint.
Since he doesn't know, we have to find him.
And we either have to rip off his name tag...
[No matter, 007 must be found!]
[On the other hand,
007 Seung Gi discovers the time bomb.]
[An alphabet combination lock that must
be solved by gathering all the hints!]
- No, start over.
- What are you doing?
I'm trying to open this.
Did you find something?
[Gary found 'Newspaper'
and Seung Gi found 'Water Sniper.]
Ah, you're trying to guess?
Did you find any hints?
Yes, I found it downstairs.
- I can't tell you that.
- You're right.
- Gary... you found a hint, right?
- I haven't found any.
No, I seriously haven't found any.
[A simple face that shows whenever
he's lying.]
- No, seriously... I haven't found any.
- Come on... you did find one!
I seriously haven't found any.
- I got a phone call.
- Who is it?
Hello?
- Gary...
- Yeah, Ji Hyo.
[Is Gary the villain?
He's acting suspicious...]
[I think he does have a hint.
Maybe I should...]
You can't rip it off now.
You can't rip it off now!
I have a hint!
- I could've won...
- You said you didn't have any hints.
You said you didn't have any.
See? I knew you were lying.
[Should've just been honest
about knowing a hint...]
004... I'm sorry, I thought...
Why are you so suspicious looking?
- You just look so suspicious...
- I was really trying to win today.
I was really trying to win today...
Gary, trust me. I'll win for you instead.
Tell me what the hint is.
- Trust me.
- I have to give it to you?
The reason is... I know something.
There's a spy within the agents.
- I was going to get 007.
- Why would you get 007?
Gary, have you ever seen 007
be the villain?
If you had given this to me sooner,
we could've been on the same team!
[Gary, out! Gary, out!]
[On the other hand, extremely
nervous Suk Jin and Ha Ha...]
[Ha Ha discovers a USB with the hint!]
We need to keep this hidden.
We can't tell Seung Gi about it.
But I have the machine.
[Ha Ha not having received a PC from
having placed last in last week's mission.]
- But you can tell me, right?
- Of course. Trust me.
You can trust me with anything.
You're like a Father to me.
I'm just joking. Hurry... hurry!
[Finally succeeds in borrowing the PC!]
- Lock the door.
- See what it is.
- Take a look. I'll stay here.
- Okay.
Lets look at it together!
[Hint hyena, Agent 001!]
[Rule: Free to share the information,
but the finder must view it alone first!]
The reason why I'll tell you is
so that you know I'm not the villain.
[But Agent Haroro doesn't know
where to insert the card.]
I, the IT specialist will do it.
- I thought you knew computers...
- Let me see it.
[At this rate, he won't be able to see
the hint he worked hard to find alone.]
- I'm not going to take it.
- You've stolen hints from me before.
- I don't want to!
- Trust me.
- You're not the one who found the hint?
- I'm the one with the computer.
Jae Suk, don't help me work this,
but just keep going on your way.
This is where I was headed.
Hurry up and try it.
[Still a foreign device to Ha Ha?]
You really are awful at that.
He doesn't even know what he's doing.
Let me see it!
Seriously...
- You two are talking too much!
- You're really horrible at it!
He doesn't even know how to use that
when he has it in his hands.
- Just give it to me!
- He doesn't even know how to use it.
Seriously...
- Just give it to me!
- You're out? So you're 003?
- You can't even do that?
- How could you just...
[Ha Ha, out! Ha Ha, out!]
[Cruel Big-nosed Brother making an
appearance for the first time in a while.]
Just go.
Go where you're supposed to go.
Hurry up and get going.
Why are you still here?
[Two checking the hint
Ha Ha found together.]
[They've found all the hints
that are supposed to be here...]
[The seventh letter in each word.]
[The passcode to the chamber is OPEN.]
[The two middle-aged men who still
haven't figured it out.]
- Let's just get going for now...
- Okay, Suk Jin. Let's go.
It's Jong Kook.
[Villain on the move... Mr. Capable!]
[From being flustered,
Big-nosed Brother drops the USB.]
[Two estimated Bond girls and Mr. Capable...
Being surrounded from all sides!]
[Big-nosed Brother besieged!]
I know that you were working
with Ha Ha...
[Agent 001 escaping out of there!]
- And Suk Jin... what is that?
- What are you guys?
We've been sharing our information
and working together.
- Aren't you the villain?
- No, I'm not.
[In that case... there's
only one person I can ask for help!]
Jae Suk!
I think I need to go, Seung Gi.
[I need to form an alliance
with Jae Suk!]
That really startled me.
What if Seung Gi is the spy?
[Too dangerous to remain alone...
what do I do?]
- See? A telephone pops up.
- I know! It says telephone.
There are four of these.
[Having found another hint by
having Suk Jin surrounded.]
We have to catch anyone who has a
hint and get it out of them.
[First...]
Why?
[Eliminating Big-nosed Brother now
that he's no longer deemed useful.]
[007 is still alive!]
- It's either Seung Gi or Jae Suk.
- You're right.
[Ji Suk Jin, out! Ji Suk Jin, out!]
007 needs to take care of this...
[007 put in a spot where it's
getting difficult to make his move.]
I think those three are on
the same team.
[Convinced there are at least
two villains involved.]
Kwang Soo was ousted when he and
Jong Kook went downstairs together.
And I ousted Gary.
Sorry to say...
And... Suk Jin was just ousted
in that room.
It's Jong Kook. He's the villain.
[So what do I do now?]
[Jae Suk, the only person 007 can trust.]
- What?
- Come here.
You have to trust me 100%
from now on.
Why is everyone telling me
to trust them?
- Everyone's telling me to trust them.
- Come on, come on...
[007 Seung Gi trying to convince Jae Suk
into forming an alliance with him.]
- Jae Suk...
- What?
What is it that you know?
Why is everyone asking me to
tell them what I know?
- I'll tell you what I know.
- What is it?
Gary, Kwang Soo, Suk Jin,
and Ha Ha have all been ousted.
- I'm the one who ousted Gary.
- You! I knew it!
Why did you oust him?
I ousted him because his
face was so suspicious looking.
[Eliminated because of his
suspicious looking face!]
His face looked like this...
- That's why I had no choice but to oust him.
- Really?
But he was an agent.
I ran into Jong Kook on my way
into the room with the bomb.
But Jong Kook was on the phone, and he
said 'What floor? Okay, be right there'.
and then he left.
Then Ha Ha was ousted right after that.
I saw that earlier,
but Suk Jin's the one who ousted Ha Ha.
Oh, really?
- You seem disappointed.
- No, it's okay. There's something else.
If you didn't have anything else,
I wasn't going to trust you.
I saw Ha Ha getting ousted with
my own eyes.
- What's wrong with those two?
- He was ousted in midst of a confusion.
- Really?
- Totally.
Okay, then lastly...
did you see Suk Jin getting ousted?
I did see him getting caught.
- Who caught him?
- Jong Kook, Ji Hyo and Shin Hye.
That's what I mean.
Those three ousted him.
- I get it.
- Those three are the villains.
Those three are telling me
that you're the villain.
I'm going to tell you this... I'm 007.
- Really?
- Yes.
- You're an 00 agent, right?
- Yeah.
If you're one of us, then trust me.
The reason why is...
the villain is one of the agents.
[Information 001 Jae Suk wasn't aware of...
The villain is one of the agents!]
[Trust me, Jae Suk!]
[Jae Suk calling Mr. Capable.]
Kim Jong Kook, where are you?
- Hey, where are you?
- I'm with the girls.
What?
Tell me the truth.
Are you a spy?
Seriously, this is driving me crazy!
Jae Suk...
Why would I be with the girls
if I'm the spy?
What floor are you on right now?
- We're on the 17th floor.
- I got it.
- He says he's on the 17th floor.
- 17th floor?
But why can't you just go along
with my plan?
But what those guys are saying...
why did you oust, Gary?
I didn't know it would be so...
oh my goodness.
- You're going up to 17th floor?
- Yeah, I am.
- You're going to get caught!
- Come here.
You're going to get caught!
Get off. I'm sorry.
[007 Seung Gi pulling Jae Suk out.]
You really... you're really decisive.
You're really not the spy...
I mean, the villain?
I swear I'm not the villain.
- Jae Suk, seriously...
- Wait.
You can't go up to the 17th floor!
We need to come up with a plan first!
I guess not going up there would be
suspicious too. I don't know...
It would be weird not to go after
telling them that we will.
- If we go...
- We have to go, otherwise, he'll suspect me.
- We have to get the information...
- See? He's calling me again.
If I don't go,
they're going to suspect me.
Wait... don't' answer right now.
Just wait.
- Wait...
- You're acting so weird!
[About to go crazy out of frustration.]
- Jong Kook...
- Hurry up!
- Where are you?
- On the 17th floor!
Okay, wait right there.
What the heck?
He suddenly hung up.
The moment that you go up there...
it's game over.
- It's final.
- He's calling again.
- Take the battery out.
- Wait, what are you doing?
[Unsure 001 vs. Frustrated 007]
- Where are you? What floor?
- Um... wait...
- What floor?
- I'll come up to the 17th floor.
Then hurry up!
We're about to separate.
- See? You could just come with me.
- If we go together, we'll both be caught.
I bet they're right in front of the elevator.
We'll be caught the moment the doors open.
- No, it won't be like that.
- 15th... let's go up to the 15th floor.
I'm telling you, I have to go.
[Why isn't he coming up here?]
Why can't you trust me? Seriously?
It's not that I don't trust you,
but I'm positive the hint said 007 is the villain.
Rip it off then.
Go ahead and rip it off.
Seriously, just rip it off so that
I can just get it over with and go.
- Look at this. He's freaking out.
- See? Look at that.
He keeps calling because he's the villain.
He's pulling you into his evil lair.
Have you ever seen a good guy
calling this many times?
- Let's go to the 16th floor.
- Hello?
- What floor on you on?
- Right now...
Jae Suk, let's meet on the eighth floor.
You want to meet on the eighth floor?
We've decided to go down to the eighth floor
because we've decided that's where you are.
Okay.
Jae Suk... we have to do this.
We have to oust him as soon as we see him.
The only chance we have is
when he gets off the elevator.
If we don't, we'll be taken hostage.
Come on, Jae Suk...
I've done this once and
ousted someone who was on my side.
That's why I'm telling you to oust me.
If you don't trust me, then just oust me.
You could be my ally too though!
Can't you just pick one?
[Getting off on the eighth floor for now.]
Why do I have to make this decision.
Hey, just rip my name tag off.
You can just rip mine off...
12th floor... 17th floor is coming down!
[They're coming!]
Just go over there.
I just need to stand here and
oust Jong Kook!
[No time and can't be convinced!]
Because once we get rid of Jong Kook,
only the girls are left remaining!
Because they're the villains!
16th floor... hurry! Hurry!
- Let's do this today... seriously...
- Okay.
What are you going to do if Jong Kook
ends up being on our side after we oust him?
No way... there's no way!
I'll give you all my money!
All the money I have.
I'll give you all my bank books.
[I'll give you all my money and the house,
so please trust me!]
[The three finally arrive
on the eighth floor!]
We're here... we're here.
What were you doing?
Why didn't you come?
I went up to the 17th floor,
and just came back down.
Where's Seung Gi?
[I'm right here!]
[007 Seung Gi!
Ambushes Mr. Capable and ousts him!]
[The black entity is still alive.]
- You believe me? You believe me?
- What does this mean though?
It's you! You're the villain!
Seriously?
- Seriously?
- You almost had me fooled!
[Just then...
Shin Hye's suspicious glint in her eye.]
Seung Gi, I'm sorry.
[Shin Hye rids Agent 001 of
his name tag!]
[Yoo Jae Suk, out! Yoo Jae Suk, out!]
See? Do you believe me now?
Did I do good or what?
You're right.
What you said was right.
I almost made the big mistake
of ousting Seung Gi.
[Off to jail for Jong Kook and
001 Jae Suk.]
- So you were the villain!
- It's not me.
It says here on your tag that
the black entity is still alive.
[The real villain is still alive...]
'The black entity is still alive'...
Then it means that there's a real villain
out there other than Jong Kook.
[The black entity is still alive.
Who is the other villain?]
Since both of you are so good at acting,
I don't know which one of you are acting.
[No way to read their expression since
Shin Hye and Ji Hyo are both good actors.]
- Are you going to give us the hint, or...
- Why do you need the hint?
- Because we have to stop the bomb!
- We have to stop it!
Really? Oh yeah, there's that...
In that case, let's not hang around here,
and go over to the site.
- Lead the way.
- Let's go.
[Deciding for now to head over to
where the bomb is located.]
- We can open it with a number.
- I'm 007!
I'm 007!
[There was a suspicion,
but this bubble head is 007!]
I'm 007. Why?
You're a villain, aren't you?
- I'm not the villain. I'm 004.
- I'm 008.
- Yeah.
- 008?
Then doesn't it mean that the villain
has already been eliminated?
[If that's the truth, then the three of them
have to join forces to stop the bomb!]
- You said 007 had something, right?
- I was told that 007 had something...
- Come here.
- Knowing who 007 is can solve the code?
Then what is this?
Have I been used by the producers?
[Whether you're an agent or a villain,
the bomb still must be stopped!]
Okay, number one. Water sniper.
Number two. Newspaper.
Number three, telephone,
then giraffe, right?
That's what you know, right?
Yeah.
[Out of sense of urgency,
rushing to the keypad first!]
[If they can't figure out OPEN by putting
together seventh letter of each word...]
Try solving it. How do we solve it?
- Seung Gi... let's rip it off.
- Mine?
- No...
- We're going to...
[Shin Hye eyeing for the chance
eliminates Seung Gi's name tag!]
[Shin Hye... why...]
[Since 007 is supposed to have something,
ousting him as a step...]
Let me see your name tag.
[Just then!]
[Shin Hye going for Ji Hyo!]
[Ji Hyo's an agent!]
[Revealed at last...
the villain's identity!]
It's you?
Shin Hye, it was you?
[Black entity...
Bond girl here to steal the gold...]
[Park Shin Hye!]
[Earlier that morning]
I will give you a chance to
get your revenge on MI6.
[Park Shin Hye becomes the
black entity.]
[Park Shin Hye is the first to receive
the information of the vault's explosion!]
[Must disguise herself as an MI6 agent
to steal the gold before it explodes!]
I'm going to pull in the one person
who has a lot of grudges against MI6.
[Recruiting the one person who has been
disqualified from being an agent.]
[The evil accomplice that she
recruited is none other than...]
[Mr. Capable!]
After stopping the bomb from exploding
in the vault at the Prism Tower
secretly steal away the gold.
[Looking back, Shin Hye is the one who
kept feeding him information all along!]
[And the one who ripped off all the name
tags has been her all along!]
[After dragging out all four
of the hints out of other agents...]
[Eliminates 007 Seung Gi herself!]
[And eliminates the last remaining agent,
002 Ji Hyo as well!]
[The evil Bond girl is none other
than her!]
[All the hints that has been found
are handed over to Shin Hye.]
Then...
what if Ji Hyo eliminates Shin Hye?
- Then Ji Hyo...
- What is it that you have, Seung Gi?
It could be in your shoe.
[Huh?]
I was given these shoes by the show!
There's nothing... huh?
You didn't know something was
in there either?
[What? Another USB in the shoe?]
- How did you not know it was in there?
- Are you sure that you're not stupid?
[007's secret that even
007 didn't know about...]
See? There's an 'R' sticker on it!
I thought it was on it because
it was given to me by Running Man.
[A hint that he didn't detect even though
he's been wearing the shoe around all day]
[Just as his nickname states,
a bubble brain.]
So this was the hint given to 007.
[The important hint given to 007 has been
in his shoes from the very beginning.]
[Will the explosion come first...
or will she figure out the passcode first?]
[Even the villain Shin Hye needs to stop
the bomb in order to steal the gold!]
[Even Ji Hyo is helping getting the
vault opened after being ousted.]
Just from my deduction, I thought seventh
letter in each word since it's 007.
That's when I thought that maybe there's
something in the seventh letter of each word
so I thought it would have
something to do with the code
and then noticed that the lock on
the vault is actually alphabet letters.
[Will... those girls be able to
figure it out too?]
[Explosion of the vault]
- Awesome.
- I really am sorry.
[A failed mission for all the agents
and villains alike.]
- Shin Hye, you really...
- Jong Kook, I'm sorry.
I should've protected you to the end.
The passcode for the lock was OPEN.
That would've opened up the vault right away.
[The passcode was OPEN]
[The important information that
007 was given and wasn't aware of...]
He said he had no idea.
I realized that on Running Man,
you really have to pay attention to details.
- You didn't know?
- What was it?
There was a USB card inside my shoe.
If you approached the vault with the USB
and the notebook, it would've opened up.
I just needed to connect it?
I had both with me at all times too.
[Bubble Brain 007 who already had
everything he needed from the beginning.]
[For the next three months, there will be
no more gold prizes on Running Man.]
Kwang Soo, do you get it?
Do you get what's going on?
- I don't think he understands.
- I think I just need to go home!
I thought you were only coming
on the show last week and this week?
How can you say such a hurtful thing?
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Next Episode Preview]
[The legend is coming]
[A legend in Korea's show history!]
Honey!
[The original Goddess of innocence,
Kang Susie!]
[Michael Jackson of Korea, Park Nam Jung!
Madonna of Korea, Kim Wan Sun!]
[The original Idol Group, The Fire Truck!]
[Hotter welcome than any other time!
Excited Running Man members!]
[A time travel to go back
in time in a time machine!]
[Back to the 8090's]