I saw it in somewhere
ah where is it
Open the door and go home
It's so beautiful here
is this wonderland
are we in the fairy tale
what's this
Genie
please come out
It seems that the master isn't here？
in here
we can sleep in here
it's raining, it's noisy when it hits the tent
Good night we are going outside
Kwon Yeol
yes
Let's sleep together
we really need to sleep in here
yes can you accept that
ah it's so warm
ah it's so warm it's so warm
I had to take off my clothes before sleep
there are 9 members here
Kim Jong Kook and HAHA
need to sleep together
We will give you a big room
Can you make me comfortable
it's the biggest room
ah just make me comfortable
Or you two can sleep together
then go to sleep
I will sleep in the car, in the car
No, no way
Ah I am not go to sleep somewhere else
I just want to sleep alone
I didn’t sieep for two days so I'm sensitive
It's because Geun Shik got married
Kim Jong Kook  -Which is my room
come here
hyung
shucks
Well hum  well
we have 9 members here
but they only have 8 rooms
Just give me a room
give me a room
in this case
you can sleep alone
then you use this one
we got the perfect solution
Is this one Got it
Take your stuff quickly
I have my own room, why did you come here
but he looks different
Give me one roomx2
why you didn't say anything
you didn't say anything either
he has a strong will
ah give me a cup
coffee
no the cup, the cup
ah cup wait a moment
I thought you need the coffee
ah
You lived as the youngest for too long
And if Mr.Song Hae is the youngest
turn off the light
I need to read before sleep
really
hum
Then I
really
ah it's so annoying
ah I'm so frustrated and tired
this book is quite good
you fits me
the colour is the same as your clothes
lie down
I want to stay before sleep
really then I will sleep
like this
ah there's a lot of space to sleep
here and here
how if I do in this way
what will you do  --I will do this
then I will do this this
in this case --I will sleep in this way
Then I will sleep like that
I will sleep like this
Ah I won't sleep
let's go  Good night
Just stay a little longer
But I will teach HAHA a lesson of comedy
I have my own style
go to take your notebook and ballpen
you need to get up at 7 tomorrow morning
you need to get up at 10 pass 7 tomorrow morning
I don't even feel like I slept
HAHA
what's wrong
you looks very tired
you snoring
you snored just near to me
ah I really
I go to the toilet in the midnight
you didn't close the tent's door
the wind blew and it's so cold
alright it's 7o'clock now
let me check the watch
ah
7 o'clock
hello
hello Mr. Yoo Jae Seok
yes
I will tell you what you need to do
Today you will go to the wonderland
ah What are you talking about
what's wonderland
To go to the wonderland
you have to pass the magic door
yes
The location of the magic door
can be found in Lee Gwang Soo's tent
yes yes
it will be more advantageous if you pass the magic door first
so do not wake up other members
it's free kill from now on
freekillx4
Where is Soesokkak
what are you looking for
I need to find something as well
is it in here
I'm gonna go
I am quite exiting when I saw the R mark
where is it
hello
I must be in first place
I need to go to the Soesokkak
where is it
hehe
you are quite fast
hehehehe
just stay there
go  hurry up
what's the matter
Ah my neck
hello
yes
go to Lee Gwang Soo's room
Mr. Lee Gi Kwang
come on hurry up
Just go to Lee Gwang Soo's room
oh it's so annoying
why it's so annoying
where did it hide
what's wrong
I pull off your cover for the first meeting
hehe
I'm in a rush
ah
oh
hyung
where is the magic door
is it in here
shucks
ah Gary
Miss Song Ji Hyo
hum
did you get up
Since they all left  Please get up and come out
They all left
hum
oh hello
Soesokkak
Soesokkak yes
What's the Soesokkak
the sea and the river
the two
ah
joint together
oh yes
It’s the place where the river and the sea joint together
yes yes
Am I right
Oh BoA is here
When did you arrive
just now
But oppa
oh
I
do not have any ideas
that what am I need to do
I need to find something
I don’t know what I need to find
ah Should we go down there
Let‘s go together
Oppa what do you have in your bag
Nothing I carry it just because it's good
Do you have anything to eat
No what's up
hehe
I'm hungry too
oh
why did you run so fast
this one
yes
this this
this one
ah yes yes
go in quickly
oh
hehe
Follow me
hum
ouch ouch
wow
Where are we
hehe
ah You can do everything
look at this
Ah what's this
Is it Alice's Wonderland
There's all sort of things here
welcome to the wonderland
I really
ah I really
What is this
Find the key and open the secret door then you can go home
There's only one person can go home
shucks
the key is in a treasure box around here
But only one
but how can we find it in such a wide place
key
hum  wow
unbelievable it's so beautiful
wow  It’s the magic door
I'm leaving
I guess I will feel nervous
ah
but it really scared me
oh
what's that
wow
oh it's cold
oh its so cold
you wore too less
it’s so cold
what's wrong
welcome to the wonderland
ah  it's my style
is it in here
I will survive today
Alice in the wonderland
I will find the key in the treasure box open the magic door and go home
hehe  zhang
the wonderland
Alice
Oh it's beautiful but it's too cold
it's that it's that BoA
wow  it's in here
ah  BoA
oppa eat this -shucks
this
Just eat a little
oppa eat it
It made the name tag become bigger
Ah I'm going crazy
oppa It's so big
You should told us first
You should told us the name tag would get bigger
I'm sorry
BoA We have no choice as it's free kill
Pardon me if I see a box and run for it first
shall we apart
alright BoA  I'm leaving
thanks to you my name tab gets bigger Thank you
yes oppa bye
oh the box
May I open it
pumpkin carriage What is this
10 mins -what
the time you can take a ride -really
And it had time limited
Hold on
wow That's nice
I feels like I'm back to my childhood
You can't just touch these without thinking  this one
oh there's a box there
let me check it first
ah  I just had to rush right as I got in
Open it
Eat me
Jae Hyung is here
Jae Hyung eat this
hyung you phone calls
I didn't take my cell phone
oh what's going on
what ah
The winds gonna blow it off
What happened
It’s too big
You have to find the key in these boxs but you can't just open any one
ah
Because you have to eat that cake and this happens
the name tab gets bigger   what shall we do
We turn into easy targets
It feels like you guys turn into easy targets
what -nothing
no not yet
how dare you  you can't do that right now
I will disappear soon
I'm going to call my magic
ah
oh
You happy
only one man will survive till the end
You really just can't eat anything
That's right There were stuff like this in wonderland
I saw this in the park
Where are the boxs
Gwang Sooah
Did you eat a cake
he did
you ate one as well
Hyung, he ate a crazy one
oh What is that
ah Gwang Sooah  come here
Look at Jae Seok  Look at Jae Seok
What's that
Don't laught at me
oh there's a box here
oh red heels
what does it use for
ah
In this case you had to open the box
ah  my feet hurts
Hyung Are you come from that side  There’s a box
Why are yo wearing your socks like that
What -I just want to
I had to wear this, I can't open it without thinking
I gotta open them quickly
I gotta find them quickly
oh there's one
I won't open it
sorry I won't open it
there's a prop there
What I won't open it
I won't open it   It is a little bit over the top
it's not good  It goes up
What you can see everything
I’m so afraid of heights
Sorry it's a big deal
oh Ji Hyo
Oppa What is this
what -What is this
You just need to open the box quickly
I just need to open the box -oh
Don't come here
Ji Hyo  open it
She open it
Ji Hyo open it
ah
I think it was a good choice to get on this I can see everything from the height
wow oh
I'm not good at finding hidden treasure when I was young
I've never found anything
oh Why did she ride that
oh stop
ah stop please
ah Please
hyung
how did it going up
the treasure box
there's a treasure box  Did he already find something
You opened this one and rode that righ -No
I found it up there
Hyung  it’s fun
You can see everyone
can you see who's where
You can see everything
who's where
the wind blows -really
BoA hi
careful careful Why it's still rising
oh my heart
Stop Stop
it's funny tonight
why everyone's here
Everyone's here
friends
it's funny tonight
here
Everyone's here Everyone's here
hold on
Am I right
may I open it
Open it
Duel with the queen
You have to beat these guys along with me
I'll give you a big hint
The key
Listen
right
Do you want to take off your glasses to fight
right right
anyway
if you win us
I'll give you a big hint
The four of you
let's try
start
You talk so much
It's a plastic hammer, it doesn't hurt
He looks strong
it looks like it'll hurt
come on you poker face
Rock-Paper-Scissors
paper
Scissors
rock
paper
You are useless
Rock-Paper-Scissors
You can't do that
we have to do it again
okay chow*n
Rock-Paper-Scissors
paper
Scissors
I'm lost*3
I didn't say just hit once
out
is it the end
not yet
You have to wear the gloves
should I have to wear it
take your time
you guys
bye
today
I'm unlucky today
Bad Luck
You have to hit like that with a plastic hammer
its more fun
It doesn't hurt that much
They did a good job
paper
Rock-Paper-Scissors*3
hyung
paper
It doesn't hurt
It doesn't hurt It hurts
rock
yes
good
The queen really nervous right now
She’s really nervous
you just exercise a little
you are so arrogant
I'm sorry
Rock-Paper-Scissors
paper
Scissors
Don't say anything
paper
get out
Get out of here
he lost
shall I go this way
hyung where's my shoes
did you unlock the magic
do you know it
The Housemaid and The Duchess
yes lion
Griffin
he wore the high heel
Find the heels
I'm leaving now
the recording’s finished today
Find the shoes
are you going to leaving now
I will tell you only
because I feel sorry for you
Hurry
there's a pair of shoes
Since when were you sorry about these things
Hurry Hurry
Follow that road
this way
hum
it doesn't matter the lie
is successful or not
There's no box
what's that over there
Its a rabbit
You’re late
You’re late Hurry up follow me
why
You’re late
Hurry up You’re late
why  -Hurry up You’re late*2
You’re late
what why I'm late
I've seen this
I've seen this in the fairy tale
it said you're late either
What it is
secrete passage way*2
it lead to another world
I’m your fan
I love you most in the book of Alice in Wonderland
is it for me
thank you
lee Gwang Soo
this is my prize
There was a really special secret in there
In that
the thing my mom called ashtray
check the mission note
this one
If you get the help of the genie, then you will be the winner
is this Genie
in Aladdin
If I touch it, then it'll come out
If you make a wish
rub it three times
and your incantation
If Genie don't like your incantation
Genie will not come out
this is the magic Genie
I saw this in the cartoon
I'm a fan wow
I can show you world
I am so exciting
so embarrassing
you are not working hard on it
I am working hard
Genie*2
please come out
are you calling for me my lord
it's you Julian
HI Gwang Soo
HI
why are you coming
What are you doing here
I live here
What are you saying
I’m genie
why are you call for me
what
I'm having lunch What's going on
How've you been
quite good
how about you
of course good
hyung are you Genie
Yeah, I'm genie
that suits you so much
and this white panty-hose
I can show you the world
stop singing
what's wrong
what shall I do now
will you satisfy all my desires
hum
Just one
tell me your wish
one
just one
Rip off Jong gook hyung's name tag for me
Jong Kook hyung
Jong Kook Kim  Kim Jong Kook
Rip off Jong gook hyung's name tag for me
the strongest man in Korea
My Genie Rip off Jong gook hyung's name tag
I want to compete with him before
Okay! Your wish is my command
Your wish is my command
OK
one more
what
You only have one wish
your wish is to tear off Jong-Kook's name tab
I just have one wish
aren't we have three wishes
our genie is a little different
The original Genie have three wishes
it's a special Genie
-only one wish -what
only one
If I fight with Jong Kook Shall I hit him or dodge him
YES  YES  YES
wow  it's so funny
Knee kick high kick
you can do that
Kwang
Soo
Cross
but wait a moment
I just can stay for one hour
I have to go to another show after finish this one
what do you mean
we just have one hour we have to hurry up
that's to say we had time limit
I am a special Genie
The wish it only got one wish
and just can stay for one hour
How could you do whatever you want  Genie
sorry sorry
How could you do whatever you want
ah I am Genie
Shucks
How can you don't respect me I am Genie
shucks
hyung you must help me to win
of course
-hyung I trust you -I know
-I'm waiting  -I know Fighting
we have to win
this woman
I don't know
we have to win   we have to win
hyung
got it
you have to get it
OK
we have to get it   Let's go
OK OK
I go towards this side   You go towards that side
go go
hyung hyung I am waiting   This way
hyung
you just can rip off Jong Kook hyung's name tab
When I rip off other guys' name tab
Help me to seize them
OK OK
You just need to do that
OK
You just need to help me to seize them
hyung it's weird that you always hide
you need to walk naturally
that's it
who pick up this guy
Jong Kook hyung
wow  it seems he is trustworthy
HI Genie didn't need to go to the toilet
rock scissors paper
paper
scissors
rock scissors paper
rock
scissors
Daebak Daebak
rock scissors paper
paper
rock
amazing amazing
how possible
you still need to beat off me
rock scissors paper
scissors
what are you doing
what's going on
what's wrong what's wrong
that's too big
Just like carry a bag
are you turtle
hyung are you going to school
ah
How can you do so
you should watch out the wind blows
Running man all changed to this
yes  it's all because of you BoA
in the circumstances
I need to disguise
wow wow wow
it's really
freaking me out
what's going on over there
you are good at nothing
I'm not scare I'm not scare
just kidding
how can you do that   You
nope
who eat it
Oh well
you should watch out the tree branch
shucks
it's over if it scraped off
nothing is worst than this
there is one thing worst than that
what
You
I didn't sleep at all because of you
the person affect my sleep
you snored for the whole night
you went to the toilet at 3 AM But you didn't close the door when you were back
the wind blew and it made me couldn't sleep
you should close the door when you went to the toilet at 3 AM
shouldn't you need to close the tent's door
No that
And the one sleep inside is sleep soundly
I was so cold so I clung to you
Since you were so close, your snoring was right next to me ear
Do you know how that feels
and you
The one who's really sorry
what's happening over there
Don't they ask others sketching for them
think about it, I live in twin room because of you
I can live a single room at first
hyung it's because of Jong Kook hyung
you didn't let me say a word
where is it where is it
do you know who I am
Uiang ang
Gwang Soo I love you
I'm freaking out
Gwang Soo Look
what's going on
hyung when did you come here
just now
what are you doing
I said it Gwang Soo I love you
Gwang Soo I love you
he love you very much
what shall I do
Gwang Soo I love you Gwang Soo I love you
Gwang Soo I love you
what's wrong
hyung this one
wait
why did you catch me just nowX2
ah because it freaking me out
it seems you want to rip off my name tabX2
hyung really -I just do this just now
ah yes yes
ohoh wait
hyung I love Gwang Soo
I love Gwang SooX2
I love Gwang Soo
what shall we going to do next
oh
Jong Kook hyung Jong Kook hyung
Gary out Gary out
who is the stranger with the name tab
Jong Kook
he is Julian Kang X2
tell me your wish
will you help me if I told you
hum
help me rip off Jong Kook hyung's name tab
your wish is my command
Genie you are coming
what kind of game you are playing
Jong Kook hyung
wow nice to meet you
you too
shucks No
what's going on right now
long time no see
Why you've been there
Cao Cao
whoops
when can we start
wait
you two are so funny
ah Genie Long time no see
hyung Genie is coming
who calls for you The guy should come out now
are you call for him
No
I just come across him
I come here by air
I don't know
ah it's so weird
are you going to eliminate us
no
it's me it's me
hyung he
no no
tell me your mission
what kind of mission you've got
why are you come here  it's so weird
I don't know
hyung I feel very strange either
there are some guys
there is something like that
is it Genie calls it
yes
If we make a wish to Genie your dream will come ture
he will help us
our dream will come true
right
ah So it is
make a wish
the guy I met first
Gwang Soo it's you X2
make a wish
Is that right   let me win
yes
ah  number 1
what's that   I don't know
what shall we do then X2
you met him the first time
how can I help you if you want to be No. 1
eliminate them all except me
who
do you know or not
hyung we won't rip off yours X2
it's not you Jong Kook hyung
wait
come back Genie
ah you fool  you can't do that
hyung you can go home
you are a simpleton  simpleton
I haven't seen that
no I'm not
ah
Don't rip off mine X2
wait
Gwang Soo don't let him rip off mine
Don't rip it off  Don't rip it off
Don't rip off Jong Kook hyung's
AH Yoo Jae Seok Dong-hun is over there
Julian Why are you here
I don't know why I am coming and wear the Genie costume
Genie is the guest
honestly at first
he made a wish when he found me
tell me
let's talk later
shucks you
Julian Kang what did he say
Gwang Soo
what kind of wish you made
Gwang Soo said something
ah NO Julian hyung you like a fool
what did he say  Hurry up
Gwang Sooah
NO How could you speak out our operation plan
they have similar height but they are so differentX2
oh
help me realize my aspiration X3
Got it
Julian what's wrong
why are you treat me like this Xn
why are you rip off mine
ah why are you rip off mine
hyung we've got the hint
we have to find out all the hints
Gee that's great it's funny
hyung Don't you know that
Don't you know the rule of running man
let's go to find other guys
where is the treasure box
Why is the rabbit running so fast
Rabbit  rabbit
I'm going to die
rabbit x3
what kind of rabbit it is
catch me
wait  let's have a rest
because of you
friends let's have a talk
let's have a talk
Make the name tag back to normal size
Okay
I am so tired
BoA do you want to make an alliance with me
What should I cooperation with you
you didn't see I'm seizing the rabbit
I'm running so fast
why did the rabbit have to run away
It's really fat but it’s really fast
Who is that  Yah it's Dong Wan
Dong Wan
I catch you rabbit
this is the name tab
ouch
oh Why Suk Jin hyung
let's go there together
it's not bad to cooperate with Suk Jin hyung
oh Gwang Soo who is he asides you
hyung
who is he
hello
My Genie's friend
what
hyung what are you wearing
what are you doing
That's how it goes That's all I open the wrong box
I've got the punishment
hyung
what's going on
sorry hyung wait
Genie we are running out of time
only 1 hour
It's Genie rip off their name tab
Genie can't rip off the name tab
So he just need to seize
okay
Let's go I'm running out of time
Show them how did he rip off your name tab
He catch me like that  Just like this x2
So you can't move
hum
ah No No
ah you guys
hyung didn't you ask me to show the way I rip off their tab
shucks
hyung the prison is more suitable for you
Gwang Sooah did we just show our facia action
Don't rip off mine x2 be care
they already cooperated
oh -they already made an alliance
who made an alliance
BoA
you and me we will survive till the end
we will survive till the end
hum hum
Don't pretend you're sincere
shucks shucks
shucks shucks shucks
shucks  what's this
hyung had been eliminated either -you are out
Jae Seok hyung
you are out
who is left right now
you and me -haha had been eliminated either
haha had been eliminated either
So I've told you don't rip off mine as they had made an alliance
Am I need to cooperate with others
I have Genie
really -we are running out of time
really got it Genie we are running out of time -got it
hyung Ji Hyo and BoA and Jae Hyung hyung
just three left three ok
we have to find them out quickly -Won Shin ah
Won Shin ah  what's it
Gwang Soo I'm sorry but
Genie had to catch the Flight
it's 1 hour -now times up
he need to take the flight now
I am Genie but I still need to take the plane
Genie didn't need to take the plane
I -how many minutes do we have how many minutes do we have
20 seconds left
ah  20sec Not 20mins it's 20sec
what shall we do -hurry to get the people
catch any of them
one hour past
seize him *4
ah  times up
hyung it's over hum
we need to go now  hum  sorry I have to go
why are you so punctual
good luck we told you it's one hour
hyung are you gonna go -call me *2 call Genie -hyung thank you hum
you are the key if I win
ah what shall I do！
it's so funny -you've had a long day
Lee Gwang Soo
Julian Kang where are you going
I ask him to leave because I felt bad for you
Don't lie to me You have been rip off the name tab
we just have one hour
you just got one hour
what are you going to do
I want to cooperate with you and I am ask your forgiveness
ah The wind might blow your name tag away -It makes tearing noises when the wind blows
It's gonna blew away -we can work together 2 VS 2
we lost out to BoA last week
okay -can we get it -hum
You just want to rip off my name tab
I am honour and I will obey our agreement
Freak Out *2
BoA  No it's not
let's end it quickly -end what
let's end it quickly
nothing in here
why are you running away -we have to catch Ji Hyo
there is a bike here
walk inside  it's there
oh you've made an alliance
No he betray me now
who -Jae Hyung oppa
catch it catch it
Gwang Soo  take care when you run away
Traitor
how could you betray her
who  -hyung did you betray her
wait
ah*2 See the position
I'm so disappointed  hyung  shucks
it doesn't matter to me  what are you doing
BoA  let me go
why shall I let you off
do you want to win  hum
catch his arm
it's waste of time
wait wait
Why are you doing this to me? wait
as you are a traitor
What did I betray
catch him
catch his arm
catch his arm *2
ah wait
hyung why are you want to survive so much
oh I really want to survive
But we still have to take off someone's name lag to know the hint
Who  -you
I will take the word out
No we have three but we need one more
we should cooperate to get another one
he wants to do it by himself
we can catch him quickly  hey  do you have the key
No I don't  -No we don't have keys
Then Jae hyung has it
Jae Hyung hyungis down there
I'm fine -sorry
I'll give you this  what's wrong Don't be angry
I am not angry
I will show you all
shucks
I found this
I lead Julian hyung to rip off Suk Jin hyung's name tab
unnie you have to win   Haha I know
I'm leaving Unnie
Me too BoA
hey hey hey
hurry up we should found Jae Hyung hyung
the centre
the centre house
where is it where is it
Jae Hyung hyung
where is the key
Don't do that to me
hyung where is the key
I am so tired now
yes I am so tired
so we have to go home quickly
You move -would you come here
would you come here  Come here hurry up
I can't get rid of you Ji Hyo
Gwang Soo  let's have a try
Where you just hiding
shucks
If I my name tag have been ripped by such man, it'll hurt my pride
My legs are too tired -ah  hyung
no -hyung just give up
you will catch cold
hurry up catch him
Ji Hyo you have to cover me
Ji Hyo man VS man first
it's gonna be cruel
No I don't know it will be cruel or not
but Gwang Soo is hard to get rid of as he is tall
I will support you
I feel like I might be able to win
that's misconception
I just want you to have this kind of illusion
aren't you think that I will lose
how could you
hahahaha
wait
I have performance so I can't hurt my hands or I'll be in trouble
my piano
what are you going to do
How do I catch him -How could you catch me like that
Gosh Jae Hyung How did you survive till now
Do you wanna guest in《you & I》
hyung then
He's too weak
how could you -He's too weak
Why are you so tall
ah ah ah  wait -what's wrong again
how could you yelling once I touch your hand
what's wrong with you  -sorry
I give up -No No No
once again
Let's end it hard in one time
Doesn't it seems like that
when herbivores fight for the territory
all right
thank you hehe hehe
you eliminate me
or what shall I do
give me the key quickly
I don't care you found it yourself
A
you're amazing when you in jeju island last time
oh
centre
Suwon
ah that's A
that's pass the garden of the art centre
give me the key quickly -I don't care
I will give you this -I don't know
where is it -It's in my stomach
How could I find it in your stomach
I don't know I won't give it to you
Gwang Soo  I will go with you
give me the key now
do you want to die
oh I get it
the key is so beautiful
hyung you've got a long day
Gwang Soo  sorry
Edit the part I fought with Gwang Soo
let me looks cool
Make me look like a cheetah
The look I run towards Gwang Soo
congratulation
how did you rip off Gwang Soo's name tab
Gwang Soo fights with Jae Hyung
hum they flight and then
Gwang Soo rip off Jae Hyung's name tab and I rip off Gwang Soo's
Gwang Soo is angry when he looks at me
why why he is angry
I hate Gwang Soo I hate Jae Hyung
ah  I hate Jae Hyung I hate Gwang Soo
I hate Jae Hyung I hate Gwang Soo
what's pity -you are so funny
you should go to see Jong Kook hyung
let's go and see
what wishes you made just now
I want to rip off your name tab
it's fine , it just a wish
Who do think I am
what -oh What is this
shucks
he is secretive everyday
wow haha
what's that -what's that
Deabak
oh you can run a jewellery store
why are you so eager to win
I really flew like a cheetah
When you see the show
you’ll know everything
Jae Hyung hyung ran towards me
but he is weaker than the wind
ah ah ah
yaooh Go