Subtitles by DramaFever
[On one sunny afternoon...
One lonely high school student]
Running High School's legendary fighter...
A rough reputation...
Hey, you brat.
Are you now crawling back home
after getting into another fight?
You said you're going on a field trip today!
- Enough!
- Just go away, you enemy of mine!
[Kwang Soo's mother's heated debate]
Field trips...
only nerds go on things like that.
Mom, we're not meant for each other.
[Whatever...]
[Running Man High School's first field trip]
Field trip?
[To the fighter, Kwang Soo...
The field trip is nothing but strange]
It's just for the nerds...
[The top student that's already studying
at the library since early in the morning]
[Even the arm muscles is the top...]
[His name is...]
[The top student of Running High School,
Kim Jong Kook]
Is today the day we go on the field trip?
I don't know why they go on field trips
and not read their books?
It would be nice if I could just study.
I'm so tired from having stayed up all night.
Today is the day of the field trip...
[Likewise, feeling burdened by the field trip]
Hello.
How you doing?
[The passionate working student who
doesn't get flustered in front of foreigners]
Here?  Okay... yes... here...
[SUDDENLY QUIET]
When you go on a field trip
you have to make yourself
stand out a little bit more like this.
[Overly strong makeup...]
[Playing the student-look too much]
Oh so pretty...
Give me a seat!  Give me a seat!  Hurry!!
Click, click, click, click.
Give me a seat!  Give me a seaaaaat!
[Typing away at a fire speed]
[Just seeing this image is painful]
Sungaga, Dosurim, you guys online?
[Sent into oblivion by the pain...]
Seriously...!  I should have bought it!!
[Graphs that could make people cry]
Ah... seriously...
I guess I should buy it
after the field trip.
Yes, mother.
I told you, mother.
I'm not going to study abroad.
I like Korea!
America doesn't even have bulgogi!
And there's no bibimbap either!
I'm going to stay in Seoul.
[Student HaHa that declines to study abroad
because of his taste buds]
Why isn't he coming yet?
[Friends to take on the field trip]
[The luxury car that's approaching at this time]
[His chauffeur?]
You're 40 seconds late already!
40 seconds!
What are you going to do about my time?
I'm 40 seconds late!
These kids are so hot right now.
I'm dissapointed, Mr. Kim!
Hurry up!  Hurry up!
Yes, mother.
I'm going to go on the field trip.
[The dancer of Running High School]
[Jae Suk - 2nd year student]
[Feels like the perfect weather
to be going on the field trip]
Ah... the freedom.
[Even his steps of heading to the field trip
is light and springy]
What's this?
- Hi.
- Get out.
I said, get out.  Get out.
- Get out of this car.
- Why?
- It's my dad's car.
- You're lying.
Your dad is working over
at my house right now.
- Get out.
- This cat costs more than your house!
You guys get out.
- Hey!
- Hey, this is my car!
Hey!
Fine.  Fine, then I'll see you later!
I can give you a ride, but sorry.
These guys don't want to.
Hey, I'll be going!
Ah... he's going in a car...
It's here, it's here.
Ah, Running High School.
Hello.
- Hi, Jae Suk.
- Hi, Gary.
- You're wearing a cute jacket.
- I just got off of work.
I've been working all night so that I can
make money to go on the field trip.
I think someone else is getting on.
[The next student to get on...
The fighter, Kwang Soo]
Is that it?
Is that the bus I'm supposed to get on?
Kwang Soo is acting again.
Hi.  I'm the fighter of the 2nd year class.
Come over here.
- I said, come over here.
- I'll let it slide just this once.
I said, come here.
- Kwang Soo...
- Yes, hyung?
- I've always sat in this seat.
- Kwang Soo.
Yes, hyung.
Will you carry my bag?
Kwang Soo, will you carry my bag too?
- I'm too tired from working.
- Just so you know...
...that you guys are really lucky today.
I really realize that when I see you.
No matter who it is today,
it would be wise not to get on my nerve.
We won't.
We're not even going to talk to you.
[The first field trip is
about to become taciturn]
- You have to talk to me at least.
- We're just going to leave you alone.
Don't worry about it.
Honestly, this is my first field trip.
Then be quiet!
-Today is Running High School's field trip.
- Yes!
This is the schedule for today
that you'll all be receiving.
To the students that follow the rules and
get along well with the other students
[Model student from the field trip
gets a gold badge]
Without a doubt,
that's going to be Song Ji Hyo.
You just need to enjoy yourselves since
this is Running High School's field trip.
Teacher,
won't you check our bags?
Is there a need for us to do that?
I think that HaHa brought
liquor in his bag today.
[Suspecting HaHa]
I brought some cognac.
I'm sorry, but is the fee about $10,000?
Because I only have $12,000 on me.
Hey... because of you, I have to buy IU a car.
Birthday gifts...
Because of you,
I can't look at IU in the eye.
I was actually supposed to be in England
playing soccer with Ji Sung today.
But look at what I'm doing instead
because of you.
You're going to England, you say?
Wouldn't it be awesome if we were to run
into other students on a field trip?
It would be the best if it were
an all-girls high school.
Especially the dance department.
[Makes them happy just to even think about it]
[Company they haven't even thought of...]
Even their uniforms are different.
[The questionable female students
that are watching them...]
With a slight wide legged walk.
[Just what are these girls' identity?]
Their skirts are really short too.
[The day of
Running High School's field trip...]
[The attack of the zombie they can't see]
[Running Man vs. Zombie]
Let's go.
[With light footsteps,
they arrive at their first location]
Wow... it does feel like a field trip.
Just where are we?
Is this a nature center?
[Incheon Natural Park]
Wow... The scenery is really great.
- Wow... It's the ocean!
- Yes!  We're on a field trip!
- Wow... it feels like a real class trip.
- Wow... nook at the ocean!
Is that real?
The first stop on the schedule
is to get in the nature center.
Which one of you know what this place is?
It's a very free place.
Nature.
Isn't this where the Incheon Landing happened?
This is the first nature park that was
established back in 1888.
You can now go into
the nature center on your own.
- What?
- What did you say?
But... since this is Running High School,
you'll each be given a mission.
[Running High School without a doubt
has a mission to carry out]
Everyone pull out a mission and carry it out
perfectly as it is written on the sheet.
And gather in front of General MacArthur's
statue once you're finished.
To the two people that are the first to arrive
there will be a gift that high school
students covet the most...
[The first 2 people to complete it
gets a cultural product prize]
Everyone, concentrate!
It's my turn to open the mission.
To go ring the bell at the history center.
- That's easy.
- You've got the easiest one.
I think it'll be the least funny
when the show's aired.
[Start the learning of the location]
[Complete each of their own mission
from each nook and cranny of the park]
Hello.
We're filming right now, elder...
[Play 'Alkkagi' with a grandfather and win]
[How are you supposed to do it?]
Then you have to be the first
to knock mine off the board, okay?
It's my turn now.  Here I go.
It's not easy.
It's not gonna end like this, right?
[Wow... The grandfather's good!]
I thought you said
you've never played it before?
- This is my first time playing.
- Are you sure this is your first time playing?
[Jae Suk loses]
This is it, this is it.
[Ring the bell at the history center]
[End of the mission?]
Is this the end?
It's this simple?
Excuse me!
[A female student?]
Hello!
- Hello.
I find you very attractive,
would you like to chat with me for a bit?
[She finds Kwang Soo attractive
and wants to talk?]
Would you like to chat with me for a bit?
My name is Oh Yeon Kyung from Yoonchun.
By any chance... are you here on a field trip
from Running High School?
Yes... I knew it!
You're here on a field trip, right?!
[Alright!  A joint field trip?!]
[Do a solo dance, and shout out 'Ho Oh!']
- Say, Ho Oh!
- Ho Oh!
That's good, right?
[Mission success!]
- Say, Ho Oh!
- You're the best!
Just a minute, please...
[Another female student for Suk Jin?!]
- I've been watching you for awhile now...
- Yes?
I find you so attractive...
[She finds me attractive?]
[Easy brothers, top popularity?!]
- Are you here on a field trip?
- Yes.
I knew this was going to happen!
You're here on a field trip, right?
You know students exchange
phone numbers and stuff on these trips.
But... I have something to give you.
[It doesn't seem like a phone number...]
What?  What is it?
[A towel?]
You're definitely going to need this.
- You can't ever tell anyone else...
- Keep it a secret?
Keep it safely,
and make sure to use it when you need it.
- Then, I'll be going now.
- You're just gonna go?
[And... A goodbye?]
People usually exchange
e-mail addresses and stuff...
What was your name?
[The female student who
appears and disappears out of nowhere]
[Just why did she give this to him?]
Just a minute.
- I have something to give you...
- Yes.
[A toothbrush?]
I'm giving this to you only because
I like you so much.
So... you have to keep this a top secret
just to yourself.
- A secret?
- Yes.
- To other people...
- This is unbelievable.
- ...you can't ever show this to them.
- Really?
I'll be going now.
[And the female student just disappears...]
Goodbye. Bye!
A toothbrush... I think something big
is going to happen today.
[Seems to think it's her token of affection?]
An angel has flown into my heart.
A cute angel...
Who has brought me a gift only for me.
[Neither one of them seems to be suspecting
the identity of the female students]
Just for her...
I'm going to make sure to win today.
Where was the path?
[Gary, who has lost the path in the park]
Wait...
Was it this way?  I don't think it was.
- Just where is the path?
- Oppa! Oppa!
[Why is a female student waving to him?]
I've... been watching you because I've
found you attractive since earlier...
Me?
[She's been watching me?]
- Can you talk to me for a bit?
- Of course!
I don't have any money,
and I don't have any capabilities either.
All I've got is the confidence to live
in this world.  Will you be okay with that?
Yes.  My name is Jo Seung Hee,
and I go to a school in Incheon.
- Anyways, it's nice to meet you.
- Thank you.
You're here on a field trip from
Seoul's Running High School, right?
You're gonna need this today.
[A letter and chocolate cookies?]
- Really?
- Yes.
I'm not giving this to your other friends,
and just giving it to you.
You have to keep it safe,
and keep it a secret.
Then are we dating?
Let's go to an amusement park in Seoul.
Goodbye.
[Gary takes the item
that the female student gave him...]
I've finally found my soulmate.
[Just what are the identities
of these female students?]
[Jong Kook, who's the first to complete his
mission and is back to studying]
Hello...
What the...?
The truth is, I've been watching you
at the park earlier...
I find you so attractive...
Can you talk to me for a bit?
Of course, I can talk.
- I have something to give you.
- Yes.
Just a moment.
I'm giving this especially to you only
because I really, really like you.
So you have to make sure
not to give it to anyone else.
- You can't!  Make sure you keep it.
- I understand.
- A secret.
- Goodbye.
[And the female student leaves...]
Bye...
Bye...! Bye!
Just what is this?
Wait a minute... What is this?
Why did she give me a t-shirt like this?
[A t-shirt for Jong Kook]
[Running High School bus
moving along with the mission]
[Running alongside the ocean...]
- We're heading towards a boat...
- Are we getting on a boat?
- I think we've been here before.
- Are we going to Moouido?
[Heading to Moouido on a boat?]
[The last course of the field trip is Moouido]
[We're going to spend the night in Moouido]
What?!
- Not many field trips go to an island...
- I have to study!
Once we get on this boat right now,
none of you can leave until the morning.
- That's not right, Teacher Jo!
- Teacher Jo...!
[Just like that... They are off to Moouido]
[Something is strange
about this field trip...]
[Not a trip...
But the feeling of being dragged]
This is like Maui.
What?!
What's this?
[The home they arrive at is the house from
'Stairway to Heaven']
[Just what awaits them here?]
Something's going on here.
The location this time is where
'Stairway to Heaven' was filmed.
There are pieces of paper marked
with an 'R' around this place.
To the first person
to figure out the puzzle...
- It's a prize!
- Really?  That's the end?
[As the day keeps on going,
something seems off about this day]
- Hey!  Why are you coming up here?
- It's my house, my house!
[While they all spread out on their own
to find the 'R' marked pieces of paper...]
I wonder if it could be here?
I wonder...
Oppa.
- Oppa?
- Oppa.
Hurry on up here.
[A female student on top of the hill?]
I followed you here from the Nature center...
Because I found you so attractive...
What did you find so attractive?
So I have something to give you...
Because I like you so much...
[Huh?  Hair spray?]
It's something you'll definitely need.
You have to make sure to keep it to yourself.
You can't ever show it to anyone else.
- You want me to give you a cat?
- Excuse me?
[In response... Giving away his treasured cat?]
[Totally head over heels for the girl's looks
that his suspicion is down to zero]
What is this?
Are you the beauty of Running High school,
Song Ji Hyo?
You scared me!  You scared me!
You are pretty just like the rumor says...
Thank you.
What high school are you from?
- I can't tell you.
- Really?
The reason why is because I have
something to give you.
[There's something for Ji Hyo too...]
Here.
[A makeup bag]
She really frightened me...
Oh my goodness!
Jae Suk!
[A hand calling him over?]
Who is it?
[First... Checking his surroundings]
Hello.
What...?
- I have something to give you.
- What is it?
[Slippers?]
You're definitely going to need this.
These?
[It definitely wasn't a simple field trip...]
[Arriving at their dormitory]
- Thank you.
- What is this?
[They each have their own little secrets...]
Doesn't it feel like a base?
[A luxurious dormitory by the ocean]
- Really?
- I'm in room 508.
[They're free to choose their own rooms]
[From Room 503 to Room 509]
[Check-in is complete]
[Recreation]
[Find the treasure]
[Running High School's field trip]
[Recreation Time]
Hey, it's  a real campfire.
- Why are they being like this?
- What are they planning on doing to us?
[They complain even if
we're trying to be nice...]
[Big Nosed brother is excited
once he gets the guitar in his hands]
The shoulder, the shoulder, the shoulder
is beautiful!
It's a campfire!!
Just look at the full moon!
It's a full moon tonight!
But why do we have to bring our bags?
Because!
As you put your bag on!
8 Times!
Your shoulder 8x looks beautiful!
Hyung, don't you have anything else?
Let's see Yoo Hyuk dance!
Yay!!
[Time for Running High School's
dancer, Jae Suk's dance?]
Dance right now?  To this song?
I'm supposed to dance to this song?
[His dancing abilities that could be
matched to any beat in this world]
[His commitment]
Now, Ji Hyo!
[Running High School's beauty,
Ji Hyo's dance time!]
['Hot Issue's dance
from her solo gig for 2 years]
[Fighter Kwang Soo's sideways dance]
Jong Kookie!
[Bookworm Jong Kook's dutiful dance]
You two together!
[Ha-Gae Brothers' sticky dance ending]
It's been awhile
since I've danced to that song.
Ji Hyo, you did the 'Hot Issue' to this song.
[Even though the beat has changed,
the moves of this woman did not change]
But why are they doing this?
- What are they doing?
- Why are they doing this?
Does anyone know any ghost stories?
Someone tell a ghost story.
A ghost story?
When you're sitting around at a place
like this in the summer...
I don't know why the ghosts
haven't taken him away yet?
- What do you mean? Come at me, ghost!
- Hey, like you're gonna take on a ghost.
The ghost who eat him will be very colorful.
A scary story would be awesome right now.
I feel like you'd know some stories.
- I bet you do...
- You know this one?
The one that appears late in the night
in the mirror during practice...
When I used to practice
while I was in the group...
While I was dancing,
2-3 people would pass by in the mirror.
- I'm serious.
- I'm sure you're lying...
I'm not!
That was me passing by back then.
[Was he the one?]
The height was really short...
When you go on a field trip, or to an MT...
- There would be 4 people in a room...
- Yikes!  Over there!
What is it?  What?!
[Something in the back...?]
[Someone else on this island besides us...?]
[A ghost without feet?]
You scared me!
- That was our PD.
- She looked so scary!
- You scared me!
- Look at the weight she gained!
- I got so scared!
- She gained all that weight!?
[After talking about ghost stories...
They're getting scared at anything...]
That's our PD, Seo Hyung,
and we got scared from her sudden appearance.
Our tonight's highlight...
is treasure hunting.
There's always treasure hunting
on field trips, right?
We've hidden treasures
all throughout this building.
Everyone come back here after you've all
found treasures on your own.
[A simple game of finding as
many treasures as you can]
[But an unknown sense of unease...]
We can't separate...
[To find the hidden treasures...]
[They enter the dormitories once again...]
[Just then...
Someone locks up the door]
The lights are turned off in here.
What's going on here?
[They came in to find the hidden treasures,
but everything is in darkness...]
- Wasn't it turned off in here to begin with?
- I think it was already off in here.
- Are you sure?
- I'm pretty sure.
[And they're supposed to find the
hidden treasures inside this darkness...]
I feel uneasy from
all the scary stories we've been telling...
What's this all about now?
What does... What does the treasure look like?
For no reason, I'm scared.
If we just find one of the treasures...
[Without even knowing
what the treasures look like...]
[They have to search all these
countless rooms?]
- Come out!  Who is it!
- You scared me!
- You scared me...
- I'm a legendary fighter.
I'm not scared of anyone!
Oh my gosh!
- It's here!
- What is it!
[Huh?  Did Gary discover something?]
You found something?
[But... Where is Gary?]
Over here.
- Did I really scare you?
- My heart almost stopped.
Sorry... You okay?
- That really was scary.
- I'm going to go home.
I thought you were the fighter...
[Even from a cursory glance...
it doesn't look like there are any treasures]
I really don't get the feeling
of any treasures around here.
- This is just...
- It's just too weird.
What do you think the treasure is?
Maybe it's something like this.
[By any chance, is the TV the treasure?]
I'm sure this is the treasure!
[No matter if they look here...
or there... No signs of a treasure]
It feels like there is something...
But just what could that be?
What could it be...?
[Strange... There's definitely something!]
What is this...?
[After all the searching,
they've arrived in front of their own rooms...]
Huh?
[Is something there?]
Why is there a walkie-talkie?
[A walkie-talkie...]
There's a walkie-talkie.
There is?
[It wasn't there when he unpacked...]
Hello?
[Then by any chance, in the other rooms too?]
[Does it mean that there's going to be a
situation where he'll need to use it?]
Why is there a walkie-talkie?
Huh?!
There's one in here too!
[It's in the next room too]
I can hear you.
- It's in there too, right?
- Yeah.
This means it's in all the rooms.
Hey, that's my room.  Grab it.
- This wasn't in there earlier when you left?
- No, it wasn't.
It's in here too, in here.
[In each room... A walkie-talkie...]
There are 6...
There's one in there too?
[As many as there are members... 7 total]
[Mystery...
The walkie-talkies in the rooms...]
How is this a treasure?
Hey guys, where are you guys?!
- We have to find the guys first.
- We have to get these to them.
[Something is strange!
[First, distribute the walkie-talkies...]
Hey, 3 of the weakest are
together again right now...
In horror movies,
us 3 would be the first to die...
[The weakest 3?  Gary, HaHa, Kwang Soo]
[But...]
[There are flags posted on each door...]
Someone stuck these on here.
[It seems as though someone has stuck
those on the room and office doors...]
Wait...
Look at the things stuck on here.
[Mystery II
The flags that are stuck on room doors...]
Mozambique.
[Just what is the meaning of these flags?]
Grenada.
- Jae Suk!
- Yeah.
- You really haven't found anything?
- I haven't found anything.
- Does that even make any sense?
- I'm being serious.
They told us there are lots of treasures.
But there aren't any!
There's something here.
We can't just miss it.
Of course there's something for us to be
doing this right now.
Why are you saying something
that's a given?
Jae Suk.  This is how you reason.
Don't you know how to reason?
I'm asking if you don't know how to reason.
- I'm listening to everything you're saying.
- Jae Suk.
Just how did he become such a chatterbox?
- Yeah?
I asked if you don't know how to reason?
Come over here.
You come here.  Come down to the first floor.
- Where?
- First floor.
Let's go together!
Don't you know how to reason?
You have to keep opening up all the doors...
It really is a relief that he's not
anyone's mother-in-law.
If he... If he were a mother-in-law,
the daughter-in-law would be...
Constantly...!
Why does that keep playing?
[On all the TV's that are on everywhere,
they all have You and I playing...]
This keeps on playing.
[Mystery III
The TV's that are on all over the place...]
This is strange...
[Whether someone's coming or not...]
[Gary... Why is it as if you're not all there...?]
- Gary...
- Yeah?
[Even when Kwang Soo calls out his name,
acting as if he hadn't heard...]
Is something...
What... What are you doing?
What do you mean, what?
- You... You have something, right?
- No, I really don't have anything.
[Am I really the only one who got something?]
You have something, don't you?
- I don't have anything.
- Then why...?
[Staring at one another to see if the
female student gave the other anything...]
I thought it was that way...
I didn't go the right way...
That was a dead end.
[An awkward smile from both...]
Come this way.
You can come with me
so that you won't suspect me.
[Am I the only one who got something?]
What is it?  Tell me.
- I don't have anything.
- I think you're lying...
[And...]
[A little bit later...]
[...Gary?]
[Kang Gary...
What state are you in right now?]
Zombie.
Zombie...
[Gary is... A zombie?]
[Just what is going on?]
[10 hours prior]
[At the first location, The Nature Center]
Gary!
[The mysterious girl that called
out to Gary earlier...]
I've been watching you because
I find you attractive...
You're going to need this today.
[A container of cookies,
and a letter that she hands over...]
You'll know once you read the letter.
Read it here right now.
To: Gary oppa
I knew from the first moment that I saw you,
that we shared the same fate.
That you are the same as me...
Tear off the nametags off of all the
Running High School's students at the dorm
and like us zombies...
And turn them into zombies like us.
- You're also a zombie today.
- A zombie?
I'll total them up for you.
[From the beginning... Gary was a zombie]
[He was only laying dormant...]
I'll be back from the field trip...
I'll be back.
[His real identity that has been
staying dormant has now been awakened]
I knew that my life wasn't meant to
pass by so quietly like this.
I knew that there was some other
being was inside of me.
And that is... A zombie!
Zombie... Zombie... Zombie!
[Gary, finally awakened as zombie!]
Whether it's the zombies that
remain alive at this field trip...
Or it's the humans that remain alive,
it all rests in your hands.
You have to makes sure to oust everyone
and turn them into zombies.
From your zombie girl
that's always cheering you on.
[Zombie]
[Then... I was a zombie all along?]
[That girl's letter that has
awakened his other being]
I've always known that there was
another being inside of me.
[Gary, who's been reawakened as zombie...
His attack is now beginning...]
The zombie has been awakened... Awakened...
[Zombie vs. Human]
Kwang Soo...
Do you guys know anything?
- You have something, don't you Suk Jin?
- I really don't have anything.
If you don't have anything,
then why do you keep...
If I had something,
I'd already have shown it to you guys.
Don't you think so?
Suk Jin...
You received something, didn't you?
- You received something, right?
- Receive what?
- I know you received something.
- Receive what?  I didn't receive anything.
- What's that in your bag?
- Water.
[The truth is, the big nosed brother
received a toothbrush from the girl...]
I'm giving this to you only because
I like you so much.
What is this?
Ah, it's my toothbrush.
You don't even have any toothpaste,
but just a toothbrush?
Who gave you that?
Who gave you the thing?
I'm asking who gave it to you.
Just some lady...
If you're going to keep being like this,
there's no use of talking to you anymore.
Suk Jin, tell us honestly.
Who gave you yours?
Some student...
- A female student?
- Yeah.
You got yours from
a female student too, right?
[Slowly revealing to one another...]
- She said the same thing to me twice.
- What did she say?
She said she gave it to me because
she liked me so much,
but you know that makes no sense.
I was told the same thing.
She said the same thing to you too, right?
I was totally fooled.
I thought it was happening for real,
and not on the show.
[Oh goodness...]
You really do fall in love quickly.
- Hey... What did she give you?
- The toothbrush.  What about you?
I got slippers from her.
[Jae Suk-Slipper.  Kwang Soo-Towel]
Just what is this?
They don't fit my feet.
They're women's slippers.
[Just what are the uses for the
items that they received?]
Just why do we have to live like this?
Doesn't it make you mad?
I just don't know why
we have to live like this...
[Every time they're shooting,
they're all stressed out to no end...]
[On the other hand...]
[Zombie Gary looking for human prey]
[Anyone who gets their nametag torn off
by him, that person will become a zombie...]
[Discovered someone...!]
[Mr. Capable, Jong Kook]
Gary...
[Yes... If only he can turn Mr. Capable
into a zombie...]
- Gary.
- What are you doing in here?
[Mr. Capable's totally exhausted
from searching for the hidden treasure...]
Everyone fessed up to what's going on.
While everyone was in the race earlier...
- We all received something.
- You did?
- You want to see it because you suspect me?
- I'm just saying, let's see it!
Jong Kook!  You should've told me earlier!
Are these cookies?
[Letter is hidden away, just the container!]
- Why did she give you cookies?
- She told me she liked me as she gave it to me.
Are these just cookies?
I don't have anything!
Wow... This is no joke.
[Huh?  What did he see?]
137 calories...
[Just give it to me]
[Ugh, that was scary]
I already showed it to you!
[Mr. Muscles, terrorized after seeing
the nutritional value of the cookies]
Just what does this mean?
[Ji Hyo enters the room too]
Just what is this, Ji Hyo?
- Ji Hyo, we've already talked about it...
- About what?
- You received cookies?
- Gary said he got them.
[Wait... If this happens...]
Yours was a girl too?
- You met a girl too?
- Let us see it.
- You saw it earlier.  Gary hasn't seen it.
- Let me see it again.
- This thing is his.
- This is mine.  See?  Running Man.
Look at this, just look at this.
Ji Hyo...
Ji Hyo, just what is all this?
[It looks as though Ji Hyo is looking at the
item that she received on her own]
- I think there's something in here...
- Inside it?
But Jong Kook...
Ji Hyo...
[Let's see...]
Show me, what is it?
I already showed it to you...
What are you looking at together?
You weren't downstairs when
we were all searching earlier...!
- What are you doing?
- Just go sit over there for now, Gary.
I'll confirm first and tell you.
[The person who gets
their nametag torn off...]
[You're saying they become
a zombie like me, right?]
[Should I make a strong zombie colleague?]
[What... What is this?]
- Jong Kook, this was an excuse.
- What the heck?
Jong Kook, I'm sorry!
[Huh? Ji Hyo... No way?!]
[The Monday Couple that were
walking together a little earlier...]
See the door's open?
It means someone's already been...
I think someone's been in here.
[As soon as she enters the room...]
I'm a zombie right now.
What did you say?
- What did you say?
- I've always been a zombie.
You've now been infected
with the zombie virus.
I can't be bitten...
[Just like this,
Ji Hyo's been a zombie since earlier...]
[How can this be...?]
Jong Kook!
He says I've been infected too!
I'm sorry, but you've got to
live as a zombie now.
[Only the head zombie Gary can tear off
the nametags.  Other zombies can lure humans.]
Since you've made me a zombie...
[Mr. Capable now is also a zombie]
I guess we can finish this within
30 minutes now.
20 minutes.
Let's go.
What is this?
This is the only thing that keeps playing!
Suk Jin... Why...
Why does this thing keep playing?
- Why is this thing always playing?
- I think there's something about that...
Don't you think so?
- It keeps playing the same thing, right?
- The same thing.
There's a TV in here too.
I wonder if there's
something in 'You and I'...
[It doesn't seem like it's on
for us to watch it...]
- This is so hard...
- Seriously.
This is exhausting, exhausting.
[While exhausted, a brief time to rest]
Just what is that about?
Where are Kwang Soo and Suk Jin?
[Mr. Capable zombie heading their way...]
Why are you watching TV?
What's this?
[Huh?  Breaking news?]
What?
This is breaking news from SBS.
We have figured out the location
of the zombie human.
The last sighting of the zombie
was at Incheon Nature Park today.
We have confirmed that it has merged itself
along with the Running High School students
that have gone to Moouido on
a class field trip.
The human zombie that was last seen in Incheon
We have confirmed that it has merged itself
along with the Running High School students
that have gone to Moouido on
a class field trip.
All the boats that go to Moouido
have all ended for the night
and until early tomorrow morning, no one will
be able to enter or leave the island.
It's amongst us?
Because they're highly contagious...
anyone who gets their nametag
torn off by the head zombie
is known to immediately become a zombie
themselves and turn on humans.
It has been found that zombie doesn't
like dark places
and because they don't look any different
from humans
it is thought that it will be
even more of a greater risk.
Especially because they don't look
any different from humans
it is thought that it will be
even more of a greater risk.
It's not me!
A way to destroy the zombie...
You have to hit the zombie's nametag with
the water gun containing the special fluid.
There are 6 of these special water guns...
They can only be obtained from the 6 countries
that have formulated these water guns.
[In order to destroy the zombie,
they need a special water gun and the potion]
[If they can get it from 6 countries...?]
The 6 water guns...
They're in 6 of the countries!
[The flags of different countries
that were stuck on the doors!]
With the head zombie...
After you shoot the nametag with the water gun
you have to also tear off the nametag
to completely get rid of it...
- Let's go.  There are 6 of them.
- Hey!  Wake up!!
- No!!
- That's not us!
- It's not you?  I'm not.  You're not either?
- No, it's not me.
You're saying there's a zombie amongst us?
No one's been bitten yet, right?
Just wait a second...
No one was acting strange...
Why don't we go find the water guns first?
[Suddenly nervous human Running Man!]
I guess it's finally starting now.
[As soon as they arrive, the easy brothers
start to search all the rooms]
We have to search all the rooms.
[6 of these rooms with the flags contain
the water gun with the special potion]
Suk Jin, let's each take 2 rooms at a time.
[Just which country room would it be in...!]
This room isn't it.
I wonder if it's already
been found in this room?
[Searching the office and the conference rooms
the flags have been attached to]
[The zombies are searching for the water guns
and the potion so they can throw them away]
[There's nothing here...]
[Somewhere else...
Come at me, humans!]
Out of all the Running Man,
one of us...
One of us is a zombie.
But...
That female student...
She gave this to me saying that
I'm going to need it.
- Because I like you so much...
- This is hairspray for your hair?
You're definitely going to need this.
I was spraying this on earlier,
but I don't think that's what it's for.
This... This hairspray right now...
It's Japanese.
Why did she give me these?
[At the similar time, other human beings
are questioning the items they've received]
Is this Vietnamese?
By any chance...
[Made in Vietnam]
[Made in Japan...]
Let's go to the Japanese room.
Where is the Japanese room?
I think I'm going to go crazy!
I don't remember!
Wait... This is it.
It's about where the items we got were made.
[Could the water gun and the potion be in
the country room the items were made in?]
Vietnam?
[That's right!]
[The country of origin of the items that
they've received is the key to the location!]
I wonder if I should keep this to myself?
[Worried that the zombies may also hear
if he were to contact on walkie-talkie...]
I don't know who the zombie is!
There's nothing.
USA.
[Made in USA]
Made in America!
It's American.  It's in America!
[The surprising skills of finding things!]
It's in America?
America.  Let's find America!
My toothbrush is made in USA.  America.
[Is this really one of the countries where
the water gun and the potion is hidden?]
[A big box with the 'R' mark!]
Here it is!
[Here's the water gun!]
I'm unbelievable today...
[Amazed at his own abilities...]
[Human, big nosed brother...
Gains the water gun!]
[Jae Suk on the other hand is off
to find Vietnam where his slippers were made]
Here it is!
[Vietnam room discovered!]
Is it here?
[A water gun is in here too!]
[Again, he gains the water gun]
The zombie can be eliminated once hit with
the potion inside this water gun.
The head zombie can't die
from the water gun alone.
You have to tear the nametag off also
to eliminate him completely.
I guess I have to ultimately eliminate it.
[Now that he's got the water gun...
He has to find the potion to fill it...]
How do I know who has the potion...?
- You found it?  Where?
- I found it.
[With a glad expression,
Mr. Capable zombie heads his way...]
[With Jae Suk holding a water gun in hand,
his approach is a little wary...]
- In the Vietnam room.
- Really?
- You only found the water gun?
- Yeah.
There should be something in there!
- You haven't found anything yet?
- I haven't found anything!
- The others are inside right now.
- Who, who?
Gary, Ji Hyo and Kwang Soo are in there.
- Where did you find the gun?
- In the Vietnam room.
- Hey... Just keep looking.
- Jae Suk... You have to find the potion.
- You can't just have the water gun.
- We have to hurry and find it.
[Off to report the truth behind finding
the water gun to the head zombie, Gary...!]
- Jae Suk!  Keep searching, okay?
- Okay.
Strange...
Why does Kim Jong Kook keep calling my name?
When I looked at him...
His eyes seemed a little red...
I think there's something strange about him.
His eyes are a little red too,
and he's being strange.
[Anyways, Jae Suk felt something weird
coming from Jong Kook]
He could've just asked me some questions,
but he was oddly being overboard about it.
Did you find it?
Hey, where are you?
Jae Suk, where are you?
Me?
Where are you?
Why are you looking for me so hard?
[Jong Kook keeps searching for Jae Suk
after seeing him with the water gun...]
Why are you looking for me so hard?
[And...]
[Ji Hyo, who's eyes opened up wide
once setting eyes on him...]
[They're starting to close in... Danger!]
HaHa, where are you?
HaHa, where are you?!
Jae Suk, we don't know
who the zombie is right now.
Where are you?  Tell me quickly.
Actually, don't tell me.  Don't tell me.
We don't know who the zombie is right now.
No one knows who the zombie is.
Be careful.  Be careful.
Many of them could already be infected.
Don't trust anyone.
I really can't trust anyone.
It could be anyone.
You're the only thing I can trust.
[HaHa finally arrives in the Japan room
where the hairspray originated from]
Who is it?
You scared me!  You're not a zombie, right?
[Jae Suk just happens to be hiding in there]
How can I be the zombie?
How did you find this room?
My hairspray was made in Japan.
- Made in Japan.
- Come in here.
You said it was made in Japan?
- You said it was made in Japan?
- Hurry!
[Leaving the door locked because
he can't totally trust HaHa]
It is in here.
[There it is!  The 'R' Case!]
[Without a doubt, the potion is inside...]
[Huh???]
Hey!  It's gone, it's gone!
Jae Suk, I'm dead then!
- Open the door.
- Someone took it!!
Hurry up and open it!  Otherwise, I'm dead!
[Did the zombie take the potion first?!]
I told you, someone took it!
[Panic]
Hurry!  Open the door quickly!
[The human beings are in a state of panic]
Someone took it!
- I'm telling you someone took it!
- Took what?  Open the door!
Someone took the potion!
- Who are you?  Are you a zombie?
- I'm not a zombie!
Jae Suk, I'm going to die.
Do you want to see me die?
- Are you sure you're not a zombie?
- How many times have I told you that I'm not?
- You're really not?
- Someone's coming!  Open the door!  Quickly!
- Who are you?!
- I'm human!
You're not a zombie?
It's Kwang Soo!
I'm not a zombie!
- I'm not one yet.
- What do you mean, not yet?  Go away.
- Show me the thing you got.
- I got a towel.
Hand me the towel, otherwise I'm shooting.
Why do you want the towel?
Should I open it?  I don't know what to do.
Hurry up and open the door.
I really don't have anything.
[For now,
all 3 of them hide in the Japan room]
- Get out.
- You, get out.
- Where was it made in?
- What is that?
Someone already took the potion.
The potion is gone.
It's Ji Hyo.
Why did you come here?
[Zombie Ji Hyo came to check out
the dynamics of the humans]
- What are you all doing?
- Why... Why are you so surprised?
- What do you mean, surprised?
- Don't come in here for now.
Why?
I have to find that and the water gun too.
- What did you receive?  Let me see it.
- Let's see it.
- Let's see.
- What did you get?
[Ji Hyo readily hands over the bag
to throw off their suspicion]
Ji Hyo, come in...
[Jae Suk gets his butt stabbed in the
door handle during the process]
- Jae Suk, don't go too close.
- Why?
- Hand it over, let me see it.
- We don't know who the zombie is.
But why are you telling me
not to get too close?
[With each word out of their mouths,
they're starting to suspect each other]
You're saying this pouch is it?
All I got was that pouch.
- Let's go, quickly!
- Give me back my pouch!
Give me back my pouch!!
[The humans are in a total chaos]
[Report this to the head zombie...]
There are so many things that are
made in China these days...
Huh?  Where's the refrigerator?
[The big nosed brother is convinced there's
something in the China room]
[Bingo!  The big nosed brother's power of
reasoning is especially powerful today!]
[Made in China.
Ji Hyo's pouch originated from China]
[There it is!  It's the potion!]
Yes!
[Big nosed brother scores
the water gun and the potion]
[Just wait, you zombies...!]
[Receiving reports on everything,
and the head zombie, Gary sends his orders]
[He still can't reveal his identity...]
Why are you asking me all of a sudden
which floor I'm on?
You scared me!
[The distrust between humans that are
even more frightening than zombies]
I told you, I don't have anything.
If I had anything,
why would I be carrying this around?
- I would've shot you already.
- I'll hold on to your water gun.
It's really cool.
[It's just a water gun,
but he looks so cool carrying it...]
Stop calling this a water gun.
It's a laser gun.
- I know that too.
- It's a water laser gun.
I think Kwang Soo has something in his bag.
I don't understand why he was
so ready to hand over his stuff...
[There are footsteps coming from above!]
[The giraffe is totally caught]
You, come here.
Let me see the bag for a second.
Let's see your bag.
Why do you want to see my bag?
Do you have the potion in here?
It's just water.
I had it in here earlier too.
How is this water?
[What?!  The potion?!]
[The giraffe had the potion hidden in his bag!
But why?!]
Just because of that,
you're going to think that I'm a zombie?
You stay right there.
Bring the bottle over here.
- Just bring that over here.
- I'm just going to dump this out then.
That's my potion.  I found it.
I was going to use it when I found a water gun.
Only 1 person can use it.
[Explosive suspicion of one another,
extreme conflict!]
Bring me the potion.
You're a zombie, aren't you?
[Suddenly being accused of being a zombie.
Just what is his identity?]
- I really am not a zombie.
- You're a zombie, right?
- It wouldn't matter if we can share this...
- How can we share that?
You're think we can split the potion?
[Jong Kook zombie enters...]
- Why aren't you responding to my text?
- What text?
- I had my phone turned off.
- Why do you have it turned off?
- He had the potion.
- He had it, but he lied about having it.
- The reason why is...
- It's because he's a zombie.
- Let's see it...
- They took it away from me.
- It's because you hid it away.
- Wouldn't you have done the same?
- Then why did you take it from him?
- That's what I'm saying.
Let's do this the right way.
HaHa, did you take it
because you're a zombie?
Why aren't you giving it to me
when I have the water gun?
Just give him the potion back for right now.
- I'll keep the potion in here.
- Why aren't you giving it back?
Hey... If we keep this up,
we're all going to get infected and be ousted.
[Ultimately, from Jong Kook's urging,
the potion goes back to the giraffe]
- He took it from me for no reason.
- It's because you lied.
- I have no idea who it is.
- You can't follow us again!
[Jae Suk and the giraffe,
and Jong Kook and HaHa in pairs]
Jae Suk.  Get Suk Jin first for right now.
- I heard from Suk Jin on the walkie-talkie.
- Give me a little of the potion in here.
You know I wouldn't use it on you!
What are we each doing with our stuff?
What happens if a zombie suddenly attacks?
Don't you think so?
I'll give you enough to shoot one person.
That's not even going to work.
[Did enough of the potion go in there
for it to work?]
You're going to have to put more in here.
It's not even working!
But there's nothing coming out,
there's nothing I can do!
I can't even do anything with this.
I'll give you $10 for it.
Give me that then.
I'll give it to you before we leave.
You think I'm not going to give it to you?
Why are you seriously being like this?
It's just so pathetic!
I'll make sure to give it to you later.
You think I won't?
First, let's you and I get rid of the zombies
and go back home by ourselves.
That'll be fine then.
- Just pour it all in there!
- I'm going to keep this much.
[The giraffe is adamant not to give it all up]
It's plenty.
It's because the gun was lying sideways.
[Now it's able to shoot]
[Let's go hunt down the zombies!]
[At last, the battle between
the humans and zombies begin]
[It is time for the ultimate winner
to start making their moves]
We don't know who it is...
Seriously, what is Suk Jin doing?
Oh!  Suk Jin!
Did you find the potion?
- Did you find it?  From where?
- Yeah.
Where did you find it from?
- Are you a zombie?
- No, I told you I'm not.
I'm really not.
- Are you a zombie?
- No, I'm not.
Suk Jin, let'go somewhere brighter...
[Huh...?]
[He wants to go somewhere brighter?]
[When the news was on earlier...]
It is known that once the head zombie
tears off your name tag
the person will then turn into a zombie
and start to attack humans.
It is known that zombies especially
doesn't like dark places...
Suk Jin, let's go somewhere brighter.
[Zombies don't like dark places?!]
Somewhere brighter.
[Aim... Shoot!]
[Shooting the potion onto
Kwang Soo's nametag]
[For now, Kwang Soo is out.
Was he really a zombie?]
Why did you shoot him?
Wait...
[How can this be?!
Kwang Soo was a zombie!]
[In the same room that Jae Suk and HaHa
were having a standoff]
[He was one step quicker
and found the potion!]
[And then of all things,
he was in the same room with the zombies...]
Jong Kook, I have this.
Didn't they say the water gun
glowed in the dark?
- Glow in the dark?
- Let's see it.  Turn the light off.
Turn it off.
[The reason why the zombies
don't like the dark!]
[Only the zombies have
a glow in the dark nametags!]
- You just stay still.
- Wait!  Just wait!
You're a zombie now.
Hurry up and turn the light on now.
You have to start helping me out now...
[This is how the giraffe became a zombie]
[The giraffe really was a zombie!
Stellar acting!]
- Hey, Jae Suk!  Look at this!
- It glows in the dark!
[Discovered the zombies have
a glow in the dark nametags!]
The ones in dark places are zombies.
No.  The ones in bright places are zombies.
The ones in bright places are the zombies.
To know that I got ousted
by people like this...
[Kwang Soo zombie-Out!]
[My power has grown weaker...
Someone has been taken down!]
Jae Suk?  Jae Suk... Jae Suk?
[HaHa and Mr. Capable zombie
are headed in their way]
We're going to shoot them
both unconditionally.
We have no choice.  No other choice.
Jae Suk.  I can see you clearly.
Suk Jin, I can see you too.
[Reflection shown in the glass.  Fail]
- Kwang Soo's not here.
- Kwang Soo got ousted!
Kwang Soo's ousted,
he's not answering his phone.
- What?  I'm a human.
- Are you a zombie?
- I'm a human!
- Are you human too?
It's not zombie, but a drowsy human.
Jae Suk.  Let's go get Gary.
Let's go get Gary for now.
[Just then!]
Where is Gary?
[Big nosed brother, locked on target!]
[Shoots!]
[Carrying out the act to the end]
- Jong Kook, you're a human?
- No way... He's a human?
You're a zombie...
[Jong Kook fools everything with his acting]
But he's not the head zombie?
[Jong Kook-out!]
Jong Kook must not be the head zombie.
[Someone else has been taken down again!]
[In that case,
time to start making my moves...]
No other way than to step up myself...]
[On the floor right above,
Suk Jin, HaHa and Ji Hyo are facing off]
[Planning on using the elevator
to attack from behind]
I'm going to have to shoot
as soon as the door opens.
[As soon as the door opens,
planning on shooting no matter who it is]
I have no idea who's who right now.
See?  Jae Suk is here.
I knew this was going to happen.
[HaHa and Ji Hyo, alert to Jae Suk]
- What is this?
- We've never formed any plans of attack.
Why didn't you come to the dark?
- I said I'll go!
- Really? Then I'll stay here.
- I'll stay here.
- I'll stay here too.
- Then I'll go downstairs.
- Go somewhere dark.
- Hey, where did Gary go?!
- Seriously... Where is Gary?
- Hurry up and go down there.
- Fine, I'll go.  I'm going right now.
Don't come down here.
Don't shoot me in the back.
[The suspicious big nosed brother
follows HaHa to the dark]
[Huh?  Who is she nodding her head to?]
[It's Gary!]
Hey, it's Gary!
- Jae Suk...
- Where have you been?!
It's Gary!
[The head zombie finally is out!]
- What?  What about me?
- It's Gary, Gary!
What about me, Jae Suk?
Hurry up and run!
[Flustered Jae Suk and Suk Jin
makes a run for now]
Jae Suk, why are you running away?!
[Suspicious of Gary after seeing him
for the first time in a long time?]
It's Gary!
Jae Suk, let's talk!
I think it's Gary.
Can't we have fun like this
for a little bit longer?
They're running away
just from the sight of me.
Wow... Is it Gary?
Is Gary ultimately the head zombie?
This place should be safe for now.
[Hiding in the dark away from the zombies]
What is going on...?
No matter how much I called him,
he didn't answer.  He finally shows up now.
[All of a sudden worrying about
big nosed brother he's been separated from]
It's one thing if we're together,
but you don't know when you're apart.
I think I'm going to go crazy.
What's that?
[Huh?  HaHa came down here?]
What the heck?
You can't come here, can you?
This is a dark place.  Why are you coming?
How are you coming? It's dark in here.
[HaHa's nametag glows in the dark!]
- Aren't you a zombie?
- How am I a zombie?
Aren't you a zombie?
[HaHa was a zombie!]
[Yoo-ruce Willis had is water gun taken away!]
[How is he going to face off the zombies
without a water gun?]
[HaHa's win for revealing his identity
and forcefully attacking!]
[All of a sudden, the zombies get the edge]
I'm going to go crazy.
What do I do?
[The zombies are everywhere!]
[Out of all the zombies,
the head zombie is the most afraid?]
Let's fool Suk Jin.
[As soon as they lay their eyes on the other,
they start to shoot!]
Suk Jin, I took his water gun.
- Hey, I'll shoot.
- I have one too.
- Where did you get it?
- I'm a human.
- Jae Suk?  You're not a human!
- I'm a human!
[If you go that way,
human life will be extinct!]
What's going on?
Suk Jin's in danger!
[He can't even help with his
water gun taken away...]
- Hurry up and call Gary here.
- Where did Jae Suk go?
- We're in Bangkok.
[Whether you save the big nosed brother...
or get your water gun back...]
Don't come here!
- Hurry, hurry!
- Did Jae Suk get ousted?
- How did you guys oust him?
- We ousted him.
HaHa... You stay here.
I'll be right back.
You guard him here.
Gary and I'll take care of Jae Suk.
[Ji Hyo's going away...
Now is the chance!]
[This really is...
Yoo-ruce Willis' true worth!]
Ji Hyo!!
Ji Hyo!
- Gary?  Where are you?
- I'm in the hallway.
Here.  Can you hear my voice?  Hurry!
Hurry!  You zombie...!
Hurry, Suk Jin!  Shoot him!
[Shoots HaHa on his nametag!]
Ji Hyo...!!
Ji Hyo!!
[HaHa really was a zombie!]
[HaHa zombie-Out!]
- You weren't ousted!
- Let's hurry, Suk Jin.
[The zombie Monday Couple that is just
one step too late]
- You've been ousted?
- I had even taken his water gun from him...
This really is no joke.
I thought you've been ousted.
Why did you have your water gun taken?
Well... I thought if I stayed in the dark,
the zombies wouldn't be able to come after me!
But he kept on coming,
so I thought maybe I was wrong.
I was unsure and wanted to check,
but that's when he attacked me
and took my gun away from me.
[Anyways,
the gun broke during their tussle earlier]
This isn't working.  What do I do?
[The thing doesn't even look charged...]
Seeing how Ji Hyo was going to get Gary...
- Gary is the head zombie.
- He's the head zombie.
[Seeing that Gary was being brought down,
they're sure Gary is the head zombie]
[The zombie Monday Couple are doing
an undercover operation]
[Ji Hyo... Right out there.
He's right out there]
[Big nosed brother fleeing for now
after seeing Gary]
I don't know if I should go out there or not.
I want to win...
[Head zombie Gary's ambush!]
[Zombies are starting to attack the human!]
Jae Suk!!  Jae Suk!!
[He's rushing to where he heard
the big nosed brother's voice coming from!]
[Huh?  Why the talking instead of screaming?]
[Suk Jin... This isn't the time for you
to feel bad...]
[What does that mean?]
[What's up with Suk Jin?]
[It sounded like Suk Jin
and Gary were talking...]
What's going on with Suk Jin?
Why are they whispering?
Look at this...!
[Could it be that his only human colleague
Suk Jin is also a zombie?]
You heard it too, right?
Right?
Jae Suk... Jae Suk!
I don't think I can do this alone.
Come here.
[Huh? Wait...]
I don't think I can do this alone.
Come here.
Suk Jin.  I heard something earlier.
What happened?
I ran away from them.
[Just what is Big Nosed bother?]
There's 2 of them now.  Let's run away.
- Does this even work?
- It works.
I don't know if mine's working.
[His water gun is damaged to a point
where he doesn't even know if it works]
You should take the lead.
- You should be able to shoot at least 3 times.
- It doesn't work.
- It doesn't work?
So you take the lead
and shoot them if they appear.
We need to go... And attack.
Once Gary is ousted, it's over.
[Seeing this... Suk Jin is still human?]
Pil-Chok-Cross!
[Jae Suk heading towards Suk Jin...
Shoots!]
[Shoots the nametag!]
Suk Jin, why didn't you come in the dark?
There really was enough to shoot
3 times in here.
Are you sane right now?
I'm a human!
Suk Jin, why did you ask me to
come out to a bright place?
I wasn't sure if you were or not,
then you stopped and told me to come out.
My feet wouldn't take further steps.
What was I supposed to do,
when my feet wouldn't move?
[Zombie Suk Jin-Out!]
Go, Suk Jin.
- How could you do that?
- I was a human once...
- Just go.
- I just couldn't go to the dark.
If you go in the jail,
Jong Kook isn't going to leave you alone.
[He may really become a zombie...]
What do I do...?
No matter what...
There are 2 of them, Ji Hyo and Gary.
[Will he be able to beat the zombies
on his own?]
[The 2 zombies going up against him]
[As soon as Jae Suk's voice is heard,
they're moving to an ambush location!]
[Even though he's a master of the water gun,
Jae Suk is feeling very burdened]
This really is crazy...
This is going up against evil.
This is no joke.
Ji Hyo!
I can smell Ji Hyo's perfume!
[Ji Hyo's perfume?]
I can smell Ji Hyo's perfume...
Ji Hyo...?
It's Ji Hyo's perfume...
Is Ji Hyo...?
It's Ji Hyo's perfume.
I can smell Ji Hyo's perfume...
I'm serious.
I'm not kidding, but I can really smell it.
[Jae Suk is backtracking after
smelling Ji Hyo's perfume]
I can smell Ji Hyo's perfume here.
[His nose, which is scarier than a zombie]
I know she was here earlier...
But I'm sure she left awhile ago.
[Ambush failed because of
the scent of her perfume!]
- It's because of your perfume!
- How do I know what that smells like?
[Just who the heck is he?]
[Anyways, Yoo-ruce Willis' amazing nose!]
This is exhausting.
I'm getting exhausted... But my heart...
My heart is pounding ever faster!
I'm seriously about to go crazy!
I'm going to go crazy.
This must be why I carry the water gun.
This is the feeling.
I'm going insane.
I can smell it again?!
[A total dog's nose!
He detects Ji Hyo's perfume again!]
I can smell Ji Hyo's perfume again!
I wonder if she was here for awhile?
See?  Right here...
It doesn't smell as strong as it was before.
- He went that way.
- Again?
[He can smell it?  But since he can't see,
his nervousness is doubled!]
My heart is seriously palpitating.
[The head zombie is discovered!]
Ji Hyo!!
[Ace zombie Ji Hyo
also attacks within moments!]
[Head zombie Gary,
gets rid of Jae Suk's nametag!]
[Human extinction]
Ji Hyo...!!
[Just like this...]
[All the Running Men have become zombies...]
[Head zombie... Gary's win!]
[The truth is, Zombie Gary...
[Was also alive 100 years ago...]
Subtitles by DramaFever
[The King is here!]
[Im Ho.  Lee Tae Kwon]
[He is ruined]
[There is no dignity]
[Getting rid of the heat through games...]
[Baggage will soon become laughter...]
[Race of the Kings]