[A National Hero's appearance]
[Marine Boy Park Tae Hwan]
[Rhythm fairy Son Yeon Jae]
[And... a mysterious witch?]
[The start of training camp
with the Olympic heroes!]
[And...]
[An unbelievable happening of
a shocking disqualification!]
Subtitles by DramaFever
Our Gary is back!
- Welcome back!
- Gary! We've missed you!
- You've no idea how we've missed you!
- It feels like I've come back home.
The weather is so nice too,
and I'm all better now too.
[The weather is beautiful too
for Gary's return.]
[Even though he's not fully recovered,
Gae-Captain is full of cheer.]
I think I'll be able to beat you all today!
[Challenging Mr. Capable by using
his injured physical state as an excuse?]
[Easy Brothers with
an opportunity to catch Gary.]
What's with the blue door and
the red door?
They usually have these when
idols makes guest appearances.
- That's where the guests will come out.
- I think it's one male and one female guest.
Blue and red color...
You're right!
Wow... you've gotten smarter!
[After being ousted 6 times the previous
week, the Giraffe has gotten smarter]
The guests whom will be joining you today
are waiting behind those doors.
- Behind the blue door is your first guest.
- The blue door?
[Who is the guest behind the blue door?]
Excuse me...
who's behind the blue door?
- Come on out!
- Who are you?
- Someone's about to come out.
- Why is he so tall?
[The tall silhouette]
It's an Olympic athlete...
I bet it's an Olympic athlete.
- The ear... the ears are a little...
- Maybe a wrestler?
[His extraordinary aura...]
I'm sorry, but have you ever shot an
air conditioner CF?
[The one who stands waiting behind the door
in a constant state of nervousness...]
[It's a set of headphones...?!]
[That is... his trademark!]
[He is here!]
[Park Tae Hwan]
[The national hero!
Park Tae Hwan's surprise appearance!]
On my! Tae Hwan!
- I'm sorry...
- Why? Why can't I even shake his hand!
[No matter where he goes in the nation,
his enormous popularity!]
- Why are you being like that with our guest?
- Oh my... how is it that he's here?
Look at his shoulders!
His shoulders!
[National Marine Boy Hero
Park Tae Hwan in front of their eyes!]
Hey Jong Kook...
I don't think you'll win today.
I just have a feeling that you're not
going to win today.
- His shoulders look like a little kid's now.
- You're like a baby now.
You're going to have to
work out some more.
- You're going to have to work out harder.
- Tae Hwan... please take care of us, seriously.
[Huh...his speech is slowly...?]
Why are you speaking in casual speech?
He's the nation's little brother!
If he's the nation's little brother,
then he's like my little brother!
He's a hero! A hero!
Tae Hwan,
you know what I mean, right?
Rip off Jong Kook's name tag
for us today.
- As you all may know already, Tae Hwan...
- Be quiet!
[Pretending to be close...]
Seriously... just give it a rest.
- Seriously, just give it a rest!
- Let him speak, so we can hear his voice.
He hasn't said a word yet.
Let him at least say hello.
Hello, I'm Park Tae Hwan,
the swimmer.
[Welcome to Running Man!]
- Park Tae Hwan...
- His looks are a bit exotic.
Seriously... all the women love him.
- It's because I have makeup on.
- You have makeup on?
- I have some makeup on my face.
- But he has very light makeup on.
How do you know if he has light
or heavy makeup on?
Whenever an athlete comes on the show,
he gets so excited!
I watched the documentary a while ago
about the London Olympics preparations.
- I did too!
- Who out there hasn't watched that?
- Tell me who hasn't seen it?
- While watching him weight train...
I was thinking the way he was doing
it isn't good for his back.
[Worrying about Tae Hwan's back while
watching him weight train]
- I'm sure he knew what he was doing!
- I was very worried watching that.
Did you all hear this?
While watching Park Tae Hwan who trains with
the best trainers and staff in the world
he was thinking
'That's not how he should be lifting.'
[Coach Kook-
'That's not how he should be lifting...']
[Like a dog trying to
teach the bird how to fly...]
He really is a mania... seriously.
I really was worried watching
how he weight trained.
I never even dreamed that Park Tae Hwan
would guest star on Running Man...
The truth is, with the London Olympics
I didn't get much chance to watch...
- I bet.
- I should've watched...
[It's ok. We understand 1000%.]
Who's name tag do you want to
rip off the most?
Yours.
[Olympic champion-like answer.]
So we have our Olympian Park Tae Hwan here,
but you're saying there's someone else?
[In that case, who's behind the red door?]
With Park Tae Hwan out here,
we're curious who else is behind the door?
Who are you?
- There's something in her hand!
- She's holding something!
Who is that?
[Ribbon?]
[In that case...!]
[The Rhythm Gymnastics' Fairy
Son Yeon Jae!]
Yeon Jae...!
[Trying to protect the athlete first.]
This is crazy!
Seriously?
- Yeon Jae!
- Hello.
- Go away! You're going to hurt her!
Pay some attention to Park Tae Hwan!
I'll... I'll just say my hello
and leave.
[Surprise! Son Yeon Jae is here too!]
Gary...
[Running Man losing their mental strings
over the appearance of two superstars.]
Let me be a playboy for just
one more day!
[The desperate plea from a man
who's already been spoken for.]
- It's the last time, Byul!
- My last!
You should've come on the show
three weeks ago!
We would all like to congratulate
Ha Ha's wedding one more time!
[Ha Ha, congratulations on your wedding]
My last!
[Whether he's awake or asleep, Haroro is
full of joy over thought of Miss Byul.]
- Now we should...
- Son Yeon Jae is here.
She's just like an angel...
[Welcome, Rhythm Gymnastics' Fairy,
Son Yeon Jae!]
We need to do it for
Park Tae Hwan too.
- Why is my voice...
- Your behavior is different.
- Why are you being like that?
- Your tone and behavior are different.
And why are you standing here all of a sudden?
Go back to where you were standing earlier.
- Are you playing around right now?
- Why are you standing so far apart?
Think about it...
listen to me for a minute.
I stood there earlier.
It's only right that I stand here now.
Then Park Tae Hwan and Son Yeon Jae,
please trade your spots.
- Like this.
- That's much better!
Then now...
[Casually going in between...]
Seriously... it was shocking enough
to see Park Tae Hwan come out
but I had no idea that
Son Yeon Jae would be here too!
- Seriously...
- This is so unreal...
I watched all the Olympic games
when they were being broadcasted live...
Is there anyone out there
who hasn't?
- Why are you even saying that?
- What point do you have by saying that?
[Let's hear Son Yeon Jae's voice too..]
- Hello.
[Being caught even the slightest bit off guard
knocks their mental strings out of the water.]
Hello, I'm a Rhythm Gymnast,
Son Yeon Jae.
Son Yeon Jae on Running Man...
[Bee?]
- Oh my gosh!
- It's a bee! Go away!
[Iron clad wall of protection.]
[Over excited uncle-like fans.]
- But... this is...
- Even the bee recognizes the flower...
But that bee was working hard to chase
our Park Tae Hwan around too.
He was afraid of being stung...
afraid of being stung himself.
Even though I just said it a
moment ago...
Even though I don't know if Son Yeon Jae
will get to tear a name tag off or not
do you think you'll be alright?
Yes, I normally watch this
show often.
- You've watched Running Man before?
- Yes.
- You just stay quiet.
- Why?
I'm just interviewing her right now.
You just pay attention to Byul.
What about you then?
You pay attention to your own wife!
You're no better!
Since I have no one
that I need to pay attention to...
- Start over with Song Ji Hyo!
- Me? Why?
[A strong rejection?]
Why should I...
He says why should I...
If you were to rip off someone's name tag...
Park Tae Hwan said he wants to rip Ha Ha's...
- So who would you like to rip off first?
- I would also like to...
I would also like to...
[Son Yeon Jae ultimately picks Ha Ha!]
- Anyways, it's a good thing for us.
- Why?
I met him once when I was in
elementary school...
- Seriously?
- He came for some kind of a shoot...
- And?
- He didn't give me an autograph.
He didn't give me an autograph.
[Celebrity Ha Ha
left in young Yeon Jae's heart.]
[A remaining scar that
even a fortune can't take away.]
That really...
that must've left a really huge scar.
Were you out of your mind?
We did bother him some, since
we were all elementary school students.
But he said 'You guys got it earlier!'
and didn't give us anymore autographs...
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
- I'm so sorry.
- It's okay.
I cleanse you of your sins.
[An already spilled glass of water
he can't hope to undo.]
- Let's stop talking about that now.
- Stop it.
Son Yeon Jae and Park Tae Hwan today...
How in the world did this happen?
[Being together with these two whose
sheer presence brings happiness.]
Since they're here, let's all take a seat
and listen to some of their stories...
- Okay.
- As much as they want to share with us.
Even if you feel Son Yeon Jae coming
up behind you, just stand still.
But that's no fun.
Good for you, good for you!
Since Yoo Jae Suk is Running Man!
[A twisted groom-to-be.]
I cleanse you of all your sins.
Well then,
what are we going to be doing?
Today's Running Man will be divided into
3 teams of 3 members each.
- If there's to be 3 teams, then us 3...
- How do we divide up the team?
Son Yeon Jae and Park Tae Hwan will play
Rock-Paper-Scissors
and the winner will have first pick
on who their teammate will be today.
[The 3 members who aren't chosen by them
will automatically become a team]
Well then, the two of you...
Yeon Jae, you would refer to Tae Hwan
as an older brother, right?
- Why don't you start then?
- Do we just start? Rock-Paper-Scissors...
Again, again.
[An embarrassing Rock-Paper-Scissors?]
- We've never really met face-to-face...
- Why is your face all red?
He says they've talked before but never
faced each other like this before.
We've only talked and never had to
face each other like this before...
- Well, you are in your prime...
- He's in the prime of his life...
This is the best time...
Let's do the Rock-Paper-Scissors again.
[Son Yeon Jae wins.]
I...
Yoo Jae Suk.
[Energetically spinning the ribbon.]
[Automatically turning into a dance?]
If I pick...
If I pick,
I'm afraid you may not be happy about it.
- What are you talking about?
- How can you say that?
That's nonsense, Park Tae Hwan.
Jong Kook really has
a lot of interest in swimming.
- That's one of his favorite sports.
- I like them all.
I like all sorts of sports.
- But if they team up, that's too...
- That's right.
Then why didn't you pick
Kim Jong Kook?
[Unable to be the playboy any longer,
everything has become twisted.]
I got a little jealous!
I'm going to pick Gary first.
[Wow! He chooses Gary!]
[A disappointed Tiger?]
Look at how disappointed Jong Kook
is for not getting picked!
Gary won't be of any help to you
because he's been injured.
What? I can run! I can run!
- Why are you saying stuff like that?
- You should quit running now.
- Your leg was barely even moving.
- Why are you being like this today!
- Seriously, why are you being like this now?
- That one leg isn't able to handle it.
Then another round of
Rock-Paper-Scissors.
- This is nerve wrecking.
- Rock-Paper-Scissors.
[Park Tae Hwan wins.]
Well then, I'm going to pick Kim Jong Kook.
[Chooses Jong Kook!]
Victory... victory... victory!
- That team has both of them?
- Originally...
I though Gary was fine,
but I just realized that he's injured...
Why are you saying that?
I can run!
In that case,
Park Tae Hwan's team is all set, right?
[A situation where Son Yeon Jae
needs to make her final selection.]
I was thinking of choosing
Kwang Soo...
She just asked me who she should pick,
and I told her to choose whomever she wants...
and she says that she originally wanted to
pick Kwang Soo, but he's just so bad...
[Dilemma...]
Then I... what do I do?
[Huh?]
Kwang Soo...
[Selects Kwang Soo!]
[A wrong selection
due to the stress from heat.]
[Team selection complete!]
The 3 teams... will now seriously start with
our all-star guests we have on today.
- Kwang Soo, you must be very happy?
- Yes?
Yes, I wonder if this is what
Heaven is like?
Well then...
we will now get off to a start.
- Kwang Soo... shall we go?
- Let's go!
Okay... start!
[With the Olympic heroes,
the race starts now!]
Wait a minute...
we haven't heard the rules yet.
[Too busy exchanging pleasantries.]
An important...
- You haven't heard the important rule yet.
- What can be important about a rule?
Simmer down a little.
Why are you being like that?
- Everyone move over a little.
- Yes, I understand.
Today's mission is
Four Season Training Camp Race.
[Today's mission:
Four Season Training Camp Race]
[Spring. Summer. Autumn. Winter]
[The Four Season Training Camp containing
specialties of each season starts now!]
[A shocking advantage to the team
that places first in each of the missions!]
[That's the chance to change the
size of the name tag!]
Let's do whatever we can
to make Jong Kook's large.
Park Tae Hwan and Jong Kook's.
[Frightening partnership of two power houses,
Park Tae Hwan and Kim Jong kook]
[Run across the street to 'D' amusement park
and find the Running Man landmark]
[The first Four Season
Training Camp Race mission is...]
[at the amusement park
right across the street!]
- Shall we get going?
- Let's go.
- Should we run over there?
- There's no reason to run over there.
- But it's good to get there fast.
- Getting there fast is a good thing.
Gary, let's all talk comfortably
amongst ourselves today.
It's good to see you, Tae Hwan.
- It's good to see you, Tae Hwan.
- Tae Hwan, can I lower my speech with you?
Okay, Tae Hwan.
Yeon Jae!
I remember you now!
It was you!
[It's already too late...]
- I remember now.
- You're a married man.
[A belated wash of regret...]
[Run towards the flag!]
- That's so fascinating.
- There it is!
- What's fascinating?
- That I'm here like this...
[We're fascinated too!]
We've only seen you on TV too...
I will now give you your mission.
- Your first mission is, Spring training.
- Spring?
This is an amusement park where lots of
people come out for a spring picnic.
Once you get inside,
you'll find two games have been prepared.
You have to quickly pass through those games.
Each time you pass one, you'll get a stamp.
- Okay.
- Then shall we go?
- The games have already been set?
- What are those games?
- Republic of Korea's Park Tae Hwan...
- You can feel his nervousness...
[Even though this isn't the Olympics,
entering with a bright smile on her face.]
- Have you ever been to an amusement park?
- Yes.
- What about you?
- Even when you were little?
Then have you only been swimming?
I see that you were
fit to win that gold medal.
And can we...
once we get a little closer...
- Can we call you Yeon Jae?
- Yes.
But I don't know how to
address the two of you...
[Oh my goodness...
putting on the cute act?]
[Jae Suk piling on the cute act so that
they can lower their speech to one another.]
- What are you doing?
- Why? What does it matter to you?
Why are you embarrassing us like that?
What is that?
What is this?
[Spring Event 1 - A calm swimming pool
with a water ball and a water mattress...]
[Spring Event 2 - The trampoline karaoke
room with the mike attached up high.]
Shall we do this one first?
This one?
[Selection is up to each team.]
[Only the Blue team
is heading to the swimming pool.]
80 points or above is a pass,
and extra points for choreographed dancing.
- Why don't we go first?
- Hurry it up.
Let's sing 'Apgujeong Nalnari'.
Stand under the mike here.
Sing it loudly...
Running Man's own singing show.
My goodness!
- Are you ready?
- Yes!
[Start of choreographed dancing
on top of the trampoline.]
[Their dancing showcase that's
happening right in front of their eyes.]
- Okay! Yeon Jae and Jae Suk!
- What about me?
1, 2, 3!
Come on over, beautiful you...
Have you come over to play?
[The key is to sing the song as
close you can to the mike.]
Have a drink...
- Get up front.
- Get closer to the mike.
Whenever I think of you
as the time goes by...
[Jae Suk crashes from not being
able to catch his balance.]
[Jae Suk not being able to get
back on his feet.]
Apgujong!
[The highlight is definitely...]
[Going after the extra points for the
added choreographed dance.]
[Karaoke room training that requires ultimate
physical strength and throat muscles.]
Your knee...
Good job.
What's the score?
- 5 points for the dancing.
- Okay.
- We'll say 5 points for the dancing...
- Sixty...
...one points.
[80 point to pass, but fails
with a total score of 66 points.]
And our Gary's back...
isn't very well right now.
- So he can't really be jumping.
- I'll stand here and shout as loud as I can.
Let's go with 'Because you're lovely'.
Let's go!
From the top of the head
to the tips of your toes...
You're so lovely!
The fact that you're my woman
is just so lovely!
Waiting for you is enjoyable,
and even the air tastes much sweeter.
This is all the reasons why...
I love you!
Is it over?
No, it's not over yet.
[Mistakenly thinking that it was over.]
Yeon Jae...
you know who Yoon Eun Hye is, right?
That's right... you do know.
[Of course, aren't they a couple?]
They really used to like each other.
He used to sing stuff like this to her a lot.
His song, 'One Man' came out
around then.
And 'Walking in place' was when
he and Eun Hye first started.
This was when... they were totally
head over heels in love.
Eun Hye...
- Seriously...
- Did you hear the song?
Stop it!
Your score is 74 points.
And combined with the added points
from your dancing, it's 77 points.
- So they're disqualified, right?
- Yes.
What song should we sing?
But I'm very sensitive
about being disqualified.
['Disqualified' is a taboo word...]
- Awesome...
- Do you understand what I mean or no?
Jae Suk,
give him a formal apology.
- Jae Suk, that was the wrong thing to say.
- His spirit is down now.
[Even though he's
saying it while laughing...]
I should just sew my mouth shut!
Since it's you, it's okay.
Since you said it's okay, I won't.
[Ultimate caution in front of Tae Hwan]
- Is it fun?
- Yes.
It's total hell over here!
The staff hasn't laughed even once!
- Is it fun?
- It's total chaos over here.
- Everyone is frowning over here.
Please make it fun!
That team is going to be shown
on the show too, right?
- They're being shot separately.
- Oh, really?
You know to keep your head on straight, right?
Otherwise, our segment will get cut.
[If they don't keep their head on straight,
they could be all cut out.]
[Placing first is their goal.]
Fighting!
Two of you need to get to this side
and take the other person on the mattress
and you have to take the mission given
on the other side and do it over here.
Fighting!
[Go!]
[Falling straight on top of the water.]
[A battle breaking out inside the water ball.]
Why do I keep going to the side?
[No matter how much he tries,
he just keeps on spinning in place.]
This is too hard!
[The people in this neighborhood said
they use the ball to cross the river...?]
[Is he break-dancing in there?]
Suk Jin! This is way too hard!
[Advanced only 1m in a minute...]
[The arduous training is also
the same at the karaoke room.]
[Only practicing their jumps
all this while...]
[Welcome to Running Man's
Four Season Training Camp]
Listen...
If these world class Olympic athletes
say that it's hard...
it's like death to us.
Don't you think this is just way too hard?
Even these two are finding this difficult.
- Tae Hwan...
- I'm fine.
What a joke!
What a joke that you're fine!
Hey...
he's the pride of our country!
Don't speak so rashly towards him!
Tae Hwan's not having a hard time.
Tell me now, I know that 1500m is hard too,
but what do you think of this?
Make me swim the 1500m instead.
- We're going with the number song.
- We'll take the number song.
- The number song?
- It's Yeon Jae's favorite song.
- That looks fun.
- That looks like fun.
This is the song that we all used to
sing while in elementary school.
1, 2, 3, 4!
When I can't see the second,
I feel so nervous...
[Comprehensive education that includes
numbers and gymnastics studies.]
Love you... I love you...
[Looks like fun]
Six!
[Young lady, Son Yeon Jae adorably
singing the number song.]
I like it!
[Strategy to receive high scores.]
No, no... just even at a glance,
I don't think you'll get the points needed.
I saw it Jae Suk...
I already saw the score.
- What score did we get?
- I saw the score.
[Looks like they didn't
score enough points...]
Jae Suk, I saw it...
I saw it, Yeon Jae.
I will give you extra 20 points more
your dancing.
[They sang until their throats went hoarse,
but that's how low their points are?]
- I'll give you 20 points.
- We'll wait for the score like the Olympics.
[Waiting for the score Olympic-style]
She now climbs up to fourth place.
[This is how we await our score today.]
The score is... 32 points.
We have to be happy with the results...
be happy with it.
- We have to be happy with the result.
[Since they did their best anyways,
a round of applause]
This is what Olympics was about.
'Run to you'...
'Run to you'.
- I like this song.
- Let's get this going!
[The Green team bursting
with energy]
1... 2...
1, 2, 3, 4!
[Powerful dancing!]
[The power brothers riding the
bounce.]
Tae Hwan!
Bounce, bounce, bounce, bounce!
[A lot of effort into singing too.]
[Jae Suk not able to contain his excitement.]
[Screaming out loud to the end.]
[Background dancers?]
- The choreographed dance points first.
- Yes, tell us that first.
3 points.
- 3 points. Your score is...
- I really can't do this anymore.
Seventy...
Your score is 77 points.
A total of 80 points. You pass.
[Passes with a total of 80 points!]
[With the addition of 3 points for dancing,
it's a success for the Green team!]
Yes! We did it!
[Immediate regret
after giving them the 3 points?]
Why don't we give them the points for
dancing before we leave?
- Should we?
- 5 points! 5 points.
Since it's Yeon Jae... 5 points plus
a point each from us, so 8 points.
[Extra 8 points!]
[Without anyone knowing, they've
succeeded in the swimming pool mission]
[Unable to get back to her original position
on top of the trampoline.]
- Yeon Jae, get up. Get up, Yeon Jae.
- Yeon Jae!
You're the national fairy!
[Exhaustion...]
Like how we sat the last time.
[Score receiving pose.]
You're score is...
[Since they're been given 8 points,
they need 72 points to pass]
Seventy...
If it's 71 points, it would be funny.
No, that won't be funny.
- That really wouldn't be funny.
- 71 points would be really funny.
[Yeon Jae feeling sick of the
karaoke room training.]
71 points...
that would be way too funny!
Your score is... 74 points!
74 points!
[Passes with a total of 82 points!]
[Tae Hwan inside the pool water ball.]
Don't get too nervous, okay?
Ready...
[What would be the nation's best swimmer
Park Tae Hwan's water ball skills be like?]
[Confident Olympic athlete.]
[A confident starting stance.]
[Marine boy's submersion...]
[Water is his playground...]
[But even to him,
the water ball is a new world...]
[Marine boy rolling around
on top of the water.]
[A water challenge he's facing
for the first time ever.]
[The water emperor wanting to
conquer the water.]
- After all the shouting...
- That's all he can do inside the ball.
Tae Hwan! Gather your strength!
It's okay!
Why is it so far?
Tae Hwan, what are you doing?
[Utter chaos inside the water ball.]
[Green team fails.]
The ocean's Prince...
the Marine Boy...
You're totally soaked in sweat.
- Tae Hwan...
- Running Man...
Isn't a very good program after all.
When I'm swimming the 200m,
the 5m felt like 500m...
And this is... like 100 times that.
And this isn't... all of it, right?
- There's more to come, right?
- Of course.
- This is the beginning.
The beginning?
I'm not good with starting races.
- You have your spurts, right?
- Yes, I have my spurts.
How many different courses
are there today?
Are there 3-4 courses?
- About that...
- Once I pass the second course...
[A slow starter. Confident that he'll come
guns blazing after the second course?]
Ready.
[Jae Suk takes on the water ball challenge.]
[What? So naturally...?]
[Comes crashing after a couple steps...]
[Even though he wanted to walk on water...]
[Not able to control his own body
on top of the water...]
[The Giraffe arriving at the other end
in the meantime.]
[Memorize what they're being shown,
and recite it exactly on the other side.]
Wooden pangolin? Clouded leopard?
[Jae Suk who barely made it to the other
side is also being given his statement.]
Botulinum Bad Impala?
[Back to the starting point.]
[The suddenly sunken Giraffe.]
Yeon Jae...
[Yeon Jae's paddling is splashing
the Giraffe in his face...]
I'm sorry.
We're here.
[Arrives at the starting point]
[And this person...]
And after a little while,
the interest fades too.
[A lonely battle with oneself.]
[Oh my...
he picks his wife-to-be's song!]
- I'm filming right now!
- Congratulations!
- I'm going to be a playboy for one more week!
Congratulations, sister-in-law!
[Totally off pitch...]
- And now...
- Get the lyrics right! It's my girl's song!
The more and more I love...
As more time passes...
They seem like
they're really drunk over there...
[Feels as though those people's
dinner party may have gone overboard?]
And not drink too much...
[Screaming tactic...]
I don't know this song!
[Exhausted Blank Ji.]
Please...
[And the score is?]
Why? What's wrong?
- Why? What's the score?
- Why are you laughing?
The score...
95 points.
[Wow! Passes with 95 points!]
Since you passed in first place...
You can choose one person from either
team and make their name bigger
or you can choose one person from your
own team and make the name smaller.
- Bigger. Make it bigger.
- I understand.
[The winning Blue team has chosen someone
to make their name tag larger.]
Since you completed the mission first,
you can be on your way first.
[Go to 'O' restaurant in Uijeongbu
and find the Running Man landmark.]
Let's get first place again
since we've already done it once.
The only guarantee that we have for being
on air is to keep getting first place.
Since we're going in second place,
this in no way is being late.
- Last week, I ripped off Jong Kook's name...
- Don't say things like that so rashly.
- Stop saying this like that.
- Jae Suk, then what do I say?
You just worry about yourself
since Yeon Jae's taking care of herself.
Seriously...
Kwang Soo... seriously know that
this is an honor for you today.
[A dreamlike partnership with
Rhythm Gymnastics Fairy.]
We were seriously so nervous.
Like we mentioned earlier,
when you would spin that ball around...
My hands tend to get really sweaty,
so those balls can get very slippery.
[Despite all that...]
[Yeon Jae always putting on a lovely
show with a bright smile on her face...]
- The ball would fly out of my hand...
- I can imagine...
That was so sad how the ball
slipped out of her hand like that.
At a match before the Olympics,
a ball flew out of the ring like that too.
- So...
- What do you do in a situation like that?
What do you do in the arena
when that happens?
I have to go chase after the ball,
and bring it back...
You've been doing gymnastics
since elementary school, right?
- I started it as a hobby when I was six.
- At six years old?
How did you first pick gymnastics?
We didn't know what it really was,
but my mom said that it would be pretty...
I see.
- Your coach... her impression is very...
- My Russian coach?
Yeah, your Russian Coach.
She looks very nice,
she's not very scary right?
She speaks to me in
a very calm and quiet manner.
- Very quiet...
- And tells me 'Do it again' so gently.
[Smooth criticizing style]
Even though she doesn't scold you...
- That wasn't right, so do it again...
- If you do it again, you'll be in trouble.
I'm so happy.
- I think Running Man is really fun.
- Really?
It seems more fun than just
watching it on TV.
This is just the beginning,
but we're in big trouble.
What do we do about your
name tag, Tae Hwan?
[Huh? Tae Hwan's name tag is...]
Park Tae Hwan.
Bigger.
[The Blue team has chosen to make
Tae Hwan's name tag bigger.]
I feel like I'm going to start flying now.
[An extremely enlarged Tae Hwan's
name tag.]
It's really funny seeing it from behind.
[A big laughter from looking at it
from the back.]
[Will return it back to its original size
with the next game!]
We can't ruin our world star like this.
We have to think of it as an honor to even
be in the same car with him...
The reason being...
is that Tae Hwan is a hero.
Thank you.
You know yourself that
you're great.
- To be honest, you feel that way a little?
- Well, I keep that thought to myself...
[Be humble.]
- He's the King with the endings.
- He's a warrior.
Tae Hwan, so I'm curious... what songs
do you listen to on your headphones?
Before your matches...
- Everyone is very curious about it.
- What song is it that you listen to?
There's a separate song that
I listen to only before a match.
- We're totally curious.
- What is it?
- It's a song that really energizes me.
- Oh... I see.
- To get your energy up and the rhythm...
- I think I need to come up with a fast song.
Instead of all the sad songs
filled with longing.
- What do you usually do on your time off?
- You don't drink either, do you?
This whole year, since I have had the
Olympics as my goal to work towards...
I drank once this whole past year.
That's pretty similar to me.
I only drink once a year on my birthday.
When you drank on your birthday...
You drank until you couldn't even
remember anything from it, Jong Kook.
But I think that is really admirable.
To get to your own goal...
[So admirable...
The determination to reach his goal]
- Yeon Jae seemed really excited earlier.
- She really is very pretty.
- Isn't she really pretty?
- She's really pretty.
- I do remember giving Yeon Jae an autograph.
- Really?
[What a joke...]
Don't lie.
It's Uijeongbu's Budae stew alley.
[Arrived at the mission location?]
- That sounds so good.
- Uijeongbu's Budae stew is the best!
[The home of Budae stew.]
[All the famous Budae stew's
restaurants all on one street!]
Uijeongbu!
- Budae Stew!
- Yay!
Hello!
What's this?
Hello there. Have you seen
the name tag on Park Tae Hwan?
- Yeah, we saw it.
- We made it bigger.
[Even Tae Hwan with his
king-sized wings also arrives.]
Look at your wings!
You look like you'll fly away!
Show it to us.
That's really huge!
He may fly away if we don't anchor
him down in the middle...
But you know something?
No matter which one of you wins
of the two teams...
You have to enlarge
Kim Jong Kook's name tag.
Let's not do the coalition thing here.
- I'll take care of you.
- You just take care of your own back!
- I will! Don't worry.
- Forget it!
I'm telling you this now,
but Gary is as good as not being here.
- Jong Kook, I'm sitting right here.
- Even though he is, he may as well not be...
- It really is good to hear that voice.
- We really missed you, Gary.
I missed saying 'Trying, Sir' so much that
I kept repeating it to myself at home.
This is your summer training mission.
Please take a look inside your pots.
- It's the broth style!
- It's broth, with nothing in it.
Through a series of games, the winning
team can take one ingredient at a time.
[Only one item per win.]
- So the person who wins...
- The person that wins can keep playing.
That person can keep on playing.
- There's only one type of game.
- What is it?
[Production assistant.
Nickname: Grasshopper]
- Is it Oh-mok?
- I don't think it's Oh-mok.
[The game is... Alkkagi!]
(Knocking opponent's off with yours]
Okay then, Kwang Soo!
You said you're good at this, right?
- Who would you like to play against?
- Who should I play against?
- How about Tae Hwan?
- That's right...okay.
1, 2, 3. Tae Hwan!
Tae Hwan.
I really want to rip off his wings.
- Okay, choose who'll go first.
- Paper-Rock-Scissors.
[Starting off with Kwang Soo's win.]
[Giraffe knowing to
dedicate a point on his own.]
- There's no need to flick it too hard.
- Keep your place, keep your place.
If you do it too hard, it could fly off.
That's right... that's good.
[Tae Hwan focusing on his defense.]
Kwang Soo, this is your chance.
[Giraffe succeeds at the attack!]
Why are you trying to beat
Park Tae Hwan?
[Tae Hwan's attack.]
- Do it with the one in the back.
- Just use that other one instead...
[Very chatty coaching.]
- Over here?
- Then the other one is left vulnerable.
No, no, it's okay.
[Have totally moved over to
the next table...]
[A confused and bewildered Tae Hwan.]
- He has to get that other one first.
- Hit the one I'm telling you to.
If you were to block that over there,
he won't be able to move.
You have to block him.
Move the black one over there.
[Coach Kook's meticulous strategy
being ordered out.]
Wait. One at a time.
Only one person at a time speak.
I'll speak. Tae Hwan, listen...
If you move that one over just a little bit,
he has to come that way for his move.
- So just don't get it too close to his.
- That's right. Good job.
[Just for this little move...]
That's right...
don't even worry about it.
- Please don't blow in my ear.
- I'm not blowing in your ear!
- He's so strange!
- Kwang Soo, calm down.
[Look at this guy...]
[Somehow wedging his way in...]
[Attack!]
He's good.
- No, no, no!
- No, that's good!
[It's the Coach Kook's strategy time again]
[An inner fight between the coaches?]
- Yeah, go for it.
- See? I told you!
No, if he hit it a bit harder,
it could've been good.
- I'll do it this time.
- 5, 4, 3, 2, 1...
- Let's see this!
[The precise attack succeeds!]
[Currently - White: 2, Black: 1]
- Which one?
- That one. Be ambitious!
- This one?
- Be ambitious! Be ambitious!
- You think you can do it?
- Protect your space, protect it.
Don't just nudge it,
but smack it out of there this time.
[Tae Hwan's first time with Alkkagi,
and it seems he's still not used to it.]
- Hit it towards me. Towards me.
- Don't you think the other way is better?
- What do you want me to do, Yeon Jae?
- That one.
- That way with this one?
- No.
- Then this way with that one?
- Yes.
Kwang Soo...
What to do?
[Giraffe crumbling down all on his own.]
- Kwang Soo...
- Wait, keep to your corner, Coach!
- What did you say?
- This is our corner.
- This is our Coach's box!
- Where is there such a thing here?
- Your coach box is over there.
- Who made up those rules?
- This is an international match right now.
- How is this an international match?
[Untiring Coach Kook and Coach Gae.]
That's right.
Think of it as following that line.
Kwang Soo!
[A staggering coaches' box.]
Kwang Soo, it's one.
There's just one chance.
This is a total chance.
Good. That's good, Kwang Soo.
That's not an easy position
to be attacking from.
- That's fine!
- You have a chance now, Tae Hwan!
[Now it's Tae Hwan's chance!]
Let's do this with confidence.
Move over there.
Tae Hwan, do it with confidence.
You have to oust him this time, okay?
[Attack succeeds!]
[Tae Hwan wins.]
Kwang Soo, you should've ousted him.
You should've ousted him then.
Move.
- Should we get the sausage?
- Yeah! Sausage!
[The Green team takes the sausage.]
He's a gambler.
[An ending with manners.]
- Shaking each other's hand like that.
- Ha Ha, fighting!
[Blue Team's Ha Ha takes the challenge.]
You have to keep playing.
I'm sorry,
but can you leave the ramen alone?
Yeon Jae really wants the ramen.
Let's get the ramen.
[Inconsiderate Impala...]
- There are three of us here.
- You have to win like the last time, okay?
[Ha Ha vs. Tae Hwan]
Good job, good job.
[Early exploration.]
Wait! Do it!
You have to make a play now.
- Should we make a play for it now?
- Good, good. Okay!
[Coach Kook and Coach Gae ordering
for an aggressive attack]
- Both of you please go to your coach box!
- It's because we can't see.
Do it! Make the attack now!
[Oh no... a miss!]
[Ha Ha with the opportunity]
Don't you think
the middle one would be better?
[Attack succeeds!]
[Ha Ha ahead by one!]
- The middle one.
- Go for the middle one.
[Coach Kook ordering a drastic attack.]
Hit it all the way!
Hit that white out of there!
Trust it! Trust it and go!
[Misses again!]
That shot was a little weak.
[A black and white bead
are both out!]
[Ha Ha is still ahead.]
- It could turn over at any moment.
- Wait...
Attack!
Tae Hwan, attack that one!
- You startled me.
- You have to attack! Attack it now!
- That totally scared me.
- I'm sorry.
[The endless forceful orders.]
The way you're standing
really looks like a coach's stance.
Let's go.
That one is pretty easy, so it's okay.
[The attack succeeds!]
[Loud cheers.]
[Dramatically coming to a tied score.]
- You have to attack, Ha Ha.
- Can I spin this around?
- No, no! No, you can't.
- Ha Ha, go to the other side.
[The match with one bead left
on each side]
Tae Hwan...
The static...
it keeps getting staticky.
- Attack it, that's right. It's the last one.
- You're going to be out, out.
You're going to fling it out of there,
fling it out of there.
[Just what...]
[Attack misses!]
[Green Team - Tae Hwan wins!]
What the heck?
I thought you said you were confident!
Yeon Jae's on our team...
but why do you keep pushing her back?
Come over this way, this way.
Let's leave the ramen out.
Ramen is for Yeon Jae...
[Tae Hwan's consideration for Yeon Jae.]
Why? I want ramen...
[Gary wanting to eat his ramen...]
- What should we do?
- Let's take the vegetables.
- That's what we need.
- Just give us some plain rice.
- You're really good!
- It's our turn this time, right?
I'll take a chance.
[Red Team - Jae Suk]
Jae Suk this time...
you have to get the ramen this time.
- No... Tae Hwan is on a real streak right now.
- We'll do the Rock-Paper-Scissors to start.
- Rock-Paper-Scissors.
- Attack, Jae Suk. Start off attacking.
- You have to take it out from the start.
- You have to win this time.
[Will it be the undisputed
Lord of catching up, Jae Suk...]
[Or a world champion in the making,
Park Tae Hwan?]
[Start of the showdown!]
It's going to fly off.
100% guaranteed, it's going to fly off.
[Coach Kook and Coach Gae
mentally shaking him.]
- Hurry! He's waiting for his turn!
- Wait... who the heck is Nala?
- Go for the left one.
- Use the left to go for the middle one.
- That's right!
- Pass it, pass it, pass it.
It passed!
[Complete success of Coach Kook
and Coach Gae's mental shakedown?]
[Current score - 2:3]
- Just tap the one in the middle.
- That's right. That was good.
Kwang Soo...
attack is the best line of defense.
That's right... it's going to fly off,
it's going to fly off.
[Marine boy embarrassed of his
Coach Kook and Coach Gae?]
Olympic athlete gets the same pressure.
[Ever untiring obstructive energy.]
Okay, that's good.
Let's go for a win.
[A drastic order of attack.]
Go for that white one.
It'll be okay. Go for it.
That's right!
[Current score - 1:3.
Tae Hwan with the advantage!]
[His behind...?]
What else am I supposed to do?
I only have one left!
You're going to make Yeon Jae
uncomfortable.
- It's going to fly off, it's going to fly off
- It's going to fall, it's going to fall.
[Brimming over with confidence with his
behind style, he succeeds?]
[Current score - 1:2.
Tae Hwan with the advantage!]
That's right.
Let's go hit that one.
[Jae Suk's turn again]
It's okay, it's going to fly off.
It's going to fly off.
[The relentless obstruction engine.]
I can't have a mental breakdown
right now.
- It's going to fall off, fall off.
- You're going to hit it too hard, hit it hard.
[Concentrating again and succeeding!]
[Score is now even!]
[The win balances on the last bead...]
Hit it off the board.
That's right!
[Attack succeeds!]
[Dance of victory?]
[Overflowing joy from the victory.]
[Looks as though he may become a
world champion in Alkkagi too!]
- What is this?
- Tae Hwan, what is this dance?
He's way too good.
He's unbeatable.
[Ultimately taking over
the rest of the ingredients]
I think Tae Hwan realized too...
what support we are from the background.
It really is...
It's Park Tae Hwan who did a good job,
why are you taking the credit?
I understand why coaches are so happy
when their athletes do well.
- That feeling.
- Wow... that really is awesome.
- Can we eat now?
- You may go ahead.
[Green team with all the ingredients.]
I apologize...
but we're going to go ahead and eat.
That looks really good.
[Red Team has ham stew.]
- It's good.
- It's yummy.
- This really is good even with just the ham.
- The broth itself is really good.
This kimchee is really good too.
[Blue team without any ingredients puts in
their only side dish, the kimchee...]
- What?
- Why are you staring?
- I'm looking outside.
- Really?
- Yeah.
If ours is this good,
I wonder how good theirs is.
[Curious about the Green team's stew
with all the ingredients.]
[Even though he feels bad, a win is a win.]
[The winning Green team's choice is?]
[Return Tae Hwan's name tag
to its original size.]
- How did you go around with this on your back?
- How did you stand it?
[The next mission card...]
[Go to the indoor ice rink in Uijeongbu
and find the Running Man landmark.]
- I have a very good feeling right now.
- I feel much lighter right now.
Wow... but we really did return your name tag
like we said we would. That's not easy to do.
- I know.
- The truth is, we haven't done anything.
- Tae Hwan did everything.
- No, I didn't.
- I was so surprised, how are you so good?
- I was worried since I've never played before.
- If you think positively, it happens.
- You're right, that's right.
[I really learned a lot about
hope and affirmation this time.]
You're right, Tae Hwan.
[400m competition
Tae Hwan reaching first place with ease.]
[But an absurd...]
Oh! Park Tae Hwan has been disqualified!
How did this happen?
What is going on?
I think we need to look into this.
I haven't done anything wrong.
Nothing was confirmed about what happened,
and something was off and strange.
The truth is... there's never been
a reverse in scoring before.
There's never been a history of it.
- So you had hope that it wouldn't...
- Yes, I hadn't done anything wrong.
So as soon as I was out, I watched the
video in case I did something wrong.
- But... I didn't.
- You didn't make any mistakes?
I don't know what's going on.
So we put our first formal objection in...
but they wouldn't accept it.
So with Director Michael and
Coach Duncan that I trained with in Australia
I showed the video and kept pointing out
that I didn't do anything wrong.
- So they accepted the 2nd formal objection?
- Yes, they accepted it at 3:30.
I was originally told that I'd get an answer
by 2:30, so I waited up the whole time.
I needed to manage my schedule...
Even though I should've in preparation for
the next day, all I could do was wait.
So I kept telling myself that things are
going to be fine and waited until 3:30.
It was finally reversed at 3:30.
Then normally...
once you finish the first round
what do you normally do until the next round?
What process do you go through?
Once the match is over and if I had won
to go on to the next round
I would do the warm up again to
relax my muscles and get massages too...
- and refuel myself with food too...
- Right, right...
But the truth is...
I didn't have the motivation to do it.
When Tae Hwan came on for the finals,
I could tell by the expression on his face...
Like he wanted to show them something...
like 'you all just wait and see.'
[Only with firm resolution and mentality,
Tae Hwan was able to stand again at the line.]
[And his energetic performance...]
His start is very good.
Based on that situation,
the score I received was so valuable.
After seeing that, I drank so much
that I didn't even get to watch the results.
[The nausea induced by drinking...]
[Proud of you, Marine boy...]
[Green team is the first to arrive
at the ice rink.]
I think this is it.
[What training will happen
at the ice rink in this late summer?]
- Hello.
- Hi.
Go home and study.
[First entering the rink in warmer clothing.]
[There seems to be quite a crowd
gathered here to watch.]
[Countless people who came to watch
after hearing of the world stars' training.]
Kim Jong Kook!
[A sincere greeting to all the fans that
came out to greet them enthusiastically.]
[The red team also arrives soon thereafter.]
[An even more enthusiastic crowd
with the arrival of the gymnastics fairy!]
[I'm here too.]
[Yoo Jae Suk! Yoo Jae Suk!]
[Marine Boy going along with the beat.]
[Thank you for your enthusiastic greeting.]
As mentioned,
this is your winter training.
The game is, human curling.
Two people get in the buckets,
and one person pushes.
The team that gets closest to the
finish line at the end is the winner.
Since the Green team arrived here first,
they'll walk over to the second round.
Let's go!
Please decide which team
will push first.
- We'll go later.
- No, we'll go later.
- How do we decide this?
- Let's play Rock-Paper-Scissors.
- Yeon Jae.
- Rock-Paper-Scissors.
[Yeon Jae easily succeeds.]
- All three people should do it.
- Let's just end it with one person.
If you were going to be like this,
you should've given Yeon Jae an autograph.
I gave you an autograph, right?
- Where was it?
- It was at her elementary school.
[Coach Kook stepping in since the
decision is taking too long.]
Let's do this quickly!
[Slipping in front of the whole crowd!]
That really hurts!
[In situations like this, the
embarrassment comes before pain.]
- Applaud!
- It's okay, it's okay...
[A rare moment of seeing
Mr. Capable fall.]
This is nerve-wrecking.
It's nerve wrecking enough with just us,
but it's more so with all these people here.
- Fighting!
- Applaud!
[Conceding - Red Team first to step up.
First up is Yeon Jae.]
[The other two have to push the bin to
get it close to the line when they stop.]
[Allowed to use props to help
the bin slide.]
You have to do it from the front.
[Red team Yeon Jae - Start!]
That was too strong!
[Before the bucket stops,
start working the ice!]
[Approaching the finish line!]
[Just how close to the finish line will the
gymnastics fairy be able to stop?]
[Wow! Amazing!]
[Precisely on top of the finish line!]
[Red team dominating with
their first attempt with Yeon Jae.]
- Didn't they go over the line?
- If Yeon Jae goes over a little, it's over.
[Green team's athlete and the coaches falling
into the competitive mode right away.]
What do I do now?
When they get close to you,
push them off lightly with your feet.
If they come close, don't feel bad
and push them off with your feet.
Get them with your feet!
[Blue team's first up is Ace Ji Hyo!]
[An energetic start.]
[It's starting off smoothly...]
[He should've just stood still,
why be a nuisance?]
Suk Jin!
What are you doing? Suk Jin!
Hurry up and push her!
[Ji Hyo, needs to slide over a little more...]
[Nuisance to the end.]
[Ultimately stopping
far away from the finish line.]
What is this?
Just what is this?
[This time, it's the
Red team's second runner's turn]
[The second runner is Yoo-Ruce Willis.]
Yoo Jae Suk, Yoo Jae Suk!
[Advantageous to protect Yeon Jae
and kick Ji Hyo out of the way.]
Hey, Ji Hyo!
Push him out of the way!
Push him and push yourself
in the process.
[Heading straight towards Ji Hyo!]
[Push her out?]
[Ace Ji Hyo grabbing onto him!]
[With savvy planning, pushing herself
right onto the finish line!]
[That is Ace Ji Hyo!]
[Red team's Yeon Jae and Blue team's Ji Hyo
currently almost at the same spot]
[While the competition
for the win is going on.]
[Giraffe using the interlude
for his ice ballet show.]
[It's beautiful...]
[But that's enough.]
[Second runner for the Blue team
is Big-nosed brother.]
- Over here, over here.
- Be careful, Yeon Jae!
- What do I have to do?
- Push him away with your foot.
- Then I'll be pushed off the line.
- That's true...
Yeon Jae, I'm sorry!
I'm going to attack you!
[Big-nosed brother looking to come out
attacking Yeon Jae]
Nothing else to do but push me
really hard.
- Push me hard towards Yeon Jae.
- I'm really scared.
[Big-nosed brother headed
straight towards Yeon Jae!]
[If he could push Yeon Jae off the line,
then the Blue team goes to the next round!]
[He's going!]
[Ah! He pushed Yeon Jae off!]
[Only Ji Hyo remains
directly on top of the finish line.]
[Pushed precisely...
and pushed off precisely]
[Blue team off to the next round!]
Yeon Jae says she wants to
try it too.
Yeon Jae's putting the knee-pads on
because she wants to try it too.
Is it fun?
It's totally fun.
[Smiling at the thought of
playing around.]
- Try it. Just kneel down.
- Just kneel down.
Isn't it fun?
You have to fling your arms back.
What do I do? I can't stop.
I can't stop.
What are you so happy about?
You're liking it too much!
[Embarrassed...]
[Curling - Final Match]
[Blue team vs. Green team]
[Coach Kook and Athlete Park
in the midst of strategizing.]
[Will they be able to pull off a miracle like
with Alkkagi a little while earlier?]
[First runner for the Green team
is Gary.]
[Starting off with caution.]
Kang Gary! Kang Gary!
Good, good.
[Mr. Capable is definitely weak
when it comes to ice...]
[So embarrassing.]
[Stopping at rather a far distance
away from the finish line.]
- Are you doing that on purpose?
- Are you falling down on purpose?
I thought you were
a spinning top or something.
[Tiger loses his strength if
he strays too far from earthen soil.]
This is really driving me crazy.
Wait here.
I'll go tell him what to do.
[Athlete Park's coaching time.]
Grab onto her and spin yourself.
As soon as she gets close enough to you,
grab onto her and push yourself off.
[It looks like Ji Hyo's
heading from the Blue team.]
Tae Hwan, I'm pretty weak
when it comes to Ji Hyo.
[Blue team's first runner, Ace Ji Hyo.]
Hard, hard. In his direction.
Nice!
- Nice!
- Grab her! Grab her!
[Heading straight towards Gary!]
What?
[These two getting up close for the
first time in a long time.]
[Holding on tightly to her wrists.]
I'm going to stay next to you.
I'm going to stay right next to you!
[Now it's Gary
who's close to the finish line!]
I did it because I wanted to
keep her right next to me!
You're not supposed to
grab like that!
[So what?]
The last one is what's important.
[Coach Kook and Athlete Park
in a strategizing session again.]
- The other team is going to try to push...
- Aren't you guys taking too long?
- Jong Kook...
- Is this the Olympics or something?
What's taking you so long?
It's because I have a lot of resentment
over the Olympics right now!
Just leave us alone!
[Ah, yes...]
I finally found someone who
I can relate to!
[Coach Kook finally meeting
his soul mate.]
You two really do fit each other well.
[Competitiveness and quick temper
all match each other very well.]
Hey!
[Continuing with the strategizing
instead of the actual competition.]
[Even though they say they get it,
going back to whispering...]
That's good.
[Finally, the Green team's second runner
Jong Kook gets on his way!]
[Huh? Heading towards Gary?]
Push me, push me! Okay.
[With Gary's push,
right on top of the finish line!]
Why? Where do you want to go?
Why are you doing this?
You can't turn yourself around!
You can't turn!
- He can! He can!
- What do you mean, he can?
- He can't!
- He can! He can!
- He can't! He can't!
- We're saying he can't!
- We're saying he can!
[Anyways, the last runner for the
Blue team, Big-nosed brother.]
Just push.
Mr. Capable, you just wait!
[With this one push, the winner for
Winter Training will be decided!]
Let's go, let's go. Straight!
Okay! Good!
[If he can only push off Mr. Capable,
it's victory!]
[The goal!]
- You got it, you got it!
- You're going to get it!
[Big-nosed brother vs. Mr. Capable]
[Mr. Capable's attempt at defense
knocks both of them down?]
We won! We won!
[In this case,
how is a winner judged?]
[A quick announcement of the results.]
[Suk Jin and Jong kook both disqualified
for falling out of the buckets.]
Ji Hyo is closest to the line.
[The Blue team wins the winter training!]
[Looks as though the winning team is
going to make someone's name tag bigger.]
We're going to make Kim Jong Kook's
name tag larger.
- Wait a minute...
- We're going to make Kim Jong Kook's larger.
What?
The truth is... Yeon Jae kept
hoping for that in the car too.
[Jong Kooks name tag gets exchanged
for the gigantic one]
Yeon Jae, you can rip it off later.
You can fly off.
[Will his wings make him fly,
or will they get broken off?]
[The last training camp,
'H' Island in Pocheon.]
[What will be the mission here
to decide the victor?]
Running Man's training camp.
[Ripping off the name tag.]
[Find the water bottle and exchange
it for 00 at the witches' house]
[Find the water bottle and
exchange it.]
I'm going to have to find it no matter what.
I think it can change our name tag size.
- Where are the water bottles?
- You want us to find the water bottles?
[The bottom line is to rip off the name tags.
The team to survive to the end wins.]
However,
when you find the water bottle...
Excuse me...
Who were you just shooting?
[Jae Suk's VJ, Kwon Yeol
is only shooting Yeon Jae.]
Who were you just shooting?
[Even though he gets scolded,
the camera goes back to Yeon Jae.]
Seriously...
You really shouldn't be doing that
with your wedding coming up.
- Just because she's on...
- That's no good.
[But still, only Yeon Jae...]
[Before going around ripping off name tags,
find the mysterious water bottles first.]
You can be ousted quickly today.
No matter what,
we'll make you the winner today.
Where were we supposed to go
with the water bottles?
- The witches house...
- We're supposed to exchange it for something.
Exchange it for something
with the witch, right?
Where are these water bottles?
No!
No! You startled me!
You really scared me!
[So cute!]
You scared me...
you really scared me!
- So this is how it's done...
- Yeah, you have to be careful.
Are the water bottles hidden
just anywhere?
- They're just hidden anywhere?
- They should be around here somewhere.
- This one? This?
- Seriously?
[That's a plain water bottle...]
That's just a real water bottle.
- So what am I looking for?
- It'll be like a magic water bottle.
The herbal scent is so nice.
Look at all the herbs here!
I'm getting a feeling here.
Wow... look at all this.
Suk Jin... it's all over!
Water bottles are all over!
[Water bottles all over the place.]
What is this?
Water bottles are everywhere!
I'm going to have to find it quickly.
I'm sure there's one here.
I'm sure of it.
[Yeon Jae is searching at the bakery.]
There's nothing here.
What's this?
[A suspicious chest under the bread?]
[A treasure chest?
Then does it mean there's a bottle inside?]
Is this a dud?
[Ha Ha's carrying around
a treasure chest too...]
We're on the same side.
You can have this.
[Huh? Handing it off to Giraffe
so easily like that?]
We are one.
- Thank you, Ha Ha.
- It's been awhile.
Bye, (traitor) believer.
We're of the same.
The name is... (Traitor) Believer.
- Believer, see you later.
- Okay, Ha Ha.
[Experts of betrayal and political games
are going to work together?]
Shin-Ja-Cross!
[Dud]
[That's more like it...]
[Icons of betrayal acknowledging
one another.]
Hello.
- You're here.
- Hello.
[Stopping their awful behavior with
the appearance of innocent Yeon Jae.]
- I found this.
- I found it too, but it was a dud.
Really? Then I'll see you later,
Yeon Jae.
- Okay.
- Believer... see you later.
[You just wait and see.]
Just where the heck is it?
Where are you going?
It would probably be better not to
acknowledge each other for the time being.
Where are you going, little groom?
I'm going to the herb garden, why?
- Really?
- No, no.
- I'll go on my own.
- I'll come too.
- Why don't you go over there?
- Since I've already been there, I'll go here.
- I was the one who came here first.
- You...
Would you like to come with me,
or should I go on by myself?
I'm going to go by myself.
Wait...
[Ultimately going up together...]
Oh my goodness! Here!
It's here!
[This is...]
[where a 600 year-old witch...]
[...performs magic with
the mysterious water bottles.]
[This is the witches' house.]
So this is where we bring the water?
- Scary...
- What are you doing, Dong Wan?
- Go find the potion.
- So this is it.
- What happens when we find it?
- So this is the place.
[Anyways, these two have found the
location of the witch's house.]
Is there only one potion?
I'm sure you'll find that out
once you find any.
[Something will happen here if they bring
the mysterious water bottles.]
[On the other hand, at the same time...]
[Giraffe working hard to find
the mysterious water bottles.]
[Discovers a deeply hidden
treasure chest!]
[There it is!
The mysterious water bottle!]
Did you find it?
[I found it.]
[Giraffe feeling as though
he's taken over the world.]
Did you find it?
[Water bottle with blue liquid inside.]
Where are we going?
What did I tell you, Yeon Jae?
I told you that I'd make you win.
Fighting.
[They have to hurry and take it
to the witch's house...]
- You know where to take this?
- Over there... second floor?
- Where?
- Come here.
Can we all go together?
I feel so weird!
[Giraffe feeling high-spirited after
finding the water bottle.]
I haven't found any chests.
I wasn't like this from the beginning either.
A year... or two...
And ultimately, this is how...
[Giraffe wanting to look like a man
in front of Yeon Jae.]
[Has no one found any water bottles yet?]
- Oh my goodness...
- What is this?
[All of Red team members arrive
at the witch's house.]
- You're here.
- I found the mysterious potion.
You can pour it in here.
Yeon Jae...
[Yeon Jae fascinated by PD Dong Wan
whom she's only seen on TV.]
- What is it?
- Which bottle did you find?
- It's the blue liquid.
- The blue liquid? Give it to me.
- Your acting's gotten much better.
- This is so funny.
You were so bad in the beginning.
- Okay, I'll make it for you.
- What? Make what?
[The cauldron changing to a blue hue!]
- I made this about 300 years ago...
- What a joke!
What a joke.
Throw in a snake...
- What are you doing?
- And a frog...
Just hold on.
I'm making it right now.
[Just what will the blue potion be
made into?]
[A gigantic name tag!]
[This is the power of the blue potion.]
[The short lived excitement...
what the heck is this?]
- I'm ruined.
- We need to find another one for Kwang Soo.
[Giraffe with wings...
what will become of his fate?]
[On the other hand,
the Tiger with wings...]
[In the midst of having
a conversation with the birds.]
There's a mirror in there too.
They must look in the mirror.
Where is Jong Kook with
his big wings?
Hey!
Oh! There's Jong Kook!
- I've been all over the place.
- We haven't found any.
There's nothing.
I've searched down there
and all the way up there too.
But I ran into Kwang Soo,
so I ran out of there.
There's nothing over there.
I never even dreamed that I would be
running away from Kwang Soo.
Walking around with this by myself
was really scary.
Seriously, this is the first time
I've felt this way.
Don't do that and
just follow behind us.
Even a tiger who's lost all its teeth
is still a tiger.
- That's right.
- No matter how Impala and the Giraffe...
- Even the tiger without its teeth...
- The important thing is...
Somehow all of a sudden,
I'm leading our group right now.
[The only realistic pillar today
is Tae Hwan.]
There he is... there he is.
He's on the boat.
Look at Kwang Soo's name tag!
Kwang Soo's name tag is
bigger now too!
He found the wrong bottle!
So inside those chests must be
name tags!
- Don't open those chests then, I'll open it.
- Okay.
Be careful, Kwang Soo.
Be careful.
Kwang Soo, be careful.
[Green team eyeing Kwang Soo
and closing in on him.]
[Since they're already in this state,
thinking of eliminating Kwang Soo first.]
[If I stay like this, I'll be caught!]
Kwang Soo... before you're
caught, run. Run! Run!
Kwang Soo! Kwang Soo! Run!
[Tae Hwan starting to chase
after Kwang Soo!]
[The ultimate speed out of anyone
who's guest appeared on Running Man!]
Kwang Soo! Run quickly!
Kwang Soo!
- Kwang Soo!
- Jae Suk!
[Easily passes Kwang Soo's VJ
who was ahead of him]
[This is... Marine Boy, Park Tae Hwan's
athletic abilities!]
[No way! Easily capturing the Giraffe!]
Tae Hwan... why are you so fast?
[After running like that,
he doesn't even seem out of breath!]
Since we've all seen what he can do now...
let's all go look for the water bottles.
I had to run all the way here,
and all the staff had to run too...
Don't you think one person
should be sacrificed?
What do you mean, sacrifice?
How can you ask that of him?
Then why don't you sacrifice yourself?
[The Red team insisting they can't sacrifice
themselves in order to protect Yeon Jae.]
Why don't we eliminate the
Blue team first?
Will the two of you..
cut us a break just this once?
Come on, just give us a break.
It was so hard with these large wings.
Jong Kook's in the same boat.
It's hard for him too.
But with the earth's tiger...
and the king of the ocean...
seriously, how can we beat that?
- Let's get rid of the blue team first...
- I've watched this show a lot...
And Kwang Soo always uses this ploy
and stabs you in the back later.
- He's been doing that the most lately!
- No, he's changed a lot.
- He does that the most lately.
- No, he really has changed a lot.
Just once... the next time this happens,
we will...
Okay then... for now, for Jae Suk,
both of you can go...
[Generous man, Tae Hwan
releasing both Jae Suk and Kwang Soo.]
[Just what result will this release bring?]
Thank you, Jong Kook.
I feel like there's something here.
[Blue team's Haroro urgently
searching for the water bottle.]
[Discovers a mysterious chest
at a suspicious location!]
[A red potion?]
This red color is making me nervous.
I feel like I'm the main character
here today.
It's just been so long
since I've found anything...
[But it seems like it's the safest place...]
[Heads to the witch's house
that he discovered earlier!]
His name tag could get
bigger too. Wait.
[Ha Ha arrives at the witch's house
with the red potion.]
Come this way.
[A red potion!]
Red potion, oh...!
- Good choice.
- Is it bad or good?
- Just tell me if it's good or bad.
- We'll see once we pour this in.
[The cauldron turns red as soon as
the red potion is poured in!]
I really love Running Man.
It's like the fairy tales!
This is just so cool!
I think he found a red potion.
This potion is a weapon...
I made it about 500 years ago,
and it's called pinch out.
Pinch out?
Even if your name tag is ripped off,
the person you pick is the one ousted.
[Even if his name tag gets ripped off,
it's the person he chooses who'll get ousted.]
Even if your name tag is ripped off,
the person you pick is the one ousted.
Now choose the person that
you want ousted.
- Is it just one person?
- You can only choose one person.
[He can only choose one person.]
[Who's the one that will get ousted
when Ha Ha's name tag gets ripped off?]
Park Tae Hwan.
[Ha Ha chooses Tae Hwan to be the one
that gets sacrificed in his place!]
[Tae Hwan, I'm sorry...
but I'm going to have to sacrifice you.]
- Ah, but that one is unavailable.
- What?
[Park Tae Hwan's out is
already sold out?]
[Someone already took that one?]
Someone already came and bought that one.
[Someone has already been here
with the red potion?]
I made about 500 of them at first,
but there aren't many left now.
[Then in this case,
who should I pick instead of Tae Hwan?]
Now, please choose who you'd
like to oust.
Okay...
Yoo...
Yoo Jae Suk?
- Yoo Jae Suk.
- Yoo Jae Suk?
[That awful!]
[Ha Ha chooses Yoo Jae Suk
to be ousted in his place!]
I knew he'd do that.
I knew he'd do that!
Throw in a grasshopper...
Okay...
It's coming out from the bottom,
so please retrieve it.
You can put that on your back now.
I can put it on for you.
So when I get ousted,
he'll get ousted with me?
- No, you yourself won't be ousted.
- So only he will be ousted?
[If Ha Ha's name tag is ripped off once,
only Jae Suk will be ousted]
Please turn around.
You over there (Jae Suk)...
I'm sure you'll be really mad next week.
You're going to be really mad
if you watch this broadcast.
[Putting in Yoo Jae Suk's marker
behind his own name tag.]
[This is how another change on
the road to victory has been made.]
[Next week's preview]
Subtitles by DramaFever
Don't be nervous,
don't be nervous, okay?
I knew he'd do that...
I knew he'd do that!
All you have to do is rip mine off.
I'm so mad right now..
and I have to keep him alive...
Rip mine! Rip mine off!
Let's fight! Why are you walking away!
You just stand back there
and don't get involved.
Jong Kook!
- Come here, come here!
- Kwang Soo!
[The herbivores in utter chaos.]
[An endless fantasy.]
This seriously is the best!
- Please oust a member of the blue team.
- Who?
[A merciless battle.]
- You get out of the way.
- Choose who you want to oust.
[A predetermined fate...
just what will...]