It's really daebak.
A head on confrontation.
Let's duke it out in one round, coolly.
Guys, where are you?
We don't have time to look at this. This is glass.
If we're caught it's all over.
-This is a cruel place. -Where exactly are the real scratch cards?
Have you seen Jiyong?
Have you seen GD?
Why did you tear mine off?
You won't even let me listen, you won't let me talk.
-I can't even go where I want to. -He tore mine off, Gwang Soo.
It's T.O.P! T.O.P. is running!
Catch him!
Running Man, manse!
HaHa hyung...
-Somehow I feel... -We were toyed with.
Humiliated.
You've brought humiliation unto me.
Oh, we're first right?
Just bring the flag in please.
-Once you enter, you'll be given instructions. -Is this the place?
What?
We should have been hiding in this sort of building.
It's so big.
It's so big inside.
We have to win this time.
-Yes. -Please listen carefully.
It's the second half.
Because you defended in the first half, this time you'll be attaching.
Similarly, you will put on bells and chase your opponents.
The difference in the second half is that he'll give you walkie-talkies.
The walkie-talkies can only he used amongst yourselves.
But, the Defence Team will also have walkie-talkies.
Because this is place is too big for attacking.
Hey, I told you we should do it first.
Starting from here on the first floor to the twelfth floor.
Can they all be used?
You and your...
-What do we do -This is really too big...
-That's why we should I have attacked first. -Exactly. I was too careless.
And if you see HaHa"hyung, you have to radio me.
Don't forget.
-Why don't we go one floor at a time? -Did anything happen between you guys?
- Firstly, firstly let's... - Huh? Well, earlier HaHa hyung...
Toyed with me.
-Where's Jiyong, Ji Hyo? -Oppa!
Where the heck did he go?
Where is he?!
-Jiyong. -Hyung!
Have you seen GD, GD?
He brought humiliation unto me.
Also...
Summoning by rings,
If the team members wear the rings and shout out the incantation, one person from the opposing team can be summoned.
What do we do with this?
The rings look like the real deal.
Firstly, let's wear the rings.
These magical rings.
Summoning?
After we put these on... how to summon them?
The power of the five rings will control space,
Put the rings together,
Put your hands with the rings together.
Call out each of your names.
Call out your own names.
If you memorize this incantation, you shout out the name of the person,
For example, if you just call out Too Jae Suk' then the member you want will just appear in front of you.
-However this can only be used on one person...? -Yes. only once,
This has to be used well.
Maybe, we should practice it?
If you can't memorize this incantation accurately. the summons won't be activated either.
Each of you shout out your name.
Tae Yang.
Seung Ri.
Dae Sung.
G-Dragon.
T.O.P.
The power of the five rings put together will control space.
Will control.
1, 2, 3
The power of the five rings put together will control space.
Kim Jong Kook!
Next we ll just surround him like this.
If you do it like this now, the incantation won t work.
-you have to do it properly. -Yes, I got it.
-Everyone has to shout it out maturity tor it to work. -Ok!
If you feel ashamed you don't have to use it.
We're more ashamed after losing.
Tae Yang.
Seung Ri.
GD.
Dae Sung.
Top.
The power of the five rings will control space.
Yah!
I didn't even do this sort of thing in elementary school.
-if you feel ashamed you don't have to use it. -Okay!
Dh, okay.
We'll use it in a do-or-die stage.
-We can go, right? We can go? -Yes.
-A friend, a friend -Stop it!
I got it.
We better get inside quickly.
-Wow, bells. -Hey, there are walkie-talkies.
-Hey! -Must you do that?
There's no need.
What are these? Authorization pads?
-What is it? -Authorization pads?
What is it?
But aren't we being chased?
Avoid the Attacking Team with bells and obtain 5 signatures!
What did you say?
This is very difficult.
How do we get this one by one?
-This can be brought along by everyone or conirmation. -And then?
Find 5 person with these Running Man Paper and get their signatures with these pens.
If you bring one back without this.
Or if this paper isn't used, it's invalid. Even if it's already been signed.
-Don't you want us to bring them back? -Inside .your pocket.
Inside a pocket.
-Hey, don't the people we're looking for have pens? -Hey, this is an authorization pen.
Let's take the elevator up first.
It's very flimsy right?
-Hey, tear off Gwang Soo's before starting. -Hey, stop all the backstabbing.
We will be giving a handicap to the Running Men who have extra members.
Please choose two people.
-We will choose the Jong Kook hyung and... -Jong Kook and Ji Hyo are the best.
-Okay. -No way.
Gwang Soo hyung.
-Ah no way! -The tiger, the tiger.
Don't tremble.
-It's not like you're holding hands with a girl. Why are your hands trembling? -I'm uncomfortable.
Guys.
You haven't found them?
Don't be like this.
Not letting me listen, not letting me talk. Wang Soo.
-Not even letting me go where I want to. -This guy tore mine off, Gwang Soo.
Really?!
-Tear off Gwang Soo's before starting. -Stop all the backstabbing.
Jong Kook, start by tearing Gwang Soo's off.
Oh hyung, I'll see how it goes.
-I like us like this. -What?
-It's weird. -So embarrassing.
Two men.
Let's go.
Everyone, fighting. Fighting today.
Thing like this aren't needed, 'fighting' doesn't have to be said.
Authorization signatures.
Would you have that authorization signature?
Is it you?
Please give me an autograph.
Please give me your signature.
You have to sign for me.
You're not the one with the authorization signature now, right?
You don't have it right, the authorization pad?
-You don't have it right? You don't? -I don't have it.
You acted look like you do.
-I was really surprised. I even thought you had. -Because I wanted your autograph.
Hello. Please give me your authorization signature.
-It's not me. -It's not?
Yes. it's not me.
You've worked hard.
-Please give me your authorization signature. -Okay.
-On a memo pad... -Huh?
Ah. I'm really...
Hey, don't open the door so hastily.
Can't you do it carefully?
We have to be quiet now and you open the door so loudly like this, what do we do?
There are bell sounds.
Hyung, help me out with this.
No, like this.
I don't hear the sounds of bells.
Hyung.
You didn't confirm it and continued searching?
-Hello. -Hello.
I am going to look around for a bit.
Okay.
Ah! Found one on the 10th floor, found one on the 10th floor.
Excuse me.
Is Manager Oh Se Min going somewhere?
Ah, manager Oh Se Min!
Manager Oh.
Please sign this for me.
-You found the authorization pad? -Yes. Please give me your signature.
How did you find this?
We're experts in finding things.
You really are an expert.
Thank you!
-Ok I'll write my name. -Yes.
-I'll sign it. -Ok.
Thank you so much Manager Oh. I wish you luck.
Fighting!
Work hard!
They can be hiding somewhere in-a place like this.
Aren't there too many places to hide though?
Someone is there?
Wow there really are a lot of places to hide.
There's a lot of places.
HaHa hyung.
Just wait.
You probably think that you let me go easily, but...
I really...
Felt humiliated.
You've insulted me.
Let's split into two.
-Hyung! -What now?
Hyung, this is the 1st floor isn't it?
So...
Let's split into two groups.
-Thatls right! -With this part and...
-Mission is 20% complete. -The other part...
We have to hurry up.
This is too hard, hyung!
Mission is 20% complete!
Right now...
My heart is racing.
If the kids appear, don't try to escape.
Then what?
-What? -If I don't escape, then what should I do?
I've never done anything but escape.
-Please give us the authorization signature -Oh! Hello.
-Please give us the authorization signature -Which authorization signature?
Ah, excuse us.
That... you know that thing.
What is it?
We're on the same team.
Spy, spy.
-Spy? -Aren't you?
She really isn't a spy.
-Doesn't look like she is. -Then... what are you doing?
What are you saying!
She's working!
-Sorry. -Sorry.
There should be one on this floor.
Hello.
Excuse us but we came to look for authorization pads.
Sorry, no.
Oh, okay.
It's not here.
Close the door, close the door.
If I come out then you should close the door immediately!
Hyung Nim...
If you're going to suddenly stop then please say something.
Please say something.
Oh Gwang Soo!
Gwang Soo, you...
He said TOP is on the third floor! 3rd floor TOP!
-What? -The 3rd floor! 3rd floor!
Suk Jin hyung is there, on the 3rd floor.
Hyung, you can't go to the third floor!
Hyung, where are you going?
What happened to Ji Hyo?
Hyung, do this for me please.
-What type of hat... -Please snap this.
-Are there one or two? -There are bells on the 10th floor!
-10th floor. -10th floor, 10th floor!
One person on the 10th, one person on the 3rd.
They must be starting from the bottom and coming up.
Ah, from below and above?
Be careful.
This is so intricately done.
-The last solution is.. -Be quiet!
-Jong Kook. -Yeah?
Look after him and treat him well.
The last solution is...
Fight fire with fire!
Please give me the authorization pad.
You're not it?
He's coming, he's coming.
Hurry up and find them.
He was here for sure. Where did he go?
Hello.
It's okay if we look around, right?
Because we're looking for some people.
Could it be that you have seen the members?
We've seen a lot, wandering around.
Where?
I'm on the 10th floor and I'm getting some tips.
Hello.
Perhaps, have you seen the Running Man members?
I saw Yoo Jae Suk.
Where?
-He's on this second floor? -I don't know.
-7th floor. Why isn't it going. -It's going down.
It's going down you say?
It's harder if I go down.
I'm in trouble.
Tae Yang!
Hold on!! Why did you guys come down?
Seriously.
Hyung, this time...
Hold on!
Why'd you come to the elevator!
Ah noona, ills okay, it's okay.
I'm a spy. spy!
Don't lie to me.
How did you know I'm lying!
Don't be scared.
Noona, don't be scared.
Ah, really!
Song Ji Hyo noona is on the 7th floor.
What are you doing here?
We re doing well! Oh, we re so doing well!
This! This feeling! This feeling!!
I'm sorry, but can I have the authorization pad?
Where is it? I think you have it.
I'm sorry, but the authorization?
Are you looking for the authorization?
Oh. oh!
Reality?
Hey! Everyone be quiet!
I did it! I did it!
Do I take all of this?
Thank you.
You were just sitting here quietly! I almost didn't ask you!
Thank you. Please continue your work.
This is so hard.
Where is 6-Dragon?
Everytime I see that, I think it's TOP and get scared to death, really.
My legs aren't that different from his.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Excuse, hello.
May I ask for an authorization signature?
Do you have the authorization pad?
I don't have the authorization pad.
Excuse me, I'm going to hide here!
Hey hey hey hey.
Kwon Ryul. you have to hide too! You have to hide too!
Give me the camera! Give me the camera!
See you on the 1st floor.
Wait wait!
You were here?
What do we do? Hyung!
What floor is HaHa hyung on?
HaHa hyung. where are you? HaHa hyung, where are you?
Dong hoon hyung! Dong hoon hyung, what floor are you on?
7th floor! 7th floor!
-Hyung, talk to them. -What?
You said you would push them if they came. You said you would show me
I can't.
Wait wait wait.
I know where HaHa hyung is! I know where HaHa hyung is!
Call HaHa hyung fast.
If he doesn't respond in 3 tries...
Wait! I'll call him with my phone.
You are really... really a horrible guy.
I think you're gonna have to surrender.
If he doesn't pick up. I'm ripping it off.
Wait, just a little bit.
Dong Hoon hyung!
What?
Where are you?
Hyung. where is your position? We need to get together.
Wait wait wait wait wait wait!
Please! Please! Just a little just a little! Just give me little more time!
I can do it! I can do it!
I'll show you how well I can do It.
Dong Hoon hyung! We have to get together!
Hey hey hey hey! Wait wait wait!
He's calling, he's calling, he's calling!
Be quiet, be quiet.
Hyung. where are you?
Hey, where are you?
Hyung, where are you. where are you?
I'm on the 10th floor. I think I'm going to go crazy right now.
Say that since it's dangerous, you'll meet him on the 7th floor,
Hyung! Since it's dangerous, let's meet on the 7th floor! 7th floor! 7th floor, there's no one there.
Okay.
-Okay, tear it off first. -7th floor! Gathering on the 7th floor!
Yes, 7th floor. Then run to the 7th floor as you rip off his nametag.
Huh?
Wait, 7th floor! 7th floor.
Hyung! Why are you doing nothing?
What are you doing, like a little girl?
Since you're showing me your betrayal, I feel betrayed.
Hyung, we should be together. Together.
Wait, what are you doing, little by little? Wait, wait.
Wait, wait! Don't do it! Don't do it!
No! Wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait.
What is this?
I'm out too.
7th floor.
Then you can go to the 7th floor.
Wait, what about the 7th floor?
He's at the 7th floor.
Firstly...
7th floor.
Hyung! Why are you doing nothing?
I'm already out, the hand strap has been broken.
-The hand strap is broken, so I am considered out -Lee Gwang Soo, out.
-We are both out. -Lee Gwang Soo, out.
We are really out already.
Didn't they say once the hand strap is broken, we will be out?
I just want to make sure.
Hyung!
For old times' sake? What kind of old times!
Have they gone?
Thank you.
Yes, please speak.
Dae Sung?
Thank you.
Ok, I got it.
Is it Dae Sung?
It's an eatery called Dae Sung.
I was shocked.
I really was shocked.
I thought you were acquainted with Big Bang's Dae Sung.
Teacher, excuse me... Teacher...
Really sorry.
Teacher, please excuse me.
Oh... I smell something fishy.
He should be somewhere around here.
Oh?
Let's see who is it in here now?
He should be somewhere around here.
Oh? Who's here.
Teacher, where are you going?
Tea... Teacher!
Jiyong, HaHa hyung is under my feet.
Where?
10th floor.
Aigoo.
Please come out.
Whether I hide or not, it's the same...
Anyway it's a matter of time before I die.
Tae Yang...
Come to the 10th floor, quickly. 10th floor. HaHa hyung is here.
Oh, I don't care already.
How should we settle this? We're in difficult situation.
Tae Yang.
Wait, Tae Yang.
I got it, I got it.
Let's talk outside.
-Ok. -Go out and talk.
Ah! I really...
This kid is really mischievous.
-I've caught hold of Dong Hoon hyung now. -Who is coming? Who is coming?
At the 10th floor. At the 10th floor chasing him.
Young Bae, where are you?
You ran to the wrong side.
Oh dear, your eyesight is really good.
Oh dear, what should I do?
Let's go out and talk, Tae Yang.
Long time no see!
Hyung, haven't you seen HaHa hyung?
-Haven't you seen HaHa hyung? -That side! He went there!
-Which side? -There. Really. I saw him!
Where is Jiyong, Ji Hyo?
Oppa.
Have you seen Jiyong?
You didn't see him?
Did you see GD just now?
-I saw him over on that side just now. -I've been looking for GD...
Reality?
-He was over there. -He was there?
Jiyong, have you seen GD?
HaHa is at-that side. Really. I saw him!
He's there, really!
-Hyung, I won't tear off your name tag. -Really?
I will also not tear yours.
-I will give you 3 chances. -Really?
Why? Why suddenly?
I saw him. I saw HaHa coming from that side.
He's just over there.
-HaHa hyung ran over to that side? -Yes, that side. I saw him.
What exactly should I do?
What should I do?
Why did they let me go?
Jiyong!
Wait a while.
Wait a while, GD.
GD.
Oh? You guys even have walkie talkies?
GD, how do you all have walkie talkies?
3rd floor.
GD, don't be anxious first.
Think about it.
When we were competing in the afternoon and just now,
There was once I really saw you but I pretended not to see.
Just once, please, GD.
Just once.
By all rights, this is wrong.
I got it, GD. I got it.
TOP also came.
Why are you all surrounding me like this?
Why are you all always moving together?
3rd floor, Jae Suk hyung.
On the 3rd floor, Jae Suk hyung.
Ok ok, 4th floor, Mr. Yoo Jae Suk is on the 4th floor.
Where is Jae Suk hyung?
3rd floor.
I say, TOP...
How many people have you all caught now?
Hey, you!
The VJ almost eliminated you!
The path for him to pass is really too small.
But where did you get so many walkie talkies?
You really have many walkie talkies...
After we catch someone, we release them if they give the walkie talkie.
Ah, really?
First, please hand it over.
Erm, ok.
- Then you are letting me go? - Please go.
- Really? - Yes.
- I can go? -Yes.
Is there anybody on the 3rd floor?
Then I II go?
Next time, you ail will...
What's that for?
5eungri Is there, Seung Ri!
Please don't run!
You will get hurt!
Why did you press that button while running in?
And you had to press that floor?
Kwon Ryul! Why did you press that?
You scared me.
I almost died.
Hyung. we can't hide here. They're on the 2nd floor,
Thank Kwon Ryeol, if he didn't press the 8th floor with his back, you wouldn't have gotten in.
I only opened the door slightly, but I could hear your breathing.
Do you know how much I've been chased?
Let's get off the elevator first.
I wasn't able to check here properly.
I'll go there.
Can I get an authorization signature?
You don't have it?
Hang on...
Approval, oh!
Perform something for me!
What?
Show her something, quickly!
Board dance? Yeah, board dance.
Turn it turn it.
This.
Please sign it.
All right. I'll sign it for you.
We worked so hard just to get this signature?
Mission 60% complete.
Why isn't anyone looking for Suk Jin hyung?
Oh?
Bring him over calmly.
G-Dragon. both our surnames start with Ji!
My surname is Kwon.
Go look for HaHa first.
Mission 60% complete.
Seems like I can t.
Why?
Where is the jail?
Ji Suk Jin out!
You're not even surprised.
It's just that he's lasted a long time this time.
I want to ask him later how he survived until now.
Really, we haven't had a hide-and-seek bell race for so long.
It feels like death.
The Running Men didn't come this way?
Sorry?
Running Man.
All right, let's go out.
I look like a coward like this.
I can just face him uprightly.
Madam, I'm really thankful to you.
That was too scary.
Good work everyone.
Sir. you don't have an approval sheet, do you?
How about here? You don't?
Authorization pad? You have it?!
He really has It.
Thank you.
Mission 80% complete.
We should use the rings now!
Gather your rings.
Shout your names.
And then recite this spell.
Then he'll appear in front of you.
These magic rings.
Who should we summon?
Dong Hoon hyung.
The remaining ones. are-HaHa hyung, Jae Suk hyung. Jong Kook hyung.
Jae Suk hyung?
Let's summon Jong Kook hyung, quickly.
HaHa hyung!
Don't summon HaHa hyung!
I'm going to catch him personally.
What?
Please observe carefully.
See how the person is brought here.
Who's power it is.
Who's power it is, please observe carefully,
Tae Yang!
GD!
Dae Sung!
Top!
The strength of the five rings...
Will control space!
Yah!
Summon Kim Jong Kook!
Why are you dragging me away?
Huh?
What's going on?
No I... hyung.
No, why? Why are you...?
No, why?
What's this? Who controlled space?
Sit down and don't move.
Sit down.
All right.
Oh, it was true.
They had superpowers.
They really had superpowers.
No, what is this? What's going on?
There was a space controller? Here?
What are you guys doing?
You came because we summoned you.
Hyung don't worry, it's nothing to be proud of.
What is it? Let's hear it.
I'm curious.
-It's nothing to be proud of. -It's really embarrassing, isn't it?
It's really embarrassing, isn't it?
Dae Sung!
Tae Yang!
GD!
Seung Ri!
Top.
The's trength of the five rings will control space! Yah!
Kim Kook Jong! Summoned!
I don't think I'd be able to use it, even if I had that. kind of power.
You made us read it.
Let's go.
It was rather useless.
You guys really...
It was really fun.
Ah, really!
Go to the jail.
Tell me why he got summoned,
No, you have to tell me. Along Kook was talking to me and he suddenly got summoned.
Would you like to hear the reason now?
Yes.
The five of them /line nog's.
And?
If they put on the rings...
And recite the spell...
That's enough.
Hearing it is embarrassing enough.
You did something similar before!
The one who controls space!
Kim Jong Kook Out!
Oh! He's there!
Over here!
Hurry up!
Jae Suk hyung is here, Jae Suk hyung is here!
8th floor, Jae Suk hyung.
Over here.
Jae Suk hyung, I said I wouldn't just let you off a second time right?
Hey, I thought it was an alien from outer space!
Your green hair.
Are they all caught?
Ah, HaHa hyung is left?
-Yoo Jae Suk. out! -What the...
-Yoo Jae Suk. out! -What am I going to do?!
They've all been caught. I have to hide.
Hey, this isn't it. How do I do this?
How am I supposed to do this alone?
Hey, this is really crazy.
Does this even make sense?
It's just me left!
I can t do it. how do I do it alone?
1 just have to find one more right?
Everyone, I'm sorry. I've unintentionally become the main character.
You must, must hide well. I can see your head.
What will Ha Dong Hoon do now?
The walkie-talkie, Gary oppa's walkie-talkie was snatched away.
Mine was snatched away too.
Yours got snatched away too?
I gave it to them to survive.
-Gwang Soo? -Yes hyung?
This is yours.
You lost a screw.
It's a situational comedy!
-Hey. twist in back in like this. -Ah, seriously.
-Twist it? . Right. -You should have accepted it and twisted it in.
Then wouldn't it be very interesting, this sort of situation comedy?
The situation comedy's wrecked by you.
-Hey, give that to me. -Do you know how difficult that... of course!
-You being like this... -I need a character more now.
-When hyung tells you your screw was loose you just have to twist it back in. -Hyung.
-You shouldn't have given it to him, you should have given it over. I might as well have given it to Gary.
The screw flew away.
Gwang Soo. this was a pitch you had to accept.
Ah, seriously. It's really...
It's a pity, right?
-let me try? again... -He wants to try again...
Ah, how funny it could have been, the screw falling out.
Seriously, this...
Hey, why did is this bracelet on the floor?
Where?
Gwang Soo went to a club.
Actually, when Gwang Soo was grabbed earlier...
-Hey, I thought you got rid of it. -Hyung was really amazing.
The bracelet... you keep still!
The bracelet was right around both our wrists.
"Keep still". Again.
What's this? Aigoo.
Getting me to do things like tightening screws but not letting me talk.
What am I?!
Why is he so pitiful?
Do I only have to do this sort of thing?
I can also be funny with my talk hyung!
Only doing things like Gwangvatar and Giraffe.
-Gwang.Soo. -I also want to be funny with my talks.
Just wait.
Gwang Soo, it will come.
If you run into HaHa hyung.
Please let me rip off his nametag.
Is there any, authorization signature here?
Over there!
9th floor! 9th floor! 9th floor!
9th floor!
Hey! Wait! Hold on! Hey, there's something.
If you tear it off it will explode, bang!
Bam, there it goes.
Got it?
Hyung!
Then what do we do?
We lost the mission and it's 1:1, right?
-Ok, it's 1:1 no. -Yes.
In awhile. the final battle will begin.
A final battle.
-How can it be done? All members will roll the dice. -Yes. and then?
That per son with largest number will be the representative. Then face off to tear each other's nameiags.
-It's one-on-one? -They'll do it one-on-one.
-In this building? -Right. in this building.
-They go up one at a time? -Hey.
Then shall we start?
Please be a low number.
6, wow.
Gary it is.
Our Gae Yang.
Gary and Gae Yang.
We're both Gae Yangs!
Tae Yang, I'll see you later.
If it's a direct confrontation,
seeing his athleticism in Running Man,
is no joke.
I have to find a good location.
To ambush him.
He's just too fast.
I won't be able to chase him.
Where's the fire exit...?
I have no sense of direction.
I was making a very cool speech...
SUN!
Sun!
Seems like someone's calling me?
Sunnnn!
Sun!
Hey, why is he so fast?
-Oh! -Oh?
Seems like they met, seems like they met.
I can hear them.
Sun!
Why are you so fast?
Where did he go?
-What the...?! -Hey!
Sun. Sun!
Sun! Hey!
Hey!
Sun!
What's going on?
It can t be that he won right?
He's vanished, he's vanished.
He's gone.
Ah, I clearly followed him here.
How can he be so fast?
He's gone.
Ah, I clearly followed him here.
How can he be so fast?
Wow.
This is really...
Acknowledged, acknowledged.
He's truly my dongsaeng.
For the winning team.
Everyone will be given a set of specially designed apparel.
-Because were at a fashion company. -Where?
Aigoo, they're so cool.
- Are you giving these as presents too? - Yes.
-It's not for this side, it's for that... Yes -That's correct.
-For the game today. -Yes.
We designed special nametags.
-What does it look like, can we take a look? -Ah. we... then...
-We need these. -This is what we need.
Hey, G-Dragon.
If I knew they were giving these things my desire to win would be ignited.
-Let everyone take a look. -They're rather cool.
Ah, it matches them.
Thank you.
Hey, Tae Yang always raises his fists no matter what he does.
This is cool!
Ok let's, thank the design company again for providing a venue for Big Bang.
Let's give them a round of applause.