[The icons of Korean melodrama
are coming to Running Man!]
[Goodbye for today melodrama!
It's time for a merciless kimchi war.]
Where did you go now?
It seems you've never done it before.
- It's so harsh here.
- I am so sick of this!
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Jeong Eob, North Jeon La Province]
What? What?
What is it?
Why are we here at Jeong Eob?
This is Jeong Eob here.
Nae Jang Mountain is
famous for its maple leafs.
Nice to meet you.
I am Lee Kwang Soo.
When it comes to Jeong Eob...
are they famous for their rice?
Oh, it's Running bus.
[Running bus?]
[Running Bus]
What is a Running bus?
[Come to think of it,
everyone is at a bus stop.]
If you wait here, a Running
bus will arrive.
- There is someone there?
- The guest will be on the bus.
- Oh, I see.
- They get off the bus?
The guest gets off the bus?
- Do you drive the bus yourself?
- No, I don't drive it myself.
They might not get off as well?
[We will see if the guest
will let them on or not...]
You can't tell who I am, right?
I am on edge today.
[He is on edge and
waiting for the guest.]
I wonder who it is.
[As everyone is waiting
for the Running bus...]
[A man who's walking in
the winter rain.]
[Go-vid, Go Soo]
Hello.
[I am a woman.]
[The goddess of innocence,
Han Hyo Joo]
[Such a nice sight~]
I heartly welcome you to Running Man.
I'll hand you your opening mission.
Team up with Running Man members
who are waiting at bus stops.
You choose three members in total.
When you choose a member and
bring them on the bus
they will be your team member
for the rest of the day.
Please pick two cards.
- You go ahead first.
- Should I go first?
This one.
Oh!
[And one more]
[Go-vid also selects two cards.]
Please open them and
show them on camera.
We don't know who
it's going to be yet.
This one...
It's number six.
[Go Soo has numbers three and six.]
- Number one and seven.
- One and seven.
Let's get on the bus together
and go.
[Let's see who will become
their team members...]
Bus is leaving.
Alright.
[Running bus, go!]
[Running bus goes to
number one bus stop.]
- Hyo Joo, you have number one, right?
- Number one.
We've almost come to
number one bus stop.
Who is it?
I am so curious.
Is this like,
we are coming there to meet you?
I wonder who the guest is today?
It would be just right if
we get a lady guest today.
Which woman of maple leaf,
will come to hug me?
[Full of anticipation~]
[Who would that be?]
[Finally, bus stop number one!]
[The door opens]
[Hyo Joo gets off to see who's there.]
[Who could it be?]
[It's Jae Suk]
Let me, let me.
I'll see who it is.
Who is it?
[What...]
Oh, it's a lady.
I can already...
- You used hand lotion, right?
- Hi.
I mean...
Hyo Joo is here...
Are we on the same team?
Woo-hoo!
Yes, the game is over.
It's like the game is over.
- You got the card for this bus stop?
- I did.
- Really?
- Good to see you.
Wow, I am just...
Oh, it's Dong Wan.
[Good for you~]
What?
Oh, it's Go Soo--
- Go Soo.
- Hi, Jae Suk.
Oh, Go Soo!
You two are here?
I was so surprised to see you.
Hyo Joo and I on the same team?
She walked from behind
me and covered my eyes.
I sensed a nice hand lotion scent.
I thought the game is over today.
Now that beautiful Miss Hyo Joo is here.
[Miss Hyo Joo?]
Yes, it's Miss Hyo Joo.
Go Soo will pick his team
at the next stop --
I am getting off on number three.
It's kind of disappointing for them.
- See who's on number two.
- Come on, why bother?
It's not that important.
[At bus stop number two.]
[Giraffe is sitting alone.]
I look forward to working with you.
Oh!
I am crazy about this.
It's Kwang Soo, see.
It's Kwang Soo.
I knew it.
Every single time, right?
He usually is that guy.
Why do you think that is?
Is that the Running bus?
[Oops? Jae Suk comes closer]
Oh?
Your hands are really warm.
Enough to warm me up inside.
- [Pushing hard]
- Ah, wait a minute!
[Eyes pressure therapy
that warms him up.]
Jae Suk!
- Hi, Jae Suk.
- How long have you been here?
I was...
a little while...
- Bye.
- What?
- I am going.
- Where are you going?
- I got selected but you...
- But me?
- You get to stay here.
- I didn't get picked?
- You weren't.
- Jae Suk!
- Bye, not you.
- Please let me get on.
- Jae Suk!
- Not enough room.
What are you talking about?
There are so many empty seats.
- Bye, bye.
- But I have money!
- You know who's on my team?
- Who?
- Han Hyo Joo!
- I am a good friend of hers!
I am a good friend of hers!
The person who gets to
be on Go Soo's team.
This is bus stop number three.
Get ready if you are getting off.
Go Soo is getting off, yes.
[There is a team member for Go Soo
at bus stop number three.]
There he is.
[Brand new groom Haha is waiting.]
[Standing by with a
perfect camouflage.]
[Poke]
Let's go just like that.
Who, who is it?
Oh, oh, a jackpot...
- Hi there.
- You didn't know who it was?
- No.
Really?
You are on the same team with Go Soo and
I am on the same team with Hyo Joo.
- What happened?
- It happened like this.
- Kwang Soo is by himself there.
- Really?
Where do I go?
[Enjoying the view?]
Don't stare at him so much.
- Could I touch your ear?
- No, come on.
He is real.
He's human.
Hey, sitting beside Go Soo,
you look like a wetfoot octopus.
- You really are--
- Jae Suk, you look like a baby octopus yourself.
- Your face is all wrinkled up.
- You are like a wetfoot octopus.
- What?
- Hey!
- Seriously.
So tacky.
[Going to number four bus stop~]
Oh, who's on number four stop?
[Blank Ji is here~]
[If no one's getting off,
we'll go, alright~]
What?
They just left?
[Of course the number five bus stop~]
Excuse me.
They said someone's getting off here.
Who's that?
Hey, Dong Wan!
[Sorry~]
They just left?
This is sixth bus stop.
[Go Soo is getting off
at number six bus stop.]
[The person waiting is...]
Look at those legs!
[Kook~]
Who is that?
Oh!
Hey, Go Soo!
What are you doing here?
[Go Soo - Kook team is complete~]
Alright, it's done.
We are on the same team!
[Go Soo-Jong Kook-Haha
team complete!]
- What happened?
- This is just too much.
- What do you mean?
- If Go Soo and Jong Kook are on the same team...
- So, this is our team?
- The handsome team.
[Final, bus stop number seven]
- It's our Gary.
- Leessang's Gary.
He'll be so surprised.
They are not here yet, right?
Oh, this is strange.
The smell of hands is strange.
Oh, hi there.
Nice to meet you.
Can I turn around?
Can I?
- Hi there.
- [Oops...!!]
- [Oops... Who are you?]
Hi there.
[Smile]
[Shy?]
Yes! Yes! Yes!
- Hi there.
- Hi.
The scent is still lingering on my face.
- What do I do?
- Gary.
Oh, Jae Suk.
[Hyo Joo, Jae Suk, Gary
on the same team.]
Nice to meet you.
Oh, Jae Suk!
There's scent lingering on my face.
- How could I sit here?
- I sat there a while too. Have a seat.
[He became shy throbbing Gary.]
This is the last stop.
Nae Jang Mountain station.
Everyone get off please.
- Should we?
- Let's go.
- Let's go. Let's go.
- Yes.
I think my heart's going
to pound all day.
I think it's them.
- Hi, dropouts.
- Camera's rolling even without us?
No, it was just for a moment.
[Surprise!]
Oh, hi.
- How are you, Go Soo.
- Fine, fine.
I haven't seen you on TV for so long.
[Hold it]
Why? Are you her manager?
[Jae Suk's stopping Kwang Soo
from getting close to her.]
Yeah, they are friends.
They've always said they are friends.
When you stand beside her,
you look like a laborer.
A fan, a fan. A long time fan.
How come do you look so
ugly today?
Okay, I'll log out from your life now.
[Not canceling the membership
but just logging out?]
Now you're logged into her life?
Today, we are with the hottest
looking man and woman in Korea.
We are doing a kimchi-making race.
It's the season for that.
You'll get the chance to win the
tools and ingredients you need
by playing missions around
beautiful Jeong Eob.
Think about our friendship.
The team who makes the most delicious
kimchi is the winner today.
If this was going to happen,
why do this anyway?
Beautiful!
Please go to the field that
you see over there.
- What's this?
- Work clothing and gloves.
I can pick anything I want?
[As if they are shopping.]
[Go Soo also gets to wear work clothes.]
[This one looks cute.]
[Hyo Joo gets ready by
wearing rubber band pants.]
You look so tacky!
Hey, look at what Go Soo is wearing.
[Go Soo's middle-aged
woman's fashion.]
Go Soo. Go Soo. Go Soo.
[Stylish~]
Hyo Joo. Hyo Joo.
[Hyo Joo is also
excited to wear it?]
Gary looks just right in it.
[Looks like he brought it from home.]
Where is Song Ji Hyo?
She's always late.
Let's have a serious talk with her.
- You, you do it.
- If you want, you have that talk with her.
- That's because she might get mad.
- Miss Blank.
- Miss Blank is kind of high maintenance.
- She needs to be taken care of.
Maybe I should have a talk with you?
- Aren't you going to have a talk?
- Let's see what you say.
- Let's have a serious talk.
- I'll do that in three weeks.
I am too scared for it now.
The first game for kimchi-making race.
Radish picking game.
Men spin 10 times in place.
And women spin seven times in place.
The team whose last runner
brings the radish back wins.
There are two guys here
who were on Dream Team.
Dream Team!
Look at that,
Go Soo is re-tying his shoes!
- What, what about it?
- He's re-tying his shoes!
Dream Team members always re-tie our shoes
when we hear that we're doing something.
You don't have to do that, come on!
There will be a game to see
who'll get a win by default.
[Pregame - Basket throwing]
No, no, no.
I said no!
What is this?
[Team Blue wins by default]
[Round one - Team Yellow vs Team Purple]
- Okay, ready.
- Han Hyo Joo! Han Hyo Joo!
Song Ji Hyo! Song Ji Hyo!
Song Ji Hyo!
Don't!
I'll go now...
I'll make sure.
I am good at telling on people.
So, I'll tell you if they do something wrong.
- Start at the right angle.
- Let's just start it.
- Let's start it already.
- Are you going to spin left or right?
Spin left till your head is pointing
front, that's one rotation.
Move back a little.
[A picky assistant referee Go-vid]
- That's good.
- He is like a handsome Kim Jong Kook.
[Fair play!]
Ready!
[Jae Suk vs Kwang Soo]
Ready and go!
One, two, three, four, five, six.
[Ew?]
You lose if you vomit.
- Eight, nine.
- That's good. That's good.
That way. That way.
[Dizzy Dizzy]
[Giraffe, where are you headed?]
[Sense of direction is off
the track due to spinning.]
Hey, it's mine. It's mine.
Hey, you need to jump over.
[Crashing into three haystacks.]
Hey!
[Giraffe can't let him win.]
[Three straight falls.]
[It's his last haystack...]
- Can't jump over.
- It's like a game of dominoes.
[Rule: First and second runners
restore the haystacks!]
Where does it go?
[What?]
[Doing martial arts out of the blue...]
[Right foot]
[Left foot]
[Won't let you win!
Fly like a butterfly!]
[Kick]
I am sorry. I am sorry. I am sorry.
Hurry. The game won't end
if you play it like that.
Hey, not like that!
- Let's agree not to do that.
- Let's agree. Promise.
That's quick.
[Giraffe, arrives earlier.]
Ready and go...
One.
[Second runners are Gary from Purple
Team and Suk Jin from Yellow Team.]
- Six.
- Seven.
- Go. Go.
- Ten!
Wait a minute!
[Impossible to run straight?]
[Suk Jin is demonstrating
a crab-walk.]
Wait a minute!
[Thump]
[Fall]
[Gary is moving forward one by one.]
Wow, he's good at jumping over.
- Suk Jin!
- Gary!
[Resorts to front kick.]
- You promised.
- We promised.
They even made a promise
before the race started.
- Gary!
- Hurry, hurry!
[Oops... a haystack has come undone.]
What to do?
[A human thresher on the field?]
What are you doing?
- What is that?
- It came undone.
[Last runners: Hyo Joo from Team Purple
vs Ji Hyo from Team Yellow.]
two, three, four.
[Just seven spins for
Hyo Joo and Ji Hyo.]
No, one more.
Hyo Joo, go!
Aargh!
[Blank Ji took a wrong turn.]
That way!
[Blank Ji is finally back on track.]
Good. Okay, good job!
[What?]
[Oh...]
[Hyo takes a light
jump over the haystack.]
Hyo Joo has long legs.
Hurry, hurry!
Hyo Joo!
Pick the radish!
[They win if she brings in the radish.]
[You have to restore the haystacks]
- No, you don't have to.
- No, you have to!
- You have to!
- No, no.
[Almost got tricked.]
[Team Purple wins]
[Seriously...!]
Team Purple wins.
- We have to do this again?
- What's the meaning of this?
Congratulations on advancing
to the finals.
It's the final round now.
Since Team Purple has a female
member, they spin five times only.
Okay, let's do that.
Should I go first?
- If it's Jong Kook --
- I'll go.
Jong Kook, make sure
that you hold your nose.
Jong Kook can't grab his nose.
Hold my arm for me.
[He got a cramp trying
to hold his nose...]
I got a cramp.
He can't do it because of muscles.
Ready and go!
One, two, three, four, five, six.
Seven, eight.
- Oh, so dizzy!
- Nine.
Ten!
- Oh, I am so dizzy.
- Gary!
- Ten.
- Oh!
[Where is this place?]
- So, dizzy.
- Wait!
Wait!
Look at him go.
[I am a capable man!]
[I've done this so many
times on Dream Team.]
Gary!
[Gary moves forward no matter what.]
[Is he jumping over or
taking them down?]
Gary!
[He jumps over the
last haystack anyhow.]
[Kook doesn't need to restore much.]
Just come, just come.
Not even a match. He dominated it.
He won it in a such a boring way!
[Looks likes the game is over?]
[Team Blue's second runner - Go-vid]
- Oh!
- Go! Go! Go!
[Oh...?]
[This is no joke...]
Go! Go! Go!
[Gary comes back in the meanwhile]
- Go Soo!
- [He is moving noticeabley slow.]
Nine, ten!
- Go! Go!
- That way! That way!
Over there!
[Ah... where to?!]
[Jae Suk crashed into the camera.]
[He barely jumps over them.]
[Jae Suk is moving forward
by destroying them.]
Go Soo! We are totally--
Go Soo, over there!
[Crashing into haystacks
pretending he's too dizzy.]
Break. He takes down three
haystacks in no time...
I was just too dizzy.
Go Soo, we could lose.
[No...!]
Hurry back after taking it down!
Fair play guy Go-vid uses
a heckling strategy.
Hurry, hurry back!
[Team Blue has a comfortable lead.]
[Team Blue's last runner.
A brand new groom, Haroro.]
Three, four, five, six, seven, eight
- Nine, ten.
- Where is it?
[Hyo Joo vs Haha]
[A fierce battle between two
people with similar heights.]
Oh, they're fast.
[Hyo Joo is speeding up.]
It's so close.
[Oh... oh... a comeback?]
What are you doing, Dong Hoon?
She might win, she might!
[Now just got to pick the radish!]
[Toward the radish~]
[What?]
Look at the way he
pushes around a woman!
[A merciless married man]
[Oops... An outer reaping throw...?]
[A fierce... battle...]
[Shocked]
[No!]
- He can't handle it
- I am out of breathe.
[Ah...! Hyo Joo's turn?]
[Ah...]
[Haha's second outer reaping throw.]
[Rare to see an actress
being thrown.]
[Hyo Joo loses the radish.]
[Excited~]
[Team Blue wins]
I won!
[Flabbergast...]
Now that he's married he
just doesn't care anymore.
[Hey]
[Hyo Joo tastes the raw
side of a variety show.]
Bring any actress you want!
I'll throw any one of them
to the ground!
Hyo Joo is so mad right now.
I am sorry, Hyo Joo.
[Don't touch!]
It's a war now.
- That's good. Okay, it's a war!
- That's good.
- You be careful too now!
- What are you doing to me?
Your beautiful competition...
Team Blue wins!
- This is a competition?
- Beautiful!
Beautiful!
[Hyo Joo explodes?]
[She suddenly loses her temper.]
Real Han Hyo Joo is back.
Finally, the real Han Hyo Joo is here.
Beautiful!
A goddess of innocence has awaken.
[Han Hyo Joo! A never seen side of her.]
Can we open it?
[Tools are given based on
the ranking.]
- What is this?
There is just one knife.
[Team Purple receives a grater.]
We received an engine.
- What is it?
- You can cut radish in no time.
This is a machine.
- How do you do it?
- I opened just three of them in 30 minutes.
The power of a monster engine!
It's done!
If they want this, they can
wrestle me for it...
[Married Haha's free-swinging challenge.]
You take him.
You know, you can take him.
[I'll get you!]
[To the next place for
kimchi-making race~]
Go Soo wanted to drive.
[Go-vid's smooth driving]
Go to Jeong Eob 'S' marketplace and
find Running Man banner.
- So we're going to a marketplace.
- We went to this other marketplace last time.
[Wonder what they can win
at the marketplace?]
- When was last time you appeared on TV?
- I can't even remember.
- It's been very long, right?
- That's true.
When I watched you guys on TV,
I really wanted to be part of it.
I was too excited to sleep last night.
I do feel sorry...
Hyo Joo must been shocked as well.
She probably couldn't believe
what was happening, don't you think?
- And two times too.
- Yes, two times.
Two times.
Congratulations on being the first
actress to be thrown down like that.
Thank you.
Thank you...
Congratulations.
Oh, it was beautiful.
- And two times too.
- Yes, you were thrown twice as well.
- It's a beautiful world.
- It is beautiful.
Also I think Hyo Joo has a temper.
'Beautiful!'
Beautiful.
Beautiful!
- Have you made kimchi before, Hyo Joo?
- Actually, it's my first time today.
Okay. Then, be thrown
one more time later on.
[Team Blue arrives at
the marketplace.]
- Let's go.
- We're the first place team. Go go!
[Jeong Eob 'S' marketplace
has 100 years of heritage.]
There is a spicy fragrance in the air.
- I love the marketplace so much.
- Right. I like them too.
There are ladies making kimchi.
Let's go. Go go!
[It's kimchi-making season
so it's busy here.]
- I need to get the mission.
- Look at those cabbages.
They are for kimchi-making.
- Look, Gary's here.
- Where?
It's Gary!
Hey, it's Gary!
[Hi, Gary?]
[Oh my, Grasshopper is here.]
Hello. Hi.
Go to a hair shop?
Why are we going in there?
Where?
Oh, what is it?
Oh, what...
What is this?
- Hi.
- Hyo Joo, how have you been?
[The merciless Haha is being stopped.]
In this mission, you can win
a kimchi-making recipe.
It's the 'Cabbage Head' game.
While one of the members gets a perm...
the other two members
carry out the mission.
Every time you fail a mission, the
member gets more and more permed.
Please choose who's getting a perm.
A perm?
A real perm?
[Hyo Joo volunteers?]
- Ah... Hyo Joo volunteered for it.
- What do you mean? You don't have to.
Hyo Joo just told me not to
consider her as an actress today.
She said she is so happy that
she was thrown down two times.
Hyo Joo, then you do it.
You were even thrown to the ground.
So, getting a perm is no problem, right?
- I'll hang out with them here.
- Okay, you do that.
[Drawing lots]
Hear someone shouting 'puff!' at a
puffed rice store and bring some here.
Is there a time limit?
- [Time limit is...]
- Three minutes.
- [Three minutes!]
- What?
- Hyo Joo, we'll be back soon.
- Hurry back, Jae Suk.
[If they don't accomplish the mission in three
minutes, their hair will be permed more...]
[Two outer reaping throws and
now getting a perm too...]
- Hurry back please!
- Let's go. Let's go.
Let's go. Let's go. Let's go.
Let's go.
Puffed rice.
[Team Yellow's hass to hear someone shouting
'puff!' at a puffed rice store and bring some.]
These are puffed rice, right?
When does the next batch
of rice get puffed?
- It will be a while.
- It will be a while?
- It takes eight more minutes.
- Eight minutes?
Eight minutes?
[Eight more minutes until
the next batch is puffed...]
[Giraffe's hair is getting
more and more twisted...]
- We are in trouble. We are in trouble.
- We don't have enough time.
[Team Blue's mission is to
buy exactly 100 puffed corns.]
20.
two.
[What...?]
[Team Yellow interrupts Team Blue
since puffing will take too long.]
What are you doing? Why are you doing this?
Why are you doing this?
Why?
[Since we can't accomplish
our mission...]
[Same time]
[Haha's hair is being twisted]
Oh, oh, why are you doing this?
- Cabbage!
- Here it is.
Green onions! Two green onions!
Five cabbages! 10 radishes!
- Eight, nine.
- 10. Done. Done.
[Speedy Jae Suk & Gary]
We need to take it to delivery truck!
Where?
[The actress's hair is being
twisted very quickly.]
- Where is it?
- They said it's here somewhere.
- Where is that truck?
- They are so heavy.
Jae Suk, hurry!
[Hurry...! Before Hyo Joo's
hair is totally permed...]
- Gary!
- Where? Where, where?
Hold it. Wait a minute.
[Maybe I shouldn't have
volunteered?]
[It's starting to
look like a perm now...]
[Every staff member came on board
for this Perm Parade.]
[Please hurry...]
Could you,
could you make it a little cute?
- Looks like you're having fun.
- No, that's not true.
You are holding back your laughter.
- Oh?
- You came back so quick.
You look pretty.
You accomplished the mission?
- [That can't be...]
- Must be so close to the clock.
They took more than five minutes.
Four minutes and 12 seconds.
[Ah~ they failed the mission!]
[How much more of this?]
I'll come back soon.
- [Team Blues arrives]
- So close. It has to be within three minutes.
[Team Blue arrives]
Kwang Soo!
[In five minutes, he became a
completely different person.]
They were interfering so much.
I won't just sit back and watch.
Just get it done, please!
Everyone out!
Don't look at me.
Don't film me either!
- Hey, you look cute.
- You look amazing.
- Where is a basket?
- Jae Suk, a hardware store.
[Team Purple must buy two winnowing baskets,
two baskets, and salts from two restaurants.]
- Two winnowing baskets!
- They are over there.
- Where?
- Follow me, follow me.
Sesame oil.
Can we get a sesame oil.
[Team Blue must buy a bottle of sesame oil,
deliver it and eat five dim sum.]
- Ma'am, where is a chinese restaurant?
- A chinese restaurant.
Oh?
It's right there.
Where is it?
Oh, you're coming with us?
Here, Jae Suk.
Put it on your head.
Ma'am, I will pay you later, okay?
Where is salt? Salt.
Where is salt?
[She leads them to a salt store.]
- Look there!
- Salt! Salt! Please tell us how much it is.
I think I know what's going on.
I hear that hair-stylist's talk.
When I asked, 'Is it going well?',
she said, 'Oh....'
She gets a peacock hair.
And my hair got burned as well.
I saw smoke going up.
I told her I am getting married soon and
she said, 'Oh, I shouldn't burn it then...'
Of course you shouldn't, Ma'am!
- How could you burn the hair?
- [Sorry~]
Oh?
- They are here already?
- They're here!
- Within three minutes.
- It's done.
- One minute and 54 seconds. Pass!
- Yes!
[Wow. Team Purple passes!]
Hyo Joo!
[The mission is a success but she has
a half done peacock hairstyle...]
And we did it pretty quick too.
Don't eat something like this!
- It's making you look pitiful!
- She picked it up from the floor.
I saw that in a movie.
Here it is.
Give me money.
500 won.
500 won if you're curious.
- Hyo Joo, 500 won if you're curious.
- You look so good with it.
Hyo Joo is doing so
much for Running Man...
- What do we do now?
- 500 won if you're curious.
Ugh!
- That's good.
- Let's fight!
Let's fight!
You hated me so much, right?
It looks good, like a rocker.
Hyo Joo, you look really pretty.
This is what true
beauty is, Hyo Joo.
[This morning]
- [Chinese Food]
- Should we have another dish?
This is good.
[Where are they?]
- I am sorry, Haha.
- You don't need to be.
We just can't do anything about it.
[Go Soo and Kook are taking
more than six minutes.]
Where are they?
Are they watching a movie?
[Yum]
It's so delicious when it's so fresh.
Where is Go Soo, anyway?
How come we get this way?
Ugh!
Take off the glasses.
I said take off your glasses.
I don't think I burned you.
Mm...
I am done.
I have a complete perm.
- How about perming his armpit?
- Do you have to perm every hair on your body?
We need rice cakes!
Rice cakes!
- Is this it? How much is it?
- 2,500 won.
Give her 3000 won.
Blanket store!
[Slow~]
Where have you been?
It took you more than 10 minutes!
- What are you going to do about this?
- It's finished?
I said what are you
going to do about this?
It took you so long this time.
What were you doing?
- Went to a chinese--
- What did you eat, Jong Kook?
- It was a mission.
- I can smell the food!
- It's dim sum. Look--
- You should've come earlier!
[Can't believe this]
Ji Hyo!
Go now!
They might even perm
my armpit hair too!
Where is jang-gu store?
[Team Blue must play a jang-gu instrument
while rotating sangmo 10 times.]
Where is a jang-gu store?
- What is this?
What is this?
[Spotted a jang-gu store]
Ready and go.
[Not easy...]
I guess you have to tighten this.
[Bite it down hard with his teeth.]
Ready and go.
One, two, three, four, five.
[Blank]
[Returning with extreme speed.]
No, no. Please. Please.
- The time is...
- Please.
- Two minutes and 42 seconds.
- Yes!
- I can't believe this!
- [Sob]
[Sob...]
Honey, hold on just a bit longer.
I said I'll wait for you here...
Honey! Honey!
Honey, you look so old...
[Giraffe got deeper wrinkles
as he got more permed.]
[He ends up staying to
make it look a little better..]
- I get scared...
- What?
when I look at myself in the camera.
Looks like she worked
hard on that perm.
[Is that so?]
Dong Hoon.
- Thank you for your extra attention.
- Let's go. Let's go.
- Thank you.
- Thank you. Have a nice day.
I am not ready for a picture.
One, two, three.
[Mm... Same difference?]
[Mm...]
With hair like that, you look like
that guy from 'Boys Over Flowers.'
- Gu Jun Pyo?
- Gu Kwang Pyo. Gu Kwang Pyo.
Looks good on you.
I think it looks really
good on him.
- Gu Jun Pyo had his hair like that too.
- He had it like this.
[Having fun teasing him.]
I am just myself.
[Yes...]
[Here comes Gu Kwang Pyo~]
[Yes... his hair has the air
of the rich, so much so~!]
[Slips into narcissism.]
[I love perm!]
[I'm Gu Kwang Pyo~]
[They drove for a while.]
[Kimchi-making mission third spot,
Folk Village of Joseon Dynasty.]
Now, this game is the chance to
get garlic and oysters.
We have to have oysters, no question.
It's called 'Cabbage take away game.'
In this village, there are
headquarters for each team.
And also there is a house
with a black flag.
That's the house for
Han Hyo Joo's team.
You find 10 plastic cabbages
that are in the village.
You win when you confirm with us that you
have 10 of them in your headquarters.
[First team to bring 10 of them
to their headquarters wins!]
You get to win only when
I count them myself.
I'll take time to get to your headquarter
too since I am a slow walker.
[Take a cart to carry the
plastic cabbages and go~]
Then, we need to take away
cabbages from other teams too?
There is one over there.
- Where, where?
- I think we can find one over there.
- Oh!
- Jae Suk, I think it was a good idea.
[Is there one here?]
- Hyo Joo, here is one.
- Here is one.
Then, I'll go and look for
more of them.
It's full with just one cabbage in it.
There is one!
Hey, she's good at it.
- How did she find that?
- Let's hurry ourselves.
[Hyo Joo already found one!]
Oh, there it is. There is one here.
- I found one, Jae Suk.
- Where?
From back there.
Let's hurry and find them.
There it is.
[Team Blue looks for them in the houses.]
I found one. I found one.
I found another one.
Dong Hoon.
- We need to go to another house.
- How about defending--
Hurry.
[On the other hand, Go Soo is...]
Everyone here?
[Managing his time and
visiting houses...]
[He is ever so slowly taking
a walk and looking for them.]
Oh, be careful.
[Everyone else is running and
sweating to find the cabbages.]
Did they find one?
How many of them are out there?
There are more than 10 of them, right?
[Instead of talking about it...
hurry and find them...]
[And now Team Blue has
arrived at the village!]
Oh, how do they look?
Show it to me.
[Hyo Joo! They might
take it from her...!]
[Poke!]
[Suk Jin's fantastic interception.]
[Poke]
[Team Yellow takes another
one to make two!]
[Team Purple was doing so well!]
[Eventually, every villager gathers here.]
Wait. Hold it!
What was that?
[Finally, chaos breaks out.]
[Giraffe lost the cabbages
that he took from them.]
- I couldn't find even one.
- Then go look for them!
[Team Purple is at the risk of
losing every cabbage they found.]
[Slow Go Soo takes them so quick!]
I knew this would happen.
Hey, you...
Are you really going to do this to me?
Hey, Michael, are you sure
you're going to do this to me?
Everyone is saying I look
just like Gu Jun Pyo.
Hey, Michael, are you sure
you're going to do this to me?
Everyone is saying I look
just like Gu Jun Pyo.
[Wake up...]
Where is our headquarters?
[Anyway, Team Blue needs to bring
the cabbages to their headquarters.]
Hey, hey, hey, don't touch these.
You should be happy with that one
you took! How many more?
Come on, let's not do this.
Look. Look at the way Ji Hyo
tries to look innocent.
Ji Hyo, they are taking ours.
[Should I take the whole cart?]
[Eventually, Team Yellow
takes everything.]
Let's take them home.
- How many was that?
- They took six of them.
That means we had 10.
[A tough woman, she
carries them all herself.]
She sure is meticulous.
- Nobody saw it.
- We should hide them.
[Team Yellow plundered
four cabbages.]
These are the ones?
[Team Yellow also hides the
cabbages in their headquarters.]
Hide them there.
Stand guard right there.
[Ace Ji Hyo is guarding the cabbages.]
- What are you doing here?
- It's too cold for you?
What? What are you doing here?
- You should offer greetings first.
- I am too cold.
You should go to your house.
And your house is so close too.
I'm not going to be childish
and steal anything.
You know me.
I know you. Of course I do.
But I'm here,
and you're so unwelcoming.
- What do you mean?
- You're so unwelcoming!
- We didn't even greet each other.
- It's been seven years since we've met.
That's right.
[Go Soo urgent during dire times.]
- You can't even do that.
- You were supposed to grab it.
So violent. So cruel.
[Again, he loiters about.]
[What's this?]
[What luck!
He discovers a cabbage!]
[But instead of leaving it at
headquarters...]
[For now he leaves it in a place
only he knows of.]
[Mostly slow, but occassionally fast.
Always tidy Go Soo.]
There's the back door.
Hold on.
[Discovers the back door of headquarters!]
[Stealing the cabbages]
It's closed.
See where it's hidden.
[The purple team looks inside
and discovers cabbages!]
Hey, hey, hey!
Hey, don't take that!
Hey, damn that guy!
- I forgot old houses have back doors.
- I forgot about the back door!
[Everyone is anxious]
This isn't finding. It's stealing.
They're stealing more...
This... this... not there...
It'll be better to put this in
a place no one knows about.
No. No...
- We're on the same side!
- No! No. No.
[He runs in the other direction.]
I said stay there.
- What are you doing?
- We're on the same team.
Kwang Soo.
[Giraffe shows no mercy on women.]
Kwang Soo, think it over.
If you take this cabbage...
Let me just take one.
Think about me.
- Give me one. I'll protect it.
- Think it over carefully.
If I...
[Big-nosed brother is here too.]
Hey, I have something to say.
Something to say!
Jae Suk!
- There's nothing you can do.
- Jae Suk!
There's nothing you can do.
Sorry. Sorry.
You should protect what's yours fool!
We're on the same team!
[What a joke.]
[Fine. You're all dead.]
[Jae Suk has arrived to steal./]
What are you doing?
You think I'd leave it here?
I'm looking around.
Why did you take our stuff?
- Why did you come here?
- Why did you take it?
Why did you take our stuff?
- I said why did you take it...
- We didn't take anything.
- Hey look here.
- Try to take it.
Try to take it!
Take it away!
Jae Suk. Throw it. Throw it!
[Out of nowhere Go Soo appears.]
Wait, this is ours.
[As expected,
Go Soo is fast when it counts.]
[In the end, the purple team
gets nothing.]
- Isn't this too much?
- This is too much.
- I'm going to protect everything.
- Make sure to protect it.
It's okay if I don't get camera time.
I'm just staying inside.
Just stay in there.
Ji Hyo!
- We only need three more.
- Awesome.
All we need is three more.
Things are going our way!
Suk Jin!
Awesome, there's one here!
Look, we have three!
Just two more.
[Yellow team has eight.
Just two more!]
- I'll be back.
- Suk Jin, we just need two more.
We're almost there.
[Now's the time!]
[Time to take out the cabbages
I hid so well.]
Leave it there. The camera! Camera!
Go Soo! What are you doing?
Here. Close the door.
Hurry up and close the door.
- How many are there?
- It's all I can do.
We have eight. Just one more.
Okay. Dong Woon!
Okay, go in! Hurry, go!
- Go in!
- No, keep them out!
- Let go!
- You can't do that.
Go away.
Who was it?
[First she was robbed, now
she's hurled away.]
[Big-nosed brother also hurled away.]
[Go Soo has closed the door!]
Guys! Go Soo! Just find one
and then let me know.
We were good for a couple of months.
[Ignores her]
[Haha has come to take the last cabbage.]
Get in. You're dead.
[No wonder Jae Suk let him in.]
I've waited for this moment.
[This was his chance to steal
the cabbage.]
- I said be quiet.
- Jong Kook! Jong Kook!
- Let me get out. I'm sorry.
- Really?
- Promise me something.
- What?
- Don't come back in here. Promise.
- I promise.
[Hmm? The giraffe arrives.]
[The giraffe's method of taking
the cabbage.]
Give it here.
Suk Jin! Suk Jin!
You can't leave either.
You two are stuck here.
[He just needs two more.]
It's a touchdown.
No! No!
[Hyo Joo takes it right under his nose.]
All we need is one more.
Hurry, hurry.
Behind you! Throw it!
- Suk Jin...
- Kwang Soo...
Jae Suk, one more person!
What kind of jail is this?
[Now that they're locked up,
look for the cabbage.]
[At this moment, Go Soo arrives.]
It's Go Soo!
[Ha Ha tries to hand off a cabbage.]
[Go Soo catches it!]
No, no, no.
[The unstoppable blue team wins!]
Jong Kook, open the door.
Open.
[A war breaks out over a cabbage.]
Why aren't you even ticklish?
- Hang onto it Go Soo. Hang on.
- Okay.
- Just hang onto it.
- Jong Kook. Please.
- Just hang on.
- Come out.
No. Just hang onto it. Just hang on.
Hold on, hold on.
What is this?
- Go Soo, did they take it?
- The cabbage ripped in half.
A ripped cabbage is not valid.
Run Kwang Soo!
[Blue and Yellow Teams need
one more cabbage.]
Take it, take it.
[Ha Ha has left with a cabbage.]
[Kwang Soo escapes with a cabbage!]
[Running to headquarters]
[Hyo Joo gets in the way.]
Director Young!
[The time is now!]
- Throw it here.
- I got it, just go.
- Three!
- Hurry. We got it.
- The cabbage!
- Hurry up.
We're ready! We got it!
The last one! That's ten!
We did it!
[Dumbfounded]
Should we have some soju?
Hyo Joo, let's go.
You worked hard.
- Is it snowing?
- Are you serious?
Are you imagining things now?
It's snowing...
[The mission has finally come to an end.]
- Wow, we even do this.
- This is nice.
I feel like I'm watching TV from the past.
- Wow, what is this?
- This reminds me of Family Outing.
This is Family Outing!
Hey, go and get some fish!
- They already got everything. It's here.
- Hurry and get stuff. They're waiting.
What do we do now?
The previous battle has determined
first, second, and third place.
The first placed team has crushed
garlic and shelled oysters.
This is really hard to get.
Don't worry. We got this.
Second place has peeled garlic
and unshelled oysters.
You guys have it all taken care of,
and we have to prep it.
Third place has unpeeled garlic
and unshelled oysters.
I'm not doing this.
In Family Outing, we went
to catch the oysters.
- That's right, we had to get it.
- This is...
We're going to give you salted cabbage.
- That we need.
- Yes, we'll give it to you.
In front of you all are certain tools.
[Yellow Team: Knife]
[Purple Team: Chef Knife and Knife]
[Blue Team: Knife Set and Cutter]
[Each are given recipes]
You have one hour to prepare.
Make it in one hour.
After you make the kimchi, the taste
will be judged. So try your best...
How will we be judged?
- We will let you know once you're finished.
- Understood.
The person judging will be...
[Who will be the person who
tastes the kimchi?]
What about us?
Are you giving us anything?
Use all the know-how you have.
I know how to do this.
- Hey but where's the cabbage?
- The cabbage...
[Purple team's Gary
is looking up the recipe.]
Put the glutinous rice with the garlic...
- Hyo Joo, remember all this.
- Okay.
- Put the glutinous rice with the garlic?
- Glutinous rice and garlic?
- What's that?
- A paste made out of rice.
[Meanwhile...]
We have it, what next?
[Blue team uses their phone to
get a recipe.]
Hey, faster!
[Food stylist gives input.]
What amount do we need usually?
The amount depends, so just make
sure to put in enough.
Put all the ingredients together
and mix it.
Put the oysters in last
since they break easily.
Okay, put them in last.
Is that it?
Okay, say bye to Go Soo!
Oh my gosh. Hello.
[Thankful for offering input over
the phone.]
Actor Cha Jung Woon's younger sister.
She's a food stylist.
I think we should start off
by combining the ingredients.
[Wake me when the kimchi's ready.]
Must be your first time making kimchi.
- You must have done this before.
- I have.
Rinse this off once.
[Purple team struggles with the unpeeled
garlic and unshelled oysters.]
Hey, can you give us some garlic?
Can't you hear me?
[Totally in the zone]
Go Soo, face forward so
the camera can see you.
He's garlic-crusher Go Soo.
This is Go Soo's crushed garlic.
We will sell at a low price to all ladies.
[Meanwile, Gary is still shucking oysters.]
This is seriously driving me crazy.
He'll go crazy from shucking oysters.
- We need something to cut with...
- Knife, knife. Down there...
Got it. Kwang Soo. Come here.
- Hold on.
- Look here.
Don't get into our space.
It's heavy. Hurry up.
[All they have to work with is a knife.]
[A cutting machine in their possession.]
How do you work this?
Go Soo, do you have a small knife?
What are you trying to do with that?
Hey, this is no joke. Look.
Suk Jin, what are you doing?
Use a knife.
[Even with a knife, moving at a snail's pace.]
I really don't know what to do.
[Secretly takes the chef's knife.]
It's all set.
Let's just use this.
[No one has caught on.]
Awesome. Awesome.
Hey, this is awesome.
- Why did you take that?
- What's wrong?
- I bought this at the market!
- Let it go...
- I said I bought it.
- Give it back.
Okay, we'll give you some oysters.
Let us use that.
Then give us some garlic.
- What kind of deal is that?
- Give us some garlic.
Be humane and give us some oysters.
- How are we supposed to do this one day?
- We'll give you half of our garlic...
Don't give them half...
- We can just peel it.
- Do you want to get in trouble?
How can we give them that?
We can just take that.
Ji Ho, we'll give you the knife.
So give us the oysters.
- Apparently, we can't.
- Seriously, just share.
I shucked three oysters in thirty minutes.
A hip hop warrior is shucking oysters.
Hip hop warrior he says...
From today, I respect all people
who shuck oysters.
Hey there. Should we give you some garlic?
- Give us the oysters.
- Oysters? Then give us the chef's knife.
Kwang Soo, just give it to us.
Go away!
- Don't treat me like a dog!
- Go away!
Fine. Then go and sleep over
there with the dog.
That's too much!
- You keep lingering around.
- I have to shoot here too.
- I'm a celebrity too.
- You've got to be kidding me...
What celebrity?
I've never seen you before.
I watch TV all the time.
Hey over here.
Let us use your chef knife.
Five slices! We'll just use the chef
knife for five slices!
- No we can't do that.
- Just five slices...
[Kwang Soo uses it anyway]
What are you doing? What are you doing?
You have to flip it over.
Hey, you had to flip it over.
Kwang Soo, watch carefully.
- This is how you do it.
- Awesome.
- You can't use brute strength.
- Be gentle.
- So there's a method to this...
- 10 slices.
- Let us use the chef knife.
- So give us the oysters.
What are we going to do with this?
Watch what we do carefully.
Wow!
It's fast.
- Wow!
- It's really fast.
We're done with this radish.
Here we go!
[Envy]
Move! I'm the hero!
Move out of the way.
Don't you see that Go Soo is
getting cut off?
Of all people, Go Soo...
- Like this.
- Should I press it?
- It's working.
- Whoa, it's done.
What have we been doing in thirty
minutes? They did it in one go.
We're done!
Hey you fools! What have
you been doing?
Oh my stomach! It's so funny!
Is there anything else to cut?
- What did you say?
- Wow, look at this.
- Wow, look at that.
- Hey, can you cut ours up too?
- Hyo Joo. Do you need radish?
- We don't need any.
I was just asking.
[30 minutes left]
Hey.
I'm good at shucking oysters now.
Oh Gary, you're good.
Hey, Gary's good at shucking
oysters now.
I have found something I am good at.
Gary, hiya, hiya, hiya!
You can't shake the water off there!
What are you doing?
I'll give you 2000 won,
go over there to play with the kids.
[That's what Kim Chang Jul's mother
always told him!]
- Go over there. Go!
- I'm making kimchi right now.
You fool.
Go and play with your friends.
Why of all days are you hanging around here...
- This is too much.
- Oh seriously.
Why are you acting like such a baby?
[What is he trying to do with the scissors?]
What are you doing?
[A heart?]
Hyo Joo, are you eating that?
It's a heart!
Don't eat it.
Do you eat everything people
bring you?
Why did you eat that?
Hyo Joo, why did you eat that?
What did you do?
- Ah, it's salty.
- Aren't you supposed to eat that?
[Finally, the ingredients are all prepped.]
We need one more.
For the time being...Gary.
Gary.
[Mixing, mixing]
Just put it all in here and mix it all.
- Then we put the seasoning.
- Red pepper first.
I don't think so.
It's okay. Just put this in.
- It doesn't matter.
- Gary bring the red pepper powder.
That's how they did it?
- I don't think is how we do it.
- No, it's fine. It's just that...
Just leave that there.
Give me the glutinous rice.
Take the red pepper powder and mix.
How much red pepper powder?
Let's just put some in for now.
- I think we can put in more.
- If you put it in, the color...
- Don't we have to put more in?
- Yes, put more.
Put in a lot more.
I'm sorry!
Sorry!
I'm going to put in the red pepper powder.
Okay. Hurry!
- Why are you keep copying us?
- Don't be so mindless.
We know what we're doing.
This is our method.
We remember. We're using this
based on what we remember.
Look, they're putting in the sprouts.
It doesn't matter.
You can put it in.
Put it in.
- See, it's finding it's color.
- What is that? What?
- Give me the light brown thing.
- What do you mean light brown?
Hey, take care of the seasoning.
You put in the garlic, right?
Yeah, we put it in.
- You smell it right?
- I can smell it.
It's here, it's here.
Put that in.
Put it in. Put it in.
There. Just put it in.
Just cut it all up. All of it.
I think it's a little bland.
There's too much.
What are you trying to make?
These big ones? You have
to cut it up smaller.
Something's missing.
[What ultimately
is missing from the kimchi?]
The reason it has to be a bit salty is...
If the cabbage goes in,
it'll make it a bit bland.
We need to season it well.
That's why at first, it tastes a bit bland.
Hey!
What is that?
What are you doing?
- We're going to eat it.
- This is awesome!
How can you put in soda?
- Soda?
- Why put in soda?
Let's all protest this!
They can't put in soda!
- We didn't put it in.
- Might as well buy kimchi from the market.
- That's soda.
- Yeah, for us to drink.
I was just going to take a sip
because I was thirsty from making kimchi.
We won't put it in.
Drink water. I'll give you water.
It's so violent here.
- Let's confirm that they won't.
- We won't put it in.
[Hands over soda to staff.]
[Gives up on soda and reconvenes
for new plan.]
Hey Kwang Soo.
Hey! Are you crazy?
What are you doing?
- What are you doing?
- Don't put it in!
- Hey, hey, hey.
- Yeah, I bet it'll be delicious.
You're not supposed to put in that much.
Just put in a little.
Give us the rest.
Taste it.
Why is it so salty?
Let's do it. Give it.
[Finally mizing the oyster sauce
with the cabbage.]
Since it's not ripe, it's really
all about seasoning.
Put all the flavor into the
cabbage leaves.
Hyo Joo's good at this.
- Then you have to press down the cabbage.
- Ah, I forgot to press it down.
- Put it in like this.
- Wow, this is the real deal.
We have to do this right.
[Must snack now and then.]
- How is it?
- How is it? Really?
It's good. Really good.
It's good! It's good!
Hyo Joo, you really are the daughter
of kimchi makers.
- Hyo Joo's family really makes kimchi.
- Really?
- Is it really good?
- Yeah.
- Let me have some.
- It's really good.
Give me some too.
It's really good.
- Is it good or not?
- Good, right?
It's good, it's good.
It's the soda.
- It's so good.
- Here, try some.
It's good, right?
It's salty.
- It's salty?
- It can't be salty.
It's really salty.
Really salty?
- Here do this.
- Put in pickled shrimp.
It's really good.
- Why is it so big?
- It's good.
Try some.
I'm not giving you any!
Hyo Joo, hold it in.
Hyo Joo, don't get mad.
How beautiful!
- How beautiful...
- How beautiful!
[One minute left]
Please finish up and present your dishes.
Please place it here like this.
Feels good to be done.
You all worked hard today.
We will have a blind testing
to have fair judging.
The person doing the judging is...
all of you.
It's all of you.
We are going to take your kimchi
into another room.
After you go in and have a taste
vote for the tastiest kimchi and come out.
- We're confident!
- Please give us more soda.
The team with the most votes
is the winner.
[Which will be the tastiest kimchi?]
Go in and follow your conscience.
Don't vote for your own.
- That's right.
- Let's promise to do that.
We'll promise to do that.
But you know that oyster kimchi
is meant to be a bit salty, right?
Don't say things like that.
First, Ha Ha.
- Please go in.
- I understand.
Bye.
[Rice, kimchi, and spoon all set]
[Can't tell who made what]
I understand.
- You can drink the water.
- Yes, I understand.
Wow, this...
I'll eat it together.
[Seems the kimchi is tasty]
The second dish.
This is a bit salty.
[I made this]
Now it's time to eat.
- They say Ha Ha's eating a lot.
- Hurry up and come out. Don't eat it all.
[Suk Jin, Kwang Soo, Ji Ho]
[Jong Kook, Ha Ha, Go Soo]
[Jae Suk, Hyo Joo, Gary]
It's good. All turned out good.
But the meat was the best.
Write it and share it with the camera.
Show it to us.
- Now put it in the box.
- Understood.
Here I go.
It's too salty.
I think these two are the best.
That one...
I can't eat it.
It's all good.
I think the first one is Ji Ho's.
It's a bit salty.
This one's different.
With rice, number two tastes good.
But just the kimchi, the first
one tastes best.
I have no idea.
- We'll just go, go, go.
- I'll just eat. Nothing else.
All I have to do is taste it to know.
Just go. I'll know.
I think this is our kimchi.
There's no replusion.
Tastes different each time
I have the meat.
I have no idea.
Jong Kook! Stop!
I'm really sick of this!
I really think this is ours.
Did we really make this?
It's all good.
I think all three are good.
This one's realy not good.
Who made this one?
I waited an hour to eat this.
They just eat and choose.
What takes so long?
This one's really bad.
Really bad.
- The first dish...
- Who's was it? It was ours, right?
The first one is the yellow team.
Second one is blue team.
Third one is purple team.
The second dish was good.
I thought I was going crazy.
The meat was the best.
I couldn't eat the second one.
[First ballot: 2]
Third team.
- I really couldn't eat the third one.
- Third one was really bad.
Second team.
- It was the soda.
- It's the soda.
- Third team.
- Yeah, third team!
- I really couldn't eat the third dish.
- But it was unique.
Second team.
It was the soda.
Does our team not come up?
- First team.
- Yes!
You must be crazy.
- Was the first dish good?
- I thought it was.
First dish.
I thought the first dish had something,
but it wasn't good.
First team.
- Awesome!
- That's ridiculous!
What's the tally?
It's 3:2.
- Please, please.
- It should be us.
- Number one! Number one!
- Please!
- Number one!
- Number two!
[And the winner is...
number one]
[The winner of the kimchi making race
is the yellow team!]
- Number one!
- We won Kwang Soo!
[As if they won an award
at a ceremony.]
- It's because you voted.
- Still, Hyo Joo's team got last place.
- But our kimchi was good.
- It was good.
Wow, we take all of this.
Let's grill this and eat it.
Wow, let's eat it!
Meat party!
- Meat party! Kalbi!
- Just give it to Go Soo.
- Give it to Go Soo. Hurry.
- Don't hog it all.
Then what was the point of
this contest?
Let's just go. Go.
Hey Go Soo! Buy it yourself.
Don't take Ji Hyo's.
- Don't take it.
- Hey what is this?
You're just taking it?
Hey guys, take what's yours.
Go. We're going!
We're leaving!
We'll enjoy the meat!
Thank you!
It's going to be scary delicious!
They didn't give us any.
It's beautiful!
- It's beautiful...
- A man's voice came out.
I am the king of Joseon!
- How could you do this!
- Do as I order!
I said look at me!
- At your command.
- I don't want to be king!
Cast a vote. Depending on the result,
the king will change.
That means I can be king.
[Who will protect their throne?]
What kind of king are you?
I'm the king.