Now you are treating me as a spy?
You are now a spy.
There is not only one spy.
Suddenly I am atone.
I will tear it all off.
-He is a spy!-You are a spy right?
Oppa did well!
She's history's strongest!
Lee Da Hae called me.
We arrived!
Where is it?
I found it!
-Hey guys! -Don't come closer!
Da Hae! Da Hae!
Hello.
Long time no see.
But I think it's tiring when I come here..,
It was very tiring escaping alone last time, right?
That time it was a little... yes, it was very tiring.
I am a little afraid. I won't be alone again right?
Choosing teammates. Choose 2 members you want to team up with today find head to their rooms to wake them up personally.
Two people.
-This me it is together? -Yes, together.
A few days ago Lee Da Hae gave me a call.
She said she was nervous and would like me to go on with her.
It is actually because of this that I came,
She said she wanted to do this together. If I choose someone else I will get a scolding.
On a personal scale I would like to choose Gwang Soo.
The members and Lee Da Hae's room numbers.
Should I choose Da Hae or not?
Let's go!
I will go to the 17th floor first.
They are sleeping very deeply.
Wow, how could he be sleeping all the way over here.
He'll be asleep, right?
What is going on?
What are you doing now? It is morning already.
Why are you here?
I didn't expect you would be sleeping like this...
Let me sleep for another 5 minutes...
You can't.
What should I do about your hair?
Regardless, we are a team today.
Hurry go change your clothes.
We are a team,
-Really? -Yes, we are a team. Hurry up.
Did I choose wrongly?
Where are we going?
To find our next team member.
I came because someone asked me to.
-Is that so? -Yes.
Da Hae. Da Hae.
Da Hae? Really? Daebak.
-Maybe drinking coffee. -Oh my. gave me a shock.
Who is that?
Da Hae!
Oppa!
Oppa, I suffered so much yesterday.
That is why I have come.
That is good.
So... be part of our team.
-I've brought HaHa with me. -We are a team?
Yes.
You know that we have escaped together for a year right?
Ah, that's right!
He is an expert in escaping.
That's right.
I kept thinking this team feels familiar.
Since yon have formed your team, we will start the competition.
Is this really? I still cannot believe.
Bundle race.
Search for the one and only real bundle.
The team who holds on to the real bundle till the end wins.
The first mission's location is...
- Jagalchi Market. -Jagalchi Market?
Tins is the bundle that came with you.
Sports bag,
A big teddy bear.
Shoes and...
The biggest TV in the store.
A Korean beef set
I want a coloured T shirt.
Tablet PC.
Desktop computer.
Just give me 1 million wons worth of spring water.
Live house has no water.
Now the remaining members will chase after yon guys.
So yon have to hurry finish the mission.
We are the bundle experts, carrying it around our waists.
We seem to be fated with escaping with a bundle.
You are the expert with bundles.
You hold on to it.
Young Master,
Nampudong Jagalchi market.
That's right.
This is exciting.
Let's go.
Ok, today we must win!
I must win too!
Da Hae, open the bundle.
You must protect it.
Real?
This is the real one, we must not let anyone snatch it, Oppa.
Regarding this type of bundle, I have a deep understanding for it.
I will keep it well.
It will not be snatched away!
I am waiting for my partner right?
Seems like there are 2 guests?
Why is it the both of you?
Why?
Are we forming a team like that?
This is the mission.
Oh, jeez.
Hey. why are you unhappy with the order?
-Do you think this is right? -It will be fine.
Let's cheer first.
I got it.
Kook!
Feel!
Cross!
They said the first team took the bundle away.
However when I saw the microphone just now,
Lee Da Hae's one is gone. HaHa's one is gone as well.
Then there is another guest as well.
Stop staying on TV and go solve unsolved crimes. Work for our country!
I think I really should.
I really want to try.
Gary.
Already.
We are the last again.
But who is today's guest?
That's right.
In Busan.
Whose hometown is in Busan.
I can't talk well in the mornings.
When I came down from the elevator, some of the cleaning ladies,
were talking about those who left first.
HaHa and Lee Da Hae.
They said another name as well.
Who is it?
They said Choi Ji Woo is here.
I'm not sure if it's right.
I really am her fan.
Really?
-Yes. I used to watch her dramas. -Really?
Will it be all right if we do not label it?
What about using perfume?
With the perfume we will know which one it is by smelling.
Should I rub it?
My feminine fragrance.
Wow. you are really not easy from the start of the morning!
Jagalchi.
We've arrived! We've arrived!
I am starting to get nervous.
Hyung it is here.
We've arrived.
I am going crazy.
I am really going crazy!
Ah, going crazy!
Oh hyung, check out the feel,
-Wow. -Huh? Oh.
This is great, oppa.
It really smells like Mokpo from my childhood.
Is that so?
Hello.
-Oh hyung, here. -Do we put it here?
Yes. put it here.
Oh? Who's here other than us?
-These two are fakes. -Yes.
You have to pass the mission to choose the real one first.
Yes.
Ok then. I’ll give you the Jagalchi Market mission,
After a team member sits in a hasin, buy the correct item in the box to succeed.
Basin?
Yes. the basin's there.
-Ah. -Hey.
-Is Miss Lee Da Hae sitting in it? -Yes.
Both of you can't look. Mr Halia. come over here.
-We can’t look? -Yes, you can't look.
Miss Lee Da Hae. come over here and put your hand in.
Huh? What is it, what, what?
Just use your hand to confirm what's inside and buy it.
-Don't be afraid. Don't be scared. -Don't look.
-No... -Look at me, look at me.
Ah! Seems like it's moving!
What?
Is it moving?
-Fell it properly, we have no time. -No, we have to do it quickly.
-This, we still have to buy this back. -Hey.
It's some kind of fish.
It's fish, with scales.
It also has a tail and it seems to have eyes.
That's of course.
Hey, you've already touched it.
It's soft, soft.
Is it this thick?
-Oh, a little... -Hairtail. hairtail.
-Is it hairtail? -Hairtail.
-But that's small. -Hairtail? But doesn't hairtail has big fins?
-I don't know, this is too hard. -Get on quickly.
-It’s a fish. -Get on.
-We have to do it this way. -One, two, .three.
-Lean towards Haha. -Like this?
Let's just buy it here.
Take a good look.
Is it this one?
What are you looking for?
Now, only her hand knows.
-Oppa. it's not this. -It's not this one, it's not this one.
Hang on, can't I touch it?
-It’s too big, -Oh, right.
-Fish, fish. -Over there, over there.
-Let’s have a look, -Over here, over here.
Hey, there's so many here.
-Eotnoni, what's this? -This is dried filefish.
-What's this called? -Halibut - Is that so?
-Halibut. -Halibut?
It's flat like this.
Was it wide?
It's bigger than this,
Ah. a bigger one. What's slightly bigger than this?
I cut off its fins with a pair of scissors.
If its fins were cut off by scissors, then this may be it
Halibut?
-I think this is it. -Halibut?
Yes, halibut. But not those dried ones.
-Not the dried ones. -Yes.
Let us have a Look at the halibut.
Get one, get one.
Take them all.
Isn't this too big?
-Here, put it here. -Isn't that too big?
Is it the same feel?
Oh?
Touch its fins.
The fins are very soft.
No, it was this big.
This is it. Let's just buy this.
Halibut, halibut.
Was it that flat?
Hey. the money, the money.
Thank you.
-Oh, oh. -Oh, it's here.
Hey, are we second?
Yes. you're second.
Is that so? Why are we second? They left before us.
-That team got lost on the road. -Ah, is that so?
See, hyung.
-Ok, there are three hundles. -Yes. yes.
One of them is the real bundle,
If you're the first to pass, you'll get to choose one bundle first.
Ah, is that so?
-Go, go, what's the game? -Hurry, hurry.
Ok, one team member sits in a basin, buy the correct item in the box to succeed.
Buy the item inside this box?
Ah, what's this?
Oh, no!
Is it hairtail?
Ji Hyo,
I really hate this sort of scary stuff.
Hey, how did you guys reach so early?
Oh, they're here.
How did you get here so early?
Why are you so late?
We took the wrong way.
And also, this is probably...
This is Ja"gaichi Market,
it's just some kind of fish.
Just get the feel, 'get the feel.
Just get the feel.
Just the feel.
-Hey, how can you do this? Ji Hyo's a girl. -It's alright.
-She's a girl -It’s fine.
-Hey, put your hand in... -Hey. don't!
Don't do that, don't!
-I already said I’m very scared now. -Grab it at once!
Hey, it's a scorpion, a scorpion.
Hey..
Why would there be scorpions in Jagalchi Market?
Hey. it's a large crab.
Is it dangerous?
It's safe.
-It's safe, just grab it. -Ji Hyo, don't worry.
-What did you feel? -What is it what is it?
That's it, Ji Hyo.
-What is it? -You touched it?
It’s still alive!
It's something alive.
It's alive.
Wait a moment!
Ji Hyo. don’t worry.
What's this?
Did you touch it?
Oh, it's a fish?
-What's it like? -But the fish isn't moving.
Five, four...
I was slapped by its tail!
The tail hits you? Who hit you with its tail?
Who slapped you with its tail?
-Ji Hyo. do you know? -I don't know.
Ah, so this is alive?
What was its size?
Oppa, it was, it was...
About this big?
Was it thick or not?
I felt it like this.
It was very slippery.
It was, it was like a fish.
Is there something famous around here?
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
A famous thing in Jagalchi Market.
No, no, oppa.
Skinny people are having a hard time carrying.
Ji Hyo is not really skinny.
-Ji Hyo's is not skinny. -Hyung, is that it?
What?
-A croaker? It’s not it.
You put it down because it was heavy, right?
-Seems like I'm right. -Ji Hyo!
Put your hand in.
Feel what it's like. Feel around.
-Don't take out your hand. -Oh. seems like there's nothing?
Hey, how can you do this?
-Don't take it out. -There isn't anything.
-Oh hang on, hang on! -Hang on, stay still.
What is it? Touch it.
Touch it well.
Did you touch it. did you touch it?
Seems like lt's a loach.
It's about this big. Let's go first.
Ok, sef off.
Hyung, it's a loach?
Hang in there. We're there.
-Who’s with... -Ah^Mr Oh Ji Ho!
-Hyung. -We re here.
They said Choi Ji Woo was coming.
So it's Oh Ji Ho.
Ah really, where...
You look like a servant among the three.
Hyung. it's the same for you in your team.
Hey, they're a couple of lovers going out in secret. What are you doing there?
This love triangle isn't a joke.
Aigoo really.
-Let's see if we're right. -Ok let's go.
-We're.here. -What did you say?
Move forward.
Hey, a fish that's this big.
What type of fish is this big?
If it's from the sea. it's definitely not loach.
The other teams carried girls in the basin!
Please be correct.
-Lets get this in one try. -We're in trouble if its not the one.
I think it's too big. right?
It's bigger but maybe it was a baby.
What's the name of the fish?
-It's halibut. -Halibut.
The correct answer is...
Its right, it's right.
We'll give you a halibut set.
We'll give you all of this 10.000 won!
This answer is...
incorrect.
Incorrect.
Going crazy!
I'm about crazy.
Ah, I'm seriously going crazy.
Hurry, hurry.
Hurry.
Hey, we were too focused on the fins.
This.,.you stop moving about!
-Hey, touch the face. -Turn your body a little.
It's big, it's big.
It's prickly.
Oh. Hang on, stay still, stay still.
Oh! Oppa, I know it. I know it.
-Ah Ji Hyo. this fish... -No oppa, it's like this.
It's about that size. How I do you put it? There are no scales and slippery.
Is that so?
Is there any fish without scales?
Mackerel.
-Do mackerels not have scales? -Mackerel,
Sailfin sandfish.
-What? -Sailfin sandfish.
Sailfin sandfish!
-That's right, boss. It seemed like sailfin sandfish. -It felt like a sailfin sandfish.
-Sailfin sandfish, sailfin sandfish. -It is very slippery right?
Boss, is it right?
It will be great if this is right.
Here you go, boss.
-Thanks. -Thank you!
Let's take a look at the fish there first.
-See which one it is. -Hyung, take a good look.
-In the water, the fish was this big. -Alright, what was it like?
-It was thin. -Thin?
-Thin, thin. -Was it slippery?
-Right, it was slippery. -Then it's an octopus.
-No. no. -It's a fish.
It's a fish.
Was it a fish?
-An eel? -It's very slippery.
Aha!
A sea eel.
Did you say sea eel?
-How big was it? -It's a sea eel. hyung.
-About this? -Hyung!
This is Busan after all.
-One, two, three. -Slowly.
You guys make me uneasy.
Hang on.
Hyung, hyung.
-Hey, just think of me as Lee Da Hae. -Hyung, how?
-Think of me as Lee Da Hae. -It's so weird,
Hyung. Wait a sec.
Where do you sell sea eel, eomonis?
-Where? -Basement.
-They have sea eels? -Yes.
Hey, we have to go to the basement.
Not the basement.
Right, this one.
-What’s this? -This one, this one.
That's rock trout.
Rock trout!
We have to feel the rock trout.
-Rock trout is right. -We have to touch it.
-I'll know once I touch it. -That's what we thought at first.
-This is it! -It's right!
-Are you 100% sure its right? -Rock trout, so it was you, it was you!
Ok.
-We're done. -Thank you.
-Wow. -Get on.
It looks delicious.
We have to go quickly.
We have no time for delicious food.
Hey, don’t you think that looks delicious?
Let’s eat one, hyung.
Let's try one.
Let's go! We'll finish quickly and come back later.
-Right, right. -Let's go, let's go.
-Get our act together. -Let's go.
Have a bite before you go.
Should we?
-Really? -Ah, do we have to?
Aunty is preventing us from going back.
Mm. it's so delicious.
-It's good right? -Yes.
Is there any rice?
The fish-we chose is, precisely...
Sailfin sandfish.
This fish is...
- not it. -Jeez.
It's a completely useless sailfin sandfish!
-How do you know it's useless? -Other than being useless there isn't any other.
But. this is 10.000 won...
-The stuff will turn it into something delicious later -Yes. this is delicious. it will be delicious.
This is such a pity.
Ok. ten seconds.
Ah!
Not being able to see this is very terrifying.
Yoo Jae Suk!
Yoo Jae Suk, Yoo Jae Suk!
Hyung, you can do it!
I thank you for cheering me on like this.
Touch the fish.
Hyung, this is all for simply touching a fish!
Ten seconds.
What to do.
-What to do? -Hyung.
Just put your hand and the fish will do it for you.
It knows how to do it.
-Hyung, hyung. -Hang on, hang on.
It's not usual right?
Ok, stop!
-Not yet, we haven't... -Jeez, it's here!
There really is something.
I got it at the end.
I touched a hit of it.
You have to grab it, hyung.
We bought it,
-Carrying a guy is too tiring. -But the fish felt ordinary to me.
Oppa. let's take a look before coming back.
Ok, what's this?
-Hyung, look. -Hyung, is that right?
Is this right?
Feel it. feel it.
-Hey, it wasn't this big. -Just feel it first.
Oh. this is it.
Ah, this is the one, this one.
Let's go.
One, two, three,
Sea eel.
This is..,
This is...
- tiie correct answer. -Yeah!
Yeah!
-We survived, we survived. -Hey!
I told you we'd survive!
Kim Jong Kook. Kim jong Kook.
Hey, seems like someone got it right.
No way, that won't happen.
-Aren't they in front of the bundles? -Lei's move quickly. Hurry, hurry.
Hey, we have to choose the real one.
Only one of these bundles is the real one.
Hyung, they've switched them.
-He's truly the Commander. -He really is the Commander.
They won't find the real bundle.
They won't get it.
Please. I beg you.
It's on the right side.
Yes, it's on the right side.
Hey, these two are loosened but this one is tight.
But this is too light.
-It's fine, it's fine. -Which one did they pick?
-Go to the used bookstore in Bosu-dong anti find the Running Man... -Let's go, let's go.
-Ok. -You'll be surprised.
This is the correct answer.
Ok.
Hey.
-This kid's name is... -Rock trout, rock trout.
One. two, three!
Rock trout!
You're surprised, right?
Ok. this is...
This is...
-The correct answer. -Yeah!
I'm seriously going crazy, seriously.
-I'm going crazy. -I'm just about crazy.
Two, three. Crazy.
Let's go. let's go,
-We're the only one who seem to enjoy this. -Yes, we're the only one enjoying it.
You get away!
You should get lost.
I'm the one chosen!
My feelings...
Hey!
The one who affects my mood.
I think this is the one.
I think this is it.
-it was the right shape but I think it was re-wrapped a little. -They must be shuffled.
It was shuffled.
It's shuffled but I think this is the one.
We choose this one.
The fish you brought back...
This isn't the correct one.
Ah, oppa.
-This mackerel, please accept it as the correct answer. -Definitely not.
Being born in this ocean...
-What will it become? -What will it become?
What does it turn into?
Consider this mackerel's position for once.
Ok. set off.
Da Hae. hyung, take a look if it's real of fake.
Please.
Please, please!
I think ours is the real one.
I feet it's the real one.
The real one. the real one.
Please, please!
Is it the real one or a fake? May it be the real one!
Ah, it's a fake.
Ah, its a fake.
Seems like they didn't change the position. 0.
It's the real one!	0.
The real one!
It's the real one!
Ah, it's real!
Hyung, these two are loosened, this one is tighter.
But this is too, bulky.
-Then I choose this too. -This doesn't seem like it.
-This one, this is the right one. -This one, this one.
-Swap their positions. -Right.
They'll think this is the correct one.
Ah. a fake.
Then we have to get it back during the next game.
So the team in front took it.
-We have to remember this one. -Right, we have to remember it so that we don't pick this.
Then, shall we mark this as a fake?
How?
I'll apply, a bit of this on it.
Oh good. good.
Lip gloss.
Great, great. Good job.
The opposing side will think it's actually the real one.
-They'll mistake it as the real one. -That's right.
-But we're not sure if those in front have the real one. -Right.
-Anyway this isn't it. -This isn't it.
We can't pick this.
-Ok, set off. -Set off.
Slippery slippery fish! A mullet!
A mullet.
Ok. this is...
- the correct answer. -Ah!
Open it first.
You never know it could be...
Huh?
-Jeez, it's a cushion. -See, its not the one.
Ji Ho hyung seems to have it.
Miss Lee Da Hae called him.
-She planned to come here and win on Running Man. -Seriously. Lee Da Hae is doing it all*.
I'll do everything.
There's also a servant following them?
Servant...
-Servant Ha. -Servant Ha.
-Seems like it's bleeding. -Does it hurt?
-Seems like you were pricked by the fish. -The fish?
We’re at the Bosu-dong Bookstore Alley.
It's one of Busan's famous destinations.
We have to hurry, hyung.
Let's go.
It's like Hong Kong, Hong Kong,
-Over there. -Wow, are these all second-hand books?
There’s Myeok PD.
-We're the first. -Myeok PD.
-Your expression's a bit... -We’re still alive.
Find a book with a Running Man sticker on it.
Where do we find it? Everything there?
How many books are there?
Ah, in here?
Where do we find it?
The bookstore's really big.
There are more upstairs?
Hey, how do I find this?
In here?
There’s a bookstore here.
-There's a mission here. -We have to find something.
Find a book with a Running Man sticker on it.
How do we find it among so many books?
Let's find it quickly, let's find it quickly.
What? Why are there so many bundles?
Why?
There are around 300,000 books in here.
Really, why make the game so easy? Only 300,000 books.
Hello!
Hey, look at that. Oh, it’s so cool. Oh, hello.
Wow, cool.
Hello boss.
Hey, this is cool.
Find a book with the Running Man 'R' sticker.
Topics related to Running Man?
Foreign language? Running Man... English...
Sports.
Because it's Running.
Hey. why are you looking in the 'Sex' section?
It may be in here.
Why are you looking at the ’Adult' section?
Ah, seriously.
I want to show them that I can find it.
This time, I'll find it first.
This is my first time at a second-hand bookstore.
Hey, hey.
Wow, they even have this here.
There are old dictionaries here.
There should be one here.
How do we find it?
-It's not inside the book, right? -No oppa. it should be stuck on the outside,
Oppa.
Huh?
Oh.
HaHa!
Oppa, oppa.
Ok, let's go!
What?
I'm going crazy.
You found it?
-I really found it. -Where did you find it?
Wow, really?
You really found it.
Wow.
-Where did you find it? -Hyung, where did you find it?
Up there.
The Purple Team can choose...
Yeah!
-Yes, yes! -Yes!
-Choose two. -Oh?
0nce you touch it. you choose it.
Two and four?
Two?
-They can take two? -Two.
-Ok, let's go. -Daebak.
Let's go, oppa. Let's go.
Hey, where at Haeundae?
Go to Haeundae Beach to find the Running Man banner.
Take a look, Ji Hyo and Gary.
Firstly, let’s...
But. it seems all of them are cushions?
-Oh, hyung! -What?
Hey this, what’s this?
-Daebak! Daebak! -Hey. this really no joke.
We did it. We did it.
Hey. we turned the tables, thanks to you!
It's done.
No.
What's with this bundle? Jeez.
-The team with the real one must be excited. -They must be Feeling great,
Ji Hyo.
Oppa, I'm sorry.
Sleep more, sleep more.
-Ji Hyo. -A little more, a little more.
Ji Hyo seemed like she was dancing the way she was dead in sleep.
Miss Blank.
You're so funny.
-Oh. there it is. -Where?
Oh, there it is.
Oh, in front there.
There seems to foe something at the beach.
Hey, it's awesome.
I'm off!
Come get me.
-It's so cool. -Catch me!
I'm the president of Haeundae's sand!
Hey, Gary. Wow.
Wow, the seagulls!
Isn't this, the ideal beach?
Do I put it here?
Oh, they'll be mixed up?
If you pass quickly, you can take it.
What are we doing?
Please give us the mission.
One, two. three. Tada!
The Running Balls that we haven't seen in awhile.
Where do we go?
Can you see the four flags there?
Find the Running Balls with your own names on them and bring them here for passing confirmation.
You can set off together.
Hello!
Lollol!
-Hyung! -This is too...
When can we find them?
Hey, there's something here.
-There seems to be something... -Hyung. There seems to he something here?
What's all this?
-Hey, suck it up. Ji Hyo. -Ah. seriously.
How do we find it here?
How many are there?
How deep are they buried?
Are there tools?
-How long wilt it take us to find them? -Where are they?
For your information, they're not buried very deep.
Is that so?
Fhere are about 800 balls here.
800?
What, 800?
800...
This is too...
So many people are watching as if we're having a huge contest going on.
Thank you!
It seems like an international competition here.
-We have to look here... -Oh, oppa.
-Something like this. -Hey, Ji Hyo. You're really like a ghost.
Do we open this?
Oh!
What?
I's not it.
Atgoo.
Hey.
Oh!
-What? -Nothing.
-What? -t's not it!
But how do we find this?
Oh!
Lee Da Hae.
Hyung, hide it!
Hide it, oppa.
Hey, the seagulls are here.
Search for it for me!
Lollols...
Search for it! Guys, help us search for it!
Come over here and dig!
Quickly help us dig! Guys!
Quickly help us dig, dig!
Dig, quickly! Dig!
Dig! Yes, that's Tight! Help us look for it!
There's my name, hers, and Gary's!
Look for it wholeheartedly!
Hey Gary, what are you doing?
-Hyung! -Don't you see this splendor?
Hyung! What's happening?
Lol lol!
Why are there so many of them suddenly?
Guys! Quickly dig up the place!
The one who aids me!
Ah, it's not like that. I'm asking you to dig the beach...
Oh what's this?
Quickly, hurry up and look for it.
What's going on?
I’m so tired.
Ah. if you found ours, give it to us.
There's nothing, there's nothing.
-We haven't found anything. Really. -Not even one?
Yeah yeah.
Of course we would give it to you if we found them.
Oppa, I found Haha oppa’s.
Where?
Ah why do we always only find theirs?
Let's dig deeper.
Ok ok.
Bury it, bury it.
They're here! Blue Team is here!
It’s so tiring!
What's this?
Looks like we have to find something?
Hyung!
What?
-It was like this during my time at FO, too. There's more around the flags -A treasure hunt?
Is that so?
Hmm, Am I right?
There, there, there!
There’s too many people here. Go there...
Yah!
Already?
That's impossible!
We just came and we found it!
Gwang Soo!
Hey, he found it in 2 seconds! 2 seconds!
Oh!
Ji Hyo!
Quickly, quickly!
Wait, wait!
Da Hae's, it's Da Hae's again!
Why do we keep finding other people's?
Oppa, I buried someone else’s again!
You did?
Hahahaha.
Hello.
You guys be more serious in-your search!
- Ah. what's this? - Ah!
You want a piece of me?
Oppa! He found it!
I found Lee Da Hae's!
Ah, this is really.
Yah!
Is there really something here?
Is there really?
- And what are you doing? - Why are you poking your nose into this?
The game isn't over yet!
Get lost!
Because of you, nothing goes right.
You too!
The one who irks me!
Scram!
The one who has an incomprehensible face!
Hey!
Scram! It was all because of you!
Oh, but then again, it is fortunate that all of you are laughing so happily.
It seems like digging in the sand is funny? It's not too bad?
Yes-
Digging in the sand seems OK. Seeing how everyone is enjoying it.
Say Ho-Oh!
Ho-Oh-
I love you, Busan.
Whoo.
Let's make a wave!
Thank you everyone! I will definitely win!
I will work hard!
Hey!
Hey, you need to work!
I found it!
Whose? Whose? WHOSE?
- Whose is that? - Yoo Jae Suk's.
Found Yoo Jae Suk's running ball!
Ya!
Found it!
Why do I keep finding others'?
Where are these balls?
They seemed like they were buried quite deeply?
Hohohohoho
I found it!
- Gary! Gary! Gary! - Looks like they found it?
Gary! Gary!
Yours is the only one left.
We are left with Ji Hyo's.
Ya, Gwang Soo! There's nothing even if you dig deeper.
There's sea water sprouting out here.
Ah, there's nothing here! What should we do?
What should we do now?
Ya, all we have to do is to find Song Ji Hyo's!
Ah Da Hae's! It's Da? Hae's again!
I found Kim Jong Kook's!
We found it!
Oppa!
Yes! we’re done!
Where?
Lee Gwang Soo! Lee Gwang Soo!
That team seems like they are done?
Ji Hyo.
Hurry, hurry, hurry!
- Ah, it's Lee Da Hae again! Lee Da Hae! - Ah. why are you treating me like this?
Let me verify the running balls. Please hold the ones with your names.
Song Ji Hyo. Gary.
Thank you!
All right, please choose 3 of these.
If you pick it up, it's over.
Oh but, please tell us if the bundles are in their original places.
You can at least tell us this, right?
I really don't know.
You really don't know?
Hyung, there're 3 here.
- Let's pick these 2. - Yes, that's right. That's right.
These 2,
And then...
Hyung, let's choose the last one over there.
Ok!
Go to Nurimaru APEC House and look for the Running Man banner. Let's go.
We just need to find Ji Suk hyung's.
How can there be nothing? Not even one?
Oh Ji Ho.
Ah, Oh Ji Ho, deeper, in deeper!
Hey, they should know where the balls are right?
Cm going crazy!
I'm going crazy! Really!
I'm going crazy!
I found it! Oh Ji Ho! Oh Ji Ho found! Oh Ji Ho!
Oppa, here!
Yoo Jae Suk! Yoo Jae Suk!
Ah where is Suk Jin hyung's ball? I don't see it anywhere!
Song Ji Hyo.
Ji Suk Jin!
Ah, what's this?
Let's go!
Ah, oppa!
Only oppa's is left!
Did you really put in mine?
Ah, I'm really going crazy.
Ah, what's wrong with us today?
Haha! I found it!
Oh you found it? Found?
Oppa, open the bundles and check the contents first.
This isn't it, this isn't it.
It's one of those two. obviously.
- Oh. it's not this one. - Ji Hyo, it's not?
It's not?
Looks like they got mixed up.
- It's really not there? -Oh!
- It's here. wow. - Ah. it's there.
- It's here. - It‘s really there.
-We did it. -Daebak. Daebak.
Wow.
Aigoo, digging around was worthwhile.
Exactly.
If we can keep it well at the final venue, we can win today.
Gary. I'm grateful to you.
It's not it?
This isn't it.
I didn't tie it up like that.
- This one is not too? - Yeah, they're all not.
The one who has the real bundle.
Jae Suk has it.
- We have those marked with lip gloss earlier. - They're all here.
Just like it was.
It shouldn't be with Jong Kook oppa's team.
Jong Kook said earlier that theirs has no mark.
That's why, it's with Jae Suk oppa.
We're here!
Get the bundle, the bundle.
That's the real one, I made three folds.
In this venue. you will carry out the final mission for one hour.
Ok.
After precisely one hour, the time will stop.
The team possessing the real bundle will win.
- But, there are a tiger and a lion on the other team - The other sides are too strong.
So you have to take advantage of the early arriver and hide well.
Use any method to protect it for an hour,
- Gary, you take care of the sack. - No, hyung.
- Jl Hyo, take it. - Oppa, let's go in first.
Really sorry, I have no confidence.
- Jl Ho is weak in front of women. - Let's just go in first.
Ji Hyo. we trust you,
Gary, let's go up.
We have to check out the passageways and all.
It's really cool.
The one hour has started since the first team entered.
If your nametag's torn off then they can take ft from you,
Let's do it.
Kook!
Feel!
Touch!
- Cross! - We have to do well.
Ok. let's go.
Nametags? Right. It's time to use my strength.
Should we snatch it from the second team?
Even if we snatched it. only one team will be left.
I think it's with Ji Hyo.
Ji Ho oppa will take care of Ji Hyo eonnie.
I'll take care of her.
Oh, hello.
Aigoo.
Do you want to swap?
- Huh? No. You can swap with me. - Let's swap, let's swap.
Let's swap.
Let's swap, let's swap. Aigoo, nice to meet you.
Ok, this will do.
Okay, let's put them all down.
Ok, let's shout 'fighting'.
Blossoming flower in Dongbaekseom.
The target is Yoo Jae Suk!
-It's definitely with that team. -Yes.
-Definitely with that team. - First, let's...
Let's ally, let's ally.
-So what should we do? -We have little time so we have to hunt them.
Hyung, Our hyung!
That's right.
Hyung, you know we only have one hour right?
-We have to hurry. -We STILL have one hour.
Let's go, let go,
-Hyung is so positive. -It's 6 vs 3,
Where are you?
You better hurry off and escape.
They're all here, all of them are here.
Hurry, hurry.
Hey. let's get out. The elevator, the elevator.
How long do we have to escape for?
Hang on.
Do we really have to do this with such a beautiful background?
Hang on. firstly...
With this situation, we have to keep moving.
But hyung, everyone now knows that our bundle is the real one.
Right, of course.
It would feel better to have mine torn off,
-I'm seriously going crazy. -Why did we pick the real one?
Hey, can we swap?
Oppa, you know this will make you a clear target, right?
I know.
Why can't I tell lies properly?
We can't lie either, we'will act strangely if we do.
Ji Ho, Ji Ho.
Here, here.
They're here. Hurry, hurry. They're here.
Jae Suk hyung.
We have to keep moving now.
Oppa. I will really lose weight like this.
How about taking the stairwell?
Right, right.
It should be the one being grabbed tightly like this.
The person who holds it tightly.
Ji Hyo was grabbing it tightly like this.
It may be swapped by now,
Hang on! Hyung! Hang on!
Jong Kook hyung!
-Hyung, Ji Ho hyung tried to tear mine off! -What?
-What did you say? -Ji Ho hyung tried to tear mine off!
We're screwed!
-Why did you do that? -Hyung!
No, that's not what I meant.
-Hyung. -Come here.
Hey, come here.
It's over!
That's not what I meant,
-I was behind him and I suddenly felt like tearing it. -Ji Ho! You can't do that!
That's not what I meant to do.
Hey, you can't do that,
-I have never torn one before. -So, you're practising?
-So, you're practising? -I was practising...
What kind of practice is that?!
Think of the person involved!
You shouldn't do that.
That's why I just tore half,
-That's why I only tore half. -Ah, is that so? - Right.
Hey, also, although we’re in an alliance, don't be too at ease.
I was together with Da Hae noona and Ji Ho hyung.
Oh, it shocked me.
Come this way.
Hide yourself there.
Can this hide a person?
There's no one,
-I don't think there’s anyone here. -There's no one here.
We have to spread out.
Is there an emergency exit?
Could they be upstairs?
There, over there!
Hurry, hurry,
-They went outside. -Over there. Outside, outside.
We have to tear theirs off, there's no time.
Let's finish this,
-The mission ends in thirty minutes, the mission ends in thirty minutes -Only thirty minutes?
30 minutes?
Ah, this won't do. I'm going crazy.
Get in.
Go in, go in, they're coming here.
They're coming. Hurry,
That door's not locked.
Ah, I'm seriously going crazy.
They're near, they're around here.
They're definitely here.
The back, the back.
So you were here.
I almost couldn't find you, hyung.
Ah, really.
Ji Ho, really...
We will go out first, Ji Ho.
Let's go together, hyung.
I know I know, come in.
Hey. hey. hey, hey!
They are here!! They are here!! Second floor!
Wait, this is the jail.
Why did you come in?
This is the jail, so let's go out.
Hyung, first let's change bundles.
No. this is not the one.
No, this... I can’t!
Ah, this is really not the one.
Can't you change this?
-Why can't you change? -I can't change this, I can't change this,
I'm suggesting that, in exchange for not eliminating them, that we exchange bundles,
-Hyung, this suggestion is not bad. -Lets go out first before talking.
-Let's go out first, this is the jail. -Let's go out first, this is the jail.
-You go out first. -You go out first.
You go out first.
-You go out first. - Let's play scissors paper stone to decide.
Scissors, paper, stone.
I won. Please go out first.
-Scissors, paper, stone. -You!
-I am just using this method of scaring him. -Hyung! Didn't I say not to leave my side even for a moment!
Come quickly.
Go out.
Hey there! We won’t tear your name tags, just give us 1 bundle.
Just give us one.
Give me Song Ji Hyo’s bundle. Song Ji Hyo's!
-No... - No, if we just leave like this, wouldn't it be too cowardly?
-Then take mine, -Okay, whichever.
Whichever one is fine. Just give it to us.
-Then take mine. -Okay, whichever,
-Give it to me, Give it to me! -No, no...
Give it to me!
Just any one.
Give me one.
Wait, oppa. wait...
Right now, you're attacking, right?
-I'll give mine. -Ok, let's do this.
-Give it to me! -No, no...
Give it to me!
-Just give it to me. Give me! -No, no...
Give me one.
Right now, you're attacking, right?
Oh!
It's Haha!
Hyung!
What did you do?
We had to have Jong Kook hyung eliminated.
We have to eliminate the strong ones first!
You did well.
Kim Jong Koofi, out' Kim Jong Kook, out!
Oppa, lets eliminate Haha.
Ok.
Da Hae is behind us.
Because she follows so quietly.
Hold on. Ji Hyo, Ji Hyo.
-Hey, they're here! -Hey! We...
Catch him, catch him!
Oppa!
Looks like it's the one Ji Hyo is holding!
Catch her, catch her!
Quickly catch her, now!
It's done.
Why is it me?
You're grateful, aren't you?
Do you want to win?
Thank you.
Ji Ho. there's not much time left, we have to start attacking.
There's no time, there's no time!
Da Hae, don't smile so much.
What do we do?
Where are you going?
Haha is following me here.
So be quiet.
Go film from over there!
Hey! Da Hae!
Ahh!
Hey! Da Hae! Da Hae!
Hyung, isn't Haha in danger?
-He seem to be shouting. -No, ,. There are two people.
Da Hae!
Haha. out.1 Haha. out!
Awesome!! Awesome!!
Why?
-Haha is out. -Doesn't matter, even if he is out...
It's mine!
Ah. you're out, too!
Hello.
Hyung! Are you doing fine, hyung!
How are you hyung!
I need to make a trip to the toilet.
Ah, it's so hot.
Oh, so this is the jail.
Ah, I feel calm.
I was wrong, hyung!
Sometimes you are possessed by other people?
I'd rather you say that.
Just so long as you let me believe in you.
Gwang Soo, you kneel down too.
You too! You are also like that.
Do you want to be Hit?
He is also possessed, Hyung!
What's the matter?
He, too, gets possessed!
How does he do this?
Hyung!
Oppa. awesome!
Oppa. what happened?
Oppa. how did you do it?
Oppa!
I set a trap... A trap...
Who?
I almost died.
I set a trap... Haha followed me in first...
HaHa saw me and followed.
I used all my energy
I eliminated HaHa, but.
Da Hae also came in.
As HaHa left, 1 closed the door.
So I ripped off Da Hae's tag as well.
But I'm now confused. Whose bundle is real?
I can't tell anymore.
I was holding it, but I don’t think I am now.
It's either mine or Gary's,
It seem like it's Ji Hyo's.
- Let's see. - Ji Hyo's, Ji Hyo's.
There is, there is.
It's Ji Hyo's,
Oh! It's Suk Jin hyung.
Hyung! Come here for a moment!
Say we'll give him his present.
Oppa!
Come over here!
Hyung! Come here for a moment!
Hyung, how are you going to do this alone?
Hey, do you think I have only been tricked once or twice?
It’s real!
Hyung! Come over here!
We have something to give you.
What?
We must spread the trap now.
Huh?
We're spreading the trap.
Hyung! Hyung, what present did you choose?
-Me? -Yes,
- Computer. - Eh?
Computer.
We will give that to you hyung, will it do?
- Do you give me your word? - Yes.
Really.
We already have a computer, at home.
So, it's like this?
Then it’ll be like this?
After we eliminate Ji Ho, then...
That's right!
After that then tear my tag off, at the end...
We just have to give you the computer, hyung.
Of course.
Jae Suk hyung is still alive?
He's still alive?
He wasn't eliminated?
So he ripped off both their name tags?
Really.
- Hyung, we will be here. - All right.
You'll be here? You want me to eliminate him and come back?!
- Of course. - What?!
Hyung, you were still alive?
Who? Jae Suk?
Yes, I survived.
3 vs 2 is very disadvantageous.
3 vs 2 is disadvantageous.
But Ji Ho, though 3 vs 2 is disadvantageous, it is 4 vs 1 now.
There is not much time left, it is about time to see the ending.
Really, just now.
- There are stairs behind. - I got it.
Oh, Suk Jin hyung.
In this case the alliance is broken.
Turn, hyung, turn!
Turn, hung, turn!
Turn the other way!
- That's right! -Who?
Great!
Also, if our team wins, we will definitely give hyung a present.
I am so curious right now.
How nerve-wrecking!
Who?
You don't need to be surprised. Just sit.
Now Suk Jin hyung is dead.
It is 2 vs 1 now.
- Yes, 2 vs 1. - Jae Suk hyung and Gary versus Ji Ho hyung.
There is still competition.
Ah, hyung.
Do you want to play Rock Scissors Paper?
Oh, that is not a bad idea.
Really, let’s play one round.
- Just one round. - And after that?
Then the loser will cleanly let himself be eliminated.
- Really? - Yes.
Hyung, wait a moment.
Isn't this disadvantageous to us?
Isn't this only for fools?
No, the chances are 50/50 anyway.
It is just do or die.
Hang on a moment.
- Let us have a discussion first. - All right, discuss.
We will discuss, hang on.
There is only 5 minutes left.
We got it.
We will discuss for a bit.
Ok, then.
Honestly, before the discussion...
Oh!
Because you're taking your time!
You want us to be faster,.,?
He's a lion.
You guys have to be faster.
He’s really a lion.
Hurry,
Rock Scissors Paper!
No one wins, hyung!
Ah, calm down.
Rock Scissors Paper!
Yay!
You got cheated!
Rock Scissors Paper!
Jae Suk hyung!
Hurry!
We won!
We caught the lion!
We!
Aigoo,
Rock Scissors Paper was too good!
Ji Ho, you have worked hard.
Wow.
Since I was born, the only thing that doesn't lie is Rock Paper Scissors.
Wow, you are too much!
You started attacking us even before we started playing Rock Scissors Paper!
I had no time left that’s why!
If it wasn't for the lack of time, it may not turn out this way.
We have to open and have a look.
Hyung, seems like the label isn't here.
If there isn't then this is not valid right?
It's moot?
Because you threw it away.
I picked up any one of them.
Then no one will get the reward.
Huh?
It will not happen.
Mine does not have it.
Wait a minute.
My hand is trembling.
-Don't tremble. -Hyung.
Is this Ji Ho's doing?
It should not be switched.
My hand is trembling more now.
Oh gosh.
You checked it, didn't you?
Oh, I thought all our gifts were going to the wind!
- Is it there? - It's here.
I thought it was mine,
- If it was Ji Ho's... - Right.
Scared me. It gave me a scare.
What?
You worked hard oppa.