I found it!
We are at Jeju island!
Jeju island.
It was so windy and rainy yesterday.
-Right now, the weather's nice -Its so nice today though.
-If you put a feather it'll just fall right back down -Exactly.
Come back here come back.
It's not time for something like that.
There are no extra cameras to film you doing that right now.
He wants to play right now.
Aren't you supposed to be playing like this in Jeju.
Oh gosh. Is the people who are going to be with us coming?
There are other people who are going to join us for running man today.
Two?
Musical fairy.
Fairy?
Usical fairy??
They're coming over there.
They're coming in that carriage.
They're hiding over there.
They're so small, like this small.
Tinkerbell Tinkerbell.
Something weird.
Something's weird, is it Minsoo again?
It seems kind of weird right?
Is it Dong Wan Fd?
Is it Joon San?
They seem a little old.
They look old.
They can't be a musical fairies.
Is this Shin Bong sun?
It's Jung Jae Hyung!
What is this all of a sudden, what is this?
Jung Jae Hyung!
Oh the musical fairy
I talked to you yesterday but you didn't tell me this?
They said to keep it a secret.
Didn’t you drink last night.
Me? no.
-There's Jihyo right behind you -Oh hello.
He's going to get caught for running man real quick.
He came out on a show and got sick for three days.
How could you call someone like this?
Will the last person come out?
BoA?!
BoA?
It's so nice to see her.
Wow it's BoA.
Hey!
Wow really, I didn't know BoA would come here
I know I was so surprised....Look at me(joke)
-Piss me off... -Piss me off too.
BoA said it's her first time on a reality show
-0h really? -Yeeah.
This is your first time?
You're lacking
I'm so used to this right now.
-Just look at the camera well -Where is it?
So this is your first variety show?
Yeah, it's my first time meeting you like this.
You're. right.
Yeah, we've never .done a*show? together, :.
She said she's nervous.
Yeah I am.
Has Haha done a show with her before?
-Yes I have -Oh when?
On a radio station.
She doesn't remember.
Anyways, BoA and Jae Hyung is here today.
Before we start the mission the two guests will chose their own team and it will be simple,
Since we are at the beach day, we are going to play catch me if you can
and each running man character will go get the flag.
Who ever gets and tags them first will get to be on that persons team.
It will be so awkward if that person runs alone.
Gwang soo will be running first.
Why me first?
I think he likes running around.
No no.
How awkward.
First off, is Gang zoo.
Ready, start.
Catch me if you can.
-You should run slower -You look like a crow.
No ones even moving.
Next, Haha.
Ready, start.
Catch me if you can.
Catch me if you can, catch me if you can.
Not you.
Catch me if you can -He's going he's going.
No, not you. No I don't want to.
You guys look good together.
So funny really
I don’t want to.
Next is.
Catch me if you can. Catch me*if you can.
BoA!
Just keep on going.
Feel - chok - cross!
Catch me if you can.
My face is getting red.
She caught him.
Jihyo ready.
Catch me if you can.
Hey Jihyo.
Just go.
Gwang soo!
Catch me if you can.
We're going. We're going.
Todays mission is to figure out the running man code.
Code?
You have to use your head.
If you figure it out correctly, you will! find the running man code.
This is the code right?
This is a trick.
Oh you just click the flag and something pops up.
Find the running man file in the green yard.
-Are you sure? -Its at’ln-sah dong.
No no that's not right.
It's that place we went to before.
Okay!
Gary, isn't this a little too tight?
No no its okay.
Why are you like this, I'm comfortable.
BoA is uncomfortable too, the chair went too back.
We need to be comfortable for BoA to be comfortable too.
She's so charismatic.
No I'm not.
She has so much aura.
Aura?
I'm so nervous.
Let's be number one today like BoA's song.
-Yes yes -Yeah that's good.
We lost Gary in our team last time and lost.
Oh really?
But why is your name Gary.
Ah, my name?, when I was younger that used to be my nickname but now that I'm a rapper and I needed a nickname.
So you just added lee
Lee.
Since Jae Hyung is smart, he can figure codes out.
Of course, just trust me.
Oh and that .. what was her name, the girl.
The girl.
Song Jihyo?
Yeah Jihyo.
If she was here, you would be in trouble right now.
Oh really?
Got my hair pulled at before.
Oh good good
I like talking with my knees bent.
Its here.
It's the yellow running man.
Right,
Miss Bo.
How are they here before us?
Be careful because you're more special than us.
I, 2
Over there.
Yeah yeah.
Go now.
The code?
Wait what?
What's over there?
-Whats over there? -Go find the code?
There's something in the flag.
This is green tea?
What is this?
Hey hurry up and find it Oppa.
There’s nothing here.
There's nothing.
There's nothing here, this is fake
Gary!
Come here, come over there
I found it!
Is that real?
This is by Jong kook.
Did you find it?
Amazing Amazing.
This is some kind of code.
What is that piano for?
You have to perform it huh?
And sing it, is there anyone who plays the piano?
I can play it a little bit.
But these seem kind of hard, the chords.
You just need the melody.
We're doing a song by Jung Jae Hyung.
Jae Hyung.
How do you do this?
You have to perform for it to come out.
But what is this.
If you do the mission, the box opens.
Yes, you must do the performance first.
Go over there.
BoA can do it.
Is that all?
It says you got it wrong.
They got it wrong.
This is Jeju green tea.
This is Jeju tea?
This is so sweet.
At this rate, we won't even find the code.
This isn't easy.
They're singing over there
I think they're finding musical notes.
It's over there! over there.
Over there the red thing. There's more over there, over there.
These are blank.
There are real ones and fake ones.
It's so cold.
This is blank too.
So cold even my undergarments are wet.
This is not a time to look nice.
There's one here, over here.
Oh Shang lee jeh, ah, this..
But you have to sing the lyrics.
Try playing something else.
Something else? what else?
Oh my gosh.
This is amazing, amazing.
If you're not going to do the mission then another team...
- No no - We will.
You have to do that song.
Oh this song?
They didn't finish.
This is a party.
Hey! Do you wanna party in tears?
Do you wanna party in tears?
We are freezing over here.
Can you do it in a domestic style?
No it isn’t. This is like a Paris style.
We should do a modern style.
Back to the challenge.
We are number one!
This one.
Here it goes.
Oh shanzelize.
Oh shanzelize
!@♪$%A&*
OH shanzelize.
Oh.
Success.
You failed so please go back.
I’m getting pissed off.
They failed
I think it has nothing to do with the play and the singing.
Is there something...
Is there a password...?
Shanzelize.
Is it something separated with the piano chord B, C?
Because they did not only write French but translated in Korean like blue ballad.
It is not detailed so it is not something big.
The other teams are having a hard time too.
And how will Gwang soo’s team do it?
Hyung let’s not succeed this.
-Yeah' action -Yeah let’s do actions.
Let’s do together with actions.
Start!
It’s winter.
The weather is cold.
Every time it is cold.
If there is something like that.
It is hard to remember that thing.
We feel sad.
Fail! It’s sad but contestant number 3.
Yes.
Ah Our director did well with them.
-We will come back next time Yes-Come back next time.
This team did their best
I was in the other team.
Aren’t you a giraffe? A giraffe
I am a person.
Bring our music sheet.
Bring it.
Number 3 the national park team.
The giraffe
I am a person, I can talk too.
Maybe the giraffe has an IQ.
He plays the piano.
Sol La.
Sol La Damn.
Hyung I think BoA will curse.
She said Damn now.
If we bug her more.
We were team with beauties right?
-Yes -They get a bit angry but.
If we wait more she will say her first bad word.
The fresh bad word...
A bit more You can say it.
It is her first time in a variety and she says a fresh bad word.
Damn is also fresh-
Ah! Because of this Pumpa I am going crazy.
BoA is doing it! Finally!
Finally BoA.
Stop it! There is someone from France.
Ah yes.
Please proceed faster
I am sorry because of my flight time that’s why.
Are you from France?
Yes.
Please proceed.
Yes
I will play now.
Following the road and stepping on it.
Coming home together.
Goes out with the carpenter.
Goes home together.
Hey!
Stolla sto I la sto I la pumpa stola pumpa.
Stolla stolla stolla pumpa stolla stolla pum pum pum.
You startled me.
If we bug her more she will lie down in the grass
I think I will go crazy!
Did you hear it?!
-You should at least give us a hint -What, Did you call me?
What are you?
Just go!
Still my number 1.
Oppa, I think I am going to be crazy!
Why?
I really don’t know what they are telling us to do...
-I will tell you -BoA is very angry right now.
BoA-ssi look at us doing it.
Are you really from France?
Yes...
What are you doing?
They are greeting each other.
Okay now we understand.
Oh Shanzelize.
Oh Shanzelize
!@♪$°/<fA, &*
Oh Shanzelize.
Running man-Code!
Running man Code.
There must be something in it.
Maybe in the lyrics.
In a Elize hills.
It is somewhere in the hills.
Bbo Ah-
Did you find that?
Hey! Wait!
In the lyrics there is La.
La La La La.
Wait. Give me a ball pen.
La La La.
Must not get a mistake even once.
No need to hurry.
Oppa this is really...
If we do this we will succeed.
Okay.
Following the road and stepping on it-
Coming home together.
Goes out with the carpenter.
Goes home together.
Stolla stolla stolla pumpa stolla-pumpa stolla pumpa.
Stolla stolla stolla pumpa stolla pumpa pump um pum.
It’s daebak!
There must be a clue
I do not know what that is.
Something fell.
It opened?
Succeeded?
Let’s go.
Yeah.
Hyung how did you find that out?
How did you know?"
The next place is.
Wait with this...
oh?! San Rok Nam Ro 776, Find the running man drawing.
Ah-Anyways we are the first.
The other teams will catch up.
How about this?
There are notes here-
Like here you press La and Do
I also thought of that
I think this is the secret code.
This is sol.
Sol Re Mi.
This is it.
This is the one! I am sure of it.
-If there is a nice person please introduce to me -Maybe it is correct.
There is also a practice when it come to love.
Someone who looks after you even though that person is busy.
Oh!
Woah!
Yes!
Did it come out?
We did it.
Let’s go.
Woah It is unbelievable.
Our team is good at reasoning.
Feel!
Chok.
Meong.
Cross.
It is so depressing.
Ah-I am getting angry.
How can you make a code like that?
You have to open the password to win.
Yeah.
It’s okay.
Jae hyung hyung, Close your mouth...
My spirit went out.
You looked pitiful
I thought I will be first but we are the last place.
But still don’t open your mouth that much
but going as the first place isn’t all.
Hyung you must’ve seen it awhile ago That’s why don’t be frustrated.
To say I got frustrated I am getting irritated...!
Gwang soo’s expression was very sneaky.
Little by little we will solve for the code like the Da Vinci code.
Isn’t it the last mission place?
-If it is like that... -I was the first place last time
I got first place last time and you know it right?
Gwang soo, You being the first did not become a big topic and you know it right?
Gwang soo got scolded by his mother.
Why were you scolded?
Because of the prize...
Sometimes they get gold and stuffs but that time...
Ah the one that looks like an ashtray?
The one that looks like an ashtray.
There is dust there about 3cm
agic lamp’s genie! Fulfill my wish.
You got a great item.
Take off Jong kook’s name tag.
But you wouldn’t know how much it would cost.
Yeah I don’t know.
That’s why Gwang soo.
It is a problem because I do not know.
Because you do not know yet.
We are here.
Let’s go.
Oh? Da Vinci?
Da Vinci’s code?
That is correct.
Here is Leonardo Da Vinci.
We need to bring this along.
Yeah you must take good care of the vault.
Do we have to bring the vault?
We have to bring this along?
It is up to you whether you bring it or not.
When we are leading we will get turn around tables... It’s a jinx
I will bring it along.
Let’s go in.
Hey what is this?
Woah.
Oh? There is water coming out.
What is this?
Hyung isn’t it like in the old days they do this to wash their faces?
Leonardo Da Vinci made this-
What is this?
There are so many things to look at-
What is that?
Ah.
Here it is-the flag.
Da Vinci museum?
It must be a drawing this time.
Wow.
He is a very smart man.
Da Vinci really is a smart man.
Oh!
You know Yun ho.
Did You know Yun ho made this?
A Rhino.
Hyung last time in running man when they came out.
What did you draw?
A Rhino...
There is something.
Is something like this is stock.
This is code.
This is tears, Tears.
U U
Tears tears.
This one smiling?
A tree?
We will get head ache the whole day.
What is this?
2nd floor-
Let’s go here.
Oh?!
Why?
Here it is-Running man drawing.
This is the one Jong Kook drew in the past
line really look like you.
It’s the same.
It is right?
Maybe we are the one finding it for the first time-
Really?
Feel.
Chok.
Meong.
Cross.
They told us to find something in the picture right?
Yeah
I really remember this-Jong kook drew it in the past.
That’s right.
Jae suk oppa...
Oh! What is this.
There is something.
It’s nothing.
Maybe they did this so that the picture will go in.
Oh!! There is something?
Here it is a number!
This is Roman numerals
Suk jing 2140?
Oh!
Enter it
2140 Enter.
It is 2140 hyung.
You sure?
Hey...
It got locked now.
It got locked.
Hyung we are first! Who found the picture first?
Who found the picture?
Who first found it?
What are you doing?
Who saw it first and grabbed it?
If you guys will be like that then I can’t cooperate with you guys.
Leave it and go.
Leave it-I only need ji hyo.
How can you say something like that?
Oh!!
A tiger.
It’s the same.
It’s all the same.
Hyung because it is here...
-You are like an artist -I drew this in the past.
It looks very famous.
Yeah Because it is hanged with Leonardo Da Vinci’s drawings...
That is like saying ‘Asia’s tiger’.
This is a number.
Isn’t this the number of strokes?
32...
6... Ey... 61.
It’s not it right?
Why did they do this in the below to make it confusing...
I don’t think the one in the below is useful... Is the one in the below more useful?
Because it is the same in the one on that picture.
Hey try to search hieroglyphics.
Hieroglyphics?
Really gonna make me go crazy.
Hyung I will search here.
What? Okay.
Oh! What is this?
There are sneaky people there.
Oh! It's Yoo Jae Suk's.
You are standing in front of my drawing.
Hey wait!!
Why?
That is my drawing.
Okay! We understand.
-Look at it 2 steps away -My drawing must be somewhere here.
It’s a masterpiece.
You should indicate the QR code there.
What?
The QR code. Bring it near the tiger.
Like this?
Yeah Like that.
This hyung is very sneaky.
What are you guys doing?
You must look at the picture in front of it not at the back.
What are you two doing there?
Running man people.
Yes.
Running man people There is a phone call in the information desk located in 1st floor.
A phone call.
Dong hoon ah-Hurry.
Why?
There is a phone call.
Where is it located?
It was in the first floor all this time.
Oppa-You are so big.
There is a phone call? Where?
This one?
Hello?
Who are you?
I am Kim Jong kook-Running man Kim Jong Kook.
Ouch!
Ok, thank you.
Yes thank you.
Running man is speed!
It is a big turn table.
Let’s go.
Basement 1st floor storage for conservation of relics.
In the basement.
Find what again?!
Here it is.
We need to confuse them.
We must be swift.
We must not move too obviously.
Hyung Jae Hyung Hyung.
Oh!
I thought she was doing ninja moves.
-I thought she was doing ninja moves - Where are you going?
Yes?
Where are you going.
Yellow You can’t do this.
That’s it BoA! Ride together!
Running man people-
Oppa!
Ji Hyo, you can't do this!
Please give me one chance.
-Hello -Hyung! Noona, Take away from him!
-Hello, hello? Hurry up, get it from him!
I got it. I'm Yoo Jae Suk.
No, it’s not! It's Lee Gwang Soo! i.
Secretly go to the ground Relic Preservation Storage Room.
There is something that can help decode the code.
Okay, I got it.
Okay, JiHyo.
Oppa, are you going to do that way?
Ah, it’s here!
Is it here?
Hurry, hurry up.
What is this?
I think we will get one each.
Really?
Did I turn back on the camera?
Shall we close the door?
-Yeah, lock it, lock it! -I will hold on to the door.
But what will we do with these? Maybe we should find another?
Do we have to use these for decoding?
Hyung, just frighten every people who comes in.
That's good.
It’s okay
I'll go to the CR.
Why is this locked?
They must have tied it up.
Ah you guys are so mean.
They opened it, ah.
Oh my! I was surprised.
Why did you* locked.
What is this?
Why, why.
Excuse me, you...
Oh did I turn my back again?
Haha I tried? everything"already.
No, No. This is not the one....
Hyung the numbers are all different..
Yeah, it's all different.
It's really different.
Let's solve upstairs.
Let's bring this one by one-
Wow, you are...
Hey, is there something inside there?
What's in there? What did you bring?
We’re one team.
Oppa you are so not fair.
Go inside.
What is this place?
Every material is here.
What is this?
This is seven....
Oh I was surprised.
This one is too easy.
Hyung hyung hyung hyung! It says 'Measure the temperature'
The heat, yeah..
In here?
This must be a number, right?
Ha-This is so tough.
Is every week this hard?
Yeah...
This shape is a scholar, and it must be something about actions.,
And what actions could it be?
What's this meaning? Isn't that Eight?
Oppa,
Number eight..
Oppa, It's almost here.
Where, where? Ah, it's here!
Ei-These guys are really...!
You have no right for being team members.
But JiHyo, these are not numbers.
Nuna!
Then Look for them.
Nuna I am number Six, I solved it by looking at this mirror
I am now number Six.
Why don't you even listen?
Nuna, it's number six.
Be quiet, be still please.
What are you doing now?
It's nearer to number seven... or is it nine?
Do this, and make your hips like this.
No, like this, more to this side
it's like number nine. Nine... Six... uh?! Seven!
Ten! Ten! Number Ten! It's number Ten.
This is number Ten?
Today's mission is, Complete the Running an Code'
Uh? There's something here...
Two, one
I solved it by looking at this mirror
I got it, I got the feeling! Hyung!
Got it, got it, got it! It's here.
Ah'! The position changes, that's why it’s not Eleven.
It's numbers 0912'
Be quiet!
Cool!! Awesome!
I did it! I solved it!
Hey, hey, it closed because of late opening.
We were late!
It's closed again!
Who did it? Who solved... who solved the secret in the mirror?!
Step aside, let's open it first!
Step aside please.
This is the one in the post office..
Oppa, maybe it has another mission when we solve this one.
Anyway we solved this.
We don't need this one.
Let's go, let's go
I said who solved the mirror?!
You!
Why do you shout...
That was so great.
Gwang Soo! Seat next to me!
Hyung, sorry but I will seat in the front.
Your legs... your legs are long...
Sorry, hyung... I have something to discuss with Nuna.
Don't try to overhear us.
'Nandeureu village’.
Is it written 'Nandeureu village'?
Our Team... is finally the first!
Why are these letters upside down?
Let's see it upside down
I think that's the clue
ake it upside down and see them through the mirror!
I think it's over there
I think that's it, huh?
Hyung, it's Jae Suk hyung. Jae Suk hyung!
Oh gosh!
Wait Hyung, look at this.
Hyung, it's a number.
This is circle, X, and what's this... one, two.
Okay.
Yeah it's open.
How did Gwang Soo solved this?
I think this is like in the movie ’Da Vinci Code'
I think that's the way to solve the code.
AH!
Isn’t this like this?
It's this one!
Gary, that's right.
Take off it, wait.
Hey this is... ah.
Ah, it's annoying.
Hyung, hyung! This is right!
Gary, Stress..
Stress.
Da Vinci Stress!
Ah, Stress!
Ah What's this.
Wow this is awesome, what's this again?
We need to...
Just give us a bell... Can't you just give us the bell?
Aww.
It's not yet finished?
I don't know why our Da Vinci lived so tough...
That's what I'm talking about.
Let’s fighting!
Hyung, the one for the Da Vinci Code... How can we solve this?
Roll it.
These five letters becomes one word-
Ah, today I really... I may do some great thing.
He made it because of me.
Hyung, sorry but we will have our own discussion for a while-
First place is not that hard
I think I just have to think the other way with the others.
Do you want to go back, Gwang Soo?
We're here.
What's this? Where's this?
You are the first to arrive. Find the Running Man code. It's here in this village.
In this village? Not inside here? A code..?
Find the code?
He said it's here in the village...
It’s so hard.
How can we find? This village is so big.
Hey, this is in the Da Vinci Code'
There's a hurdle.
-It's in there -Ah, really?
Yes, it shows there.
Oppa, how was that one...
You see this... This has five alphabets, right?
Oppa! Look at that view It’s so amazing.
Wow Look at this scenery It's so nice.
Should we find in the light house?
What's that? Why are they with a name tag?
Maybe we have to catch them!
Who's that?
-Huh, why are they in name tag. -No, we have to catch them!
They have a name tag.
What's going on?
There's another guest?
Huh? What the...?
What's that? Why are the grandmothers so fast?
The villagers here are fast!
Kim Ji Hye-ssi! Wait a minute!
I took of Kim Sol Mi-ssi!
Kim Sol Mi-ssi... There's nothing.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much, good job
Kim Sol Mi-ssi.
It was like this...
There's nothing here.
Ah' we are to look for a person
I was surprised, I thought a grandma is running that fast.
Thank you!
Why were you in wig??
This... There is a real one inside the name tag. Ours were fake.
Wow-that place is really-
Isn't it?
Ayoo-it's so cold...
If you put this around your neck...
Really?
BoA is really tired and hungry now..
It drives me crazzzy, really-
drives me craazzzy.
Makes me craazzy!
You can't even tear that off..?
Hey, Jae Suk!
Why do you try to tear here?
No..This... This... is sticked too tight.
No no no!!
That was close.
Is it this way?
Uh They're running over there!
What is?
It's a Staff.
No they have a name tag!?
They have a name tag.
AH!!! Yeah, it’s right!
Where are you going?
Hey! It's at the back of the villagers.
That's right!
Why are they running?
Hey, the villagers
I will surely get the name tag...
Huh? They ran off!
This village is so weird.
The villagers are here.
It's here!
It's a grandma!
Hey, What's with this today?
Wait a minute, please... mother, wait...
I think you have an important one in here, because you ran.
You had a fun game.
Aigo-it's so hot!
What the, do I have to tear that off?
There are many down there.
Catch him!
He can never catch!
Hyung, what are you doing?
Let me go!
I am warming up
I'm so tired.
Did I drool?
Hello.
Excuse me.
Aigoo-teacher.
Thank you.
Are you okay? Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
Ah.. I must have come first.. Name tag was with him... Hello, nice to meet you. Hello!
Wow, you're amazing! He's doing good!
Don't show them, hide it.
What the...? There's nothing!
Wait, excuse me.
Uh? What's this?
Gary.
There’s something we have it!
Where’s BoA?
Hyung, she's not normal, right now.
Really?
I'm about to die right now.
Thank you!
Thank you so much.
Hello there.
No, you can’t.
Good job! Take care.
BoA BoA Hey guys, go on-it's so cold.
BoA, where were you?
I was running over...
You really look like you played much in a village.
There’s nothing!
There's something inside it?
We have one hint.
You got one hint?
Yeah, one...
What?
Letter I.
-I ah.. it's an alphabet .. -Yeah..
But they don't give us a name tag.
If you do this, it's pretty fun
other Mother! Wait a minute
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Be careful.
Hold on, its not here.
Not here.
You seemed to be having fun.
Thank you.
There's none.
Hello.
Hello, hope you're doing ok.
They took it off
I'll use this for later.
Hello.
Good bye.
This is my first time running this much.
Hold on, mother.
Hold on for a minute, let me just take the name tag.
Why are you running, mother.
Yes!
Thank you.
Thank you for your hard work.
It's an S.
There are five letters.
- Can you just turn around real quick can I see the name tag - Can we take a look?
Yes.
Thank you.
Thank you father.
- It's a letter! - A letter?
It's a c?
There's another one?
You had this on your back.
Than you mother.
Father.
What are you guys doing?
Father, hold on.
Thank you!
Wow!
Thank you father.
We need more letters.
We only have..
M, C
M, C, U?
Hello, oh here it is! thank you.
Oh here it is!
Thank you.
U
M, C, U
S, C, U, M
What is there to get back to Jeju?
If a letter is missing or there are two letters.
M, I, C, U? No that makes no sense.
C, U means to see someone somewhere isn't it?
What's custom?
No that doesn't work.
M, U, C.. Oh its that!
M, U, C .. isn't it music? m u s ic?
Music fairy.
- M, U, S, - If this is right I'm going to die.
Oppa, you're amazing.
There's a code in here.
The cross means that it will become unraveled?
If we cross then we will know the code?
Let's go to this address first.
If you feel the cross, then you will know the answer.
-We need to know this -Sukjin and Gwang Soo...
Yeah we need to know this.
There's Yoo Jae suk in this too.
There's Lee Gwang soo...
We figured it out.
Without me?
Let's go to the car first.
Feel, Chok, Cross!
Today is difficult but l think we need to look at the words around it
I don't think it's the cross.
That's fake.
There's a lot of those words, maybe if you reword then something will come out.
These are name tags!
Then suk Jin.
Suk Jin Gwang soo name tag.
What with music fairies?
What about music fairies?
This morning, they mention something about music fairies.
That's two.
Then we need to see their name tags.
-We need to see inside -There's something inside their name tags.
Let's see what's inside you name tag first.
Then I‘m out brother.
What are you doing, we are ace, in the same team.
Cross! We are ace.
This is really fun.
Hyung, what should we do?
What if I get one person?
The last step.
This must be it.
If you put something inside I think something comes up huh?
Just between it, right?
Yeah just between us.
Then we can get the other answer if we get one answer.
Gwang soo...
We have the same thought but I'm holding back.
Let’s hold hands.
-Are you trying to take the tag off? -No no.
They probably went that way.
They're over there.
That's them.
Is that them?
The clothes are so visible.
Did you figure it out?
Did you figure out the code?
No we couldn't.
Gwang soo!
-Is the code cross? -Yeah.
-That if the cross splits then the code is answered -Yeah,
So is that why you guys split up?
Why is he running away?
Did you guys meet?
Oh wait.
Let’s split up.
Why split up? Why?
He leaves Jihyo and runs away.
Why are you grabbing me and running?
-I'm not a bad person -I know.
That scared me.
Gwang Soo is here!
Hey; Gwang Soo's here.
Wait!
You got it, You got it, you're good.
How'd he get it?
He ripped mine off.
There's nothing there.
Suk Jin
Lee Gwang soo.
Suk Jin Gwang soo, name tag.
There's something on Jae hyung’s name tag.
Really?
Are you thinking it's me? Wait hold on.
Think about it. Wait, hold on a minute.
It’s Jihyo. It's on Jihyo.
It's not on Gwang soo?
It's not on Gwang Soo.
This?
Did you see something on the name tag.
-What / -This.
Where is it.
-I have it but you can't take my name tag off -Ok I won't
I'm telling you I won't.
This.
Ok?
H?
You have to one of the coins in there. The other one's with BoA.
Because the cross, so the cross is split up. I erased it and the fairy name tags came up.
-But those are Jae hyung and BoA -Exactly.
So you have to find BoA.
But we find BoA and take the tag off then what's the secret?
We need to put the key back over there.
Then the result is..
If we win the prize, I'll give a third to you.
Let's just find it first.
-Yes -Yes.
Let's go.
-Why? Wow you’re too much -I thought you weren’t going to do that.
-You're too curious -Let's hold hands and go.
Let's hold hands and go..
I can't live because of this.
They look like zombies.
It's not like that.
Let’s hold hands.
No no lets hold hands and go.
Lets go, for real.
Is the camp fire strong?
Why are you guys together?
Jae Suk, be careful of your back.
-Why? -Be careful.
What?
We'll be back where the last step is.
Can you not go?
I don't understand, be careful of what?
-If we run, do we win? -Brother should we run for a change?
Should we all run
I feel like we can win easily.
Then.
Should we take mine off and see?
Wait no hold on.
Then.
-Then you take mine -Then we can take each other's off
we have to because one of us can be a spy.
Yeah take it off
1,2,3 rock paper scissors.
This is so annoying.
-Theres nothing here.
-Nothing?-Yes.
Then put it back on.
This can happen.
Wait no hold on.
Hey this is annoying so I don’t know.
-Then I have to take mine off -No no.
No no you can't BoA.
No let me.
No you can't, don't let her do it.
What is going on. What should we do?
What is going on here?
You and Gary both did rock paper scissors huh?
The most important person.
What are you going to do?
Why are you here?
Why are you guys just roaming around?
We'll be back.
Ok go go.
If you win, we all win right.
Did BoA take off her tag?
I'm not sure.
We'll be back.
What are you doing?
What is this.
- There's none! - Eyyy, that is not right!
Eeyyy, hey! Hey!
Wow this is a little too much.
Jihyo, this is the type of person he is!
-Woaah! -Aish, seriously!
I lost for no reason.
Do you guys trust each other?
Stay there.
Wait a minute. Oh Hyung!
You didn't do that, here!
I didn't do that, I didn't do that! Hold on.
Ah... seriously.
This is so pathetic.
What's this?
-There's something? -Yeah.
Put both the coins in.
-It's coming up -What is it?
Should I open it?
What is it?
-It's a cord.. -huh?
Today's mission you need to find a running man code.
Code?
This is the code.
This is music, music.
The music fairies.
Running man code.
Code?
Cord!
Number one!
Thank you.
-Seafood -Thank you.
-Lobster, lobster! Abalone and -This is so good
I eat this every morning so.,
oh gosh I'm going to just!
Wait... What?
This is something you do during camping.
There's meat in there too
I said "for tomorrow do something good".
Acting like he prepared this.
This is so good, Hyung!
Do the guest usually do this?
Where are we going?
Alice in wonderland.
Open this door and go back home