Subtitles by DramaFever
[Preliminary Major Leaguer]
[Monster Pitcher- Ryu Hyun Jin!]
[Already a Major Leaguer]
[Our Nation's pride, Choo Shin Soo!]
[A pairing of dreams-
These two will now join Running Man]
[Psychic baseball]
[A surreal game of psychic baseball!]
[When it comes to a psychic competition,
knowing what's to come is impossible.]
[Run!]
[Korea's University of
Broadcasting and Communication]
[A returning student, Jae Suk.]
Hello.
I know that Choo Shin Soo and
Ryu Hyun Jin are on today...
They really are great athletes.
I've been wanting to meet them.
[All the clothing with their names are
aligned next to one another...]
Green?
[Green outfit,
which is perfectly suited to Jae Suk.]
All these other colors are so nice...
I really like these colors too.
[Entrance of first Running Man!
Entrance of first Running Man!]
What is this?
We're not starting already, right?
What... what are you doing already?
I just got here.
[Trouble-making student, Kang Gary.]
Are we starting right away?
Thank you. I really like blue.
When is Song Ji Hyo coming?
- Want to take it to her?
- Should I?
I'll just take it for now.
If you want to see it, come see me.
[Entrance of second Running Man!
Entrance of second Running Man!]
[And just like that, in order...]
[All the Running Man members
make their entrance.]
How are we doing the opening?
Are we starting right away?
[And as for the seventh...]
[Huh? This person is...]
[SBS drama, Five Fingers]
[The female lead of the drama,
Five Fingers, Jin Sae Yeon.]
[The new heroine of small screen who's
captivated us with her emotional acting.]
I'm scared...
What if I'm eliminated right away?
[Sae Yeon is the seventh Running Man?]
Hey! Give me my clothes!
- Ji Hyo!
- Why did you take my clothes? Give it!
I wasn't sure...
What are they doing?
Hey! Are you guys dating again?
What are you guys doing?
Jae Suk, Kang Gary took my clothes.
You guys are really acting funny
these days.
Did you come again because
you missed me?
Just what are you guys doing
these days?
She always follows me around
whenever Autumn rolls around.
- Yeah, Fall is making me feel nostalgic.
- I know you're feeling nostalgic.
[They're weird...]
[And on the other hand,
in the school basement...]
- Did you pull it off?
- It doesn't pull off easily.
[A fight is breaking out already?]
Did you pull it off?
[This person is...]
[And this person is...]
[Ryu Hyun Jin - Choo Shin Soo]
[Major Leaguer - Choo Shin Soo]
[Currently a part of the Major League Team,
Cleveland Indians.]
[Currently known as one of the best pitchers
who's got everything from speed to strength!]
[The proud Korean, Choo Shin Soo!]
[And...]
[The ultimate left handed pitcher,
Monster Pitcher, Ryu Hyun Jin!]
[2006, the year of his debut - Placed
first for number of wins and defense.]
[Just having scored the highest paid contract
in history for a Korean pro ball player!]
[The Monster Pitcher with a career
in the Major Leagues right in front of him!]
[And these two are in the midst of practicing
how to rip off the name tags...]
I don't think it'll work unless it's
ripped off in one smooth motion.
I'm not going to rip it off from the front.
I'm going to do it from the back.
I'm going to sneak up from the back.
[A source of worry even for these
world-renowned athletes.]
It's not very easy...
I'll just sneak up from behind...
It doesn't feel good when that happens.
But... to go and start ripping off the tags
without even meeting them first is a little...
Say 'It's nice to meet you', and then...
[Surprisingly playful, Ryu Hyun Jin]
You should be more careful...
[Just wait... A new image
for the these ultimate athletes.]
[Ninth Running Man,
Choo Shin Soo's entrance!]
[At last... Choo Shin Soo makes
his entrance!]
What? Choo Shin Soo's here?
[A sense of nervousness flowing through
a once quiet school hallway...]
Ninth Running Man,
Choo Shin Soo's entrance!
[He's coming!]
- What?
- Choo Shin Soo!
I wonder why I feel so excited
to see him?
[Let's do well today...]
Ninth Running Man,
Choo Shin Soo's entrance!
[Choo Shin Soo's dignified entrance]
[Is today the day for him to show off
his skills in his homeland?]
[Tenth Running Man,
Ryu Hyun Jin's entrance!]
Hey! We're in trouble!
[Terror]
It's started! It's started!
[The herbivores are the first to
detect a sense of threat in the air!]
That means there are pretty much
three of Jong Kooks here today.
[Kim Jong Kook]
[Kim Jong Kook?]
Is this even possible?
I think I should start working out now.
[Emergency weight training session?]
[We wish that your preparation
goes well...]
[Huh? An announcement?]
[Running Man Members,
we are glad to see you here.]
Running Man Members,
we are glad to see you here.
I'm scared. Who's voice is this?
[Entrance of all 10 members is
now complete.]
It's not nine people?
I will now announce
what your first mission is going to be.
[Your first mission...]
Your first mission...
[First mission]
[Name tag elimination]
[First mission: Name tag elimination]
It's name tag elimination.
[Start of name tag elimination!]
[The ultimate winner will be given
a useful advantage!]
Ryu Hyun Jin and Choo Shin Soo
are here...
Right now?
This is what we're starting with?
[And it starts now.]
What the heck is this? How can
we start with name tag elimination?
Why are we starting off with this?
I'm not even warmed up yet!
[Name tag elimination - Start!]
Hey, Kwang Soo...
[Right off the bat, a call for help
is sounded off from everywhere!]
Come on! Come up here!
Let's work together!
Hurry up and get up here!
[As soon as the game starts...]
What the heck?
What the heck is this?
[Shin Soo's attack!]
Shin Soo! Wait!
[Haroro, out...]
[As soon as the game started,
Shin Soo was lying in wait...]
[And attacks Ha Ha who was oblivious
from shouting out for help.]
[Seven seconds was all he needed...]
What the heck!
What the heck is this?
[Shaking his hand in greeting
a moment after.]
I'm a huge fan of yours.
Choo Shin Soo!
[Jae Suk having discovered
Choo Shin Soo from afar.]
It's nice to meet you!
You're already eliminated?
What the heck...
I can't believe he's already eliminated.
Your name tag is already ripped off?
Come down here so I can say hello.
I think I need to escape.
[Actively making his escape.]
[Red card for Ha Ha.
Red card for Ha Ha.]
I guess I should go face them now.
[Giraffe in the midst of disguising himself
from having witnessed the terror.]
[Joining the seminar hosted by
a visiting foreign professor.]
[Tiger!]
- We have to work together, Kwang Soo.
- I think we're on the same team.
I think we're on the same team.
Jong Kook!
[Choo Shin Soo's here!]
He's behind us! Jong Kook!
I just stood still!
I seriously just stood still!
Jong Kook! I thought you
said we needed to work together?
[Shin Soo captures the Giraffe.]
[The overwhelming sense that's making
even Mr. Capable nervous.]
[Will Giraffe's life just perish
in this state?]
[The Giraffe's counterattack!]
[Could it be that Giraffe
eliminates Shin Soo?]
[Figures...]
[Giraffe easily becoming eliminated.]
[And finally properly greeting
one another.]
You said we needed to work together!
[Whatever...]
[The thunderous attacks by the
Major Leaguer.]
If I had been just a little bit faster...
the outcome would've been different.
Choo Shin Soo...
[You've arrived at jail now.
Hurry up and get out...]
[An all-out escape!]
[Tiger Shin Soo on his tail
like a streak of thunder!]
[And Hyun Jin's about to join the fray?]
[It looks as though they're ready to
chase him down to the ground.]
[Ultimately, losing even
all their camera VJ's...]
[Hyun Jin following up from behind.]
[Jae Suk already having been captured...]
Hyun Jin... you want to rip it off,
or you want me to do it?
[The two athletes with no mercy.]
[The world of professionals where greetings
come after determining the winners first...]
Where were you?
[Blaming it on his VJ, Gwon Yeol.]
Wait... how could you have just
ripped it off like that?
How could you have just ripped it off
without any warnings like that?
We should've talked it out first...
- Ryu Hyun Jin, where are you going?
- I'm running from him now.
[Hyun Jin escaping from Shin Soo.]
It's nice to meet you.
He just... rips off the tag
as soon as he sees one.
Shouldn't you be going to jail now?
Yes, I have to go to jail now.
[The pride in our own hitter...
Eliminated three people within 10 minutes.]
[Terror]
Wait! It's nice to meet you.
[And right away!]
[The National Treasure pitcher
showing no mercy.]
Why...
Why are we doing this so early
in the morning?
Hyun Jin...
it's so great to meet you.
[Red card for Gary. Red card for Gary.]
It was an honor.
At least I got one now. Good.
[I got one too...]
[Exhaustion?]
This is killing me...
[As for exhaustion,
it's the same for Choo Shin Soo.]
I haven't worked out once
since the season ended...
Aren't you giving us any water?
Hyun Jin, come here. Seriously.
Who do we have left?
[Until they're the only ones left, they're
competing against each other for now.]
- Let's join forces.
- Okay... until the end, okay?
[After doing some running,
realize they need allies?]
- This is harder than working out.
- Look at how sweaty I am.
- How many have you eliminated?
- Three.
You did? Did you
eliminate them all right away?
Since... there's only
a two-way crossroad here...
I got you...
[Uh! Ji Hyo and Sae Yeon...]
- Did you see?
- Flower girl!
- He called me flower girl...
- Did you see?
- I saw it all.
- Did you see them getting eliminated?
- I saw it from a distance.
- Jong Kook, I saw it from right here.
And he ripped off the whole name tag
including the backing!
You two girls shouldn't be going
around alone.
We had no other choice.
Come over this way.
[Heading to Mr. Capable who is weak
when it comes to female guests.]
- You're not trying to rip mine off, right?
- No, I promise that I won't do that.
Jong Kook, we're all afraid right now.
His screams sound like Min Soo's...
How are Ryu Hyun Jin and Shin Soo
related? Are they a team?
This is an individual battle.
But Sae Yeon said she wants to
rip off Suk Jin's name tag.
[Sae Yeon's wish is to oust Suk Jin.]
I have no idea where Suk Jin
is though.
[Just where in the world is Suk Jin?]
[Ah...]
This really is pathetic.
[It's an especially cruel jungle for
Impala to be playing in today.]
There are a lot of carnivores
out there today.
I can't even drink this.
[It's hard to get his fluid intake
in his hideout position...]
[Readily joining in on the picture taking.]
I can't keep staying here forever...
I should get out of here.
[Could he be heading into the jungle?]
As soon as I'm seen,
I'm going to be ousted.
[Ah! They saw each other!]
I got you...
[I'm caught...]
[Tiger Shin Soo giving chase.]
Shin Soo!
[That's why you should've
just stayed in hiding...]
[As planned, Monster Pitcher, Ryu Hyun Jin
has him corralled on the other end!]
[Right - Hyun Jin]
[Left - Shin Soo]
[This truly is a siege.]
Wait... wait!
Are the two of you on the
same team?
It's been an honor.
[Out within one minute of
leaving his seclusion.]
I'm telling you, it splits just like that.
It was a good plan.
[Red card for Ji Suk Jin.
Red card for Ji Suk Jin.]
[Darn!]
You should go down the emergency stairs,
and come up and flush them out this way.
Are the two of you on the
same team?
Yes.
I told him that I'd lose to him at the end.
Since he's come from so far
to be here...
[Mr. Capable seriously on the move.]
[Hyun Jin is on the other side...]
- Hello.
Hello. Wait... wait...
[Running away?]
- Seriously, don't come any closer.
- Hyun Jin...
- No.
[Monster Hyun Jin avoiding Mr. Capable.]
- Excuse me?
- You close with Choo Shin Soo?
- You're asking if I know him?
- You know him well, right?
- Yes.
- Are you two close?
Well... wouldn't it nice if you were to win?
Because there would be advantages to that.
So why don't the two of us work together
and oust Choo Shin Soo first...
[The target is to beat
Tiger Shin Soo first?]
- Are you going to betray me?
- No, I won't betray you.
I'm not known for betrayals.
Seriously.
[Negotiations a success?]
When the three of us face each other later,
pretend that you haven't met me yet.
Yeah... I'm known as Mr. Capable...
so I need to act the part.
[Mr. Cable's vigilance.]
[Since I've recruited Monster Hyun Jin...]
[Let's oust him first between the
two of us!]
Choo Shin Soo... I used to like you...
I never knew we'd meet like this.
[Tiger Choo Shin Soo vs. Mr. Capable's
fight that is no longer avoidable.]
[Automatically running away once
he is faced with him.]
[Turning around in the opposite direction
right away to give chase.]
[But Mr. Capable stays calm.]
[After confusing him with sounds of his
footsteps, heads in the opposite direction!]
[An imminent situation!
Monster Hyun Jin needs to get here soon.]
[Tiger Shin Soo having come up
from behind!]
[A situation that is no longer
avoidable.]
- I knew it!
- It's good to see you!
[Monster Hyun Jin... hurry!]
[Completely disoriented.]
How do I get upstairs?
Wait... let me take off my watch.
[Even taking off your watch?
Just what are you planning on doing?]
Why don't we get everything else settled
and save this until the end?
[Proposing to hold off
facing each other to the end.]
I have to do that with Hyun Jin.
Why are the two of you doing that?
You should be doing that with me.
[Shin Soo with all his faith
in his alliance with Hyun Jin.]
You shouldn't be doing that.
Why don't you and I do that later?
[Trying to escape
the situation using this method...]
You don't seem to know very well...
- Body fat is...
- I know that body fat means strength.
Of course... of course, I know.
- Hello. Come on up.
- Excuse me?
- Why don't you come on up?
- Huh?
[Ji Hyo and Sae Yeon on the floor below
unsure of what to do.]
So why don't we... later...
[Major leaguer's competitiveness
gearing its head.]
Seriously...
Hyun Jin...
[The ones left watching
are in a state of nervousness.]
Why are you so sweaty? I can't
even get a grip because you're sweaty.
[What to do...]
[Because he's a man who's lived all
his life for the win...]
[So fast!
Mr. Capable capturing his arm!]
[Monster Hyun Jin's arrival?]
[Tiger Shin Soo vs.
Mr. Cable's fierce battle!]
[A man's battle without any leniency!]
[Mr. Capable having pushed him
into the wall!]
[And Shin Soo's name tag!]
[How could this be? Mr. Capable!]
You should've listened when
I was being nice!
I told you that we could've waited
until the end!
[Darn... I lost!]
See? What did I tell you?
[Total elation]
Ji Hyo!
I did it!
We are Running Man!
This is what you call skills!
Everyone...
[The result of the battle that he wants
to announce to the whole world.]
That's why I should've done it quicker.
[Upset...]
[That guy is something else...]
I don't think this is right...
[Choo Shin Soo - Out!]
Hyun Jin!
[The two finally meeting again.]
Did you eliminate him?
- Hyun Jin...
- You're not going to betray me, right?
- You're not going to betray me?
- Where have you been?
I told you to stay by my side
when we faced off with Shin Soon.
- You should've yelled for me.
- What did you say?
Yell?
I yelled so much, everyone
stepped out to see what was going on.
Hyun Jin...
Why don't we oust the ladies first,
and you and I can wait to the end...
What do you think?
What did you say?
- What are you whispering about?
- What did you say?
[How absurd!]
- You're going to betray us like that?
- What are you talking about?
Hyun Jin... we didn't talk about
that, right?
Jong Kook...
I just saw you negotiating with him.
- It wasn't like that.
- Whatever. I just saw everything.
[Huh?]
What are you doing?
You know what I'm saying, right?
[Hand signaling back and forth
with Ji Hyo?]
Ji Hyo...
Think... think about this carefully.
- Think about this carefully.
- Ji Hyo, I am thinking carefully.
[Both of them are trying to recruit
Hyun Jin to their side.]
Ji Hyo is not an easy opponent.
Think about it carefully.
And I have Sae Yeon here too.
- She really is not very easy...
- I gave her a break earlier.
Really?
If you've let her go once,
isn't it time to oust her now?
[Since he let her go once,
it's time to oust her now?]
[Nodding his head yes?]
[Not to us delicate girls!]
It's not that...
- What should we do? What do you think?
- What are you going to do?
- In that case...
- Where are you going?
Where are you going?
[What? Heading towards
Mr. Capable's back?]
What are you doing?
The moment I turn my back...
It's like a sickness...
[Sae Yeon also eyeing Ji Hyo's back...]
Wow... did you just see her?
You just saw her, right?
[Symptoms of Running Man-itis:
Desire to rip-off any name tag that they see.]
I think she's got the sickness too.
How's this going to work?
[Everyone to scatter for now from
not being able to trust one another.]
You go too! I want you to go too!
[My hand just automatically...]
Those two were really enjoying it.
He was seriously enjoying it.
The expression on your face...
You know I've been
eliminated countless times...
but he really was the worst out of
anyone that I've been eliminated by before.
Shin Soo made me feel most nervous.
I wonder what'll happen between
him and Kim Jong Kook?
You're out?
By Jong Kook?
[Shin Soo enters the jail room after
being ousted by Mr. Capable.]
- What happened with Jong Kook
- It's nice to meet you.
By Jong Kook?
I'm sorry. I didn't even get to
greet any of you properly first...
Was it one on one?
- I really wanted to win...
- He says he really wanted to win...
[The battle with Mr. Capable
that he really wanted to win.]
When I found out that
I was coming on the show
all my friends and people around me
asked me to make sure to get Kim Jong Kook.
- But what to do now?
- That he pretends to be so fierce...
They all said they think he acts like
he's so tough and fierce.
But when your friends see it,
I bet they'll be really surprised.
They'll realize that he's not
pretending after all.
They'll just acknowledge that
he is fierce.
Wow... he's fierce!
[No other choice but to go hide,
and then attack his back!]
[Blank Ji collapsing to the floor.]
Are you going to be like this?
What? What was that?
You are out.
[Easily... Ji Hyo is out!]
Seriously...
I think I'm going to faint.
That was way too intense!
[Huh? Where is he headed?]
[Sae Yeon is in the elevator!]
No... no!
- Do you know who I am?
- Yes.
You know...
I'm sorry, I was wrong...
Coolly ousting her.
I didn't get to rip off any
name tags...
[Red card for Jin Sae Yeon.
Red card for Jin Sae Yeon.]
Red card for Jin Sae Yeon.
How could he... he's really cruel.
[The power of Monster Hyun Jin.]
He's slyly cruel.
Jong Kook and Ryun Hyun Jin
are the only ones left now.
It's a battle between
the Monster and the Tiger.
[The cheer is without a doubt for...
Ryu Hyun Jin?]
Ryu Hyun Jin!
[The two facing their final battle.]
- You've won a lot, haven't you?
- Excuse me?
You've won a lot.
On Running Man?
Yes, I've won a lot.
I have done a lot... yes, I have.
Then why don't you give
this one to me?
You have to get to the major
leagues now?
- Yes.
- Shouldn't you go easy on your body?
- No. This is nothing.
- What are you talking about?
- You shouldn't be doing this.
- This much is no big deal.
[Two men without any leniency
when faced with a chance at a victory.]
Have you learned any skills when
it comes to ripping off the name tags?
No. It was difficult even when I had to
rip them off the ladies' backs.
Really? I don't believe you.
I heard the announcements
right after one another.
Shall we run at each other from over
there and go at it in one shot?
Should we?
[Standing apart from left to right
and facing each other in a single blow?]
I think I can picture it.
Yeah, I'm getting the picture.
Okay... then why don't we do this?
Then... come running.
[Run at each other and no defense?]
- Okay?
- Deal.
[Only attack!]
[A handshake to seal the deal.]
[The Monster's attack!]
[Eyeing the opportunity
and going for the attack!]
[Hyun Jin with Mr. Capable's name tag
tightly in his grasp!]
[Will this be the end of the battle?]
[Monster Hyun Jin's attack is a success!]
[I won!]
[A celebration over
Monster Hyun Jin's victory!]
Do you know how angry Shin Soon is
from having been defeated by you?
- He is really mad.
- Why do you have that?
This is...
[His anger seems to resurface as soon as
he saw his ripped off name tag...]
Choo Shin Soo is really angry right now...
I heard that you really beat
up Shin Soo?
No, that's not true!
Do you know how much he's worth?
- When did I...
- Look at his arm!
I can't lift up my arm...
What do you mean, you can't lift it up
when it was your name tag that was ripped off?
I will explain today's race to you.
Today's race is...
Two rounds of psychic sports,
including psychic baseball.
- That sounds like fun!
- Psychic baseball!
[It's baseball!]
Through psychic games that are about to start,
you have to earn psychic power vouchers.
And once you get to your final location,
you can trade that in for a psychic power.
[- What is that?
- I don't know...]
We're all clapping without knowing either.
[Just big smiles for now.]
Sae Yeon's really full of big,
bright smiles.
Aren't her smiles so bright?
Since this is a baseball game,
you will be divided into two teams.
There's an advantage for Ryu Hyun Jin
who won this first game.
[The victor of the name tag elimination
Hyun Jin is given an advantage.]
[And that is...]
[Psychic power card?]
Then what does it mean?
[Team Ryu will start off with
two psychic power cards.]
You said we can trade them in later?
He already has skills
when it comes to baseball...
You'll find out what psychic powers they're
for once you get to your final location.
But since you don't know what you'll get,
the more vouchers you get, the better.
I understand.
[Team Ryu: Jong Kook, Gary, Kwang Soo,
Sae Yeon]
[Team Choo: Jae Suk, Suk Jin, Ha Ha, Ji Hyo]
[Team Ryu getting ready for takeoff.]
[His seat seems to be too small for him.]
Please excuse us.
Okay. This is the race to win
psychic powers.
[Go on to Baebongsan Amusement Park!]
Let's go!
Let's go.
Hyun Jin, when we play games today,
you have to do a good job, okay?
Me?
[Already ordering Hyun Jin around.]
He's an athlete, I'm sure he'll do well.
- Why are you telling him that?
- When it comes to games...
[He's the man that would give shooting
pointers even to Michael Jordan.]
Shin Soo and I decided to speak
in casual speech with one another earlier.
- Seriously?
- How old are you, Ms. Ji Hyo?
- Yes... I'm older than you.
- Seriously?
She's older than she looks.
I'm sorry to tell you this,
but you're the youngest here.
- I am?
- Yes.
- You're the youngest.
- But it was really funny earlier.
What Shin Soo mentioned earlier.
Go Choo (Hot pepper).
[The cheer they shout out for
Shin Soo in America.]
People in America shout out 'Go Choo'
for that he can feed off their energy...
It's what they shout out for him.
Go Choo! Go Choo!
- But since they shout out Go Choo...
- I bet Korean people laugh at that.
- Yes, all the Koreans laugh at it.
- He says that they do.
Go Choo! Go Choo!
Do it a little faster.
[Team Ryu's car]
Ryu Hyun Jin looks like it's a tight
squeeze for him up in the front seat.
[The image of Hyun Jin's tightly
squeezed in body in his seat.]
[Tight]
Choo! Choo!
Go Choo! Go Choo!
Hyun Jin... isn't your
seat a little too tight for you?
I feel so uncomfortable right now.
He's really cute.
He's so cute,
I just want to pinch him.
[Imposingly large cutie pie]
We've arrived!
[Arriving at the amusement park where
beautiful autumn leaves are abundant.]
What is that?
[A scene has been set up...
and two chairs?]
- Wow!
- What is it?
['Thigh wrestling'- Two players per team.
Can earn two psychic power vouchers.]
Two representatives per team.
[First up is Jae Suk for Team Choo.]
- Would Jong Kook like to be first?
- How about you go first?
- But this is...
- You can do this.
- Really?
- Jae Suk's legs are pretty strong.
Look at this...
Look at Hyun Jin's thighs!
I can't even get both of my hands
wrapped around the width of them!
I think it's about three times
the size of yours.
[Jae Suk's legs looking
very tiny in comparison.]
I can't even wrap my legs around his!
[Starting off with his legs
in an open stance...]
His legs are going to rip open.
Rip his legs open, okay?
Hyun Jin, if you can't open them up
all the way, then it doesn't count.
Why do you keep backing up?
[A tight mental battle to start the game.]
What are you doing?
But that's too much!
Actually...
[Older kid and the little kid falling in sync.]
[The National Treasure Pitcher's
overwhelming cuteness...]
So cute! He's so darn cute!
Jae Suk, we don't have a single card.
We have to win this.
We're going to start.
[Defense- Jae Suk vs. Attack- Hyun Jin]
[A competition where the psychic power cards
and the victory is hanging on the line.]
[I must endure it!]
[Jae Suk enduring it
with his teeth clenched tight!]
[Will Jae Suk successfully withstand it?]
[Jae Suk's legs have to open all the way
for Hyun Jin to win the game.]
What are you doing?
[Time left on the clock- Five seconds!]
[Both arguing that they themselves
have won.]
We'll make the decision.
It's Team Choo's victory.
[Team Choo wins!]
Go Choo! Go Choo!
We're going to move on to
the second round.
[Thigh wrestling- Round 2.
A round of Paper-rock-scissors for players]
Okay, okay.
Jong Kook usually throws out a rock.
Paper-rock-scissors!
[Choo Shin Soo wins!]
I saw him mouth the word, paper.
[He got me...]
He saw it?
Go Choo! Go Choo!
Feel his legs!
- How am I going to beat this?
- You remember your name tag being ripped?
[Revenge for getting his name tag
ripped off earlier...]
[Shin Soo having been defeated
by Mr. Capable.]
[I remember...]
[Shin Soo chooses defense position.]
Come on, give me a break!
[He won't lose this time?]
You can do this! You have to win this!
Why are you trying to back up?
Okay... let's go.
[The Major Leaguer bent on revenge...
vs. a singer who coaches athletes.]
Go Choo! Go Choo!
[An all-out effort!
Face starting to turn red...]
Go Choo! Go Choo!
[A fiery battle without any concession.]
[I won't lose this time!]
[The awakening of Mr. Capable?]
[With every last ounce of his strength...]
[Total depletion of power...]
[A perfect win for
Shin Soon this time around!]
[The singer simmering in anger after
having been beaten by the Major Leaguer...]
[Jong Kook vs. Shin Soo's
rivalry will keep continuing.]
You're so cute!
You're so cute right now!
You just wait and see.
Okay, with the order now in place...
please turn around for the next event.
[The next even is behind the curtain?]
- What's going on?
- What is this?
[As soon as the curtain drops,
they find themselves facing a huge crowd!]
[A special outdoor Ddak-ji stadium.]
DDak-ji... this is for Ddak-ji!
Ddak-ji game?
[Ddak-ji's for a game of Ddak-ji...]
[Each team picks a player to go up one
by one to compete against one another.]
Since they're baseball players...
I think this will work.
[Anticipating the skills of
Monster Pitcher, Hyun Jin.]
That's right!
[A deafening sound from the
other side too.]
[Choo Shin Soo with a throw
that's fast as a flying bullet!]
[Monster Pitcher, Ryu Hyun Jin]
[Awesome! These two to
compete in a Ddak-ji competition!]
[Fail]
[Flipping his over.]
[Monster Pitcher, Hyun Jin's turn.]
[Seemed to have hit it on
the right spot?]
[Ah... fail...]
[Shin Soo's turn once again]
No, it's okay for him to pull it closer.
[Wow! He flipped it over!]
[Choo Shin Soo hitting it perfectly
and making it flip over!]
[Similar feeling as hitting a homerun...]
[Team Choo- Five people vs.
Team Ryu- Four people.]
- Okay, Gary!
- Gary!
[Mr. Capable wannabe, Kang Gary's turn.]
[Huh?]
I'm sorry. Please, go ahead.
[Ddak-ji's that are hard to flip over.]
[Seemingly awkward throw...]
[Oh!]
[Fail! Too bad...]
[What?]
[Gary flipped it over!]
Kang Gary! Kang Gary!
[With one precise blow, wins his battle
with bullet-throwing Shin Soo!]
[Team Choo's Suk Jin vs. Team Ryu's Gary]
Suk Jin, you can do it.
You can do it!
[Eh...]
[Sound of air hissing out...]
Why are you so weak?
What was that?
[Gary's turn]
[He flipped it over again!]
[Team Ryu's Gary wins twice in a row!]
Didn't I tell you?
I told you, you could do it!
[The crowd's feverish cheer.]
[Team Choo's Ha Ha vs. Team Ryu's Gary]
[What?]
[Another chance again for Gary.]
[Wow... again!]
[This guy... he shows off some
shocking skills once in a while...]
Kang Gary! Kang Gary!
[I'm the performer, Kang Gary.]
[Elated]
- Hey!
- Hey! Get away!
This guy is like the Ddak-ji whiz!
Wow... this guy is like the Ddak-ji whiz!
[Team Choo's Ji Hyo vs. Team Ryu's Gary
for the third time in a row.]
Hit the center with all your might.
- Like this?
- Yeah, and don't hesitate.
Hit it right in the center.
[Oh my...]
[A total miss...]
Are you throwing out a ticket
or something?
You're really trying to
flip this over right now?
- You don't want me to flip it over?
- Don't flip it over. Why would you do that?
Then tell me that you'll date me.
[Number one when it comes to
creating sweet moments.]
[For the third time in a row,
it is once again Gary's turn.]
[And again!]
[Precisely! And lightly!]
Kang Gary! Kang Gary!
Yoo Jae Suk! Yoo Jae Suk!
[Best record of four wins in a row...]
[Team Choo's last competitor,
former King of Ddak-ji, Jae Suk.]
[Will Jae Suk be able to protect his pride?
Or will Gary's pride climb even higher?]
[Starting off with a stare down
before the competition starts.]
[I'm now the Whiz of Ddak-ji!]
I don't have the confidence...
[Taking off his glasses
for the sake of his pride...]
[Are you the Whiz of Ddak-ji?]
[Then I'm the founder.]
[Undeniable overflow of power.]
[An event to garner all the attention.]
Finish it with one blow.
Don't even give him a chance.
Just don't even give him the
opportunity.
[Nervousness]
- Gary, don't give him the chance.
- Please... please...
One blow. One blow!
Don't give him the chance, Gary.
[Ddak-ji Whiz Gary's clean sweep?]
[Oh... fail...]
Hit it right in the center!
[The skills of the Founder...]
[Fail...]
This Ddak-ji isn't really working for me...
[Gary's turn once again]
[Just this once...]
I shouldn't get greedy. What's wrong with me?
Why am I suddenly being greedy?
- Don't get greedy.
- Just do as how I've always done.
[Another chance that's been given to him!]
[A fervent cheer to restore the life
back to the Founder of Ddak-ji.]
You're going to flip it over!
[For sure this time...]
[Will he...]
[Eh...]
What's wrong with you?
[The God of Ddak-ji
not having made his comeback.]
Why don't you just concede
to Gary and I?
[Gary having been given
the opportunity once more.]
[Wow... he flipped it over!]
[A clean sweep!]
[Gary's record breaking five wins in a row!
Team Ryu's victory!]
You used to be the King of Ddak-ji!
You can come to me after you've
defeated Gary.
- This is really sad...
- Thank you.
[Team Ryu- Five psychic power cards;
Team Choo- Three psychic power cards.]
Wow... Gary, who knew...
Jong Kook, I think I'm discovering new
talents for myself on Running Man.
You're really good at doing
the odd things.
But Hyun Jin,
you really have an adorable face.
- You're really cute.
- Cute, cute...
Let's be honest, Hyun Jin...
you're a little chubby, aren't you?
[His famous nickname 'Ryu-chub', which is
already common knowledge amongst his fans.]
Your hairstyle is really cute too...
and your legs are cute too...
- Did you perm your hair on purpose?
- No, I didn't.
- There it is. I see it.
- Where?
- It's right in front of you.
- Of, I see it.
[At last, Psychic Baseball is
about to start!]
Go, go, go!
[Huh?]
Ryu Hyun Jin...
What are you doing?
[Making sure to let him know
who's the one in charge...]
- I can't get out like this.
- He's a little jokester.
[Hyun Jin seemed to be
surprised over something?]
Congratulations.
[On that day, a post went up announcing
his move from the minor to major leagues!]
[Major Leagues wasn't far off in
the future for Ryu Hyun Jin!]
- Really?
- Seriously? Congratulations!
- Seriously?
- Just now?
- Thank you!
- Seriously?
[And just yesterday...]
[$25.7 million dollars! Highest paid contract
for a Korean baseball player in history!]
[Players for both teams are finally
making their entrance.]
[Running Man Field -
Running Man Ball Park!]
[Where psychic baseball
is about to take place...]
[The showdown's diamond!]
[Who is this person?]
Hwan! What are you doing here?
[Kim Hwan - SBS Announcer]
[Shocking all the baseball fans with
a pitch with the speed of 130km!]
[SBS' flower boy announcer
with a background in baseball.]
I sincerely welcome all of you
here at the psychic baseball field.
[Welcome to Psychic Baseball Ball Park!]
I'm SBS' announcer, Kim Hwan who's been
honored to be here as the referee today.
[Announcer Kim Hwan,
Umpire for today's psychic baseball!]
I'm glad to be here.
I will briefly introduce psychic baseball
which you all will be playing today.
You will be able to choose the psychic powers
that you all see lined up in front of you.
[Trade in the vouchers that they have for
the psychic powers that are to their liking!]
[Team Choo starts by choosing the
powers that they'd like to have!]
First... let's take this one.
[Team Choo chooses
'Ryu Hyun Jin Controller'.]
[Just choosing for now! Will find out their
powers amongst their own team later.]
Choo Shin Soo controller...
Take Choo Shin Soo controller.
[Team Ryu chooses
'Choo Shin Soo Controller'.]
Jong Kook...
can we pick one thing that I want?
I want the glove shape shifter.
I want to have the Glove Shape shifter.
Why?
- What for?
- What's the point of a Glove Shape shifter?
Why does no one ever listen to me?
Hyun Jin, you tell him.
You try telling him.
- Come on...
- What would changing the glove shape do?
What good would that do?
It's not going to do us any good.
I'm 28 years old!
[Only thing I have going for me
is my age?]
[Team Ryu Hyun Jin]
[Choo Shin Soo Controller,
Absolute homerun summoner.]
[Ball shape shifter, Summon to
move the fence telekinetically.]
[Summon to steal two bases,
a fly ball summoner.]
[Team Choo Shin Soo]
[Ryu Hyun Jin Controller, Bat shape shifter,
Incredible strength summoner.]
[Summon to move the bases
telekinetically.]
[Drink the potion you've chosen
and gain your psychic powers!]
[Sae Yeon's turn to drink the potion, who's
never experienced psychic powers before.]
Roll-Roll summoner.
That was so cute!
- He's going to change now.
- It's coming, it's coming.
Why are you burping?
[And the Major Leaguer...]
[Even Ace Ji Hyo swallows her
drink down.]
[Side effects to psychic power potions...
it makes you ugly?]
And now... we will start the game.
Both teams, please bow
in greeting to your opponent.
Just stay like this... stay like this!
Don't go!
What are you doing?
Everyone... everyone,
please face forward.
[The forbidden love...
it's blossoming in the ball park.]
Please face forward.
[For safety reason,
tennis balls and aluminum bats were used]
[Psychic power can be used once per inning.
The pitcher can be switched out at any time!]
Kang Gary, fighting!
[Team Ryu's Kang Gary]
[Strength: Unending discovery of new skills.
Weakness: Love.]
The world's greatest pitcher,
Choo Shin Soo.
Ball!
You're throwing too hard.
- Don't you think you're being too much?
- This isn't the major leagues!
[Major league style from his
first pitch.]
Don't you think you're playing
too seriously?
This is for fun...
we're doing this for laughs.
[Kang Gary, you've hit it!]
[The ball rolls towards Ji Hyo.]
[Gary, safe at first base.]
- Yes!
- Yeah, Gary!
[Trying to make the blame fall somewhere
from having played defense once.]
You're not supposed to come this way.
You catch it and throw it to the base.
It was so that you could catch it.
I'm not good at catching balls...
[One base loaded with no outs]
[Team Ryu's Jin Sae Yeon]
[Strength: A bright smile
Weakness: ?]
[Changing out the Pitcher
to Big-nosed brother.]
Hit by pitch.
[The ball having hit the toe
of her shoe.]
[Clearing of the benches]
That's no way to treat a lady!
What are you doing?
- Were you hit?
- I was hit.
- Where were you hit?
- It hurts so bad!
- Ouch, that hurts!
- What? It really hurts?
[Anyways, Team Ryu:
two bases loaded with no outs!]
Where are you saying it hurts
so badly?
[This seems to be the perfect plan for
Sae Yeon with her acting abilities!]
[Team Ryu's Ryu Hyun Jin]
[Strength: The ultimate pitcher.
Weakness: Limited experience as a batter.]
It's Ryu Hyun Jin...
Let's play a round, Ryu Hyun Jin.
- Let's go...
- Play ball!
The one who controls the batter!
[It has begun!
Triggering his psychic power!]
[Ha Ha transforms into an
evil pitcher!]
- What is...
- Watch closely.
What is this?
[Just what is this psychic power
capable of?]
[This is the power of an evil pitcher!]
[Evil Pitcher: When the ball is pitched...]
[the batter is thrown into confusion
so that the batter is struck out.]
He swung his bat. He swung his bat.
[What? I swung my bat?]
[It spun...]
Strike one.
The one who controls the ball!
[The Evil Pitcher triggers his
second power.]
What is it this time?
What is he doing right now?
[What... is this?]
Strike two!
[Another strike since it passed
through the center of home plate.]
What the heck is this?
- What is this?
- Why did I get another strike?
[This is what we've all been
curious about since earlier...]
The one who controls the batter!
Don't get flustered!
Strike!
[A strike out!]
[Something to tweet about!
Ha Ha strikes Ryu Hyun Jin out!]
How could you get struck out?
I got Ryu Hyun Jin!
[Anything is possible in psychic baseball!]
At this rate, the major league player
is going to get struck out too.
This really is something else.
[Team Ryu's Kim Jong Kook]
[Strength: All sports.
Weakness: Yoon Eun Hye, Moon Geun Young.]
[Be aware! Coach Kook is up at the plate!]
[Mr. Capable, who's strong in every category!
Will he be able to pull off a homerun?]
Play ball.
- What was that?
- What is he doing?
Throw me an easy one.
Throw me an easy one so
I can hit it.
[Mr. Capable hits it!]
Catch it!
[What? His hand slides off!]
[With split of a second to spare,
Gary's safe at third base.]
Jong Kook! Come here! Jong Kook!
[What? Sae Yeon is at second base?]
[If Jong Kook doesn't rush back to
first base, then he is out!]
Out!
[Shin Soo catches it, and he is out!]
[Without even knowing what's going on at
the bases, he just took off running!]
What are you doing?
[Now that we're looking at it,
Mr. Capable's baseball skills are a little...]
Why are you trying to
play baseball on your own, Jong Kook?
I thought with Gary being safe at third,
she ran to second too.
[A surprising weak link, Mr. Capable!
How will he transform for the battle?]
[Running Man Series-
Bottom of the first inning.]
- Baseball is fun.
- Isn't baseball fun?
Baseball is a lot of fun.
[Team Choo's Song Ji Hyo]
[Strength: Running Man's Ace.
Weakness: Sleep and food.]
- Kang Gary, is that you?
- That's right, it's me!
Play ball!
The one who controls the bat!
[Ace Ji Hyo triggers her psychic power
as soon as the game starts!]
What's that?
[The bat... transformed itself!]
- What is that?
- What is it?
[Bat transformer]
[Once the spell is incanted, the aluminum
bat transforms itself to a giant bat!]
[She may be able to hit the ball
by just holding the bat up in the air.]
The ball isn't going to go too fast.
Listen to the whooshing air sound!
Hyun Jin, if you catch it,
throw it to us so it's easy to catch.
- We can catch her hit.
- Ji Hyo, just hold your bat up.
Ji Hyo, just hit it hard.
Shin Soon, you should try using that!
Don't wink at me!
- Why do you keep winking at me?
- I was winking at the catcher!
[Catcher- Kim Min Gyun]
[Ace Ji Hyo succeeds in hitting the ball!]
[Thrown over to Mr. Capable at first base!]
[Mr. Capable drops the ball!]
[Ace Ji Hyo, safe!]
Safe!
- How could you throw the ball like that?
- How else was I to throw it?
- These psychic powers are working well!
- Good, good...
That team isn't working because
of Jong Kook.
How am I supposed to catch the ball like this?
How was I supposed to do that?
- You could've caught that, right?
- That was a perfect throw! It was perfect.
Wow... I'm seriously about to
go crazy.
[Team Choo with all bases loaded,
and one out!]
[Team Choo's Yoo Jae Suk]
[Strength: Common sense, the chase.
Weakness: Choi Min Soo.]
- Do we have anything?
- Kwang Soo...
- Show them what you're made of.
- I will show them all.
[Giraffe stepping in as the relief pitcher.]
I will show everyone what a
frightening pitcher I really am.
Play ball!
Pitcher Roll-Roll!
What is that?
What is pitcher Roll-Roll?
[Alter egos?]
[Then could it be that
there are three pitchers?]
[Just what kind of skills does
pitcher Roll-Roll possess?]
- Seriously...
- Play ball!
When I shout out, pitcher, you
have to separate and throw together.
Pitcher!
Roll-Roll!
[Total chaos]
What the heck...
how can all three of you throw?
This isn't even right!
That was to hit us with the balls!
[Every time the ball goes back and forth,
so does their annoyance level?]
There are a lot of angry people
on this baseball field.
- You have to throw it together.
- Pitcher!
Roll-Roll!
One, two, three!
[What?]
[My goodness! He hit some of the balls?]
[A lucky strike!]
[Ha Ha crosses the home plate!]
[Shin Soo also crosses the home plate!]
[Team Ryu- 0 : Team Choo- 2]
Jae Suk... that was awesome!
[It seems as though Hyun Jin needs to
step up to the game!]
[Team Choo's Ha Ha]
[Strength: New groom.
Weakness: He's now a married man.]
The one who controls Ryun Hyun Jin!
[The power that we've all been curious
about right from the beginning!]
The one who controls Ryu Hyun Jin?
[Huh? What is the basket for?]
I wonder if this is better?
[Batter can switch out the ball Ryu Hyun Jin
throws out to whichever one he likes.]
And what about this little ball?
That one! That's a good one!
[Switched out to the big and
easy to hit bounce ball!]
Giving a ball like that
to the world class player...
That's so funny.
Do you think this is dodge ball?
- Ha Ha, don't hit the ball!
- That was so fast!
Wait! Dong Hoon, wait to hit the ball.
- Watch the ball.
- We'll catch the ball, so don't worry.
Give him a ball.
[Big-nosed brother dashes for the
home plate from third base!]
[Just then!]
[Gary catches the ground ball,
and goes to home plate himself?]
[Gary drops the ball... and Suk Jin
doesn't step on the home plate.]
Safe! Safe!
Touch it! He didn't step on the plate!
Out!
[Big-nosed brother gets tagged out
at home plate!]
[Random Mr. Capable, Gary!
He was able to protect the team!]
What the heck, Suk Jin!
Okay, that was good.
That ball is good even if they hit it.
[Team Choo's Choo Shin Soon]
[Strength: Major leaguer.
Weakness: Unknown.]
The one who controls Choo Shin Soo!
[Kwang Soo triggers his power
to control Choo Shin Soo!]
- What is that?
- The one who controls Choo Shin Soo?
[Huh? Another basket?]
[He can switch out the bat Choo Shin Soo
uses to hit the ball with whatever he likes.]
What about the tennis racket?
What to do?
Don't you think that's just too much?
[The really long looking one is just
part of the magic basket inventory.]
We should have him use that one.
- Do you want him to hit the ball or not?
- We don't want him to!
Really?
Didn't you know?
We don't want him to hit the ball.
[A man who checks out
all the bats out for him in detail.]
[Ultimately chooses an ironing stick.]
[Will he be able to hit the ball
with the ironing stick?]
Go Choo! Go Choo!
This is turning out to be really funny.
I'm sorry.
[But his expression
still looks pretty confident...]
- Play ball!
- Go Choo!
I'm going to strike out Choo Shin Soon!
Being struck out by Kwang Soo?
[What? He hits it!]
[A clean hit to the left!]
[Both teams are having a hard time
believing what they're seeing!]
Wait...
What's awesome!
[In the meantime, Jae Suk and Ha Ha
both make it safely across the home plate!]
That's amazing... that's amazing!
I heard that Shin Soon once even hit
a ball with a wooden chopstick.
How did that happen?
How could you have given him a bat
no matter how small it is?
Don't we have toothpicks around here?
No toothpicks?
[Running Man Series,
top of the second inning.]
[A new plan must be devised
at the change of an inning.]
Suk Jin... move in. Move in.
Move in? It's Sae Yeon.
[Sae Yeon! Use your psychic power!]
Okay.
Play ball!
[What is that laughter all about?]
The one who dominates homeruns!
- What?
- What is that?
[She did shout out her spell,
but what's going to happen?]
- What is that?
- What's that for?
[She definitely missed the ball...]
[Just what...]
[Huh?]
[A ball out in the bleachers?]
[Homerun!]
[As long as the bat is swung,
it always becomes a homerun!]
She struck a ball thrown out
by Choi Shin Soo!
That's a homerun?
[Team Ryu's Sae Yeon is the only one
to get a homerun so far in the game!]
Our player hits a homerun!
This is a blow to my pride.
[Team Ryu: 1, Team Choo: 4]
Sae Yeon, it's embarrassing
for you too, isn't it?
[The important point here is that
they scored a point in the game.]
Seriously...
It's Ryu Hyun Jin!
- Time!
- What is it now?
The one who moves the fence!
[Move the fence?]
What is this now?
[The fence's are moving!]
[How... of course, it's people...]
What are they doing?
What is this? It's a homerun
as long as he hits past this?
[100% manpower -
Moving the fence forward.]
How far are you going to come in?
- How far are they going to move in?
- They're coming onto the diamond!
- Is this homerun?
- Yes.
- If he hits past that fence, it's a homerun.
- That's absurd!
[One the spell is shouted out, the fence moves
to the infield and hitting over is a homerun.]
So what I hit earlier could be
a homerun in a case like this?
That's good, that's good.
That's absurd! The fence
came in all the way to the infield!
[Okay then, let's see...]
[Ryu Hyun Jin hits it hard!]
[Oh... my!]
[Homerun!]
[Team Ryu's Hyun Jin
hits the ball out of the park!]
Look at how happy he is.
Shin Soo, how many homeruns
is that now?
This is the first time it's happened
ever since I started playing baseball.
Shin Soo...
Shin Soo... why are you
giving them so many homeruns?
[Team Ryu: 2, Team Choo: 4]
Do they seriously have to go that far
just to do a single trick?
[Since what needed to get done is done,
the fence is moved back into place.]
[Please don't use the fence
power too often!]
Play ball!
Gary, aren't you going to use it?
Time!
The one who calls in a hit by
the pitcher!
What is this?
[Put on a suit to make the body bigger,
and use the ball that end up hitting the body]
Your stomach is blocking the home plate.
What can I do about it
when I've already gained the weight?
Wait... I don't know where to
throw the ball.
[100% effective! Gary moves
on to the first base after being hit.]
[Everything is good,
but if he has to keep that on...]
[And next up at the plate...]
[Sae Yeon gets to move on again
from getting hit by a ball.]
[And the ball Hyun Jin hit is...
a fly out!]
[And Jong Kook who's gotten
the feel for the game...]
[Anyways, Team Ryu gets
two of their players onto the bases!]
I've been waiting for you.
Lee Kwang Soo...
That's something that I should
be saying.
I'm going to make sure to
strike you out.
This time, I'm going to hit a homerun.
The one who strikes out Lee Kwang Soo!
The one who humiliates
the crap out of Yoo Jae Suk!
[The ball is airborne up high in the air!]
He's out, he's out!
[If the runner gets outside the line,
then that player is out!]
He's out. He's out of the line.
[When even a single meter outside the line
means out, he was about three feet out...]
I don't know baseball all that well.
Why am I out?
Can you explain it to me?
Player switch out.
I seriously don't know...
[Running Man Series-
Bottom of the second inning.]
Fighting!
Play ball!
Time!
The one who controls the glove!
- What...
- No, it's the bat. The bat.
- Bat, it's the bat.
- Oh...
Here, take my glove!
- Try doing something with my glove!
- Ji Hyo, it's the bat.
He wants her to try...
Time!
The one who controls the bat!
[The bat Ji Hyo previous used by calling in
on her powers makes its appearance again.]
It's going to Jong Kook! Jong Kook!
It's going to Jong Kook!
[Mr. Capable blunders his move!]
What are you doing?
She's safe!
- This is just too sweet! Kim Jong Kook...
- You can't play baseball!
Let's always play baseball
whenever Jong Kook is around.
It's the first time I've seen him
like that.
He's playing like a newbie...
a newbie!
Time!
One who controls Ryu Hyun Jin!
The one from earlier.
[Choosing the bounce ball that
he used earlier again.]
[But Blank Ji Hyo seems to have
strayed pretty far from the base.]
[Will she be okay?]
Ha Ha, hit the ball.
[Checking up on first base.]
[Amazing...
Song Ji Hyo even knows how to slide...]
Hey! Ryu Hyun Jin!
What kind of a woman slides to
the base?
[Our Ace Ji Hyo,
who doesn't mess around.]
[Sliding]
[Team Choo slides to safety
at first and second base.]
Jae Suk... the one who controls
the bases!
The one controls the bases!
What's that?
The one who controls the bases!
- Where are you going?
- The home plate is going to third!
[Once the spell is shouted out, the home plate
moves to third and once crossed, you're home.]
[An easier way to score
a point than a homerun.]
[And on top of that,
first and second bases are loaded.]
[The golden opportunity to
score points!]
Ji Hyo, just run! Run unconditionally!
[And... the moment has arrived...]
[Batter, Choo Shin Soo]
[Pitcher, Ryu Hyun Jin]
[Choo Shin Soo]
[Anointed as representative of Korea
for major league baseball.]
[Ryu Hyun Jin]
[An athlete who's now
about to face a much bigger stage.]
[Batter, Choo Shin Soo
vs. Pitcher, Ryu Hyun Jin]
[A face-off by two players representing
the face of Korea in baseball!]
The fact that these two players are
meeting out on the baseball field like this...
is a great treat for all of us
and to the viewers watching this at home.
[The first battle between these two
major leaguer's that we'll soon get to see.]
[Just what will be the outcome?]
[No desire to joke around.]
- Choo! Choo!
- Ryu Hyun Jin!
Go Choo! Go Choo!
[Seems to be putting too much
force behind his shoulder.]
Ryun Hyun Jin seems to be
a little nervous at the moment...
- It's a ball!
- No, that wasn't.
- It's definitely not a ball.
- It's not?
[Let's see then...]
[A slight curve?]
[In that case...]
[Shin Soo bunts the ball!]
[An easy ground ball
headed towards Jong Kook!]
[Home plate is at the third base!
They need to tag Ji Hyo quickly!]
[Ji Hyo uses that moment to run as fast as
she could and successfully makes it home!]
One point!
She made it to the plate.
[Running Man Series-
Top of the third inning]
[Team Ryu currently behind 5:2.
This is their final attack.]
The one who steals second base!
[Once the spell is shouted out, second base
disappears allowing direct access to third.]
What the heck? What happened to
second base?
What the heck?
What happened to second base?
Where did second base go?
[Giraffe not having seen the explanation
sheet for Second Base Stealer.]
- Where did second base go?
- Where did it go?
What the heck?
We got it, we got it.
- Where did second base go?
- I'm the one who steals the second base.
You should've told me about
it sooner!
Seriously...
[Next batter up, Jin Sae Yeon]
[Okay... here it is...]
Sae Yeon!
The one who controls homeruns!
- The one who controls homeruns!
- No way! That's absurd!
[Team Ryu already seeming to
sense their victory.]
I think we can do this!
Use your power.
Homerun!
[A masterful homerun!]
[A smoke blast]
[Team Ryu bringing home two players
with Jin Sae Yeon's homerun hit.]
That was absurd...
[A reversal!
Team Ryu- 6 : Team Choo- 5]
This is the last inning,
we have to do a good job.
[Running Man Series-
Bottom of the third inning.]
[Team Choo's last chance at an attack!]
[Shin Soo stewing in anger over
how the game got flipped around.]
You could use your spell.
Let's score some points and win.
Shin Soo's worked so hard for the win.
Ryu Hyun Jin, get out here.
Ryu Hyun Jin.
[Discussing who should be pitching.]
Ryu Hyun Jin,
are you avoiding the battle?
You... stick boy, get out of the way.
Ryu Hyun Jin, come out here.
Ryu Hyun Jin!
You telephone pole,
get out of the way.
- Kwang Soo...
- This is their last offense.
Ha Ha! Hit one out of there!
Not you, but send Ryu Hyun Jin
out here.
Pitch Roll-Roll!
[Giraffe using his psychic power again.]
You have to hit it. We have to score!
- Ha Ha...
- Pitcher!
Roll-Roll!
[The ball that Kwang Soo threw directly...]
Hitting him in the face with one...
[The Roll-Roll's throws their balls
at the batter at top speeds.]
- Seriously...
- Why don't you try talking again?
I guess you must be afraid of me,
having to use your Roll-Roll's like that.
You coward...
You coward... Giraffe...
Roll-Roll, released!
- Kwang Soo!
- Hey! What are you doing?
I guess you didn't like hearing that!
Roll-Roll's, you are released.
Thank you for your hard work.
- Are you crazy?
- That's good!
Ha Ha, let's do this!
Just picture me beating you
if you lose this game for us.
I'm going to get my revenge.
[An unexpected situation]
[Haroro vs. Giraffe-
Their first fight in two years!]
[No right or wrong-
A typical fight between children.]
Kwang Soo's the only one who's been hit.
- Kwang Soo's the one who got beat.
- Both of you... you're out!
- Both of you are out!
- Why?
Out!
- No, no, no!
- We've already made up!
- We've made up! We're okay now!
- We're fine!
- We're actually really close!
- We fought because we're so close!
[Adamant Umpire Kim Hwan]
You're out.
- We were fighting because we're friends.
- What were you guys thinking?
- We were doing it to be funny!
- You didn't think it was funny?
Play ball!
- Okay, this is for real.
- You're playing for real?
Hyun Jin, we have to finish this up.
Show us what you're made of.
Strike!
Strike, you're out!
[A strike out- Two outs total]
[If one more batter is stuck out,
then it's Team Ryu's win!]
Ryu Hyun Jin is throwing it for real.
Strike one.
Strike two!
[Two strikes on top of two outs!]
[Is this the end of the game?]
Yoo Jae Suk, fighting!
[Just barely hitting the ball!]
[Why did it have to roll in front
of Hyun Jin of all people?]
[If he throws the ball to the first base,
then the game is over!]
[Misses!]
[The tennis ball is much more difficult for
players to control than regular baseballs.]
Run! Run quickly!
Get to the home plate!
[A glimmer of hope! With two
outs, moves on to second base!]
Time!
The one who controls the base!
[The home plate is moving to the third base!]
[Have to use every psychic power
that is available to them...]
- Use that other power too!
- The one who controls the bat!
[Team Choo- Simultaneously using
all the psychic powers that they can use.]
- How did this happen?
- We can't let them score the point!
- What are we going to do?
- Bring it home!
The incredible strength!
[If he can cross the home plate with a teammate
on his back, then it equals two points.]
[Team Ryu tightening up their defense!]
[Defense Roll-Roll!]
[Several Roll-Roll Alter-egos are
brought onto the field for added defense!]
How many of them are there?
This is the final round!
Two outs with two at base.
Ji Hyo, you have to hit it!
Don't you think he's out too far?
[Straying that far out with someone
on his back on top of it?]
If you don't like it,
then check and oust him.
[It does seem possible to oust him
by doing a quick check...]
[Nerve-wracking...
If they make it, then it's two added points!]
Yes, I understand.
I'll do as you tell me to do.
Strike!
[Swinging a strike from a ball
having flown by too fast.]
- I almost just checked on him...
- Ji Hyo, just hold the bat in front of you.
You can just hold it out in front of you.
[A reversal of the game with one point,
and next up to bat is Choo Shin Soo.]
[There's no way to go!]
[It hit Ji Hyo's bat!]
[And the ball if rolling towards Hyun Jin!]
[Flying like lightening to bring
the ball to first base himself!]
Ji Hyo, you should've ran!
[With Team Ryu's Hyun Jin running the ball
to first base himself, he ends the game!]
[Blank...]
Wait!
Future Ddak-ji!
The one who sees into the future!
- What?
- I just saw the future!
- You have to run as soon as you hit, okay?
- I got it!
I didn't... I didn't know
that I should've been running!
Here... the one who sees into the future!
Me too!
- Hurry up and throw it down too.
- I can't do it.
And so, Team Ryu Hyun Jin wins
today's Psychic Baseball game.
[2012 Psychic Baseball- Team Ryu's win!]
- I'm sorry.
- We almost had it...
[The prize is...
a trophy with a pure gold badge.]
2012 Running Man baseball victory.
Look at Shin Soo...
- Shin Soo really is angry.
- He looks very mad.
We should've been the one to take that!
I came on the show to win that trophy...
That's really cool.
Anyways... Team Ryu Hyun Jin wins!
[The pride of Republic of Korea,
Choo Shin Soo and Ryu Hyun Jin...]
[We wish you the best with
your careers in the major leagues.]
Subtitles by DramaFever