[Running Man Chaser]
Subtitles by DramaFever
Kang Dong Yoon is sentenced to
eight years in prison.
[Kim Sang Joong sentenced
to 8 years in prison]
[The power forced to kneel in front of truth]
[Definitive evidence that brought
the truth to light]
[And that's how he received
his judgment of truth]
[Eight years later]
[Sang Joong, who's been lying in wait,
is finally released]
[The location seriously has the ominous feel
of 'The Chaser' season 2...]
[And the one person who is
approaching in his direction]
[Sang Joong's shadow, Aide Jang Shin Young]
[An emotional reunion after eight years...]
You've suffered a lot in there all this time.
You've suffered a lot too
during this long period of time...
[At the same time]
[Another crime that is exactly like the one
from eight years ago has happened...]
Please give us a judgment on this case.
[Today's judge is the God of Disguise,
Judge Dong Wan]
[Jo Jae Yoon- Special appearance by
Yong Sik from The Chaser]
Detective Yoo!
Come sit down over here.
-You're already here.
-Detective Yoo...why are you so late?
[Yong Sik is helping Detective Yoo,
who's been put in an unfair situation]
That PK Skull guy or whatever that you
worked so hard to arrest...
[PK Skull:
Hallyu star, member of Skull and Ha Ha's duo]
Even though he may be a popular Hallyu star,
you don't think he can escape jail, right?
PK Skull...
He ousted my little sister by ripping off
her name tag on her back...
He will pay for it.
PK Skull, you're over as of today.
You're over.
Defendant... Do you have any last words?
[Will PK Skull receive a "not guilty" verdict?]
Even though I haven't sinned...
If there's anyone who's upset because of me,
I just... feel bad about for it.
Case number 107.
I will now announce the verdict for
the defendant PK Skull.
Defendant PK Skull...
[What will the verdict be for PK Skull?]
Defendant PK Skull is... innocent.
[The verdict for PK Skull is innocent]
[Just like eight years ago,
the verdict rules innocent]
What? He's found innocent?
Does this even make sense?
Or is this a load of trash?
Don't move!
[Water...water gun!]
[The fire being sprayed down
from everywhere!]
The judgment...isn't over yet!
As of this moment...
I'm the prosecutor...
And this water gun is the judge.
Save me.
Say it....say it with your own words!
Look here! What are you doing?
[The court room being thrown into chaos]
[Detective Yoo enraged with fury]
[Yong Sik throwing
his whole body in to intercept]
[Detective Yoo overpowering PK Skull]
[What?... The water gun has been fired?]
[Skull-Out! Skull-Out!]
[Jae Suk taking care of
his own sister's revenge]
[PK Skull's soaked name tag]
You have to escape!
[Jae Suk able to escape with Yong Sik's help!]
-Are you Detective Yoo?
-Yes.
-You have a package.
-A package?
[But there's a package for Detective Yoo?]
What is this?
[On the other hand]
[This is the day that
Sang Joong has been waiting for?]
What do I need to do?
There's a press conference at Y university
in Songdo tonight.
All you have to do is to get to
the conference with the gold badge on.
Where's the gold badge?
It's being delivered here right now.
Senator...
If you were to win this,
what will you do for me?
Shin Young...
If I were to win,
half of that winning will become yours.
That's not enough.
Give me half the gold badge.
You have to become
a useful person to me first.
Then...you will be able to earn
everything that you want.
[If you become a useful person to me,
you will get everything...]
You've got a delivery.
[The awaited package arrives.]
[At last...the time of resurgence has come]
Senator...the gold badge isn't here!
There's only a water gun in here!
[There's no gold badge...but just a water gun?]
What do you mean,
the gold badge isn't there?
If we don't have the gold badge
knowing where the final destination is
doesn't even matter.
It seems as though...
someone has switched our packages.
[Someone has switched out your packages?]
Can you show me the delivery roster?
[These are Running Man members' names!]
One of these took the gold badge.
[At the same time...
Packages have been delivered to Running Man]
Thank you.
[Who amongst this group
was delivered the gold badge?]
-Shall we go after them right now?
-No.
These are Running Men,
who go crazy over anything gold.
And if we just go after them without a plan,
they may all band together, or...
Whomever has the gold badge may take it
and go into hiding somewhere.
A chase...
Isn't about me chasing after them.
It's about making them chase after you.
[Who is it?
The one who blocked my resurgence...]
[Reporter Lee Kwang Soo. Giraffe Journal]
Cue.
[Giraffe's messy reporting]
Coming! He's coming!
[Fierce interview competition]
How is the family related?
[Wardrobe malfunction...]
[The interview scene and Giraffe's pants
falling into shambles]
-Are you Reporter Lee Kwang Soo?
-Yes.
You've got a package.
[A mysterious package]
[Gary with a back injury]
-Doctor!
-What's wrong?
I'm being chased right now.
Please fix me so that
my identity can't be revealed.
I understand.
Then I think we need to do a whole face lift.
What? A whole face lift?
[Fading fighting spirit after being injured]
You're doing the surgery immediately?
Aren't you going to put me under first?
[Immediate FACE-OFF without anesthesia]
Will this complete the surgery?
Kang Dong-Won Bin...
Make me into KangDong WonBin!
KangDong-WonBin...
[All he did was to wrap the bandage
around Gary's face like that...]
[Surgery's complete?]
It's perfect.
Are you satisfied?
[This is... KangDong-WonBin?]
[Face-Off... Success!]
Wait! How can this be!
I'm really KangDong-WonBin!
Oh my God!
Doctor! Thank you so much!
[Gary has become Dog-nose...]
-You've got a delivery.
-Thank you.
[Without a doubt, he gets a delivery too]
[Groom-to-be playing his last round
of pool before getting married]
It's the detective.
Oh my! Detective...
Our name tags are being dealt
without us knowing right now?
I'll call the guys and look into it.
Don't you think we should
get together for a dinner?
I'll treat you to grilled chitlins.
I understand brother.
A package?
[Haroro gets a package delivered too]
[And just like this,
a package was delivered out to everyone]
[Detective Yoo opening up his package]
What's this...a car key?
What is this?
Where's the car? Where is it?
Shouldn't I be
making my escape quickly right now?
During the judgment in the courtroom,
I shot Skull with the water gun...
And ousted him. So there has to be a car...
Otherwise, it wouldn't make any sense.
Wait. My phone...
Is there a member with a car right now?
[If Jae Suk was delivered a key,
then was another member delivered a car?]
Who should I be calling right now?
[After starting chaos, coming back to the mission]
It's Jae Suk.
-Kwang Soo...
-Yes, Jae Suk.
-Do you by any chance have a car?
-Yes, I have the car.
-You have a car?
-Yes, I have a car.
-I have a car key...
-A car key?
-The members...yeah...
-You said you have the car key?
Hey...where are you?
-Where are you, Jae Suk?
-Where are you?
I'm in front of
an elementary school right now.
Kwang Soo!
Jae Suk! Hello!
-Where is the car?
-I've been waiting a long time for you.
-Where's the car? Where?
-This way.
-That's it? How could this have happened?
-Yes, that's it.
-It is the one!
-What?
This is seriously...
As soon as I received this, I thought that
I should call another member who may
have the car, and that's why I called you.
-So you just called me on chance?
-Just load this box in there for now.
Load up the box in the car.
My phone's ringing. Yeah, Jong Kook.
-What's going on?
-Hello, Jong Kook! I have missed you!
-I love you, Jong Kook!
-Kwang Soo...
-I think you're supposed to come pick us up.
-You think that's what it is?
I think you're right...
I think I'm supposed to come get you all.
So call everyone and get their location,
and figure out where they all are.
Jae Suk, it's too hot in here.
-And then I'll come pick you all up.
-Make sure you bring Kwang Soo!
-Okay, I got it. He's in the seat next to me.
-Okay, I got it.
I got it. Let's get in for now.
We're going to get on the way.
Hey... I think everyone has something then.
I told you that from the beginning...
Do you still not know Jong Kook?
Whatever! You still don't know
this game itself!
-I'm seriously about to go crazy...
-You don't know this game itself!
-This is so frustrating.
-This is it...this is it.
Miss Blank!
Ji Hyo!
What did you get?
-Miss Blank...
-Why is the tape still on yours?
What I have is...a navigation system.
-I think it's to put up here in the car.
-I think so.
-It was difficult finding this place.
-Okay.
The really important thing is to find out
where the destination is...
-But you're the one who knows that.
-There's a destination in here, Jae Suk.
-What are you saying?
-Someone else has the destination.
I'm seriously about to go crazy...
Who would have it?
No one is even telling us what they have.
-There's someone who I think may have it.
-Who is it?
-A friend of mine came today.
-Really?
[Blank Ji's friend?]
A guy...
[A total disappointment?]
He has the information regarding
our destination on him.
[By any chance...this friend?]
Even though I don't know
who your guy friend is...
But if he gets here...
we have to ride together with him, right?
Of course.
It's a pretty tight squeeze in this car...
-Okay, then you can get off.
-Ji Hyo...
[Why is he adjusting the volume in the car?]
Did you just...turn down the volume here
while trying to adjust the volume on that?
Why would you turn this down?
This is the audio volume!
You should be turning the volume down
from that unit itself.
-How do you work this thing?
-How is it that you...
Seriously... I'm seriously about to go crazy!
-What are you doing right now?
-Don't you know how to use the GPS system?
Just attach it to your face, why don't you?
-What are you doing?
-Just stick it on there...
Hey, Kwang Soo...
Put that thing up here and give Ha Ha a call.
Why are you putting it up there?
Jae Suk's the one driving,
and he needs to be able to see it, you dummy!
But there was no need to call him a dummy...
You should scold her!
Don't you think that you're being too harsh?
That much is just a term of affection.
Hey, don't you know how to work
a navigation system?
-Give me some room to breathe here!
-Hurry up and give Ha Ha a call.
-Check and see what's going on with him.
-What are you telling me to do now?
[The endless nagging
from his older brother and sister]
[The chasing team also gets in their car]
-This is my first time seeing you drive.
-Seriously...no kidding.
After keeping them all dazed for a while...
Then we'll catch the one
who has the gold badge, right?
That's pretty hard.
I feel like I'm the one who's going to
get confused in the process.
Even though it sounds simple...
In the drama, we're a formidable brain power...
First, out of all the members...
the gold medalist for betrayal is Kwang Soo.
And the member who is most loyal...
-Is Jae Suk?
-Kim Jong Kook?
And Jong Kook.
Ji Hyo is the Ace...
What is Ji Suk Jin?
Is he in Kwang Soo's league?
I think he kind of goes back and forth.
[Big-nosed brother changing his course
depending on the situation]
[Huh?
The chase team arrives at some location]
[It seems as though the Running Man
team may be heading this way]
Shin Young...
Let me check the water in your water gun.
-There's water in it.
-Try shooting it.
[On the other hand,
Ha Ha is waiting for his ride]
-Hello, Ha Ha!
-Hey...
Hey, Dog-nose is here.
Hey...what the heck are you wearing?
What is it that you have, Ha Ha?
-Let's see it.
-I told you...I have the USB.
Why do you look so angry?
Hello, Jong Kook!
[And lastly, arriving at where Impala awaits]
-Sorry for making you wait.
-What is it all that you have?
I bought some stuff to eat.
Suk Jin has money...
Ha Ha, let me see the USB that you have.
[Dog-nose has the name tags,
Jong Kook - team shirts,]
-Here's the USB.
-What is the mission?
Who has the mission?
Running Man members...
It's nice to meet you all.
[Huh? Kim Sang Joong!]
-Can you turn it up?
-It's Sang Joong.
There's something that you all
need to do for me today.
And that is to find the gold badge.
First, go to M-used sales lot in Incheon
and find the black box.
If you can't find
the black box within an hour...
The black box is going to self-destruct.
Then now...
To make this Running Man enjoyable
as the water floating down in a river...
I hope that you come running along with me.
He tries too hard to act cool.
[Incheon M-used car sales lot]
-I've never known this place existed.
-How do we find the black box in here?
[Running Man members
arriving at the upper floor]
-We have to find it within an hour!
-The person that finds it has to yell it out.
[They have to find the black box within
an hour like Sang Joong told them...]
If you don't find
the black box within an hour...
The black box if going to self-destruct.
[Find the black box
hidden in here within an hour!]
-Where's the black box? It's not here.
-It's not here...where could it be?
[So many various car lining up each level
without even a space in between]
[It has to be a car that all
7 of them can fit into?]
Let's go down. You guys go up a floor,
and I'll go down a floor.
[Deciding to scatter to find the box
within the allotted hour]
How am I to find it in here?
-What does a black box look like?
What does a black box look like?
-Don't you think this is it?
-You get the feeling too?
-We can open the cars.
-Aren't we finding it too soon and too easily?
[Huh? The door's locked?]
It's locked up.
I can't open the door.
[Does this situation mean that each
and every car needs to be checked?]
[Just then]
[The chase team is entering
the emergency stairwell]
[Moving to the upper levels where
the Running Man members are]
Not there.
[Huh?]
[An unlocked car?]
So there are cars that are unlocked.
[Starting a thorough search of cars
that are left unlocked]
Since the concept is the chaser,
I think it'll be an older car.
[Blank Ji checking out the car thoroughly]
[There they are...]
[Running Man team are too absorbed to
even notice the Chase team]
[Yes...just a little bit closer!]
[No way of finding
the car containing the black box...]
[The Chase team is closing in!]
[Sang Joong, springing an ambush
from between the cars!]
[Springing on Kwang Soo like lightning!]
-Wait... Huh?
-Kwang Soo...
-I'm going to tear this off.
-Why? Wait...no.
Be quiet.
Do you know what this is?
-A water gun?
-It's a water gun.
Stand up quietly.
[Why... Why me?]
-Nice to meet you.
-Hello.
You're glad to see us too, right?
Follow us quietly.
If you scream, or do anything else...
you'll be shot down by the water gun.
-Am I out?
-I can oust you.
[The name tag!]
I listen very well!
-But the black box...
-Did you find the black box?
-No, we haven't found it yet.
-You haven't found it?
I didn't know.
[Completes moving down to a safe lower level]
-Have a seat.
-Huh?
-Sit where?
-You have to sit down. You're too tall.
-If you make the slightest strange move...
-Are you going to shoot me?
[Kwang Soo will be ousted on the spot
if he were to be shot right now]
-Please don't shoot!
-I haven't shot you yet.
-Why are you so tall? Spread out your arms.
-You really are so tall...
[Doing a body search
for the missing gold badge]
-Right now, I'm...
-Wait a second...
-What are you doing?
-Let me see your phone.
-Huh? Hyun Joo?
-Yes, I met him the other week.
[Kwang Soo received Sohn Hyun Joo's
signature the last time he met him]
He's supposed to be the chaser,
but where did he go?
I don't have anything.
[Kwang Soo doesn't have the gold badge]
Sit down.
-Sit where?
-Just sit down here.
[Starting a casual conversation
with the hostage]
What's your mission today?
First, find the black box here...
What did I say on the USB earlier?
I forgot.
Find the gold badge!
-I said to find the gold badge, right?
-Yes...
You have to find that gold badge.
You got the package earlier, right?
-Yes, I did receive it.
-What was in the package?
-I received a car.
-A car?!
I received a car.
[A car was delivered to him?]
The moment I tell you to,
shoot him with the water gun.
[Momentarily forgetting the danger]
Please make me feel a bit more relaxed.
I will make you more comfortable.
The way I hear it, you're the icon of betrayal.
Is that right?
-I won't betray you.
-Can I trust you?
What did you guys talk about when
all the members were gathered together?
While watching the video clip earlier...
That you were trying too hard to look cool...
Trying too hard to look cool?
Who said that?
[A little while ago]
He's trying too hard to look cool!
[Who was it that said that?]
[Just what will Kwang Soo's response be?]
Jong Kook said it.
-Jong Kook said it.
-Jong Kook said it?
I think it would be best to tear off
Jong Kook's name tag off first.
Then what is it that I need to do
in order to oust Jong Kook?
-I have to lure him in.
-Right?
You need to lure him in.
And you have to try to oust him.
[The Chase team looks as though they may keep
Kwang Soo alive to eliminate Jong Kook?]
-Where am I going? Where are we going?
-Just follow along.
Put your seat belt on.
[Hostage Kwang Soo.
On the move with the Chase team]
We're moving onto the next location
to continue the mission.
What about the black box?
They're all going to get suspicious
when they realize that I've disappeared.
What do I do? What am I?
Kwang Soo, you are our wild card.
[Wild card?]
-Things like this is my specialty.
-Really?
[What is he talking about when
betrayal is his specialty...]
I've been waiting for this moment.
Just because you survived...
If you think that you can do
whatever you want in this game...
No...we have another card with which
we can definitely oust you.
[Of course, no such card exists. But...]
[He was completely fooled...]
Did you check them all?
-Did you check them all?
-I checked them all.
[Still not been able to
locate the black box...]
You don't think that someone is being given
a mission while we're all separated, right?
[Mr. Capable being suspicious as always]
I was just saying...
[Ha Ha and Jae Suk discover a 7-passenger
vehicle that's been left unlocked]
-Are you going to buy the car?
-I'm checking out the car right now.
Hey!
-Jae Suk.
-What?
[Could this be...?]
[There's a cellphone in there!]
-We found it!
-Tell them to come quickly!
[The black box they've all been
searching for is a small black box]
Should we all...
[A video message from
Aide Shin Young in the cellphone?]
-Let's start it.
-But Kwang Soo isn't here.
-It's Shin Young.
-Wow...it's Shin Young.
Hello, Running Man members.
This is Jang Shin Young.
Take this cellphone and move on to
Songdo elementary school in Incheon.
Then you'll find a car
that's been readied for you.
Those members who find keys by
approaching the citizens who are holding them
will be able to get in the car.
The secret pass code is...
Running Man members will say:
'Isn't the weather really cold?'
Then the townspeople...will cough.
As I've mentioned, those without a key
cannot get in the car.
Work hard and find the keys.
Where did she say it was?
Are we just going to leave without Kwang Soo?
-She told us to just go.
-What the heck?
Kwang Soo...
[Without Kwang Soo...heading on their way]
Anyways, what the heck happened to Kwang Soo?
-Has he been kidnapped? Or...
-I think he's been bought.
-I don't think it's a kidnapping.
-How does it actually go on The Chaser?
In The Chaser, you can't leave out
the corruption of someone being bought out.
[Suspecting the corruption of someone being
bought out like in The Chaser?]
I think he's been bought out.
Today's a very meaningful day to me.
Today's the day I finished my 8-year sentence
and have been released.
That's really cool...
-What about you, Senior?
-Me?
Huh?
How is it that Shin Young
is Kwang Soo's senior?
I'm 29 years old...What? You're 28? Really?
-Seriously?
-You're only 28 years old?
-No way!
-Are you serious?
I'm being serious! Why are you all asking?
I'm seriously only 28 years old!
-Really?
-Wow...you really are the icon of betrayal.
[Starting with his face, he's a traitor]
It really is nice to see you...
I had no idea that you were so young!
[Kwang Soo's age revelation that
took the inside of the car by storm]
Is that right?
So you're just tall...
[Young Giraffe in his twenties...]
- What's with Kwang Soo today?
- I feel nervous about Kwang Soo.
-Huh? It's Kwang Soo! He's calling!
-What?
-Answer it.
-Kwang Soo...
Hello? Where are you?
Suk Jin, where are you?
I'm on the 6th floor.
We're already in the car and on our way.
Really?
Have you been kidnapped?
-He's acting right now.
-That's an act.
-Let's all listen to him together.
-Put him on speaker.
What do you mean, kidnapped?
Where are you? Come pick me up!
[Nervous]
We're thinking that you've either been
kidnapped or bought out.
Kidnapped? What's that?
I'm being serious! What am I supposed to do?
Come and get me!
He's acting!
There's no doubt that he's acting.
-Suk Jin!
-You received a mission, didn't you?
Just hang up the phone.
-See? Look at this...
-He hung up?
[Sang Joong hung up the phone]
How can he make it so obvious?
They're all going to suspect me
if you do that!
Just call him again.
Tell him that the connection is really bad,
and your call got dropped.
He's calling again. What the heck?
-Hello
-Suk Jin, I have a bad reception here.
But you hung up right when I asked you
if you received a mission.
I'm on the 6th floor right now, Suk Jin.
-Where do I have to go?
-Tell him to come to Songdo elementary school.
Then Suk Jin...
I'll ask people and find my way there.
-You're going to ask your way there?
-The fact that he's saying that is weird!
[A blatant lie that doesn't get through]
-I'm being serious.
-Hey, Kwang Soo...
-Where are you?
-That makes no sense.
[Hang up! Hang up!]
Suk Jin...I'll just...I'll just text you.
[Extremely frustrated Chase team]
[Always a mess... It's the Giraffe style]
[The Giraffe is being scolded here too]
I think there's about a 30% chance
that I've been caught.
[More like being caught 100%...]
You're really awful at lying!
-You get so turned around!
-I'm really not good at this stuff.
[He's not only a hostage, but also baggage]
[Incheon 'S' elementary school]
[Being led to
a place of ambush by the Chase Team]
No, I'm not going to shoot you!
We don't even need the water gun
for Kwang Soo anymore...
-We have other methods to oust him.
-I feel really nervous right now.
-Kwang Soo...look at this.
-Don't do that!
No, I just wanted to show you
how it shoots.
I just wanted to show it to you.
-Where is this place?
-You think you can find your way back here?
-Yes, I can find my way.
-You can?
We'll stay here...
So you go and bring Jong Kook here.
[Given the mission to lure in Mr. Capable]
I will try.
-You have to succeed. Fighting.
-I will succeed.
[The Giraffe heads out
with a crucial mission]
I think we need to turn here.
There it is. The elementary school.
What the heck? There's a car here.
We have to find the key for that car.
[This is the 5-passenger car that they will be
using as transportation after this mission]
-I think there's one person who'll be left.
-One person won't be able to get in the car.
[1 person is going to get left behind again?]
-'Isn't the weather really cold?'
-'Cough, cough'...
So if we can't find the keys here,
then we'll become like Kwang Soo?
So we're going to become like Kwang Soo?
-Just know that it's first come, first serve.
-Let's go.
You can usually tell who they are.
People that act awkward...
[A market corridor right next
to the elementary school!]
[Just who are the ones with the car key
amongst these countless number of people?]
-The ones who acts unnatural...
-Or they avoid making eye contact.
[There's such a person here!]
[They're here!]
We have to find it quickly...
Find it quickly.
[The sooner they find it,
the sooner they're out of danger!]
-'Isn't the weather really cold?'
-You want a glass of iced coffee?
'Isn't the weather really cold?'
-Yes, it's really cold.
-I know...
-Please give it to me. (The car key)
-He wants an iced coffee.
No, that's not what I meant.
Hello!
Isn't the weather really cold!
-Isn't the weather really cold?
-Yeah, it's really cold. Come in here.
-You can just come in here.
-No, no, no...
I can't come in right now... I can't come in!
[They think he may have heat exhaustion]
-Sir! Isn't the weather really cold...
-Oh my! What is this!
-But how...
-This is how summers should be.
-What are you doing?
-I'm on a mission right now.
I guess this isn't it.
You need to have a key.
-You don't have a car key, right?
-We have one.
[She has a car key?]
Isn't the weather really cold...
[Could this be the pass code?]
See? It's right!
-Why are you teaching her?
-When did I do that?
When did I teach her that?
She did it on her own!
-Mother, do you have the car key?
-Yes.
[Anyways, she says she has the car key...]
[Thank you!]
-Isn't this her car key?
-I think that's her car key.
-Wait...is this your car key?
-Yes, it's mine.
It's mine, it's mine.
[She hands over her own car key?]
-But we need our car key...this one is yours?
-That one is mine.
-This isn't our mission car key?
-No, it's not.
Then you're looking for a mission car key?
[No wonder...]
How can you just hand over your car key?
Why is the weather so cold?
-Isn't the weather really cold?
-No kidding.
Don't you have anything for me?
Don't you have anything to give me?
We have nothing to give you,
but we can give you blood sausages.
No, not blood sausages...
-The weather is...
-Excuse me?
-Isn't the weather really cold?
-What are you doing?
-Why are you being like this?
-I'm not doing anything...
Wait...mother!
She has a key! It's a key!
Isn't the weather really cold?
-Isn't the weather really cold?
-What? What are you doing?
Isn't the weather...
I don't think she has it!
[I'm not a weird person!
I'm Dog-nose, the singer!]
[Who has the gold badge?]
[It's definitely one of those members
that has the badge]
[I have to make it to
the press conference with the gold badge!]
Hello, ma'am.
Isn't the weather really cold?
[Huh!?]
[Pass code a success!]
Thank you!
Thank you! I found it!
[Now the car key that was hidden away...!]
Thank you! Thank you, mother!
I found it!
I found it.
[Ji Hyo, the first to succeed the mission]
[Jong Kook enters a dish shop]
Ma'am...isn't the weather really cold?
Isn't the weather really cold?
[Mr. Capable also succeeds with the pass code!]
[Acquires the car key]
Did you find it?
-I found it.
-Really?
It's Kwang Soo!
Kwang Soo!
[Hostage Kwang Soo
finally discovers the Tiger!]
He's trying to lure me in right now.
Seriously...he's trying to lure me in.
[He is trying to lure me in right now, right?]
[Darn...]
-Hey, Kwang Soo's trying to lure me.
-Kwang Soo's here?
-Over there in the corner...
-That awful jerk!
How did that happen?
[Huge failure]
Why did I have to get caught there?
[Torturous life of a hostage]
-Someone's calling me. Kwang Soo?
-It's probably Kwang Soo.
Yeah, it's Kwang Soo.
[Dog-nose with the car key also arrives]
Yeah...
You're not alone right now, are you?
Is it Kwang Soo, Jong Kook?
I'm being serious right now...
Yeah?
Seriously...just you...
-Only when you're alone...
-Yeah?
-If you come here by yourself...
-Why?
I have something to tell you. Really.
[Are you trying to put a bell
around the Tiger's neck?]
-Forget it. Hey...
-Why? Who is it?
It's Kwang Soo.
He was trying to lure in Jong Kook.
I'm being serious. Serious...
-What the heck?
-Why is it you?
-What do you mean, why is it me?
Where's Jong Kook?
[Seriously dramatic Easy Brothers...]
Suk Jin!
[It's not Jong Kook, but Suk Jin...]
What the heck is going on?
Where have you been?
Suk Jin...
-Kang Dong Yoon...
-It's been a long time.
How?
Well I...just got a call too from Hera...
-How have you been?
-I've been well, but why am I here?
What is...
[The name tag right away?]
-Right now...
-Mr. Kang Dong Yoon, please...
-Right now, I'm...
-Hello.
Hera...
Did you just...did you just lure me here?
I tried to get Jong Kook here,
but I saw Suk Jin while I was on the phone...
Really?
Why did you see me?
Why did you have to see me?
[The Chase Team kidnaps the Easy Brothers]
You could be ousted right away.
If he rips off your tag, you're ousted.
Please...I'll play a very good role.
Why isn't anyone coming?
One more person needs to get here quickly.
Hey, let's just...go.
Yeah, let's give ourselves some time.
The way I see it, whomever is left
is going to get taken by Kwang Soo.
-You think that too?
-Yeah.
-Ha Ha's coming! Ha Ha's coming!
-He's coming?
[Ha Ha's heading their way!]
So ultimately, it's Suk Jin again?
Who is it? Who's missing?
Suk Jin.
[Suk Jin's missing]
-What's that noise? It sounds like a phone.
-It's a phone call!
-There's a phone in here.
-What the heck? What is it?
-Hello?
You want us to check the video?
-Gallery...
-Gallery.
-It's Shin Young again!
-It's another one!
Running Man members...
You're really confused right now, right?
What this situation is all about right now...
And who it is that you should trust...
But do not worry.
There's one thing that's a guarantee.
And that's to find the gold badge.
[Find the gold badge!]
[Come to the Y University campus
located in Songdo]
That's where the gold badge will be.
She wants us to go to the Y University now.
-Let's go find the gold badge.
-Anyways, she wants us at Y University.
-We need to get to the Y University.
-That's going to be our final destination.
Right?
So Suk Jin is ultimately being captured
and taken by Kwang Soo like this?
[Suk Jin and Kwang Soo's
unknown whereabouts...]
In the back right now...
is Kang Dong Yoon and Hera.
You're curious about what's going on, right?
He's just been released from
serving his eight years...
-Right now?
-This is the story about what happens after.
-Seriously?
-We're in the story of what happens after!
We're in the sequel?
[Thrilled Easy Brothers?]
[HA HA...can it really be that?]
[The chasers and their two hostages
arriving at the final destination first!]
Who are these guys?
[Bodyguards?]
-He looks so much like that comedian...
-Wait...wait here for a moment.
[Sang Joong getting out of the car first]
-You look so beautiful in person.
-You can speak in casual speech with me!
[Giddy hostages]
Okay...grab them!
Grab them!
[What? Grab us?]
What the heck? Why?
-Why are you grabbing us?
-We're on the same team!
[Thought they were on
the same side as the Chasers?]
[What is this turn of events?]
This is not what you promised!
Why? We're on the same team!
-Wait... Sir!
-But we're...
[I'm not...]
[Someone who gets ahead of myself
and makes easy promises]
Wait!
[In order to realize someone's dreams,
someone else's dreams had to be shattered]
[The game starts now]
[A little while later]
[Running Man Team arrives]
[Looks like the gagman Oh Jung Dae,
but it's PD Dong Wan]
What the heck?
Isn't that Jun In Gwan?
Who am I?
-Batman? Is that Batman?
-Please stand in a line.
In a line?
He actually looks pretty cool
when he dresses normally.
[At this point,
not realizing what is going on]
-What is this?
-What's going on?
[Anyways, what are they all doing...]
-What is this now?
-What is this?
[Easy Brothers are seen bound in the screen!]
-Save us! Save us!
-Save us!
[What in the world...]
-Save us! Hurry!
-Is this for real?
-Let's just leave them alone!
-Is this a recording, or...
-It's a CCTV!
-It's Sang Joong and Shin Young!
[At last, a face-to-face with the chasers]
-Hello.
-Everyone...hello.
-Is this real time?
-It's real time!
-It's real time? You can see us?
-We're being held captive right now.
You're all worked very hard to make it here.
-Hello.
-Sang Joong...
-Who are you?
-It's me, Jae Suk.
-Jae Suk...
I heard that you pretended
not to notice me earlier?
When did I pretend not to notice you?
Sorry, but I told him.
These two that are tied up here
are our hostages.
That's what I want to know!
That's what I want to know.
Until recently, they were your comrades...
-Isn't that correct?
-Yes!
And now, we will make you a proposal.
[A proposal by Sang Joong, the chaser]
I'm going to say something
to my two hostages here...
One person will have important
information for all of you...
And the other person could be a spy
who would cause trouble for all of you.
Watch the expression on their faces...
And figure out which person can pass
the important information along to you...
Can you just kill them both?
-You seriously...
-What are you doing?
But both of them are really horrible liars.
One of these two that you choose...
I'm going to set free.
Now I'm going to tell them each something,
so watch their expressions carefully.
[First Kwang Soo]
I can't see his expression.
I can't see his face at all.
How can we tell?
[Will the information Kwang Soo hears
be the genuine important information?]
-It's not Kwang Soo.
It's seriously me!
You have to believe me!
I didn't get to hear it because of you!
[Kwang Soo's expression was a bit unnatural?]
[This time, it's Suk Jin's turn]
[Suk Jin's expression looks like
he really is hearing something important]
Now...I've told both of them something.
Which one of them will be the person to
pass along a vital information to you...
-Both of them seriously...
- think it's Suk Jin.
You have to make the selection.
[Just which one has the vital information?]
[The start of closing argument]
Jong Kook...look into my eyes.
I'll put you on the line...
Seriously...
I don't know what it is that I should do!
I'm the one, Jong Kook!
-I swear, Jong Kook!
-Why don't you say something, Suk Jin?
I seriously...
Have something I want to tell you guys.
The thing I heard just now.
[Worried...]
But if Kwang Soo's being that serious...
[Kwang Soo's being especially desperate,
and Big-nosed brother is earnest...just who?]
-I'm serious!
-It's Suk Jin. It's Suk Jin.
-It's Suk Jin.
-I think Kwang Soo's the one being real.
-I think Kwang Soo's real.
-No, he's not...
-Suk Jin.
-I say Suk Jin too.
[Through a vote,
Suk Jin wins majority of the votes]
Suk Jin!
[Big-nosed brother is selected]
Wait!
-Wait! They're saying they want to save me.
-What?
We're saying we want to save Suk Jin.
[You have to listen to the whole phrase...]
[An innocent person's life almost
went out the window!]
[Easy Brothers always trying to take
the other person down along]
You really can't do this!
You can't save Suk Jin!
Then as you all want, Suk Jin will be saved,
and Kwang Soo will be killed.
-Kwang Soo is ousted.
-Wait...wait!
-Wait...please wait!
-Is he ousted?
[Is he seriously being ousted like this?]
[He really...ripped it off?]
Then from now on, Ji Suk Jin...
[Lee Kwang Soo-Out, Lee Kwang Soo-Out]
Wait, seriously?
Am I seriously out?
[Officially ousted.
Doubted it for a moment, but he's really over]
-Lee Kwang Soo's out just like that?
-I'm really out?
But I haven't done anything today!
Only thing I've done was being
dragged around all day!
-Kwang Soo...
-I haven't even seen him since this morning!
-I only saw him for a bit this morning.
-You tricked us this morning in the garage.
What the heck?
[Real-time video time over!]
It's over?
Seriously?
-What do we do?
-What are they doing?
This is a security zone.
You've all entered the security zone.
If you're caught by us,
you'll be forcefully detained.
-What are they doing now?
-You have 5 seconds to make your getaway.
-How can they only give us 5 seconds?
-What the heck is this now? So annoying!
[Making their getaway for now!
No idea as to what's going on...]
-This isn't where he is!
-Where the heck is Suk Jin?
What is this?
Hey!
[Running Man members being frightened
to the point of their hair turning gray]
-Run!
-We have to escape!
[They've met their ultimate chaser today!]
I'm being set free, right?
The fate of the hostage who's left alive
will be decided by the two chasers.
What about me?
A jail has been prepared.
You have a jail prepared?
[His rationality that can't be
controlled again today...]
-Wait...I'm really out?
-Kwang Soo...
Wait...
I've done everything that you told me to!
Wait...seriously?
I told you earlier, didn't I?
Not to trust anyone.
-Huh?
-But before we set you free...
-We have to check you.
-Me?
We have to check you first.
I'm sorry. Just a moment.
I don't have anything.
Why are you taking my shoe off?
I'm sorry.
[Checking thoroughly in case Suk Jin has it]
That's just a tissue. I don't have anything.
Am I going to jail?
-Am I seriously going to jail?
-Bye...
-Really? Am I seriously ousted like this?
-Thanks for all your hard work.
[Ah...my life isn't going very well today...]
Ji Hyo...
Ji Hyo...what am I going to do now?
-Suk Jin was the wrong decision!
-Be quiet.
[No one is sympathizing with
the traitorous Giraffe]
[Big-nosed brother, who managed to survive,
is being released as he was promised]
Fighting!
[Is he really the one who was given
the vital information?]
[Or the spy to throw
the Running Man members into chaos?]
Then...as of now...it wasn't on Kwang Soo,
and Suk Jin didn't have it either...
Then it means that
one of the other five members has it.
For now, I don't think there's any need
for us to go chasing them ourselves.
Just quietly keep watch,
and when we're needed, then...
[On the other hand...]
-Hey...
-I think we need to meet up with Suk Jin.
Let's use our brains a little.
I think there's something going on here.
Don't you think we should be using our brains
as we make our way around here?
First, we need you to take out
all the bodyguards, Jong Kook.
[The fact that he can
probably do that is the real problem!]
Since there's supposedly
vital information out there
I don't think we can just find the badge
by just walking around searching for it.
[Top priority is to meet up with Suk Jin, whom
they believe to have heard the vital info!]
We have to find out
what information he has first.
But he can help us find the gold badge,
or he can help them catch us too.
[Oh...sharp intellect]
[With the growth of his head size,
his intelligence also grew?]
In any case, we need to meet up with Suk Jin.
I'm sorry.
Just why is it...
that whenever we come to a university...
We have to be chased around by guards...
and run away from them like criminals?
Yoo Jae Suk-2nd floor!
[All over the place...]
[The bodyguards are everywhere!]
[The pressure of the bodyguards closing in
without a chance to catch his breath!]
This is like a sauna in here!
Just what the heck is this?
What is this?
Why are there so many bodyguards?
I thought I was in an Olympic race earlier.
Hey!
Suk Jin! What's going on?
Let's all go downstairs and talk
since we've all gathered together now.
I'll tell you the information.
[He really is sounding like he heard a vital
piece of information from Sang Joong...]
The genuine piece of
information that I was told...
-We're all searching for the gold badge now...
-That's right...
-Where is it?
-One of our members has it.
[The gold badge that we're searching for...
One of our members has it?]
[This morning]
[Sang Joong, who received a delivery of
a water gun instead of a gold badge...]
I think someone has switched out the packages.
[They realized that a delivery was mistakenly
made to one of the Running Man members]
-You've got a delivery.
-What is this?
[Boxes that were delivered at the same time
too all the Running Man members!]
[Out of those...]
[Inside one of the boxes...]
[Was a gold badge!]
[The person that
the gold badge was delivered to is...]
[Jae Suk!]
[It was Yoo-ruce Willis!]
Kwon Yeol...take this with you.
[At the time, he didn't know what it was,
so he gave it to his VJ to carry around]
But what could I do?
I can't carry that around with me.
Even though I'm happy that
you got yourself a girlfriend,
don't you think that you've changed
too much since you got a girlfriend?
[Thinking that it wasn't anything special,
it was cast aside as something insignificant]
And that is to find a gold badge.
[The gold badge I have is the mission?]
[Because of that he was being cautious
and careful to even breathe all day...]
You're keeping it safe, right?
You can't be caught with it, okay?
[I'm in big trouble!]
[So the vital information
was that one of us had the badge...]
Anyone could have it.
[If anyone finds out that I have it, I'm dead]
But if it's a lie...
-Why would I lie to you guys?
-It could be Kwang Soo too though.
Kwang Soo could have it too though.
[I just want to get out of here...]
Sang Joong is heading this way!
-We should go!
-He's coming, he's coming.
[Just then, Sang Joong and Shin Young
are headed their way.]
[Jae Suk taking this opportunity to escape!]
[Now he has to hide the gold badge
even more securely]
I don't have any pockets.
[Whether it be a chaser, or a Running Man,
if I'm found out, I'm going to be targeted!]
Here, here...
I have it here.
[Totally hidden inside the mike belt!]
Seriously...what do I do about this?
What am I supposed to do?
-What is it that you have right now?
-A gold badge.
Keep it safe.
What happens when I get ousted then?
Does the badge go to that other person?
[If Jae Suk is to get ousted, the gold badge
goes to the person that ousts him]
[Yoo-ruce Willis...
His lonely battle is starting again]
What the heck?
[The final location.
Press conference for Running Man winner]
[Ah...]
[The final destination that the chasers
will be going with the gold badge...]
[...is this place!]
[If I can protect the gold badge and last
until the press conference, then I win.]
What are you doing standing there?
You have to hide right now!
Kwon Yeol!
-How many years have we been together?
-I'm really nervous right now.
Be quiet! You have to be more quiet!
[Jae Suk and his VJ are both
being especially nervous today!]
I'm not holding onto this
because I want this thing right now!
[Jae Suk escaping for now so that
he's not detected by anyone]
[Someone is outside the glass doors...]
[The chasers Sang Joong and Shin Young!]
Jae Suk...
It's been so long since I've seen you,
so why are you running away like this?
-I have to run away from you!
-But let's talk for a minute.
[If he is to get ousted by them, then
the badge will fall right into their hands!]
Let's talk later...later.
-Hi Shin Young.
-Hello!
-Jae Suk...
-Sang Joong...
-Have you eaten?
-Yes, I've eaten.
Sang Joong...
You're the villain right now, aren't you?
No, I'm not. I told you earlier...
That I would give a very vital
piece of information to the two of them.
-Why are you holding onto that water gun?
-This?
[Discovers the water gun
that Shin Young is holding]
She has it since she's a girl...
But...you have to keep this in mind.
You can't think of me as the villain.
-I told you... Ji Suk Jin...
-No, Sang Joong!
-You're the villain, right? You're a villain!
-Whether I'm the villain or not...
Yoo Jae Suk's on the 2nd floor!
[Soon...we'll meet again, Jae Suk]
[I survived...]
Jae Suk!
-Did you find something?
-You scared me. I thought you were...
-Aren't those bodyguards behind you?
-Huh?
Yoo Jae Suk, Song Ji Hyo!
[Shutting the door in his face]
That Song Ji Hyo!
[Fully discharged]
What the heck is this today?
What is it that you're trying to do?
What the heck is this?
[Will Jae Suk be able to protect
the gold badge to the end?]
[On the other hand, Ji Hyo, who has yet to
hear the information that Suk Jin has...]
[Huh? The jail]
Kwang Soo...
Ji Hyo, are you out?
No, of course not.
I came to talk to you.
Hey...what did you hear earlier?
Do you think that I'll tell you that now?
Really?
If you're not going to, then I'll leave.
Don't go, don't go!
Stay a little bit longer and talk to me!
What did you talk about?
What was it about?
-Don't try to think of another scheme...
-No, I'm really not trying to do that.
Don't think and just tell me!
Right now...you have to oust Jong Kook.
Ji Hyo...
I heard we have a spy today.
There's a spy?
It's not me! It really isn't me!
You said one of us is the spy?
Then Suk Jin is the spy!
I don't think they'd make you the spy.
You failed at being the spy the last time.
Has Suk Jin ever succeeded in it himself?
-If one of us is the spy...
-Suk Jin is the spy?
-I'm not the spy.
-I know that you're not the spy.
Even if you were the spy, it doesn't matter
since you can't do anything.
What's going on? What's the mission?
What's going on out there?
-I really don't know.
-You just sit here and think about it.
Ji Hyo, can you come back again later?
-Why?
-Come by again later.
In case I can get on the air...
-Can you send someone in here? Anyone?
-Okay.
Tell someone to
just stop in here for a moment.
[If he has no customers,
is this the end of his deal?]
[Ji Hyo and Shin Young discovers each other!]
[Ji Hyo starting to back away
after seeing Shin Young's water gun!]
-Hello, Sang Joong.
-Hi, Ji Hyo.
Shall we shake hands?
I'll shake your hand next time.
-Ji Hyo, but...
-Yes?
-Have you seen Suk Jin?
-I haven't seen him yet.
-You haven't seen him yet?
-You haven't spoken to him yet?
I haven't seen him yet.
-You're not by any chance trying to kill me?
-No, we're not trying to kill you.
Shin Young's gun
is very threatening right now.
-Nice to see you.
-Yes, it's nice to meet you.
-I've been running all day since this morning.
-Ace...
-The mission I gave this morning was...
-To find the gold badge.
The important thing is to search
for the gold badge together...
-We can search for it together?
-Of course...
Then for now...why don't we join forces
and go search around together...
-Then we'll see you later.
-Thank you.
-It was nice to meet you.
-Okay, Ji Hyo.
You're tired, aren't you?
You want me to stand guard for you?
No, it's okay.
[Then for now...
Shall I let Ji Hyo live?]
-Hey, Shin Young.
-Yes?
Where are you going?
-Come here.
-I'm so bored just standing around.
-Really? In that case...
-Yes...
[Shin Young wanting some action
against the Running Man members]
-Want to meet back here in about 20 minutes?
-Yes.
-You can't get yourself killed.
-I understand.
Okay. Then go run around for a bit.
-Let's just meet back here in 10 minutes.
-Okay.
[30min-20min-10min!
Ever decreasing free time?]
[Shin Young nevertheless excited
about an active hunt!]
[Yoo-ruce Willis seen on the other side...]
[Already looking exhausted from
being chased around]
[Taking a brief rest in a safe research room]
Kwang Soo...wants me to stop by the jail?
But I don't know where the jail is.
What are you doing in here?
[He thought no one would know about this...
But how...]
[When a person is too shocked,
they usually can't make any sound]
Please listen to me.
Sang Joong, I...
-I found out who has the badge.
-Really?
Who has it?
[If he can't spin a story, it's game over]
I think it's Kim Jong Kook.
[Since the situation was dire,
he turned it on Jong Kook]
-Jong Kook?
-Yes.
-What is it that you're doing here today?
-I don't know either.
I just came on here because
they told me to be the chaser.
So all I'm doing is chasing people down.
-I'll go out and oust someone.
-I want you to live for a long time.
The truth is...
In a situation like this, you have to be
cold about who your school seniors are...
-But you're...
-Since we're from the same school...
-Let's try and see how far we can last
-Yes, thank you.
-You said we're going to...
-I was just trying it.
I was just giving it a try, Jae Suk.
Because this is my first time on here...
Since I don't know about you guys'
reaction, or anything...
But I won't tear it off. Trust me.
The reason why I'm standing here
is because I trust you.
I'm not going to tear it off, see?
The moment I feel you put some strength in it
I'll hit you off like this, grab you,
slide behind you and then I'd be out.
It's because I trust you too
that I'm standing here like this.
-Why don't we get going?
-Yes, Sang Joong.
Go ahead.
Just what is it that we were
trying to earn in here?
And what is it that the other
could be thinking right now?
Our writers...
-Which brings me to say...
-That! 'Which brings me to say...'
[Jae Suk, a fan of his phrase...]
Don't you think your tone is too low?
Whether I should kill you here right now...
Or...whether I shouldn't kill you...
I will...
think about that a little more carefully.
-But you have to look and finish it like this.
-But my camera is over here.
[I almost had my badge taken away...]
[Shin Young hunting to her heart's content
during her free time]
[A temporary truce with Ji Hyo
whom she met with earlier]
-You're tired, aren't you?
-I'm so tired!
I'm tired too.
We haven't caught anyone yet.
-Shin Young...
-Yes?
-You're searching for something, right?
-Yes.
Is that in a place somewhere,
or does someone have it?
Both of what you said could be right.
How can you say it in such a
twisted and confusing way?
-One of the Running Man members has it.
-Are you sure about that?
-Yes, that I'm sure of.
-The gold badge?
-I'm positive.
-One of the Running Man?
The thing that we're curious about...
Is it on the person?
Is it something that can be hidden?
We have no idea if it's something that
we can rip off their name tags and...
Oh my God...oh my God...
My legs are so weak all of a sudden!
[Shin Young attacks Ace Ji Hyo!]
Your strength is no joke!
-Sang Joong...
-Shin Young...
Since Ji Hyo said she would
work with us earlier...
[Chaser Sang Joong coldly
eliminates Ace Ji Hyo!]
Dog-nose, come here! We can fight him!
We can fight him off.
Dog-nose, we can do it.
We can do it!
Ah...I forgot.
[Have to search Ji Hyo to make sure
that she doesn't have the gold badge]
-I really don't have it.
-You really don't have it?
Who has it?
Why are you asking me?
You shouldn't have killed me then
until you found that out!
Dog-nose, we can do it. Grab him.
Just come down here right now.
[Chaser Sang Joong eyeing Dog-nose]
Dog-nose, you can do it. Just do it!
Come down here from up there.
-Ha Ha, come up here.
-I'm on my way up.
-Two against one!
If we fight 2 against 1, we can win.
[Sang Joong vs. Ha Ha and Dog-nose]
[Calm...]
Dog-nose,
you're saying you want to go a round?
[This is definitely an uneven situation...
But why is Sang Joong so calm?]
To the back, to the back!
Get towards his back.
[Why is he nagging so much all of a sudden?]
To the back, to the back.
Dog-nose, we have to stick together!
[Ha Ha and Dog-nose sticking together]
Hey, come here...
it's blocked, it's blocked!
-Shoot the gun, shoot the gun!
-Ha Ha!
[What? Shoot the gun?]
[Ha Ha! Just what is...?!]
Shoot the gun! Shoot the gun!
I'm sorry, I'm the spy.
I'm sorry.
[What...what did you say?]
[Ha Ha is the spy?]
[Just when...and how did this happen?]
[Earlier this morning]
[Before all the Running Man members
were gathered together]
[They came to the place where Ha Ha was at!]
Sang Joong!
-What the heck!
-Don't move an inch!
As of this moment, you're going to be
a spy for me and Shin Young.
[Become a secret spy for the chasers!]
That's my specialty!
Being a spy is my...
Wow...you're so pretty!
[Instant compliance over Shin Young's beauty]
You have to become our spy,
and keep everyone confused.
In exchange...a third of the gold badge...
If you can guarantee me that,
I'll be able to work very hard for you.
You have to pledge yourself to me first.
After that, everything you want can be yours.
I'm going to tell these two a story.
I will tell one of them something that is
a vital piece of information to you.
And the other could be a spy who could
cause trouble for all of you.
[The perfect crime]
[Spy Ha Ha,
who hasn't let anything show until now]
[The feeling of betrayal...]
-Then Ha Ha...
-Can you check his back pockets, please?
I don't think I can check those.
[Only thing under Dog-nose's hat
is his yet-to-grow-in hair...]
[He doesn't have it...]
[Then just who is the one
with my gold badge!]
Shin Young! Move quicker!
I can totally see you!
They can't see us advancing on them!
Come in here, quickly!
Come in here quickly!
If those guys see me
coming onto them like this, I'm dead.
[Spy being frustrated to death
over the slow moving chasers!]
They can see us from outside!
[Having a nervous breakdown on his own]
-I'm telling you, I'll be dead.
-Okay, just sit down.
-It's okay..
-It's not okay!
If anyone comes in here,
I'm being held captive, okay?
[Pretend as if he's being held captive
if anyone is to walk in on them]
Hold on to me like this while you talk.
-Hold on to me like this.
-Don't worry, it's okay.
[Is there really a need to go that far?]
Out of the ones that are still alive,
someone has the gold badge.
-We have to find that person.
-I understand.
[Haroro taking his responsibility as the spy]
I'll bring one person in here.
It'll be the quickest for Shin Young
to shoot Jong Kook with the water gun.
She can hide behind the door and shoot him
in the back when he walks in here.
Okay, let's give that a try.
Where did Shin Young go?
You have to stop opening the door like that!
Hey!
Seriously!
Some here, Shin Young! Hurry!
[Shin Young looking as though
she wants to go hunting again]
-I think there's someone there.
-Huh?
-I think there's someone back there.
-Come here, come here.
I think Ha Ha ran down that way earlier.
I don't think I can work together with them!
What the heck is he doing?
[If anything, it sounds as though he's
broadcasting that Ha Ha's in the room]
[Ultimately, coming back into the room]
Excuse me...
[Holding onto her
and explaining the plan to her]
Excuse me!
- This is not how you do it!
- Really?
We can't keep seeing each other like this!
Let me please get out of here!
-The three of us can't be together!
-Okay. I'm trying to get you out of here.
You guys are really scaring me!
They're going to come find me when I walk
out of here, because they'll be suspicious.
They'll naturally suspect me because
I haven't been seen in a while.
[A given basic.
You can't be seen when the door is opened.]
I'm going to turn the light off for a moment.
-Okay, go ahead.
-You have to kill him in one shot. One shot.
Go get me something to drink.
-I don't have any money on me.
-Seriously...you...
Whenever I see you taking a rest,
you're always drinking something!
But you...
Let's be honest...you've lied about not
having money when you had some, right?
You know you've done it.
Kwon Yeol...seriously...
-A long time ago...
-What do you mean, a long time ago?
Seriously...
Ha Ha, where are you?
-You have the badge, don't you? Be honest.
-I told you, I don't have it.
-Everyone is suspicious of you.
-Hey...
Jong Kook is planning on ousting you right now.
What do you want to do?
You want me to pretend to work with him,
and then turn on him? What do you want?
Hey...even though I'll be out once Jong Kook
rips off my name tag, let's meet up for now.
Let's meet up and talk.
I'm in room 310. Come to room 310.
Okay.
I'll start showing you now
what an awful jerk I am.
Hello? Jae Suk said he's on the 2nd floor
and that he wants to meet?
No, Jae Suk is going to be coming to
room 310. So come to room 310.
-He's coming to room 310?
-Yes.
[First gathering up all the Running Man
members in one location]
Hello?
Where are you?
They're all coming to room 310,
so come to room 311. Okay?
They're going to be in room 310,
so come to room 311.
Okay...
[Carrying out the plan!]
[Soon...the gold badge will be in my hands]
When I still just think about it...
You and your suspicion...
-Do you see how he is?
-I know...
-Did you come alone? Where's Suk Jin?
-Yeah, I'm alone. Suk Jin's gone.
-He disappeared from being chased.
-Show it to him.
-Don't just trust Suk Jin.
-It's not like that...
[They're trying to put Big-nosed brother
under a suspicious light]
[Even Kwang Soo is laying up
false traps from jail]
He sent that to me too.
-Kwang Soo's just doing that for nothing.
-From jail?
Then what do we do?
-What do we do?
-Jae Suk...
What do you mean, what do we do?
You old man...
[Spy Ha Ha has marked Jae Suk
as his mark for now]
-What do you take that text for, you...
-Where are you hiding it?
-I didn't think it was any big deal.
-It was tough to bring him here.
[Gold badge holder,
Yoo-ruce Willis in danger!]
-Okay.
-It was hard bringing him all the way here.
Stand up! What are you doing?
-Then...before you oust me...
-Say it.
-Let me get a drink of water first.
-What did you say?
Drink it when you get to jail.
The water in jail is the coldest.
And if you have the gold badge,
then join forces with us!
-We'll become your bodyguards.
-Don't worry about it.
-You have it, don't you?
-I really don't have the gold badge.
-You really don't have it?
-I don't have it.
Put your hands down here then.
Lean against the table.
[First searching Jae Suk out of suspicion]
Seriously...
[The gold badge is securely hidden
underneath the mike belt]
-The shoes. Search the shoes.
-Take off your shoes.
This is really degrading.
[I have to get away from this danger!]
Wait!
[Spy Ha Ha's name tag?]
[Yoo-ruce Willis eliminates
Ha Ha's name tag as fast as lightning!]
I'm sorry. What the heck?
I thought it would be in his shoes...
[Ha Ha-Out! Ha Ha-Out!]
Ha Ha-Out! Ha Ha-Out!
[...What the heck?]
[Ha Ha who called us out here
got himself ousted?]
[Out of utter ridiculousness,
dissolving into laughter...]
I'll go eliminate Jong Kook's name tag.
[Did Impala just say that
he's going to oust Jong Kook?]
-Why do you keep running away alone?
-You really are being strange today.
-Sit down here for a moment.
-Why? Why?
Why do you keep running around on your own?
[Just wait until you come out...!]
I'll stand over here.
Then one of us definitely has the gold badge.
-Why are you suddenly talking like that?
-Isn't that right though?
-I don't think it's him.
-I know it's not you.
No, I'm not! Hurry up and grab him!
-No! Hurry up and grab him!
-It may not be me either!
-Grab him! Grab him!
-Listen to me!
-Wait. Listen to me carefully.
-What? What?
-What is it?
-If by any chance, I don't have the badge...
-Then Jong Kook will be the end of you.
-No! No!
[Mr. Capable pushing on like a crazy man]
[Big-nosed brother attacks
Jong Kook like he had stated]
That was good! Suk Jin, you did good.
[Mr. Capable, who almost got ousted]
[Huh? That's...]
-It's him!
-Seriously?
If I'm not the one...if I'm not the one...
Jong Kook is going to end you.
-Suk Jin...
-What?
-I'll give you the win today.
-Really?
-Promise.
-Okay. I just need to oust him?
-Yeah, do it.
-Okay.
[Just...]
[What is going on...]
[What the...!]
-I just need to oust him, right?
-Okay. Do it.
[Big-nosed brother bought by
the promise of a win!]
You really can betray me,
I'm telling you that you can.
-Put everything into it! Hurry! Rip it off!
-Okay, I got it!
Hurry! Rip it!
[Ah...didn't even get to shoot it]
He even had a water gun.
I was wondering what he was holding.
[So disappointing...]
-You're in big trouble now.
-Why?
Why am I in big trouble?
[From Big-nosed brother's reed-like play...]
[...the war surrounding
the gold badge enters a new phase.]
-You have something, don't you?
-Yeah, I do.
So you had it all along!
Check it over here. Suk Jin...
Yeah...it's not here. Where is it?
It's not there. Where is it?
You have it.
-Me?
-If you have it, seriously...
-Here it is.
-It was you?!
[The gold badge is found on Suk Jin!]
[Bewildered]
I had no idea!
-What the heck is this?
-You were lying to us?
So even the person who has it
doesn't know that they have it?
-This is really disappointing...
-I seriously had no idea.
This really is so disappointing.
After we even talked earlier...
-Since you have it now, you're in big trouble.
-Why? Why?
-What do you mean, why?
-That's the power there.
Jong Kook...Jong Kook is going to
go crazy now trying to oust you.
Jong Kook doesn't know.
-What do you mean, he doesn't know?
-Don't you have to give this to him too?
And Suk Jin...you can only shoot this once.
[Giving him the water gun that can
only be shot once.]
Shin Young...
Think about this. It's strange...
This is strange...
Someone should have it.
Ji Suk Jin didn't have it
when we searched him.
Then where is it?
If they all don't have it?
Do you have it?
-Then one of us two have it?
-Are you sure it's not you?
[Finally...the chase team is starting to
suspect one another!]
...We can just go down
to the press conference.
You think I'd just keep
holding you like this?
And now we're starting to suspect
each other in this situation.
The situation is awkward now...
It's too well-known now
that you have the gun.
Since it's too well-known that
you have the gun, give it to me for now.
-Why?
-Give it to me.
Why? How can you take the gun from me now?
Since it's too well-known that
you have the gun now...
-They all know it now anyways...
-No, show them that you don't have the gun...
And you can go talk to Jong Kook.
-Are you not trusting me right now?
-No, it's not that!
But you're taking the gun from me
when we're at the end...
No, it's because it's become too
well-known that you have the gun.
Think about it.
Let's say that I go talk to Jong Kook.
Then he'll think that you're going to come up
and shoot him while he's talking to me...
So he's never going to
give us that opportunity.
So I'll either shoot him with the gun,
or tear off his name tag. Understand?
[Will this change in plans work?]
He said a change in plans...
'I'll take all the responsibility...'
If he takes all the responsibility,
he'll oust everyone...
And he'll take the victory.
Couldn't that be what he meant?
[Oust everyone,
and go to the press conference alone?]
[Just what could he be thinking?]
[No one saw that, right?]
[Sang Joong trying to face Jong Kook while
hiding the fact that he has the water gun.]
I bet he's hiding somewhere
planning something.
[Kim Jong Kook-Out! Kim Jong Kook-Out!]
So...ultimately, Jong Kook's been ousted?
[He was preparing for the showdown...]
How did Jong Kook get ousted?
Who shot him?
[Shin Young not knowing the situation either]
Something tells me that
Sang Joong shot him.
[So Sang Joong ousted Jong Kook...]
That's good that it happened.
I got rid of him without
having to get my hands dirty.
-Suk Jin, wait! I don't have anything.
-Come here. Are you alone?
[Shin Young running into
Big-nosed brother, the lone survivor]
-Trust me, and come here.
-What happened to Jong Kook?
I ousted him.
I shot him with the water gun.
[Ultimately, it was him...!]
[Just a little while ago]
You need to keep it hidden.
Put it in your pocket quickly.
[Just then!]
[With the water gun
that can only be shot once!]
[Mr. Capable-Out!]
[Big-nosed brother's gigantic hunt!]
I'll make you the winner today.
Seriously.
As long as we can oust
Sang Joong together.
Sang Joong came to me just now
and took the water gun from me.
Seriously? That's not right! He's a man!
-Does that even make sense?
-It doesn't matter if you're a man or a woman!
I'm telling you this now...
If we can oust Sang Joong, you'll win.
I'll seriously have you be the winner.
[Now the gold badge is definitely on Suk Jin!]
Here he comes!
Run away!
[It is a priority to escape
from Sang Joong who has the water gun!]
Did he see us coming in here?
Did he see us?
[With a spot on dead instinct]
[Sang Joong finding them
hiding in the same room]
-Suk Jin...you really...
-Wait...
You can't stay in there forever.
There's not much time left
until the press conference.
We can either go down
to the press conference together...
And split it 3 ways...
Or one person take it all...
Sang Joong...
[Fine...without the need to go at it,
this water gun will just...]
Sang Joong...
[An imminent confrontation!]
[Sang Joong's name tag!]
[A surprise attack sprang on by his Aide!]
[This was an ambush plan
put together with the Big-nosed brother?]
You really scared me!
Sang Joong, sorry.
I'm so sorry!
I guess I don't know much about this game.
[Shin Young...
I had no idea that you'd betray me...]
[Kim Sang Joong-Out! Kim Sang Joong-Out!]
-Please come with me.
-I'm sorry. I'm so sorry!
Wow...Shin Young...
[5 minutes before the press conference.
5 minutes before the press conference]
-You have to search him.
-Yes, we do.
-You have to search to see if he has the gold.
-I'm going to do that.
-I'm really a big fan of yours.
-I'm a fan of yours too.
-Shin Young...you know something?
-What?
-That I can tear the tag off a woman?
-Yes, I do know that.
-So you've heard?
-Yes, I've heard.
Do you know who ousted Han Ji Min?
I was the one who ripped off her name tag.
I'm sorry...for having to do this.
This really is my first time too...
But Running Man...
-The reason why I...
-I knew it!
-See? I knew this would happen!
-I had it.
-I think I'm going to have to win today.
-I knew this was going to happen.
I came on here to win!
[Top star, or an actress...
Big-nosed brother attacking without mercy!]
Who was the one that got you here?
Whether it be in the drama, or here,
Shin Young...
-Then Shin Young really did it?
-Suk Jin would really rip off her tag though.
[Shin Young vs. Suk Jin
The ultimate showdown!]
[Big-nosed brother not able to easily
show off his back due to Shin Young's gun!]
Why are you so strong? Wait!
Wait!
[Throwing down the water gun...]
[And going for his name tag?!]
[10 seconds before the press conference]
-You feel unjust, right?
-Yes. Totally.
-You're angry, right?
-Yes!
When you haven't done anything wrong...
when you've worked so hard...
Do you want to become
a righteous Running Man?
-Yes.
I'll make that happen!
[That's the infamous phrase from The Chaser]
Become my friend.
-Isn't that a line from the script?
-Running Man...
Where's the gold badge?
[Ultimately, Jang Shin Young is the winner!]
[Next week's preview]
Subtitles by DramaFever
Kwang Soo! You're the main character!
[Running Man's unprecedented special!
The 7 name tags!]
I will protect you.
[Who's going to protect who?
The worst male lead in history]
You said you were going to protect me today.
[Just who will be the ultimate lead
in this cruel romantic comedy?]