The winner is Gary!
A trip to Europe.
What do you know?
Gary knows it.
-No. -It seems empty.
We're missing one person.
Excuse me, you were very satisfied with last week's program weren't you?
Suk Jin Hyung kept smiling so wide that it reveals his teeth this morning.
Did you see his expression when he was tearing the name tags?
He's like someone furious.
He furiously tore off the name tags!
That feeling is no joke!
I think you will replay it over ten times.
Look at Jong Kook and Ji Hyo's name tags, they got the special detective name tags.
-Today is the day that Gary returns right? -Where's Gary?
Yes.
Later, Gary will be coming out from that direction.
Gary will surely bring something.
-These are the postcards that Gary sent back from Europe. -Postcards?
Hyung-nim, the place is filled with peace and solitude.
Jea Suk hyung-nim, this place is filled with peace and solitude.
Sometimes, it gets busy. I'm experiencing many emotions.
Hello! I'm a Europer! Europer!
I'm so excited to go to Europe that my nose turned red. Ah, seriously.
After taking a nap.
You won't say "The power to control the space" and I'm back to Korea, right?
It's not a joke right?
Finally, my freedom in Europe, begins now.
This person here, taking up the role of a tour guide today, Germany's tourism personnel.
Soren.
-How old are you? -I'm 45.
Hyung!
-Frank sausage? -This is Frankfurt's typical sausage.
Wow!The pig trotters is so tender!
This is about Romerberg's history. It's the heart of the Frankfurt city.
It has medieval architecture which attracts tourists with its unique scenery.
-Hello. -Running Man!
-Yes. How do you know? Where are you from? -I'm from China.
China? Glad to meet you. 1,2,3 dim sum.
-Wow! Thank you! Thank you! -Yeah, you're welcome.
This is a proud moment of being a Running Man.
Oh! Crow!
There, there.
Something good is going to happen today.
The crow flies, Kang Gary is here.
ObiGaerak.
Even the trees are beautiful.
What a busy schedule. Myeok PDnim.
Seriously, what a lightning speed holiday.
After arriving at Frankfurt only 24 hours ago, I have arrived at London.
If Germany has Frank sausages, England has Fish and Chips.
Because I only can see it once, I have to look around quickly.
Nice.
It says that if there is someone crossing the street here, vehicles would stop automatically.
It is a famous place in London.
The car did not stop!
I must catch the right timing and cross quickly.
What am I supposed to do here?!
I'm Gary!
Clown Kang Gary.
Good job.
Don't use the tone like as if you are training a dog!
Geraid?
Can't you let me enjoy a proper holiday?
Wow! So cool!
Running Man that is going global.
In front of the bridge, I will build a new Running Man history.
Are you okay?
One person coughing, the other person has nightmares.
What are you going to do about this?
But I'm totally fine?
I feel like my soul has already flown away.
Wow Eiffel Tower!
Because of the fog at night, I can't see the top!
I'm only able to see only it once but there is the fog.
Wow!
Okay 1,2,3!
Everybody, take a look at the Eiffel Tower!
What is this? This is only Kang Gary!
What is this! Look at my face. This looks like a Christmas tree.
An Eiffel Tower without a tower tip.
It looks like a beautiful moment, but I have no idea what are they talking about.
Let's break up.
That's right, I've think about it and it is a good day for breaking up.
The first time we met was at the Eiffel Tower, right?
Let's break up here. We had good time.
Why is there nobody?
I'm not allowed to move so I'm feeling nervous.
Oh! Similar! Oh! Similar!
Oh, it's here. In the postcard. Wow
This are the postcards Gary sent from Europe.
-Wow. -Isn't this the Louvre Museum in Paris?
To Jae Suk a.k.a Yoo hyuk hyungnim. This place is filled with peace and solitude.
Sometimes, it gets busy. I'm experiencing many emotions...
-What are you doing? -That's how Gary would write this.
-But I haven't seen any Europeans wearing green. -Green!
-Why are you all green? -Even the shoes are green!
That's really too much! You might as well change your cap to green.
You're driving me crazy!
And there is no sight of Europeans wearing green.
-"So now..." Hmm? -It's an English acronym.
-This, this. -"Lollol".
"In 2012, I'll have even more 'fighting' moments."
"Nurture me so I can get the Deasang."
Me? Nurturing? It's so funny.
"I love you! Kang Gary"
"The Monday Couple." It's for Ji Hyo.
"The Seine River. The Seine River glitters like your eyes."
Let's have a look, let's look at the Seine River.
-Ji Hyo, Let's have a look at the Seine River. -No, oppa.
"The Eiffel Tower's very high, just like how I can't reach your heart."
"That's why my heart has been stolen away a blue-eyed ladies. Lollol."
It's becoming shorter, ah?
"Let's have even more 'fighting' moments in 2012."
"From a cafe in Montmartre, Monday Couple's Kang Gary"
"Monday Couple", oh my god.
-Hey, it's becoming shorter now. -It's so obvious.
-This, this is shorter, this one. Look. -Right.
Right? These are so shorter.
This is a result of being tried while writing.
"Ha Dong Hoon."
"This place is so beautiful, it's seriously driving me crazy."
"Hey! I love you."
Hey, if this is how you do it, I'm tearing it up!
An autograph.
-Jeez, what's this? -An autograph.
-No, this is really too much. -"Be happy."
He told you to be happy.
-Be happy, he wants you to be happy. Gary wants you to be happy.
-This is too much. -Kwang Soo, be happy.
-I'm not touched. -No, didn't he tell you to be happy? Be happy.
Though it's like this now, when we look at this ten years later we'll be extremely touched.
Of course. Hey, how rare is this...
-What's so touching about this? -Hey, he said he loves me.
What are you doing?
-What are you doing? -Welcome, welcome.
I just came back and you give me this.
This, isn't this too much?
It feels so foreign? Our Korea?
No presents?
Of course there are presents.
Needless to say, I have presents for the members.
-Hello. -I just returned from Europe.
Yes.
Today's race, will start when Gary enters the country.
-Immediately? -Ok, bring the bags in.
What's that?
Oh, one for each.
Ok, inside these bags today, are extremely important tools for today's race.
Starting from now, everyone will take a bag.
-Randomly? -Beacuse you can't open them.
-Please think carefully before taking it. -Are they different?
-Didn't he tell you to 'think through it carefully'? -I don't know, aigoo!
-I've picked mine. -Kook Jong!
-These are all different right, the contents? -They should be different
-Oh, mine is so heavy. -Mine too.
-Mine's extremely heavy. -Everyone's all the same?
-Mine's heavy. -What does Gary do today?
-Oh, it's Kang Gary! -Oh, Kang Gary!
Gary hyung!
Hey, he doesn't look like came back from Europe?
Gary!
He doesn't look like he came back from Europe?
Oh, Gary!
Lollol!
Oh, it's really the Lollols?
Oh, Lollols.
It's really thank to the Lollols that I had a good trip.
Yes, danke schoen.
-What's happening there? -What's going on?
It's the Lollols, the Lollols.
It's because of them that Gary hyung could go on his trip.
What are you doing here?
Are you really here to meet me? Let's go.
-Why are you in formal wear? -Gary!
-Gary hyung! Gary!
Why are you doing?
-Oh, what's all this? -Why are you doing this, why are you doing this?
-What,why are you doing this? -What, what?
-Gary! -Why are you taking my bag?
My bag, Lollol! Lollol! Lollol!
Why are you taking my bag? My bag, Lollol!
Hey, what's going on?
-What's this? -Where are they taking him?
-What are they doing? -What's going on?
-What? -You're not bringing me along?
-A trip to Europe! -We can't go together.
Oh, Lollols. We'll go to Jeju island to play next time.
Oh, what's this, what are you doing?
No, just...Myeok PD, please stop coming near me.
Where are you taking me?
Inside Gary's stolen backpack is a precious treasure from Europe,
-A treasure? -Hey, we have to find the bag.
What's going to happen again today? It's making us nervous.
Where did Gary oppa go?
Ok, we'll start giving you the mission now.
Before we give you the mission, we'll be confiscating your handphones.
Why, why?
My mom will call me. It won't do.
Why?
Jeez, they're taking everything away.
Today's mission is 'Gary knows'.
-'Gary knows'? -'Gary knows'?
The item inside everyone's bags is a question card about episodes during Gary's trip.
Fill in the answers for those questions to find out the location of the mission backpack.
How did he do so many things in Europe?
Gary ate blank in Germany.
Gary ate a, blank sausage in Germany.
Hey, It says 'three' here.
I already know this one.
Gary received the 'Find Gerald mission' at Trafaigar Square.
Why is there an answer here?
-You have tracking devices in the bag... -Yes.
In the device, you can see the locations of hints for the questions.
Once someone finds a hint, the indicator will disappear.
We're at Incheon Airport, right?
Hey, what's this?
Central Park.
Where we went the other time?
Where we have the Spy special.
What's with the key?
All items in your bag are important so please keep them well.
Oh, it's Songdo.
What did Gary ate in Europe?
What's the key for too?
We may have to unlock a door somewhere.
'Gary knows'. Then, I should find Gary hyung?
Gary hyung, hang in there. I'll save you!
Where are you taking me?
Is it here?
-Gary. -Hyung.
-What are you doing? -You found me?
Hey, what's going on?
-Hyung, I'm here to look for my bag. -Why are you here?
I don't know. I was dragged here, by Myeok PD.
-Gary. -Yes, hyung.
You...
-Hey. -Hyung,why are you here, hyung?
I need your help with today's theme. Today is "Gary knows".
-What's that? -You know all these things.
Gary boarded the Eurostar at blank, that set off at blank pm. Do you know?
I just followed them so I don't know. You know me, hyung.
Hey, so what did you eat in Germany?
In Germany?
-There were so many. -What exactly did you eat?
Hey, it's great.
Germany's sausages are very famous right, their sausages?
Frankfurt. Frank sausages.
Frank sausages!
I'm starting to understand Europe now.
Wow, where is this? It has the smell of Germany.
Food, Frankfurt food.
Sausages!
Oh, sausages!
This is Frankfurt's traditional wine, apple wine.
Korean culture.
Two hands.
-Thank you. You're welcome.
There's so many different meats.
This is schweinshaxe.
Schweinshaxe is German style pig knuckle.
Do I just eat it like this?
Wow, this is good. The sauce...
Wow, the German pig trotter,very tender.
-What is it called again? -Schweinshaxe.
Schweinshaxe!
Ah.
Why is it so delicious?
What did you eat in Germany?
Germany, right?
I ate a lot! I ate romance!
Frankfurt...sausages? Germany is famous for their sausages.
-Beer? -I ate romance, romance.
-Ah, you ate romance? -Why are you asking me all this?
There are the questions we have to ask you.
Am I not supposed to tell you so easily then?
It's not like that, you can just tell me.
-I have to go find my bag. -Where did you go to find Gerard? England?
-Why are you interrogating me,hyungnim! -I'm not interrogating you!
I went there to enjoy freedom!
I'm asking because you went to Europe, give me some hints.
Oh! It's Gary hyung!
It's "Gary knows", rignt?
-Just give me one answer. -I didn't just eat one or two things in Germany.
-Right. -So let me look at the question.
Hyung!
Why are you all looking for me, I need to find my bag!
Hyung I'm done for if I can't find my bag.
-Hold on. -It's okay.
Walt! This kind of disorder would nerver happen in Europe.
But Hyung...
Why! Don't touch me!
Okay, let's find a hint first.
After finding the tapes, the hint should be in the tape.
After finding the tapes and play in with the video player, I will find the answers to these.
It's Avantar, Avantar!
Gary ate an Avatar in Germany?
Kwang Soo!
Hyung do you have the player?
How are you going to finish this by yourself if you can't even do this.
Why are you like this?
What are you doing?
Is that all?
The real hints have the videos of Gary's Europe travels.
There are fakers too?
Ah, this...
I was just about to say... It's the first time I've worded well with hyung.
So there are a lot of videos, but only one is real.
Fake.
Just tell me one answer, just one. So that I can complete the sentence.
If I tell you, I wouldn't be penalized would I?
You won't, why would you?
Hey, Sherlock. What are you up to?
Gary.
Hyung, I went to Shamp-Elysees!
It's Champ-Elysees, not Shamp-Elysees!
Champ-Elysees!
I will continue walking on the path of freedom.
Do not stop this wanderer's footsteps!
-Gary, come over here. -I'm very sleepy right now!
-I flew for 20 hours. -Are you doing this again?
Gary, you just have to fill it out. This is your homework.
-I want to go home! -Hurry up and read it.
I haven't even called my mom yet! -What did you eat in Germany?
Guten Tag! Guten Tag!
Guten Tag! Guten Morgen!
Danke!
Fine, let's do it this way.
Everybody seems to be very curious about my trip to Europe.
-So I will answer one question per person. -Okay I understand I'll ask first since I came first.
Please wait. Hay-Hay, please wait a moment.
Tell me the answer to this one.
Hyung, about this one...
Oh, St. Pancras Station.
Oh, here?
-What was it? -St. Pancras Station.
-Is this a nice station? -Uhm, what are we taking to get to Paris?
-Euro train. -Eurostar.
Eurostar. We board it from there.
St. Pancras Station?
So, this place is called...
This is... What station did you say this was again?
-In order to go to Paris... -St...
You can get on the Eurostar here.
You can go to Paris by taking the Eurostar here.
-St. Pancras Station. -St. Pancras.
Crass?Cross?
-Cras. -It is St. Pancras Station.
Oh, there. St. Pancras.
-Here? -Carriage 1.
-Where is the carriage number written? -It is written here.
In our country. It's usually written here? On the train.
We get in now?
-My memory is blurry. -Just do it.
I think it was 1:03pm.
You didn't use the KTX right?
I'm not sure. I'm a Europer.
Then, this question. What did you eat there?
I ate sausages in Germany.
And I ate it with romance.
Hay- Hay.
Hyungnim, I love you.
-Just hear about my trip to Europe. -He heard it too.
He didn't hear it.
-You heard what he ate? -No, I didn't.
-You obviously heard it. -Korean cuisines?
-I ate sea-snails, sea-snails. -The one who changes my mood.
The one who always ignores me.
Hyung, hyung.
Please do not stop the wanderer's footsteps.
The place where you took Gary Potter picture.
Gary Potter. Where was it?
-Is King Cross far? -No.
It's right there.
Is this King's Cross street?
Where?
What's this?
Platform numbers should not have fractions, right?
This only exists in Harry Potter. Platform 9 and 3/4.
I need to go from there?
I'm going. Don't look for me.
I wondered why you bought the glasses...
Did you buy it for me?
It doesn't fit me.
Why didn't you buy something that matches me.
Gary Potter will now take Eurostar to Paris.
Lollol, lollol!
Is that enough?
Harry Potter went from here. But I'm Gary Potter so I go from here.
It's just a prop. It won't go in.
Push it hard.
Lollol!
Subway station.
Really? How about this?
Eurostar, isn't that Tevez?
-Tevez is a France train. -It's T.G.V.
-TGV? --It's T.G.V.
Tevez is Park Ji Sung's friend, right?
Looks like I have to go to Europe again.
Huh? What's this. Isn't that Bong Sun?
What is this?
Bong Sun, how have you been.
Just now Jong Kook...
How are we supposed to find this?
It surprised me.
How do we find it when it's hidden there.
Oh! This is it!
It's Gary.
Is this King's Cross?
It won't move. It's just a prop.
Lollol!
King's Cross.
Wow.. This... I almost fell into a maze if not for this.
There shouldn't be anything here, right?
Oh, there's one here.
Got it!
How can it be found when it's hidden here.
Eurostar...
-Where's the carriage number? -Here.
Our country's number is on here, on the carriage.
Eurostar?
What time did it leave in the afternoon?
It's 2 in afternoon.
Shouldn't there be more than one hint?
Is it a hint?
Is this a hint?
What is this?
It's a newspaper.
What?
Kang Gary!
What??
Nice.
I'm so sleepy.
Kang Gary!
-Ah Ji Hyo, can I rest for awhile? -Kang Gary!
Now is not the time to sleep.
Hurry up and come out.
Kang Gary!
Kang Gary hurry up and tell me what you know.
-Are you sleepy? -I'm going crazy.
I'm really sleepy.
-He can't talk properly now. -Can you find my bag?
Oppa, before I find your bag shouldn't you tell me something?
-Alright, I'll tell you what you want to know. -What did you eat in Europe?
Meals.
Breakfast, Lunch, Dinner.
And romance.
-This game doesn't seem to be related to me. Hurry up and find my bag. -Oppa, but what is this?
This is the newspaper I read.
-Oppa you read this? -Yeah, the economics column and...
There was a lot of information.
It's the newspaper that I read when I was in Germany.
-It's the most famous in Germany. -So, where did you meet Mr.Gerald?
Just tell me that.
I met him in the UK.
I have to quickly view everything. Because it's my only chance.
Because it's my first and last time, I have to quickly view everything.
It's the black structure in front.
I saw it! I quickly saw it!
Everything seems to be happening in a very fast speed.
The England's sausage and beef tongue and
You mean Germany?
Oh, Germany.
Look! I'm all confused now!
Because the countries have been changing every 12 hours!
Wow, this is so great!
Gerald?
Can't you just let me tour around here freely?
IS Gerald the name of a young man or an old man?
There are a lot of people with this name in UK.
A lot of people named Gerald?
Hello.
Are you Korean?
Running Man.
Hello.
Wow. The popularity of Running Man carries on to the UK too.
This is really no joke!
Excuse me. Excuse me.
Are you Gerrald? Gerrald?
You name is Gerald?
-No, he's David. -David?
Sorry.
Excuse me,sir.
Are you Gerrald? You name is Gerald?
No no.
Wrong person.
Ah, Gerald
Ah Mr.Gerald... I mean, even if we say there are a lot of "Min Seok's" in Korea.
How are you supposed to find a "Min Seok"?!
Gerald!
Trafalgar!
Trafalgar?
8th Street.
8th Street!
London's 5th Street, 6th Street, 7th Street... is like Euljio's 4th Street, 3rd Street.
I think there's Tra 1st Street, 2nd Street, 3rd Street.
The 8th Street.
Why are you lying?
I'm not lying. It's true.
Is England like Korea? Why would they name it "8th Street"?
Isn't there something like block1, block 2 or something?
Then shouldn't 8th Street be said in English? Why would they use "8th Street" (in Korean)?
Tra Eight Street!
What?
Anyway Ji Hyo, can you help me to find my backpack?
-Ok, I'll find your bag for you. -Seriously.
You follow me today. Come here.
But I want to sleep.
I know. The treasure is in Oppa's bag pack.
-I will find it for you as fast as I can. -Don't tell the others that I'm here they are very irritating.
All right.
-I'll look for you later. -Ok.
You are telling the truth?
Ah, I'm so sleepy!
It was a very windy day.
Dong Hoon Hyung
Dong Hoon Hyung!
Oh, HaHa hyung ran this way a little while ago.
But he's not here.
Dong Hoon Hyung!
He's like a ghost.
Has he been learning something recently?
-How did he disappear all of a sudden? -Dong Hoon Hyung!
-Oh, it's been a red light all along. -He's seriously making me go crazy.
Hey!
Where did Jae Suk Hyung go?
What happened? Where did he go?
Wasn't Jae Suk here just now?
-Ah, you surprised me! -Haha, you couldn't see me, right?
It was a perfect green camouflage.
How amazing. Your skills remain the same.
Kwang Soo,get up!
Kwang Soo,get up quickly! Get up!
-You'll freeze to death. -What are you doing?
Cold!
Why is it so cold today?
-Hyung, I heard there's a cold snap starting from today. -Excatly.
-The park is here. Come here. -Hyung.
It's not that.
But there are so many boxes.
Then you go and take a look.
Hyung!Why are you ordering me to do things as if I'm a dog!
Don't stand there blankly!
Kwang Soo!
We are the ones who search regardless of reasons.
Lee Yoo Cross!
What are you doing?
We are the Easy Brothers!
You traitor!
Then...
Show us yours.
Hyung, you found the tape, right?
You know the purpose of finding that thing?
So cold, so cold.
Are you Easy or Lee Yoo?
You created Lee Yoo brothers just like this?
That's how we are "Lee Yoo Ji"!
That's right! We are Lee Yoo Ji!
If we're together, we're...
-Lee Yoo Ji -Lee Yoo Ji
What is this? Seriously.
How could you say Lee Yoo Ji all by yourself?
The 3 of us are : Lee Yoo Ji!
-Lee Yoo Ji! -Cross!
-Lee Yoo Ji! -Cross.
How could there be a cross with three?
That's exactly how we are if we're together.
Lee! Yoo! Ji! Cross!
-You shocked me! -Why did you suddenly raise your hand up?
It's not like this.
Why did you suddenly raise your hand up? This is too childish.
-Hyung, tell me. Why are you looking for this thing? -You don't know?
Hyung, tell me the truth. You found that already right?
I'll show you what I have.
We are Lee Yoo Ji. How can I not show you?
-I'll show you. -Yes take it out and let us see.
Show me something now.
There's nothing in here!
I'm jealous of you two working together!
-What? We are just filming a show together. -Hey! What are you saying?
Why are you jealous? We are just filming a show together.
Because the both of you are together.
What are you saying?
Why are you jealous? It's not like we are filming a drama together.
-No it's not like this. -What? Hey! Kwang Soo, let's go!
We can't stay here anymore.
Ah, seriously.
It should be somewhere here.
Hyung!
Kwang Soo, it's here!
We found it.
What is inside?
Kwang Soo, we have to hide something with this.
We have to hide something with this.
He's sleeping. Hyung!
I'm dying.
Hyung! Tell me a hint quickly!
Where did you meet Mr.Gerald, hyung!
Trafalgar
What?
Trafalgar 8th Street.
Trafalgar?
It's like Euljiro's 3rd Street, 4th Street...
I've a survey card with me.
Let's quickly solve these questions and end this.
Help me find my bag.
I'll help you to find it.
Please answer the questions I ask you.
Gary ate sausages in Germany. Is that correct?
Gary received a mission to look for Gerald in Trafalgar Square. Is that correct?
-Gerald...Gerald... -Gerald. -Yes.
Where did Gary board the Eurostar from?
Eurostar... Family line...
The one moving forward... Compartment number 1...
What time in the afternoon did you depart?
-Ah, that I can't confirm. -Then think of it to confirm.
-It was from the hall... -Yes.
After exiting from the place I drank a cappuccino.
-It started to drizzle lightly. -Yes.
-We're supposed to board the train at approximately 1:30pm. -Oh! 1:30pm?
At that time it was also a little... Ah! I remember it now!
When I saw the train ticket ant that time.
I was thinking... Usually it is 2:30pm, or 3pm, or something like that.
But why is it 2:03pm?
-I wondered why it was 2:03... -Really?
-This information is just great! -Now that I remember it.
Why was it like that? If they want 2pm, put it as 2pm, If they want 1pm, put it as 1pm.
-Why is it 2.03pm? -2pm.
Ah, could it be 1 or 2 minutes?
Where can it be?
Found it!
There are so many tapes.
I really don't know which one it is exactly.
-Frankfurt? -Sausage!
This is Schweinshaxe.
It's delicious!
There's not much time left. How is it? Is there or is there not?
Is there!Or is there not!
What are you doing this?
Who knows, they might give me a CG effect!
Kwang Soo, what CG are you still making? We must find this quickly!
Suk Jin hyung has been looking for a while but hasn't not found anything yet.
Hyung, this side has been looked through.
-Kwang Soo! -Yes hyung.
That's why you...
You clearly just passed it.
But...
You did not see anything.
You just left the clue here.
-Running there with you mouth wide open. -I was wrong.
If you were alone, you wouldn't be able to accomplish anything.
Kwang Soo, let's take a look.
This is 100 percent...
Turn on the machine.
Power.
-Login. Password:38... -There's no time for this.
Hey! Hey! Wanna die? Hey let go! Let go! Let go!
-What is this? -It is a case of hair pulling.
That could be the one.
Turn on the machine. There's no time.
-I'll give you 5 seconds. 5,4,3,4,1. -Ah hyung, why are you like this?
If you were in a movie like this you would have died. It would have exploded!
Are they all fakes?All of them.
Those that can be seen are all not real. I 've gotten so many of them already.
What do you know?
You would get into big trouble like this.
Bingo. Bingo1
Please!
Oh? What is this?
What is this?
What kind of hint is this?
Wait.
Ah, so it's like this!
Mr. Detective!
-Shall we share? -Huh?
Let's share.
No no.
-Hello. -Oh, ok.
Hyung, I've solved all of them.
Do you really know all of it? How do you know?
-I guessed them all! One by one! -Hey! Then... Dong Hoon!
You and I can go together!
Dong Hoon... Do you have the last card?
That hyung seems to have something decisive.
Do you have the last card?
What did you say?
Last card.
Last card? Why?
Without it, you won't know the final location.
-Don't tell me... -Hyung, do you have it?
The last card, hyung do you have it? Let us see it, hyung.
Don't be like that, take it out and let us have a look.
Ah, If you again it with our card, we will get a word!
It must be fitted with our card for it to work.
Of course! That's exactly it!
But the most important thing is we must work together.
From what I see, even if the hint is not correct...
Maybe we only need to know 5 and we'll be able to know the answer already.
Kwang Soo, do you have 10000 won?
Oh? Isn't that Gary?
What's this?
Hello. Hello.
-Hey Kang Gary! -Hyung!
What are you doing here?
You are alone here. Do you know how cold it is outside?
Hyung, please let me have my meal.
-Soup... Let's share the meal.
Why do you all keep chasing me like this?
Gary, no...
Hey! That enough!
I'll tell you honestly, we just found this.
-Let's solve it one by one. It seems like it should be placed here.
Eh?What is this?
Where did you go, your eyes are bloodshot.
Can you guys all leave? I'm eating right now.
-How many do you know,oppa? -Not many.
How many do you know?
I have nothing now. This is really a big issue.
What is Sauerkraut?
-What is that thing? -Sauerkraut?
-This is really my first time hearing it. -Sauerkraut?
-Kraut. -What is Sauerkraut?
This is really my first time hearing it.
Oppa, don't just write it down.
How can you just write that down? It won't do!
Why? Isn't this what you said, Sauerkraut?
This is really my first time hearing it.
Is it Germany?
What is the meaning of that in German?
Germany is really difficult.
The only one I remember is this.
3,3!
Oh, yes Mong Ji?
I couldn't remember this just now. This is 2:03pm.
I think it is row 1.
Hyung, don't run away!
Let's walk together!
Don't be like that. I already know.
Ya! Really.
Close the door,close the door.
-Sorry, Suk Jin hyung! I have no choice. -And we love you.
I knew it would be like that so I made a mark.
There is always someone out there who is better!
This is it.
Wah, I'm never going to trust all of you again.
Ji Hyo, let's look at it together.
-Ji Hyo,Ji Hyo? -Yes.
Let us see.
If Jong Kook and the rest go first, we will be finished.
He doesn't have this paper.
What makes you think that there is only one?
There is only one.
-Really? -Yes.
-There is another one. -See.
Why are you keep doing that me! Keep quiet!
Keep clam, put down your hand.
They say that there is one more, they might have taken it.
Oppa, we should hurry up.
-Oppa! -Alright, alright.
Oppa, it tore.
Give it to me first! Let's put them on the table.
-Sorry! -You are always like this.
Last time you even bit me.
You don't even get flustered.
You did not even hesitate to retaliate when it got snatched!
They're all locked, oppa.
After I snatched it, she didn't look at me and look for the door instead.
Oppa, I already know.
-We have to open up the card first. -I know, oppa. Give it to me first.
-What's going on? -It's Suk Jin oppa.
Oh, it's Suk Jin hyung.
-Hurry and take it out! -Hurry, hurry!
You can't do it without me.
-Why? -Can't do what?
-You really cannot do without me! -Why?
I...
Have this?
-We were talking... -Isn't there only one?
There are many fake ones!
Mine is real, real!
Look, what is this?
Which number of eucostar he take?
Number 1, car number 1.
I know this, hyung!
Left at 2:03pm.
That's no it. It does not matter anyway....
That is 1,2,3.
I have asked Gary oppa about this before.
No. He might not know.
It points to the exit.
We have to go out?
Good. 1,2.
Is there none containing 't'?
central park
This is Schweinshaxe.
Schweinshaxe, German style pig trotters.
-What is this? -Newspaper that Europeans read.
Ah, okay. I will read it well.
I can recognize some words.
Eurostar!
I want three of this.
What?
Wait
We should walk towards the central park.
This is not it... Central... 123?
-Central park, one place, two places. -There are three places. What to do?
-They are near each other, right? -Hyung, hyung...
Central. Central.... There is a road name...
-Kwang Soo! -Yes hyung?!
Go to central 123!
Today we will show what we hyung and dongseang can do!
-Our hyung! -My dongseang!
Is that your car? -Uh, that one in front.
What are we going there for? Are we searching?
-Jong Kook hyung is already searching there. -Kim Jong Kook is also searching.
Don't we all have keys? It has something to do with the keys.
Ah, this is really!
Where? Looks like it is racing park.
Are they car keys?
Please. Is it not this?
Seems like it's not this.
All right, go play for awhile.
Let me sleep for a little.
This is a good place! I should have gone here before.
Ji Hyo.
Let oppa sleep for a while.
I cannot live anymore, really.
Is this the time to sleep? We need to look for the bag!
Dong Hoon!
It's here.
Oh, hold on.
This way.
What's this?
Dong Hoon, let's go there.
What's that?
It's a Pye Beak hall.
It can't be here right?
It seems right! What to do?
We found it!
-We found it! -There are two locks?
So it's like that.
Hyung!
It's good we have two keys.
Perhaps, it's yours and mine. That would be too coincidental, right?
-Do you have a key? -Yes.
But, isn't this an individual game?
Oh, it works!
What? Hyung's doesn't work?
Oh!
There are different keys?
Oh, this one works.
This isn't it.
It cannot be opened right?
Doesn't work, right?
Seems like someone else has the other key.
What is this?
There is no specific hint.
I think my key can open it.
-I will try it myself. -You try to open it.
Try opening it.
Try this one.
Open it.
What about this?
I told you not to do it.
How frustrating. We have it right in front of us.
How come it cannot be unlocked?
So disappointing.
Jae Suk hyung!
What?
I got it.
What do you know?
Lee Yoo Ji!
-If you go to the 3rd floor and walk to the left, there's a treasure box. -Really?
But you need two keys.
-One of the locks can be opened by all the keys. -And so?
But the other needs a different key.
In Europe.
Is there a place like this, in Europe?
There is no such place in Europe.
There seems to be something there.
Hyung, we need to hurry before the others come.
-Hyung, we're a team right? -Of course.
It doesn't seem to be here. -What?
Kim Joog Kook must be searching for the key now.
How does he search so well?
It should not be in these kind of places.
Where is it hidden?
Maybe we have to tear off name tags?
No, it is not.
-Why are you like that towards me? -Kwang Soo.
Just curious if it's about tearing name tags.
Gary knows?
Gary knows.
Therefore Ji Hyo...
So I have to look for Kang Gary!
Perhaps someone else has the key.
-Is that so? -Maybe we should to snatch it away?
-Kwang Soo, show me your key. -I already tried it.
You cannot open it? Both of them?
But there seems to be something there.
The treasure that I lost.. Ah, why?
Perhaps someone else has the key.
-Is that so? -Maybe we should to snatch it away?
-Kwang Soo, show me your key. -I already tried it.
You cannot open it? Both of them?
But there seems to be something there.
The treasure that I lost.. Ah, why?
Ah, why?
Why are you like that? I am very tired.
Gary hyung knows it?
Hey, Lee Kwang Soo!
What are you doing?
What should I do?What should I do?
Ji Hyo, why didn't you even move?
That is mine, mine!
I found it.
How did I open it?
Why is he giving this to me?
-It is for you to bring it back to Korea safely. -For me to bring back to Korea safely?
-A souvenir from France to be brought back. -For me?
Mercl.
-Did Gary hyung know about it? -I didn't know!
If I knew I would...
I am really very tried.