[The final showdown]
[You can blame me.]
[What he wants...]
[There's just one thing that he wants]
[On that day two years ago... the insult...]
[Okay... the game starts now.]
[Meticulously planned and thought out...]
[The hunter's trap!]
[Tapping all the Running Man!]
[The final showdown]
[Just who will be the victor?]
[One cloudy day in October...]
Subtitles by DramaFever
Hello.
What is this? The Monday couple?
What is this couple thing about?
You're obstructing the sign.
Hi, Suk Jin...
- We're... pairing off today.
- Pairing off?
Would it be okay for me to have
some expectations today?
Who? Yang Jung Ah?
- Jung Ah...
- Yang Jung Ah...
Does he think he's going to the sauna?
Why is he in just a shirt?
Isn't he even cold?
[The manly man, Kkuk arrives.]
Why do you have the shirt open like that
when it's so windy out today?
- What the heck is that?
- Hey...
- What are you doing?
- Well, I...
What are you doing?
- I didn't know it would do that!
- Why did you pull on my shirt?
Why are you wearing a shirt
with snaps?
[Unhappy with how he flaunts
his body even in this chilly weather.]
Can't you tell by looking at the shirt
how it snaps? You shouldn't have pulled...
Why aren't you even wearing
any socks?
I do have socks on.
They're just not showing.
What are you doing?
Start dressing appropriately.
Then are we...
are we being paired off today?
- Yeah!
- Seriously?
Hello, brothers!
Wow... it's really windy!
It's really windy.
[Greeting everyone with their eyes shut
tight against the fiercely strong wind.]
What do you mean, good morning?
It's three o'clock in the afternoon.
Why isn't Gary here? Kang Gary!
- Where are you?
- I'm not going anywhere!
[This man is a trouble maker.]
- No more... seriously, no more!
- Why are you trying to scare us?
- Enough...
- What's going on here?
[Today's mission is 'Pairs'-
I want to become Monday Couple too.]
The wind is blowing so hard that it's
changing the part in my hair.
- Please tell us quickly.
- Tell us what's going on.
Starting with Yoo Jae Suk down to Kwang Soo,
you'll become males number one through six.
I've seen this show on TV!
As for the details,
once the lady participants arrive...
- Women participants?
- Women, women, women...
Why are you getting all excited
when you have Moon Geun Young?
I think someone's here.
There's a car pulling up.
I wonder who's going to get out?
- Who is it?
- Who could it be?
[Black cars are starting to
pull up one by one.]
- Is that Ji Hyo's car?
- I'm sure she'll be paired up with Gary.
Come on, I doubt it.
All the lady participants have arrived.
Wait... shouldn't there be six ladies?
Do you think only one person
is getting paired up?
- Do you think it's a girl group?
- You think they'll all get out together?
Wait... someone's about to get out.
[Just who could it be?]
[Blank Ji]
- It's Ji Hyo!
- Ji Hyo? It's just Ji Hyo.
[Ji Hyo looking especially beautiful today.]
Why is she wearing heels?
- Ji Hyo, why are you looking so pretty today?
- Why are you looking so skinny?
You have something planned for today,
don't you?
- What do mean, something planned?
- I think you've gotten prettier.
[Everyone acting a little awkward
over how pretty Ji Hyo looks today.]
With you clubbing lately...
I don't know if it's because you've been
clubbing, but you've gotten prettier lately.
[Becoming beautiful for her club outings?]
[Immediately picking up the club vibe.]
One last lady participant is waiting.
- What did you say? Last?
- What do you mean, last?
[There are six men,
but already down to the last lady?]
We're getting paired off,
so there should be five more.
She's getting off!
[The car door opens...]
[The one who will protect even the wolf...
Park Bo Young.]
Bo Young!
Hello!
You can't block the camera
just because Bo Young is here!
Hello!
- Bo Young, have you been well?
- Yes, hello!
- It really has been a long time!
- Hey... wolf girl!
- Hello.
- Hi, it's good to see you.
- Bo Young!
- Yes, it's good to see you.
Bo Young... Bo Young!
[Bo Young too preoccupied with
making sure to greet everyone.]
Were you the only one in there?
There's no one else in that car?
- No, it was just me.
- But we need five more...
- Don't say things like that!
- There should be four more in there!
Shouldn't we just be happy
to have Bo Young here?
How is this 'Pairs'?
- You seem disappointed.
- There should be four more ladies!
You seem really disappointed...
- There's another car over there!
- That car is pulling out.
[Giraffe putting on his debonair act.]
- Don't do things like that!
- What are you doing?
Why are you reacting like this?
[Getting criticized from trying to act cool.]
If you're going to take it off,
take it all off!
[Forcing him... to strip?]
Don't look!
[Giraffe exposing his bust.]
[Using his leopard print scarf in a rush...]
[Chief of the Giraffe tribe?]
You really took my clothes off!
Kwang Soo, here...
- Stop acting like you're cool!
- Don't act like you're cool!
[Being humiliated from trying to
act debonair.]
[Since everyone is here...]
I will explain today's mission to you.
As I have told you earlier,
today's mission is
'Pairs- I want to become Monday Couple too'.
Those who win first place for each mission,
will be given the opportunity for a date.
And after the date goes well,
and you two have become friendly
if the male is chosen as a partner at
the final location, then you win.
Winning the chances at a date by
winning each mission
gives you that much better chance
at becoming the final couple.
But with Ji Hyo... it's pretty much already
decided who her partner is going to be.
So it's not fair to do it like that.
- Am I going to win today?
- Seriously...
You have no idea if
I'm going to pick you or not.
What a joke. I know you're
reminiscing about us right now.
How would you know if I am or not?
You lost weight so that
you could look better for me.
[The tight relationship between the two
even with the change in season.]
Before we get started on the missions,
why don't you introduce yourselves first?
Starting with Male number one,
please introduce yourself.
And if there are things you two are curious
about each other, you may ask questions.
[Male number one - Yoo Jae Suk]
Hello. I work at a broadcasting company,
and my name is Yoo Jae Suk.
I'm in the field of broadcasting...
and it's been about 20 years
since I've first made my appearance.
Then how old does that make you?
I got started in this field
when I was ten years old.
I'm not really that old, and I...
Then considering your age,
you have such an old looking face.
- Lady number two...
- I'm finished. Male number two, please?
- Will you please stop?
- Male number two please.
[Male number one vs. Lady number two.
A mental battle right from the start.]
We're all set!
Number two, please step up!
- Number two...
- What a joke!
Seriously... what a joke!
[Male number two with the big nose.]
- I'm Male number two.
- How old are you?
Um... I'm 47 years old.
There's only three years
of difference with my Mom...
Isn't your mother younger?
She's younger than him, right?
- No, my mother is 50...
- She's 50 years old?
If you do the seven degrees of separation,
she's probably someone I know very well.
Anyways, I hope to make
some nice memories today...
[Prized male, Male number three.]
It's Moon Geun Young's boyfriend!
Oh, that's right... I saw that last week...
What are you doing? Seriously...
He's already forgotten her.
It's only been a week...
[Very seriously starting to
introduce himself.]
He's rumored to be linked to
Yoon Eun Hye and Moon Geun Young!
[Male number one specializing in
having multiple relationships?]
Actually, I'm a singer.
So the title for my current album is
'All the men are alike'.
But I'm not that kind of a man,
I'm a man of sincerity.
On this show, Running Man,
there are a lot of games that we play.
I would like to become your partner
so that I can win all the games for you.
And Male number three...
I think his shirt is too small for him.
- It bothers me.
- Does it?
I can see huge chunk of skin
on his chest.
Does it...
He says to Ji Hyo, 'Does it'?
Why are you being so polite?
You want to become a couple that badly?
I'm just wearing it for a moment
because it's cold outside.
I will... change out of it later.
Please step back into your spot!
Why are you walking like that?
Hello. I'm...
I'm... a flake.
[Male number four is a flake?]
My specialty is being a trouble maker.
And to be honest...
I want to cause some trouble today.
Who is it?
Who do you have your eye on?
Number two...
[Male number four in the clear?]
Seriously... next person, please.
Congratulations on your
upcoming wedding!
[Male number five
is facing his upcoming wedding.]
And today is his fiancé's birthday!
[And on top of that, the day
of the recording is her birthday!]
[Male number five, please be happy.]
- Be happy!
- Wish your fiancé a happy birthday.
Once the camera starts rolling,
I no longer know who that woman is!
There's something that I have to do today.
It's to give you ladies my love.
I really hope that you choose me.
Lady number one... I love you!
You've just shown me way too much.
Is this your birthday gift to her?
[I'm sorry... you're the only one for me.]
Hello, I'm Male number six.
- More than anything, I sincerely...
- Song Joong Ki's friend!
Song Joong Ki's best friend!
[Male number six is Song Joong Ki's friend.]
I really like Song Joong Ki!
- Where is Song Joong Ki?
- Seriously!
[Male number six doesn't like it when
the subject of his friend is brought up.]
- Don't talk about Song Joong Ki!
- Song Joong Ki!
Once you start looking, you'll see that I have
many more better qualities than Joong Ki.
Please be on the watch for that.
Male number one told us earlier...
that there's nothing to see with you.
Aren't Ladies number one and two
going to introduce themselves?
Hello...
[Lady number one introducing herself.]
[A strong reaction.]
Thank you, I'm Lady number one,
and my name is Park Bo Young.
[Lady number one's name is
Park Bo Young.]
- Young! Young!
- You're so pretty!
I met all of you before just briefly...
but I wanted to see you all again and get to
know all of you better, so I came on the show.
We're so glad that you're here!
Yes, I will give it my best today.
Thank you.
[Breaking out in a cheer.]
Yes, I'm Lady number two.
You really are shameless.
I will never choose number six.
Even though I've been with you all
for the past two years...
I will put my best effort in with
the intent of getting to know you better.
I don't know if this is the
right thing to say from the get go...
but it seems like Lady number two
has a bit of an attitude problem.
I will also not be picking Male number one.
- I will never pick him.
- Do you like clubs?
Yes, I like clubs.
- Yes...
- I like clubs too!
See? I like it too!
[At that point...
they were only full of happiness...]
[Changing into their outfits.]
He has interest in Lady number one.
[Full of nervous energy even
while they change their clothes.]
[Six men vs. Two women]
[Checking his style before
the interview starts?]
Lady number two is...
which Male was it?
Is it number four? I think
there was something between them.
Is it okay for people who have
a past to be on the show together?
I don't know...
but I like Lady number two
who showed off a bit of an attitude.
[Male number four is taking care
of Lady number two.]
I'm not really sure yet.
I think Male number one is
going to be very caring...
but it bothers me that he has a child.
[Male number one has a child.]
And as for Male number three...
there are other people that I'm reminded
of whenever I think about him...
[Related search for Male number three
are all names of women.]
So it makes me wonder if
there's even a space for me.
And I heard that Male number five
is going to get married soon?
And Male number six is just
too tall!
Number one...
Lady number is already
about 40% in love with me.
And in case anything happens...
I'm going to keep the door open for a
possibility with Lady number two to the end.
As of right now...
Lady number one?
[I'm sure you're all flying high
on cloud nine right now...]
[Yeah... enjoy and have fun...]
[Because soon enough, it's going
to get hard to even just breathe.]
[Do you want to know who I am?]
[Soon you'll find out...]
Okay... everyone's all gathered now?
Yes!
First up is 'Doshirak Corner' where you can
share a Doshirak with someone you like.
You'll notice there's
a convenience store to your right.
Go to the convenience store and
buy whatever you each would like to eat.
- Number one... what are you going to eat?
- Yes?
Number two,
please be careful of the steps.
[All the men are being considerate in
order to buy the women's hearts.]
Thank you. You're very caring.
- The employee here...
- You work here now?
[Dong Wan PD working his shift
at the convenience store.]
- Hello...
- What are you going to eat?
- I'm not really sure.
- Number two, what do you like to eat?
What should I eat?
- I'm going to get some steamed buns...
- Steamed buns are really good!
[Surprised by the hot steam
that shot out of the bun steamer.]
- Gary, come here.
- Why?
- Stand here.
- Open up the door.
Ugh! That's hot! That was hot!
Don't buy any steamed buns.
I already got one for you.
- Seriously...
- Do you like fish cakes?
The competition is way too cutthroat since
there are so few ladies on the show today.
Aren't you going to eat anything?
All the men are buying the food...
so there's no need for me to buy anything.
- I think you probably need to buy some!
- Forget it!
- I'm not going to eat any of yours.
- I didn't buy anything for you.
- Forget it! Don't even talk to me.
- Seriously...
I'm not even considering
Lady number two.
I'm not sure how this is going to sound,
but she just seems so cold.
[Lady number two heading
to her spot.]
What did you buy?
I...
[Merely two americano coffees?]
Aren't the men supposed to
prepare the food?
Why would I have to prepare
that myself?
[The men getting the meal prepared.]
This is awesome.
What is this?
- This looks really good.
- I want to have one right now.
Lady number one, over here!
You can sit over there,
and I'll sit over here.
- I can't eat with you?
- We have all the men.
Lady number two...
[All the men making their way over.]
Stop over here.
Where are you both going?
[Sitting down right away?]
You have to go stand in front
of the sign.
[Have to choose first...]
Popcorn?
[Male number two bought popcorn.]
There's the pleasure of sharing
the same tub.
Male number two... hurry up!
You can be disqualified.
10 seconds!
Disqualified.
- Male number two... out.
- Is he disqualified?
I'm so sick of hearing the word, out.
- How many years have I heard that for?
- Have you already eaten?
Starting now...
the men will choose the Doshirak.
[Men will choose the women.]
Please sit at the table who you want
to eat your lunch with.
[Six men vs. two women -
A fierce competition]
- Okay.
- Let's go to number one.
Aren't you going to start
with Lady number one?
[All the men choosing
Lady number one in a hurry.]
[Always consistent Male number four?]
I heard that you like fish cakes...
[Male number five
also chooses lady number two.]
You have beautiful eyes.
[I guess he feels guilty!]
[Male number six heads over to
Lady number one.]
- I guess you're done playing hard to get?
- Yes, I've made my decision.
[Lady number one's table with
plenty of food to choose from.]
Instead of eating things that are bad for you,
here's some things that are good for you.
[Male number three handing her
some fresh fruit juice.]
You have to eat things that
are good for you.
Let's eat quietly over there.
If you want to eat in quiet,
go home and eat!
[And that's how their lunch went,
full of laughter...]
Give this to Lady number one
and tell her it's from me.
[Male number five sends the hotdog that
he was eating over to Lady number one.]
- He already ate some...
- He sent you what he was eating?
Tell her to eat this along with it.
Lady number one... wants me to ask you
if you'd like to be stabbed by this stick?
I guess she doesn't like this
kind of food.
- Are you almost finished eating?
- Yes, we're done eating.
If you'll take a look to your right...
you'll see a camper parked there.
[The camper of destiny that will lead
them to the pre-determined location.]
You'll be taking that camper to
your mission location.
[Entering the camper]
- Wow...
- This is so nice!
Male number four...
please pass this to Lady number one.
- Yes, I'll pass it on to her.
- Tell her that it's from me.
Isn't this what I'm supposed to do?
- What are you doing?
- You should be doing that to Lady number two!
[Oh no.. all the coffee!]
[A really high maintenance
Male number two.]
- Be careful!
- Here, let me wipe you up.
[Okay, laugh...
laugh to your heart's content...]
[And that's how all the Running Men...]
[tumbled into a situation that
they're completely unaware of.]
All the colors in the trees are so pretty!
- Wow... they really are pretty.
- Look at all the colors.
[Be careful... he's not far away...]
This is where we start the mission where
you can win a date with the ladies.
- What is it?
- This is important.
The first mission is... 'Pull the umbrella'.
But there's only one umbrella?
The first man to pull out the umbrella can go
and put it over the woman that he likes.
However, if that woman doesn't
reciprocate that man's feelings...
[If the female contestant that gets chosen
doesn't like the male contestant...]
She can refuse the umbrella
by flicking it out of her way.
- Good! We're all set.
- This is good.
This isn't bad.
And if a couple is created,
that couple is granted their date.
We will start by hearing
what Lady number one thinks.
I... I think I'm going to like the
first man who comes to me the most.
Okay, I understand!
Please, don't worry!
Number one! Number one!
I... like fun people.
Aren't I fun? Aren't I fun?
You have to open up the umbrella
over the lady once you get it.
Ready...
[Pull the umbrella game - Start!]
[Male number five-
The groom-to-be's surprising force]
- I was second place.
- The whistle sound was too quiet.
- Yeah, it was too quiet!
- Dong Hoon got it?
It's too soon to tell... too soon to tell.
Dong Hoon, congratulations
on your upcoming wedding.
[This man is getting married on
November 30th.]
Okay, I got it...
I've watched her from afar.
[Male number five's hearts belongs to...
Lady number one? Number two?]
- Her name is... Pocket girl.
- Huh?
I will keep her in my pocket,
and take her with me everywhere.
[Who's the number that Male number five
would like to take around in his pocket?]
[Lady number one - I'll carry it around...]
You have to open up the umbrella!
[Male number five chooses
Lady number one.]
He called her his pocket girl.
[Male number five being really showy
about covering her with his umbrella.]
One, two, three!
[Lady number one who said that she'll like
the man who gets to her first the most.]
[Male number one who isn't even considering
Lady number two is watching closely.]
I think my style is very compatible
with Lady number one.
Why... are you being like this?
[Male number five was refused!]
[Celebrating]
[Male number five's bangs flapping around
in the wind and looking lonely.]
I'm sorry.
- I thought she was going to accept it!
- I really thought she was going to take it.
You're the best!
You can still go up to Lady number two.
Of course, I'm going to!
I was just trying to make her jealous!
[That was all...
a plan to make her jealous?]
Okay... get ready...
[A ferocious battle at the starting line.]
[Male number three's body check.]
[But Male number six flies in
to nab the umbrella!]
Wow... that was amazing.
Who's the one who jabbed me
on my side with their elbow?
- Suk Jin?
- No, it's Jong Kook!
[Male number three's fierce shove.]
Jong Kook's hitting everyone
with his elbows!
[Pissy men are all pouring out
their frustrations.]
- Are you going to do it or not?
- I'm going to do it.
Then hurry up and do it.
- Make sure you choose wisely.
- That Giraffe...
- Lady number one isn't a joke either.
- No, she's not your average girl.
She puts on her nice act,
but she hurts you with her words.
Did you see how she threw down
the umbrella earlier?
[Lady number one's adamant refusal.]
She threw it hard on the ground.
From the first moment I saw her...
I really didn't think much of you.
Why are you... you're way too jealous!
From the first moment I saw her...
I became her captive.
He's looking towards Ji Hyo.
I think he's showing interest
in Lady number two.
[The one who made Male number six
a captive of love is...]
[Lady number one?]
[Just what will
Lady number one's choice be?]
Thank you.
[Lady number one chooses
Male number six.]
- This is no fun! This is no fun!
- Hey! Are you trying to ruin our show?
- Lady number one... Lady number one!
- Wait!
She accepted my heart,
why are you all reacting like this?
This is seriously insane...
[Showing interest in
Lady number two right away?]
Yes, I'm fine. Really, I'm fine.
- I should've grabbed the umbrella!
- It's me?
- Yes, it's you.
- You really don't suit each other!
They really don't suit each other!
- I thought he'd fail without a doubt.
- Why would I fail?
[There's still a chance!]
- Lady number two! I'm coming!
- Lady number two, you remember me, right?
[Male number three uses his force!]
It hurts! Seriously... it hurts!
As for me...
even if I'm refused,
it has to be her...
- I want to give it to her.
- You really sound like a man.
[Male number three stealing glances
at Lady number one.]
[Will his steps...]
Look at Kwang Soo's glare...
look at Kwang Soo...
[Male number six
is glaring at Male number three.]
- He really is being catty...
- That's just dirty... so dirty!
[Without a care to all the criticism,
he remains obvious about his displeasure.]
[Male number three's footsteps...]
[are headed towards Lady number one.]
One, two...
[Just who will Lady number one choose?]
I've never thought otherwise
since the first moment I saw you.
Please don't do this!
[Lady number one abandons
Male number six.]
It's you that I love.
- From the first moment I saw you...
- Hey! What are you doing?
What do you think you're doing?
She's going to be my woman soon!
What are you doing?
What's wrong?
I guess Park Bo Young is going to pop up
in search for Kim Jong Kook from now on.
- She's going to pop up in the search too!
- Wait... why are you being like this?
You're surrounding yourself
with women, aren't you?
What did you say? Why are you...
[While they're all immersed
in the couples' game...]
[Somewhere in the woods nearby...]
[A suspicious shadow?]
- Okay, okay...
- There's much we can learn here.
[What is the reason for him being here?]
[Then he...]
[Makes a move?]
[While everyone remains oblivious...]
[Moving in on them?]
Don't relax too much.
You never know when things will change.
[What he's after...]
[Is what? The staff?]
[One staff member being dragged away.]
[And he is... Jae Suk's VJ, Gwon Yeol?]
Don't yell out anything.
[Just why is he kidnapping Gwon Yeol?]
Go!
[Just where is he taking Gwon Yeol?]
[While no one's noticed anything,
and after Gwon Yeol has disappeared...]
[Male number one and Male number four
battling for Lady number two.]
- He's really a manly man...
- What a manly man!
[Male number four
definitively making his mark.]
I know that this is what she's
going to do!
- Will my umbrella... what are you doing?
- Will my umbrella...
What are you doing right now?
[During the scrimmage,
Lady number two's sticker falls off.]
Your mate is right here!
[Male number one vs. Male number four-
Lady number two's selection is...]
Don't you think Male number one
looks a bit pitiful?
I didn't want to make you feel burdened
by telling you this...
- But the truth is...
- If you feel burdened, just go!
[Male number one was
refused by Lady number two.]
Come over here...
Jae Suk, come over here.
Seriously... this is unbelievable!
This is seriously unbelievable.
What is your deal?
[Couples have been decided.]
[Aboard the camper and head to
the pre-determined camping site.]
Why don't you get on first?
- Does this have second floor?
- Yeah, it's two story.
Male number one,
you're not hurt, are you?
- I'm much cooler than I look.
- Are you?
To be honest... I don't really like you.
I know that...
you really are a catty man!
What do you mean, catty?
What about me is catty?
[Camper leisurely heading on its way.]
[But... could that person possibly be...]
I kept these hidden...
[Lady number one pulling out
the sausages she had kept hidden.]
Male number three,
you don't eat that kind of stuff though.
- Male number three doesn't eat that stuff.
- I do eat it!
You can just hold onto it then.
[The remaining men can't even stand
the sight of the two couples.]
I want to treasure this...
it's a keepsake for me.
- It's our first meeting's...
- We can share it.
[The day just keeps on getting darker
while they're getting along harmoniously...]
[In truth, their way to Aejung campground
was being led by someone up front...]
[Aejung Camping Ground]
We're here!
[Yes, we are here...]
- Let me get off first.
- What is all this?
- What is it?
- It's a barbeque.
[Outdoor barbeque that's been
prepared for them at Aejung campground.]
[However, only the couple are
permitted to enjoy the delicious meal.]
But why do they keep feeding us?
It's making me nervous.
I'm sorry to be eating all this beef
by ourselves over here.
This is going to cook up real fast,
so we're going to have to eat quickly.
- Wow... look at this.
- Just smell this stuff!
What do we do with all this?
But I think the best part of it all is
being able to eat this stuff outdoors.
- The smell of charcoal...
- That looks so good.
I can smell the meat cooking.
- Here, why don't you try this?
- What are you doing right now?
- Please don't be like that!
- You two aren't an official couple yet!
- You don't need to be doing all that...
- Well, he's grilling right now...
- What are you doing?
- It's because she's very kind.
Since he's grilling...
- Here, take a bite.
- Thank you.
- That's about to burn...
- But there's no need for you to feed him...
[Male number four trying to feed
his lady a lettuce wrap.]
What are you two doing?
It's because I'm so happy
to be with her again.
You two really are
out here camping, aren't you?
- How many garlic pieces did you put in here?
- Four!
I put four pieces of garlic in there.
It's so that you become more human...
So that you can become more lady-like!
[Monday couple from the past.]
I will give you your second mission with
a chance at a date as the prize.
Lady number one and Lady number two
will draw a piece of paper
with the tent number on it
and will go wait inside the tent
that they have drawn.
If the men finds a tent with a lady inside,
and they're together, they'll become a couple.
- So this is all by chance?
- Yes.
And they will go on with the mission
as instructed at that point.
Please draw a piece of paper
which has the tent number written on it.
Please step up to the front.
Ji Hyo, I'll see you later.
- Ji Hyo, see you later.
- Okay, I'll see you later.
[The ideal opportunity
to change up the couples!]
We'll see the two of you later.
Please wait just a little while.
- I will make sure to come...
- This is all pre-destined.
I will come to where you are.
- Yes.
- No matter where that may be...
[Lady one and Lady two getting
a head start.]
[Does fate means that it'll allow
them to see each other again?]
[Soon after, all the men start out to
meet up with Ladies number one and two.]
Wait... you're not Gwon Yeol.
Where did Gwon Yeol go?
- I don't really know.
- Seriously... what are you talking about?
Lady number one...
Lady number one, are you in here?
Lady number one?
There's no one in here.
Who could be in here?
[Every tent that they open
is completely empty.]
Not in here either.
It's not this one.
Lady number one?
If not, Lady number two?
[But they seem to have
completely disappeared?]
Lady number one? There's a table in here.
Wait a minute...
What is this?
[You didn't become part of a couple.
Please return to base camp.]
Are you making me to be a spy again?
Come on... seriously...
[You didn't become part of a couple.
Please return to base camp.]
Tragedy! Tragedy!
Is no one coming?
I wonder if Lady number one didn't get
coupled off with anyone either?
[You didn't become part of a couple.
Please return to base camp.]
[Someone's shadow...]
[The same shadow near the other tents too?]
Lady number one?
Who are you?
He's leaving... excuse me!
Answer me if you're a woman,
but go away if you're a man!
Who are you...
[The suspicious shadow
casting on the tents...]
[The identity of that is?]
[From disappointment of not becoming a part
of a couple, Haroro is trying to leave...]
[But someone was waiting for him
right out front!]
[A terrifying invasion!]
[Who is this intruder that
overpowers Ha Ha within moments?]
[Just what is...]
[Disappearing into the woods after
capturing Ha Ha... Just who is that man?]
- I don't see Ha Ha here.
- You think Ha Ha became a couple?
Then does that mean... does it mean
Ha Ha and Bo Young are a couple?
I should be protecting Lady number one
in this dangerous darkness.
- I really was going to watch over her.
- You can just keep your mouth shut.
- Bo Young was just playing with you.
- Stop with your lame jokes!
- Where have you been, Lady number two?
- Any of you become a couple?
- No, we haven't.
- Lady number one isn't back yet though.
What is that?
[Couple off in two's (Temporary coupling)
and set off on your mission!]
Couple off in twos and set off on your mission.
[Couple off in two's (Temporary coupling)
and set off on your mission!]
[Each couple can receive the mission card
at the location each couple is assigned.]
[Jae Suk - Jong Kook; Suk Jin- Kwang Soo;
Gary- Ji Hyo.]
[Without even any explanations...
where is this coming from?]
[All couples must make sure to move
with their arms linked together.]
- You mean, us two?
- You want us to link arms?
- What is this now?
- Link our arms?
- Why do you want us to link our arms?
- I'm so sick of this stuff.
You want me to link my arm with yours?
Here, link your arm in mine.
[The Easy Brothers' couple
is the first to get on their way!]
- Do you know what this is about?
- No, I don't know.
[Not having a clue as to what's going on.]
I'm going to couple up with her
no matter what.
Is that still even within play?
Of course. The last ones to remain
a couple are the winners.
I liked Lady number one too.
- This is how all the horror movies start.
- I know...
With all the couples out for some fun,
they start getting picked off one by one...
and some scary stuff starts to happen.
And the couples start to
disappear one by one.
You scared me!
You really scared me!
I see that you are still more fearful
than you let on.
My nose is running...
[They've arrived where they were instructed,
but where is the mission card?]
You think there's something going on
with the other couple?
Then what are we supposed to do here?
Have a date?
Shall we have a date?
Since it's pretty windy and chilly?
- Color of those leaves are so beautiful!
- Where?
What are you doing?
Why don't you come have
a seat over here?
[Oh my... are they
seriously starting their date?]
Seriously...
instead of finding
what you're supposed to be finding...
Flashlight, flashlight...
who is the fairest of them all?
Come on, you lie!
But seriously... what's the mission?
Let's hurry up and find the
mission card.
What is that? There's a string.
- What is this?
- Look at this... what is this?
[What is this horizontal bar?
And what is the string for?]
What is this? For hanging?
This is to hang something!
This is to hang someone? What is this?
- What is this?
Look... let's take a look around.
[Scared by the sound of wind rushing by.]
Since it's here,
let's see what this is about.
[And why is this standing up?]
What... just what is this?
Why don't you check it out?
Just what the heck is this?
Why wouldn't I be able to kick it?
I can just try kicking it.
[After talking all the talk,
still not able to touch it.]
Why can't you touch it?
- I bet it's underneath it... it's under it!
- That's what I'm saying!
Then why aren't you checking it out?
Just kick it like this!
- Why aren't you checking it out?
- You try it, Jae Suk!
[Brothers with a good relationship that
push each other when afraid?]
Why don't you check it out?
I think the mission card is underneath it.
- You're saying you think it's underneath it?
- Yes, I do.
- Then why don't you push it over?
- You do it!
[Huh? There's nothing...]
I can't believe you pushed me.
Either way, you did push it over.
But why isn't there anything under it?
[But... there's nothing underneath it?]
Excuse me!
- You don't have a mission card, right?
- No, we don't have one!
- You don't have one?
- No, we don't.
See? I think there's something
going on with that other couple.
Then shall we get going?
- Something doesn't feel right.
- I know, something feels suspicious.
[A gloomy aura that's making them
feel uneasy.]
[The Easy Brothers on the other hand...]
[Searching the warehouse
that they've been sent off to.]
Is something in there?
[Arriving in the rest area
where a light has been left on.]
- What is this?
- What is this place?
There are mattresses, and things...
are we supposed to sleep here?
[Come on... do you really think so?]
Look over there.
Maybe there's something.
We haven't received our mission yet.
What's the mission?
- What is it that we're supposed to do?
- Mission?
We need a mission card before doing anything.
I have no idea what we're supposed to do.
[Huh? What is that card?]
- Why are you looking at the price?
- Wow, that's cheap.
[The light is suddenly shut off?]
[The intruder that ousted Ha Ha?]
Who is it?
[He slowly approaches them!]
[Easy Brothers in danger!
What is their fate?]
[Running Man members set out
in search for Easy Brothers.]
- Male number six!
- Male number two!
- Where are you?
- Lady number one!
Where are they?
- Where in the world are they?
- Lady number one!
Something feels strange...
Something's been feeling off...
[No mission cards to be found,
and now people are disappearing too...]
They're nowhere to be found.
- What is that? Giraffe... Giraffe!
- Where?
- Giraffe!
- Hey!
[Oh? That's Male number six...
there's the Giraffe?]
- Male number six!
- Why is he acting like that?
[His inexplicable expression...]
- Male number six...
- Male number six?
- What's he doing? What's wrong with him?
Why are you just
standing there like a mannequin?
- What's wrong?
- What's wrong with him?
- What's wrong with you?
- Male number six, what's wrong?
- Come to the playground.
- What did you say?
- You want us to come to the playground?
What's wrong with you?
I told you to come to the playground.
Why aren't you listening to me?
[His tone of speech and expression
are as if he's under a spell...]
Something... wait, it's like he's being
controlled by something?
Is he being controlled by something?
Are you under some kind of a spell?
To the playground...
run over there within one minute.
[Should they do as they're told or not...]
- What is this?
- Hey!
Look, there's the playground.
Wait... what if he's playing us
right now?
- I don't think he is.
- You think he's playing us?
[Suspicious to see if the Giraffe
is possibly playing a joke on them.]
[But nothing but a mysterious expression...]
- See? Something's strange.
- Come over here.
- Gather at the playground.
- He wants at the playground.
- Jae Suk, where are you going?
- Over this way!
We can go that way too?
[Gathering for now at the playground
as the Giraffe told them to.]
[It's just an empty playground...]
Did we just get played?
Why do we have to do
as Male number six tells us to?
Let's be honest here...
Why are we being told to gather here?
- Male number six!
- Male number six...
What is this, Male number six?
- Where are you going?
- The moon looks really strange tonight!
- The moon looks so strange!
- Why does the moon look like that?
Doesn't it look creepy?
It looks like the moon
from all those scary stories.
[There's something in his ear?]
Okay, members...
Face left!
All the members, face left!
Why do we have to do as he tells us?
Members, march forward!
[Doing as they're told for now...]
- Left, left, left...
- Halt right there!
Face forward!
Hello, Running Man.
Grasshopper, Jong Kook, Gary and Ji Hyo.
Have you all been well?
Hello, Running Man.
Grasshopper, Jong Kook, Gary and Ji Hyo.
Have you all been well?
- Jae Suk, he said Grasshopper!
- Is it Min Soo?
Min Soo is the only one who
calls you that!
No way!
Especially...
Jae Suk, you...
Especially... Jae Suk, you...
[How can this be... how can this be?]
[Ousting him two years ago by
sticking his name tag on his back...]
[Declaring to hunt down the Grasshopper!
His dramatic revenge last year...]
I hate him the most.
Min Soo... the score is one and one
right now.
The score is one and one right now.
[He's come to finish it?]
Seriously?
Is it Min Soo?
After stabbing a person in the back,
and with a human mask on
I see that you're living well
laughing the whole time.
Kim Jong Kook, to the front!
Take 10 steps forward.
Look at that... that's totally Min Soo!
Stop!
About face.
Now, go back.
Go back!
The way I see it, that could've just
been just Kwang Soo's doing.
Go back!
[Slapping the Tiger in the face
is an act by the Giraffe alone?]
- I think that was just Kwang Soo...
- Go back!
[Definitely makes sense...]
You have to think very carefully
right now.
- That could've been just Kwang Soo doing it!
- I think you're right.
That wasn't on my order,
but Kwang Soo did it on his own.
Kwang Soo, relay that
message exactly as you're told.
That... that wasn't on my order...
That wasn't on my order...
- But Kwang Soo did it on his own.
- I did it on my own.
Kim Jong Kook, stop.
And that again wasn't on my order.
And that again wasn't on my order...
[I even relay the laughter...]
- It must be Min Soo...
- I really think it's Min Soo.
Monday couple or whatever...
You were all so immersed in it that
you didn't even notice that I came, did you?
It's just the program! We have
no interest in the Monday Couple.
- I'm okay because I have Geun Young.
- Kim Jong Kook, your mouth!
Kim Jong Kook, your mouth!
That was Kwang Soo...
that was totally Kwang Soo.
'Kim Jong Kook, your mouth'
wasn't something I said.
That trap of yours is your problem.
[What? Now doing what he pleases?]
Kwang Soo...
Sit down and get back up.
Do it again.
I'm sorry.
[The Giraffe getting punished from
doing as he wanted.]
What a sight, you deserve it!
Okay, and now...
We're going to play,
'The Rose of Sharon has bloomed'.
The last person to play and
win this game...
I will give them a kiss.
Excuse me?
I said, I will give them a kiss.
I will give them a kiss.
And now... the game will start.
The Rose of Sharon has bloomed.
[He didn't tell them to do this
without a reason... so why?]
[Now...]
[The time has come...]
[It's been a long wait...
right, Running Man?]
The Rose of Sharon has bloomed.
- What?
- What!
[Ice...]
- Why?
- What's wrong?
The Rose of Sharon has bloomed.
- Why? What is it?
- Tell us! What is it?
[The unseen terror...]
[At last... coming up behind them...]
- What is it?
- Tell us!
[A total chaos breaks out
in their frozen state.]
- Why?
- What's wrong?
[The man cloaked on mystery
getting closer and closer...]
- Hurry...
- Tell us.
- Is he on his way?
- Tell us... is he coming?
- Me? Is he it?
- Hey! Kwang Soo...
- Why? Why me? Why is he after me?
- Kwang Soo...
[At last... it's time to meet!]
- What is this?
- Why? Why?
- What is it?
- You're both out.
- I'm so scared!
- What is this you've got here?
- Okay, the game is going to keep going.
- Yes.
- Have you been well?
- Yes, I've been well.
Jong Kook, you're out.
Ah, it's because I moved.
[Gary is the only one left!]
- I have to pay my respects though.
- Gary, keep going.
Keep going.
[How can he go on with the game
when he's scared out of his wits?]
[Automatically freezes over.]
I have to endure it... I can't move!
I have to endure it.
I can't move... can't move!
The Rose of Sharon has bloomed.
[Stop...]
- If you even budge, your name tag is gone.
- I'm not moving!
The Rose of Sharon has bloomed.
- Where did you get your mask?
- Do you want to see my face?
[Hunter Min Soo makes his appearance!]
That's scarier!
- I'm on your side, Min Soo.
- I'm sorry.
You have to continue with
the Rose of Sharon. Go ahead.
[Anyways, they have to finish
the game they started.]
Should I do it again or not?
The Rose of Sharon...
What do we do? What's going to happen?
Jong Kook... Jong Kook, stand right there!
Jong Kook... Jong Kook,
stand right there!
[Hunter Min Soo summons Mr. Capable!]
If the rest of you don't run away,
I'm going to get you and eat you.
[For now, the rest of the members
are freed.]
[Mr. Capable and Hunter left behind
in the playground.]
- You can avoid me any longer.
- Min Soo, what do you mean, avoid you?
- Guard!
- Excuse me?
Stand guard.
Did you just tell me to stand guard?
[Beast vs. Beast!
Facing off as Man vs. man!]
Guard...
Yes, Min Soo.
Begin. Sparring.
[Mr. Capable vs. Hunter-
Shadow boxing face off: Start!]
[Doing it properly from the beginning
as if it was for real!]
[Hunter Min Soo
aggressively attacking Mr. Capable!]
[If they're even slightly off,
they could strike each other!]
[Just then!]
[Hunter Min Soo, goes for the name tag
in the midst of shadow boxing!]
Why are you grabbing my back?
You know this isn't right!
This isn't right...
[Hunter Min Soo eliminates
Mr. Capable's name tag!]
[Everything...
is going along the Hunter's plans...]
I'm so scared!
That was so scary!
- Did you feel chills going down your spine?
- You felt it too?
- Seriously...
- I saw his shadow.
Why did he have us playing
Rose of Sharon?
- That was terrifying...
- Hey! Lee Kwang Soo!
What's he doing?
What happens to me now?
[How did he become the Hunter's avatar?]
[While they were searching for their
mission in the room earlier...]
[Hunter Min Soo walks in...]
I'm seriously... scared for real.
Are you curious as to who I am?
Do you want to know who I am?
Hello.
- I want the two of you to fight.
- You want us to fight?
[Easy Brothers always tearing away
at each other when it's decision time.]
- You're really going to do this?
- I have no other choice.
[The Giraffe's signature move-
Attacking with his teeth!]
I'll tear it off!
- Hey! Hey!
- Five... four...
I tore it off.
You're over now.
Pil-Chok-Cross or whatever...
You and I...
As of now...
you're going to become my avatar.
[That is how the Giraffe became
the Hunter's avatar.]
I've always been an avatar.
This is the perfect role for you...
Only you and I can communicate
with this now.
If I give you an order to say something
you'll have to relay exactly what I'm saying
to the members, do you understand?
- Yes, I understand.
- You got it?
[However...]
[this was only a part of the plan
that the hunter had in mind...]
[Earlier on the same day...]
[Hunter having arrived first and planned
his hunting attack on the Running Men.]
[Everything that day was to go
according to his plan!]
If I bring them up by the camper
the mountain is to this side
and the campsite to the other side.
[Even the jail, monitor and walkie talkie
was planned out!]
[Playing 'The Rose of Sharon has bloomed'
was also a part of his plan!]
[Even the paths around
the mountain were explored!]
[Ah, and also...]
- I've explained everything, right?
- Yes.
That backstabbing Grasshopper
is my main goal...
So I guess I should tell you guys
how you can possibly win too, right?
[With everything planned out, explaining
a chance for Running Man to win.]
My name tag is scattered around
in pieces...
[If the Hunter's name tag which has been
scattered around in pieces are gathered...]
[and stuck on his back,
then that Running Man is the victor!]
[All of this...
is the Hunter's final secret...]
If you look behind you,
you're dead.
[The final hunt has to be fair...]
When we were playing
the Rose of Sharon game
I was going to tear off his name tag,
but it wasn't on his back.
- You saw it too, right?
- Min Soo?
- Then are we supposed to find his name tag?
- Did Kwang Soo have his name tag?
Then do we have to find it
and put it on his back and rip it off?
[These ones left remaining are slowly
starting to piece the rules together too...]
We're supposed to put the name tag
on him!
Jae Suk, we have to find his name tag.
We have to find the name tag!
[Not knowing that his name tag
is scattered around in pieces...]
You think they're insides all
those tents?
[On the other hand, in order to let others
know how to beat the Hunter...]
[Plan is to write down how to bring him
down on a paper plane and send it out.]
See if you can hear anything.
[Paper telephone, it's been awhile...]
- The line has to be taught.
- You're not going to get the distance.
The fact that he's doing something
is what's important.
- Hey, Dong Hoon.
- Yes, Suk Jin. I can hear you!
[If it can't be heard in that distance,
there's a problem...]
- I'm going to throw this outside, okay?
- Okay, do it.
I'm throwing it.
Look... the airplane just fell.
Can you get it for us just once?
[Get what?]
Sorry.
He's here, he's here.
[We're ruined...]
- Min Soo, I think we can be let go now.
- Let me just tell you one thing.
Ha Ha... you'll be in trouble
if you fly out any paper airplanes.
It was because I was bored.
I'm sorry!
Should I open up the plane
and check what it says?
Knowing you, I'm sure you wouldn't be
doing it without writing anything on it first.
And now... read the content out loud
as if you're making an announcement.
Begin.
Choi Min Soo, I love you!
- Min Soo, it's great to see you...
- Give it to me.
- Before the warmth of spring, winter comes...
- I said, give it to me.
I'll unlock the door and come in there.
- I'll give you one more chance.
- Your love that you have...
- Is for eternity...
- Shall I come in there?
[Getting rid of the evidence.]
- It's right... that's what he wrote.
- What he read out loud is correct.
One, two... One, two!
One, two.
[Hunter Min Soo's voice?]
The surviving Running Man are...
Grasshopper, Gary, Ji Hyo...
and Kwang Soo, the four of you.
I have hidden four boxes
around here.
Inside those boxes are instructions
on what you have to do now...
So make sure that you each
find one.
If by any chance, any of you wastes time
and don't find one, I'll oust that person
so don't waste any time,
and make sure to get it done.
Sir, I'm on your side!
I'm on your side!
[Giraffe put in a tough spot.]
What am I supposed to do here?
I think I need to find the box first.
- He said we're the only ones left.
- Then is Jong Kook out too?
I'd rather just get ousted early.
This is agonizing.
- Seriously...
- He said there are four boxes.
Where are we supposed to find
these boxes?
I think they're in those tents.
He still has a lot of resentment left
towards Jae Suk.
Min Soo still has a lot of resentment
left towards Jae Suk.
[Who is this chatterbox?]
[Oh...]
[It's Gary...]
[Should I go out and play?]
[Hunter Min Soo's chase!]
[Chasing right at his tail
without any difficulty!]
Save me! Save me!
[Gary out of pure desperation
begs to be saved in jail!]
[Panic!]
Please save me!
Please don't do this!
- Where is Jae Suk?
- Jae Suk?
He went up that way!
- He ran that way...
- He went that way...
What is going on?
Why is he being so scary?
- I'll let you go this once.
- I understand.
Do you know why?
It's so that I can catch you again.
[Where is the Hunter going now?]
Min Soo! Save me... I'm on your side!
[Attacks the Giraffe!]
I'm on your side!
I... I have to...
I have to relay your messages.
You didn't carry out your role
as my avatar correctly.
No... I'm just getting started.
Please give me some time.
- Should I get you?
- No.
- Should I let you live?
- Yes.
Avatar...
- Please trust me.
- Follow me.
[On the other hand, Jae Suk is searching
for the box that he's been ordered to find.]
[That's...]
[Is that a fragment of a name tag?]
- Choi!
- Jae Suk!
- Min Soo!
[Hunter Min Soo screaming out his name.]
Choi, it's Choi. Choi...
[This is one of the name tag fragments!
If he finds them all and puts them together!]
[Gary coming into the room
where Big-nosed brother was ousted.]
[Another fragment!]
This looks like a fragment of a name tag!
Wait...
It's Min... Min!
That means there are others
besides this?
Then how many fragments are there?
[This is the horizontal bar with the rope
that Jong Kook and Jae Suk saw earlier?]
Turn around.
I'm going to sit down with
my back turned towards you.
If you run... I'm going to chase you
in the most frightening way.
- What are you doing?
- I'm sorry.
[Anyone who tries to save Kwang Soo
who's hanging here... I'll come and get you!]
[From the beginning, this horizontal bar
and the rope...]
[Was a contraption meant for Kwang Soo...]
Okay, hang on.
- If you talk too much, I'll tear this off.
- Okay, I'll remain still.
Start humming a children's tune.
[Taking care of Kwang Soo according
to the plan is complete!]
[If he falls from the bar,
then his name tag will fall off too!]
Jae Suk!
Save me!
Ji Hyo!
[Jae Suk discovers a box that
the Hunter ordered them to find!]
- Where did you find that?
- I found it here.
[Head back to the headquarters and
watch the projector closely.]
Okay... so that's what it looks like?
[Head back to the headquarters and
watch the projector closely.]
Why do I need to go back to headquarters
and watch the projector?
Why all of a sudden?
[Something feels off...]
[On the other hand, Ace Ji Hyo
is busy searching for the box.]
It's so scary over here.
[Finding herself deep in the forest.]
Why is it so scary?
Quickly... I need to find it quickly.
What the heck?
Found it! I found it! I found it!
[Discovers the box.]
I found it!
[Human? It's the Hunter!]
What is that? Ji Hyo?
Ji Hyo's not one to scream like that
over something small...
Ji Hyo!
[On the other hand...]
This is so hard!
I don't think I can endure this!
But if I let go, I'm finished!
Is anyone out there?
[Giraffe's voice!]
Gary!
What happened to you?
Save me!
[If Gary hadn't come on time,
there could've been big trouble!]
- Calm down...
- I feel like I'm going to fall!
Save me!
I'm sorry.
[Afraid of getting bitten,
Gary cancels his plans to help.]
Gary, I won't betray you! Please!
I'm sorry, Kwang Soo!
Please...
Jae Suk!
What?
What did you say?
[Kwang Soo in danger!]
Save me!
Seriously...
- What are you doing?
- Jae Suk, a bit faster!
[Kwang Soo... this is no laughing matter!]
Faster!
I'm so scared...
Are you out?
So this is what this was for?
This is what it was for?
I'm so scared!
Kwang Soo, what is this?
Jae Suk, I'm so scared.
[Traitor Giraffe having a mental breakdown.]
It says... it says he'll bite whomever
tries to save you.
Kwang Soo...
- That's what that was for?
- He's crazy!
[Blasting him venomously.]
- Where did Ji Hyo go?
- I don't know. I heard her screaming.
Jae Suk, just hurry up and come to jail!
- Seriously, I'd rather... Kwang Soo!
- Jae Suk...
Just tear off my name tag!
Jae Suk...
Rather than living this hell...
- Kwang Soo...
- You're the only one who can do this.
- You have to win!
- I'm seriously about to go crazy!
This hell! Since when has Running Man
become so scary like this?
This program isn't supposed to
be like this!
Seriously... this is unbelievable.
It's unbelievable!
So that's what that horizontal bar was for?
What do I do?
We're all getting ousted one by one.
I think this is...
just so that Min Soo can oust everyone
and just toy with me at the end.
This is seriously...
- Gary!
- Jae Suk!
- Everyone's been ousted...
- Why are we back here?
- That's what I'm saying...
Ji Hyo's been ousted
and Kwang Soo's been ousted too...
- In my opinion...
- Yeah?
I think Min Soo...
wants to battle with you.
Since I don't know what'll happen,
I'll give you this now.
[Gary giving the Hunter's name tag
fragment that he found to Jae Suk.]
I think this is the end.
I think this is the end of your
fate with Min Soo.
Seriously, why is he being like this?
But why isn't this projector on
when we've been told to watch it?
[The order was to 'Head back to the
headquarters and watch the projector.]
[The Hunter is on the screen...]
Do you know what the heaviest
thing in this world is?
It's the air...
- The air?
- Why?
The air that you breathe in
right before you die...
Why is he talking about death
when this is just a game?
You guys may even blame me...
You can blame me.
But don't let it be obvious.
Cause I'll come and bite you.
Why does he keep saying he'll bite us?
I'll... show you guys some generosity.
There is a way... you can oust me.
- There's a way.
- He says there's a way we can oust him.
Every time one of your friends
disappeared...
A fragment of my name tag would've
fell at the spot.
[Pieces of the Hunter's name tag that they
need are where their friends were ousted!]
[Gather up all the pieces
and attach them on his back!]
Then I'll be ousted.
Jae Suk...
I still can't forget how you attached
the name tag on my back...
It's been two years...
that happened two years ago.
[That day two years ago...]
[After proposing they work together...]
[As soon as the opportunity rose
in front of him...]
[He betrays the Hunter that day.]
Let me get back on Running Man
within the next two months.
I will... hunt down the Grasshopper.
What is 'touch' in English?
It's touch!
Touch in English in touch!
You backstabbing Scoundrel...
[Just watching him on screen is enough
to make them have a mental breakdown!]
Come get me...
At any time... whenever...
I welcome you.
[The Hunter!]
[My goodness...
Busting through the screen to appear!]
[Total chaos!]
[The two remaining survivors who are
barely holding onto their mental strings!]
It's scary enough to just
see you, Min Soo!
- Really, it's scary enough just seeing you.
- Why did you bust out of there?
Why did you film that
and bust out of the screen?
Is that the first time that's happened?
That's very true. Min Soo...
You are pretty comedic.
[The Hunter overflowing with
comedic sense.]
I still have long ways to go
if I wanted to catch up to you.
- Min Soo...
- You two play Rock-paper-scissors.
Why?
Rock-paper-scissors.
Run.
- But what about Gary?
- Leave him behind.
You're really leaving just because
I told you to leave?
Then what am I supposed to do?
You told me to leave.
You're just going to abandon him?
Then what am I supposed to do?
What do I do?
Jae Suk, just leave.
Stab me in the back and go.
You always live your life
stabbing others in the back!
- Gary!
- Jae Suk, just leave!
- I'll see you next week!
- Jae Suk!
[Coolly abandoning him.]
- Yes, Min Soo?
Min Soo, what are you doing?
That's what we always do.
- This is what you are.
- Really?
This is what's going to happen to you.
Gary!
I'll make sure to oust Min Soo!
You just wait!
[All the pieces to the Hunter's name tag
are at where his friends were ousted!]
Just wait and see!
- Gary...
- Yes, Min Soo?
- Shall we go where the other members are?
- Yes, I think I would like that.
I should've tore off your name tag earlier,
I made a mistake.
No, Min Soo. I enjoyed myself.
- In that case... let's go. Get up.
- Yes, Min Soo.
- We weren't just getting up together?
- This must be yours.
I wonder why that fell off?
Take a look... there it is.
[A fragment of a name tag at the spot
where Kwang Soo was ousted!]
The spot where Gary was ousted...
[Another fragment!]
[Four pieces currently!
Now just need two more pieces!]
[Heading toward the hill where
Ji Hyo's screams were heard.]
There it is!
[Obtained five pieces of the name tag!]
[And lastly, to the spot
where Ha Ha was ousted...]
[Ha Ha went towards where
all the tents were earlier...]
[Discovered!
A fragment to the Hunter's name tag!]
[That Scoundrel...]
[There's only one chance.
Attack the Hunter's back!]
I just need to stick this on his back.
[The battle two years in the making...
will Jae Suk be able to win?]
[The Hunter's appearance!]
[Yoo-ruce Willis vs. The Hunter!]
[The challenge is...]
[to be met face to face!]
[This is their final face-off.]
[His completed name tag!]
Is this what you want?
Don't you even age?
- Pick it up.
- Excuse me?
Pick it up.
[Wait...]
[Hunter's tangled raincoat...]
[If I attach it there now...]
You knew?
You knew that your coat was
turned around?
Did you know that it was turned around?
Or did you not know?
You scared me. You didn't
know your coat was turned around?
You really startled me!
You really are a man.
You're very cool.
[Spectators having come out
to watch the battle.]
[Now...]
[His back is once more...]
[If not now...
I'll never get another chance!]
[If he hadn't flicked it away,
it really may have stuck on there!]
Were you going to throw it...
and stick it on my back?
- You were going to throw it on?
- No, that's not it...
That's... that's not it.
That's not it.
[First and second attempts both failed!]
[What to do now?]
[It won't go as you want...]
Jae Suk and I are going to
start fighting by ourselves now.
Satisfied?
I'll see you in the woods.
[At last... it's the beginning of the end!]
[Hunter vs. Yoo-ruce Willis-
The final battle...]
[Hunter Min Soo,
taking the final battle into the woods!]
[This battle has been
a long time in the making...]
[Shouldn't we end this now, Jae Suk?]
Jae Suk!
[The final call...]
Isn't that Min Soo's voice?
[Heading toward where the noise came
from to see it to the end.]
This is the last time for me.
[Heading towards the battle site
while vowing to himself.]
Why is it so windy today?
It's creepy...
[Running Man hunting
that started two years ago.]
[There's no more room to back up now...]
[Yoo-ruce Willis discovers something!]
[Hunter Min Soo's back?]
[Being more cautious about how he
approaches more than any other time!]
Stay here. Don't come.
[Soon... I will end it all, Min Soo.]
[Just as I did on that summer day
two years ago...]
[This time, I will make sure again...]
[At last...]
[No... something is...]
It's not him. I was wondering
why he was just sitting still.
[Shaving 10 years off of his life.
Total mental breakdown- Critical!]
Do you really have to oust me
like this?
Aren't you even curious about
who that is?
[No way...]
[Wait... now that we look at him...]
Why are you helping Min Soo?
You should be helping me.
- He was holding me captive.
- What did you say?
I was going to finish it in one shot
but when I got up close, I noticed
that he was smaller than Min Soo.
[And just like that,
through meticulous planning...]
[The final battle wins with
the Hunter's victory.]
- Jae Suk...
- Yes?
- That was great.
- Yes.
- Goodbye, Min Soo.
- But you're this.
Goodbye.
Come down in couple of hours, okay?
[We thank Park Bo Young
for making a special appearance.]
[Barely getting himself freed]
Seriously...
[As soon as the Hunter disappears
from his field of vision...]
[He starts talking crap.]
[Hm... I knew you'd do that.]
[Then... now...]
Subtitles by DramaFever
[This will be my victory!]
[The legendary game...]
Baseball isn't this kind of game!
[The Gods of Korean baseball
are coming!]
[The nation's major league glory,
Choo-choo train, Chu Shin Soo!]
[The pride of Korean baseball,
Monster pitcher, Ryu Hyun Jin!]
[Chu Shin Soo pulling a car...]
[And Ryu Hyun Jin's Ddak-ji skills!]
[World class dynamic stars' chase!]
[Strength vs. strength!
Chu Shin Soo vs. Mr. Capable!
[Surreal... and amazing!]
[The physic baseball game!]
[And a real competition between
Chu Shin Soo and Ryu Hyun Jin!]
Everyone, gather around.
[Next week - Psychic baseball]