Ah, mother!
Do you choose to die or be a Spy?
Spy,Spy!
Oppa!
Ah hyung,can't you let me off this once?
There's just one left!
The whispered secrets as I look at the clock
The stories in my heart I long for most
It's all right if I'm
It's all right if I'm pushed
Please call out my name
From the gaps between my hands
I'm afriad my heart will be revealed
My heart's overwhelmed with sadness
Please wait a little while for me
You and I, can't be now
Althought I want to make the clock go faster
In the future you'll be in
Please call me out my name
Please come out, all of you please come out.
Ah,  don't just, stand there and watching.
All of you, please come out.
Why aren't they coming out?
I'm afriad my heart will be revealed from the gaps between my hands
My heart's overwhelmed with sadness
Please wait a little while for me
You and I, can't be now
Althought I want to make the clock go faster
In the future you'll be in
Please call me out my name
You and I, can't be now
Althought I want to make the clock go faster
In the future you'll be in
If I were to wander
In order that I may recognize you
Please call me out my name
-Thank you. -IU!
Wow.
Yes, will the remaining please come out quickly?
It seems like, there's something to do with order, or doing something like that now.
Seems like you have to come out quickly?
Now, five people have already come out.
Yes, please just stand accordingly in this order.
Today will surely be a good day too.
Yi yoo!
Yi-yoo!Yi-yoo!
Why is the sky today so blue?
IU!
It just happens the wind today is that perfect
Pretending not to know, pretending not to hear a word
Pretending to forget and start a new topic
In order to close you lips, can I kiss you
With tears welling up and lifting my head
Not letting the tears fall and giving a smile
Why are you treating me like this, I don't know what I'm saying
Everything we said today will be thrown to the sky
Wrods I 've never said before, words I didn't know were said while crying
I like Who? You, oppa
What do I do
IU, IU!
I even thought they were playing an album but she's really here.
Ah, who wore my shoes?
It's done as long as everyone's here right?
Will the last few people hurry up too?
Was my new hairstyle very bad?
Come quickly, hurry.
Are the clothes I'm wearing today unsuitable?
Hello
Pretending not to konw, pretending that I don't remember
Should I just pretend nothing even happened?
Should I just get you to out?
With tears welling up and lifting my head
Not letting the tears fall and giving a smile
Why are you treating me like this, I don't know what I'm saying
Everything we said today will be thrown to the sky
Wrods I 've never said before, words I didn't know were said while crying
I like you, oppa
What do I do
Yes, thank you everyone, I'm IU.
IU, IU!
Yes
-What's this really about, Yi-yoo? -Daebak.
Why did you tell IU, to do this sort of thing?
Are you even thinking straight?
Exactly.
NO, no, why must Yi-yoo do this so early...
-Because Miss IU is Yeosu's Goodwill Ambassador. -Ah, really?
Earlier on, IU, was beside Chun Hee.
Ji Jin hyung said this.
"Ah, looks like she'll be paired with Chun Hee, he must be so happy."
I even thought he was the owner of this pension.
That's right.
-Ok, let me say something. -Yes.
The teams have just been assigned now!
-How? -What?
How did you split the teams?
Starting from Miss IU at Number 1 all the way to Number 4, you're a team.
Hey, you're really...
Ok, from Song Ji Hyo at Number 5 to Yoo Jea Suk at Number 8, you're a team.
Ah, seriously.
-Do you feel it's a pity? -No, although it's all good...
Can't we just group the eight together?
Number 1 to Number 8 like this.
Why don't we just let IU choose on her own?
Ok also, from Ji Suk Jin at Number 9 to Jong Kook at Number 12, you're a team.
Ah, I'm Number 12, me?
Why don't we group ourselves?
-Just let IU choose her own team. -Exactly.
Ah, it's a good idea.
Jeez, if it's like this, if it's like this, Boss, IU coming here...
Then there's no point in her coming here to sing in the morning.
I'm the owner.
Just do what I say.
But these things are still better said early.
Hey, but Sang Wook too, after removing the suit, you're really...hey.
You couldn't recognize him?
I couldn't even recognize him.
He, looks so comfortable, like a neighborhood hyung.
Hey, Chun Hee's really, reminds us of his image in Family Outing.
What I saw on television, is just like what I'm seeing in front of me!
I was also shocked.
Whatever it is, there are two Gwang Soos here.
But what's this, what is it, Yi-yoo?
This was, given to me.
-By whom? -Sung Soo hyung gave it to her when he came out.
When someone comes in the moring a flower basket should be prepared.
Ah hyung, what's with the sunglasses in the morning?
Make-up!
It's really make-up, make-up.
Ah seriously, you're really...
The decision should still be given to you IU.
Ok...
Jin Hee, listen to what he has to say.
-Anyhow, IU already has her group. -Boss, you're too blunt with your words!
-Why don't you we let IU choose instead? -He keeps mumbling by himself.
Why do you put your hands in those pockets?Put them down here.
You're supposed to be the Big Sunbae
-I suppose you're all hungry? -We are.
So, the mission we have prepared today is...
A Tasty Bingo Race.
We will hand out a bingo board containing all the famous dishes of Yeosu to each team.
You go to the restaurant of your choice, eat the dish
And complete the mission to complete one square on your bingo board.
Complete a straight line using three adjacent squares to achieve bingo and win a humongous advantage in the final mission.
A huge advantage?
We will start immediately after you change into your team uniform.
-White car! -I think it's this one.
I...I need to shake hands with IU first.
-IU, can we shake hands? -Oh! Of course.
-You have to take your gloves off first. -Ah, yes.
Thank you very much.Please get in.
-Let me get that. -Oh thank you.
I can't believe I got to shake hands with IU.
-You sound like you're never seen IU before. -This my first time meeting her.
-Really? You first time? -I still can't believe my eyes.
-The two of you... Hyung! -Really?
What I can't believe is that you and her even know each other.
All right here's the plan.
We eat whatever IU wants to eat.
-Agreed? -Of course.
-Can I do that...? -Whatever you want to eat first.
The best choice would be to eat the middle one first.
-The one in the centre. -It would be wouldn't it?
I want to eat all of them!
-We only need to check off three don't we? -Yeah.
Then, oyster?
-Okay! Oyster is fine. -Are you all right with oyster?
Yeah I love it.
-Is there anything you can't eat? -No I'm fine with all of them.
-Can we start right away? -Of course you can!
-Then shall we have spicy seasoned crab to start the day? -Gatkimchi and rice!
He suggests we go for "spicy seasoned crad to start the day."
Spicy seasoned crab in the morning HaHaHaHa.
You know, I've already been in a program with Sang Wook before.
He actually has a lot of weak spots.
-People with this kind of laugh. -HaHaHaHa!
They're full of weak spots. See? Like this: HaHaHaHa!
-Anyway we should first start moving. Ji Hyo? -Here. Yes.
Where are we going?
-Let's go with what Sang Wook hyung wants to eat. -Sang Wook we'll go with what you want to eat.
Then how about we start with Seodae Spiced Sashimi?
-Okay then let's try there. -The way you speak is very clear and precise though.
Wait, no, this won't work.
Of course not, Sang Woo this pen is...
-It's to work with the PC. -Now I see what this laughter means.
I told you.
Hold on this isn't Gwagju.
-You have to select Jeonnam. -Jeonnam isn't being selected though.
Isn't not working?
-Oh, it's working. -Yes it is.
How could it not work?
This is embarrassing.
So...Does anyone have any IU songs downloaded?
You must have some.
Wow, you really have them.
This morning I woke up, heard this song and looked out the window,
And when I saw IU there singing,
I... I just... Is this... something that could really happen?
-And there's that part of the song. -Yes.
The sight of IU singing in the morning light with the rising sun as a back drop...
We’re one team for the rest of the day, right?
-That would be lovely. -We'll stay one team, right?
-We should have gone with oyster first! -Because the oyster is the middle one.
-We should have picked oysters. In bingo, you always pick the middle. -Exactly!
Hyung we only have to finish one line though don't we?
We need a plan.
-So this is the bingo board. -Ah,here.
-Use the pen. -No?
Give me that.
It doesn't work.
-Sang Wook hyung is a style that can't complete things in one shot, huh? -This is...
-You need to double tap is Sang Wook. -HAHAHAHAHA!
I should warn you, Ji Hyo is suppressing herself.
Oh, she is?
You have to double...
"Please click twice".
Oh, Ji Hyo you were watching.
-You have to double click, I see. -Ji Hyo, you're being unusually patient today.
Usually by now Ji Hyo would be after you hair.
If it was me or Gwang Soo in your position she would be cursing street-style
Ji Hyo's being very patient.
-Your age would be...? -I'm a '78
Your expression...
-She's getting annoyed. -If you had been younger than her...
-It's a bit... -Hyung, you look really young for your age.
-Are we the first ones here? -Do we just go in?
-Are we? First?
Hello.
-Here is your mission. -So there is a mission.
-If we don't pass the mission, we can't eat? -Yes.
Place the shellfish over the fire and open all of them within 2 minutes to succeed. What does that mean?
-Oh I remember this! -What is it?
You can't open them by hand.
-Didn't you do this before in Family Outing? -Why yes I did!
-It's opening! It's opening! -Wow! Wow!
Please!
Please! please!
Wait! It's opening! It's opening!
The important thing here is...
How fast you can fan it.
-We need to work hard. -You need speed?
-You need as much heat as possible. -Oh, is that so?
-We have to find something to fan it with. -This hyung is so smart!
-He's the smartest person I've ever seen. -Find a fan, you say?
-Look he's already found one! Wow. -Here's one.
Here, for you, IU.
Thank you.
Because everyone has to succeed, remember.
Hyung does this really make it open?
This makes the fire really heat up.
Two minutes?
This doesn't look easy.
-So if it stays shut we don't get any oyster? -Yes.
That's so sad.
Oh dear.
Are you ready? Three, two, one, go!
Three, two, one, go!
Is this possible?
-Does this actually work? -Are you sure this is the only way?
I don't think it'll work.
Even if just one opens...
It’s not even getting hot.
When it's about to water it will start leaking.
Hyung it's as dry as it can be though.
-To succeed here...! -I just heard something inside!
Look! Hyung, yours is moving.
Really?
I don't believe this!
Please!
-This is really hard. -Time's up.
You have to try again using new shellfish.
What a sight!
-It's like eating fish straight from the rod to the kitchen. -Exactly.
-It's already set up. -Good morning.
Looks delicious.
-But I bet there's a mission. -There'll be something for sure.
Oh, this is the menu?
Everyone Correct Quzi. Listen to the qusetion and when each person answers, everyone must answer correctly to succeed.
I see.
-When can we eat? -Correct, correct, correct, correct to win.
Then can we eat?
We can't eat before then?
-Should we go start with Gary first -This way you'll be blamed, Gary.
I understand.
-Here is the first question. -Yes.
What is the Chinese idiom meaning "The fish's head tastes best"?
-Gary, you know this right? -Of course he does, right?
-Everyone knows this, right? -...Fish Head Cut Tall.
What?!
What did you say?
-It's not Fish Head Cut Tall? -It's Cut Taste.
We'll try Ji Jin Hee first then
-Starting with this hyung. -An easy one please.
-There are a lot of different types of sashimi. -Yes.
What do  you call sashimi that is slightly cooked?
-Do you know it? -I can't remember!
-What was it...? Tuna... -It's that.
Shabu-shabu!
Does it come prepared or do you stick it in something right before you eat it?
You laughed. Shabu-shabu!
It's not?!
-He whispered it to me. -Shabu-shabu? Really?
-Shabu-shabu is when you have meat! -I'm sorry.
The answer was Suk Hwe
Suk Hwe, of course.
My stomach is growing.
It's here, it's here.
On the right.
Oh! It's here!
Ah, really.
-This part will be aired no matter what. -You've worked hard.
This part will be aired no matter what!
"It's here", this part will definitely be aired!
Let's alight.
Furnish the dining tabale following the one you just saw. If it's placed exactly the same, you will succeed.
I can't see.
Ah, I don't know.
The colors are about the same.
Hyung, pass it to me first.
-That one. Pass me that one. -First, memory...
First, this one is here.
-Do you know what is below this? -Vinegar and spicy paste is here.
-Sesame oil is here. -Ji Hyo, where are the bean sprouts?
-I've forgetten everything very quickly. -I've also forgotten where the bean sprouts should be.
Bean sprouts are here.
How many chances do we have? Does it end if we get it wrong just once?
Chances, as everybody knows...
-Until you get it correct. -Right.
Ah really! In front of this food, my stomach is ...
-I'm almost going crazy, really. -Really going crazy.
-This is really making me go crazy. -Really going crazy.
Ok! It’s done.
What? Wait a moment...
Wait a moment! What are you doing?
-What are you doing Sang Wook? -No, I think it's right.
Np, no, no. Wait awhile.
If it weren't for Ji Hyo, I also almost wanted to just see it again.
Wait, wait. When we see it from here.
The dishes here are roughly...
Please open it!
What will happen if we open it?
-If you open it, we will add one more dish. -That's much better.
-What is much better? -Adding one more! If we create a plan of action...
Then the top part, you take the middle, and I take the bottom part.
Yes, let's do that. I will look at this part.
-Let's look! -Let's look!
Look carefully, how to lay it.
Yes.
Lettuce, this, that...
Radish, radish, spinach...
-This is the new dish. -Yes.
-We didn't see this. -Do we place this anywhere we please?
We had already placed this in just below.
Oh, really?
-It's really hard. -where should this be?
-Ah! I've forgetten it really quickly! -No, no...
-Lotus root. -Pass me that! Pass me that.
Ji Hyo, pass me that.
Like this, like this.
Just like this.
It's roughly this feeling.
Oh, it's roughly like this.
It seems like it’s correct?
Our strategy was right.
I'm going crazy.
Oh! The water is coming out!
There is water coming out! There is water coming out!
We can do it!
You have failed!
Very good!
Gwang Soo! Keep it up!
Hyung, I'm tired.
Gwang Soo, go for it! Persist!
It's too tiring!
We can do it! For IU's sake!
Now I'll give the second question.
In the tv series "Jewel in the Palace", what is the position of the character who is acted by Ji Jin Hee?
-Of course I know this. -Oh!Thank goodness, thank goodness!
King.
Ahhh!!
Are you kidding? How can it be "King"?
He was on a horse all day!
He rode a horse and ...
In the year 2012,what sign of the zodiac will the babies be born under?
-Snake! -No, no!
-It's dragon,born in the year of the dragon -It's not ?
This is ...
This position is correct .
This position is the correct one .
Correct?
Oh, this and that were  interchanged?
What is this ?
-Now what are you doing? -Really, what are you doing?
This is also not correct?
Let's take a look.
We have to look again. We have to look again.
-On top... dongchimi, spinach, lotus root. -Is that kimchi?
Dongchimi, spinach, lotus root.
Kimchi, doenjang...
-Kimchi, doenjang... -OK!
Kimchi...
Doenjang.
Dongchimi, spinach, lotus root.
Yours is gatkimchi.
-Also.. -The gatkimchi was here.
The newly added bean sprouts is here.
-Where is the gochujang? -Oh!Yes, bean sprouts!
Here, here.
Ok! We're done!
Done!
1, 2, 3, challenge!
Now we can eat!
Really...
Oppa, let's start eating!
-Ji Hyo, let's eat now. Quick, let's start eating.
This is really so tiring.
In here, according to one's tastes...
It's really delicious!
With some lettuce...
It's almost done, It's almost done!
The one whose clam opens first, do help the people beside you after that, got it?
OK.
Oh, algoo!
It opened, it opened!
We shouldn't have came here. Shouldn't have...
There's no one here. We shouldn't have come.
It's opening!
It's opening! It's opening!
Go for it! Go for it!
Oh! There's water!
It's opening! It's opening!
Chun Hee's clam, Chun Hee's clam...
Faster, help Chun Hee. Help Chun Hee's!
Chun Hee's clam still needs fanning.
The clam is scorched why is it not opening?
It's opening! It's opening!
It's opened! It's opened!
Good, pass!
Hyung, these are all well cooked.
It's too delicious!
This is no joke.
This oyster, when eaten together with kimchi, tastes especially great.
-It's too delicious! -It's really good.
Ah, freshly cut sea bass.
People say the fish head is the most delicious. It really is!
Although it was really hard work,
But the most important thing is where to go for our next destination?
That's right, we have a lot of choices now.
What shall we eat?
Ah, I really want to try everything here.
IU, what do you want to eat?
I would like...
Seasoned crab!
I really feel like eating seasoned crabs.
Do you like crabs marinated in soy sauce or spicy seasoned raw crabs?
-We'll say it together at the count of three! -1, 2, 3.
Crabs marinated in soy sauce!
I totally love crabs marinated in soy sauce!
Crabs marinated in soy sauce are delicious.
We will be reaching very soon.
Hello.
Hey! What is that?
Flip the crab shells placed on the tray
Every member must succeed in flipping it over once to succeed.
You have 5 chances.
Oh?
It's a little hard.
-Start from you. -Start from you.
Fighting!
Fighting! Fighting!
There's no problem.
Doing two is possible.
Actually if you listen to his voice, you will think he can do everything well.
Hahahahahahaha. Something like this, Hahahahahahaha.
This is nothing.
1, 2...
It turned one complete round exactly.
-Sang Wook, what are you doing? -Didn't you see?
-Is it that funny? -How can they both make one complete turn?
Ah, can you please do it properly?
Really, this person is so frustrating!
This person is so frustrating.
Sang Wook, come and stand here.
Please give us some water.
This is really funny.
This person is so frustrating.
Let's start from Ji Hyo this time -Let Ji Hyo start.
Ji Hyo, you will succeed.
Don't be nervous.
Done! Ji Hyo, good job!
Done! Ji Hyo, good job! Well done!
Ji Hyo, good job! Well done!
Ji Hyo did quite well.
What? What?
You’ll do it last.
Ji Hyo finally succeeded. How could you...
Both of you wasted two chances!
Be more serious!
-Hyung!Are you all done? -Oh! They are here!
It's IU, IU!
Ah!They are all IU’s manager!
I am the president. He is the hair stylist.
Hair designer!
Chun Hee is the on-set manager.
But the president's outfit is quite cute.
Let the Yellow Team take a look at the mission first.
All the members must flip the crab shells on the tray over to succeed!
You are left with two chances.
Do we have to flip it over at the same time?
The last chance.
Be confident! Be confident! Be confident!
Anyway, the Yellow Team definitely wouldn't do well.
1, 2, 3. Fighting!
But if it's like that...
Just do what you need to do!
Today's ending will be Ave Ji Hyo pulling Sang Wook hyung's hair.
1, 2.
That hyung really can't do anything well.
Yeah, what you said is ture.
This is actually quite a feat. I did the same thing twice.
It was the same just now.
No matter what, it is a fail, It is the Yellow Team's turn now.
-It will only be your turn after they fail. -Ah, so we failed for this turn.
-So we can sitll continue during the next turn. That's good.
Let's laugh at them together.
Let me explain it to everyone. There are 5 tires...
It doesn't matter if it is placed like this or the other way...
But you will have to flip it onto the other side to succeed.
Then the next person takes turn. When all 4 members succeed, the mission is successful.
Try laughing,try laughing.
-He is really good. -His stomach contains speakers, speakers.
Chanllenge!
We will succeed.
Let’s get ready to laugh at them!
Place them more towards the front.
Hyung there is no use saying it so just do it.
Doing that is useless.
You failed. For the first try, it's a fail.
It will be very awkward if this try fails.
You can do it.
-IU~ -Ah, don't do that.
This is quite awkward for you.
It is impossible to succeed, really.
1,2,3. Fighting!
I heard there is a team that is leading by a lot.
Oh, really?
So we will now remove one shell.
It will be too easy if there is only 1 shell.
-We need to control the strength used as well. -Yes.
Ah... jeez!
Let's me start thsi time.
Go to the back!
I’m going crazy.
I'm really going crazy.
-Let's do the cheer again. -Come. let's cheer.
No, no, excluding him.
He has to do some srtious reflection.
1,2,3. Fighting!
You try not doing it well .
I will get back at you.
Come over here. Oh!
Come over here. Oh! Sorry.
I get the trick.
That's it. Well done.
Come, Joo Sang Wook! Joo Sang Wook!
Sang Wook, do it well!
Don’t try to be funny! Don’t try to be funny!
I had never once tried to be funny!
I am doing it very seriously.
This is a game, game!
The crab is looking at you, right now. You have to do it well.
Ji Hyo...
You have to look at it closely.
Look at it closely.
1,2,3.
Sang Wook, you did it.
We are only left with HaHa.
-HaHa, we are believing in you. -HaHa, don't feel too burdened.
HaHa, don't feel too burdened, don't feel too burdened.
Hyung was joking with you just now.
I am really going crazy.
HaHa, you can definitely succeed. You can do it!
The one who controls time!
I'm sorry, I'm really sorry.
What are you doing? Even Sang Wook succeeded.
Let me complete it 1, 2, 3.
What are you good at?
What is this?
Ji Hyo, calm down!
This child is quite kind. Come over.
Come, challenge!
I didn't want to, but I have to take it off.
Giraffe!
This hyung really looks less inposing with the vibrant color.
HaHa, don't fell burdened.
Good!
Ah, bravo!
This hyung's voice is like drama tone.
I don't usually gets nervous easily.
Lightly, lightly.
1,2,3.
Laugh, laugh!
The team that succeeded can enjoy the meal now.
Ah, thanks.
I will just do it quickly.
You are too fast!
You did it! You did it!
He already did it twice.
Hyung, you can do it!
The last one.
1,2,3.
Ah, this restaurant serves really delicious food.
Ah, really, I'm about to go mad. It's too delicious!
The bingo grid shouldn't be 3 by 3.
It should be something like 10 by 10...
-Everyone enjoy your meal! -Be careful on your way!
Ah, it is really funny.
The father and daughter with two giraffes.
-We're here. -it smells nice.
Hello!
-Nice to meet you! -Hello, everyone!
After listening to the question,answer using 'O' and 'X'. If all of the members answer it correctly, you succeed!
-Ah, this is easy. -It's really difficult!
Answer the quiz correctly twice in a row to succeed.
The first question. Red bean soup is eaten on Winter Solstice.
Is Winter Solstice the coldest day of the year?
1,2,3.
No matter what, you failed the quiz.
What is the correct answer?
The correct answer is X.
Of course.
Ah, so this is correct?
I was looking at it like that.
-Ah, oppa, you should have done it properly! -I thought I have to look at X like this.
Anyway it is the fist try.
Ji Hyo, HaHa, do your best.
What is the correct answer? Please say it again. -Winter Solsticeis is the ...
the 2nd coldest day of the year.
Look, comrade Ha.
Comrade Ha.
Ah, comrade Yoo!
Hello to all my comrades!
Ah, really. It's alright, let's try again.
Can hyung tell me what is Winter Solstice?
I am curious about the next qusetion. Let's just forget this.
Come on and tell us.
It is not that I don't know.
Was the 'Diary in War' written by Admiral Yi Sun one month before the war?
1,2,3.
The correct answer is O.
That is why the 'Diary in War' is famous!
Right, I think I saw an article before, so...
The way I see it, you are good at guessing.
Really, you are good at guessing.
If this goes on, will we run out of questions?
-There 's more than enough. -Is that so?
Is Oh Dongoing island the biggest island in Yeosu?
1,2,3.
Hyung!
Comrade Joo, what are you doing?
-Dong island... -Didn't we go to Oh Dong island before?
It looks small to me?
Eh? Isn't it?
-The correct answer is X! -Ah! Really!
I really can’t work with you guys.
-It's not Oh Dong island? Then what is it? -Tell us, what is it?
I really don’t know about this!
I don't know what is the correct name of the island.
-Sang Wook's ability at guessing is really good! -If the biggest island is not Oh Dong island, then what is it?
What is the biggest island?
The biggest island is Dol San.
Ah, Dol San?
So is that Kat Dol San?
No matter what, you are really good at guessing.
His guesses are really accurate.
He answered all the questions correctly. We'll be fine if we just follow him.
The questions are a little too tough, it is too hard to guess.
-We'll give you some eaiser ones. -Yes.
I will give you a question regarding the Running Man members.
Then I am at an disadvantage.
Among the Running Man members is HaHa the shortest member?
1,2,3.
Isn’t it Song Ji Hyo?
Isn’t Ji Hyo a little taller?
I'm over 170 cm.
Ah, alright, we get it. We didn't know.
Ah, that is not an easy question!
You get up and we'll measure. Are you guys joking?
Ji Hyo is a bit taller?
Ah, I'm taller!
HaHa is taller.
It is obvious just by looking at the shoulders!
It is indeed a tough question...
Why is this a tough question?
I am really going crazy.
To us, it is really a very tough question!
Although it's unlikely but if this was a question on a high school examination paper,
It will really be the hardest question.
Is an airplane’s Black Box black in color?
1,2,3.
Of course it is!
It is X.
What color is it?
It is orange!
HaHa, think about it. Everyone has experienced this before,
If I choose the opposite of what I think is correct, the result is better.
Get it?
It hurts my pride. I can’t do it!
Does the deer’s antler shed and grow again every  year?
-1,2,3. -Ah, it is too easy!
This level...
I really don’t know...
-How can you not know... -The correct answer is O.
You bunch of fools!
Haven't you been to a Chinese Medicine clinic before?
Sorry, HaHa, Really.
They shed their horns every year.
If not, how do Chinese Medicine clinic get them?
So we have to start all over again?
Yes.
-If we carry on like this all the other teams will finish before us. -Ah, I am really going crazy.
Because the red bean is sweet, it is called 'sweet bean' in English.
We all answered X right?
The answer is X. It is called 'red bean'.
Do you need a passport to go to the Antarctica?
X!
The correct answer is X.
-I knew it will be like that. -Enough.
Thank you~
Oppa, how is it?
It's delicious.
This is the taste.
We succeeded at eating the red bean porridge.
Oh! The final mission is appearing!
What is it?
The grids are 4 by 4 with the numbers 1 to 16.
What is the meaning of this final mission?
Oh? What is this?
From now on, we have to wear our jackets.
Oppa, this is a race.
A race?
We have to complete that Bingo.
We have to complete that Bingo?
We have to find these numbers.
Ah! This is quite difficult.
Although we don't know where are the tags from number 13 onwards.
But Suk Jin hyung is number 3 and IU is number 1.
Who is number 5?
Me!
Ah! Ji Hyo is number 5.
Then what is our strategy?
First, we have to quickly find the numbers hidden on the island.
-Right, tearing IU's number tag won't be easy. -Because there are a lot of people protecting her.
Anyway, don't we have the preys from the savanna?
Gwang Soo...
Suk Jin hyung...
And Chun Hee.
We can immediately surround them and tear off their number tags.
We are setting off!
We are all targeting you.
Gwang Soo! Be careful, Gwang Soo!
No matter what we have to find the numbers first.
We must find the numbers first, before going further.
It is more advantageous for us if we find the numbers hidden on the island first.
Hold on, what are the other numbers that we can get hold of?
What are the numbers that we have?
Who is number 5?
Number 5 is Ji Hyo.
Who is number 9?
Jin Hee hyung.
Jin Hee hyung's difficult.
Who is number 8?
Uncle Jae Suk!
Number 10 is...
Number 10!
Number 10! Definitely number 10.
We are done.
We have to find number 15.
Attack number 10 Gary and number 8 Jae Suk.
Why not we exchange it with them after we find it?
Good.
It's coming it's coming!
But how are we going to find it on such a big island?
Search carefully.
How are we going to search for it on such a big island?
Captain! We are going up from there.
-Oh, so cool. -Hey, how exactly do we start searching on such a big island?
Exactly, aren't there any hints?
-We need hints to be able to find it. -We don't need it.
Ok, from now on, we will begin, a race on this island.
There are numbers on this island.
The team that completes their bingo first, gets to leave this island in the fastest and most outrageous way.
Ah, really?
We wouldn’t be taking a helicopter out or anything like that right?
Ah,it's the same as...ah, a submarine !
-First oppa, we, have numbers up till 12 right, we do? -Yes.
-We have to find 13,14,15 and 16. -Now, we have to find them quickly!
-Yes, find them quickly... -To get a bigger advantage.
Ah, greater odds of winning, greater odds of winning.
Hyung, let's hurry before the remaining teams arrive!
Hey, search quickly, let's search.
-Oppa, let's split up! -Split into pairs, search in pairs.
Go!
The village is very pretty.
The village is really pretty.
No, this is hidden rather...
Hey, this is so frustrating.
Is this just hidden somewhere or what?
In the past...
When I was in school and had to find something...
I could really find it.
I have to recall, the teachers' thinking.
Where they hid them.
Hey, where do we find this?
Hey, there isn't any, path on that side...
They’re here, they’re here, this is bad.
Why are they running, why run?
-To get, to tear off our numbers. -Do you see them running?
They’re coming to tear off our numbers right?
Ah, it can’t be.
Ok, are you giving using the mission once we’re there?
Eariler, what you receiced eariler was the mission.
Which is to complete your bingo.
No, wherever it's hidden, just find them unconditionally?
-We can go anywhere? -Seriously?
On this island?
Find them unconditionally?
The island, is extremely big?
This isn’t a joke.
So on this island, what's the most famous thing on this island?
That solar panel.
So there's definitely one there.
-Sun... -There's definitely one on this island's famous spot.
Take a look at, teh solar panel here!
Ah, but why is this so high so high up?
-Where do we go? Ah, this is really... -I'm really too tired now.
Oh, it's here!
What's over there?
Hey, we needed it. We found it.
-Ah, be careful it doesn't fall out! -This jacket doesn't have pockets.
Let's split up. You go there and take a look, I'll go this way!
Wow, how do we search here?
Hello.
Hey Gwang Soo.
Hyung.
Where are these things usually placed?
I've honestly never, found these things too.
I usually just watch it when it broadcasts.
Look at these. These things that appear out of nowhere might have something.
Something like this, like this. A place somewhat like this?
It should be in those places that you wouldn't notice.
-Those places that don't catch your eye at once. -Yes.
And they just stick out.
Isn’t that a helicopter there?
Oh, should we go see?
Wow, this is too cool.
Why would a helicopter be here?
This helicopter, couldn't this helicopter be on top of it, holding it down?
Then we’ll have to check below the helicopter?
Let’s lift it up once and see.
One Two Three!
Ah, this isn't it.
What about Number 8?
Oh, oh, the Blue Team's here, the Blue Team's here!
Oh, we've arrived.
Wow, we're here.
The Blue Team is about to start!
Hey, we have to take this off.
We have to find 13 to 16 right?
13,16.
Finding those that are nearer will be more advantageous.
Oh, it's quite all right.
Hyung, a chive field. Let's search in the chive field?
It might be in the chive field!
I think it's hidden.
I don't think it should be so easy?
It's not here, nothing here.
It shouldn't be here.
-Then what should we do? -Hyung!
Why, is there something?
Someone took something away from here.
Yes, it's a bit weird here but nothing's here.
You have to find the person and take it from him.
The person who took it?
We can take it from the person who found it?
-The person who found it. -Great
If we take person's number... Hey, does this make sense?
Where was it?
Someone took it!
Ah, there's a camera inside.
Ah, there's another kennel?
I feel, hey...it's not that we didn't see it...
Are you shooting a pictorial?
The ending!
Are we going there?
Of course we have to go.
We’re here already so why not?
Hyung, are you going up there?
I have to take a look!
What are you doing now?
Hey.
Kwon Ryeol, what are you doing?
If we turn here, if we turn here we'll definitely find something.
I, I should be doing it, why did you do it?
"Ohh". Why are you doing this?
Nothing. There's nothing.
Oh!
What is it?
What's that there, what's that there, what's that?
It wouldn’t be wild pigs right?
You should have been fliming me, why did you turn around and flim?
Let's go back first. Let's go back first.
I found it!
Don't lie.
What number is it?
Number 13!
Number 13 is here though?
I found it!
Number  13’s here though!
Hey, IU!
IU of Year 3 Class 2, come out!
I have something to say to you!
I like you!
Please wait for a year!
IU, I like you!
Ha!
Dong!
Hey, you're seriously...
Hyung is now... hey, I came out from the wilderness.
You’re here confessing your love to IU?
What are you doing here and not searching?
Hyung, I wrote this.
What is it?
Hey, I have one too.
-Why did you do this? -Hyung, it isn't for that.
Why?
The one who controls space.
Hey, it shoulf be like this.
The one who controls space!
Hey, you're really...
While I’m talking to you nicely, go to another team
Staying in this team doesn't have any meaning too.
You're really...
Help the team a little.
Do you want to go back in time to this morning?
I'm going crazy.
That’s our team?
Is that Sang Wook?
Yes.
Sang Wook!
Joo Sang Wook!
This is just like the training in the army.
Why are you coming over here?
Hey, Joo Sang Wook!
Just stay there!
-He's really werid, really strange. -He's really strange.
-Ah, he was over there so why is he running over? -Let's walk over to him.
Ah, hyung!
Wow, what?
Hey, you really ran over, from there?
Ah, I found it.
-Just over there. -What did you find?
This.
We'll have to go down.
So we'll just have to tear off Suk Jin hyung and IU's numbers.
Looks like Jin Hee can find it.
There should be a camera or something?
Where are they all?
Up there.
-Let's go up first... -Ok, they're up there now.
Hyung, hyung, they're over there.
Look at that yellow, Gwang Soo and someone from the Yellow Team.
The Yellow Team's over there.
Why is the Yellow Team there?
They're pointing at something.
Shall we create a commotion?
I found it!
Wee found two, two!
They should be super confused right?
-Who found it? -Gwang Soo found it.
If they find it we can just snatch it over.
We have to snatch it over. Who found it?
We have to see who found it.
Hey, it's the Red Team, it's Red Team!
-Where? -There, there!
Hyung, we've searched this side but there's nothing.
It's all been taken by the Yellow Team.
Why are four people walking together like this?
Seems like there's something here?
It could be appropriate later, appropriate.
Where's Ji Hyo, Ji Hyo?
You seem to have something in that pocket?
Ah, here, here, there's something here.
For me...
I've always been like this!
Hey, I'm really on the right side today, I am!
I'm really, lucky today.
That's not it.
Hey Dong Hoon.
Where are you going!!
Should I tears yours off, me?
We don't know anything.
Then we just won't tear yours off first!
-We'll see you later. -We'll see you later!
We'll see you at the top.
We won't let you off the next time!
Ji Ji Ji Ji baby baby.
Hyung, is he making fun of you now?
Oh, provoking... Jin Hee, he's making fun of you.
-Then what should I do? -Hey, call him a Grasshopper.
-Ah, how can I... -Try it, for once.
...Call the Nation Grasshopper a Grasshopper?
-It's the Nation's Grasshopper! -The Nation's Grasshopper.
The Nation's Grasshopper!
The Nation's Hopper, the Nation's Hopper.
The Nation's Hopper.
-Found anything? -Nothing.
Let's move together.
-Ah, together. -Yes, let's move off together first.
Now on that side, both Gwang Soo and Chun Hee are together.
Ah, it's most likely down there.
-I didn't see anything at all. -Nothing?
Are you tired?
I’m hungry.
Let's, take a look in here!
-Yi-yoo. -Yes?
Are you hungry?
-Huh? -Do you want to eat this?
Oh!
Deabak.
No, how could it, be here?
How do we find it here?
Ah, hiding it here is really...
Ah, I really want to find one.
Oh.
14.
The numbers found up till now are 13,14,16!
This is HaHa oppa's.
We can go this way.
Then what should we do now?
Run quickly.
Follow me!
Where has our team gone?
Gwang Soo and all, they're being chased over there.
Hey, do it quickly before Sung Soo comes.
Oh, there. They went there.
-Where? -The Red Team's there.
Jin Hee, put on your detective gloves.
Your detective gloves, the most useful gloves today.
Hey, what do we do?
-Hyung. -What is it?
Are you coming to tear ours off?
Hang on.
Hide, Yi-yoo.
Don't do this. Don't do this.
Hyung, I'm a courageous man today.
Yi-yoo, come here.
What are you saying?
Yi-yoo.
He's coming over!
Wait. They're here, Chun Hee hyung!
No, no!
Yi-yoo!
-Yi-yoo, stay where you are. I'm sorry. -No, no.
Run, run!
What do I do? Oppa, hurry!
Catch him!
Although we don't know which side will win, someone will tire out on each team.
-Right. -What are the numbers?
It's best to go when they're out of strength.
So when their fight's almost over...
-We'll go. -It'd be fine if I go during that time.
Oh, Ji Ge Liang! Ji Ge Liang!
This strategy is really like Ji Ge Liang.
Supposing that they will walk there after they fight,
Going up or going down..?
-Should be going down.. How about waiting down there? -Then let's wait for them down there.
-Zhuge Liang! -Under that.
Hyung! It seems like they will join forces.
Then let's observe awhile more.
Look at the atmosphere around them.
We have three teams.
Those people. Those people.
There are four people there, why not join forces?
We have three teams.
Although the winner is not known,
One of us should be the winner.
-Eliminate the Bule team first. The Bule team is too strong.
Gwang Soo, shout"Kim Jong Kook come out!" and run away.
Make him come down from there.
If you two do ti, they'll get angry.
They aren't talking about us right?
Are they talking to me?
Kim Jong Kook get down here!
Don't hide there! Get down here!
Kim Jong Kook come out! Are you scared of us?!
They already joined forces.
IU is at the back.
Kim Jong Kook come out! Are you scared of us?!
HaHa, HaHa, there's danger.
What are you doing?
They're fighting! They're fighting!
Let go!
I've torn it out!
Torn out! Torn out! Torn out again!
It's Gwang Soo!
That's why we said joining forces is not possible!
Gwang Soo got torn out first!
It was tore out at the same time! At the same time!
HaHa torn off Gwang Soo's tag first.
Afterward, Gwang Soo tore HaHa's tag out.
Followed by Sung Wook tearing out Ji Hyo's tag.
Quickly give your number to the Red Team, Gwang Soo.
We have a chance of winning!
Gwang Soo, faster. Hand it over to us.
-That team came down. -Faster!
That team is coming to us now! Quick!
Quickly! Hand it over!
Gwang Soo, where is it?
Sung Soo, you too hurry and leave!
Give me. Give me.
Hyung! That's 15 and 16. What's this?
What are you doing not escaping?!
Move back.
I'm number 8.
Number 3. Number 16.
Look at Jin Hee.
We only need to get one out of these two numbers.
This game will then end and we will win.
Why are you coming from there?! So troublesome!
Hyung, I saw you already.
Our team hasn't arrived?!
-Hyung was there. I saw it all. -Really?
-If you come up from there, you will be totally exhausted! -You suddenly talking to me like that...
You're making me embarrassed.
What do you all plan to do?
You guys seemed to have joined forces.
The moment we show our back, it's over.
Jin Hee hyung is coming! Jin Hee hyung is coming!
Ya! Ya! Ya! Jin Hee hyung!
Hyung! Even your shirt is torn!
Jin Hee hyung is coming! Jin Hee hyung is coming!
-Hyung! Let go! -Faster come over! -Faster come over!
He's here!
Number 10 either Gary or Jin Hee Number 11.
Sung Soo! Sung Soo! Faster!
Everyone go! Everyone go!
Both teams are safe..
Hey, not our team!
-IU what are you doing?! - This is a misunderstanding!
-IU what are you doing?!
IU is here.
It's not me. Oppa!
Our team only needs 10 and 11.
Who is number 10?
Either Gary..
Our team only needs 10 and 11.
Who is number 10?
Either Gary..
-Bingo! -Bingo!
-I love you all! -Bingo!
Red team Bingo.
The award for this success is to travel in a helicopter.
Goodbye everyone!
Hello!
Move to the back.
It's taking off.
HaHa! HaHa! I'm really scared!
Captain, hold on.
Taking the helicopter looks rather troublesome.
Feels like it is turning around on purpose.