- I'll solve the riddle.
- The time has stopped.
[Pass the mission to earn the hint.]
[Because the answer is contained within.]
[Think!]
[Carry it out!]
[The secret of the riddle shedding its
veil more and more they go!]
[The riddle race]
[6 a.m.]
[All the Running Men are asleep from
exhaustion from having seen their futures.]
[In the silence of the morning...]
[Appearance of ghosts?]
[Just who are these ghostly women?]
[Jae Suk deep in thought?]
[Jae Suk...]
[Another being behind him?]
[In this moment where he wishes that
he could have the use of Future Ddak-ji...]
[Back tumbling onto his bed
first thing in the morning.]
- Hello.
[Suzy and Yubin,
shining Gwangju born stars.]
[Suzy and Yubin who've come back to their
hometown to greet Running Man at 5 a.m.]
Scare all the scaredy cat Running Man members
awake and gather them up in the front lobby.
Song Ji Hyo...
What is this? Suzy?
And Yubin...
- We scared you, didn't we?
- Yeah, I was totally startled.
[Jae Suk with 10 years taken off of his life.]
[But anyways...]
[Opening up the curtains for the sudden
visit from his lady guests?]
It's so dark in here.
You could've just turned the light on...
Seriously... you weren't too happy about
the guests we had yesterday, but today...
[An expression that's
hard for him to keep hidden.]
- Have you had your breakfast?
- No.
[Seriously!]
[Shall we get on with scaring
some of the other members awake?]
[Putting on their disguise
in front of the door...]
[Come in, come in.]
[Deep asleep scaredy cat, Haroro.]
Ha Ha...
Wake up...
[As soon as he's scared awake, he's
worried about the way he's dressed.]
It's okay, we all know that you're
only in your underwear right now.
Ha Ha...
Get up... you know who this is?
[Who is it?]
- Hello.
[Even more shocking than seeing
ghosts come to life.]
He's more surprised to see Yubin and Suzy
here than seeing ghosts.
[Now that we think about it...]
[His mate, Suzy that he's been
longing for.]
[This is... a miraculous morning.]
I really am... really glad to see you.
You look way too happy right now.
[A happy grin on his face
to start off the morning.]
- Hurry up and get up.
- Where are your pants?
[Need to get dressed quickly to
go and wake up the next person.]
Jae Suk! Come on, don't do it!
[Older brother Hyuk
getting his little brother dressed.]
Jae Suk... Jae Suk...
Here, I'll hold this up.
- I'll take care of it.
- His underwear is showing right now.
[Just what is being done to him
in front of Suzy right now...]
Hey...
You're all dressed now.
Yubin, you can turn around now.
[Oh my...]
[Are those 'Mom pants'?]
They're not interested in your underwear.
Jae Suk...
High waisted pants...
You're not that important,
so hurry up and get up.
I'm not this type of a person!
[The next person to be awoken is...]
[Peacefully asleep Ji Sung.]
[Ready]
[A surprise visit to chase
all his sleep away!]
- Ji Sung...
- I knew something like this was coming.
- Ji Sung, you're so cute.
- This is Suzy and Yubin...
- Hello.
What the heck is this?
What the heck?
- Look at how shocked he is right now.
- Look at how much you brightened up.
I thought it was you and Jong Kook with
the wigs over your faces.
[Immediately brightening up?]
It's so nice to see you.
This is pretty nice.
The smile is coming off your face.
[Putting on his gentle face and demeanor.]
Are you shooting
a commercial or something?
This is the first time I've seen Ji Sung
using both his hands to wave and greet.
[Welcoming them with a double wave.]
You look like you're having
way too much fun with this.
This is the most fun I've ever had.
[This time, it's deeply asleep Jin Hee.]
Sorry, I was wrong.
- I'm sorry.
- What are you looking for?
[Ah... what do I do about this?]
[Did he really think they were ghosts?]
[But it's impossible to fix this situation.]
I'm sorry.
[Scaring the daylights out of him.]
[I'm so scared...]
[It's the sleeping Tiger's turn.]
[Not even startled by it,
but gets up from all the noise.]
What the heck is this? What's going on?
You totally startled me!
Gary... just calm down and take a look.
- It's Ji Hyo, right?
- Yeah...
- Hello.
- Don't do it... don't do it...
- Gary...
Out of everyone so far,
you look the worst.
[My morning look that I don't want
to show to the ladies.]
Yubin and Suzy are here right now.
What the heck is this?
It's a wet towel so the room
doesn't get too dry.
[Sensitive Gary with his wet towel...]
It's something I need to do
as a singer.
As a singer...
[Completes waking up the whole team.]
[A much different morning the one before.]
- Have you been well?
- Yes.
[That's enough now...]
This is what you wanted so badly...
and now she's here.
Why is it that I can't seem to
say anything?
Should I just let it go this week?
They say it's not cheating when
you're doing it front of other people.
[His natural instinct that's been
dormant?]
Have you been well?
You're the most pitiful.
- Why?
- I said, you're the most pitiful.
Because you have less than a month left
until your wedding now.
- It doesn't sound like you're happy about it.
- No, I'm happy.
I am happy, but I feel really bad for you.
[Gathering everyone up
in the lobby is now complete.]
There will be an announcement of
the teams in a little bit.
I'm sure everyone's pretty much
feeling the same way this morning.
It's the same as being in hell if you're not
teamed up with Suzy and Yubin today.
What about you, Ji Hyo?
Does it feel bad to hear him say that?
- It's okay. I'm like family.
- You have me, you fool.
Kang Gary can look so ugly.
- I will announce the teams.
- Okay.
[Fast forwarding to the future
after the teams have been announced.]
[Grumpy?]
[Celebrating?]
[A result that can be known
with a single glance.]
[The left of the lobby where
the celebration is going on.]
[Right of the lobby in solemn mood.]
Chang Ui...
You seriously have no luck, do you?
[For some reason, situation like this
seems fitting for him...]
Okay, today's race is, 'The Riddle Race'.
[The riddle race!]
Today is a race to solve the
ultimate riddle.
[Solve the ultimate riddle!]
[Complete the various missions
throughout Gwangju...]
[Earn clues to solving the riddles
by succeeding the missions!]
[If you gather the clues and solve the riddle
at the final location, then you win!]
[Riddle Race - Start!]
What is the bag you have there?
My Mother packed up some
things for us.
- What?
- What did she pack up for us?
[A bag full of snacks that Yubin's Mother
packed up for the members.]
[Snacks packed up with Mother's love!]
Seriously?
Thank you.
[Go to the Town Hall in Gwangju,
and find the Running Man landmark.]
[A sunshiny morning in Gwangju.]
- Are you tired?
- No, not at all.
- What about you, Gary? Are you tired?
- No, I'm not.
The moment I saw Yubin,
all my fatigue melted away.
- I really like Running Man.
- Really?
I've been watching it
from the very first episode.
That's when I was really ugly.
[The past days of calm Gary's expression
that used to be the center of visual shots.]
- Being with Suzy...
- A day with Suzy...
- Suzy...
- Is the best!
I want out of here!
It's been awhile since we've seen Suzy
looking embarrassed like that.
It would be so nice if everyone in the world
would shout that out loud with us.
I bet if we asked,
all the viewers will shout it out with us.
- With the viewers...
- Okay, get ready.
- Being with Suzy...
- A day with Suzy...
- Suzy...
- Is the best!
There's talk that Jin Hee tends to
joke around a bit...
[Bingo!]
- He used to be shy around new people...
- Yeah, he used to be like that...
[Who is?]
[Thanks to Suzy,
starting off to an enjoyable morning.]
Normally, this is the worst time of the day,
right after you get out of bed.
- I'm usually pretty groggy...
- Yeah, and annoyed easily.
I wish the time would stop right now.
Don't misunderstand this, okay?
[What the heck?]
Go Eun, I'm sorry!
But it's okay, it's Suzy!
- That team is already here!
- Yeah, all the others are already here.
[Gwangju Town Hall]
- Being with Suzy...
- A day with Suzy...
- Suzy...
- Is the best!
This is the first time I've ever seen
Jin Hee smiling so big like that.
Why don't you just go on being the MC?
- None of you had breakfast yet, have you?
- No!
- I'm hungry.
- Actually, we had our breakfast.
Yubin packed up a bag of snack for us,
so we've already enjoyed ours.
- And we're full from Suzy's love.
- Yes.
Do you want to fill up on
some insults?
We'll now have our morning breakfast
mission.
Just to make it more delicious,
we'll have a morning workout.
The name of the first topic is,
'The Queen's morning workout'.
[A relay race while
giving the Queen a piggy back ride.]
[Complete it within allotted time,
and you'll pass the race!]
No problem.
I have experience in this already.
- Since Yubin is so light...
- Of course, this isn't even a race.
Do you all see the Start flag
behind you?
The race will start
when that button is pressed.
Everyone will start off at the same time
after the button is pressed
and you have to go a full round
outside of the yellow boxes
and come back to the finish line and press
the button again, and it'll all be timed.
But... while your Queen is on your back
if you drop her along the way
then you will be disqualified right away.
And sooner you complete the race,
better clue you will gain to solve the riddle.
[Coach Kook starts his lesson plan.]
And if you hand her off to me there,
I will come and finish the race.
Over here, over here...
You start over here
and run down to that point.
No, over there and there...
why aren't you guys getting this?
[Screaming Coach Kook]
See? There are three points out there!
Why are you being so sensitive?
This is a great day!
Come here and take him away!
[Ji Hyo's team is feeling as though they're in
hellish training camp, rather than a fun race.]
You think you're a coach for
some sort of a national team?
I seriously need to start exercising my legs.
Since I barely workout...
[Jae Suk secretly hiding behind
Big-nosed brother!]
Ready... set...
Hey, be more careful...
Hey! You should wait until I'm ready.
You should've waited until I'm ready.
Faster! Faster!
[Big-nosed brother hurrying along with
a different team member, Jae Suk.]
[Kicking out of rage?]
[Big-nosed brother having wasted
his energy for nothing.]
I... I was thinking that Ji Hyo's thighs...
I was thinking that she must have
a very sturdy lower body...
[Ji Hyo's team's
authentic attempt at the challenge.]
- He's quick...
- He's really fast!
He just threw her.
[The weak link Chang Ui's run.]
I think they might do it... they might win.
[Ah... what a waste...]
[A big laughter from weak link
Chang Ui's tumble on the grass.]
He's just like me...
- What the heck is his deal?
- What are you doing?
Chun Hee, are you watching this?
I thought we were going to win this.
- Pil!
- Chok! Cross!
Kwang Soo... Kwang Soo...
[They do say that you start to
act like your friends...]
I had a feeling that he was
going to fall.
Kwang Soo's looking really nervous
right now because of Chang Ui.
[Worrying he may get his spot taken away after
having worked on it for two and a half years.]
-Fighting!
- Fighting!
[The Giraffe's tall back.]
She's climbing on there like a horse.
I thought she was getting on
top of a horse.
[A camel riding experience in Gwangju.]
I'm ready!
[Their plan? To run alongside together?]
[Nice! Nice!]
Arm! My arm!
[Giraffe's arm having being caught
while passing her off to Ha Ha.]
[Fail...]
- My arm was caught...
- I want to give her a piggy back ride!
But it wasn't bad.
Going from tall to short was a good move.
Doing it in reverse wouldn't have worked.
[Wait...]
Jae Suk, how about this plan?
The last relay person can stand right
next to the buzzer and hit it right away.
[The third person lying in wait
right next to the buzzer?]
[Since it takes time to pass off the Queen...]
[Proposing that the last person to wait right
in front of the buzzer to make the pass to!]
Why don't we try as you suggest?
I'll stand right here.
Right here... I'll just stand here.
[Yubin's team- Start!]
[Even though the runners have to run
further because of the plan...]
[It's still a great plan if you think
about the time it saves.]
[Handing off to second runner, Jae Suk.]
[It's still not even 12 seconds
on the clock!]
Jae Suk, run!
I think they're going to press the button
as they make the pass at the end.
- Almost there, almost there...
- He's really fast!
[At this speed...]
[Jae Suk heading to the finish line!]
[If he can pass her off to Ji Sung,
and the button is pressed!]
[Not able to pass her off correctly
at the very last minute.]
[However, it's a great record!]
- Wow... look at the time.
- That's a good plan.
That's a great plan.
There are no specific methods, right?
She just needs to be on our backs?
Okay.
[Placing the last runner, Big-nosed brother
right in front of the buzzer.]
Widen out your legs a bit more,
and stick out your behind more.
This is a good plan.
We can do it this time.
[Team Ji Hyo's attempt.]
Ready...
Why is he so wobbly?
[Weakling Chang Ui, turning his first corner.]
[Ace Ji Hyo's shocking jump pass!]
- That was quick.
- That was fast!
That's great! We're at 10 seconds!
Hurry!
[Down to the finish line!]
[Team Ji Hyo may win this!]
[As long as she can be passed off to
the last runner, Big-nosed brother!]
[Ah... he just pressed the button...]
[That was within 20 seconds...]
No, she has to be on your back.
On your back.
- Why don't we give it a try?
- Okay.
Right here... right in front of it.
[This time, the plan is to pass her off
the moment they start the race.]
[Taking a little longer
to make the first pass.]
[Now rushing to the third runner.]
[A jumping pass to the third runner, Gary!]
My arm is caught!
[Jae Suk having to run alongside them.]
[Fail...]
[If only his arm hadn't been caught,
it could've been possible...]
- Then I'll wait like this.
- Okay, that's good.
Then who's back am I going to
get on first?
Come here. Climb on my back here.
[Step on his back like that?]
[Getting ready to start off in a position
that would be easiest to pass her off.]
Let's just see how it goes.
[The Giraffe's run... and Jin Hee too?]
Faster! Move faster!
Hey, Jin Hee, why are you running?
[Coach Ji encouraging on the Giraffe.]
No, that's not going to work.
That's too difficult.
Nice! Nice!
[Getting close to the finish line!]
[Right in front of the finish line!]
[Pass her off to the final runner Jin Hee!]
Press it!
[As long as they can press the button!]
[19.80 seconds! Pass!]
[Team Suzy's plan worked!]
[I came up with that plan...]
[Team Suzy is the first
to pass the morning mission!]
- Being with Suzy...
- A day with Suzy...
- Suzy is...
- The best!
[Being handed a clue
regarding the ultimate riddle.]
You can put the hint right here
when I give it to you.
And gather up all your clues to put together
and figure out the answer.
- Do we have to choose?
- Yes.
Should we go with gold?
It looks like gold, silver and bronze.
Suzy, you pick.
[Team Suzy chooses the silver envelope.]
[Time to decide on the next location.]
[Since it's plus one, they're
moving onto Dduk-galbi restaurant!]
I'm ready!
[Team Ji Hyo is also going with the
method Team Suzy used.]
[Mr. Capable passes her onto himself
right away and gets on the way!]
[Just flinging her onto his back?]
[Incredible strength!]
[And Ji Hyo for sticking onto him
is pretty incredible too!]
Look at them...
How can he run with a person
hanging off of him like that?
[Barely 12 seconds in!]
[The last runner, Chang Ui,
who's standing in front of the buzzer!]
[18.04 seconds. A success!]
Are you okay?
I think you broke the world record.
This is the first time I've ever
seen him collapse like this.
Jong Kook... you really were amazing!
I could have been a little faster...
[Being handed their clue
to the ultimate riddle.]
What is this?
Is this gold and bronze?
I bet there was silver too,
looking at how the colors are.
- Why don't we go with the gold?
- Okay, let's take the gold.
Spin the wheel.
And what do we throw at it?
[Team Ji Hyo gets plus two,
so they move on to the market!]
- Being with Suzy...
- A day with Suzy...
- Suzy is...
- The best!
- This is awesome.
- Let me see the hint card.
[Inside the silver envelope is...]
[Just a zero?]
- So what is this riddle?
- We have to solve it.
I wonder if it's like
zero minus one,  plus one?
Zero...
[With merely one hint,
it seems impossible to...]
[Team Ji Hyo's hint is five.]
So we have to win other clues to
solve the riddle...
[Are there advantages or disadvantages
to the color of the envelopes?]
What does the number two mean?
Don't you think it would have
something to do with Gwangju?
[A riddle that has something to do
with Gwangju?]
For example, something to do with
2002 World Cup?
[What could these mean?]
- They're all Dduk-galbi restaurants.
- This place is so big.
I wish I could take some home.
[Being able to taste the Dduk-galbi
that just melts in your mouth...]
- Here it is.
- There it is, there it is.
There's the landmark.
[Discovers the Running Man Landmark.]
This is unbelievable...
Can we just eat this?
This looks so good...
it's driving me crazy.
I'm seriously about to go crazy here!
This is all thanks to Suzy... seriously.
Hello... hello.
[Team Yubin also arrives.]
Hurry! Before they get here!
Seriously...
just the sight of you makes me angry.
- Wow... look at this!
- Wow!
Do we have to answer questions?
[But I'm hungry...]
If you want to eat the delicious food
in front of you, you have to pass a mission.
[In order to eat the delicious Dduk-galbi,
they must pass a mission first!]
[Ah... the Dduk-galbi is right
in front of their eyes!]
[Dduk-galbi restaurant- spatula OX quiz]
[You must answer two answers correctly
in a row to succeed the mission!]
Since you were first to arrive,
Team Suzy gets to go first.
The other team has to wait.
Here's your question.
[In the movie, Introduction to Architecture,
Suzy was a Cellist? One, two, three!]
[Ha Ha picks 'O'?]
[Introduction to Architecture:
Suzy's character was a piano major.]
You haven't seen
Introduction to Architecture?
And you call yourself a fan of Suzy's?
I'm so disappointed!
How could you...
- How could you not have known that?
- Suzy was a piano major.
[Anyways, Team Suzy fails]
Okay, Lambada...
Lambada means, the feel of the rhythm.
One, two, three!
[Everyone picks 'O'?]
What kind of a discussion are you having?
And also, I'm giving you a warning.
[Warning! Talking is prohibited!]
That's not the right answer?
In Portuguese,
the meaning of Lambada is...
- Seduction?
- Passion?
Passion? Love?
- And hope!
- Dreams?
Our everything... our future.
- Lambada means, the whip.
- Really? The whip?
Lambada, lambada, that's...
Whip! Whip!
- Okay, I'll give you an easy question.
- Easy question!
Please give us an easy question.
It's a very easy quote question.
Quote question?
I should be answering that...
Gary... Gary's really good with quotes.
['Know thyself' is Shakespeare's quote.
One, two, three!]
[What?]
[The correct answer is a very famous
quote by Socrates.]
- What are you doing?
- Why are you joking around, Suzy?
- She's just full of jokes.
- JYP... make her study some!
She really didn't know?
- JYP...
- Seriously, JYP...
- She was just trying to be funny!
- Yeah, you really got us with that one.
- I was just trying to be funny.
- Of course, you were.
Putting the food in front of us like that...
[Dduk-galbi is getting
colder by the second...]
The next question is Gwangju related.
[Dduk-galbi was originally created for a
King who had troublesome teeth?]
Oh my goodness...
- The correct answer is... 'X'.
- X?
Yubin was the only one
who got the correct answer.
I was just holding it up because
I didn't know what to do...
[Dduk-galbi was created for Kings as they're
not supposed to tear anything off the bone]
So it's pretty much the same thing.
Why do you keep putting in little
pitfalls within the questions?
But Ji Sung... he's a King too!
Ji Sung and we are...
[Team Suzy's turn]
[The main character in 'Hamlet'
is the King of Netherlands?]
- 'X'!
[Correct answer]
[Hamlet was the King of Denmark.]
Good job, Suzy!
[Just one more question!]
[So what country is he from?]
[Tango question?]
Tango originates from Argentina?
- 'O'!
- Without a doubt, it's from Argentina!
The reason being is that
Marco used to talk about it all the time.
[Argentina native, Marco
used to talk about it a lot?]
Please bring us some silverware!
One more question?
You want us to answer one more?
- What are you doing?
- What do you think you're doing?
[Just what is the correct answer?]
[Correct!]
Chopsticks... chopsticks.
Please warm this up for us.
- Dduk-galbi...
- We get to eat!
This is so delicious.
- This is insanely good.
- It's really good.
[Steamy bone soup is also served!]
[The scent is wafting throughout
the room.]
[Is Jin Hee trying to taunt them?]
Ouch, that's hot!
[Jin Hee's unstoppably annoying jokes.]
- What are you doing right now?
- I'm sorry.
- This is good.
- Jin Hee's just like us now.
Here's your next question.
Ji Jin Hee is older than Jung Joon Ha?
One, two, three!
Seriously...
What year was Jin Hee born in?
They're the same age.
- I knew they were similar.
- Really?
- You could have told us since you're here.
- But this is so good. I was busy eating.
Why don't you give it a try?
It's really delicious.
[What? A lettuce wrap?]
I'm not allowed to give it to him, right?
I'm sorry.
He really is getting on my last nerve.
Since we're already on the subject,
here's another question about Ji Jin Hee.
I don't really know much about this guy.
Jin Hee... all he's doing right now
is getting me angry.
[A mental battle with Jin Hee.]
- Here's your next question.
- Do you see how angry Ji Sung is right now?
- Right now, he is...
- He's not even talking anymore.
When this morning, he was waving
at the girls with both hands...
I'll give you a really easy question.
Give us a question like
'What is one plus one'.
Snakes have two tongues.
One, two, three!
[What? Gary answers 'O'?]
Isn't it split like this?
Come on, let me eat!
Aren't their tongues split like this?
There's two! Like this!
[So they only have one?]
In the movie, 'Shim Chung Jeon',
the place Shim Chung falls into is Yookgaksu?
We're positive of this one.
[Correct answer]
Then if Gary answers it correctly,
we'll accept it.
[If Gary gets the answers,
it will be accepted.]
Indangsu.
Didn't I answer this correctly once
on Running Man a long time ago?
Back then, I said, Indangsu.
I remember it.
- Gary... I knew it.
- Yes.
If you answer one more question correctly,
then you'll get to eat your meal.
It's a question about bugs.
I'm sure it's about grasshoppers.
[The reasons why crickets cry
is because they're hungry?]
- X!
- I guess they're going to get to eat now.
[Correct]
- Let's eat now.
- Yubin and Ji Sung, let's eat.
Hand me your paddles.
Aren't you curious about the
reason at all?
I'm sure they're looking for
their mates or something.
Great job. Enjoy your meal.
[Now everyone can enjoy the delicious
Dduk-galbi together.]
[Time to receive their clues
for the ultimate riddle solving.]
- Yes, I understand.
- Hey, let Suzy pick it.
[Team Suzy picks
a different envelope this time.]
- Since we picked the silver one first...
- Good job. You did good.
- I'll spin it this time.
- What are you doing? Let Suzy do it!
What am I? Just a scarecrow?
- Just stand over there like this.
- Come stand over here, Suzy.
The way I see it, it's like the Wizard of Oz!
And you're the Scarecrow.
[Plethora of nicknames for him.]
Should I spin it now?
You're such a great spinner!
[Move plus two!]
[And the hint Team Ji Hyo gained
after passing the mission in the market is?]
I wonder if it means that there's something
that's greater or better than two?
[What could this be?]
I have absolutely no idea.
I wonder if it's part of a formula?
It's like math problems that I used to do.
Is it something like, it's greater than zero
but smaller than five?
- Find something greater than two?
- Two time two is four?
- Four?
- Could it be something like that?
What could this mean?
- Does it mean that two is greater?
- Two is greater...
Could it mean, teeth?
(Teeth and two are both pronounced the same)
[It seems as though they're still
in need of some more hints.]
- How do you like placing first again?
- I love it.
Should we lose a bit to make it interesting?
- If it's something you want...
- What is it that you want?
- I would like to enjoy it as we go along.
- Shall we? Let's do it that way.
- Let's find some ice cream somewhere...
- Yes, that sounds good.
Let's grab some ice cream on our way.
[Gwangju 'D' Elementary School]
The Elementary School is right up there.
- It's the elementary school I went to.
- Seriously?
And that's the middle school that I went to.
We're heading to my elementary school!
I'm a little nervous.
- What do I do?
- You must be a little nervous.
- There it is!
- Nice!
Hello!
Here's your next mission.
[Elementary school mission
is inside the envelope?]
Hello, Running Man.
I have curly hair, and I wear glasses.
And I have a scar on the left side
of my face.
And I'm pretty popular amongst my class.
Please come and find me.
- This sounds pretty easy.
- He wears glasses and has curly hair?
And a scar on the left side of his face?
[Where is this child?]
- This is...
- This is her Alma Mater.
- You have to find this student.
- A student?
Hello, Running Man.
I have the same name as the most
beautiful celebrity in our country.
I'm going to be someone who shines our
country like my Suzy when I grow up.
I have a pretty flower pin in my hair,
and always wears a cell phone pouch.
- A hair pin? That's the big clue.
- The clue?
Her name must be Bae Suzy.
[Since the letter says it's the prettiest
celebrity in the country, her name is Suzy?]
Since she wears a cell phone pouch,
I bet she's at around the third grade.
Here is your next mission.
Please read it quickly.
Look at this.
[If Jae Suk doesn't find me...]
We have to look for this kid?
You have to find him and
bring him back here.
If he's in the lower grades...
that means third grade or lower.
That's right...
and he doesn't have a front tooth.
And he has short hair up in the front...
It's probably a little boy right?
Since he called Jae Suk 'Hyung'?
[Find the students - Start!]
[The filming was possible thanks to the
cooperation of the students and the faculty.]
- Suk Jin, let's split up.
- Okay, let's split up.
Okay, we'll start over at that end.
- What grade is this?
- This is second grade.
[Enthusiastic greeting from the students
at the news of a visit from Running Man.]
Hi! Study hard!
Hello, Teacher.
I'm sorry for interrupting your class.
Hi!
[Wow! It's Mr. Capable!]
I have to find a certain student,
so may I please take a look around?
Does anyone in here have curly hair?
- Curly hair?
- Hi!
You have curly hair!
But you don't have glasses on.
Okay, bye!
Hi!
Here... let me see you.
[He does have curly hair but the glasses...]
Your glasses are at home?
Hello.
I'm sorry for interrupting your class.
Hi...
- You all know who this is, right?
- Yes!
You know that she went to
this school, right?
Yes!
- Hi, guys!
- You have to help us, okay?
Anyone here who wears a cellphone pouch?
- What is your name?
- It's Moon Ji Won.
Ji Won?
[She said her name was the same
as a pretty celebrity's name...]
Anyone with a pretty flower pin in her hair?
So it's someone different than ours.
And anyone else with the name Suzy?
- Excuse me?
- Anyone in here named Suzy?
There's no one by that name in here?
That's too bad...
Hello, Teacher.
- Hi!
Hey, guys...
[A child that stands out to them right away?]
Did you write me a letter?
[Missing his front teeth!]
- No...
- You didn't write me one?
I think someone in here wrote me a letter...
[Just which one of them wrote the letter?]
- Who wrote the letter?
- Did anyone write the letter?
- Hi.
- Not here... he's not in this class.
Everyone has their teeth.
Everyone has their front teeth in here.
- Hi, guys!
- Hi!
Everyone show me their teeth!
[Checking their teeth?]
Oh! There's one here! Wait a minute...
- I think it looks like him.
- It does look like him...
[He does look like the picture
in the letter...]
Do you think that this picture looks like you?
- No.
- No?
[Even though he does look similar,
it's not the student they're looking for.]
- Sparrow.
- Peep, peep.
- Duck?
- Quack, quack.
- Giraffe?
- Traitor!
What are you guys saying?
No! No!
[Playing around with the weak
Giraffe's name tag.]
- If you tear it off, I'm out!
- Are you out then?
If you tear it off, then I'm out!
Hey!
What are you doing in here?
- It's Mr. Capable!
- Hey, guys!
Let's go... let's get out of here quickly.
[Kkuk's shocking popularity!]
Hi!
Hello, Mr. Capable!
You can't oust me like that!
- Stop joking around.
- Guys... hang on a second...
[Clumsy Chang Ui being measured
with a tape ruler?]
Wait... calm down.
Okay, let's all concentrate.
[Mr. Capable getting surrounded by kids.]
[Everyone is interested in the name tags.]
- I'm looking for someone.
- Who? Who are you looking for?
[Let's all take turns
tearing off the name tag!]
Glasses... he has glasses on,
and has curly hair!
- Ha Ha?
- No, it's not him.
Put it back.
You have to stick it back on.
Stick it on... stick it on.
That's enough. Stop it now.
[Ah... just where are these kids?]
- Hello, please excuse us.
- I'm sorry.
- Hi, guys...
- Look!
[She looks like the drawing in the letter!]
- Hi... what's your name?
I have the same name as the most
beautiful celebrity in our country.
[Same name as a beautiful celebrity?]
What's your name?
[And this student's name is?]
- Kim Tae Hee.
- Kim Tae Hee?
[Kim Tae Hee!]
[Found her! Tae Hee!]
Your name is Kim Tae Hee?
Wait... this is a cellphone bag, right?
- What is this?
- A cellphone bag?
- We love you!
- Tae Hee! Tae Hee!
[They really found her!]
[Kim Tae Hee - Six years old]
- Hi!
- Hello!
I'm looking for someone...
Glasses and a scar on the face...
[Getting a gut feeling
the moment he sees him?]
Hey!
Hi! I think it's him!
Let's go!
[Song Sung Won - 10 years old]
Hi...
[Could it be him?]
- Show us your teeth.
- Did you send me this letter?
[He looks just like the drawing!]
Did you draw this picture?
He says he did!
Okay... let's go. Let's go.
[Lee Seo Joon - Eight years old]
Guys, we'll be right back!
Bye!
It looks like they're already up there.
We're the last ones again.
- Let's go.
- Okay, let's go.
[There's no need to go this far...]
[I'm not a little kid!]
Here's your next mission...
Elementary Milk Box Jaeji
[The team who kicks the most number
of milk boxes in wins.]
[However, children can use their hands.
Each team just gets one chance!]
[Practice time]
- Here, give it a try.
- Good job!
[Oh... Tae Hee's a great thrower!]
Lee Kwang Soo!
[A crowd of students who have gathered
outside to watch the mission.]
Winning team is our team!
[Team Suzy is first up!]
[There's just one opportunity!]
[Using the advantage of
being the Alma Mater...]
[What the... a miss]
Bae Suzy!
- No, you can let her go one more time.
- That wasn't fair. This is her Alma Mater.
- This is her Alma Mater?
- Yes, this is her Alma Mater.
[Since her foot never touched it,
she gets another chance?]
[All the Junior are watching...]
Guys, cheer Suzy on!
[Senior, fighting!]
Thanks!
Challenge!
[A nice kick!]
[But the direction is...]
[That's too bad!]
Lee Kwang Soo! Lee Kwang Soo!
Enough! Enough!
[Too much of the cheer is putting
too much pressure on him.]
[Team Suzy's Kwang Soo taking
the challenge.]
This is the moment that battle cry
turns into jeers.
- Okay, you just throw it in there.
- That's right.
[Tae Hee's turn]
Just throw it in there.
[Rule: Kids can use their hands to throw]
[Tae Hee easily succeeds in scoring!]
[Team Suzy succeeds getting one in!]
[Ha Ha also fails!
Lastly, it's Jin Hee's turn!]
Challenge.
[Too bad! Hit the camera and bounced out!]
[Team Suzy succeeds getting one in!]
You go first.
Seo Joon, where are you going? Come here.
[Seo Joon's turn at the challenge.]
Slow... take it slow.
[The look of concentration!]
[Seo Joon with the glint in his eye!]
[Ah... too bad!]
Nice! Nice!
- That's too bad...
- It's okay! You did great!
It's okay.
We just need to get three in.
[Yubin's turn at the challenge!]
[Ah... too bad.]
- That was looking good...
- It almost went in.
- That really is too bad.
- We need to get one in and we can win.
[Inciting a cheer from the crowd?]
Yoo Jae Suk! Yoo Jae Suk!
[More! More!]
[A roaring cheer from the crowd!]
Louder!
[With the roaring cheer from
the students at his ear...]
[With his knee!]
[Huh?]
[It almost hit Kwang Soo as the backboard
and made it in the basket.]
- You should've nudged it in!
- Why would I nudge it in?
Why isn't it going the way we want it to?
Okay... take your turn.
- Challenge!
- Challenge.
[Team Ji Hyo - Starting with Sung Won]
[The milk carton heading
in the right direction!]
Great job!
[Team Ji Hyo's Sung Won
succeeds in getting his in!]
It went in! It went in!
[Ji Hyo's turn]
Fighting!
[Kicking the milk carton precisely!]
[Success!]
[The amazing Blank Ji!]
[This is maddening!]
[Team Ji Hyo earns another hint!]
Suk Jin, will you hand me the hint?
[The hints Team Ji Hyo currently have.]
As far as the numbers go,
there's only zero, five and two.
- Five is...
- Five is greater than zero and...
It's a given, but...
But two is less than zero?
Soowon's fried lettuce.
This is unbelievable today.
Whatever we end up doing,
at least we're eating delicious food.
We're hitting up all the eateries
on our way.
But... I looked at it earlier,
and it was a dud.
- It's a dud?
- It's a dud.
[The hint they received this time is a dud!]
[Still not a clue as to what it is...]
Since the riddle is supposed to be
solved at the end...
I think solving the riddle is...
To be honest, I have no idea.
I'm even more confused with
this new clue.
[The more hints they gain,
the more confusing it's getting!]
Do you think... it could be
a name to a certain project?
- Like a name to a piece of work?
- So we have to find what that work is?
- Is Running Man normally this hard?
- This is how it can be at times.
But it seems even more difficult today.
[Just what is
the correct answer to this riddle?]
[Team Ji Hyo arrives at the
amusement park!]
[Just what is the mission
that awaits them here?]
[Amusement Park - Disco Step counter]
[Get on the amusement ride with the
counter strapped to your ankle.]
[If the total count for the team is
less than 300, you succeed the mission!]
[Try not to move while being on
a shaky amusement ride!]
[Team Ji Hyo getting on the ride!]
This is going to be really hard.
[The counter is strapped to their ankle!
If the total count is less than 300, success!]
Press the reset button after you put it on.
Yeah, don't press the reset button
until you have it on.
[Have to save every last count!]
[Starting the disco ride!]
[The stop counter around their ankle!
Will they be able to endure not moving?]
[Moving faster and shaking around more!]
Lift up your leg! Hold your leg up!
[Unlike just seeing it,
it can't be easy withstanding it...]
[Team Suzy also arrives
at the amusement park!]
They're already here.
[Getting an idea of what's coming from
seeing what the other team is doing.]
We can do it, we can do it!
[Big-nosed brother!]
[Ultimately, not being able to withstand it,
he ends up break dancing on the floor.]
[Ji Hyo is clinging on...]
[Head banging?]
[Ah! Big-nosed brother's step counter!]
[I'm... ruined!]
[At least others need to stick it out!]
[Disco ride - Stop!]
[Will the four people's combined count
ne less than 300?]
- 125.
- I have 125!
[Mr. Capable's count is 125]
[Ji Hyo's count- 142]
[Chang Ui's count- 110]
I have 182.
[If 300 or less, it's a success.
Team Ji Hyo fails with 559.]
[Confident Team Suzy's turn.]
Sit on it... sit on your leg.
[Coach Jin Hee. Pull up the
leg with the counter on it?]
- Jin Hee, are you sure?
- I'm sure!
I'm positive! If anything,
it's your right leg receiving the shock.
[Starting the shake the moment it starts!]
Lift up your foot! Lift up your foot!
Lift up your foot!
[No matter how much it shakes...
keep your foot off the floor!]
[It's easier said than done...]
[Now what in the world is he...]
[My counter! It fell off!
Wait... the counter fell off!]
[Giraffe's counter falls off!
He needs to get it back on his foot!]
[Why does things like this always
happen to the Giraffe?]
[Oh my goodness...]
Wait! My counter!
[The Giraffe's untiring breakdancing.]
[The disco ride finally comes to a stop!]
This shook more than usual.
[What is the combined count
for Team Suzy?]
10! 10! 10!
[Jin Hee's total count is 10!]
Jin Hee is no joke.
10?
[Ha Ha's total- 109]
[Suzy's total count- 137]
You currently have 256 and if
Kwang Soo has less than 44, you succeed.
Kwang Soo, what is your count?
198...
[Team Suzy fails with 454.]
I found 500 won.
[On the other hand, Team Yubin is...]
- We're here...
- Fried lettuce...
Wow...
so this is the fried lettuce place.
[King of snacks,
spicy rice cakes is a given.]
[And the fame of Gwangju,
fried lettuce.]
This is fried lettuce.
- With the delicious food in front of you...
- We should eat then.
[You have to receive your mission.]
[Blow the tissue with your mouth
and pass it to the person next to you.]
[If you safely get it in the basket without
dropping it on the floor, you succeed!]
Ah... the tissue?
[Get it in the goal by blowing the tissue.]
[You must get five tissues in within
one minute by blowing it in!]
If you can get it to me,
I'll run over and blow it in!
The tissues that you use during the game
will have to be used by you later on.
Ready... set... go!
[It's falling!]
[Huh?]
It's not on the ground yet!
[It's still hanging on the leg!]
[Since it hasn't fallen on the ground yet,
they will be given the chance.]
- It's not on the ground yet!
- Hold still. I'll blow it up.
[He got it up!]
[Ah... ultimately, it fell to the ground.]
[With them fighting for a while,
20 seconds have already passed!]
[Rushing to get the second tissue!]
[This time, it falls on his shoulder!]
[Barely gets one in!]
[They have to succeed in getting four
more in during the time they have left!]
[Jae Suk using his foot in haste.]
[They got it!
Succeeds in getting two sheets in!]
[After merely getting two sheets in,
the time on the clock is almost out!]
[Time over!]
[But for their first try,
it was a very good attempt!]
I think I got it figured out.
[Going right into their second attempt.]
[Gary's got the feel for it now!]
[Oh my... having after done so well...]
I got it... I got it!
You have to blow on it fast!
[This time, blowing with all his might
all on his own again!]
Jae Suk, I figured it out.
[Tossing it lightly to Ji Sung.]
[Then Gary will receive it and then... huh?]
[Jae Suk receives it
and it lands on his lips?]
[A kiss?]
[Barely keeping the tissue alive!]
[If they're careful with it,
they may get it in the basket?]
[Too bad!]
[By trying to move the basket again!]
[Time over!]
I'm getting angry!
Everyone...
I'll give you the option of getting
three in within one minute...
or getting one in within 25 seconds.
One within 25 seconds.
[Simultaneously shouts out
one within 25 seconds.]
- Isn't that a given?
- One, two, three! One within 25 seconds.
[On the other hand,
at the amusement park.]
[Still riding the mighty Disco ride!]
[Putting in their best effort to lessen
the impact on their leg.]
[Feeling like death...]
[This is killing me.]
[This person is about to pass out.]
[Disco ride - Stop!]
[Will the four of them combined
be less than 300 this time?]
[Chang Ui's total count, 120.]
[Mr. Capable's count, 49!]
[Ji Hyo's count, 81.]
[Current total is 250.
As long as Suk Jin has 50 or less...]
[Wow! Suk Jin's count is 39!]
[Team Ji Hyo succeeds with 289!]
[His own personal victory!
They succeed with Big-nosed brother's play!]
Are you sure that the counter
was showing false count?
I was holding onto my leg!
[Jin Hee's in the midst of
his coaching session again.]
This bent leg will absorb all the shock,
so keep the other leg up.
[That may sound easy...]
- Just sit on the seat like this.
- When I was looking at you earlier...
your back was being knocked around.
That's why I raised up my leg.
But we kept getting knocked around
like this.
I know, but still...
[Anyways, they're going to go ahead
with Jin Hee's plan!]
[Make sure to keep the foot with
the counter attached up in the air!]
Put your foot up! Keep it up!
[They did as planned...
but what will the total count be?]
[Jin Hee's count - 11!]
Her count is 86.
[Suzy's count - 86!]
His count is 63.
[Kwang Soo's count - 63!]
[So far, the total count is 160. Success
as long as Ha Ha's is less than 140!]
- You know it's not over that!
- I don't' think it's over that.
[Ha Ha - 63!]
[Team Suzy succeeds with 223!]
[After working so hard just as
Coach Ji's plan outlined...]
[Team Suzy's turn to gain their hint.]
Please...
Gold!
What? Five is greater than zero?
Since we don't have much time,
let's talk about it on our way.
Thank you, everyone! Thank you!
- Goodbye!
[Right around the same time,
Team Yubin also succeeds their mission!]
[Choosing one of the hints...]
What is this? Two is greater than five?
Think about your clue very carefully.
- Thank you! We enjoyed the food!
- Thank you.
- Goodbye.
That's right, five is greater than zero.
But five is less than two?
What is this? Two...
What about this? It's less than five,
but it's greater than two?
[If they try to make it complicated,
there's no end in sight.]
This isn't easy.
Two, five and zero...
In reality,
five should be greater than two...
[Different than the number concepts
they're familiar with.]
We need to know what
five, two and zero means...
[Is there a different meaning
behind the numbers?]
What do those say?
Zero, one, two, five!
[Blank...]
It said one, zero, two, five.
As in October 25th.
- Something about construction expo...
- Construction expo?
[Like Suzy's movie,
'Introduction to Architecture'?]
You know what we initially were
talking about?
Instead of thinking that it's greater than,
maybe it's stronger than?
Instead of it being a number,
it could be a count of something.
Like if there are five people,
it's not as... Ah!
[Did Ha Ha realize something?]
[Just what is the answer to the riddle
that he just realized?]
- What is this now?
- I don't know.
What is this...
[Gwangju City bus square]
[A vaulting horse?]
[Gwangju tour riddle race.
What is their final mission?]
[Use the vaulting horse to land on
the archery scoreboard.]
[And if the combined score of everyone
is more than 10 points, then you succeed.]
This is because both the gymnastics and
archery athletes are from Gwangju
that's why we created this hybrid game.
Yes, I understand.
[Team Suzy and Team Ji Hyo
also arrives shortly after.]
Fighting!
[Team Yubin is first to make their
attempt!]
Gary, fighting!
[Use the vault to jump and score more than
10 points with the whole team combined!]
[First one up for Team Yubin is Gary.]
[Jump as far as you can to
score the highest score possible!]
[Wherever the toe lands
will be the point given.]
[In front of countless Gwangju citizens...]
[Even though it's nerve-wracking,
jump with confidence!]
[Here I go!]
[A high jump!]
[Just what will he land on?]
[Scores three points.]
[Even though it was his first attempt,
he coolly scores three points!]
[And finishing it up with a strut.]
[10 points or above combined.
Gary scored three points for Team Yubin!]
I'm so embarrassed!
This is so embarrassing!
[If the other three scores a total of
seven points, it's a success!]
[Second jumper for Team Yubin is Jae Suk!]
I have to get three points too...
Yoo Jae Suk! Yoo Jae Suk!
[I have to get at least three points
to make it less burdensome for others...]
[Harden up his resolve, and go!]
You can do it!
[Lands at two point line!]
[Jumped like a grasshopper to
gain another two points for the team!]
[It would've been nice if I could've
jumped just a little bit further...]
[Team Yubin - Gary's three points
and Jae Suk's two points.]
[The third jumper for Team Yubin, Ji Sung.]
[Jumping into it without any hesitation!]
[So lightly!]
[And the result of his jump is?]
[Going by where his toes landed,
he scores three points!]
[Ji Sung, easily gains another three points!]
[Team Yubin: Gary- three points,
Jae Suk- two points, Ji Sung- three points]
[In that case... if Yubin can score
two points, it's a success for the team!]
- Yubin, fighting!
- Yubin!
Your toes... you just
need to get your toes in there!
[Even if she scores just two points,
they'll succeed with a total of 10 points!]
[No big deal...]
[Without any hesitation!]
With confidence!
[Jumping with confidence... to plunk!]
[With Yubin falling in the water,
she garners zero points.]
[Gary- 3 points, Jae Suk- 2 points,
Ji Sung- 3 points, Yubin- 0 points= Fail.]
[Next team on deck, Team Suzy.]
[Team Suzy's first jumper, Ji Jin Hee.]
Challenge.
- Ha Ha, you're next, right?
- Yeah, I think so.
[Coach Ji, will you
show us your skills here too?]
[Going by where the toe lands!
He lands on 3 point section!]
[Jin Hee scores three points for Team Suzy!]
- Three points!
- You have to stretch your feet out.
My pants are way too tight.
[Second jumper for Team Suzy, Ha Ha.]
I want you to ride the wave!
[Starting after hearing Byul's name?]
[Team Suzy's Ha Ha gains one point.]
[Team Suzy has a total of four points.]
Can I go now?
[Third jumper, Suzy]
[Suzy still gains one point!]
Suzy, are you okay?
[Currently, a total of five points!]
[If the Giraffe gets five points,
then they succeed!]
He needs to get five points.
Five points.
[Can he jump this far?]
[He may be good at it since
he's so tall?]
[After jumping like that...
a mere two points?]
[Team Suzy fails with
a total of seven points.]
You have to jump big!
[What a right thing to say...]
[Team Ji Hyo's turn!]
- Okay, let's do this.
- Is it okay?
Since the others got three points,
you should at least get four points.
Should I go now?
[Team Ji Hyo's first jumper, Mr. Capable.]
[Demanding for him to show that
he is on a different level.]
Five points, five points, five points...
[Will he be able to do it?]
[Fly!]
[Just how many points?]
[What did he land on?]
[His toe lands in the four point zone!]
[An amazing jump that renders
the ones watching speechless.]
[Flying high to gain the first
four points in the game!]
[If the rest of Team Ji Hyo can gain
six more points!]
[Team Ji Hyo's second jumper,
Chang Ui.]
I can't wait to see what
Chang Ui does.
[The glint in his eye...
how many points will Chang Ui get?]
[Flying high like Mr. Capable did!]
[Something doesn't seem right
about this.]
[Barely gains two points.]
[Current score for Team Ji Hyo:
Jong Kook - 4 points, Chang Ui - 2 points.]
[At least, Ace Ji Hyo's turn!]
[When it comes to her,
three points could be possible?]
[Hitting the vaulting board on the way...]
[With her Ace reputation...
nicely scores zero points!]
- Hey...
- What the heck is this?
[Team Ji Hyo currently has six points!]
[The fate of the team rests on
the shoulders of Big-nosed brother!]
[If jumps four points or above,
then the team succeeds!]
[Big-nosed brother... will he be
able to pull a Herculean miracle?]
[What in the world...]
[After giving after a big laugh,
he manages zero points.]
[Team Ji Hyo fails with six points.]
At least I jumped it...
for the first time in my life, I jumped it.
Everyone... I have a proposal for you.
I will give you one point for
landing in the water.
And I will pull the score board
one point closer to the vaulting board.
Okay.
[At this rate, it may be possible to
pass with a little more effort!]
[Team Yubin's turn again.]
Gary, fighting!
[The first jumper again is Gary.]
[Gary's who's shown us his
most confident side earlier.]
[His endless hidden skills!
What will he score this time?]
[Five points!]
[Amazing, Kang Gary!]
[Kang Gary's scary skills that takes
everyone by surprise once in a while!]
[Another chic ending...]
[I'm cool...]
[Team Yubin is suddenly up
at five points!]
[Gary acting cool is the funniest part!]
[Second jumper Jae Suk
with a little less burden.]
[There it is! The feverish cheer!]
[Jae Suk is on the move!]
[Far... far away!]
[Four points!]
[Jae Suk gains four points!
Team Yubin has a total score of nine points!]
[Team Yubin's lead athlete,
Ji Sung's turn!]
[I will finish this!]
[Flying lightly through the air again!]
[Scoring three points with ease!]
[Team Yubin: Gary- 5 points,
Jae Suk- 4 points. Ji Sung- 3 points.]
[Team Yubin succeeds
with a total of 12 points!]
[With cheers from the crowd,
first to leave for the final location!]
Here is your final clue.
[Team Yubin earns their final clue.]
Just what in the world is this?
[Can discuss it on the way!
Hurry on to the final location!]
- What is this...
- Just what in the world is this?
After having come all the way
to Gwangju...
Hey, just what in the world is this?
Of course, zero equals zero.
And I think this is going to be
the final destination.
What does zero equal zero mean?
Don't we have to solve the riddle quickly?
I don't think this means numbers, right?
[Gary in deep thoughts without
any words.]
- Why is two greater than five?
- That's what I don't get.
How can two be greater than five?
I think there's something there,
but I don't know what that could be.
Two is greater than five...
- Two is less than zero...
- And five is also less than two...
[Starting to deduce that it has
nothing to do with numbers.]
[Team Ji Hyo is also just as confused.]
[Two is being crushed by zero...]
And five is less than two...
I think this is like a food chain.
Zero eats the two... and two eats
the five and five eats the zero?
[Wait...]
Win... zero beats two.
- I got it! I got it!
- What? What is it?
[Just what could be the answer that
Mr. Capable has deduced?]
Since you were the first to arrive,
you get the biggest advantage.
- You can open it once you're inside.
- I understand.
[Inside...]
[Is it a structure the three teams
can stand on?]
[With that aside...
Team Yubin still has no answer.]
[Huh? That is...]
[It seems as though
Gary has thought of something!]
I figured it out...
this was actually very simple.
This was very simple.
You figured it out too?
You just figured it out, didn't you?
You know it too, right?
[Just then, Team Ji Hyo also arrives.]
[It seems as though both teams have
figured it out, but is it the right answer?]
[This is the National Asia's Cultural Center
slated to be completed in 2012.]
[The mystery of the riddle will be solved
in this future heart of our culture.]
I don't know if you've all figured it out,
but you'll all be given a white board.
After writing what you think the answer
is to the riddle on the board...
lift up the board in our direction
at the count of three.
One team at a time will reveal their
answer starting with Team Yubin.
Please lift it up high towards the front.
One, two, three!
[Rock-paper-scissors]
[A man of many wonders, Kang Gary...
after having opened up his hand by chance...]
You figured it out too, didn't you?
[Rock-paper-scissors]
[Next, Team Ji Hyo's turn
to reveal their answer!]
Again, Rock-paper-scissors!
- I think this is like the food chain...
- Food chain?
[Big-nosed brother's deduction,
food chain...]
- Two eats five... and zero eats two...
- I got it!
- I got it! I got it!
- What? What is it?
Rock-paper-scissors!
Zero... two...
[Not a bad deduction! Is the
correct answer Rock-paper-scissors?]
[And lastly, Team Suzy's answer?]
Rock-paper-scissors.
[All the teams answer
Rock-paper-scissors.]
[That's right! The answer
to the riddle is Rock-paper-scissors!]
I had no idea that all of us
would get the same answer.
What happens now, Gary?
[All the viewer's get it too, right?
Rock-paper-scissors?]
[Rock]
[Scissors]
[Paper]
[All three teams answered correctly!]
[But this isn't the end!]
[The correct answer isn't the end!]
Please open up the envelope you received
at the door and show it to everyone.
[Open up the mysterious envelope they
received at the door!]
Four people can participate!
Three people can participate.
[A piece of paper with how many people
are able to participate written on it.]
[If they hadn't figured out the correct answer
participation wouldn't have been possible.]
But since everyone came up
with the correct answer
the final team left remaining after a round
of Rock-paper-scissors is the winner.
[This is today's Riddle Race's ending!]
[Team Yubin- 4 people, Team Suzy- 2 people,
and Team Ji Hyo- 3 people can participate!]
[A mental fight from the start!]
[A face off with a member of each team
to start off the game!]
- Fighting!
Do you feel the need to film us playing
Rock-paper-scissors up this close?
[The ultimate game of Rock-paper-scissors,
which no one can predict the results!]
[The final face off,
Rock-paper-scissors- first round!]
Rock-paper-scissors!
I won!
[Team Yubin Jae Suk's win!]
[Jae Suk is the only one to throw out
a scissors, so he wins!]
[Four people! Team Yubin with the most
number of participants takes the lead!]
Those who lost, please step down.
Kim Jong Kook and Suzy
can step down now.
That's so annoying!
[Jin Hee vs. Chang Ui vs. Jae Suk]
- It's too easy, isn't it?
- If Jin Hee loses, that's it for this team?
That's correct.
[The final face off-
Rock-paper-scissors, Round 2!]
Rock-paper-scissors!
Rock-paper-scissors
[All three throws out paper.]
[Tougher for those standing by watching.]
- This is making me really nervous.
- This is really nerve wrecking.
Rock-paper-scissors!
[This time, everyone throws out
a scissors!]
[At the breaking point of
nervousness!]
Rock-paper-scissors!
[Team Suzy's Jin Hee is defeated!]
[Team Suzy eliminated from the
competition!]
[They were in such high spirits all day...]
[Team Yubin's four people vs.
Team Ji Hyo's two people.]
[Even though Team Yubin seems to have
the advantage, you never know in this game!]
[Final face off -
Rock-paper-scissors, Round three!]
This could be what you're
good at, Chang Ui!
This is really nerve wrecking...
Rock-paper-scissors!
[Wow! Team Yubin's Jae Suk wins again!]
[Team Yubin breaks out in celebration!
Jae Suk wins three in a row on his own!]
You can finish this!
[Their final warrior, Suk Jin!]
It's okay, we have our Suk Jin.
Running Man's champion
of Rock-paper-scissors...
[Rock-paper-scissors champion of
Running Man, Ji Suk Jin!]
[The King of Ddak-ji, Yoo Jae Suk
all of a sudden seems to be afraid!]
Suk Jin is really good at
Rock-paper-scissors...
[The final face off of Rock-paper-scissors,
Round four - Jae Suk vs. Suk Jin.]
Rock-paper-scissors!
We won!
[Four times in a row...
Team Yubin's Jae Suk kills them all!]
[The ultimate winner, Team Yubin!]
This is a record! A record!
Ddak-ji isn't my calling,
but Rock-paper-scissors!
Rock-paper-scissors! Rock-paper-scissors!
Subtitles by DramaFever
I won again!
[But... times of joy are short lived...]
[Their worst nightmares is about to start...]
[The coming of their nemesis!]
[He is coming!]
[Running Man vs. Hunter...
to go down in history!]
[Their victory hangs on the balance!]
[The ultimate battle to go down in history!]
Please save me!
[A return one year in the making...
The hunter who's grown ever stronger!]
[The extreme terror and chaos
that tightens its grip on Running Man!]
[Cannot be controlled!
Thrown into the vortex of his revenge!]
[The legendary hunter,
coming back to put an end to it all!]
[Running Man vs. Hunter Min Soo]
[Who will be the ultimate victor
of this bloody battle?]
Please!
[Running Man Hunter... The Final Hunt]