Subtitles by DramaFever
[Ambush in the basin]
[There is no giving up.
You must endure it!]
[In miserable shambles]
[This is Basin style]
[Utterly chaotic basin match]
[The nature's mudpack that
no one can escape]
[Ambush in the basin]
[Super match in the basin]
[Eight o'clock in the morning]
[X-man and Geun Young are both still asleep.]
[Ah... time for morning workouts?]
[Catch me?]
[DBSK's U-Know, Yoon Ho]
[DBSK's Strongest Chang Min]
[DBSK]
[Early morning Hallyu Star concert
in the front lawn]
[Laughing?]
[Wake up...]
[The highlight of the concert!]
[A perfect reenactment]
[The morning sun too bright?]
[Ah... the grass on his back...]
[What the...]
[Ji Hyo and Geun Young
wake up too.]
[Who is that?]
[DBSK!]
[They're finally recognizing who they are?]
[Dancing first thing in the morning?]
[A serious grass stage performance
without any hesitations]
[Even Haroro is awake.]
[DBSK's front lawn stage performance]
[Catch me]
Why are you making
DBSK dance on the lawn?
[A front lawn performance that
almost didn't happen]
This is the first time I had to dance
so early in the morning.
Making these stars dance so early in
the morning on the lawn...
- Look at their knees!
- They were dancing so intensely.
[Oh my... Gary!]
Look at their sweat suits.
Here comes the owner of the place.
- Our cool friends!
- Hello.
- Our cool friends...
- Seriously...
First, I'll explain today's race
to all of you.
Okay.
Today's race is... the bell race.
[Bell Race]
[Starting off with attaching bells
to all the Running Man members]
[Protect and keep the bells until
arriving at the final destination]
[The last person to arrive at
the final destination...]
[will lose their bell and
be immediately eliminated.]
[The team that’s been eliminated cannot
participate in any further missions.]
The eliminated team cannot participate
in any further missions.
Kwang Soo, what are you going to do?
[His expression looks as though
he's already been disqualified...]
You will first be divided into five teams,
and I will announce the teams right now.
Kim Jong Kook and...
[Could it be... Geun Young?]
[Last week...]
[The two people who’ve hinted
something's going on between them]
- Do you like Geun Young?
- Of course!
[Will that sweet ambience continue today?]
Geun Young... Geun Young.
Please let it be Geun Young!
PD, let Geun Young be on his team!
- Is there someone you want on your team?
- Excuse me?
[Don't you know?
Or are you asking for fun?]
Then why are you standing between them?
- I'm just standing here!
- It's not like that...
Since you're both wearing yellow,
just team up with Suk Jin.
[Someone always has to ruin
these romantic moments.]
The thing is, he likes Moon Geun Young.
- She is his ideal type!
- He really likes her.
- Come on now...
- We have to form teams sometime today.
- I'm just saying that I like her as a person.
- Isn't there too big of an age gap?
That’s why I'm saying it's not like that.
- There's a 10-year age difference.
- Kim Jong Kook and...
- Please...
- Geun Young! Let it be Geun Young!
It will be Moon Geun Young.
[Same team as Geun Young]
[Falling down out of embarrassment...]
Why are you seriously being like that?
- Every single time...
- Why? What about me?
- What are you talking about?
- Why are you seriously being like that?
I guess there really is something going on.
- No, that's not true!
- Your face is so red!
- Why are you being like that?
- What’s wrong with you?
Since this is how it is, we need to get rid
of both their bells at the first mission.
What did you say?
Then I guess we know how the rest of us are
going to team off without you telling us.
Yes, you got it.
Us two?
[Teams have been chosen]
Did you ask the writers for this?
You're always hanging around me lately.
[Bell Race... Start!]
- You're from Gwang-ju, right?
- Yes, you are too, right?
[Yoon Ho and Geun Young are
from the same province.]
[It's morning]
Since we're all in the same car like this,
shall we form an alliance?
- We may have to get rid of them first.
- Don't get rid of us, Jae Suk.
I want to at least get rid of Suk Jin
first before getting eliminated.
[Starting off with the feeling of
setting off on a vacation]
You're not cold, are you?
- Are you cold?
- No, we're fine.
- I was asking you.
- I'm fine.
Just pretend that we're not even here.
- We're just their shadows, right?
- Of course, we're nothing but shadows.
- Just think of us as your shadows...
- And your clothes are actually black too.
Glancing in the rearview mirror like this,
I feel like you guys are nothing but heads.
[Jae Suk in the back getting grumpy]
Why are you staring at me like that?
What... you actually think you can date her?
- We're just a team...
- You two don't suit each other.
- Why not?
- What?
- She asked 'why not'!
- I don't think she'll be an easy opponent.
I'm telling you, she's not your average girl.
Why not? Why not? Seriously...
- I wish I could go fishing.
- You like to fish?
I haven't done it much.
[This... type of fishing?]
You're going to be 29 years old next year?
I want to be your bed for a day.
(line from a DBSK song)
[It seemed like yesterday that he was
a young man making his debut...]
When I look at myself back then...
it really makes my toes curl.
I don't know how I was so confident enough
back then to wink at the camera.
It's really amazing, isn't it?
Even he used to wink a lot back in the day
with his small eyes.
I never got to wink because
I always wore those sunglasses.
People never knew if I was winking.
But I knew...
[Wow... completely into the game
of making a love connection...]
Miss Moon... I can't believe...
She has such a pure and gentle heart...
- You heard it too, didn't you?
- Yes, I heard it.
[Eyeing the new Monday couple spot?]
You're no longer a young girl...
- Don't hesitate...
- Okay, I won't.
[The flower jewel, Moon Geun Young
making her entrance on the show]
We all seem to be in
a good mood right now.
- Of course.
- Seriously, we are.
It's because Geun Young's here right now.
If he wasn't here, the mood
could be even brighter.
Wow... that’s so beautiful!
That’s seriously so beautiful!
[Monday couple making their appearance
together for once in a long time]
You know those awkward couples who break
up and meet again for the first time.
[Hm... I wonder who that could be?]
In a strange coincidence,
they meet again after breaking up...
And somehow getting close together again...
That's what I slightly feel like we are today.
No, you and I have been teamed up
together a lot lately.
You're not making calls to the writers
before the shows, right?
- No, I don't... why? You do?
- No, I've never done that.
You know the Monday syndrome
after we broke up?
I got a little bit of that too.
You had it?
Three weeks? Maybe for three weeks...
I felt like I really needed to meet someone...
I felt like I needed to be a couple
with someone...
To be honest, I don't think
Moon Geun Young is that pretty.
Why don't you say that when
Geun Young is standing in front of you?
I can't do that...
Wow... the Korean Coast Guard!
[Arriving at the mission location]
Incheon Coast Guard Station - Special Forces
[The place where all the special equipment for
the Coast Guard Special Forces are gathered]
Kim Jong Kook, you should be thankful to me!
- Look at them holding hands.
- You're holding her hand thanks to us.
There was a time when I used to
get excited like that.
Hey, do we really have to run?
[Running towards the flag]
Why are you running? Let's all go slow!
[Yoo-ruce Willis and Yoon Ho speed on by!]
We're first!
- Second!
- What are we running for?
[Ha-sseiopeia]
(Cassiopeia is the name of DBSK's fan club)
You'll be changing your clothes now...
[Huh? Clothes?]
[The reason for changing their clothes...]
[Is because of this basin!]
[Oh no... it's the basin...]
[Next to the special coast guard forces...]
[The basin that stretches on and on...]
[No matter which basin it is...]
[You can't get out
no matter how hard you try...]
[And no matter how hard you try to escape,
you cannot escape it.]
[It's the worst location to be at
in the history of variety games.]
[And it is here...]
I think this'll be easy for me.
[Gary the fisherman?]
[Now in basin style...]
[Geun Young looking cute even in
fisherman's clothing]
[Welcome to the basin!]
You can't get your foot in, can you?
[Kwang Soo's feet not fitting into the boots]
My feet aren't fitting in there.
[Having to find some tools]
- I don't think this will cut into it.
- Why are you trying to cut?
Cut out the front like sandals...
[From boots to sandals - Instant reform]
- You're the best.
- Peel! Cut! Cross!
[Specially made for Giraffe--
rubber sandals complete!]
[A sad giraffe with the big feet...]
I wonder if we're going to be in for
some physical humor today.
[Entering the basin in turn]
We are the strongest... Hasseiopeia.
[Conquering the basin]
[Jong Kook and Geun Young with
their light footsteps]
- Where do we go?
- Where?
[Jae Suk and Yoon Ho also walking
with hands tightly clasped]
[Now to the basin...]
This is no joke!
[This is the power of the basin -
it sucks you in!]
[Crawling on their knees]
[The lovers of the basin]
Oh no! What do I do?
[Taking a stroll out on the basin
with their hands tightly held]
We're all having to hold hands right now
because of those two!
Just because of that one couple,
we all had to walk hand in hand.
What's wrong with it? It was nice!
[These two with their hands
also tightly held...]
If you're not here in 30 seconds,
you're eliminated.
Run, run, run!
[Walking leisurely... in plastic rain boots?]
Kwang Soo! What’s taking you so long?
Yes, we're coming!
They're moving really fast.
I think this is Suk Jin's first time
out in the basin.
Why are there so many first times for him?
[First experience out in the basin -
Going forward impossible for Impala]
[What are you doing?]
[Easy Brothers dancing
a traditional Korean dance]
[First person to get
the whole body basin experience]
- What are you doing?
- This is how you're supposed to walk.
They really are clumsy.
So clumsy...
What to do... what to do!
[After barely getting Impala
back on his own feet]
This time, Kwang Soo's in trouble...
You can't waste all your energy like that!
[Springing?]
[A surprising impersonation in the basin]
[Ultimately, Jae Suk to the rescue]
I'm just going to give up.
I don’t think I can do this anymore.
I don’t think I can do any of this.
[Already exhausted from having to
take care of Impala and himself]
The first mission, basin photo zone!
It's a success if the couple's faces are
captured in the photo up on the platform.
The last team to succeed is eliminated.
[The team that doesn't succeed
is immediately eliminated.]
That team won't be able to move on
to the next round.
Once I shout, 'I'm taking the picture,'
the picture will be taken in five seconds.
[The terrifying Basin Photo Zone - Start!]
- Are you ready?
- Yes!
I'm going to take the picture!
[Move to the photo zone!]
[Easy Brothers parachuting off the platform]
[You have to be gone for me
to get my picture taken!]
[With smiles on their faces
and feet all over the place]
Stop!
What do you mean, stop?
[Just which of the couples succeeded?]
I didn't even get to get on there.
I was standing on the platform.
[Haroro, is that you?]
[A smiling face]
[Gary wanted to get in there too]
[In the middle of planning a strategy?]
- Chang Min and Geun Young...
- Okay, good job.
[Chang Min hiding Jong Kook's face]
[Everyone fails the first attempt]
I think we should be standing over there.
[Oh my... linking arms?]
You guys are walking with your
arms linked now?
- It's because it's dangerous out here.
- Yeah, sure...
- They really can't date?
- No, they can't!
- Why are you being like that?
- I said, they can't.
But whenever I said they can't,
Geun Young keeps asking why not.
- Are you ready?
- Yes!
[Another attempt]
[Ha Ha and Chang Min quickly
scurrying up to the platform]
Block them, block them!
[Turning around immediately and
strongly blocking them off]
[It's time to take the picture now...]
[Ha Ha and Chang Min succeeding
in protecting their spots]
[Kkuk also smiling brightly in the corner]
[Photo session over!]
[Trying to block his face to the end]
[Did Ha Ha and Chang Min get
their faces in the picture?]
[Ha Ha and Chang Min's blockade]
[Holding her down so that she can't
get in the way of their faces]
[We have to look behind us now]
[Did they...]
[Succeeds in a clear shot of their faces!]
[Their defense plan is a success!]
Seriously... you guys are no fun.
What the heck was that?
What? We succeeded in our mission.
If you're out in the basin,
shouldn't you roll around in it a little?
What did you say?
Roll around in the basin?
[Jae Suk vs. Haroro - Basin faceoff]
Why don't you try rolling in it too?
Hey!
[The real taste of the basin that’s
finally being shown]
If it's so much fun to roll around in it,
why don't you do it too?
Fine... let's get your face in it too then!
Get your face in it too!
[The natural mud pack]
Now it finally seems like the basin!
- What the heck is this?
- This is the basin!
This is the basin...
It's the basin, it's the basin...
[Mud pack is give and take]
- I have nothing to fear anymore.
- I don't either.
- I'm not afraid either!
- I'm still afraid of the basin.
[Somehow Chang Min also
got covered in mud.]
Ready, set, go!
[Run!]
Let's win!
[Getting pushed off?]
[Kwang Soo's attack]
Who was it?
[The brave knight with long arms fighting off
whoever gets within his reach]
[The Tiger's rear attack]
[Photo-shoot complete]
Ji Hyo... there's no point in being
the first one to get up here.
[Kwang Soo pushing off whoever
gets within his reach]
[Being chastised by the Tiger]
[But Tiger, we only got your chin...]
Just my chin?
You guys look awkward together.
Are you okay?
One, two, three!
[Playful Gary]
Tell me that you want to
start seeing me again.
- Tell me! Tell me that you do!
- Hey!
[What is he saying
in the middle of the basin?]
Hey! Get lost!
[Blank Ji's definitive answer]
They're having a lovers' quarrel
in the middle of the basin.
- This is basin love... basin love!
- It finally seems like the basin!
[Desperately looking for their
past love in the basin]
Okay, I'm going to take the picture.
[Are the Easy Brothers cheating?]
- What are you doing?
- You guys are the ones being weird!
- Oh, get up there!
- You're right!
[Everyone rushing to get up]
Push them off!
[Easy Brothers being disposed of]
[The remaining three couples fiercely
fighting for their spots]
Get up here.
Hurry!
[Their attention is on the camera]
[A victory sign by myself?]
[Giraffe... there's a time and a place
for your jokes too...]
Jae Suk, hurry up and get up here.
[The photo-shoot will soon be over!]
- It's over, it's over...
- Kwang Soo, get up here.
[The photo-shoot is over!]
These plastic bags are too slippery!
[Once again reformed to sandals
from plastic rain boots]
This is just too hard...
[Giraffe enduring through it all
with his eyes wide open]
[If I'm going to block them,
let's do it right.]
[Jae Suk and Yoon Ho succeeds!]
Jae Suk and Yoon Ho, success!
Jae Suk perfectly blocked Jong Kook's face
with your yellow towel.
[Wow, this is exhilarating!]
[Thanks to Jae Suk's towel, only
Mr. Capable's eyes were showing.]
This is a much sweeter victory now!
This victory is so much sweeter now...
[Jae Suk and Yoon Ho second to pass]
Once two more teams succeed,
one team will be eliminated.
[Without participating in the next round,
they will be coldly eliminated immediately.]
- Get out of the way!
- Mister!
- I am getting out of the way right now!
- Hurry up and get out of the way!
[Mr. Yoo coming out to get a drink]
Why are you going that way?
Is that guy drunk or something?
- You should be heading home...
- We're shooting a show over here!
If this is a show,
why are you standing there?
What did you say? I'm a celebrity!
- You're lying!
- I'm a celebrity!
- I've never seen you on television!
- I've even given out autographs!
Even when I've watched television all day,
I've never once seen you on it!
Let's just die together!
Are you ready?
I’m going to take the picture!
I'm going to take the picture!
[Blank Ji not even able to get started]
[Using that opportunity to
take over the photo zone?]
[The photo zone battle uncaring of
any tears or blood shed]
[Gary and Ji Hyo clumsily making their way in]
My feet are so slippery on here!
Ji Hyo, hurry up!
[Gary's strength is eliminating everyone!]
Ji Hyo, hurry! Hurry!
[Will they...]
[Pushing Gary off]
[Gary ultimately parachuting off]
[The dramatic photo zone battle]
[Gary's back-end strong force attack]
[Ji Hyo, hurry!]
[Ji Hyo gets on it... but, huh?]
[You should’ve opened your eyes.]
[Gary and Ji Hyo unfortunately fail.]
Hey, Jong Kook got pushed off!
[With the platform being slippery,
even Mr. Capable's strength is obsolete?]
- It's so slippery, I keep getting pushed off.
- We can do this!
[Plans to overthrow Mr. Capable]
- Okay, let’s go!
- Wait, wait a minute!
[Starting to sink more
and more into the basin]
- Ready!
- I'm not ready yet!
I'm not ready yet!
I'm not ready!
Okay, I'm ready.
I'm going to take the picture!
[Easy Brothers quick to get up
on the platform this time too]
Just look forward for now.
I said, look up front!
Why are you...
[Easy Brothers easily being discarded]
[Now posing for the picture]
I'm just going to go home!
[Mr. Capable couple holding down
the photo zone.]
[Getting rid of the Easy Brothers first]
[Smiling brightly...
and Gary getting in the way]
[Easily with one hand...]
[Gets rid of him]
[Now a couple picture
with just the two of us...]
[Jong Kook and Geun Young succeed!]
[We are the basin lovers.]
[Harmony...]
[Battered...]
- Is he seriously leaving?
- Isn't that Mario from Super Mario Brothers?
- Who’s Mario?
- Are you Super Mario?
[By any chance... are you Mario?]
Put it on for me, I have to wear it.
Seriously, you are so high-maintenance!
You didn't know that?
You have to do it with your heart
to get it back on my foot.
You can't do it with just your hands only.
These rain boots were
made very special like that.
You've never been this good to me before.
[You're being really good to me...]
They really do look good together.
How did they ever break up?
It's good, it's good.
You really are high-maintenance... seriously!
That’s why women can't leave me.
[That’s what attracts them to me...]
[Collapsing out of sheer ridiculousness]
[The final basin photo zone battle]
I'm going to take the picture!
[The couple that doesn't make it this time
is immediately eliminated.]
[Easy Brothers first to climb up
onto the platform]
This isn't the time to be
just standing back here!
[Looking forward with the hands to the side]
[Fixated forward]
Hurry up and get up here!
Wait a minute!
Ji Hyo!
Come up here!
[Gary in discomfort from his position]
You look like a mermaid!
[Basin mermaid?]
It's a mermaid!
Help me get up there.
He's taking the picture. Lift up your face!
[Huh? Switching partners out of urgency?]
What are you doing?
- Hey!
- What are you doing?
[Just who will be the final team to succeed
in the photo zone mission?]
[A fierce smile]
[A gaze filled with resolve]
[Photo session complete!]
[The team that succeeded...]
The couple that succeeded...
[A fixated gaze]
[Whatever!]
[Open your eyes!]
[Oh?]
[Easy Brothers succeed!]
[Basin photo zone's four successful couples]
The first and second team to have won will
move to the second location in a helicopter.
[First and second place teams to move
in a helicopter]
And the third and fourth place teams...
will move in an all-terrain boat which can
move on land as well as on water.
And the last team... is just eliminated.
There's a bell attached to
each of your shoes, right?
Take them with you and put them on
after getting cleaned up.
Make sure that the bells are still attached
and be careful to not have them fall off.
- Which one of these are your shoes, Gary?
- These ones down here.
[Getting rid of the bells immediately]
This is going to be a rough day.
[Just... what is Gary and Ji Hyo's fate?]
[The remaining couples
move to the next location.]
Helicopters are scary.
[Jae Suk is also scared.]
- I think it's going to be fun. We like it.
- Really?
[The excited DBSK]
[The two teams gathering
in front of the helicopter]
- Hello.
- Thanks for all your hard work.
- Why do we have to put those on?
[It's all for safety...]
Song Ji Hyo didn't get first place?
- No, she didn't.
- That’s too bad.
[Disappointed that Blank Ji didn't win]
[Third and fourth-place teams
getting ready to board the hovercraft]
This looks like a lot of fun!
[Amazing... the boat is starting to inflate!]
[Eyes opening up wide in wonder]
[Hovercraft slowly going into motion]
[The power of the immense hovercraft!]
[The helicopter is ready for lift-off!]
[Even though they're all still smiling...]
[Not even able to look out the window]
[Helicopter slowly lifting off]
[Flying lightly to the next location]
[Hovercraft is heading straight for the ocean.]
- It's the ocean! Nice!
- The ocean? We're on the ocean?
[Hovercraft freely moving on land and sea]
[Moving at an incredible speed
through the ocean!]
[Gary playing around]
Hey!
[A lightning-quick response]
Hey, don't you think you hit me too hard?
- Don’t do it!
- Sorry.
Where are we being taken to?
[Incheon Marine Police Station]
[Could... the next mission location be here?]
[I can see something...]
[The helicopter slowly
starting to make its descent]
[The hovercraft making its way
to the same location]
Wow... this is really amazing!
That’s what they must've taken.
I think this is the police.
[The helicopter that’s given a ride to the
other two teams is lifting up again.]
Bye!
This is nice.
[This is the second mission location!]
[What is the mission at this place?]
[Second Mission - Dodgeball Quiz]
[Name seven things related to the theme
while dodging the ball.]
[If you get hit by the ball, then you fail.]
- If you get hit, then you're out.
- Even women?
Of course.
If you catch the ball,
you can hold it for three seconds.
Ah, if you catch it?
Once we count to three,
you have to throw it again.
That must be so cool...
you get to be her bodyguard.
[Take the challenge in turns starting
with the first-place winning team.]
- Fighting!
Jong Kook, I'm so nervous!
Kwon Yeol, what are you doing?
Kwon Yeol's not very athletic.
[Jae Suk's personal VJ, Kwon Yeol,
who's famous for being out of shape]
The VJ is going to throw the ball?
[And on the other side...]
[Jong Kook's personal VJ, Ki Jin]
[First-place winner among the VJs
during the arm wrestling match]
[In excellent physical condition]
[A world of difference in physique
between the two sides]
Once both members have been ousted,
then the team will be changed out.
You will take turns answering
one person at a time.
- Yes.
This question is...
[Name seven capitals]
[Republic of Korea, Seoul - Correct]
[Forceful]
[Not easy to think of an answer when
you're so busy avoiding the ball...]
Tokyo!
Hey, do it right!
Do it correctly okay?
[This is no joke]
Kingston! Kingston!
[Jamaica, Kingston - Correct]
He's really good.
Washington!
[America, Washington - Correct]
You have to catch it. Kwon Yeol!
[Huh?]
[The ball flying out of bounds]
[Go get that ball yourself!]
- Seriously, Kwon Yeol...
- Take Kwon Yeol out!
[An outburst towards Kwon Yeol]
Beijing!
[China, Beijing - Correct]
[Oh... at this rate?
They already have five correct!]
[Even from a short distance,
fails at taking him out]
- What are you doing?
- Kwon Yeol, you really are bad!
Kwon Yeol, why...
[Kwon Yeol, after being
scolded, ousts Ha Ha.]
You have to shout out the answers!
[Chang Min is also out.]
[Ha Ha and Chang Min fail.]
This is hard.
Just a minute, since he's so bad...
- Kwon Yeol isn't good at it...
- Kwon Yeol got into trouble.
I think he got into trouble for
not being good at throwing the ball.
[Emergency swap]
- Look at how he's already tired...
- I want Kwon Yeol to stay.
[Ha Ha's own VJ, Sung Yong]
[Jae Suk and Yoon Ho up
to take the challenge]
[Question - Seven proverbs]
[As soon as the game starts,
he's out with one shot.]
What the heck is this?
['When it's not correct, blow
smoke up the chimney' - Correct]
[Without a doubt, Yoon Ho is quick!]
Hey, hey... Sung Yong is good!]
[This time, Yoon Ho is also ousted!]
[The power of Sung Yeon is
quite different from Kwon Yeol!]
Give it to my Kwon Yeol... my Kwon Yeol!
[Going back now?]
[Jong Kook and Geun Young's turn]
There he starts again!
- Sister-in-law, fighting!
- Fighting!
Here comes the question...
[Seven character idioms]
[Barely escaping the ball]
[Oh?]
[Are they embracing right now?]
[Coming to support her in a flash
for fear that she'll fall]
[Going after Geun Young
right at that moment!]
[No!]
[In ultimate defense mode -
Geun Young's bodyguard, Kkuk]
[I took the shot.]
[You... you did?]
[Ah ha...]
Born poor!
[Born poor - Correct]
- Behind you. Geun Young, behind you.
- Oh my goodness...
Seriously, you guys...
[Not being able to think from
being so busy avoiding the ball]
Geun Young,
hurry up and shout out the answers!
[Ah...]
[Did you...]
[Upset Geun Young's bodyguard]
Are you out of your mind right now?
- [I’m sorry.]
- I'm not threatening him!
Ah, seriously...
[Question - Name seven capitals]
[Taking it upon himself to lie down
so it's easier for the ball to hit him]
Seoul!
[Republic of Korea, Seoul - Correct]
[Easy Brothers ousted in the shortest time]
You have to be careful of Sung Yong...
he and Ki Jin are dangerous.
[Question - Name seven of Jong Kook's songs]
- You are lovely! One man!
[You are lovely, One man - Correct]
One man, what’s next?
[That’s what we thought...]
Jae Suk, why are you so out of sorts?
[Doing a good job of avoiding Ki Jin's
powerful speed balls]
[Flying Yoon Ho]
[Goodbye yesterday - Correct]
[Yoon Ho in danger!]
[And he escapes it!]
[Fighting spirit while running only in socks]
[Ultimately is ousted]
[Mental distress]
[Emergency situation]
- Are you okay?
- Yes.
Chang Min and Sung Min are so good.
If you guys are really bad at it,
then we'll give Kwon Yeol another chance.
Please give Kwon Yeol a chance.
Kwon Yeol, please go in.
Ki Jin, out. Kwon Yeol in his place.
[Question - Name seven mountains]
Maebong Mountain, Suri Mountain!
[Correct]
Chunggae Mountain!
[Kwang Soo - Out!]
Acha Mountain!
Acha mountain!
[Correct]
Gaeryong Mountain!
[Impala Brother doing a good job of avoiding]
Ulsan!
[Ulsan?]
[Barely catching on to the ball]
What else is there?
Keto Mountain?
- Surak Mountain!
[Surak Mountain - Correct]
You've answered six correctly.
[If he can name one more,
then he passes!]
[But the ball is heading straight
towards him this time!]
Inwang Mountain!
Correct.
[Oh... he passes!]
[Zero response?]
Give us a round of applause!
Clap for us...
[Somehow...
Easy Brothers are the first to pass.]
[Question - Name seven seas or oceans]
East Sea! Yellow Sea!
[Correct]
The South Sea!
The Pacific Ocean!
[Correct]
- Mediterranean Sea, the Indian Ocean...
- Dead Sea...
Indian Ocean!
[Indian Ocean makes five.]
[Yoon Ho is out after being
grazed with the ball at the knee.]
[Only two left!
Hurry and shout out the answers!]
One more...
[The ball is heading
straight towards Jae Suk!]
[Avoid this ball and answer!]
[Ah... the familiar place...]
[Jae Suk's ordeal on the ocean...]
[Why do you keep hurting me...]
[You guys, seriously...]
I didn't get hit on the side either...
he got me right on the spot.
Seriously?
At least he can get it in the bull's eye!
Come here, you guys.
Is this the only area you guys stare at?
This is totally off limits!
It's on fire right now... and it really hurts!
Here comes the question.
[Question - Name seven Olympic categories]
Judo! Fencing!
[Correct]
Basketball! Taekwondo!
Volleyball! Soccer!
[Correct]
- Fencing!
- You already said fencing.
- Archery!
- Green team passes.
[Ha Ha and Chang Min pass!]
[Ha Ha and Chang Min
still running full steam ahead]
Be careful... you guys, watch it!
[Angry Jae Suk gives a warning to the VJs.]
Here comes your question...
[Name seven domestic actors]
Song Seung Hun!
[Correct]
[Duplicates are prohibited]
You already said that one.
- Ahn Sung Gi!
- That’s two.
[Ah... fails at catching the ball]
There's Go Chang Suk!
[Being mortified by Kwon Yeol...]
I told you to catch the ball!
More than anything right now...
to be had by Kwon Yeol...
[Being had by Kwon Yeol,
whom he makes fun of every day...]
[The eliminated players
still going on their way]
There's a fly in here....
Kang Gary, catch that fly.
You want me to seriously show you?
[Oh... in one shot?]
- Don't do it. I feel so bad!
- She says she feels bad now...
Hurry up and kill it.
- Here's another fly!
- Where? Am I the fly catcher now?
Catch that one.
I'm not in the right position for this.
It flew away.
I didn't sleep at all last night because
of a fly in the room.
I sent it in there.
- I sent the fly in there.
- You did?
Where?
[This time, it's on Ji Hyo's left arm!]
Hold still.
I'm sorry.
- It fell, it fell...
- Hey!
[Getting scolded right away]
That hurts.
I'm a man who doesn’t know
how to do anything.
[Is that why women can't leave you?]
[Jong Kook and Geun Young up to
the challenge again]
[Switching out for Ki Jin to throw again]
[Question - Name seven foreign actresses]
Natalie Portman!
[Correct]
[Even though he went for Jong Kook,
Jong Kook catches the ball.]
Julia Roberts!
[Correct]
Drew Barrymore!
[After answering three correctly,
Jong Kook is out!]
Jessica Alba.
[Correct]
- Drew! Drew
- I already said that one.
[Oh... she caught it!]
Zhang Ziyi! Gong Li!
[Correct]
Audrey Hepburn!
[Jong Kook and Geun Young succeed!]
You did it, Geun Young!
[The teams that have succeeded to move
into the lifeboats on board]
- We'll see you later.
- Okay, see you!
[Yoon Ho and Jae Suk get rid of their bells
after being eliminated.]
[Just what fate awaits them?]
[In just a moment!]
[To set the eliminated players'
hearts pounding...]
[Terrifying chase will soon begin!]
[Third mission place - A park in Incheon]
[The three teams who've been able to
protect their bells arrive here!]
Traitor! Traitor!
Before we get to the final round,
we're going to eliminate one more team.
The third mission is... chicken fight.
[The third mission - Chicken fight]
[With the final round left to go,
a serious physical battle]
- What do you mean, at a disadvantage?
- But...
What do you mean, but? What is it?
I will introduce you to the people who
will be chicken fighting with all of you.
[There are other players whom
they'll be in a chicken fight with?]
[By any chance, will it be 50
young men like last time?]
[The opponents for the chicken fight
are none other than...]
[The eliminated teams]
[We were wondering where they went,
but here they are.]
These are the best you could come up with?
[The survivors putting
their mind back at ease]
- Why are you walking out so confidently?
- The four of us are all on the same team.
- The four of us are on the same team.
- So it's four against one?
[The eliminated four and each team's
two members will go in turn.]
[If all remaining three teams lose, the team
who lost in shortest time is eliminated.]
Other than wrestling and pogs,
the thing I'm good at is chicken fighting.
- Fine, we got it!
- Wrestling, pogs, and chicken fighting.
You really are a king amongst
all the weaklings over there...
Ready!
[The mission before the final round!
Which team will be eliminated?]
They're timing this!
[The opponents aren't an easy match.
Quickly approaching eliminated teams]
[Cornering the Giraffe within moments]
[The eliminated ones are going after
Big-nosed Brother this time!]
[Just then!]
[U-know, Yoon Ho attacks!]
[After attacking Big-nosed Brother,
he loses his balance!]
[Suk Jin and Yoon Ho
are simultaneously ousted!]
[Remaining target, one Giraffe.]
Kwang Soo!
[Giraffe becoming the
object of target within moments!]
[Tactical moves to attack with his long legs!]
[While trying to attack,
no thanks to his weak lower body...
[Totally humiliated]
Kwang Soo!
[You can't do the chicken fight
because you're a giraffe...]
[Within moments, easily
eliminates Suk Jin and Kwang Soo]
We finished that very quickly.
[The eliminated team gets to choose
who gets to go next.]
For the next one, go up
against Kim Jong Kook.
Chang Min is better. Chang Min...
- We choose Ha Ha and Chang Min.
- You're afraid of Jong Kook?
Just go up against him.
Do it while you still have some energy left.
Don't you remember our first episode?
He's the one that sent 10 people away.
[Two summers ago, the incident where
he sent numerous opponents down alone]
- Are both teams ready?
- Everyone, fighting!
- Fighting!
- Everyone, scream!
[An extraordinary voice somewhere?]
You scream by yourself!
One more time!
Everyone, lift up your leg!
[Ha Ha and Chang Min vs.
The eliminated ones]
Why are you just standing there?
[Ha Ha and Chang Min's plan is to drag out
the time for as long as possible.]
Wait, wait, wait...
[Before he's taken down,
he's escaping as far away as possible.]
[Ha Ha being solely being attacked
in the meantime]
[Jae Suk trying to attack awkwardly...
falls down on his own]
Are you the X-man again?
[Just then! Chang Min heads somewhere!]
[Heading in frightening speed
towards Yoon Ho!]
[A fierce attack on Yoon Ho!]
[In the meantime, these three are
escalating things on their own!]
[While Ha Ha hits Ji Hyo,
Gary hits Ha Ha!]
[Strong Chang Min vs. Gary and Yoon Ho!]
[A battle between DBSK!]
[A battle that had to happen sometime!]
[The initial attack is by Chang Min!]
[When it comes to strength,
they really are on par!]
[Yoon Ho's deadly attacking skills!]
[Ah! Both at the same time!]
[After attacking Chang Min,
Yoon Ho's ousted at the same time!]
[Thanks to Gary staying out of the way,
the eliminated ones win the battle!]
[Jong Kook and Geun Young loosening up
their muscles before their turn]
To the left!
[The problem is, how are they
going to attack Mr. Capable...]
[A word from Coach Kook]
It goes without saying,
but chicken fight isn't about strength.
- I'm sure it's about muscles!
- It's art.
[Jong Kook and Geun Young vs.
The eliminated teams]
You scream by yourself!
When I say one, two three,
you scream. I won't blow the whistle.
One, two, three!
- Okay, we're going to start the timing.
- We have to drag out the time.
You can start your attack!
Attack!
[The eliminated team is approaching...]
You have to get closer.
[Jae Suk,
first to start the attack on Jong Kook]
Be careful, be careful.
[He's so cool]
[Geun Young starts attacking Jae Suk]
Geun Young, hurry up and attack him.
[Just then!]
[Mr. Capable attacks Gary!]
[Without any strength left, Gary is out!]
[Geun Young not letting go of Jae Suk!]
[Even Yoon Ho is out with one shove!]
I haven't used this yet.
Think of pogs! Pogs!
[Jae Suk...
even withstanding Mr. Capable's attack?]
[This time, it's on the offense!]
[After flying like a bird...
slammed down to the ground]
[Even though they feel bad, it's still funny!]
[Wrestling - Pogs - Chicken Fight.
Total humiliation.]
[In the meantime, the girls!]
[Running Man's last hope is
always Ace, Ji Hyo!]
[What do I do?]
Song Ji Hyo! Song Ji Hyo!
[Geun Young attacking
Ji Hyo with her strength!]
- Hey!
- Blank Ji, Blank Ji...
[Good job, Geun Young!]
[Geun Young's aggressive attack!]
Good job! You're doing great!
Why is she so scary?
Why do you keep running away and
tiring Geun Young out?
[Exhausted Ace Ji Hyo is finally ousted.]
[Dumping the blame]
It must be nice for you to beat a girl!
Feels good to have beaten a girl?
I didn't do anything!
I was just standing there!
You lifted up your leg!
All I did was slightly lift up my leg
when you approached me!
Ji Hyo, we saw it. Don’t worry.
[At this rate, there's going
to be another eliminated team...]
- Who is it?
- The quickest team to have been eliminated
will be on the same team with us.
Ji Suk Jin and Lee Kwang Soo.
We welcome you to our team.
Congratulations!
Welcome to our team.
At this point, we'll take off your bell.
[Cutting off their lifeline bell]
[The final mission is 'Bell hide and seek.']
[The two teams who've been able to keep
their bells are automatically the chasers.]
[There has to be something for
the defense team to win too...]
This team will be chasing you first.
Other team will head to the final location first.
- Defense team will head off first.
- Okay, let's go.
Thank you! Thank you!
[The battle scene...
Marine police station in Incheon]
I'm nervous.
I can't go in because it all says
intelligence, investigation and things...
[All the names on the offices...]
[We'll safely film the show thanks to
the cooperation of the police station.]
I'm scared... I'm kind of scared.
[It seems like the defense team
is looking for something...]
[Just what is it
that they're all looking for?]
Should we look for it first?
I feel a little strange snooping around
at a police station.
Right?
[Finally... the bell-chasing team
makes their entrance.]
[The dangerous team who's been
able to protect their bells to the end!]
If you watch closely at how
the elevators move...
that could also be a tip.
Right about now...
I bet they're on the 7th or 8th floor.
[Predicting where the Defense Team would be
by calculating the time]
[Geun Young excited over being the
chaser with the bells on]
The light in the hallway is on...
I wonder if anyone is down there?
Yes, I think so...
[Discovers Big-nosed Brother!]
[Of all places...]
[In danger of being ousted within
two minutes into the game!]
[Jong Kook and Geun Young chasing
at frightening speed!]
[And of all places, a dead end!]
[Without even any negotiations,
immediately ripping his name off!]
I told you to give me a minute!
- I was going to give you information...
- Suk Jin, start the race!
Race... start!
[The name even Geun Young knows well...
Race-starter, Big-nosed Brother!]
I think this is the quickest
I've ever been ousted.
[Ji Suk Jin - Out. Ji Suk Jin - Out]
When did they oust him? Where?
Already?
[The Defense Team becoming flustered at
the sudden announcement]
- Suk Jin was ousted!
- Suk Jin was ousted up there.
[Whatever they're searching for,
it seems they haven't found it yet.]
[The nervousness about the bell chase
that they're suddenly starting to feel]
I'm sure they're watching us right now...
Be careful going around.
[Defense Team is on the way again
to find something.]
Do you think we can go in there?
[A box with an 'R' sticker?]
Why do we have to get chased all the time?
[All of you without the bells are
on the Defense Team.]
If you survive to the end without having
your names ripped off, you win.
[However... if you find a bell with a
chaser's name on it, that person is out.]
[A chance for the Defense Team to
oust the chase team!]
[Is this a box with a bell inside?]
[A dud]
I'll keep it open so they just pass by it.
[Keeping it open so that the other
Defense Team members can see it's a dud]
I feel like it's going to be in here.
[Kwang Soo and Yoon Ho
are searching the office.]
- Have you seen a box by any chance?
- No, it's not here.
[A firm response fitting of a
Marine police station employee]
[The bell sound...]
[Escaping into an empty room!]
Lock the door. Lock the door!
It can be nerve-wracking like this.
Constantly being on the run
isn't always the best.
No matter if we lock the door or not.
It's like hiding in the women's bathroom.
- Someone's in here! In here!
- Someone’s in there!
Come out, come out!
[Ha Ha and Chang Min guarding both doors]
Is someone in there?
[The same person from earlier who can't lie!]
Sir, this is the police station, right?
There's a criminal in there
that we have to catch.
[Seeming as though they're trying to
escape into the hallway]
[As soon as Yoon Ho runs out by himself...]
[Traitorous Giraffe locking the door again]
[Ha Ha and Chang Min starting to chase
after Yoon Ho!]
I'm sorry... I'm sorry.
[Now's my chance!]
[Yoon Ho, you have to survive...]
[Meanwhile, Ha Ha and Chang Min
chasing Yoon Ho down with fervor!]
[Planning on capturing
by splitting up!]
[But Yoon Ho easily
bursts through the barricade!]
[Ha Ha trying to block him off again!]
[But he barges through again!]
Yoon Ho! Yoon Ho...
[They've got him cornered in a room...]
[They're going up against one another!
DBSK!]
[Yoon Ho in danger!]
[U-know Yoon Ho vs. Strongest Chang Min]
[Throwing their whole bodies
into the bloody battle!]
[U-know Yoon Ho is out!]
[In danger...
Defense Team's pillar Yoon Ho is out.]
[A feat brought on by
Chang Min's competitiveness!]
[U-know Yoon Ho, Out.
U-know Yoon Ho, Out]
[What do I do...]
[U-know Yoon Ho, Out.
U-know Yoon Ho, Out]
If Yoon Ho's out, what do we do?
What do we do?
There's only Jae Suk, Kwang Soo,
you and me left.
And we don't have any bells right now...
[Huh? Wait...]
[That guy in the uniform...]
[Giraffe in disguise, Kwang Soo?]
[A little while ago]
Excuse me, can you lend me
your clothes for a moment?
- Okay, I'll lend you mine.
- Is that okay?
[The Marine police officers helping out
the filming as a whole in every way]
Thank you!
If you go to the Internal Affairs office
downstairs, you can get a hat.
I'll bring it back to you on the fourth floor.
[This is how... he's been temporarily
transformed into a Marine Police Officer!]
[Oh... not bad!]
[In search of an 'R' marked box in uniform!]
[Meanwhile, a more enthusiastic Chang Min
after the capture also on the move!]
I'll just go through for a moment.
[As if his chasing instinct has been
awakened from its slumber...]
[Where could the box be?]
[Chang Min earnestly on the chase]
[This isn't it either...]
You must be tired.
[It seems as though Chang Min may
do more than his share today!]
[At this rate,
it's impossible to go downstairs!]
[Racing to escape back up the stairs
without having any other choice!]
Jae Suk...
[Of all things, running in to Ha Ha!]
- Ha Ha...
- You want to make a go at it?
[A big trouble since he can't rip off
the Chase Team's nametag!]
- Who were you with?
- I'll be honest with you...
You're trying to run, aren't you?
Then hand someone over to me.
I’m too tired to go up against you right now.
If you go down 2 floors...
Kwang Soo is down there.
- Can you swear to that?
- I swear.
Let's go together. You lead the way.
How can I go with my back to you right now?
Then... you can come behind me.
If you run from me,
I'll chase you to the ends of the earth.
[Yoo-ruce Willis bluffing his way
into buying himself some time?]
Seriously...
[Meanwhile, at the same time,
the Giraffe in disguise...]
[He comes to a place where there are
many boxes piled in a room...]
[Could there be a box
with the 'R' mark in here?]
[Finally discovers a box with the 'R' mark!]
I found it... I found it!
[Discovers the mission bell!]
[Someone from the Chase Team
is about to get ousted!]
[Just whose name is inside the bell?]
[Strongest Chang Min, Out.
Strongest Chang Min, Out.]
[In that case...]
[Strongest Chang Min's name
was inside the bell!]
[Strongest Chang Min, Out.
Strongest Chang Min, Out.]
[Chase Team becoming flustered at their
partner being ousted so unexpectedly]
Lee Kwang Soo has
found a bell with your name.
Kwang Soo?
[It wasn't even someone else...]
Kwang Soo did?
All the Cassiopeias...
[A formal apology to the DBSK fan club]
I didn't mean to get them both ousted,
but I was just trying to do my best too...
[Meanwhile, Jae Suk who bluffed
about taking Ha Ha to Kwang Soo...]
Bring him out here to me.
- Okay, I got it!
- Hurry.
- Do I really have to betray him?
- Quickly.
You promised.
Kwang Soo!
[Pressing the elevator button in
preparation to escape]
[He has to make his escape before
Ha Ha finds out that he was bluffing!]
Ha Ha is keeping watch from over there.
[There's only one way to make his escape!]
[Why isn't he bringing Kwang Soo to me?]
Kwang Soo...
[Pretending to be calling for Kwang Soo]
[Getting in the elevator...]
[He's been deceived!]
[Just in the nick of time!]
[Yoo-ruce Willis barely escaping danger!]
I'm so mad!
[Ha Ha, out. Ha Ha, out.]
Me? Me?
[Huh? How did this happen?]
I was just with Jae Suk...
Me? I'm out?
Why am I out?
[Ha Ha, out. Ha Ha, out]
[The person who ousted Ha Ha is...]
[Is none other than the Monday Couple!]
[Just discovered
the mission bell in the display room!]
[Ha Ha]
[Chase Team - Jong Kook and Geun Young vs.
Defense Team's Jae Suk, Ji Hyo, Gary, Giraffe]
[Ha Ha, out. Ha Ha, out.]
Who? Ha Ha?
[I was seriously just going to let this go...]
Did Kwang Soo find your name?
Why are you running around so hard?
Your face is sweating so much...
I caught Yoon Ho first...
- It got your spirits up, didn’t it?
- It really got my spirit up...
And I ran around like a dog
that’s lost its mind...
What? Is that Kwang Soo?
Hey! What the...
- What are you doing?
- Kwang Soo!
Kwang Soo, we can still tell that it's you.
- It's really noticeable.
- It's noticeable?
- You're still alive, right?
- Yes, I'm still alive.
- I'm sorry about earlier. I...
- No, it's okay.
[Yoon Ho coolly forgiving Kwang Soo
of his betrayal]
I'll make you proud!
Chang Min, I didn't know it was your bell.
[I can't forgive you...]
- You're looking for mission boxes?
- He's calling someone!
- Look. He's calling someone.
- Jong Kook, Kwang Soo's in a police uniform.
Yes, Jong Kook. In a police uniform.
- What are you doing?
- He's in a blue police uniform.
He's on the second floor... yes.
Just take it off!
Why isn't he answering the phone?
Shall we meet back up on the second floor?
Second floor? Okay, okay...
[Jong Kook and Geun Young
actively on the hunt]
It's Jong Kook...
[Now he can tell just from
the sound of his footsteps...]
It's Kim Jong Kook...
[Defense Team is searching through areas
where they suspect the box would be...]
Ah, there's no prize room? Thank you...
Gary! I hear the bell!
[I'm pretty sure I heard Ji Hyo's voice...]
Gary! I can hear the bell!
Hide! Hide!
I can't believe he's running away by himself!
How can you run away by yourself?
They can't see in here from outside.
Don't worry.
[Escaping into the interrogation room.
And they can look out from here...]
[No one can see in from the outside.]
Coming... someone's coming in.
Who is it?
[Mr. Capable steps into the room!]
I'm so scared!
Did anyone come in here by any chance?
[He is slowly approaching...
what if he can see inside?]
Quiet... stay quiet.
[Whew! It seems like he's headed back out!]
He's coming back! He's coming back!
[Why is Mr. Capable coming back?]
Please... you can't tell him!
Excuse me, but by any chance,
was anyone in here?
Was anyone in here?
You're smiling... Seeing how you're
smiling, someone's in here?
People don't usually smile for no reason.
They usually don't...
Was... someone in here?
[Something is fishy in here...]
[He's coming this way!]
[Mr. Capable having made up his mind
to thoroughly search this office]
Please excuse me.
I'm sorry, but people are smiling and...
[He really can't see in here...]
[Interrogation room]
[He's... just leaving!]
Why is that door locked?
[Whew...]
He's leaving!
[Mr. Capable finally steps out of the room!
What a relief...]
Just in case... let's wait a little to leave.
Jong Kook is back! He came back!
[Mr. Capable coming back with
his investigative instinct!]
[This time he returns with
his chase partner, Geun Young!]
[Still no worries thanks to the
special two-way mirror!]
[Gary’s even starting to joke around now!]
Is anyone in there?
[Strange...]
I'm sorry, but if the door's locked,
isn't there a key to open it?
- I think she’s in charge of that.
- Oh, really?
[The same woman from earlier
who wouldn't say anything!]
Ma'am...
Geun Young, go stand in front of the door.
[Convincing her to lend them the key
to the interrogation room for a moment]
Ma'am?
I wish I could tear your nametags off!
She said she's going to get us the key.
Just wait a minute.
[Alarm like a bolt of lightning]
If you come out before we get the key...
Jong Kook is getting the key!
I definitely told you!
I'm going to count to three. One...
[It's only a matter of time until
the door is opened now!]
You've all worked so hard...
[Monday couple full of fear]
Geun Young, don't hold onto me right now.
- What were you doing in there?
- We can't escape anyways...
Wait...
[With his hand on the tag...]
- Hurry up and tear it off.
- No, Jong Kook... that’s not right!
[Without any negotiations,
Ji Hyo's also ousted]
[Within moments, the Monday Couple is out!]
[Blank...]
- Goodbye!
- Thank you!
[Leaving after thanking everyone
for cooperating with them]
Gary, out. Gary, out.
Song Ji Hyo, out. Song Ji Hyo, out.
What do we do?
[Jae Suk and Kwang Soo,
the sole survivors of the Defense Team]
Are they right below us?
What do we do?
[Will these two be able to beat
Jong Kook and Geun Young?]
What should we do?
I can't find it anywhere!
[No other choice
but to find the mission bells!]
The fourth floor... let's go up there.
Jong Kook! Jong Kook!
Kwang Soo! Kwang Soo!
[Starting the chase!]
[It's now two against two!
The real battle starts now!]
[Escaping like a bolt of lightning!]
[The Chase Team is
slowly starting to close in.]
[Mr. Capable searching one room at a time]
[The two succeed in escaping
far away in the meantime.]
I really don't want to live like this.
[The story of their lives...]
This is too hard...
Seriously, Kwang Soo...
I don't want to live like this.
What is it that I've done so wrong?
Nonstop for the past two years...
why do I have to be chased by Kim Jong Kook?
What is it that I've done so wrong?
[Still shaking in his boots every time
he locks eyes with the Tiger]
What do we do?
[If they can find
at least one of the mission bells...]
Then let's get moving.
We have to move quickly.
[Deciding to each take an office
to search for the bells]
[It could definitely be around here
since no one's searched here yet.]
[The sound of bells ringing!]
We're in big trouble...
[There's no place to hide...
under the desk for now!]
[His own VJ, Kwon Yeol, has to hide too!]
Hurry up and hide! The camera!
- Have you seen Lee Kwang Soo?
- He went that way.
[Huh? He looks familiar...]
[The one who lent his uniform
to Kwang Soo earlier...]
- Have you seen Lee Kwang Soo?
- He went that way.
[Kindly notifying them where
the traitorous Giraffe went to]
I took it off...
I took off the police uniform.
[The Chase Team closing in!]
I'm in big trouble...
[The ever-so-nearing bell sound!]
What do I do? My shoes are ruined.
[Geun Young discovers Yoo-ruce Willis!]
[Kind Geun Young gently approaches...]
[And pulls him out]
Wait... wait...
[Yoo-ruce Willis in extreme danger!]
Geun Young, wait...
[Maybe Kwang Soo will come to help!]
[What is Jae Suk's fate?]
[The cold killer instinct, Geun Young...]
So this is where you were hiding.
- Whose shoes did you see, Geun Young?
- Your shoes.
- You... who's shoes did you see, Geun Young?
Geun Young, you're amazing!
[Huh?]
[Kwang Soo...]
What the heck? It's Kwang Soo!
[The prey, Giraffe,
delivering himself to the door]
[He came thinking he'd help...
but ruined himself instead!]
[Totally caught, Giraffe!]
Jae Suk!
[Giraffe meat being delivered to
the Tiger's den]
Jae Suk! Please! Jae Suk...
[Cold killer, Geun Young finishes him off!]
Why would you come here?
[Chase Team's Jong Kook and Geun Young's
hunting is a huge success!]
He was about to open the door...
Why would you come down here?
- I didn't know he'd be standing there.
- It's okay...
I came to help you!
You should've just abandoned me
and gone on your way!
I didn't think you were ousted yet
because I didn't hear anything.
What did you say? It’s over, right?
[With such a chaotic ending,
not able to believe that it's all over]
Everyone...
My Geun Young did it.
[My... Geun Young?]
And... Yoon Ho who's here after such
a long absence... he's like our black hole.
And every time he loses,
this is what he does.
[The only memory they have of him is his
disappointed face every time he lost.]
Chang Min, he's really good!
[A prize to the four members
of the Chase Team that won the game]
[What is it? What is it?]
[The winning prize...
A gold Marine Police Badge]
- It's a police badge...
- It's gold!
Our sister-in-law for being with us
for the past two weeks...
We're really grateful that
you came on the show.
I thank everyone for all your support...
and I'll try to start a new life too.
What is this?
You think this is a dating game?
- What about you, Geun Young?
- I'll try to live happily ever after too.
[Oh my goodness...]
[Oh my goodness...
look at their beet-red faces!]
Do you all know what
the number for the Marines is?
- Yes!
- 122!
We'd all like to thank you again! Thank you!
Next week's preview
[Does he want to change the future?]
[Today, that becomes a reality!]
The one who sees into the future!
[The one who sees into the future!]
[He controls the future]
If I hadn't seen the future,
I would've been had by him.
Why am I here? What am I doing here?
- What happened?
- I can see the future.
[The one who tries to see the future]
I saw it! I saw the future!
[Pay the price for changing the future!]
I didn't do anything!
[A town where the bounds
of time have disappeared.]
[A place of utter chaos!]
[The one who sees the future -
Coming next week]