You're bleeding!
it's okay.
I will absolutely not let this pass.
They want to kill us.
Oppa Is annoying.
Who does she think she's talking to?
Really?
Oh, hello.
Please bring another cup of coffee here.
Please get me a cup of coffee.
Really long time no see.
Yes. really.
Are you alone?
Yes, as for now it seems like this.
By the way, how old are you?
I'm born in the year 1978.
Ah. I'm born in 1979.
So you are hyung.
I am proposing to Miss Han Ye Jin now.
I will solve this, don't worry.
Hyungnim!
Oh, hyung. What are you doing here?
I didn't even see you guys because you’re in black.
Hello.
Please come over this side.
What are you doing here, Dong Wan?
You really do anything and everything!
Welcome to YeoSu.
Please proceed over there to take a bus.
Follow here, please follow me.
What do you mean by this?
"Follow here" and "Please follow me" what's that?
Who's that?
Oh, hyung!
Hyungnim, you've come.
Yes. I've come.
What sort of weapon is placed inside here?
Bell Hide and Seek.
Please eliminate all the Running Men.
We will give you 2 chances to recruit spies.
Chance to recruit...
What did you just say?
We will give you 2 chances to recruit spies.
Before the Running Man members complete their mission
Eliminate all of them for your mission to succeed!
What, what does this mean?
What on earth does this mean?
There were never such things in the past.
We will give you 2 chances to recruit spies.
So this means we can recruit 2 spies?
Eliminate everyone...
What's the meaning, I don't understand a bit.
To eliminate means to tear off the name tags, right?
What is the method of elimination?
Today's mission is,
Running Men will foe moving around 3 areas in YeoSu.
While moving about,they'll be give missions They'll think they doing the race aione.
The Running Men totally do not know' of your existence,
At the final location,tear off the Running Man members' tags to eliminate them, and yon will be victorious.
if there is at least 1 person remaining to successfully complete the mission, then tiie victory belongs to tiie Running Men,
There's only one person left.
Do we succeed if we don’t tear off our spies' nametag?
- Yes.
So, this means... Jae Suk, HaHa. and Kim Joong Kook...
The spy should be one good person and one slower person.
One of them will be the spy?
Can't you follow?
I am just thinking.
What if...
the spies are also in the Running Man team, right?
Of course. Didn't I just say?
-1 am listening.carefully.
Us wearing black clothes, the four of us...
It's better for us to split up into teams.
Hyung, you should have eaten before coming for a recording.
So let’s split into 2 persons per team, how's that?
-I'm listening -2 persons a team, what do you think?
Good idea.
If we move together, it will he too obvious.
So let's split according to our height.
I am the shortest..
No, no.
Tall team, and short team.
It's so good to be tall..
It’s all settled, so let's go.
Let's do a cheer.
Killers also do cheers?
I don't know.
1, 2, 3, Fighting!
Not bringing the bag along?
It will explode by itself in a while.
After conveying the mission, it will automatically explode.
Wah, this place is really beautiful! It's all beaches!
I will now introduce, the first sightseeing location.
-YeoSu Fisheries Market. -Yes.
Now I will give all of you this. There will be information inside.
YeoSu sightseeing information. It's here,
if you take a look at tiie map.
There's a place called YeoSu Fisheries Market.
It's here!
It came up!
Below, there will be information about this market.
Are we studying now?
Why are making us study a lot lately?
Full shot. Best best!
But is it a little coincidental today?
There are 4 men.
Yes.
Shall we duke it out with Jong Kook?
It's not like you're alone, us hyungs will be around too.
Us hyungs mean what we say.
This is the fish market.
I’m getting jittery.
Hold on.
Isn't it too easy to be exposed in here?Youxan-see everything with ease.
Plus our black suits are even more eye-catching.
Aren't they movie actors?
Shh, it's a secret.
Are there good places here?
How about here?
Hey, how about that dry cleaning shop?
It's not ba ?
Hello
Do you know Running Man?
- That show on tv... -Yeah,that's right.
Something about chasing?
- You do know.fight? - What are you here for?
We're looking for a place to observe the area.
That place with a window can help us.
We'll observe from there for awhile.
But there are no guests today?
There should be.
But there will be an elimination here.
When you react  there, complete your mission after alighting,
but finish within the time limit.
-It's like that. -There's no elimination?
Completing the mission and boarding the bus within the time limit will be a success
failing to board wifi lead to elimination.
-Who will be eliminated? -Kwang Soo, Haha.
We're here. Hurry up and give me the mission.
Starting from now, you have 30 minutes.
Find Aunt Im Sun Shim and buy blue crabs.
And you have to get the person's signature.
-Buy clam skewers from Aunt Park Bong Jin. -Me. What is it?
Buy mustard leaf kimchi from Aunt Son Chun Ja.
Buy octopus from Aunt Jang Yong Ja.
Yong Ja. I got it.
What do you know?
Buy pickled big-eye herring from Aunt Shin Geum Ja.
-Huh? Pickled big-eye herring? -It means pickled Jong Kook*.
Buy Washington Ciams from Aunt Sae^ Veon Aunt Shim.
Buy tongue soie from Aunt Park Hwa Ja.
Tongue Sole. ah.
Washington Clams? Washington Clams? This Washington Clam?
The sea! It's the smell of the sea!
Hello.
Perhaps you know Aunt Shin Geum Ja?
Do you know Shin Geum Ja?
Shin...Aunt Shin Geum Ja!
Hello!
Hello. Aunt Park Hwa Ja.
-Park Hwa Ja ? -General goods store is there.
No not the general goods store. Aunt Park Hwa Ja.
Aunt, it's not the general goods store.
Hello! What a delicious smell.
Aunt Son Chun Ja!
Aunt Shin Geum Ja!
Aunt Shin Geum Ja. we're running out of time!
No not spinach (shigeumchi), it's Aunt Shin Geum Ja.
Shin, Aunt Shin Geum Ja .
It's already afternoon now.
Really? Is that bad?
Just nice, the position Is just nice.
Right, what will the mission be?
I'm really curious about the mission. I'm going crazy.
Why aren't they here yet?
Actually we don't know if they will take this path.
Then we'll be waiting in vain.
After 2 or 3 hours they'll all be going home and we'll still be waiting.
Ah, it couldn't be.
That will be a real betrayal.
Have you seen it on the web?
The toughest.jdb is the policeman during a game.
Oh. that's right.
They have their backs to the game while listening to cheers.
I can't do that. I'll be too curious to do that.
Can we eat this mandarin orange?
I didn't prepare anything.
If you want to eat go ahead, but don't eat too many.
I felt like eating the orange when I saw it.
I'll start eating. Just one.
Delicious, delicious!
Aunt Son Chun Ja.
Aunt Chun Ja.
The one selling mustard leaf kimchi, Aunt Chun Ja!
Have you found yours?
Aunt Chun Ja!
Where do they sell clam skewers?
Oh. behind?
Aunt Park Bong Jin!
Hello, are you Aunt Park Bong Jin?
I am Park Bong Jin.
Oh. Aunty, hello!
Oh, Aunt Park BongJin!
I found Aunt Park Bong Jin.
Please give me some Clam skewers.
-How much is it? - It should be 18000 but I’ll sell it at 16000.
- No no. I'll buy for 18000. -16000 is enough
-No, no. 18000. -No need to measure.
I found her. I'm thankful that she raised her hand.
Thank you very much. Please take 18000.
Eomoni. please give me a signature.
-How do I sign? -Just sign here.
Be careful, be careful.
Where is Park Hwa Ja ?
Eomoni.
Your name is Park...?
-Park Hwa Ja. -Park Hwa Ja .
Aunt.
You're here. Aunt.
Aunt Park Hwa Ja.
That!s right. Aunt, I'm here to buy tongue sole.
-Tongue Sole? -Tongue Sole, Tongue Sole.
Aunt, is this Tongue Sole? Tongue Sole!
More handsome in real life.
-Aunt Shin Geum Ja! - No...
I am Shin Geum Ja.
Jeez, hyung.
You haven't found her yet?
Aunt, you must take care of your health.
Here's wishing you a happy new year.
May your business prosper.
I'm going off. Good job everyone!
-Aunt Jang Yong Ja. -I'll check it.
Aunt Jang Yong Ja. octopus, correct!
Please get on.
Haha, aunt Park Bong Jin.
Aunt Chun Ja. Is Aunt Chun Ja here?
Aunt Shin Geum Ja!
Aunt Chun Ja!
-Aunt Chun Ja? - I'm not.
Gary, Gary.
Aunt, Aunt Chun Ja.
I got it, I know the mission.
He's looking for some mustard leaf kimchi Master.
Ah, some aunt, some aunt.
Aunt! Mustard leaf kimchi!
It's mustard leaf kimchi.
Aunt Shin Geum Ja!
I have something to tell you.
Over there.
Aunt Chun Ja!
-We can't just. -stay here. Let's go.
Uncle, thanks a lot. Happy New Year.
Ah, where is it?
Aunt Shim Geum Ja!
Aunt, hello. Are you Aunt Shim Geum Ja?
Oh! Aunt, I finally found you.
Please give me some salted fish.
Are you Aunt Son Chun Ja? Ah, really?
Please give me some mustard leaf kimchi.
Aunt, where have you been.
Quickly!
You've been here all this while.
I was going crazy looking for you.
Please sign here.
Hang on, Aunt Shim Geum Ja!
Be quiet.
Do you want to die or to be a Spy?
- Quickly say it. die or Spy? -A Spy. a Spy.
You are a Spy now.
Hyung, when did you arrive?
We came two days ago.
Am I a Spy now? What do I do?
Together with us. you eliminate the remaining members.
I'm extremely good at this game.
I got it.
Hyung, I'll do well. No one will suspect me.
Ok, I got it.
Thank you so much.
You don't have to be too grateful.
I've always wanted to be a spy.
It will be an important turning point when you watch the show.
That's right.
If you tell the Running Man members, you are immediately out.
Yes, out immediately.
It will end our relationship too.
- That's our relationship. - We'll sort our relationship like this.
Jeez, hyung.
Can he be a Spy?
-I don't know. -He doesn't feel too reliable.
We could just hold him and not let him go back in 30 minutes.
Ok. go. Go.
- I'll really do well. -Fighting, go!
Fighting.
It's done.
Firstly, our goal has been achieved.
Aunt!
Yeosu is a city that brings luck!
This is like a dream!
Sung Soo, our mission has succeeded.
We instigated Kwang Soo.
Let’s rip them all here.
I have lots of confidence after catching Kwang Soo.
- Is he eliminated?
I passed right?
You passed.
Hey. why was it so hard?
Oh, the jeotgal shop was too far in.
Look, Kwang Soo sent this.
Kwang Soo sent a heart, a heart.
Hyung, it's a little weird.
Isn't the mission too easy?
Could there be something else? Someone has different mission?
Recently you are so sensitive!
- The music is not bad? -It is, right?
We're going to the next destination.
It's Odong Island.
It's here.
While we’re here, we need to decide where to lie in ambush.
We need to decide which Running an member to target.
Firstly, find the path that the unning Man will take.
Hey, it's really awesome.
We have to find a place to hide, then jump out and catch them.
Behind the trees.
Chun Hee. Everything can be seen, just come out.
Why?
It's hard to even get in.
Hyung, we can just find a black tree.
It's pretty dark in here.
That's because we're wearing sunglasses.
The second attraction is the famous Odong isiand
Wow, the water is really clear!
Hyung, look at the water!
There's a time limit for this mission too.
The second mission's time limit is 45 minutes.
Alight the camelia train and find Running Men!
-What?Running Man? -Aren't we Running Man?
There are people giving the mission.
Looks like it’s Dong Wan's first time introducing the mission.
Dong Wan, is it like this or what?
I don't think so.
-But what is camellia car? -It's my first time here too.
The camellia's are really beautiful, hyung.
It's Miss Camellia.
Wow, it's seriously awesome,
see the sea and not the steps below.
So over here, like this.
Should we test it?
Oh Chun Hee, what are you doing there?
You can see me?
But it's better here.
Anyone approaching can be seen.
We only have to hide ourselves properly.
We have to climb the hill?
Hello.
Today we're running around and climbing hills.
It's Running Man.
Hey. one at a time! Ah, seriously...
Wow, it's really nice here, the best.
Hey, it's aivesome.
What's this place?
Odd or even?
Even!
-Odd! -Stand aside.
Ah, you have to be up ahead for this.
Should I guess odd or even?
Odd or even?
Even, even!
Even!
Thanks.
-Ah what is this? - Is it really the end?
Only one can win at the mission.
It's over?
It s over?
Hey, we have to go elsewhere.
Go quickly, go quickly.
Kwang Soo. really, thank you!
Jong Kook, see you later!
Kwang Soo!
Seriously, thanks so much!
I was about to say 'odd.'
This is the best view.
How can it be so nice?
-How old are you? -21 years old.
It's very cold, isn't it?
Your hands are completely frozen.
Seems like you have a girlfriend?
-Ah, no, I don't. -You don't?
Lets go to the Cave of Dragon.
Shouldn't I get it right here?
-Dong Hoon! -Ah, I'm sorry. Somehow I unconsciously...
-Hello, little girl! - Hello! -Hi! - HaHa!
Why won’t you greet me? Hello!
-1. 2, 3! Ah, I took it, thank you! -Yes, thank you! Bye, see you again!
Ah, seriously I...why is this so far away?!
If I don't get it right here. I'm seriously going to lose my temper.
Ah. seriously...
Should I pick odd or even?
-It's even! -Odd!
Ah, I'm seriously going crazy!
-Hyung. -I didn't play these games when I was little!
Hyung. I'm sorry but I'm going to get it right.
Even!
You thought you'd win before your hyung?
Bungeobbang is so delicious.
I haven’t eaten this in a while.
Killers have to eat too.
Killers may show a tough image
but they eat bungeobbang and everything else, as well.
Of course.
Wow, seriously, there are too many places to hide over there.
-It was a good idea that we went first. -Yeah, it was.
-We have to run. We have to run. -This is so far away, really.
Hang on, it should be somewhere over there.
Sunrise Place!
Oh, he's there!
Found him!
Found him! Ah, oppa!
Who are you?!
No one is coming, nobody's coming.
-When did you two get here? -I told you JI Hyo would come here.
-How long have you been here? - We've been over there since morning.
Daebak!
-Someone might come. -Nobody's coming, seriously no one is going to come.
They all went off to do the mission.
-They're really all somewhere else. They're all gone. -We can trust you, right?
-If your name tag is ripped off, you're out, right? -Why are you taking it off?
Do you want to be eliminated or...?
Do you have it?
Do you want to be a spy?
What kind of choice is this?
-What kind of choice is this? -Then do you just want to be out right from the beginning?
-No. no, I understand. I'll be a spy. I'll be a spy. Hang on. -You'll have to be on our side.
No, I mean. oppa...
-If someone is chosen as a spy. they should be happy. -No, no.
-You’ve truly decided, right? -Yes, yes, ok. I'll do it.
However, if you're found out by the other members, you're out right away.
-I got it. - You understand, right? - Yes.
-How were you hiding here all of this time? -It was so cold, we have been waiting here since morning.
-Do you know how scared I was? -You're on our side now.
-I got it. -It's nice to see you.
- We already chose Kwang Soo. -Ah, really?
Why did you pick Kwang Soo?
If Kwang Soo is the spy, no one is going to believe there's only one spy.
They won't think he's the only one. They'll suspect others.
It's entirely possible the fact that there are spies at all will be revealed.
-Why did you choose Kwang Soo? - It’s not like we can change spies at this point.
No, you can’t. He's by himself on the other side.
I'm not running by myself.
Two individuals are sitting on my shoulders.
I must run. I must run.
I'll be going, oppa. See you later.
-Do not tell anyone our secret otherwise you'll be out immediately. -Ok, I understand.
-Our side. -Our side, our side, yes. Goodbye!
This turned out well.
-Since Ji Hyo is really smart... -She is.
Will I be a successful spy today? I'm in big trouble.
If we take too much time, the oppas may start suspecting me. Let's hurry.
Hello?
Who did you choose?
We chose Ji Hyo.
Ah, Ji Hyo. ok.
We pretended there were only two of us.
So you're saying you picked Ji Hyo, right? I see.
Aw. you worked hard. We bought something delicious for you. so come quickly.
-We're going to the city hall now. -Ok, see you there.
They said they chose Ji Hyo.
-It s Ji Ho, right?*-Ji Hyo.
-Ah, Ji Hyo, Ji Hyo. -This will probably go on air.
It's Ji Hyo. right? JI Hyo.
-I think we'll be able to win. -Yes, with Kwang Soo and Ji Hyo. Excellent.
Good job in this cold weather.
We'll go around quickly, and watch from afar.
One person will be the bait, you do it. You'll be the one to lure Jong Kook out.
I'm going to be the bait?
-Ok, so I'll get caught then. - Yeah.just get caught by him first.
Do you think Jong Kook hyung will give up then?
-They won't even follow us, since they're not the chasers. -They're just gonna run away.
-They don't know who we are. -They'll just avoid us.
Because they're afraid of the bell sound, they'll avoid it.
-Then we should make as much noise as possible, right? -Then they'll just going to run away,
Hey, it's good you mentioned that now, otherwise we we'll be big trouble with your making that noise later.
-Do you want to do a test run of encountering Jong Kook? -No.
How about we try it out slowly with the three of us?
-Ok, let's try it. -Three people will be needed.
I can't do it, it's too painful.
1, 2, 3...Fighting!
-Can you tell us what's going on first? -What is this?
-Please receive the walkie-talkies first. -Walkie talkies?
-What's going on? -Wow. it's been a while since we used those.
-We're all one team? -There are definitely guests.
-Hey, I guess have to hide. -So we're going to be escaping and running around.
It seems like forever since we last used these,
Avoid the seekers wearing bells and find__________! Hints are located in the city hall's computers. The password is runningman
-runningmanl is the password? -I'm not good with computers, so how am I supposed to find the hints?
We don't really have an IT guy here.
There's me.
-Ah, Suk Jin hyung does know a little. -I'm good with IT.
Who's the seeker?
-It's been a longtime since we've all been on one team. - That's true.
Hey, come here! This is set for password login!
These all have password logins!
Don't you think we found this too quickly?
Is that the case?
What do I do? Do I click this here?
Hyung, do I click this?
-You have to press Enter. -Where do I press Enter?
Oh, here?
Ah, it says the password is incorrect.
It says it's the incorrect password.
Hyung, it's not this one!
This is an important time, if we get caught here...
Hyung. it's not this one either!
Not that one?
It's not this either.
Hyung, I think we came to the wrong place.
From the beginning, I had a bad feeling about this place.
This place must not be it.
The sound of bells...
It's nerve-wracking...
These doors are all locked.
They're here, they're here!
Oh, I hear it!
Really?
Hang on. hang on, hang on!
This is daebak, daebak! Completely daebak!
Hey!
What are you doing?! Run away!
-Come here. -These doors are all open.
Hyung, this means we have to escape at all costs.
It's been such a long time since we've done Bells Hide-And-Seek.
-It really has been. -The guests might just stake out so their bells can't be heard.
Think about what we did in the past.
We never staked anyone out during the Hide-And-Seek.
One person should stand guard. You do it.
We just fully chased one other everywhere.
You stand guard.
Ah, it's the wrong password.
The right computers are somewhere...
Hyung!
What?
-The sound of bells, the sound of bells, the sound of bells! -Where, where?
I hear ringing coming this way!
Hey, don't be frightened, don't be frightened!
Do we go right away?
We're going right away!
Who are they?
What is this?
Chun Hee hyung is here, too?
Who is it, who are they?!
Who is it, who is it?
Who are you? It s Chun Hee!
Oppa, go downstairs, downstairs!
Hyung. how can you let them escape!
Hurry, hurry!
Oppa, where are you?
Second floor, second floor!
Who is it. who is it, who is it?
Sung Soo hyung!
Let's hide. All the way at the end.
Let's hide here.
Wow, they were chasing us to the end. While wearing pitch-black clothing.
Oppa, hurry and check outside!
Me?
We should check the computers at least.
Check outside first so we can at least see if they're there or not.
Hey, hey!
Hey, Ji Hyo, no! Don't do it!
Ji Hyo. no! Don't do it!
Hang on. Chun Hee, hang on for a moment.
Hey, Ji Hyo, what are you?
Ji Hyo!
Hey, whose side are you on? Are you a spy?
Wait a minute, wait a minute.
No, no!
Why are you so strong?
You Clumsy Chun Hee! I'm telling you to hurry and rip it off!
Hey, what are you? Are you a spy?
Hey, what is this? What are you doing right now?
Hey, what is this?
You Clumsy Chun Hee!
SongJi Hyo! Seriously, you!
Hey, you!
Oppa, sorry, sorry.
You're a spy!
Look! You died before Sung Soo oppa came. Isn't that good?
-Oppa. -You're a spy?
I'm sorry!
Comer over here.
Ji Suk Jin. out! Ji Suk Jin, out!
Ah, somehow I feel sorry for him.
What are your missions?
Our mission is to key in the correct password in the computers in this floor.
Then hide from those wearing the bells, look for something.
By saying 'something1 you guys still don't know what that is, right?
Ahh! Alright. I understand.
Then let us finish them up!
Noona! Why was Suk Jin hyung eliminated?
Hey! You come here.
Why?
Come over quickly!
-Why? -Come here!
What?
You...You're a spy, right?!
We already caught Kwang Soo...
Ah, really? Why Kwang Soo?
You're a spy, right?
Oh?
What spy?
Are you a spy?
No, I'm not.
Stop lying!
Who did you meet up with and where did you go just now?
I hear the sound of bells.
Oh!
Who?
-I don't know! - Oh!
Isn't Kwang Soo a spy?
Noona is a spy?
Noona, you're a spy?
We're both spies!
-You're a spy. too? -That's right.
Noona, you're a complete wily fox.
Because we are spies, so we're on the same team.
We're on the same team?
They are on our team!
Ahh! Hello.
Hello.
One, two, three. Fighting!
But, we're too strong now.
Ah! What to do? It's my first time feeling like that!
So the other members don't know the existence of these two. right?
No, they don't.
So let's split up first.
They are over there!
Hyung! You go catch Jae Suk hyung.
Start from here. One by one.
I'm going crazy! When can I finish looking?
Is this how you switch on a computer?
I'm the hero of the race!
Can you believe it? I'm finally the hero!
Lee Chun Hee. out.' tee Chun Hee, out.'
Me?
Me? I'm out?
Lee Chun Hee got eliminated? Just now?!
How come?
How did Lee Chun Hee get eliminated?
Ah! I can talk using this.
Hey, Chun Hee! What happened?
Chun Hee!
I didn't do anything.
Why am I out?
Hyung, you search around carefully.
I’ll be going.
It's Me.
Chong Wook Ah.
come Over after you Sleep. Don't Cry.
What does this mean?
Don't film me!
Sir! Sir!
Excuse me, but can you sit over here?
I think I'll get caught.
Please help me.
Thank you!
Aren't you cold?
I'm fine.
When there are sound of the bells, I might be in danger.
So if someone wearing a bell asks if there's someone here, please say no.
Just act like you're working.
Anyone got caught?
Thank you! I got to live because of you.
Sir! Thank you so much!
Please sign for me before you go.
Yes, of course.
Why was he eliminated?
Use the computer and enter the password, there has to be a hint then you'll be eliminated.
This was how Chun Hee was eliminated.
So before they find the hints, we have to quickly tear off their name tags.
So we have to move faster?
We have to tell Jin Hee.
How did they eliminate Chun Hee?
Did you see?
- Yeah, I saw. -ls it the same as ours?
What's this? Did any of the Running Men crack the code?
Has anyone cracked the code?
HaHa here. I was the one who eliminated Lee Chun Hee.
How?
They'll get eliminated once you've found the computer.
So now we just have to quickly find the computers,
We have to quickly^finct the computers, so that we can quickly eliminated them.
Quickly find the computers.
Sir, please!
Oh. I'm tired.
I think your coffee is ready!
I'm coming out.
- There's no end to it! - I'm a fan.
I had no choice. I'll see you later.
Am I out just like this?
Hyung, do your best.
Can I take this?
That, you can take home.
Ah, I got it. a souvenir.
Fighting.
You, you, what are you doing?
Hey, Lee Kwang Soo.
What are you doing?
What situation is this?
Gary, out. Gary. out.
Kwang Soo, where are you?
Hyung, l'm on the second floor now.
Where are the Killers?
They're not on the second floor now. Hyung, where are you?
Hyung's on the third floor.
Hyung, I'll go to the third floor first.
Ok, you come over.
Hyung, hyung!
Jong Kook hyung!
Kwang Soo is weird!
Why?
Kwang Soo's acting weird.
-Is that so? - Yes!
Kwang Soo couldn't possibly have survived till now.
That's why!
We have to check over there quickly, hyung.
Jong Kook hyung's must be eliminated by me.
HaHa. you hide at the back, lie In ambush.
Dong Hoon, lock the door when he comes in, got it?
Just lock it.
Kwang Soo.
- Oh hyung, why are you here? -Are you all right?
-Yes. Why are you, why... - Hello.
-Are you alone? -How did you come here?
-Ah, I ran here, what do you mean how I came? - No, how did you come here.
Ah. this here, do you enter the password here?
I didn't do anything, I didn't do anything, I don't know anything.
But hang on. How did you come over here?
I took a plane.
No. no. How did you come into this room?
-I just came along while searching, how else? - Really?
-You came here after searching on your own? -Of course, yes.
-Why, why? -Oh?
-Where did he go, my dongaseng? - What dongsaeng? There's still a dongsaeng?
Why are you. why are you here?
Me, I came to take your nametag.
-Why else would I be here? - Hyung! Ah, hang on.
Don't do this.
- No. no. -Aigoo. just hang in there a little more!
Can't you tear someone else's?
They're all caught, they're all caught.
-Really? -They've all been caught.
Ah hyung, can't you let me off?
Hello.
Has anyone been here? Have you seen the others?
No one came?
Jae Suk hyung!
Hang on, hang on.
Hey, catch him quickly.
Ah, how many of you are there?
Sung Soo.
-Huh? -Sung Soo.
Ah. Sung Soo?
Where?
Where is he?
Sung Soo's here?
Ah, Sung Soo...hey, Kwang Soo. you...
Hey, Sung Soo came!
Hey! Ah, you came too? Hey. you came?
No, when did you come?
Ah, there are four of you.
What?
This is seriously fun.
How many Chasers are there now?
Ah, if you're coming you should have told me, sent me a text or something.
Ah. what are you doing?
Ok, he went up right?
Did he go up? There's no way up.
So did he go down?
Hey. I was chased...hey.l was searching, when they came in!
Hey. how can you not keep up?
Ah, how did I end up here?
I shall leave first!
Ah sure, Sang Wook.
-I'll leave first, I’ll see you later! -Right, right.
Go catch the others first.
Ah yes, I got it!
They normally won’t leave.
Sang Wook won't leave either right?
I'm seriously sorry to the female employees.
I'll stay for awhile and leave.
I’m seriously sorry.
I have to go out and look around.
I can't be hiding in the lounge.
You have to open the door.
What? Ah yes, yes.
-Is someone inside? -I'm sorry, yes.
Ah, thank you for your help.
Why Joo Sang Wook...
No, what's with all this?
No. I was sorry for hiding here just now!
I thought you were sleeping inside.
Did have to do this?
Ah yes, thank you.
How could you help him? I've been caught now.
I'm his fan too!
-I'm sorry, for going into the female lounge. - Yes, thank you.
I'm seriously sorry.
I was just too desperate.
Hyung, you escaped so well, but in the end...
You have to catch hold of him.
Ah. really.
Now we'll...
Hey, Lee Kwang Soo.
Hey, Lee Kwang Soo, you're seriously too much.
Tear them all.
There’s no time, let's go. Let's go up.
-Yoo Jae Suk. Lee Kwang Soo. out. -Me too?
Hey. what are you?
Weren't you a Spy?
I'm a Spy.
Then? Why are you out?
Why are you out?
Hide, hide.
Daebak,daebak.
I'm the main character, I'm the main character.
I'm the main character of this race!
Joo Sang Wook is out. Joo Sang Wook is out.
Hey Jae Suk, you're out?
Ah, why is Sang Wook here too?
Exactly.
-Chun Hee, you should have told hyung, if you were coming. -Hyung, hello.
Hey, Lee Kwang Soo. you...
- Hey but, wasn't he a Spy? -Why is he out if he's a Spy?
- You were of no use so we got rid of you. -You were of no use.
Greet each other.
If Family Outing had you. Running Man has Kwang Soo.
I've heard a lot about you since I've been here.
No, but now...
Do you know Ji Hyo's with them too?
- Also, it's really... what? -Did you know Ji Hyo's on their side?
-Ji Hyo's on their side. -Why?
-How many Spies are there? -There are two.
Why am I out?
What's the reason?
The Killers were doing very vveii.
What did they do well?
-Earlier, you had other missions, in the day right. -Yes.
During that period, they were recruiting their Spies.
Ah, really?
They were at the market and Odong Island the whole time.
Since when?
Ah. when we were purchasing the items?
I. I was In a Mason.
I was in a Mason.
Being with spies like you...
This informant!
You're really the informant, hey!
Hey, but why are you here, you're the Spy.
Ah, what's with him?
Which side am I on, what am I?
Ok. have fun!
That walkie-talkie, isn't that ours?
Sir, let us use the Internet for awhile.
Yes. can we search for this, 'the creator of the turtle ship'?
It's coming out, it's out.
See! It's done, it's done.
Let’s check this too.
Ah! 'Never tell the enemy the news of my death'.
That's what I was saying.
'Never tell the enemy the news .of my death1.
Thank you.Thank you.
-Anyone there -No one.
Ji Hyo, about this. Tell Jong Kook hyung about it.
He's on the first floor, the first floor.
Jong Kook hyung, Jong Kook hyung. do you hear me?
Hey, it's just left with us both.
Ji Hyo, HaHa.
Ah, HaHa!
Hey, HaHa has to be caught.
Where is HaHa?
We don't even know where HaHa is and he's been searching all this while.
Dong Hoon, where are you?
Ji Hyo.
What? I'm together with HaHa oppa!
Oppa, let's go to the first floor.
Let's go, let's go.
Hey, hey.
Hey Ji Hyo. run!
Oppa!
Not me!
Ah, so frustrating!
Ji Hyo, run!
Come here, come here.
Ah. hyung!
Hang on!
Ji Hyo! Ji Hyo!
Who is it? Oh man. Sung Soo hyung's here too?
Done.
- How have you been? -Oh man, you've worked hard.
Song Ji Hyo, out. Song Ji Hyo. out.
Only one left.
Ah. you guys are too brutal! Ah, being like this...
Ah, we're all dead!
What will happen to the Running Men?
- HaHa. out. -Ah. shut it!
We have to finish this quickly, otherwise we'll be dead.
On your way here earlier, wasn't there some computers left unchecked?
Turn off all the monitors.
Turn them off!
Otherwise they'll know those havn't been checked right?
The others have been completed.
Oh, exactly.
Ah, sitting here is really lonesome.
Sang Wook. you have to try it out.
Then what's that paper there, there?
This seems to be a prank by Ha Dong Hoon.
- Hey, then now the other team... -No no. There must be more than this.
They're just left with both Ji Jin Hee and Kim. Kim Sung Soo right?
Firstly, what's T?
'Tomorrow'.
Do you know? What?
This seems like there's a mission.
Does it make sense? Does it make sense?
Heyraren't you on our side?
Hyung, we're on the same side.
You're not, you!
I'm hot even a spy.
You're the Spy!
-I'm not. -You are the spy.
Do I have to be sorry towards yungs?'
-Of course! -Of course you have to be sorry.
What about to hyungs?'
You're also hot on our side now!
Of course you should be sorry to us.
-Ah, Chun Hee's right. - You're an outsider now.
He keeps swaying both ways, going back and forth.
I'm so curious about this.
I know this now.
Really?
-Can I reveal this? -'Midday tomorrow',
actly, this is 'Midday tomorrow'.
This is clearly 'Midday tomorrow'.
'Midday tomorrow...'
Hey Song Ji HytT why did you do that?
HaHa's out.
Never tell the enemy the news of my death.
Have you been staring at it but not figuring it out?
’Never tell the enemy...'
Ji Hyo, isn't it’Midday tomorrow'?
isn't it 'Midday tomorrow'?
What? What did you say, what did you say?
Isn't it 'Midday tomorrow'?
Aigoo. seriously!
Aigoo. I can't take it, I can't take it.
-'Midday.tomorrow...' -It was all your own thinking.
'Jae Dong goes'.
It wasn't just.me. You saw Sang Wook right?
Aigoo. it's 'tomorrow', 'midday tomorrow'.
Hey, Sang Wook was behind while we were puzzling over it!
Ah, everyone was going. "Hey, how did you know?"
I thought I got it too.
Hey, HaHa's out?
Ji Hyo's the Spy.
Oppa. I'm really the Spy!
You're the Spy too?
-He's a Spy too. -I'm a Spy.
Hey, how many Spies are there?
-That's why I, I... - Wait a minute.
- Why did you tear Kwang Soo's off, Kwang Soo? -Ah, Kwang Soo was too obvious for the oppas.
He's too obvious.
We were about to die, so we were discussing it.
-But he was still alive when he just suddenly... -Ah, how can you pick Spies like this?
Can you carry out the game like this?
You can’t do this kind of game.
It's just Jong Kook left, didn't you see him?
I caught Jong Kook, I did.
And then?
After catching him, I was tearing it midway.
When he pleaded for me to let him survive.
Really?
Ah, Kim Jong Kook pleaded?
Ah hyung, can't you just let me off this once?
-Wow, he really did it. -Oh, he really did.
There was even someone filming it right?
-Ah. did he really plead? -Of course.
What's this?
-Hey, he tore Jin Hee's off... -I'll show you something shocking.
I still have one more inside.
No one would believe it, no one would believe it.
No one would believe it.
Who is out?
Kim Si mg Soo. out.
Well done!
Ah, why did you come in here?
Kim Sung Soo, out.
Ah, why are you here?
Hey Kim Sung Soo, what are you doing?
It's not the time for me to stay here.
-You have to catch someone. - Don’t get caught while trying to catch others.
I'll leave first. Ok.
Hey, why are there so many?
The computers...
Oh, I'm about to die.
Please!
Ah. this is seriously...
-You can't find it right? -What?
Ah, I'm so tired.
How did you come in here, hyung?
This is it. This is it.
That's why I have to turn off the monitors.
What's this?
It should be like this.
It would be alright if I turn off the monitors.
I need to turn off those which are already turned on.
Here, there is one already.
So there isn't anymore here already.
There won't be 2 here.
Why are there so many?
This has not been pressed before.
He looks like he is in a rush?
Ok, the 3rd floor is done.
Where is it?
Ok, ok, ok.
It's not here, then...
Why are there so many?
We still do not know the end result.
Now it's 1v1.
-Hyung, Jin Hee hyung looks like he's going to win. -Jin Hee will win.
Jin Hee's body is full of muscles.
What happens if the two battle base on strength?
Jin Hee hyung is really strong!
-The kid is doing rock climbing... - Really?
You looked that up from the internet right?!
Jin Hee told me over the phone.
Ah, l'm going crazy.
It's a battle between beasts, battle between beasts.
-The person who is laughing would have won. -I feel like Jong Kook would win.
They're here!
Who won?
What happened to the two of you?
-Jong Kook hyung won. Jong Kook hyung won. - It looks like Jong Kook won.
How did Jong Kook hyung lose?
No. when did you get in here?
How did you come in?
I nearly found it, really...
The last room, hyung was also in it.
Hyung locked the room too.
-My plan was to lock all the doors. -It was too tiring.
The battle between the beasts, the lion and the tiger.
-In the end it was a mental battle, a mental battle. -They, so which side are they on?
-You are of course on the Running Man side. -See!
I’ll see you off-the-camera, Kwang Soo.
Quickly turn off the cameras!
This is really...
They even give the meat, really.
It's Korean beef.
Is that Yeosu mustard leaf kimchi?^
Wait! Why... are you removing the kimchi?
They suddenly didn't want to give it.
Keep going!
What can you do well?
Ah what is this?
Last chance, our last chance
The sleeves also have numbers and symbols
-The most important thing is that we have to find it quickly. -I found it!