[The final decision of deceit and betrayal].
Everyone listen carefully...
I'm going to do this right today.
Subtitles by DramaFever
[The ultimate non-stop survivor game]
What are we doing today?
Are we playing a game?
Give me the water gun.
The water gun.
You have to give me the water gun
for us to get started.
I'll be waiting for the Sherlock Holmes
game next year.
-I'll do one for all of you!
-What are you saying you're going to do?
-Then let's all say what we want.
-I want to do the first love.
How about a True Gary's show?
-What about you, Jong Kook?
-No matter what it is, I'm going to ruin it.
[One word from the tiger, and it's all set]
He's really a scary guy.
This is our 93rd show today.
A lot of things have happened,
but there's been a survey on what's been fun.
What's the super power that people
want to have the most?
No matter what it is,
I'm going to be the last.
-Time controller.
-The duplicator.
-Sixth sense.
-Mind controller.
-Phoenix.
-Death note.
Space controller.
[The most desirable power that
the viewing audience has picked?]
Who do you think is going to win,
Kwang Soo?
-Of course, I'd want the death note to win...
-Death note is in 7th place.
Since it's over after one use,
no one wanted the death note. It's last.
2.2% has picked it.
Now...in first place...wow...
I'm sure it's either Ji Hyo or Ha Ha.
-Time...!
-The mind controller...Song Ji Hyo!
65.9%.
That means that people
can't trust other people.
What are you talking about?
That's not what this survey is about.
That's what it means....it is!
[Why is he being so serious about it?]
It's because he wasn't picked...
because his power wasn't picked.
The one that controls the time was
in 2nd place at 15.5%
3rd place was the space controller.
-I'm the time controller.
-I'm the space controller.
Can the space controller use his power
for anything in real life?
Of course!  It's the best!
Why are you getting angry?
-Why are you getting mad over it?
-You don't know the value of the power!
-Because I can control the space?
-Of course!!
I can call whomever I want to me at any time,
like if I had a girlfriend...
-Of course.
-I love you.
-Of course!
-stop it!
Survey of Running Man's athletic abilities.
The best runner of Running man that was
picked by the Running Man's VJ's...
(**VJ's are the cameramen)
Our pride is riding on this...
-I bet they picked Yoo Jae Suk.
-Why didn't you tell us that you were picking?
-This is awesome...
-In the first place...!
Our VJ's pick this for us...
First place...is Kim Jong Kook!
Thanks you!  Thank you!
Hey...you should be happy and give
me a hug when I come to you.
-You should be happy...
-He got scared when Jong Kook came.
Why are you running from me?
Since you're the best runner,
it's been hard on him.
[Following Jong Kook around with the camera
all this time has been a tough job].
2 people have tied for the 2nd place.
Lee Kwang Soo!
It's you, yeah...
he's denying it...he's denying that he voted.
Don't expect anything. Why are you expecting?
[I didn't pick you].
-The VJ is saying no.
-You didn't pick him?
-You didn't pick him? You picked Jong Kook?
-I picked Jong Kook.
[The uncomfortable truth that even Kwang Soo's
VJ picked Jong Kook].
2nd place!
It's Yoo Jae Suk and Song Ji Hyo!
The best runners that our VJ's picked...
This is no fun!
Oh my!  It's so much!
[Today's highlight gift.
The best looking male member of Running Man].
It was already decided last week!
My sin for being unattractive!
If you dip below second place here,
then you're dead.
I'll acknowledge up to the 3rd place person.
-3rd place?
-I'll acknowledge up to the 3rd place winner.
5th and 6th place here really is the end.
Suk Jin is going to be below me.
What are you talking about?
I'm better than you!
-Of course, I'm better than you.
-I think I'll get 3rd place.
-It's all been shown through subtitles already.
-It has?
Yes! Yay!!! 2nd place!
The truth is...we really should be grateful
to the viewing audience every day.
Anyways...why are you gifting us with
all these surveys today?
We will be having a non-stop race today.
[Running Man's first non-stop race].
[Welcome to Running Man's survivor game].
[The member that the viewers have voted
to want to kick off the show...]
[Will become the target].
This filming will be
non-stop from the beginning.
-Wait!
-Will you please shake my hand?
Don't come here!!
[This is what happens
when you let your guard down].
Bring in the chair please.
Chair? What's going on?
There are a lot of chairs coming.
[Chair...?  This is...?].
-What's this?
-Is there going to be a voting?
The viewers have
voted on a lot of things today...
Before we start on our missions,
each of you will cast your own vote.
Starting with Ha Ha, if you go in there
you'll find what you need to vote on.
-Go ahead.
-I'm nervous.
-What is this?
-What are they doing to us now?
Hello.
If you had to disqualify one person
from the Running Man race,
who is the member that you want to
disqualify the most?
[After you write the name down,
tell the camera the reason for the decision].
This is really...
What a dilemma.
[Before it even begins, you have to choose
the one you have to disqualify...].
from the race...disqualifying one person...
Disqualify one person from the race?
I don't know who to write down...
[Time for a decision].
If I had to choose...
It's this person.
The member that gets in the way.
It's not that I don't like the
person personally...I like the person...
Sorry.
I'm sorry.
-Go ahead, Kwang Soo.
-Kwang Soo, you go on ahead.
[Icon of betrayal goes in as the last voter].
If you come out too soon,
It's going to be awkward, Kwang Soo.
At least give it some thought.
Kwang Soo's going to write it down
as soon as he reads it.
Couldn't you have made it a little taller?
Don't you think of me at all?
Aren't I a member of Running Man too?
It's you who's abnormally tall.
They could have made it just a little taller.
The giraffe.
His height is the one that everyone
wishes they had...
-but why does he complain so much?
-Being that tall is useless...
[Before the talk of his height is even over,
he's already made his decision].
-It took him 0.01 second...
-Seriously...he didn't even hesitate.
Kwang Soo!  As soon as you step out,
look at that person.
[Staring straight through the Tiger].
[Even though they're laughing,
no one knows how they're feeling].
[Who's the one that got voted as the one
others like to disqualify?]
[Running Man Non-stop Survivor Game]
[1st round location. Yangjaedong Art Center].
Ha Ha...don't...don't betray me today.
I wonder what will happen today...hello.
Do I have to betray someone today?
Something is definitely weird!
Lee Kwang Soo, please go in.
-Let's not betray anyone today, okay?
-Do it honestly!
He's already thinking of betraying someone
as he's walking off like that.
What's this?
I don't know what I'm supposed to be doing...
I feel like I'm going to be surprised.
[Gary is off to the performance stage].
I feel like they're going to combine all the
stuff we've done before into today.
Why am I sent upstairs?
Excuse me? You want me to wait here?
This is weird. Why am I waiting?
Gwan Yul, what's going on?
All I know is that
we're supposed to stay here.
[Everyone's waiting anxiously...]
What is this?
I really hate this...
Welcome to Running Man Survivor Game.
Survivor.
[Survivor game?]
-Survivor game...
-Survivor game?
Welcome to everyone that's
joined Running Man's survivor game.
Here's the voting results for Running Man's
survivor game's first round.
The 1st place member that's others want
to disqualify the most from Running Man is...
Kim Jong Kook!
It's Kim Jong Kook.
[Mr. Capable...
Indeed, Running Man's ultimate man!].
[All the Running Men that wrote the name
down without even a hesitation].
-Sorry.
-I'm sorry.
I've never once ripped his name off
his back.
Everyone wrote his name down today.
Within 30 minutes of this point, rip off
Kim Jong Kook's name tag, and take him out.
How are we supposed to do that
within 30 minutes?
Within 30 minutes of this point, rip off
Kim Jong Kook's name tag, and take him out.
And the remaining 6 members
will go on to the second round.
If by any chance, Kim Jong Kook
remains live in the game,
then all of the 7 members will
go on to the second round.
Running Man Survivor...start!
I'm not going to go easy on them.
I was going to,
but I don't think so anymore.
[1st round]
[Get this man within 30 minutes].
How are we going to get Jong Kook?
30 minutes?
I can get him.
This is exciting.
Then do I...I have to...
take Jong Kook's name tag off?
30 minutes.
Excuse me!
30 minutes isn't much time.
I'm going to get out of here.
Hey. If we can get the tag off of Jong Kook
on a day like this, it's an honor.
-It's really an honor!
-You be honorable then.
Should I?  I should.
I'll do it.
Jong Kook's name was written
down the most...
Ultimately, Kim Jong Kook
was written down the most.
As you probably guessed...
if you fail at ripping his name tag off...
Kim Jong Kook will come along
for the second round.
-Really?
-I'm sure that makes you really uncomfortable?
Of course, I'm uncomfortable.
What do you think Jong Kook is thinking?
[Mr. Capable who's busy making his moves].
[Mr. Capable can tear the name off other
members and pause the time].
There is an emergency exit...
Who's that?
Kim Jong Kook!
Jae Suk.
Is Jae Suk by himself?
How is it that I'm running into
Kim Jong Kook?
Let's run!
[The chaser being chased down by the chase?]
[Jae Suk is the one who's supposed
to catch Jong Kook].
[When it comes to running,
he's faster than lightning].
-You scared me! What's wrong?
-Kim Jong Kook...
-I ran into Jong Kook...and ran away.
-Where did you run into him?
Jae Suk...we have to combine our
strengths together no matter what.
What is it?
We should gather and strategize...
I ran into Jong Kook as soon as I started!
-Really?
-You ran into him?
-He was hiding...
-If we make a mistake or something...
-Suk Jin, you wrote Jong Kook down, right?
-Yes.
-You wrote Jong Kook down, right?
-No.
-You didn't?
-You wrote down Jong Kook, right?
If Jong Kook survives this,
he'll go on to 2nd round with us.
Do you know how scary that is?
We have to oust him before we go.
Jae Suk!
I thought I just heard his voice.
[Ha Ha...lost on his own]
Jae Suk!
[Kim Jong Kook,
chasing down the lone ranger].
I'm sorry...wait!
I didn't write down your name.
-Let's all get started by going...
-Ha Ha, paused.
It's started.  It's started!
[Panic]
-Come here!
-This way!
[Who's the target,
and who's the chaser?]
-Come on! This way!
-He's a monster!
[Rather than thinking of catching him,
their first thought is to run away].
-We can't run away!
-Okay, fine.
Before they all gather together...
I have to oust them one by one.
That's the only option.
Because if they're all together, it's over.
This is so unfair.
There are 20 minutes left to the game.
[Ha Ha's been paused, so he has to stay
in his spot until the game is over].
-Are you over there?
-You need to run away!
I guess we shouldn't run away...
we should be catching him.
We have to run together as a group.
If we don't catch him and he goes on to the
2nd round, we'll be at a disadvantage.
If we run into Jong Kook,
I'll grab onto his arms.
Okay, I'll rip it off.
You think you can hang onto him?
Of course.
And if I run into him, I'll grab his arms.
-There are 2 of us...
-What?
Suk Jin!  Suk Jin!!
What's going on?
He's over there! We need to go over there!
Suk Jin!  Suk Jin!!
Hurry!  Jae Suk!
Lee Kwang Soo, paused.
-He went that way?
-That way.
I guess this is the
only role that you can play.
Jae Suk, this is a very important role!
I'm really going crazy.
Everyone, listen carefully.
[Wait...this is...].
You wrote me down?
I got it.
But still...that was too much.
I'll tell you this.
Even though this is a comedy show...
First round is not a comedy.
Oh goodness...I think he's really mad.
I'm going to do it right today.
I'll see you soon...
Jong Kook, I was wrong!!
Jong Kook, I'm sorry!
He's scary.
I'm scared!
He...he sounds like he's going to
rip us apart today.
I'm going to go crazy, Gary.
I mean...what does he mean by that?
I can't even hear it because I'm so scared.
Jong Kook.
I can't stray too far. I have
to listen to what they're saying.
Jae Suk!
This is Serengeti.
First round is not a joke.
The penguin and the giraffe are
already caught.
The grasshopper is still alive.
[Herbivores trying to catch the carnivore...]
-I'm running today.
-What?
-Run quickly, Suk Jin. We have to run quickly.
-Kim Jong Kook is over there!
-Where?!
Kim Jong Kook!  Hey!  Kim Jong Kook!
Why are they going around in a group?
[Gaining momentum to chase after him].
I'll just go up against him with confidence.
Why are you laughing? I'm going
to go up against him with confidence.
[What unexpected luck].
[Noise coming from up above].
-You had it ripped off? Yours is ripped off?
-Gary!
-We're ruined!
-You had yours ripped off?
He was standing right there when
I opened the door.
That makes no sense.
-Yours got ripped off?
-He was standing there when I opened the door.
[He's already disappeared].
He's a ghost.  A total ghost.
He's not a human.
Why are you scared?
Why are you being scared?
You should've helped me shut the door.
You should've shut the door with me.
10 minutes left in the game.
Gary, Ji Hyo, Suk Jin.
My hearts beating really fast now.
If I can get just one more person,
it'll be over then.
-Ha Ha!
-Giraffe!
-We're all over now, Ha Ha.
-Yeah, it seems like it's over.
I didn't write Jong Kook down.
I didn't...
I didn't write him down either.
Don't lie.
Be quiet.
Gary!!  Ji Hyo!!
You're saying I'm over now?  Here?
When so many people
are watching in anticipation?
What do you mean, next time?
I have to catch Kim Jong Kook right now.
[You should've caught him earlier].
I should've just stood up to him...
if I had, it would all be over right now.
But I got caught off guard...
If I hadn't been caught off guard,
Jong Kook...
Jong Kook... oh my goodness!
Oh my goodness!  He scared me!
[Suddenly aged 100 years].
Ugh!  He scared me!
-Ugh, he scared me!
-Jae Suk.  Did you see him?
-He went up there.
-Up there?
-Where is he?
-He went that way.
-Hey! Where is he running around off to?
-Ji Hyo, did you see him?
What did you say?
You want to go up against him?
Come on...being caught off guard,
and being scared are two different things.
I just got caught off guard right now.
Not scared.
[The survivors are more afraid now]
He's a ghost, a ghost.
He's not human.
He's a ghost.
It's Kim Jong Kook!!
It's Kim Jong Kook!
[He's hiding in such an easy spot...].
What are you doing here?
You can't be here.
Wait a minute...hey!
It's Kim Jong Kook!
I thought you were the giraffe!
Why are you of all people coming here?
Ji Suk Jin, paused.
[Ji Hyo, Gary...
Somehow, they are the only 2 left].
What did you say?
-Do we need a plan?
-A plan?  Maybe we should stay hidden.
Because you and I are the only ones left,
we can't be apart.
We have to stay together
and face Jong Kook.
It's Kim Jong Kook again...
Kim Jong Kook.
What are you doing?
The remaining survivors
are looking for the color pink...
So if they were to see this, they'll think
it's strange and pause for a moment.
If they see me, they immediately run,
but they'll pause when they see this.
Are you lecturing me right now?
Are you trying to lecture me, or what?
-Who did you write down?
-What did you say?
I'm asking who you wrote down.
-Who?
-Who did you write down earlier?
-I didn't write your name down.
-You're lying to me.
If I had to do it...it's a given...
[Name written is Kim Jong Kook].
I didn't write your name down.
[He definitely wrote Jong Kook's name down].
-What did you say?
-What a joke...
I wrote Ji Hyo down.
-Really?
-I've never once ripped Ji Hyo's name off.
-That's right.
[Pretty naive. He's believing that?!]
Hey... how are you going
around so quickly?
How... do you get around so fast?
Hey... is this the jungle or something?
-Jae Suk.
-What?
I'll see you in the 2nd round.
What do you mean,
see you at 2nd round?
You're being very scary.
Wow...you all worked together
as a unit so well earlier.
It's been so long since I've seen you
guys united like that.
-The one I work the best with is you.
-What are you talking about?
You guys were all over the place
when I was watching you earlier.
You were just going back and forth
with one another.
You're misunderstood.
That's a misunderstanding.
Ah...seriously.
Why are you so afraid of Jong Kook?!
All you have to do is just shoot,
but why are you cowering?
Why are you so afraid of Jong Kook?
Seriously...
I don't hear anything here,
so let's go over that way.  See you later.
What do you mean, see you later?
[Because I'm going to remain alive
until the 2nd round].
Seriously... hey. When Jong Kook comes,
you just have to shoot the camera.
Why do you keep getting scared
whenever Jong Kook shows up?
3 minutes left to the game.
Gary... let's try going upstairs.
-Ji Hyo? What happened?
-Yeah?
We can't find him.
Jong Kook is nowhere to be found.
He hiding.
He's hiding because he's scared.
You sure he's hiding because he's scared?
There's no way to win.
If I knew it'd be like this,
I wouldn't have written Jong Kook down.
Just rip it off! If he comes
to the 2nd round with us, we're dead!
[There's not much time].
[Just where is Jong Kook?]
I can't find him.
[Battle stance].
Ji Hyo! We can't stop now.
There's only 3 minutes left.
We have nothing to lose.
We're the captors,
and we're going to out Jong Kook.
Since we have nothing to lose,
you go grab him first.
What are you doing?
There are only two of you left now.
[Extreme nervousness]
-Come here...
-Why don't we go somewhere more open?
-What's wrong with here?
-There are 3 of you, and only 2 of us.
What do you mean?
Your 2 arms and neck...there are 3 of you.
[There's no room for escape].
Ji Hyo, I'm sorry.
I told you without a doubt that
I wouldn't go easy on you today.
-I can't go easy on you.
-I understand.
-I see you as a man right now.
-1 minute left to the game.
-There's only a minute left!
-Hurry up and get him!
[No time...standing head to head].
-We should...
-I'll grab him, and you tear it off.
-Then you grab him, and I'll tear it off.
-Okay.
What if I get caught?
-What do you think would be better?
-Okay.  You try to grab me.
There's only a minute left!
Hurry up and grab him!
-You grab him!  Ji Hyo!  Ji Hyo!
-What are you doing?!
[2:1! 1st rounds last stand].
Ji Hyo! Hurry! Now's the chance!
Ji Hyo! Right now! Hurry up, Ji Hyo!
-Ji Hyo!  Ji Hyo!
-Come and get me!
-Ji Hyo!  Now's the time!
-Ji Hyo!  Try to grab it!
Ji Hyo!  Now's the time!  Ji Hyo!
-You have to pull him off!
-He's caught me too!!
I'm caught too!  Ji Hyo!
I got it!  I got it!
[Gary!  If you can do it well...really!!]
-Ji Hyo!  Ji Hyo!  I got it!
-Hurry!
First round, over.
-Hurry up and grab it!
-Ji Hyo!
I got it!  I got it!
[Unfortunately...at the nick of time...]
[Gary tore the name tag off after
the time has been called].
[It's void because time has passed].
-Why did you grab me?
-Sorry, I was wrong.
You should've tugged harder!
[Kim Jong Kook survived the 1st round].
-3 seconds? You couldn't do it quicker?
-He had me by the arm too.
Let's go to the 2nd round.
[Kim Jong Kook survived the first round].
[All 7 members to go on to the 2nd round].
I feel so exhausted.
We need to get on this?
Hello.
-What are these metal chains for?
-What are these?
If Kim Jong Kook would've been out,
that's where he would be sitting.
[If Jong Kook would've been disqualified,
that would've been his seat].
-Ah...if he'd been ousted.
-That would've been his seat?
We'll move moving on to our
2nd round location.
Like before, you have to vote the one person
that you want to disqualify again.
But can't we go in a separate car
from Jong Kook?
[to ride in the same car with Mr. Capable
right away is a little uncomfortable].
And Jong Kook who survived the first round,
can cast 2 votes for the 2nd round.
Why don't you give him some more
while you're at it?
Why don't you give him 3 or 4?
He's had to suffer so much!
He should be given as much as he's ran.
Since we know how this works now...
It seems right to get rid of the person
that's easy to get rid of first...
After thinking about it... it doesn't seem like
a bad idea to keep him in the game either...
Kim Jong Kook.  Kim Jong Kook.
Okay then...
-He said it's okay!
-Let's take this to the end.
And if you get hurt in the process,
you have to understand it.
What did you say?
-Let's all bound together!
-You don't even contribute anything to it...!
[Running Man non-stop survivor game]
[2nd round location:
Gwacheon National Science Museum]
Thank you.
[The voting station is waiting here too].
-It's better to get rid of the tiger first?
-Of course!  We have to!
One more time...
but we have to think about this.
Where are my allies going?
Unless we stick together,
there's no way we can oust Jong Kook.
No matter, we have to see who's going in?
[The tiger and Ace coalition?]
Ha Ha can start the voting.
-Just remember...
-Don't say anything.  Just go.
Remember our promise.
[Ha Ha starting the voting process].
[Of course?  Voting for Jong Kook].
-You can go to the right.
-Am I done right now?
Yes, you may go in.
The reason why I chose Kim Jong Kook is...
is because we all think that...
[Gary's turn to vote]
Think carefully about this.
There's an imprint of what Ha Ha wrote here,
and it's definitely Kim Jong Kook.
There are 4 exclamation marks!
-Gary.
-Yes, Jong Kook?
-If I remain alive...everyone will be in danger.
-Yes, Jong Kook.  I'm aware of that.
[Writing the same thing as the imprint?]
If Jong Kook keeps surviving at this rate,
how are things going to end today?
Then we'll be shooting 2 night 3 days.
(After the popular 1 night 2 days).
-Don't worry, it'll end for sure.
-It'll end?
He doesn't ever get tired...
and he's overflowing with strength.
[Ha Ha]
Who did he write down?
He wrote it very quickly.
-Seeing how it's only two letters...
-He wrote it so quickly.
[Jong Kook gave his 2 votes to Ha Ha].
[Everyone, just wait and see].
I'm not going to let anyone off the hook...
[Will everyone's vote this time around
ultimately be Jong Kook?]
I'm really scared.
I wonder if I teased Jong Kook too much?
The one who teases too much
usually gets it at the end.
[The nervous energy...]
Mic testing, mic testing..1, 2, 3.
[The alarm bell sound].
Here are the voting results for the
second round or Running Man Survivor Game.
The member that has
the highest number of votes...
[Member of Running Man they'd most like
to disqualify from the race is...]
Ha Ha.
Ha Ha has received the most votes.
[Reversal?]
-Ha Ha.
-What happened?
[Voting time earlier].
[Jong Kook collaborating with Ji Hyo].
-Fighting.
-Yes.
[1 vote for Ha Ha].
[Suk Jin watching them with consideration].
Have a seat.
[That's how Ha Ha ends up with 4 votes].
[Without hesitation,
Kwang Soo writes down Jong Kook].
[With this, the vote is tied]
[Jong Kook-4; Ha Ha-4].
-Lee Kwang Soo wrote Kim Jong Kook!
-No!  That's a lie!
-He wrote down Kim Jong Kook!
-What are you talking about?
Lee Kwang Soo.
What is it?
I checked the votes, and it's a tie.
-A tie?
-You don't know who's tied right now.
Take out one vote from there
and give it to us.
Is it possible for there to be a tie?
[Kwang Soo takes out one vote].
You can just go in now.
We'll announce the results over the PA.
-You can't see.
-It's not Jong Kook?
We'll broadcast the results.
You can wait to hear the results.
Ha Ha.
[Kwang Soo has picked Ha Ha].
It's me?
Me?  Me?
Me?
It's me?
It's not Kim Jong Kook...but me?
Me?
It's me?!
[2nd round target-Ha Ha].
This is great!  Ha Dong Hoon...Ha Dong Hoon...
You wait and see, Ha Dong Hoon.
So if I rip of Ha Ha's name tag,
I get 2 votes then?
Then I'll have to rip it off Ha Ha quickly.
I'm seriously about to go crazy...
that Lee Kwang Soo!
No one did what they said
they were going to do!
Wow... seriously...
you can't trust anyone.
-As for the promise...
-You can't trust anyone on Running Man.
Give me Ha Ha.
I'm asking for this favor.
[The tiger that's become the hunter]
[Tightly preying on the prey]
Jong Kook!
Well... I don't know who you wrote down,
but give Dong Hoon to me.
Okay, Jong Kook.
My brother... the one I trusted so much...
[3 minutes into the 2nd round].
He's' not here?
-He could be in here.
-Everyone, spread out.
-We can leave Jong Kook on his own.
-Yes!  I understand!
We can go grab something to eat, right?
[The tiger is searching with fire in his eyes]
[Big trouble!]
[For now, run away]
[Hiding inside a storage room]
[Yikes!  the storage room door!]
[The nervous state of the prey]
25 minutes left to the game.
[Is the hunt over like this within 5 minutes?]
-25 minutes left to the game.
-5 minutes have passed already?
[He just passes on by]
[Where is he hiding?]
[Jong Kook... that was Jong Kook].
[Ah... so scary].
[If anyone comes in here,
he's caught without a place to run].
[No one is out there].
[Using the time when no one's around
to go downstairs].
20 minutes left to the game.
-Hey! Ha Ha!
[Found after coming out from his hiding].
He's out here, Jong Kook!
-Jong Kook!
-Where?  Where is he?
Opposite way!
You have to go the opposite way!
There he is!
-Where?  Where?!
-That way!  He's over there!
Jong Kook!  The subway!
Jong Kook!  Come this way!
Kwang Soo!  Corral him!
Kwang Soo... get out!
[Running Ha Ha escapes
the giraffe's barricade].
Can't you catch him?
[The target that's being corralled].
Jong Kook is here. Just give up.
Get away!
You traitors...
how can you do this to me?
Mine!  He's mine!
[If you tear off the target's name tag,
you get to cast 2 votes].
[Get rid of target, Ha Ha's name tag].
[Tangled Jae Suk and Jong Kook's hands].
[Who will ultimately get the name tag?]
[Jae Suk gets the name tag].
You're out.
Ha Ha out. Permanently out.
Ha Ha out.  Permanently out.
[ Permanently out]
Permanently out?
You can have your meals now.
-Since I'm out, I can't eat with you.
-Come on, you can eat with us.
-Let's at least eat together.
-Of course.
This is the place.
Do you remember, Jong Kook?
These are the escalators where you dragged
up 4 people that were grabbing onto you.
[4 people...!]
Seriously... I totally remember.
[Running Man non-stop survivor]
[4 hours into the game].
How in the world did I get caught?
[You be quiet].
I'm sure there will be something at the end.
[Right away, the food is being
consumed at a non-stop speed]
From now on, it's time for dinner.
When the dinner is over, once again,
you'll have to vote someone to be disqualified.
[Day of endless voting].
The time for eating and rest is one hour.
3rd round will also be the same in which the
target will be picked through a vote.
The 3rd round will be the last round
for target hunting.
Then do I have to keep staying here?
Ha Ha has to remain disqualified
to the end today.
The 4th round later on will be
the last round for the day.
Really?
Let's write down the person that's not here.
I know that I won't get kicked out.
-Who's the one that you want out?
-Kim Jong Kook.
[He wants to oust the tiger...].
When I leave my spot, I get nervous.
Everyone wants to get you out.
I know that you always suspect me...
[Jae Suk, who's listening to everything].
He will always and unconditionally
betray us at the end.
[Running Man non-stop survivor]
[4 hour and 50 minutes into the game]
I don't know, I don't know.
Let's write!
[During this voting round,
only Jae Suk has 2 voting rights]
Why didn't I think of this earlier?
I'm not going to say anything.
I'll just let it go.
[3rd round voting complete]
[Running Man non-stop survivor]
[5 hours and 30 minutes into the game]
If we just wrote his name... ah...
I don't know...
[Nervous]
[Everyone's waiting for the voting results
with abated breath]
Who is it this time?
I wonder who it is?
Kwang Soo.
[Giraffe that was hiding is found]
Since you've already got this place...
Jae Suk.
Even if you're picked this time,
I won't rip off your name.
Really?
[That means he wrote down Jae Suk's name]
Since this isn't the end.
Going by what you're saying,
it means you wrote my name down.
-I really didn't write your name.
-Really?
-When I see the broadcast, I can see...
-Seriously... I didn't.
-Since we don't know...
-Okay.
If I get picked...
this is where I'm going to run to first.
[Time to reveal the voting results]
Running Man survivor game.
I will reveal the target for the 3rd round.
The person that others wants to disqualify
the most in Running Man is...
You have to consider the last round
before you write it down.
If I get picked, make sure you oust me.
Otherwise, I can't guarantee what I'll do.
-Jong Kook...
-How can you say that?
[If there's no Jong Kook, Jae Suk will
have the advantage later]
What about Kwang Soo?
[Who will be this round's target?]
The person that others wants to disqualify
the most in Running Man is...
[Lee Kwang Soo]
[Kim Jong Kook]
[Jong Kook; Jong Kook]
[Lee Kwang Soo]
[Kwang Soo is picked]
Is Lee Kwang Soo.
Me?
It's not Jong Kook?
[The target tag is attached to the giraffe].
...will go on to the final round.
If Lee Kwang Soo isn't ousted...
Does this even make any sense?
[3rd round target is the giraffe]
Lee Kwang Soo!
[Mr. Capable's inevitable success?]
Is Lee Kwang Soo!
You have to rip his name tag off within
30 minutes and out him.
Everyone else is laughing?
Even the staff are laughing?
[As soon as it's announced,
the giraffe is looking for a hideout]
[Jae Suk?]
[Round 3 start!]
Why is it me?
Why is it me?!
Who wrote my name down?
Kwang Soo?
[Relaxed giraffe hunters]
You're scared aren't you?
Hey. When your name was announced,
the whole staff was laughing.
Kwang Soo?
Kwang Soo...!
Kwang Soo!
Kwang Soo! Where are you?
[The giraffe's name that's heard everywhere]
Kwang Soo!
-A traitor has to be taken out.
-That's what I'm saying.
[Find the target, Kwang Soo]
Why did they write me down?
This is really hurtful.
[Unlucky man that's even being
chased down by bugs]
I'm going to kill it.
25 minutes left in the game.
Even though there are only 25 minutes left,
no one seems to be worried about it.
We're all going around comfortably...
very leisurely.
This is so different than when we were
chasing after Kim Jong Kook.
[Playing a game]
[The target is a weak target]
[It's just the giraffe...]
[All the hunters are not very interested]
[Giraffe in hiding underground]
I can hear footsteps!
[Something...]
[is here]
[Suk Jin?]
Kwang Soo.
I'm alone. It's just me.
-Suk Jin.
-What are you doing here?
Why are you here?
What are you doing?
Remember what we talked about earlier?
We have to do that...
[Huh? Grabbing Kwang Soo's arm?]
What are you doing?
Don't you know we're easy brothers?
I'm not joking either.
This is the first time I'm up against you.
Let's go up against one another.
[Quietly spoken provocation underground].
[Finally...Easy Brother's civil war].
[Let's see who's stronger...!]
Pil-Sook-Cross!
[Now that line in friendship...?]
[What is this?]
[Suk Jin who wants to be the lone hunter
at least once]
[Even they are busting out laughing]
[The giraffe twists his arms]
[With his mouth?]
[Kwang Soo gets rid of Suk Jin's tag
with his mouth]
-How can you do that?
-Why?
-What about you?
-After screaming out Pil-sook-cross!
-How can you tear it with your mouth?
How can you?  That's not right!
Jin Suk Jin, paused.
Suk Jin!  Suk Jin!
[News that's been dumped on
the hunters that've been playing around].
Where is he?
Suk Jin!
Is he by the emergency exit?
-Suk Jin!
-Check by the emergency exit.
I've met a good opponent.
Running Man's history.
This was my first fierce battle.
That was my first time tearing off
the name tag like that.
You think he would be here?
The sound came from up there earlier.
[After turning the lights off,
he hides in an empty office].
Why is the light off in here?
I wonder why the light is turned off in here?
Kwang Soo.
Kwang Soo...
-You didn't forget what I said earlier, right?
-What?
Even if you were called,
I wouldn't tear your name off.
Yeah...
I would stick to that...
but others are here already.
Lee Kwang Soo,
that's where you've been hiding?
Since this could get out of hand,
why don't we go out and do this?
Okay. Then let's go outside first.
Ji Hyo. Don't' show him your back.
Kwang Soo...
[The giraffe who's stepping into battle...]
[Could he win again?]
Come here.  Come here!
Wait... let's talk for a minute.
At the next race,
I'll do whatever I can to protect you two.
I'll protect you from Jong Kook.
I'll stay in here.
I'll make sure to keep my promise.
We have to follow you out.
-Why don't we meet up somewhere else?
-Where?
We can't just let you go, Kwang Soo.
-Give me some time...
-...6, 7, 8...
[Ace Ji Hyo following close behind]
Hey!
I'm seriously so stressed!
There aren't even any cameras in there.
Kwang Soo,
there aren't any cameras in there.
Is there another way from there?
[Mysterious man coming from the office]
Have you seen Kwang Soo?
[The giraffe's disguise that's more obvious]
You haven't seen Kwang Soo?
You haven't seen Lee Kwang Soo?
[You can stop it now]
-Where is it?
-It's in here.
-I'm going to take my jacket off.
-Take off your jacket.
-Like a man... why don't we battle it out?
-Fine.
Ji Hyo!
Rip it off, Ji Hyo!
[Ace Ji Hyo, succeeds
in getting the target's name tag]
That was really... a serious showdown.
[Target, giraffe-out!]
[Permanently banned]
[2 dropouts locked up
in the temporary makeshift jail].
How long did you last?
15 minutes.
That's great.
[4th round]
[5 members to advance].
The real race hasn't even started.
[Since Suk Jin who announces the start
of the race is still alive]
[Moving onto the final round]
We'll soon arrive to
the final round's destination.
There's no more voting.
The last person remaining after the survivors
rip off each other's name tag,
The final person...
Is the winner of Running Man's survivor.
-This is what I told you!
-You ruined it all!
-That's what I told you!
-That's why I told you that earlier!
[Jong Kook who can't control
the expression on his face]
Hye!  Why didn't you guys write down
Jong Kook's name?
You have the wrong people locked down.
Why didn't they write my name down?
I was thinking about that the whole time.
He really scares me.
You can see the glint in his eyes change.
However... in the final round location,
there's an angel's room.
An angel's room...
If you go in there,
you'll be meeting an angel.
Depending on which angel you meet,
it could be a huge benefit to you...
or it could be a huge
disadvantage to you as well.
There will be a huge change...
So the angel we meet could be
a huge benefit to us?
Greatly beneficial.
[Running Man non-stop survivor]
[8 hours into the game].
Everyone wake up.
We've arrived at our destination.
Suk Jin!  We have to wake him up.
-How do you expect to win like this?
-How can your face already get puffy?
[Running Man non-stop survivor]
[4th round location-Gwachon S Land].
The first running man, Kim Jong Kook, enter.
I think I should hide somewhere...
and wait.
The second running man, Ji Suk Jin, enter.
Even if we all gather together,
we can't beat Jong Kook.
The third running man, Gary, enter.
The fourth running man, Yoo Jae Suk, enter.
It really has been a long time
since I've been here.
Where did Kim Jong Kook go?
It was my wish to come into a dark
amusement park,
and playing to my heart's content.
The two dropouts, enter the jail.
What the heck is this?
I can't believe I can't do it with them.
It's cold at night.
It's weird not having Suk Jin
next to me in jail.
Are you guys okay over there?
-Hurry up and come here.
-I'm nowhere near that place.
Can't you see that I'm at a different place?
You guys look especially pathetic tonight.
It's Jong Kook.
Jong Kook.
You're not going to tear mine off right now.
Right? There's our promise from earlier.
Suk Jin is tired. Have him sit next to us.
-Should I?
-What are you saying? I'm not tired.
-I'm not tired. Really.
-Suk Jin. You want to go around some more?
You want to go around some more?
[The utmost mercy that the tiger is showing].
I want to go around some more.
If by any chance, others gang up on me,
you have to stand by my side.
Of course!
If I get tired, I'll let you know.
-Then you can tear it off of me.
-Then have fun walking around.
He really does know
how to softly creep around.
I wonder where the angels are?
I doubt they'll be somewhere
that's easy to find.
A place like this would be...
Hurry up and come here!
I'm too scared to go in by myself.
What's this?
[Huh? There's someone on stage].
An angel?!
[Angel: Miss A's Suzy]
-You're an angel, Suzy?
-Welcome.
-Really?
-Gary oppa.
I've been waiting for you.
-Welcome. Shall we shake hands?
-What are you doing?
-Would you like to shake my hand?
-Are you an angel?
-Yes, I'm an angel.
What do we need to do?
Does she need to come along with me?
-I have something to give you.
-What is it?
-Wait. Please stand over there.
Should I turn my back?
Is it a surprise?
Okay.
Here you go.
-Since you're cold.
-This is it? (Hot pack).
I'm sorry...
[Huh? A bell?]
I have to tie this on?
You said you were an angel!
This is the devil, not an angel!
I'm sorry, but please get taken out.
I don't think you're an angel...
-Normally I'd just let this go...
-I'm sorry...
Since you're so pretty,
I have no choice but to tie it on.
I'm sorry.
Only your face was angelic.
That's right... you are right...
-You need to practice being an angel!
-I did try practicing...
-I'm going to go crazy.
-Goodbye.
Please shut the door on your way out.
I'll see you later, miss angel!
-[What the heck is this?!]
-Goodbye...
I've sent out one person now...
[What is angel Suzy's identity
who passes out the bells?]
Wow...so pretty!
-Wow...that's so pretty.
-I've walked down this lane.
-Jae Suk...
-What?
It would've been perfect if you weren't here.
Hey! What are you
talking about right now, Ji Hyo?
It would've been perfect if
you weren't here.
We have to get rid of Kim Jong Kook first.
We should all join forces,
and get rid of Jong Kook first.
Where are these angels?
That's right...
we have to find the angels, Jae Suk.
What's this?
Hurry up and come. Let's go in together.
[By any chance, is there an angel inside?]
What?
[Another angel that's hidden inside]
[Angel: KARA's Han Seung Yeon]
-Hello!
-Hello.
-I'm an angel...
-It's Seung Yeon!
-Hello.
-What are you doing here, Seung Yeon?
I'm an angel today.
-Really?!
-Yes.
What is it that we need to do?
-I have to pick just one of you...
-Really?
In that case...
since Ji Hyo came in first...
You can go first.  I'll step aside.
-No...that's okay.
-Go ahead.  I'll let you go.
Jae Suk... I doubt Han Seung Yeon
would give you something weird.
-Let's do paper-rock-scissors.
-Okay, the loser has to do it.
Paper-rock-scissors.
[The angel's effect goes to Jae Suk]
-Only I can see it?
-Yes.
Okay then... bye Ji Hyo.
Good luck.
-And...Jae Suk.
-Yeah?
You can tell me whatever it is outside.
Seung Yeon, when did you get here?
I came here earlier.
What are you going to give me?
-It's a good thing that you came!
-Why?
My gift is...
This.
[A small name tag?]
[Suzy gave Gary a bell earlier,
but this is...?]
[An hour before Running Man arrived here]
[5 angels that've been
waiting for Running Man]
[Miss A's Suzy]
[KARA's Seung Yeon]
[KARA's Gyu Ri]
[4 minute's Hyun Ah]
[f(x)'s Krystal]
[These are today's angels to Running Man]
Please vote for who you'd like
to be the winner of Running Man today.
If Running Man comes to finds you,
you can help them.
[Kim Jong Kook]
[Suzy voted for Jong Kook,
and since Gary came and found her...]
You said you were an angel!
This is the devil, not an angel!
I'm sorry, but please be taken out.
[Other angel's also vote for the
member they hope to win]
[Seung Yeon...]
[Voted for Jae Suk]
[Since the one she voted for came,
she gives him the small name tag]
[That's how Jae Suk's life got
multiplied by two]
I picked this out because
I really wanted you to win.
You really are a good angel...
you're a really nice angel.
[Ace Ji Hyo, listening to everything]
Why?
[If you put it on like that...]
They can tear that off easily.
You have to stick it in the middle.
-This won't stick on here.
-Where?
How am I supposed to stick this on?
-This is the only way it sticks.
-How?
How did you put it on, Seung Yeon?
-Ah, pull this off and put it underneath?
-I'm getting another one?
-There you go. Underneath it.
-Then I have 2 name tags?
Nice!  Seung Yeon...fighting!
I'll make sure to win.
-I'll share my prize with you.
-See you later!
-Bye angel!
[Angel or not, Suk Jin, who's concentrating
on surviving this game]
[Found Ji Hyo]
-Kang Gary.
-You saw me?
-Okay.
-Kang Gary.
Hi, Ji Hyo.
There's Ji Hyo and Gary.
-Did you see him?
-No, I haven't seen him.
Strangely,
things are going the way I want...
Where is he?
[Jae Suk! Why is he...?]
How can you do this to me when
we haven't seen each other in awhile?
I'm sorry... I didn't know you'd come.
[f(x)'s Krystal that met Jae Suk]
-Krystal!
-Hello.
Krystal! What are you doing here?
I'm an angel.
I can help you, but you have to get on that.
You have to get on that
before I can give you something good.
I really want to get your help...
But there's no way I can get on that.
You have no choice.
Why don't I have a choice?
-Why don't I have one, Krystal?
-Because I'm an angel.
Since you're here...
I'm in trouble...
You have to grab the handle to your right.
-You're awesome.
-This isn't awesome, Krystal.
Krystal... Krystal... this is...
Krystal!
-What is he doing right now?
-That's really scary!
Is that...
[Suk Jin is coming up behind Ji Hyo]
-Is that what the angel's doing?
-No.
She's not an angel.
[Suk Jin succeeds in tearing off
Ji Hyo's name tag]
[Song Ji Hyo, out]
I'm sorry, Ji Hyo!
I didn't know Suk Jin was
going to do that!
Okay.
But... just know this.
I know something very important.
Because I'm out, I can't tell you.
Why did you tear that off?!
We should've found that out
before you tore it off!
Song Ji Hyo, out.
Hey, tell us.
-Krystal!!
-Fighting!
What to do?
Please!  Please!
3, 2, 1, bow!
Pull it!
Guys!  Guys!!
[Unbelievable speed.  Unbelievable height!]
[Heart's of people watching drops]
How can he ride that?!
How can he ride that?
[Awesome]
Guys!  Guys!!
Krystal!!
Gary! This is crazy!!
Don't come here!!
-Don't come here!!
-Jae Suk! Stop saying that!
How can he ride that?
We're going to give you
the round one next time.
Just give it to me now.
[Anyways, succeeds in the ride]
Wow...you look cool.
[Receiving an applause from everyone]
-Have you ridden that before?
-I'm not going to ride that.
Jae Suk... you're very cool.
I'm not going to ride that.
You're saying that was cool?
Jae Suk... you succeeded.
You're very warm.
[Sound of bells ringing?]
Krystal...come on.  Krystal.
[This can't possibly be?]
[Gary].
[Voted for her sister Jessica's ex].
If you pull out a bell,
I'm not going to let you get away with it.
-Give me something else.
-I don't have anything else.
[Only thing to receive is a bell]
You think I rode this to get a bell?
But I had no choice because you came.
You're mad because
you had to ride that, right?
-So then tell other people..
-You want me to bring you customers?
[Gary found another angel...]
I can smell the perfume of a girl.
I can smell an angel's perfume.
[4 minute's Hyun Ah]
Hyun Ah, why are you wearing killer heels?
Then I should stand on my toes.
To be honest, I didn't think you'd come.
Angel!  Jong Kook, it's an angel!
-There's an angel here.
-Hello.
[In front of an angel, he's acting mellow]
-You have to decide.
-What?
[Just what would it be that
the angel has to give to Gary?]
[A small name tag]
I think Gary would be nice,
so I hope that he wins.
What do we do?
You didn't see it, right?!
-I saw it.
-No!  You didn't see it!
I won't give it to you!
I didn't count on this, but here.
[Hyun Ah angel gives Jong Kook a bell]
Why's everyone doing this to me?
Jong Kook, hurry up and tie it on.
I can tie it on...
-This is nice...
-Thanks.
-Hurry up and run away.
-Make sure he ties it on, okay?
-Fighting!
-Thank you! You're the best!
Gary. Gary!
[This is the only chance to run].
I can't believe Kang Gary got...
I can't run fast with
this bell making all this noise!
[Gary has 2 name tags]
[He has to be caught now].
Suk Jin! That way!
-Gary...Gary.
-Suk Jin!  Wait!
Have a seat here, Suk Jin.
He has 2 lives anyways.
-What do you mean, I have 2 lives? Come on!
-Tear it of right now!
-What do you mean, I have 2? Suk Jin!
-You have 2!
Think about this carefully? Think about it!
-Think about it!
-Tear it off!
See? He has another one.
Do you see that little one?
-Don't you see that little one?
-I have to tear that one off myself!
[Gary, out of both name tags. Out!].
-Suk Jin.  Have you met an angel yet?
-Yeah, I met one.
You know the place that looks like
a rice wine house? She's in there.
-Rice Wine  house?
-Yes, she's in there.
[He finally meets one!]
Hello!
[KARA's Gyu Ri]
-You have something to give him, right?
-Yes!
-It's a good thing, right?
-Of course!
-What is it?  I'm nervous!
-Jong Kook, come on in here.
-Wait out here for me.
-Jong Kook...I really have been waiting...
-No, this isn't it...it's not it.
-Here you go, Jong Kook.
[Ultimately, it's a bell]
It's a bell?
That was not very nice.
[Jae Suk preyed on Suk Jin].
Jae Suk!  Jae Suk!
[But with reflexes that's unlike Suk Jin,
the chance was lost!].
He's running fast!
Come here! You come here!
You come here!
There's no way he'd go that way.
I think he went this way.
[Mr. Capable and Suk Jin working together].
[Separating to capture Jae Suk].
I'm going to win today.
[Using his instincts to chase,
Yoo-ruce Willis]
Hey! Jong Kook! He's here!
[Yoo-ruce Willis tears off the whole
name tag off of Suk Jin's back].
Yours was really hard to tear of, Suk Jin.
Ji Suk Jin, out. Ji Suk Jin, out.
Ultimately, it's between Jae Suk
and Jong Kook.
See? I told you. Jong Kook is going to win.
We should've done whatever we could
to get rid of Jong Kook from the beginning.
[Ultimately...]
[These two...]
[This sickening, unavoidable fate...]
[Running Man's two major power players...].
It's been awhile since I've seen you.
This place is too big.
What do you mean, it's been awhile?
I see you all the time.
Jae Suk. Did it make you happy
to hurt our feelings like that?
What do you mean, I hurt your feelings?
-Jae Suk.
-Why?
I've missed you.
-So...
-It's just the 2 of us...
The fact that it's just the 2 of us...
let's have this out.
[Since the early days of Running Man,
the consistent 2 super powers...].
[One of the two is superior...
somehow 2 years have passed].
Let's do this now.
You're like a Spartan...
And I'm... more like Yoo-ames Bond.
I have to have something.
You're like the Spartan that runs,
and tears things off...
You got some exercise with me.
Even if I exercise... there's a limit.
[No matter what he does,
he can't avoid this battle]
[With this opportunity...]
[Let's finally find out who the top player
of Running Man is...!]
[Jong Kook successfully defends himself
by grabbing Jae Suk by the wrists]
[Jae Suk being pushed back by Jong Kook]
Wow... you're so strong! So strong!
If I had... if I had a water gun...
I wouldn't be humiliated like this...
[The tiger is playing with the grasshopper
that's been sapped of his energy]
-This way...
-Jong Kook...
[What...what is he doing?]
[Earlier Kwang Soo... Why is everyone...]
Jong Kook...do you really have to do that?
Jong Kook!  Fine. You can take it.
[Jae Suk lies down so Jong Kook doesn't
notice his second name tag.]
What are you doing?
Why are you lying down?
I'm out.
I can see it.
-I can see it.
-You saw it?
-I can see it right now. I can see it!
-See what?
You saw that? You really are strong.
How many years have you been
working out for?
[We thought he's been sapped of energy,
but he's starting to attack!]
You hate having your hairstyle
touched the most, right?
[Mr. Capable who's
very sensitive about his hairstyle]
You don't like this?
Getting your hairstyle messed with?
[The two go on fighting like this
for another 15 minutes...]
[Both are exhausted...]
You've worked hard today, Jae Suk. Okay?
[However, the one who's more exhausted
is undoubtedly Jae Suk].
I will make sure to get my revenge!
We should-- we should've without a doubt
ousted Kim Jong Kook in the beginning!
You've worked hard today...
[Jae Suk, out!]
[Running Man Survivor Game]
[Kim Jong Kook-The ultimate winner]
[But the thing Running Man has truly
been waiting for is...]
[Meeting time with the angels]
They're here!! Welcome!
-Don't you think you were too much, Krystal?
-It's Suzy!
[Everyone gathering in cheer]
It's Hyun Ah!
-It was so fun!
-Wow... Hyun Ah!
How did these busy angels join us?
-Wow.... I'm so shocked!
-Are they doing this with us tomorrow?
Tomorrow is... a pair race.
-Who's the survivor winner today?
-Kim Jong Kook!
The survivor winner today is receiving a
prize that's much more grand than ever before.
Does he get a chance to perform
with a girl group?
-That's really grand!
-That's nice!
He's going to be shooting with the angels...
He will be picking who the angels
will be working with for everyone.
I'm ruined!
[Right away, everyone flocks to him
to beg for their chance].
Kim Jong Kook will choose however he wants.
You know what I did for you today...
-Be quiet! Quiet!
-You go over there.
[That night...]
Ha Ha...
[The pairs that Mr. Capable picks...]
Subtitles by DramaFever
[2012 upgraded pair race]
[Wedding race with the top girl Idols]
[Get married all over Seoul]
[Honeymoon's livelihood's...
essential abuse?]
[And...Running Man's ultimate prize!]
[And even a quiz to test
the ultimate knowledge!]
[Next week!
5 romantic brides are coming your way!]
I'm going to take a picture.  1, 2, 3!
[Next week's Running Man...
Wedding Race]