Start.
To all Running Man viewers nationwide and abroad. fellow citizens and workers, hello to you.
We'll start the opening ceremony of the first Running Man Championships.
I'm today's commentator, SBS announcer, Choi Ki Hwnn.
Hello. I'm Announcer Hint Min Ji.
The place we're at now was selected last night as the opening venue...
-Yes. - ... the front entrance of the SBS main entrance.
Yes. viewers have been anticipating this first Running Man Championship tournament
it will be very exhilarating.
Ok first, Announcer Kim Min Ji will introduce how the Running Man Championships will be carried out today.
Yes. today all the Running Man members wilt he participating in today's Running Man Championships.
There are four events in total.
The winning team will receive the gold medal.
To find out which team will receive the gold medal. everyone please stay visit us till the end.
As we re speaking, Athlete Yoo Jae Suh has entered.
Why do I have to hold this?
Athlete Yoo Jae Sult is making his entrance.
-Yes, Athlete Yoo Jae Suk is 41 this year. -What's this?
You're 41 years old right?
Athlete Yoo Jae Suit.
Recently, he's loved by many as Yooruce tVillis.
Wearing tight training pants is his trademark.
Today is no different as he's wearing; them again.
This is so sudden...
Athlete Yoo Jae Suk's best events ace...
teasing and chattering.
Ah, yes well, it's the truth,
-Do you acknowledge it? -Yes.
Ok. as we're speaking Athlete Ji Suk Jin has also entered.
Yes, Athlete Ji Sul Jin is 47 years old, his speciality is the Easy Brothers combo play.
Yes. they are our athletes.
What championship?
What is it today?
-What competition? -I don't know what sort of championship this is.
Ok. the championship's strongest candidate. Athlete Kim Jong Kook, is entering.
Ok now...
The championship's strongest candidate, Athlete Kim Jong Hook, is entering.
Yes. he's 37 years old and excellent in all events.
His only weakness is... women.
-That's deadly. -Especially with idols, idols.
Especially when Miss Yoon Eun Hye is mentioned, he crumbles.
I'm anticipating what sort of performance he will put forth in this championship.
-Hello. -Yes, hello.
What do you think of me?
Is this really your first time?
I'm sorry.
-Is it really the first time? -I come here as a fan.
I'm a total Running Man fan.
Are you a Running Man fan or Jong Koo' s fan?
Running Man.
She's very clear.
Oh. Gary s here.
Ok. coming right up is Athlete Gary entering the venue.
35 year old Athlete Gary is entering.
Athlete Gary is also known as a dark horse with his hidden skills.
That's right, I'm the best.
Ok. this time Athlete Haha is entering the venue.
Yes, Athlete Haha's strong event...
is being a playboy.
Haha’s good at being a layboy and making thoughtless remarks.
I've just seen both of them.
I will come on to you.
Also, he'll apologize the next week.
He likes to apologise.
-How many times must he apologize in a week? -I'm sorry.
Ok. after Athlete Haha.
Hey, Ji Hyo's really...
The next athlete to enter is Athlete Song Ji Hyo.
Hey. Ji Hyo is still in slumber.
She's sleeping.
Like oing to the mineral sprin.
-Hey, it's not a red carpet. -Run, run.
-It s not a red carpet, run. -Run, run.
What's this?
Although our strongest candidate is Athlete Kim Jong Kook...
The title of Ace truly belongs to Athlete Song Ji Hyo.
Yes. that's right.
Gwang Soo.
Ok, next is Athlete Lee Gwang Soo who is flying in.
He's using up his energy early.
Gwang Soo, here, here.
Entering with the speed of light.
Ok, Athlete Lee Gwang Soo has entered the venue,
The last athlete.
Yes, Athlete Lee Gwang Soo is 28 years old this year.
And his main experience...
seems like there's none.
There is no main experience,
in the recent Gary Knows edition, he had his first individual win. Unfortunately.
No one seems to care.
Everything can be made up if you do well today.
I hope everyone gives their best.
-Ok. coming right up... it hasn't ended yet. -What? - Gaeko!
Athlete Gaeko...
is making his entrance.
Athlete Gaeko has entered.
Why are you here?
I’m here to play.
Hey, come here, come here.
Hey Gaeko, you're blockin their views.
Hey. what's going on?
Mr. Gaeko passed the preliminary rounds in his company.
Did you beat Choiza? And Simon D?
I received a call from the director,
he said there's only one T.O,
Athlete Gaeko's entrance ends this segment.
Now. the representative athlete will come out to light the flame.
-We have to do the flame? -What's all this?
Excuse me, announcers.
What's all this for now?
I just went back form mineral sprin.
It seems that way.
Anyway. let me introduce the invited representative of the first Running Man Championships.
Korea's representative actress.
Of course, I knew it.
Jeez, what's that?
Who is it?
Oh, what?
Hey, it s Ha JI Won!
Who is it?
Hey, it s Ha Ji Won!
Impossible.
-Hey, I'm very close to Ji Won. -Be quiet.
Hey, I'm extremely close to Ji Won.
Oh. today's special guest is, Korea's National Actress.
Athlete Ha Ji Won.
-Both our surnames are Ha. -Give Athlete Ha Ji Won a round of applause.
Ha Ji Won. Ha Ji Won.
-Kang Gary, Kang Gary. -Here I go.
Now. the Name is lighted to mark the start of the first Running Man Championship,
Athlete Ha Ji Won is an all rounder in boxing aerobics, horseback riding and table tennis.
Hang on.
What are you doing? Wear it. Just wear it.
The atmosphere is heating up.
Following which, Athlete Ha Ji Won will lead all athletes in taking the oath.
Hello.
I'm Ha Ji Won.
Ha Ji Won, Ha Ji Wo.
The oath,
I will love you forever!
For life!
Hey. Hey.
Running Man athletes' oath.
So cute.
For Running Man's ho our and the reputation of the guests,
I vow to respect the true spirit of variety, we will respect and observe at the rules of the Running Man Championships.
-Applause! -The oath.
Ha Ji Won, Ha Ji Won!
The opening ceremony of the first Running Man Championships tournament has officially come to an end.
Viewers please continue to tuna in to the first Running. Man Championships till the end.
Thank you.
You 've worked hard..
Pretty, pretty.
Ji Won.
Oppa. hi.
Ah, reality.
When did you arrive?
Why didn't you twit to tell me you're coming.
Why didn't you, Ji Won?
Miss Ha Ji Won has come today.
Ha Ji Won!
Haha doesn't normally come to the middle.
Why are you here?
Be nervous, I might go out with her.
I'll invite you to our 100th day anniversary.
Today is the first Running Man Championships.
In today's championships, you will he divided into 3 teams.
Like this? Three people.
Why three of you?
We're standing in this order now.
Before we start, we have to decide on the teams.
All of you know the sit-up scene in Secret Garden, right?
Each one of you will do a sit up with her.
-And then? -If Miss Ha Ji Won accepts, you will form a team.
Oh, when you say accept you mean, lips?
How will she accept?
Will she hold our lìàntls?
She'll let you know.
If she doesn't like you, she'll first flick your forehead With a finger.
Ok. the first person.
Yes.
Hey, you'll be eliminated.
Hey, you'll be eliminated .for sure.
Eliminated, you'll definitely be eliminated.
Please hold here.
I feel great.
I love you.
Ok, get ready!
Get ready.
Ok get ready, start.
I'm oing.
One chance, you only have one chance,
I'm going.
Hey, look at his belly,
-Hyung. -He's gaining weight.
Ok, three, two, one.
Oh, for real?
That's It.
Hey, drag him out, drag him out.
Drag him, drag him.
I swear, I'll seduce you by the end of the day.
Gary.
Ah yes. I'm comm.
I'm sitting up.
Oh?
Seems like he'll get it.
No way, Jeez.
It s Gary!
Gary,
It's not funny.
What's that?
-Wow, Secret Gary*! -Really?
What should I do?
Anyway, Gary's chosen.
There are 3 people in a team, right?
That's right. She can choose one more person.
Shall I do it this time?
What's with your tone?
What's that? He seems confident.
It's just that she's my dongsaeng.
Although I've already mentioned it...
Miss... Ji Won and I...
We go a long way back.
Why are you suddenly calling her Miss Ji Won?
Are you getting nervous?
Ok. here I come.
Aigoo, aigoo.
Hyung, why are you pretending to be cute?
-Don't try to be cute. -You should remove your lasses.
Ok fine. Okay.
Ok, I'll do it again!
Ah!
-I ll do it again! -Ah!
Ji Won. Ah, Ji Won.
Ji Won. Ah, where are you going?
-Looks like she's afraid. -Ji Won, it's me.
Aigoo. 'It's me?'
It’s someone else, someone else...
I got a shock.
Hey, from this side you look like Myung Soo.
-Oh. it s Myung Soo. -He does look like him.
Ji Won, Just bear with it for a while.
Start.
Ah!
She really doesn't like it.
This is not acting.
-Yes. Yeah!
Did you see?
I win despite looking like this.
I'm going crazy.
I won like this.
-I won from you like this. -I didn't know she liked this sort of style.
Gaeko, come here.
From now on. the first Running Man Championships will start.
The competitions will be Like place all around Seoul.
Bowling, badminton, high jump. nud relay. There are four events in total.
The final winners will be awarded gold medals,
Gwanghwa-mun.
-The first event? We are competing here? -It should be like that all the way.
Isn't Miss Ji Won very good in sports?
Miss Ji Won's very good. I'm thinking of humming.
How's that, Ji Won? Isn't it very natural?
Did you write the song?
Ji Won...
Roughly how old...
When I went to school?
No, not that one.
Oppa, please just drive.
-Ji Won's starting again. -Hyung, did I see this just now?
-That's right -That Aegean force! - Of course.
Hey, Ji Won said it.
Oppa, oppa. Just drive!
Girls normally don't do this stuff.
The laughter keeps coming. Gary, the laughter keeps coming.
Hey Gwang Soo, you're beside him but Just relax. Don't be like this.
Kook!
Not that one. Aren't we the Tiger and Giraffe?
-And that hyung is... the Impala. -Impala.
Today, we're a bit like the Serengeti.
-It's here, it's here. -Ah, it’s here?
Sejong Centre for Performing Arts.
-It seems whoever reaches first will go first. -Is that so?
I'm the quickest.
No.
There?
Running Man Championships, the first.
Hey, shouldn't we warm up first?
-Hyung, what's that? -What’s that?
Hey, it’s bowling.
It's bowling!
-It s bowling! -They install a bowling alley here?
Are we first?
To all Running Man viewers, hello.
This place is the first Running Man Championships at a specially constricted bowling alley in Gwanghwa-imm.
A bowling alley was constructed in Gwanghwa-mun to be identical to an actual bowling alley.
Enthusiastic crowd has gathered and they're waiting for the Running Men.
So. which team will be able to showcase their abilities today?
There is huge anticipation.======.
-Bowling! -They set up bowling alley here?
Are we first?
This is the first urban Running Man Championships.
-Its bowling. -Yes.
You'll bowl one at a time.
If two people get a stride then the team will pass.
Ah, two people.
Is this the same as actual one?
-It's identical. -Oh, it's heavy.
Oh, its really like the 01 epics.
Hurry up, hurry.
Fighting, Fighting.
-Serengeti. -Kim Jong Kook, Kim Jong Kook.
Kim Jong Kook. Kim Jong Kook.
Why is it so slippery.
Oh, strike.
Oh, strike!
-It’s slippery. -Very slippery.
Both of you have to succeed.
They put a bowling alley here?
It's no joke. How did they set this up?
Running Man is daebak.
In the Running Man Championships...
Wow, I can't even imagine this.
-The first event... - It's great, right. Running Man?
It's daebak.
-I'm going. -Go.
Jeez.
Myturn? My turn?
Ok everyone, 'Strike1!
Go, go.
Haha, Haha.
Do it quickly.
Ah, do it quickly!
-What's this? -What’s this?
Yoo Jae Suk must be here.
Yoo Jae Suk, Yoo Jae Suk.
-Is it bowling? -It's bowling.
-He's good! -He's not bad.
Oppa's daebak. you did well.
-What are you doing with that? -You don't need them.
What are you doing?
- It’s uncomfortable. - That's used by professionals.
He who affects my mood.
He who underestimates me.
Fighting.
Fighting!
He who controls bowling!
Hyung, be careful with your butt.
The hips area is tight.
Looks good.
Looks good, hyung.
Oh, It looks good.
One two three. One, two, three, straight.
Fighting,
-One. two, three, straight. -Fighting.
Jeez.
-It's funny, it's funny. -What's with you?
Hang on. Hey. it wasn't on purpose,
It really fell.
-I told you not to wear it. -I won’t use it.
-Boo. -Fighting!
Boo.
Wow!
I've never bowled before.
Hey, stop it, stop it.
Ha Ji Won!
-Hey. what are you doing? -Hey. I told you not to.
It s because of love!
Good, great. The middle. It’s good. That's okay,
hat's it! That's it!
What is?
That's it! That's it!
I think I tried bowling about three times.
-What should we do? -You're in trouble.
Let’s go.
Everyone, Kim Jong Kook!
Kim Jong Kook, Kim Jong Kook!
Thank you.
Let's do a human wave!
He looks even more like a giraffe because lie s wearing yellow.
Kim Jong Kook!
Great! Great, great, it's done.
Oh yeah.
That's daebak.
That's good.
Gwang Soo.
Gwang Soo, Gwang Soo.
Giraffe, Giraffe.
What's with the pants?
That's good!
Great! Good, it's done, it's done.
Yes.
You'll be the first to leave.
Jongno H Mart.
Next, next.
Next,
Hey, hit a cool strike.
Oh, he's quite good.
0h. he’s quite good.
Wow!====.
You can do it, you can do it.
Haha, Haha.
Oh, it's good!
Oh, he did it.
We did it.
Hey. we're in trouble.
Thank you.
-We have to go. -Let's go.
This is bad.
Figliting!
Our team s too cool.
Aren't we?
Hey, I left without changing my shoes.
My shoes.
Fighting!
Fighting.
Ha Ji Won, Ha Ji Won.
From now on, you're the Bowling God.
Thank you.
Fighting!
Fighting. Fighting.
Good, good.
Ah!
Hey, she's still smiling though.
Hey, JI Won.
Ji Won, I thought you fell off a cliff.
I thought you fell off while bowling.
Hyung, it’s like in manhwa.
When she says "What do we do now?"
"What do we do?" With both legs up.
-Ji Won is... hey, Gary. -What do we do?
Let s do it quickly.
If we do it quickly, we can still go first.
Gary! That's right!
That's right!
That's it. Hey, that kid s still here.
Oppa, hurry.
Why is he taking so long?
Let's go, let's go.
Hurry!
Let's go. Hurry, hurry.
-Oppa, fighting. -I got it,
-Hyung, Its green! -Oh, it's green.
It's so worn out.
Just this once.
Hyung, I got the feeling.
Give me strength!
Good, good!
That's it! Truly, the green power.
Everyone, it's been hard on you.
Truly, it's green. Ji Won, I'm green.
-We did it all with green. -Hey Gary, we should do it with green.
Isn’t Ji Won really like a heroine from a manhwa?
-Yes, when she bounced around earlier. -Yeah, when she was bouncing around.
It's my first time seeing someone jump like that.
That’s how Ji Wonie umps.
Also, did you see it earlier? I thought she fell off;a cliff.
Over there!
-Where? -There, on the left.
There it is.
This is the mission.
The three teams will have a badminton battle and set off in the order of the results.
We win the first one by default.
Yeah, we win by default.
Hello to the national audience of Running Man.
We're having it here?
-Where? -Ah. the put something in the middle.
This is specially builtibadminton court.
An eco-friedly court in a large-scale mart.
Here, this one.
Athlete JI Silk Jin especially is the head of a celebrity badminton association.
Which team will win? Please stay tuned to find out together.
Oppa. I'll stand behind.
-I'll stand behind. No, Gaeko stands behind. -Fightin!
One, two. three.
Fighting!
Let's start.
Ready!
Hey. it's evenly matched.
Fighting.
Ok, good.
That's it! That's the way!
Referee, hang on. Time out, referee!
Jo PD! Then; we can serve from here?
Here, using this method?
What was that? I'll at least serve from here, this far back.
I'm a person without the basic.
Come here.
That's not right.
-Alright, so we can't do it this close. -Right. Make this line the limit.
Defend after you serve.
That’s it.
That's it!
Oh? It's here.
0h? It's here,
What, what?
Look, she didn't touch it.
Gaeko, I can’t see.
Gaeko, I can't see.
What's this?
This... does this make sense?
I know that Ha Ji Won is a very special guest, but...
Oh, your eyes are so pretty.
Oh. sexy.
Hey, nice trick.
It’s really jjang.
Ji Won was a badminton player in junior high but she scores tisin this method.
Hit it closer from below. Get closer.
Go a little closer.
-That's it. That's it. -Good, good.
Out.
One more point, one point.
All of you et out.
Get out. Not getting out?!
It's our serve. Gary.
The last one!
Gary, fighting!
Yeah.
We won?
Hyung, get out.
Hey, its over. Hey, it's over!
Your greed caused this!
Fighting. fighting.
Why are we so bad in badminton?
-What were you doing? -Get out!
What were you doing?
Get out of here.
Get out.
Hey, but Gwang Soo...
-Am I not a Running Man? -Hey. don't come into this area!
I'm at loss for words.
Don't come here.
Don't even touch a strand of hair on my body.
Good Job, Kim Jong Kook.
Ready!
Serve it to Gary hyun.
-Good. -Leave it.
-Yeah! -It touched, didn't he touch it?
Didn't he touch it?
Mr Gwang Soo's racket touched it.
-It didn't. -Exactly, it touched.
You sit down.
Han on. Why are you doing this? I really didn't!
Sit here for awhile.
You sit here.
Gwang Soo.
Sit down, Just sit down for awhile. Just like that.
What's this?
The match between the Red Team and the Yellow Team's totally fascinating, they're not Joking.
Are you ok, Mr Gary?
Yes, I'm fine.
Hey, you two, are like the leads from a high teen drama.
I should have thrown my body at it.
I'm sorry.
The teamworks very good, it annoys me.
If I do anything wrong please tell me any time.
-Criticize each other's play, got it? -Yes.
-Let me know if my playing Is unsatisfactory. -Please throw it over.
Hey, don't come Into this area!
Get out of here.
Are you ok, Mr Gary?
Yes I'm fine.
-Our serve. -Ours?
She's really pretty when so does that.
Seriously, affecting our mental...
Looking where to hit the ball to... so gorgeous.
Oppa,
Are you calling me?
Hey!
Jeez!
You told me not to move, so I didn't move,
Hey, I'm the head of a badminton association!
-Seriously... -Hyung. You told me not to move.
He’s really petty.
One Man!
Don't be swayed.
Hey, he's being swayed.
He's having mental breakdown.
Why are you so restless?
One Man, out.
They're really good.
Why Is his face so red? Look.
Hey, they're having a mental breakdown now.
How can all of you be defeated Just by an 'oppa'? Aigoo. seriously.
One Man and Oppa.
-She's truly my woman. -She's truly charming.
Jong Kook, you're too negligent.
You're a hole here,
Hyung.
Chairman, give me a chance,
Hyung. Let him do it.
-Then let Gwang Soo have two serves first. -Give it a try then. Go ahead and hit.
President! President! Feel! Feel! Cross!
-You stand here and hit, don't come over to my spot. -SukJin. h un became the ace!
The ace!
First time in my life I met someone so bad at badminton.
With Jong Kook hyung out, they're winning!
Well, because we can't say this has to do with skill.
But Gwang Soo plays well?
Hit first and we'll see.
-It should have been like this earlier. -Well done!
Our team is going to win.
-Not bad! -We're catching up! We're catching up!
Gwang Soo! Feel!
Feel! Cross!
Hyung! You should play with Ji Hyo later.
Now's the chance!
What is this!
Do it well![Must do it well!
You’re forcing me to get into this.
Should have caught It.
Nice! Nice! Nice!
Serengeti! Serengeti!
Nice! Nice! That's it!
Won! Won! Won!
Time! Time! Time!
Hyung, my stamina is now lacking.
-Ji Won, you should drink some. You should drink some. -Thank you.
Now, one more point. One more point.
0ne, two, three. fighting!
One, two, three. Serengeti!
Awesome. Really.
The three of us must end this.
Fighting! Fighting!
Serengeti! Serengeti!
Get out.
Invincible Serengeti!
We won!
Seriously wasted.
-President take it. -Okay.
-Myeongdong! Myeongdong! Myeongdong! -Okay!
First place...
Never thought that Hyung was so capable.
-Everything is going well for us today. -Everythin is falling into place.
Why didn't you say earlier?
-Oh my... -Why?
My face is no joke.
My face...
The dark circles on my face are no joke.
Mine is serious.
High jump! High jump! High Jump!
This is the competition place in Myeongdong where the high jump event will take place.
In this event, will the Serengeti team be able to keep their lead? Let us wait and see.
-How to do this? -How do we do this?
-The sum of all three members' record must exceed 4m to succeed! -4m?! I can't do this...
Why can't you?
Jong Kook, this is your speciality right?
4m? If it's 4m...
lm.
Im, 150cm.
For us, he is 140cm.
I'm 150cm, him 140cm, 110cm.
I'm 110cm. Okay.
Hyung. 150cm. 150cm. lm.
150cm, 150cm, lm.
I have no confidence.
You still need to jump!
We are 150cm, 150cm, lm.
We have no other choice!
Oppa! Can you see anything.
Oppa fighting!
Everybody!
Hyung! Oh, this is what happened during the llsan competition!
Woooooooo....
Yah!
Eeyah!
I don't know if this will work.
Where are you going?
-What are you doing?! -I asked where are you going!
-You gave me a big shock! -I asked where are you going!
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Almost got in trouble!
Fighting!
Hyung, you can do it!
Jumped over?
Suave! Totally sexy! Totally sexy!
-It's 150cm! -It's amazing!
Why sexy?
After watching this... it's touching.
Wow! Best! Best!
Gary!
Must challenge, challenge.
Kang Gary! Kang Gary! Kang Gary!
Seriously! It's too hard! Hard!
T's not even the Olympics!
Why am I so nervous?!
This isn't anything serious!
Calm down. Calm down,
He hit his head.
You re not embarrassed, right?
What are you doing?!
You do this well. Let's do rock paper scissors then.
-What do you mean rock paper scissors? -I can’t.
What do you mean you can't? Seriously!
-You want me to jump lm 50cm? Now? -I don't care.
Why don't you just Jump? You're athletic!
What a joke!
You are good at sports! Jump 1.4m!
Then 1.1m. 1.5m and doesn't that settles it?
1.5m! Raise it to 1.5m!
-I don't think he'd be able to do 1.5m. Should be lower -150cm! 150cm!
-Give it a try! -That’s right.
Gaeko try it! Gaeko try it!
It's too high. That...
You’re nimble, don't worry.
Challenge!
Gaeko! Gaeko! Gaeko!
He jumped really well!
-How can you jump so well? - Yung I am only 170cm!
No, 150cm, 140cm, 110cm.
Ha! 110cm!
150cm, 140cm, 110cm.
It's too high.
Jong Kook fighting!
Fighting! Fighting!
Challenge!
150cm!
150cm challenge!
Kim Jong Kook! Kim Jong Kook! Kim Jong Kook!
Daebak.
He’s not kidding around.
0ppa, how did you Jump over this?
1.4 m.
How do I Jump over this?
What?
Challenging 1.40 m!
Fighting! Gwang Soo, fighting!
Gwang Soo, fighting!
Upwards, upwards.
He's too tall!
He didn't even Jump,
Hey, he didn't even Jump, he Just rolled.
1.10 Ni.
Just roll over, head first.
You can do it.
-Use your shoulders like this and jump sideways. -Ah, Is that so?
Your shoulders.
No, no, hyung.
Hey, come here, I'll tell hyung.
-When you jump, lean sideways... -Challenge, challenge.
Let's go!
Hyung. Just roll forward, roll forward.
Forward?
-Please decide, sideways or forward? -Forward. Go forward.
Just think about curling over, use roll forward.
-Your head first. -Challenging, 1.1m.
Hyung, you just need to roll forward, forward!
Just jump over, use jump over!
Hey, if you couldn't even Jump over this then...
He, our team the Serengeti's is really no joke.
Why are we so good?
They're giving this to us already?
Ah, it's too easy.
-Thank you, it's been hard on you. -Thank you very much!
Hey, fortunately Suk Jin hyung jumped over.
We never missed first place, right?
-We've been first all the time. -Exactly.
Let's just change our team name to First Place.
We’ll start with Ji Won. 1 meter,
1 meter.
Ha Ji Won. Ha Ji Won!
-Challenge! -Challenge!
Ji Won, be confident like earlier on.
We should have raised another 10 cm?
Hey, she could do 1.2 meter.
Fighting!
-Fighting. -Fighting, Mr Gary.
Gary, just like what you did earlier. It will be fine.
What if I can't do it? That would be bad.
I completely forgot.
I'm having mental collapse.
I hate this sort of tension so much.
Challenge.
I have to go to the toilet.
Oh, I'm going crazy.
That's the way!
That’s the way!
Hyung, I've totally got it.
I've totally got out.
I'm the only one left.
1.50 m.
Look, this is the centre portion.
That's the bounciest part.
I want to go to the toilet.
Ji Won. I'm going crazy.
Ok, I'm going.
I'll Just jump!
Challenge!
-Challenge! -it'll be dangerous if you don't pass this time.
Please give a round of applause!
Clap, clap.
Hey, this round was dangerous.
Let's not he disheartened at times like this.
We're’going!
-Fighting! -Thank you!
We can do it.
-Do we go now? -Let's go.
Challenge.
Everyone, a round of applause!
-Let me hear you scream! -Ha!
Go!
You Jumped really cool.
To Mokdong.
We just leave like this?
-Hey Ji Won. I’m really going crazy. -Go to the nearest gas station.
Ah, Gary...
Are you sure you're fine?
I'll drive.
No, hyung is...
Hyung, there’s a coffee cup back here.
-Ji Won. -Yes?
In the worst case scenario, just pretend you didn't see anything.
Hyung, is it just my feeling that the driving bit rough?
It's just your feeling.
-I feel that the car is a bit rough, hyLing. -No, no.
I'm a bit uneasy.
Gary, it's just your feeling.
Forward, roll forward.
Challenge!
I can do it!
Time Controller.
Challenge!
I can do it!
Hyung, aren't you embarrassed?
Why can't I do this?
T me Controller.
What's difficult about this for me?
I can do it!
It was really cool.
We're good, we re good,
his is the most tense moment during the game.
Hey. this is too bouncy.
Ji Hyo, we succeeded.
We did it!
Ah. I've gotten older after the high jump.
Gaeko hyung, if you're tired I can drive too.
I'm fine.
Hyung. really.
-Hyung, this really isn't a joke. -Usually, you'll et moregur ent as you reach the destination right?
It's oscillating now.
We're here.
Let's go.
Hey, this...
What's this, doesn't it feel like a relay?
What’s this?
The final event of item first Running Man Championships is...
The Death Relay.
-Let me explain the rules first. -Ok.
-First decide on the 1st, 2nd and 3rd runners -Ok.
The 1st baton carrier will run to the 2nd baton carrier in SBS Building.
Locate the next runner, stick the name tag and pass the baton,
When everyone has their name tags on. you can start tearing the other's name tags.
But! If the baton carrier has his name tag torn off, the whole team is out.
You need to protect the baton carrier.
I'll be the first runner?
Ok, you go first.
You guys are so early!
You'll be surprised, you'll be surprised!
What is this?
It's bigger than our box. Wow!
Wow, sexy. So sexy.
Wow, so manly!
Hurry!
Wow, it's a 40 inch TV,
Hyung. what is this-?
Fighting!
-Don't run too fast, it’s dangerous. -Alright.
Looks like we are destined to get first place today!
Hey, this is long distance.
Start!
Hyung, this is long distance race.
-The second runners are on the 6th floor! -6th floor?!
-Gwang Soo's legs are too long! -Really long.
I'm tired already.
I can't run anymore.
Where to?
-Here, here! -Where, where?
They are here, they are here!
Really?
-You have to find the name tag before the second baton carrier can run. -Ah, yes.
-Where is it? I have to look for it? -Of course!
You have to find it before you can continue!
-He's so fast... -How did he come so fast?
I'm touched!
What's so touching about this?
-I'm so touched! -Realiy?
The name tag... where's the name tag?
I think the name tag is in the editing room.
They are here!
Gwang Soo, find it quickly! Run!
Giraffe, hurry up.
Hey, this way!
Gaeko hyung! Find my name tag!
His name tag is so funny!
I can’t...
I won't find it...
I’m going crazy, really.
Ah here! It's here!
It's JI Won’s.
Who is it?
-Ji Won. -You found it?
Ji Won...
-Ji Won, let's go! -Ok, hand the baton to fier.
Also. the 2 runners will go to the 9th floor to find the 3rd runner's name tag.
-Alright, go! -I have to go too?
Depart!
I'm going crazy!
We have to go outside.
Ji Won. I'm sorry.
Take the stairs.
Be careful!
Oppa is very tired right?
Why is this so funny?
Ji Won, I feel like dying.
-Oppa, get a rest, I'll go look for it! -It s ok.
This is not something that’s over after we find the name tag.
We have to tear off the other s name tags.
I'm going crazy.
Oh, he found it!
Quickly stick it on! Quickly stick it on!
9th floor, 9th floor! Let's go, quick!
We'll make a move first-
Why is ours still not here yet? Why isn't Gwan Soo coming?
Oppa!
-Ji Hyo! -Oppa, we ll find it quickly and fetch you soon so please wait.
-Hurry, hurry, hurry! -Hyung! Jae Suk hyung!
It might also be outside!
That's what I think too.
Look around in the bushes!
Found it! Found it! Found it!
-Take a look to see whose is it! -You can't, Ji Hyo!
-Oppa, let me take a look! -Ji Hyo. wait a sec.
Gary!
Ji Won! Ji Won!
Stay here! Ji Won!
We did It.
I found it! I found it!
Ji Hyo. still nothing?
I found it!
-Haha! I found it! -Oh yeah!
The team leader Indeed!
Take note! If the person with the baton is out. the whole red team is out!
You take this!
-Alright get ready! -Shouldn't we make a strategy?
-Oppa. let's go to the 13th floor. -Hey, this makes a sound when we walk through.
Oppa, this is no joke.
-Just brushing it off with something and... -Right, it’s going to fall off.
Let's go to the 13th floor, and have a meeting first.
Ok!
Let s find and talk in somewhere bright.
What, what!
Hyung! I found the Blue Team!
-Haha's team. -Go. go, go!
Oppa, this is no joke!
-Just brushing it off with something and... -Right, it's going to fall off.
Let s go to the 13th floor...
Oh! What?
Oh, what?
Oh, what's that?
Gary! Rip it off quickly!
-Gary! -Quickly rip it off!
Gaeko out!
How do we find this?
Hyung! Just now, inside there...
They're coming, they're coming,
Let's go quick. If someone attacks, don't just hide. Try to attack them and you will win!
Hyung.
-Hyung! We still haven’t found it yet! -You haven't found it?
Why did you do that? You surprised me.
You haven't found them?
Hyung. Jong Kook hyung.
After we find it...
pretend we haven't found it.
Pretend we haven't found it, then attack Jae Suk hyung.
Let's do it. Ok.
Gwang Soo, is this it?
This?
This is it. Oh, ok.
It won't stick? Pull the sides.
-Hyung. -Yeah? - Stay here.
-Why? Why? -Stay here.
-We still haven't found it yet. -You haven't found it?
-Why did you do that? You surprised me. -You haven't found it?
-You haven't found him yet? -Yeah!
-You frightened me. -You haven't found it?
-Yeah, don't do this. -We're still finding it!
Hyung. our strategy's been exposed, let's go quickly.
Jong Kook, I'm sorry,
-No oppa, they found it already. -We didn't find it!
It was noona's tag in that box.
-We haven't found it yet! -Jong kook. I'm so,..sorry.
Oh, I was really shocked.
No, they found it.
-What do you mean we found it? -We didn't find it.
Then, if you haven't found it then let's tear it off once as a oke.
-What? -That's right.
-This kid? -That's right.
Why should I do that?
-Just for a joke. -Anyway if you didn't find it...
So that we’ll believe' you didn't find it.
-This kid's? -Then you can just leave as you please,
That's right.
-Tear it. -Really?
I'm really not it, I'm really not it.
Aligoo, aigoo.
See?
-We didn't find it. -Look at this kid.
I saw his eyes,
-Hyung, I saw Jong Kook hyung’s eyes. -You found it, right?
Why are you like this?
Hey Ji Won, move back, move back.
Me?
I can fight.
She says she can fight.
-Why do you want to fight? -What do we do?
Why do you want to fight?
Why did she say we're fighting?
We get along well, we get along great.
We re not really fighting now.
-No, no. -Let s not fight like this.
Leave first.
Come here, come here.
-Hey, what's going on? -Hyung.
Yeah.
-We almost got into trouble. -Why?
Huh, why?
When we came out. there seemed to be someone hiding there.
Who?
They found it. they found it right?
It would be great if I could rip it off from here.
I should have torn it earlier.
But, why We don't have any special abilities so why are you targeting us?
Just tell us, we won t ask anymore questions.
-What will make you believe us? -You have super powers right?
Should I go?
Can they see me from there?
-Just go and find it. -Stop giving us that look.
-I got it.. -Ah. seriously.
These people are seriously...
Hey. there seems to be one less member.
She's probably hiding somewhere.
Look, can't you see Miss Ji Won's red clothes?
Miss Ji Won!
Noona.
Miss Ji Won.
I'm asking Miss Ji Won why she’s hiding here now.
The staffs have gone out.
Hyung, we’ll find it as soon as possible,
-Find it quickly. -But to find it we have to leave here first.
We'll look for it.
-But, why are you coming here? -We've searched the other area,
Hyung, if it s not here then it s not on this floor.
Are you sure?
-Mr Ji Suk Jin doesn't have a nametag yet, you're sure? -That’s right.
-Seriously? -Of course.
You're serious?
-We're sure, it's not with us. -100% certain.
-If not, we have to start the fight now. -Exactly.
-Right? You're sure? -Yes.
-Why are you looking at me? -Hang on.
Oh?
See this?
They’re alive, they're still alive.
Let's go.
Ah.
Hey. you're really jjang.
-This is seriously very disadvantageous for us. -What do we do?
Hey, firstly...
See? When they’re back with Suk Jin oppa. we can't do anything.
Suk Jin hyung won't go easy with the women.
This is bad. What do you guys do about this?
Hey.
You tore it? You tore Jae Suk's?
Ok, ok.
They ran off because we tore off Jae Suk hyung's.
Yes.
There. Over there.
They're over there right?
They 're over there right?
You all seriously work hard for our entertainment shows.
Hello.
-Run! -What?
I tore it off.
Out. Team out!
Hey, should you hold on to this?
-The girls might be ail over me. -Fight, right.
It won't be easy for me to get away.
This important mission.
Hey, why are you wanderin off.
-The baton was with him? -Why didn't you look around?
Why didn't you look around?
Yellow Team, out. Yellow Team, out.
Yeah!
Yeah, Ji Won.
Wow, seriously.
Hey, I'm out because of you!
Why, why is it my fault again?
Because of you I died.
It just ended like this.
-What happened? -Hey, what...
Hey Ji Won, what happened?
What happened?
I did well.
Ah, you did well!
Hyung, you've worked hard.
You’ve worked hard.
Camera Director Kang Chan Hee will hand out the awards.
Oh, thank you, director.
Is this silver?
It's silver.
Hey, if you did a better job we could also get the gold now.
It's not platinum, right?
-Aigoo! -Wow.
One, two, three.
Yeah.
Nice to meet you, I'm Han Ga In. Let's be friends.
Nice to meet you.
Ga In, please be my last love.
One, two, three!
We have amnesia now.
-What... -Yeon Woo!
Don't come closer.
Oh, Yeon Woo.
I remember now.
Today's Monday.
Hey!
Don't come any closer.
Even so...
Oh I'm really about to cry.