This place is so hostile.
[Leisurely relaxed turtle, Go Soo]
How beautiful!
[Not the least bit prudish,
the beautiful Han Hyo Joo.]
[A race of taste buds that's about to happen
in the district known for their food.]
Just take one bite, okay?
I think this is nice weather
for a race like this.
[Only the one who's become King has
the right to rip off the name tags.]
The next King that Running Man
has chosen is...
- That's absurd. It's not voting, right?
- Let's go, Yoo Jae Suk.
- Who should I vote for?
- Who do I vote to be King?
[The voting gets under its way!]
Running Man's time of the Royals
is about to start now.
[City of Jeon Joo where the history
of Korea is still left fully alive.]
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Eight o'clock in the morning.]
It's morning. Time to get up.
The first person to get out here will have
the biggest advantage. Hurry on out here.
[The first person to wake up...]
[What the heck? Blank Ji?]
[Next up is Jae Suk, who's
usually always the first to wake up.]
Song Ji Hyo...
what are you doing up already?
Go Soo! Go Soo!
My knee hurts...
[Slowly getting up one by one.]
Hyo Joo!
Hyo Joo's not the most
productive type, is she?
She's lazy.
Me? I'm productive!
I'm productive!
Productive, my butt!
How are you productive when
you're the last one to get up?
I'm productive!
How beautiful! How beautiful...
I didn't know that the siren meant
I had to get up and come outside.
Hyo Joo...
- How beautiful! How beautiful.
- Right?
Seriously...
[Everyone is now up and awake!]
Today's race...
is the 2012 Running Man Selection Race.
Selection race?
Jeon Joo is a district that's famous
for their food, right?
So your first race is a taste bud race
around various different locations.
- Wow...
- Taste buds race, I like it!
[First selection- Taste buds race.]
You have to choose the dish that you like
better between two dishes
and beat the mission
your selection decides for you.
There are a total of four courses where you
have to choose between the two dishes.
Every time you pass one of
those courses
you'll be able to complete one swipe for
the word, 'King', in Chinese character.
The first person to arrive at the final
location with this completed word...
will become Running Man's
King for the day.
[Running Man's King...]
[Become a King?]
[The omnipotent power of a King.]
[Only through a vote,
can a King's seat be replaced.]
[Just who will become the King?]
The person who becomes the King will have
the most power at the final location.
So it is of utmost importance to be
the first one to get through the race.
As I've already stated,
you have to choose one of the two dishes.
Your first round of selection...
is between Jeon Joo's Bibimbap
and Jeon Joo's bean sprout soup and rice.
[A refreshing bean sprout soup and rice
or the taste of Korea, Bibimbap.]
[Taste bud Race - Start!]
I wonder how many delicious things
I'll get to eat today.
Even just the thought of it is...
Jeon Joo's Bibimbap is really good...
but since it's the morning,
that soup and rice sounds really good too.
At last, I finally get to eat
Jeon Joo's bean sprout soup and rice.
It looks as though I'll get to start off
my morning with a bowl of Bibimbap.
There it is. Running Man.
Okay... Running Man.
[Arriving at the mission location]
[To the mouth watering
bean sprout soup and rice restaurant.]
Jong Kook, you've chosen Jeon Joo's famously
refreshing bean sprout soup and rice.
[The mission of this location is...]
When finished with the dish,
wrap the blanket around your body
and jump over the pillow with
the blanket wrapped around you.
I have to wrap this around me
and jump?
- You have to tie it tighter.
- It's wrapped really tight.
- What is this?
- I know.
Why is Kim Jong Kook here?
Hey, I'm the one who should be asking that.
I was already here.
- You're here too? Why is everyone here?
- What are you doing here?
- What are you all doing here?
- Go Soo's here too.
- Go Soo...
- Darn...
- Why did everyone come here?
- You need broth in the mornings.
[Yum... nice warm soup for breakfast?]
[On the other hand,
at the Bibimbap restaurant...]
[Jump while in a seated position, and if you
land on top of the blankets, you succeed!]
- You want us to jump on top of that?
- Yes.
[A feast for the palate on the table.]
- What is this?
- Is that supposed to be the yolk?
[Passing out the egg yolk.]
Okay, let's do this.
[Bibimbap restaurant's mission-
Become a human fried egg and jump!]
- I'm going to succeed with my first try.
- You can't go first. I got here first.
- What is all this?
- Han Hyo Joo is here!
- Hyo Joo, we're human fried eggs.
- Come on, and put this stuff on.
We're human fried eggs.
You're hungry, right?
I can't eat right now?
You get to eat once we succeed the mission.
We don't have any time to waste right now.
Weren't we going to get to eat
once we got here?
No. What do you take Running Man for?
I'm seriously hungry right now.
[When I'm so desperately hungry...]
[I can't even eat when the food
is right in front of my eyes...]
[No other choice than to become a
human fried egg and succeed!]
- Gary!
[So cute!]
- Your hair is a little...
- That suits you very well!
Do I look ugly?
I'm asking if I look ugly.
- Not really ugly, but just weird looking.
- Really?
[Not quite ugly,
but rather looks like cartoon character.]
Seriously, Gary...
I wish I looked like you right now.
[A perfect look for a variety show.]
[The leisurely Go Soo has nothing on
how he's taking his time to get ready.]
- You really are hateful.
- Is he like that all the time?
- I'm so sick of it...
- He's like this all the time?
Go Soo, you've only witnessed it for two weeks
but we have to see this every single week.
- Every single week!
- Here I go!
Okay, let's do this.
[Kkuk's turn at the challenge]
[Wow... he jumped over it.]
What are you doing? I passed over it!
- No, you didn't say 'Challenge'.
- I did say, 'Challenge'.
[Did he fail because he didn't
say 'Challenge'?]
[Result of verifying the footage-
'Here I go'.]
[And with that, Kkuk fails.]
You didn't say challenge.
My turn. Challenge!
- You can't do this.
- No way. He can't do it.
[Low expectations from his
surroundings.]
- There's no way...
- Give it a try.
[Jumping in place with difficulty.]
Set, go!
Yoo Jae Suk...
can't you do this? This?
- Seriously...
- You can't do that?
I'm getting a feel for this.
[It seems you got the feel
for falling over?]
- Suk Jin, why do you keep falling lately?
- What's wrong with you?
[Big-nosed Brother who can't seem to get
a sense of balance lately.]
Here I go.
[Big-nosed Brother's challenge!]
[Exquisite skills when it comes
to body gags.]
- Just get some sleep down there.
- Just go to sleep.
Suk Jin has become an icon when it comes
to body gags on this show lately.
We'll get our breakfast only
when we jump over this, right?
The pillows can't topple over either.
At this rate, I'm not even sure we'll
get to eat the soup and rice.
I'm so hungry.
Don't they ever feed us on this show?
I think I need my breakfast.
Challenge.
- Jong Kook, I'm going to do it first.
- Okay.
- You're going to get it done?
- I think he'll get it done.
[Go-vid jumping lightly over it?]
[Ah... it's falling over...]
I'll get it done. It's my turn, right?
- Okay, then...
- I'm really going to get it done this time.
Challenge!
[Flying Tiger...]
[Is it a success?]
What are you doing?
[After slyly swiping at the blanket
with his foot...]
[Sighing deeply as if he's disappointed...]
- Why are you all seriously being like this?
- I honestly didn't do anything!
- It's because I'm disappointed for you!
- It really is disappointing.
Go Soo, did we do anything? Did we?
They just fell over.
[We'll go with them
just having fallen over...]
- You think Go Soo would lie?
- Of course not.
How disappointing...
I'm going to remember all of this
at the final race.
[A red hot Tiger's warning.]
- Go ahead.
- I'm being serious!
I'm serious. I'm going to make sure that
you're gone for most of this week's show!
- Fine.
- You saw what happened to Kwang Soo, right?
Let's see... let's see an episode of
Running Man without Yoo Jae Suk.
[I'm going to oust every single
one of you!]
You really are so hateful...
Everything about you is so hateful.
[Can't hear you...]
Challenge.
I'm going to get this done.
[Making sure to shout out 'Challenge' first.]
[Girls get to jump over three pillows.]
[Oh? Did she succeed?]
[Blank Ji succeeds!]
[Finally at last... Time to
enjoy the delicious soup and rice.]
This is so delicious.
I really want to eat.
This is really delicious, Jae Suk.
The broth is...
[Enough to make your mouth water...]
[Ha Ha's turn at
the seat cushion jump challenge.]
I think I'll get it this time.
I'm going to do this.
I'm seriously going to do this!
One, two...
[Ha Ha succeeds!]
I succeeded!
This is it! I did it!
Can I eat now?
[At last, getting to taste the infamous
Bibimbap of Jeon Joo.]
- Hyo Joo!
- Is it good?
Is it good?
[I'm hungry. That delicious dish...]
[Huh? Where's Hyo Joo going?]
Move!
[Suddenly climbing on
top of the seat cushions.]
- Endure it. Calm down... calm down.
- Move out of the way.
- Calm down.
- I said, I got it!
What are you doing?
[Fail...]
[Hyo Joo falling into despair.]
This is seriously so delicious!
This is like a work of art.
Everything is so good.
[I know I can finish a whole bowl
in a flash right now...]
- That looks really good.
- It really is.
This is almost too much.
Come here.
It's okay.
You can eat it too once you succeed.
[Sneaking in again.]
What are you doing now?
Hyo Joo... when do I get my turn?
I'm hungry too!
[Her eyes are only set on
succeeding the mission...]
She's very greedy.
[Success!]
[Succeeds through sheer tenacity.]
[You just wait, Bibimbap...]
I was starving!
Thank you!
But isn't it cheating since she
went out of turn?
[Is it cheating because she was
out of turn?]
There's an order we have to follow?
[That's how tenacious Hyo Joo...
finally got her Bibimbap.]
[Ha Ha's on his way to the next
mission after finishing his meal.]
[But first, he has to write one portion
of the word, 'King'.]
[The next selection is...]
[Family style Korean meal vs.
a formal style Korean meal.]
[Ha Ha chooses
the family style Korean meal.]
[Family style Korean meal vs.
a formal style Korean meal.]
I'm going to choose the formal style.
[Formal style for Blank Ji.]
Family style.
Here it is, here it is!
[Ha Ha is the first to arrive
at the family style restaurant.]
No one else is here?
Have a seat, please.
How can this be?
Did someone already come by and leave?
- No, you're the first.
- I'm the first one here?
- What place am I at right now?
- Right now, you're the King.
King!
[If I can keep this up,
then I'll be the King....]
- I'll explain the mission to you.
- Yes!
Jeon Joo shows how bountiful
a family style meal can be.
[District of Jeon Joo is famous for
the bountiful family style meal it serves.]
[He'll be given orders on what to choose
out of the family style meal table.]
[And if you succeed 10 in a row,
you succeed the mission.]
Wow... you guys are good at
coming up with these games.
[The things we do for a living...]
[Ha Ha's challenge.]
Set... go!
Lift up the Fern Bracken.
[One. Fern Bracken.]
[Fern Bracken?]
[Fails right away from looking around.]
What... what is this?
What is this?
[I'm over here.]
- Ha Ha!
- Hyo Joo, you're here.
[A little less hungry Hyo Joo also arrives.]
I'm telling you right now,
this isn't easy.
If you see what you have to do,
you're going to be shocked.
- You haven't eaten yet?
- No.
There's no way to eat this.
Hey, hey, hey!
[Dreaming of revenge from last week?]
Set... go.
Eat the bread.
Eat the rice.
Don't drink the water,
but lift up the poached pork.
[Don't drink the water,
but lift up the poached pork.]
Wrap the pork in napa cabbage
and eat it.
What is this?
You really are coming up with
all sorts of games now!
Come on in.
[Leisure Go-vid also enters the room.]
Hyo Joo! And Go Soo...
- So he came after all.
- That soup and rice was unbelievable!
That Bibimbap was out of this world!
- Everyone's here.
- What's the mission here?
Look! It's bread!
Okay, it's Han Hyo Joo's turn.
Set, go!
Debone a piece of croaker
and eat it.
[Debone a piece of croaker and eat it.]
Debone a piece of croaker
and eat it.
[Fail...]
Come on...
Debone a piece of croaker and eat it?
You should've already had it
deboned for us.
- You're being really cruel now.
- Don't you think that you're being too much?
Hyo Joo, out.
Get in there, Go Soo.
Move over, Ha Ha.
I'll move over, Jae Suk, scoot up.
- Ha Ha, live happily in your marriage.
- Jae Suk, have a second baby.
Go Soo, be happy.
[Leisure Go-vid's challenge.]
[Slowly and leisurely taking a look
at all the side dishes.]
What is this?
Go Soo, can we start now?
Poached pork. Yes.
- He's like a slow and serious airhead.
- He's worse than Gary.
He takes his time with everything.
[Finally finished getting ready?]
He's just slow, but he pretends he's just
being relaxed about things.
- He's totally slow about everything...
- It's like a slow motion video.
Here we go.
[Re-adjusting his position before
getting started.]
He's taking so long getting ready!
- He's really slow.
- He's totally slow!
He's like a turtle. Go-rtle.
Go-rtle...
Eat the rice.
[One. Eat the rice.]
[You should've had the lid off...]
[A slow Go-rtle.]
- Go-rtle... he really is a Go-rtle.
- Go-rtle!
-Go-rtle!
- I'm Go-rtle's fan.
- Me too.
- He's an air-headed Go-rtle.
[Go-rtle, Go Soo. Making others
laugh with any fast movements.]
[This is a formal Korean style restaurant.]
[Gary and Ji Hyo both arrive
almost at the same time.]
No, I was the first to pull up
to the door.
[If you eat the delicious dishes and avoid the
ones with the hot peppers, you succeed!]
[Formal Korean meal bursting with
flavors and beauty of the cuisine.]
[Hot pepper is hidden among
these dishes...]
- This is good, Song Ji Hyo!
- This is good. Glad I ran into you!
- I'm good at eating spicy foods.
- I'm good at eating them as well!
[The two with confidence at being
able to handle spicy foods.]
Hello.
[The Giraffe also rushes in there.]
- How did you get here so fast?
- Formal Korean meal!
Since you're all here,
I'll explain it to you all at once.
[Mission explanation]
You know what a taste tester is,
correct?
- Taste tester...
- Is it a name for someone?
[Taste Tester: Person to taste the food
before a King to check for poison.]
So it's a woman who tests the
food for poison?
On the table before you are 37 different
delicious formal Korean dishes.
Of these dishes, there are some that has
slightly spicy peppers mixed into it.
[There are some slightly spicy dishes
mixed into the lot.]
[If you can't handle the spicy food after
eating it, then you're disqualified.]
[Stay alive by avoiding these spicy dishes!]
You will go in order of your arrival,
and we will start the game.
I have to finish this quickly
to get to the next destination.
[Just which out of these delicious dishes
are the spicy peppers mixed up in?]
I'm going to start off by eating a pancake
which is one of the representation of Korea.
- Pancakes... those are good.
- Starting off with pancakes.
[Gary selects a pancake.]
There's really nothing
they can do to pancakes.
I'm going to take a bite of
pumpkin pancake which resembles Ji Hyo.
[The taste is...]
Mm... good!
[Gary luckily avoids the spicy dish!]
Then I...
I'm going to choose the sushi.
[Ji Hyo's selection is sushi.]
I will eat the flatfish sushi
which resembles Kang Gary.
Why aren't you dipping it in the sauce?
Everyone has a different preference.
Are you two just going to keep talking amongst
yourselves? I shouldn't have come here.
Taste tester Lee, you can wait outside.
Where would I go?
Lee Kwang Soo, Gary!
- It's Jong Kook.
- Ugh, Song Ji Hyo...
I'm going to try the porridge.
[Gary's turn once again.]
[Vegetable porridge
full of the spicy peppers!]
This is delicious.
[Is it in there?]
This porridge tastes better than
the pancake.
[His chatter becomes almost nonexistent.]
- Gary, you don't have to keep eating!
- The smell! I can smell it!
Do I have to eat all of it?
I can smell the spicy peppers!
- Then I shall finish it.
- Your lips are purple right now!
I put on some extra makeup today.
- What is that smell?
- Isn't what I ate enough?
Can I try a bite?
- Is it okay for me to give him some?
- If he wants it, yes.
Here, try it.
What's wrong?
Is there something spicy in this dish?
How did you eat this?
This isn't right.
It's not right that he ate that much.
[Eyes tearing up?]
- I'm not crying.
- Did he endure it?
What do you mean, endure it?
I thoroughly enjoyed the dish.
He passed when his eyes are
tearing up like they are?
[This guy... he sure does surprise us
with his skills sometimes...]
- Okay, he passes.
- Yeah, we have to pass him.
[Because he endured it, he passes!]
It's pepper porridge. Pepper porridge...
It's totally pepper porridge!
- That was totally pepper porridge.
- That's just unbelievable.
[Being able to endure that...]
[I'm a red hot Mr. Capable
that can withstand any spice...]
Here we go...
It's our leisurely friend's turn.
Set, go!
Eat the bread.
- He failed, he failed.
- He totally failed.
Eat the bread!
[Is success impossible for Go-rtle?]
Did you see him?
Eat the bread!
- He's just too slow!
- It's already over for him.
- Go Soo, get out of there.
- When you say, eat the bread, eat it fast?
- Eat it like this?
- Of course.
- You think you can get out of here?
- Is this how I eat it?
- Hyo Joo...
- How did you say you eat it, Hyo Joo?
[A demonstration of
Hyo Joo's quick hand movement.]
That's right!
You need to be fast like that!
- How beautiful!
You're so beautiful!
Okay, here I go.
You have to be quick in a game like this.
Watch. He'll be disqualified with the first.
I will swear to that.
- With the very first one.
- Hey!
Watch... watch me do this.
I'm soaking everything up with my eyes.
All the side dishes...
[Soak everything up with his eyes?]
Like this... open them up wide.
[In the process of soaking things up
with his eyes.]
Mackerel?
[Wait... the mackerel is...]
There's no mackerel on the table.
- I said, it's not up there.
- Why are you mentioning that's not on here?
- You said you soaked everything up?
- Why mention something that's not on here?
Jeon. Myun. Go. Pa.
[Acronym of side dishes in the area.]
He sounds like someone who has
no idea what's going on.
I got it.
Jwa. Bae. Bread. Seaweed.
Jwa. Bae. Bread. Seaweed...
[Let's see just how well you
end up doing...]
Lift up the fern bracken.
[Huh? He's grabbing green laver
next to the fern bracken?]
You're out, out.
- Move.
- I thought you soaked everything in.
I thought you were soaking
everything in!
What did you soak in with your eyes?
You think I didn't see that?
- You think I didn't see that, Hyo Joo?
- This is hard.
- Okay, here we go.
- Fighting, Hyo Joo, fighting.
Hyo Joo! Hyo Joo!
Joo! Joo!
Eat salted cuttle fish.
Eat the kimchi.
Eat the salted shrimp.
Eat the anchovy.
- She's actually doing pretty good.
- But I bet it's a little salty for her.
Wrap the pork in kimchi and
give it to Go Soo.
Eat the radish water kimchi.
Wrap the anchovy in
napa cabbage and eat it.
Anchovy wrapped in napa
cabbage is a little...
Drink some water.
Eat the bread.
But that was way too slow.
[Success]
- Eating like that is really...
- Success!
- Hyo Joo, we'll see you later.
- Okay, see you later!
[Hyo Joo wins the write to write
the second portion for the word, 'King'.]
That turned out well.
[Jeon Joo's Omogari Soup or
Jeon Joo's beef rib soup.]
Beef rib soup.
[Heading off to the rib soup restaurant.]
[And over at the formal dining restaurant,
Ji Hyo and Kwang Soo fails their mission.]
[The competition is now between
Jong Kook and Gary.]
Okay, go ahead.
You have to eat all of it.
[Blinking his eyes rapidly.]
Why are you doing that with
your eyes?
- Look at your eyes!
- Why? What's wrong with them?
Seriously though... you blinked
like five times within one second!
- Really?
- Why are you taking your coat off?
[Why is he getting angry all of a sudden?
Or is he just getting hot?]
- What did you just say?
- No, that's not what I meant...
You have to eat the rest of it.
His eyes got this big all of a sudden.
- Hurry up and eat the rest of it.
- Jong Kook, just come over here.
[Starting the hiccups?]
He's hiccuping... I think it's
because the food's too spicy for you.
- No, no...
- It's because it's so delicious, right?
Shouldn't he have failed by now
with all that?
Look, he's hiccuping!
Jong Kook, come over here.
He's scratching up his chest!
[Jong Kook gives up and fails the mission.]
I've found Jong Kook's weakness now.
I should carry some hot pepper flakes
around with me and throw it at him.
What are you doing?
He's eating weird stuff over here.
[Uh... that's not for eating...]
[Hyo Joo arriving at her next location.]
Hello. I'm the only one here?
[Hot and steamy bowl of beef rib soup.]
[If you can split up three pieces of firewood,
then you succeed. One for women.]
[If she can split up one piece of firewood
out in the front lawn, then she succeeds!]
I'm the King right now?
That's so great!
[However, this mission
doesn't seems so easy...]
Hi.
I have to cut up this firewood right now.
[Let's play together some other time.]
[Even with a strong blow, there's
no damage done to the firewood.]
Do we only get one chance with this?
No, you can do it again.
This isn't really working.
This is the place.
Hello.
- Hello.
By any chance, do you know how
to split up firewood?
Easy way to split up firewood?
Hello, yes, hello.
- Hyo Joo, what are you doing?
- I'm splitting up firewood.
- So you're already doing the mission?
- If you're trying to split up firewood...
You have to follow the grain of the wood.
[If you want to split up firewood,
follow the grain of the wood.]
If you follow the wood and hit it hard,
you'll have it split with one blow.
- If you don't, then it'll never work.
- Thank you, Elder.
- Thank you.
- Thank you, Sir.
Goodbye, Sir.
Three... I have to split up three
to succeed?
I can do it.
Challenge!
[That's right... Follow the grain...]
Ugh... that was a good try!
Look! It did split!
Challenge!
It seems like the perfect weather
to be splitting up firewood.
What made you think of that
all of a sudden?
I thought of it while staring
up at the blue sky.
- It's beautiful.
- Hyo Joo, get move a little.
- Okay.
Just like the elder told us,
I'm going to follow the grain.
[Planning on striking just as
the elder taught him to do.]
You have to follow the grain
of the wood.
['In order to split up firewood, you
have to follow the grain of the wood.']
- If you follow it, you'll get it in one shot.
- I see.
[One clean shot!]
That's unbelievable!
Challenge!
[Two in a row!]
[If he can do one more,
then he passes the mission.]
[Will he be able to do it with one strike?]
[Splitting up firewood
is definitely my game...]
I did it.
- This is the perfect game for Kim Jong Kook.
- Jong Kook, when did you get here?
Hyo Joo, one shot. Just follow the grain.
- Challenge.
That piece of wood is too sturdy...
Let me see it. I think it's too sturdy.
I'm sure this must be hard.
[It's hard, you said?]
- Why is that hard for you?
- No, it is hard.
I shouldn't have come here.
I should've chose the other soup.
[I shouldn't have come here...]
It would be so nice if I could just close
my eyes for five to ten minutes.
[Ah... so sleepy...]
[I wonder if I can close my eyes
for a few minutes...]
[Ultimately...]
[Go-rtle reclining the seat back
and laying down to get some rest.]
I'm just going to take a nap
for five to ten minutes.
[He really did fall asleep
for five minutes...]
- Here he comes.
- Who is it?
- Isn't that Go-rtle?
- Yeah, I think it's Go-rtle.
[Much livelier than earlier?]
- Look at the way he's walking.
- He's just walking here instead of running.
- He doesn't run.
- When did you get here?
Why are you getting here so late
when you took off before us?
People these days are
too quick with everything.
They're too quick.
[Go-rtle having a tough time with
this fast paced world.]
- Suk Jin...
- Kwang Soo, finally we get to see you.
- Yes, Suk Jin.
- Are you good at breaking things like this?
- What?
- Is it brick breaking?
[Breaking bricks at this location?]
- Brick breaking?
- I've never done it before.
This restaurant is an Omogari soup place.
In Jeon Joo dialect, it means clay pot.
The game we've prepared in the spirit of the
clay pot and the earthenware of the soup...
- What does that mean?
- It means, gain strength from the soup.
Anyways... that sunshine really
feels great.
[His ease of being able to
enjoy the sunshine.]
Anyways, that sunshine really
feels great.
- See how much ease he has?
- He's really relaxed.
All of us have to try to break the bricks
and become the King so we can get going.
- Oh! It's Ji Hyo!
- It's Ji Hyo!
Look at her happy expression after
having seeing the brick breaking.
How many bricks do the women
have to break?
12 bricks for men,
and eight for women.
- But Ji Hyo's not...
- Ji Hyo's no girl though.
[Big-nosed Brother taking his turn first.]
This feels a little off.
Should I do it this way?
[Taking so long to get ready...]
- What are you doing?
- Suk Jin, this is how you do it.
Hold your fist like this,
and bring it down like this.
- Don't you even know that?
- Ji Hyo has to teach you that?
- Fine, you're better than me, okay?
- Just bring it down like this.
- You're taking way too long.
- But this is my way of doing it.
You can do this... you can do this!
[Eight bricks. Fail...]
I'll be on my way first, okay?
Go-rtle is being way too confident right now.
He's saying he'll be on his way first.
If he gets it with one blow,
then he'll be King right now.
- If you get it, then you'll be King.
- Really?
Okay, here I go. Challenge.
If you can get it in one blow,
it'll be really cool.
- Is this your first attempt?
- Yeah, this is my first.
Fighting...
[Even the cheering is Go-rtle style.]
[Okay... let's get on with this mission...]
[Will he be able to get it done with
one blow as he's guaranteed?]
[Huh?]
[Barely breaks six...]
- One, two, three, four, five, six.
- You did worse than Suk Jin!
- Only six!
- This guy really is a klutz!
What was it that you said?
'I'll be on my way first'.
- I'm sorry...
- That was like an air punch.
- Where did the fierce Go Soo go to?
- Are you sure you're Go Soo?
Wait, you think you can do it?
Just worry about yourself!
- This seems a bit tough for you...
- I bet she can do it.
- Ji Hyo...
- You have to break eight, okay?
- Eight.
- Let's see how good you are.
Challenge.
After all the things you said to me...
[I hope she's careful...]
- Look at her position. That's not a girl.
- She really isn't a girl.
[Breaks all of the eight bricks!]
Go Soo...
Go Soo breaks six and
Ji Hyo breaks eight.
[Really is Running Man's Ace
as her nickname states.]
What the heck are you?
- Did she pass?
- I'm telling you, she's not a girl.
- She has to be made to break 12 like us.
- I really don't know I broke them all.
[Ultimate humiliation for the men...]
With this...
[Blank Ji's brick breaking lessons.]
You have to jump down on it and strike
with your arms extended like this.
[Professor Blank kindly explaining
the method to her disciples.]
- Held out straight. Don't bend.
- Don't bend the arm?
Just in that position,
strike it down like this.
[While he was worried about her earlier,
now he's learning from her.]
It's okay with us, so let
Go Soo break just eight bricks.
No, don't do eight.
Let's just give him seven.
- Are you enjoying your meal?
- Yes, I am.
[And in the firewood splitting place...]
- I succeeded the mission too.
- I'm sure that you did.
[Gary's turn at the challenge.]
- It's not hard. You can do it.
- I've never done this before.
Hyo Joo, stay behind.
Something can fly your way.
Stay behind, okay?
- It's easier than I thought.
- There's no need to strike it really hard.
- Yes, you're right!
- See?
Entrusting my pride and honor
to the firewood...
and letting my arm fall wherever
this ax will fall on the firewood..
You and I will become one to the end...
To the end...
Okay...
[His third and final piece.]
[A world where you and I are together...]
- I'm sure you and I will become one.
- Yes, that's good.
[Wood splitting troubadour,
Kang Gary, succeeds!]
- Let's go eat!
- Gary's done.
[I definitely should've picked
the other soup...]
Hyo Joo, you have to utilize
the weight of the ax.
Slam down on it with the
weight of the ax.
[Trust the power of the ax...]
[And follow the grain!]
That's right!
- That's right!
- You did it!
- You did it.
Hyo Joo, what are you doing?
Hyo Joo, you did it.
Look at how happy she is.
High five! I knew you could do it!
[Everyone succeeds the third course
of splitting up the firewood!]
[Jae Suk having won the opportunity
to write the third portion to the word, King.]
Where's the next location?
[The final selection is...]
I love these dishes...
[Jeon Joo's thick noodle soup vs.
Jeon Joo's sweet bean thick noodle soup.]
I'm going to choose
the sweet bean noodle soup.
Kwang Soo...
[Kwang Soo's turn to break the bricks.]
Calling on the energy of giraffes!
[Oh my... it's really there.]
[Okay... receive the energy of
the giraffes.]
[Giraffe succeeds.]
- He really did it.
- He did break all of them.
[Is it thanks to the energy
of the giraffes?]
[Thanks, giraffes...]
- I'm so jealous.
- Show me your forms.
- I'll see if your stances are correct or not.
- I thought you only broke 11.
11?
[Jeon Joo's thick noodle soup vs.
Jeon Joo's sweet bean thick noodle soup.]
Jeon Joo's thick noodle soup.
[Professor Blank is heading off to
thick noodle soup.]
[Only Go Soo and
Big-nosed Brother are left.]
I don't like how only the first place winner
gets all the attention here...
- But we still have the next game.
- That's right. This isn't the end of it.
We still have one last game.
Since we still have one more...
Yeah, we still have one more.
Fighting!
[Darn... missed one...]
Wait! It's broken in the back!
- It's broken in the back!
- 12. He succeeded.
[Oh... he succeeded.]
There's a slight fracture in the back.
[Even though it's a slight fracture,
it's still counts as being broken.]
Wow! You actually did it!
It's broken in the back! It's broken!
[Even though he may be slow, he's
still honest about showing enthusiasm.]
It's telling me to go slow.
I don't think any one of them
has any sense of ease.
Everyone is only given one
chance at life...
They need to enjoy life more.
- We don't know who the King is at the moment.
- I'm not the King?
You have a very good chance since
you were the first to arrive here.
This mission is a dish that cannot
be left out in Jeon Joo.
But in this area,
they just call it sweet bean porridge.
- This mission is 'Move the bean'.
- What does that mean?
Do you see the two plates in front of you?
We're going to spill the beans out for you.
- Red beans?
- It could be red beans and others too.
And we're going to give
you a folk song...
And while you sing it nice and long
without taking any breaths...
you have to use your chopsticks to move
20 beans onto the plate.
- Please choose a number.
- Lucky number seven!
[Number seven is corn kernels.]
- You have to move 20 kernels.
- Can I do this in on try?
- Of course, you can.
- I'm very good with chopsticks.
Of course, you can.
[Kkuk also arrives.]
- Ugh... here he comes again.
- What is this?
Okay, here I go.
What are you doing?
[Not being able to grasp onto
any corn kernels.]
I'm not good at things like that.
- I'm not good at things like that.
- This is impossible!
I've been crazing sweet red beans...
What is this now?
Please make your selection.
[Kkuk's selection is... rice.]
Ah, he has to move the rice?
- You think rice is going to be hard?
- 20 pieces of grain.
- Rice is easy.
- Give it a try.
- I'm telling you, rice is easy.
- Give it a try then.
We can't hear you!
- Wait, there was a break!
- There was a break!
[Kkuk fails.]
- Let go.
- It wasn't a break!
- My voice is just a little hoarse!
- No, it was a break.
Didn't you know that my
voice is hoarse?
You're all here?
- You're here.
- Yes, hello.
- Number two!
- Number two?
[Gary chooses barley.]
Gary and barley...
[They need to beat this mission quickly
in order to become King...]
I need to get it close together...
It's too close together.
It's too close. Excuse me.
[Coach Kkuk separating the two plates.]
20 is too hard.
[Tiny little barley grains...]
I can hear your voice wavering a little.
Here it comes... it's here.
[It seems as though the end is near?]
[But Gary still manages to
move over quite a few!]
[All done!]
[Gary fails...]
This is hard... this is too hard!
I can't believe it ended there!
[Fourth course - Noodle soup restaurant.]
[Just like the others,
they're making their selection here too.]
[Ji Hyo chooses a maple leaf.]
[Kwang Soo's selection is a broccoli?]
How can I blow this all the
way over there?
[Place down your selection here.]
[And blow it over with your breathe,
and get it over the line to succeed.]
Challenge.
[Broccoli dreaming of a contingency plan.]
What is this?
What are we doing here?
[Going to grab Myuk PD by his throat...]
That's not it, but how is that possible?
[Unlike Kwang Soo, who's having a
tough time with his poor selection...]
[Awesome... she chose beans!]
[Hyo Joo getting an opportunity to win!]
- But this isn't working.
- You have to let the plate down.
[If you grab onto the plate,
then the plate leans over to the side.]
If you try to grab it with the plate leaning,
then you can't grab onto the beans.
- The way I see it...
- That's right. Grab it like that.
[The beans definitely look easier.]
[Her start seems
a little short on the breath?]
- There it is...
- It's already here.
[Fail...]
[Hyo Joo loses her chance
with the beans.]
- What a loss...
- Han Hyo Joo...
[The end?]
- The end! End!
- It's already over...
[Fails faster than anyone else.]
- Let's do this quickly!
- Pick number four.
Number four!
[Kkuk's selection is number four.]
[He chooses jujubes.]
I told you, I can see everything.
To all the students watching this,
I really can see everything.
Even his mentality is so hateful.
He's telling all the student viewers
that he can see everything.
I really can see everything.
If you think you can do it, you can do it.
I'm being serious.
- I'm going to finish this.
- Okay, finish it.
[Kkuk with the chance to win with jujubes.]
I guess I'm going to win.
It looks like I'll be the King.
One mistake, and you're finished.
[Jujube head?]
He said jujube head!
[What is a jujube head?]
You heard it, right?
[Mr. Capable's mistake from having
been too over confident.]
All our young viewers,
you saw that, right?
- Trying to be too clever is no good.
- Don't trample on their dreams!
[All our young viewers,
make your own decisions wisely...]
You know the story of
the hare and the turtle, right?
- Don't do it.
- Jujube... jujube head.
[Kkuk ruining his perfect chance at a win.]
- How confident he must've been to say that!
- Jujube head...
Why? He should've said bratty
head instead.
[Giraffe trying to win
the challenge with his broccoli.]
Kwang Soo seems to be getting
smaller in size.
- You really think so?
- I think we're just getting used to his size.
[The broccoli... definitely seems smaller
now than it had before.]
[Earlier... now.]
[Definitely is an herbivore...]
[Anyways, the broccoli is
definitely smaller now.]
No, I think we're just getting
used to the size now.
I wonder if it's because
we're just used to it now?
I feel like I look smaller now too.
[Even Kwang Soo's starts to seem smaller
after getting used to him for a while?]
I thought he was over 2 meters at first.
But you're not, are you?
Challenge!
[No way...]
[He really succeeded...]
[I did it!]
[Giraffe having succeeded at
the broccoli blowing!]
I'd be crying too.
Go ahead and cry.
Cry as much as you want.
[Tears of joy from being
the first one to succeed.]
[Tiger mixing up the seeds.]
Look at him right now!
He's being a brat, up to no good.
Number two.
[What is it?]
- I can't believe she picked it!
- Jujube?
Be careful not to say jujube head.
Mugwort head...
- She's not very good with chopsticks.
- She's already too late.
[Her chopstick movements are too slow?]
I guess someone else just got here.
[Her movements are getting
a little quicker?]
- I can hear it. It's here.
- There it is. Hyo Joo...
- This is the toughest part...
- Hyo Joo...
Even though you think you may do it...
[Will she succeed?]
There it is... there it is.
[Oh no! One fell off the plate!]
[Hyo Joo failing at the last
crucial moment!]
- Wait! Wait!
- Hyo Joo, wow!
You really are a fool!
- Why did you do that?
- Wait a minute...
Two, four, six, eight, ten.
[What? Hyo Joo had moved 21 pieces!]
- She did...
- Success!
[The goal was 20 and even though she dropped
one, she succeeds from having moved 21.]
[Kwang Soo having earned the right to
finish off the word, 'King'.]
[Am I King?]
I finished first for the first time.
[Kwang Soo also heads off
to the final location.]
I won't forgive anyone
who tries to get in my way.
Because today... is D-day.
[Have to be the first one to arrive at the
final location to become the ultimate king!]
[Just which one of the two
will become King?]
[The place where the seat of the king's throne
will be given to the winner, 'J' University!]
[Just who is the first one to arrive?]
[Giraffe! It's the Giraffe!]
What happened? Do I just go in?
[Is Kwang Soo the first one
to have arrived?]
[Thanks to the cooperation of the school,
we were able to film the show safely.]
- Am I first?
- You are...
[You are... King.]
[Hyo Joo having lost her chance at
being King by a split second.]
Why is he King? How can that be?
- How can that be! No way!
- I got here first!
Kwang Soo was the first one to arrive.
I don't like this.
What are you doing?
[Then what is the mission given out to
the commoners outside of the King?]
You, who was not crowned
King is a commoner.
Even if the King gets his name tag
ripped off, he is not ousted.
Avoid the King who's trying to oust the King,
and find the ballot to cast your vote.
And according to the vote, the
King can be changed out to someone else.
[The person who receives more than half
the votes will become the new King!]
[I could've been the first King...]
[King Kwang Soo is to move to
the King's throne.]
[The first Running King is Lee Kwang Soo.]
- The King cannot be ousted.
- The King is untouchable.
Avoid the King who's trying to oust the King,
and find the ballot to cast your vote.
The person who receives more than half
the votes will become the new King!
Then we can keep switching out the King?
So the last person left remaining alive
will become the final and ultimate King.
[Battle of the Kings... Start!]
[The throne and the robe...]
- Is that a real throne?
- Your Majesty, please come this way.
[Eunuch Dong Wan]
Please change into your royal gown.
- I have to change too?
- Your royal gown.
This really is like being the King!
Okay. Then I shall change into
the royal gown.
I'm the King of Joseon!
[The intimidating stare...]
[The birth of the Running King...]
[His name is... Kwang Soo...]
All those that tried to undermine me,
and tried to plot against me...
All my enemies that have tried to
rid me of my name tag...
Those who are vying for my seat on the
throne by voting against me...
I will make sure to catch you one by one.
And I will... pull you out by the roots.
I am...
Kwang!
Kim Jong Kook...
You're dead.
Can't we just get started right now?
I can't endure this any longer.
I can't wait!
[Will he be able to take down
his enemies?]
[King Giraffe finally steps
outside the palace!]
You scoundrels...
You dare vie the King's throne!
You won't be forgiven!
Kwang Soo... it's Kwang Soo!
[King Giraffe Kwang Soo
frightening the villagers.]
Seriously... Lee Kwang Soo is the King?
[Commoners getting flustered over
the presence of the King.]
Hey! Lee Kwang Soo!
I will follow you to the depths of hell!
Kwang Soo... it's Kwang Soo!
Where?
Where is he?
Kim Jong Kook, come out here!
[Within moments, King Giraffe Kwang Soo
has become an object of terror.]
- This is really hurting my pride.
- Seriously.
[A stab at their pride to be
chased around by the Giraffe.]
[Is he gone?]
[Two commoners frightened
over the King's tyranny.]
Kwang Soo's gone crazy
and is causing chaos right now.
He's a total tyrant!
- You go keep watch over there.
- You're going to the other side then?
I'll start searching over here.
Think, Hyo Joo.
There's no way that it would be tucked
inside one of these countless number of books.
How am I going to check through them all?
That would make no sense.
But maybe I should still check.
Welcome to Running Man...
[Even the Go-rtle is leisurely
searching for the ballots...]
[Where are the ballots...]
[Could that be?]
[It is! He discovered a ballot!]
[Oh... the leisurely Go-rtle is
the first to discover one!]
[Right around the same time,
Big-nosed Brother discovers one too!]
The voting booth was around
that way somewhere!
- I found one!
- Suk Jin, you found a ballot?
- Jae Suk, this is what it looks like.
- Where did you find it?
Suk Jin, hurry up and vote.
Go and vote for yourself.
Hurry up and vote. Go do it.
- Jae Suk, did you tell Suk Jin to do it?
- Suk Jin needs to become King for now.
I'm going to vote for myself.
- Hyo Joo...
- Yes?
Is Kwang Soo up there?
You found one?
Hurry up and vote for Suk Jin.
- That way...
- But why are we voting for Suk Jin?
We have to have the weakest person be
the King so that it puts us more at ease.
[Putting the weakest person on the
throne will make it easy for the rest of us!]
And as soon as the vote comes out,
we'll get rid of Kwang Soo first!
- That's the way to do it, Hyo Joo.
- Jae Suk, then I'm going to vote for Suk Jin.
Yeah. Go vote for Suk Jin.
- Where's Gary?
- There's Kwang Soo.
King? Is he the King?
He can't be, right?
[If he can somehow catch those two,
that would be a great feat!]
- He's King...
- No way he could be the King.
[Approaching without even greeting anyone...
and changing his direction...]
[His first target is to attack Mr. Capable!]
Let go of me!
I have to do this!
- Okay... just let go of my arms.
- I don't want to! No...
[Even though he's become the King,
he's still as powerless as ever...]
Your Majesty... it's time
for you to return to the palace.
[Hwan Goong -
Means, return to the palace.]
Ah, he has to go back to the palace?
It's time for you to take care of
your affairs at the palace.
There is such a thing?
[Rule: The king has to return to the palace
every 10 minutes to take care of affairs.]
[Tsk tsk... already down to no energy?]
[Just what kind of affairs does he
have to take care of at the palace?]
What are my affairs that need
my attention?
[He needs to take care of his affairs for
him to go back out to the chase!]
I don't have any time.
[Huh? Paper and the seal?]
What is it?
Your Majesty... you have to seal
each of those documents...
to take care of our governmental affairs.
Get out of here! I don't want to see you!
- Your Majesty, you have to stamp it correctly.
- Do you want to be punched correctly?
I thought that you were...
I thought you were here to help me.
[No matter how many time he stamps it,
the pile of paper seems to be never-ending.]
I don't have any time.
Why are these papers so thin?
[Did you think that being
a King would be easy?]
How many sheets are there?
[During the time that the King is
taking care of his affairs...]
[The commoners are finally
starting to cast their votes.]
Suk Jin...
[Go Soo casts his vote for Suk Jin,
making it a total of two for Suk Jin.]
[On the other hand, Gary also steps in
to the voting booth after finding a ballot.]
[Suk Jin now has three votes. He only
needs one more to be the new King!]
There are two more here.
I'm finished!
- Your Majesty, it's time for inspection.
- Yes...
[King Giraffe Kwang Soo
heading off again?]
I think there may be something here...
[A huge white box...
could someone be in there?]
[Big-nosed Brother waiting in hiding
until he's crowned the new King.]
- Why are you in there?
- Hey...
[King Giraffe Kwang Soo having
witnessed the whole thing!]
[I'm in big trouble...]
[Big-nose's life hanging on the balance.]
- There's not much time.
- Wait, Kwang Soo, wait...
- Wait...
- There's no other choice!
[The affection between the
Easy Brothers comes and goes...]
- Let me be the King just once!
- You can't!
This isn't right!
Suk Jin... you and I can be together
again next week!
What did you just say right now? Hey!
Let's do it next week!
I have to do this!
- Lee Kwang Soo...
- Suk Jin... Pil-chok-cross!
Do you want to die?
[Ji Suk Jin, out!
Ji Suk Jin, out!]
[The votes that you've cast so far are
no longer is valid.]
[With Suk Jin being ousted,
the three votes casted are moot!]
Those votes are no longer valid?
[Has to start all over from the beginning
by finding the ballots again...]
I shouldn't have voted for Suk Jin...
[King Giraffe riding the high from the kill
to keep up with his hunting!]
Yes, come on in.
[But he surprises them with trying to
attack from behind!]
[King Giraffe can be quite terrifying!]
- Why is he so strong?
- Look at how aggressive he's being!
Ji Hyo, sorry.
Why don't you go over there?
[King Giraffe lightly letting go of Ji Hyo...]
[Then changes his target and
grabs Haroro!]
You evil King!
[King Giraffe putting in every bit of
his effort into the attack!]
I've fulfilled my purpose.
You coward...
[Ha Ha, out!]
[Needs to hurry and pick a new King...]
The ballots are white and folded in half.
It could be stuck in a book.
[Jae Suk finally discovers a ballot!]
You found one?
I don't know who to vote for though.
[Who should they vote to be King now?]
- Want to be King?
- Me?
- Why don't you be King? Gary...
- Wait...
Why don't you be King Dog?
[King... Dog?]
- I'm going to vote for you.
- Really?
Thanks, Jae Suk... I'll be a good King.
Of course, I'm sure you will.
[Jae Suk heading off to the voting booth
to cast his ballot for Gary.]
Hyo Joo?
Hyo Joo!
[Jae Suk casts his vote for
Hyo Joo to be the new King.]
Hyo Joo.
[Yoo-ruce Willis suggesting they pick
Hyo Joo to be the new King.]
In that case...
- Let's make Hyo Joo the King...
- Yeah...
and oust a few people ourselves
that needs to be ousted.
- That's right! That's good thinking!
- And we can do another voting later.
- We can go about it that way.
- That's a good plan.
Where is it?
Did you find something? Where?
[A ballot...]
- I found it! Look!
- You found it?
[Gary discovers a ballot!]
[Gary hands off his ballot to Hyo Joo
and encourages her to vote for herself.]
There's a voting booth over there...
hurry up before you're caught.
What should I do once I become King?
[Hyo Joo casts a vote for herself.]
[Will she be able to become the
second King for Running Man kingdom?]
[King Giraffe taking care of
his affairs once again.]
- Eunuch Go...
- Yes?
- Get me some water.
- Yes, Your Highness.
Don't take the time out to answer,
and just get it to me!
I'm done!
- Your Highness, it's time for you to...
- Be quiet!
I'm the King of Joseon!
- Kwang Soo's coming!
- Where?
Come here, come here.
[Kwang Soo's closing in where
everyone's gathered around standing.]
- Hurry...
- I think he's gone crazy.
[King Giraffe getting crazier
with each passing moment.]
- How much time do you think you have left?
- I just need one of you!
- You don't have much time left now.
- Think carefully!
Hyo Joo... hurry up and find a ballot.
You're really tired too, aren't you?
Move out of the way.
I have no intentions to get you...
and I'm not even seeing clearly right now,
so just get out of the way!
We have to stop you.
We have no other choice.
Kwang Soo...
what's it like being the king?
Don't become King... it's hell.
How is this being the King?
It's okay. We have to stop him.
We have to stop him any way we can.
Everything is a battle right now...
[Where's King Giraffe heading to
all of a sudden?]
[The goal he's been eyeing is...
Han Hyo Joo!]
Hyo Joo... run!
[Go Soo succeeds in helping her get away!]
[While the men are busy warding him off,
the women can get busy searching!]
[Ji Hyo discovers a ballot!]
Let me just try it once.
- You can't tear it off. He can't be ousted.
- I just wanted to tear it off once.
[Trying to get him worked up even though
he's fully aware the King can't be ousted.]
[Fine... you're playing with me?]
[Out of six commoners,
Hyo Joo currently has two votes.]
[King Giraffe operates on full power!]
[Ji Hyo's vote... goes to Hyo Joo!]
[Hyo Joo gains half the votes
from the commoners!]
[But it can only be put into effect
once the poll results are announced!]
[Jong Kook in danger!]
[Will the announcement be made first,
or will he be ousted first?]
[Total chaos]
[Cease all activities!]
We have the poll results.
Any surviving commoners,
please cease all activities.
We will be announcing the poll results.
[At last... there will be a new King.]
You can just stay here
until you are sent off to jail.
No... let me formally apologize
to everyone.
We have the poll results.
But I can be the King again.
You think anyone of us would
vote for you?
The next King that Running Man
has voted for is...
Out of six, three of you have chosen...
Han Hyo Joo.
- Grab him!
- Wait!
[Han Hyo Joo voted as the second King
of the Running Man kingdom.]
Then I'm the new King?
Then it means...
I can oust them all now?
Your Majesty... congratulations.
It's a great pleasure to meet you.
I am Eunuch Go.
I see. I'm very glad to see you.
Go on. Attach it to my back.
[Second King of Running Man Kingdom-
Han Hyo Joo.]
Cease on all activities removed.
Time of the new King has arrived.
That feels really good to hear.
Your Majesty, you will have to return to
the palace in 10 minutes
so you have to hurry on with your inspection.
What's there to rush when I'm the King?
[A completely different Hyo Joo
now that she's the King!]
There's nothing to rush around for.
I can take my time with the inspection.
Shall we go to meet the commoners?
[Heading off to find the former King,
commoner Kwang Soo first?]
Everyone will be waiting for me to
oust Kwang Soo first.
- Hyo Joo...
- We have him captured as an offering to you.
- Hyo Joo!
- We worked really hard to capture him.
[The dethroned King's rage.]
- Please send him for us.
- Please take care of him.
- You have to let me go!
- Please take care of him...
[The request to take care of him
by all the commoners.]
- He's caused too much havoc as King.
- I was going to let him off the hook once...
- Let me off the hook just once.
- But you've committed too many sins.
- What wrong have I done?
- You made me eat fermented fish yesterday!
You made me eat fermented
fish yesterday!
[Did you think I'd forget?]
- Try to remember!
- I don't remember that!
[The night before when
they were making kimchi...]
[Kwang Soo having tricked her into eating
super salty fermented fish wrap.]
- You're still holding that grudge?
- I want you to remember!
- You remember what you did!
- You can't forgive him!
Wait! You can't! I'm a King!
I'm a King!
[Ah... what ruin of power...]
You really are a righteous King.
[Lee Kwang Soo, out!
Lee Kwang Soo, out!]
I was a King...
[All the power is given to the King
by the people...]
We will follow the will of our King.
- Just give us the order.
- Who shall we take care of for you?
My King...
[A market target?]
A target tiger in a hunt
needs to be skinned...
[Starting off by eliminating Jong Kook
to make it easier for the ultimate victory?]
- We have to get the tiger of its skin.
- If anything, keep me by your side.
- Why don't you use me as your man instead?
- Oh... that's not a bad idea!
- I can catch them for you...
- Think about this carefully.
How are you planning on taking care of him
when it's just the two of you left?
- Please use me as your man...
- Please look at the size of his thighs.
[They're all making right arguments...]
Use me as your man...
and remain eternal as the Queen.
[Just what will she select?]
You've said something
very interesting just now.
I appoint you as my personal warrior.
- I appoint you as my personal warrior.
- Yes, that's right!
[Jong Kook appointed as the personal warrior
to the second King, Han Hyo Joo.]
Wait, wait...
- Wait, wait...
- Darn it!
When we made you our Queen!
How could you?
Who should we catch, my Queen?
- Gary!
- I will catch Gary for you!
My Queen! I will get him for you!
My Queen!
I don't have to do any work, right?
Since I'm the King...
[Leave the hunting to her warrior,
and the King takes a leisurely stroll.]
[Forgetting the grace of the commoners
for choosing her as their King.]
I have to find the ballots.
Wait... when we're the ones
who made her King...
- But within moments...
- Jong Kook really is something else.
[But the commoners always have
the power of the ballots!]
[Find the ballots and elect a new King!]
Please...
I have a lot of interest in thrillers
and chase movies.
I feel like I'm one of the
characters in those movies.
The thrill of it is no joke.
Warrior!
- Yes, My Queen!
- Warrior!
Where are you?
Who should I catch for you?
[Loyal servant to the Queen.
Commoner Jong Kook promoted to her warrior.]
My ultimate goal during my ruling...
is to eliminate all commoners.
[Ballots, ballots...]
[Warrior Jong Kook attacks Gary!]
Did you find him?
- I have captured him, My Queen.
- Wait...
I will give you one last chance
to say your peace.
Say just one thing.
I love you.
[I... love you?]
I have loved you.
If that's a sin, then be rid of me.
A commoner isn't supposed to
love the Queen.
- My sin is to have loved the Queen.
- Your sin is too great.
[For the sin of loving the Queen... out!]
- You really are a righteous Queen.
- You won't last long.
[Gary, out! Gary, out!]
[The Queen and her warrior rushing
off to their next target!]
[While the number of commoners
are diminishing one by one...]
[Jae Suk discovers a ballot!]
Who should I pick?
[Jae Suk finishes voting
without a long hesitation.]
[Go Soo also heads into the voting booth
after having found a ballot.]
[Go Soo also rushes to cast his vote!]
[Just who did they pick?]
[At the same time...]
I played a Royal Concubine until recently...
And now, I'm the King.
- Your Majesty...
- Yes?
We've received some things that needs
your attention while you've been gone.
If you can thread five of these marbles,
you can go back out to hunt.
Yes, I will thread them quickly
and capture the rest.
In that case...
Oh my, this isn't threading easily.
I hope they don't find any ballots
while I'm gone.
Your Majesty, your subjects are finding
ballots right now, you must hurry.
I'm aware of that.
Don't rush me.
It's making it even harder to thread.
I'm almost done.
[Already finished threading four!]
This is my last marble.
Shall we go back out to hunt?
I need to dress like the commoners
when I'm going outside the palace.
Where is my warrior?
- Go Soo...
- Yes?
Who did you vote for?
- I voted for you.
- You should've voted for Ji Hyo!
[Warrior Jong Kook seems to be
planning on making Jae Suk his offering.]
[Commoner Jae Suk in extreme danger!]
Here... we're here!
[Just then, Ji Hyo discovers a ballot!]
[Just who will she vote for?]
Cease all activities.
The voting is now over.
All surviving commoners cease activities.
Voting results will soon be announced.
No way. That's a lie, right?
There hasn't been a vote, right?
I'm not... no way.
[It seems as though Ji Hyo's vote
was the deciding factor!]
- I was going to vote for Ji Hyo...
- We now have the voting results.
I'm sure it's one of you guys.
The next King that
Running Man has chosen...
The next King is...
With two votes out of four votes...
Yoo Jae Suk!
Me?
[Yoo Jae Suk,
the third King of Running Man Kingdom.]
Me?
[Go Soo and Ji Hyo voted
for Jae Suk!]
Good work.
Go Soo...
[As soon as he becomes the King,
his speech pattern suddenly changes.]
This can't be!
I can't step down from my
throne like this!
This can't be!
- I'm honored.
- Oust them.
I don't want to be a warrior.
You're not a warrior, but a General.
- You're a General.
- I don't want to be a General either.
I want to remain a commoner.
Your Majesty... it is my honor to
serve you. I'm Eunuch Go.
Start off by ousting Jong Kook.
We'll talk again after
you've ousted Kim Jong Kook.
Ban on cease of activity  is lifted.
Ban on cease of activity is lifted.
[Third King of Running Man Kingdom,
Yoo Jae Suk.]
Warrior!
Make sure to stay alive!
[Now that she's returned to being a commoner,
she is off to find the ballots yet again!]
Down. Get down!
[Along with Eunuch Go and his
VJ Gwon Yeol...]
I feel like there would be one
around here somewhere...
[King Grasshopper discovers Hyo Joo!]
[King Grasshopper trying to stop
her from trying to steal back the throne!]
Warrior!
[Even though he is no longer
her warrior...]
Come here.
[So even though he no longer
has to protect her...]
Wait...
It's all over.
Queen...
[In order to protect her...]
- It's all over now.
- Run, My Queen! Run!
- Run!
- Hey...
How could you do this to your King?
I'll go and get back the throne!
- I will buy you some time!
- You're not going to buy anything!
[Escape... far away...]
I got to make kimchi...
Got to split firewood...
And even got to become a King.
I have no regrets.
[Her warrior trying to buy her
time to the end.]
- I will buy you time. Make your escape.
- You're not buying her anything.
Run... run and stay alive.
Hurry up and rip it off.
Warrior...
I will never forget...
your grace and loyalty.
[Jong Kook, out!]
We just ripped the skin off the tiger...
You really were so dashing...
Thank you.
[Thank you...]
[Three commoners left alive are,
Go Soo, Ji Hyo and Hyo Joo.]
[Go Soo and Ji Hyo taking a brief rest.]
- I bet the show really gets you in shape.
- No...
- How long has it been? Seven years?
- It's been seven years since I've seen you.
The movie we did together.
But you haven't changed a single bit.
- I'm still the same? Is it a good thing?
- Even back in the day, you were very...
You were always at ease...
and was often lost in thought...
I was watching you speak yesterday...
And I though to myself,
'He's just like he was seven years ago!'.
I kept thinking that to myself
all day yesterday.
[Whatever...]
[Just the two that voted for me are left...
I'm left with no choice...]
[Ji Hyo discovers King Grasshopper!]
[Leisurely Go-rtle fails at
making his escape.]
- My shoulder is in pain...
- But why are you standing there?
[Who will King Grasshopper oust first?]
- What are you going to do?
- About what?
You're not about to
betray me right now, are you?
[To anyone eyes, it looks as though
he's getting ready to sacrifice Ji Hyo.]
- You two are working together?
- Ji Hyo...
You two are working together?
You think you can oust Hyo Joo?
Think about it carefully.
You may need me more than Go Soo.
Think about this carefully, okay?
- Think about it carefully, Jae Suk.
- But I have no greed for the throne.
Like I said, I don't want the throne,
but I can be of great help to the King.
- You know I played a lot of Princess roles...
- That's true.
- So think about it very carefully, Jae Suk.
- This is getting confusing.
You really have to think carefully.
- Go Soo...
- Yes?
I'll grab onto him.
[It seems as though King Grasshopper
has decided to get rid of Go Soo first.]
- Wait...
- Come here for now.
[Will the naive Go Soo be able to
escape this danger?]
[What humiliation...]
This is all thanks to you...
Ji Hyo... remain alive, okay?
[Go Soo, out!]
[Hyo Joo coming onto the scene
one step too late.]
[Only person she has left to
rely on now is Ji Hyo...]
[Where is everyone?]
Ji Hyo!
[Finally meeting up with Ji Hyo...]
Go Soo and I looked everywhere for you.
Where have you been?
[King Grasshopper slowly
starting his attack.]
What are you doing?
Go! Go away for now!
[The two still working together.]
You're scaring me! You're too fast!
[Going back to the last spot she
and her warrior were together.]
Ji Hyo, let's do it together.
- Ji Hyo, let's...
- Wait.
I want to meet my death at the spot
where my warrior met his fate.
[If that's your wish...]
I will not forget your grace...
- Thanks for everything.
- You're driving me crazy.
[Queen who's already given up hope.]
I want to remind you that it was us and Gary
who put you on that throne in the first place!
- Seriously...
- I will not forget your grace.
Just go.
[Even Hyo Joo who rallied to the end
is ultimately ousted!]
[And the final two left remaining...]
I will consider your faith and loyalty
that's served me until now...
- and I will give you 20 seconds head start.
- Okay, give me just 20 seconds.
- I cannot allow you any more time than that.
- I understand.
Keep that in mind and...
and don't consider me too cruel.
I am honored.
- Go on.
- I'm honored.
Song Ji Hyo's not an easy opponent...
No way... how many seconds
has it been?
No way...
No way!
[Just one possibility that King Grasshopper
hadn't thought of!]
No way!
No way could she have had
a ballot on her!
No way!
[Could she really be inside the
voting booth?]
- You scoundrel!
- I'm writing!
I'm writing!
You can't touch me while I'm voting!
[Rule: Not allowed to touch anyone
while the person is in the voting booth.]
[How can this be?]
[In truth, way in the beginning,
Blank Ji discovered a ballot.]
[Just in case,
she kept the ballot hidden until now!]
- Why you traitor...
- You can't touch me right now!
Song Ji Hyo had a ballot!
You deceitful traitor!
How could you have deceived me?
You can't see who I voted for!
Okay, a secret vote...
- I will let you cast your vote in secret.
- However, your time on the throne is over.
- I knew I couldn't trust you!
- How dare you set foot in here?
I will not let you get away
with this, Song Ji Hyo!
You only have a minute left
until you have to get back to work.
Be quiet, Go Dong Wan!
What have you been all this time
to just appear now?
When my reign is about end here and now,
you dare say to me...
[King Grasshopper at a loss of words...]
I've been completely fooled.
I've been fooled, I've been fooled,
Song Ji Hyo...
You deceitful Song Ji Hyo...
[Having no other choice but to go
and see to the affairs as a King...]
Your Majesty, have a safe trip back!
Looked at how well I stamped it!
[Ji Hyo completes voting for herself!]
Cease all activities.
The voting poll is now closed.
The next King that Running Man
kingdom has chosen is...
Song Ji Hyo.
[The fourth King for Running Man
Kingdom is Song Ji Hyo.]
[Back to being the commoner Grasshopper,
Jae Suk heads back outside in common clothes.]
The King is here...
Must you do this?
Do you know how you got to
your throne?
I... got to my throne by my vote.
You think that you'll be able to sleep
with a clear conscience tonight?
I think I'll be able to
sleep very well tonight.
[Cleanly and concisely...]
Let's go.
Traitor of all traitors... Blank Ji!
[The ultimate winner of
Battle of the Kings, Song Ji Hyo!]
[Go Soo seems to have something
that he wants to say.]
I had such a great time, and I really enjoyed
getting to meet everyone through the show.
I'm so glad I got to say hello to the viewers
through the show and I had a great time.
- Come back to the show again sometime.
- We're so glad that you came.
- And you guys really don't have any scripts!
- No, we don't use them.
- I was so surprised.
- That's nothing to be surprised about.
Me too!
[Hyo Joo seems to have something
she'd like to say as well.]
I also had a great time
and am really grateful.
And I was really surprised to see you
doing the show without any written scripts.
It really was impressive.
It's beautiful!
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Angelic Christmas gifts that's come
to find them at a beautiful ski lodge.]
Merry Christmas!
- Just keep quiet until you leave.
- How rude!
[Five Santa's have arrived
bearing gifts of laughter!]
[Extreme Santa, Screaming Santa!
All together join in on a Christmas race!]
[Christmas Santa's that will never let go
of an opportunity at a feast!]
[Training camp that takes place
on top of a snowy mountain!]
[A satisfying Christmas gift
that fills your belly with laughter!]
[Five Santa's]