[The wildest challengers of
Running Man's history has returned!]
[Average age 23.7 years old]
[Nation's 7 Idol Representatives]
[Average age 34.7 years old]
[Running Man, beat the wild challengers!]
[Strong rascals are headed your way!
Be ready!!]
[7 against 7.
Running Man vs. Idol-Start!]
[A week early-Olympics.
Running Olympics 2012]
Hello to all the viewers in the nations,
and to the overseas viewers.
It's very nice to be here.
Hello everyone.  It's nice to meet all you
Running Man local viewers.
And viewers from other countries.
My name is Jung Jae Hyung who will
be MC'ing the Olympic opening ceremony.
Hello everyone. I am Jung Jae Hyung.
Music Fairy, and host for the Running Man Olympics.
[What is this?]
(Trying to read French)
[Continuing on in French]
[Going on without faltering his steps]
[Tri-lingual Running Man MC-Jung Jae Hyung]
For our first team,
Running Man are entering the arena!
As we speak, Team Running Man
is now entering the arena.
[French] As we speak, Team Running Man
[Entrance of the athletes]
[Running Man's enthusiastic entrance]
[Running Man Team-
Yoo Jae Suk, Ji Suk Jin, Kim Jong Kook...]
[...Gary, Ha Ha, Song Ji Hyo, Lee Kwang Soo]
What is he doing here?  He's a pain...
Kim Jong Kook, Gary, Ha Ha and Song Ji Hyo
are all entering with a bright smile...
[Unyielding progress]
What is this race all about?
Jae Suk Yoo, Suk Jin Ji, Jong Kook Kim,
Gary, Ha Ha... Where's Ha Ha?
Oh, I just didn't see you
because you're so short.
Stop it!!
Why did you come here! Why?!
If the PD in charge orders him to do it,
he does it to the end...
If he's told to just look that way,
then that's what he does!
Giraffe, will you go out and enter again?
Who?
[MC requesting giraffe to re-enter alone]
Jae Hyung, go home!  Go home!!
Why do you keep bringing out the piano
whenever Jae Hyung is on here?
-Is the piano a part of the set or something?
-I think he brings it himself.
[Live performance of Kwang Soo's theme song]
-That's cool!
-Jae Hyung's piano performance is cool!
Jae Hyung, that's so cool!
[Sting's 'St. Agnes and the burning train']
I didn't know that this song
was such a sad song like this!
Let's use Jae Hyung to play
our background music from now on!
[Put him in charge of all the
background music to be played?]
-He can play it live...
-I was so ashamed the last time I was on...
-Okay.
-Why?
I still can't manage to
forget losing to Kwang Soo...
Since I have experience on Running Man now...
Now I'd like to get past the giraffe,
and Jong Kook...
Before you attempt Jong Kook,
why not go through me first?
There's a huge difference there.
-Now for the Idol representatives...
-There's an Idol representative?
Over there... There's something over there.
-What's that?
-Idol?  Who?
-Look at that double decker bus... Over there.
-Oh, is that it?
[In commemoration of the Olympics-
London's double decker bus]
-That's a double decker bus!
-It is!
All though Asia, America, Europe,
and throughout the world...
Creating the Hallyu wave all over the world
as Idol representatives of Korea...
It's the Idol team consisting of 6 males
and 1 female.
[Same member composition
as the Running Man team!]
[Unyielding MC, Jae Hyung]
-Who is it?
-6 guys...?
[First representative athlete]
[Super Junior's Eun Hyuk]
It's Eun Hyuk!
-It's Eun Hyuk!
-Man... He is really good!
-Eun Hyuk is such a good athlete!
-He is really good...!
Eun Hyuk is so good at all this...!
[The feeling of unease settles in
starting with the first member]
The next athlete to enter...
Is Nichkhun of 2PM
[Second athlete-Nichkhun of 2PM]
-It's Nichkhun!
-Oh my goodness...!
-He's a really good athlete too!
-We're in big trouble!
He is a foreign element,
which isn't found on the Running Man team.
[Extremely worried]
This is unfair to us!
-Are they all seriously going to be athletes?
-Nichkhun!
And following behind him is
Jung Yong Hwa of CN Blue.
[CN Blue's Jung Yong Hwa]
-It's Yong Hwa!
-Yong Hwa?!  This is crazy!
[Already forecasting their defeat]
Even though he's been on Running Man the most,
he unfortunately has never been able to win.
However as the only guest today to have
torn off Kim Jong Kook's name tag
the anticipation for the game is high.
And here's Lee Joon,
following out without an introduction.
We lost, we lost...
But still... Even though he's on the Idol team,
Lee Joon. I don't think it will be too bad.
[Easy?  MBlaq's Lee Joon]
Seriously!!  We got it!!
-We got it!
-Hey! Your hat...!
And next... It's Yoon Doo Joon from Beast
who comes from a soccer background!
No way!!
I mean, how are we supposed to compete
against these guys?!
Doo Joon is too good at sports...!!
At his level,
he could be a national athlete...
This is really too much!
We now see our next athlete entering!
And he is... Im Si Wan of ZE:A!
-Him?
-They picked all the best athletes...!
[The power of the Idol team with
not a single easy opponent]
And at last, for the female athlete,
it's Eun Jung of T-Ara!
-It's Eun Jung!
-Hello!
-Hey you had something with Ha Ha before?!
-Yes!  Hello!
-How have you been?
[Immediately going into French mode]
Jae Hyung, what are you doing?
They asked me to do all this,
as if this was the official broadcast.
And this completes both teams' entrance.
Following the tradition of opening ceremony...
There will be the lighting of the flame.
[The passing of the torch]
It's Dong Wan.
[The honor of passing the torch goes to...
Greece's God of Disguise, Dong Wan PD]
Hey, he's coming from over there.
Let's blow out his torch.
Run quickly.
Dong Wan, who's going to do it?
[Shooting the flaming arrow
directly to light the fire?]
Dong Wan, be careful!
-Is he for real?
-He couldn't possibly...!
You have to be careful!
[A prearranged play...]
[Extinguishing it out immediately]
What are you doing?
What are you doing right now?
What do you think you're doing right now?!
[The lighting ceremony is now complete]
How funny!
[Running Man Olympics'
grand opening is now over!]
We hope that all the viewers will stay with us
to the completion of our Olympics.
And this has been... Jung Jae Hyung.
It's all over now!
This has been Jung Jae Hyung.
Merci beaucoup!
-Good job...
-Jae Hyung, get out of here.
[MC Jae Hyung takes his leave
with a shy farewell greeting]
-Why aren't you shaking Idol's hands?
-Because I feel awkward.
Kim Jong Kook!  You just wait!!
I'll call you.
So... What are we doing today?
As you can see...
The team will compete against one another...
But we can't realistically
compete against them...
To the members of the ultimate winning team,
the prize is a real gold medal for everyone.
[All the members of the winning team
to receive a real gold medal]
[All the Idol members' eyes shooting open
at the news of a real gold medal]
You have to succeed 3 missions...
And from there you will have to go
to your final mission destination.
In order to have the most advantages
at your final destination
it's important to win the most
of the 3 missions leading up to it.
In which case, you will be able to start
your final mission with an upper hand.
-Is that right?
-We just need to win it all, right?
We'll do that.  We'll just win them all.
Why are you saying
such a scary thing like that?
-I'm sorry, but...
-You make a scary comment like that so easily.
A comment about winning it all...
If you look over there,
you'll see the Olympic double decker bus...
The first level has a roof,
but the second level doesn't have one.
Which team will ride on which level will be
decided by playing Rock-paper-scissors.
[A rock-paper-scissors showdown!]
It'll be a single game with the captains
from the each teams.
[A single competition with the
captains from the each teams]
[Idol team's captain is Eun Hyuk,
born in 1986]
-Who should be the captain?
-You do it, Jae Suk.
-I can't do things like this...
-Suk Jin, have Suk Jin do it.
[Running Man team captain is Big-Nosed brother,
born in 1966]
[Self-assertive Big-Nosed brother]
It's a single game... Just one game.
[Will it be a fight against the blazing sun,
or saving their energy on the first level?]
I'm going to throw out a rock.
A man always goes with the fist.
-I'm throwing out the rock.
-Rock-paper-scissors!
[Big-Nosed brother, born in 1966 wins!]
[Overpowering from the get go!
The danger from the start of the race.]
-It's okay, it's okay.
-It's okay.  We're young.
We'll take the first level!  First level!!
[Even though Running Man
has the current advantage...]
[...Will they have the final victory
over the fierce Idol Group?]
[2012 Running Man Olympics-Start!]
[A nice and cool first level
with air conditioning!]
[Envious]
We'll be up on the second level then.
Si Wan, I'm sorry!
Yong Hwa... Oh my stomach!
-Hey Nichkhun...
-We're all one team!
-You go on up there.
-We'll see you later.
Nichkhun has become a lot more relaxed...
[Hot...!]
[Sun roasted seats]
[Still giving them a bright farewell]
Bye everyone!
Since some people feel awkward here...
Let's find out how old everyone is.
-'88.
-Si Wan is '88.
'88... '88... '88...
[Si Wan, Nichkhun, Eun Jung, Lee Joon all '88]
Yong Hwa and Doo Joon is '89.
They're the kiddos.
-I'm the youngest, sir.
-Yong Hwa, you're one of the youngest?
-Is Doo Joon the youngest?
-He's the youngest.
That really seems so unlikely...
-Doesn't he not seem like it?
-I even got a perm to look younger!
-Don't I look much younger?
-And I'm '86.
[And the team captain is a mere '86]
Our experienced veteran.
I'm not a veteran...
-So the oldest is the one born in '86?
-Yes.
Suk Jin was born in '66.
[Today's competition
which transcends 20 years]
-If he was born during the war...
-My mom was born in '61.
-Going up against Suk Jin...
-Why are you revealing your mom's age?
What?  She's my mom!
Why are you reacting about my mom?
[I guess...]
I'm the one revealing my mom's age...!
-You two are funny.
-You're funny!
[The duo displaying an unusual sense of humor]
Instead of rock-paper-scissors,
it should've been mook-jji-ppa.
You know that Lee Joon kept telling me
what to throw out for that, right?
-i just... I just wanted us all to do well...
-You're a spy, aren't you?!
-How am I the spy?!
-Spy!!
-They have spies on Running Man!
-I don't have what it takes to be a spy.
I'm not someone that could be a spy,
you rascal!
-There's no spy on here today.
-There's no spy!
I think we're here.
-There it is... Running Man...
-I see the Running Man flag.
[Discovered the Running Man flag]
Shouldn't we get off the bus quickly?
Let's get off the bus!
-Yes, sir!
-Let's all get off!
I'm sure it's really hot up there!
[The heat that can be felt
as soon as they're off the bus]
-Are you guys hot?
-Yes, it's really hot.
[A world of difference from the second level.
A cool and refreshing first level interior]
-We have to win no matter what.
-Yeah, we have to win.
We're going to start the race right away.
The first team to get to the destination
will gain the advantage.
-Where?!  Where is it?!
-I knew this was going to happen!
My shoe!  My shoe's about to fall off!
[Idol team's overwhelming start]
How can you run off so quickly like that?
[The first team to cross by sticking the name
onto the person in front of you
...instead of passing the baton wins]
We guessed it right!
You have to stick the name tag
onto the person in front of you.
[And this team is already looking defeated]
In front of you is the entry to the race,
and the race is over there.
[A special natural race course
that's been prepared on the Island]
You'll start at the R1 flag,
and go on to R2 flag
Then you'll pass through R3, R4, R5, R6,
then make it down to R7...
And lastly, the final runners will have to
loop around and come out the finish line.
[Idol team that was the first to arrive
has the inner ring]
-I'm getting nervous for no reason...
-This is our first game.
[The last R7 is
Jae Suk vs. Eun Hyuk]
You have to be careful because
the corner is very sharp.
What's worse than that is my situation.
Being in this situation
is worse than that corner.
Does this situation itself of going up
against the Idols even make any sense?
I have an overwhelming need to win this.
It's not just about winning...
But an overwhelming urge to win...?
-But with you Idols...
-But aren't you guys pretty fast too?
Jong Kook and Gary seem very fast...
Even if they're fast,
they're fast amongst ourselves.
We're just fast amongst ourselves.
[I guess...
They do like to fight amongst themselves a lot]
What we talked about was that
even though that's what you all say...
You may be hiding your talents to yourselves,
so we're all going to work very hard.
It's good to think that way
so that you don't get cocky.
However... Just wait and see.
Just wait and see how things turn out.
What will happen with Suk Jin?
I'm most curious about that...
He's up against Doo Joon of all people?
He really has rotten luck.
How can he be matched with Doo Joon?
They should've had me up against Eun Jung...
It's iffy enough having to go up
against Eun Jung...
-You won't make me look too bad, will you?
-Why would I do that?
-We're like a family!
-Of course...!
You know what I'm saying, right?
Don't embarrass me too much.
I'm actually pretty good
at running on this show.
Really?
This is quite the distance...
Nichkhun and Ha Ha...
[The more they think about it,
the more they're worried...]
[Will Running Man be able to do well?]
[Everyone ready at their station.
Ready to start the race!]
[On the foot too?]
Ready!
[A single game with no concession]
[Will it be the experienced Running Man...
Or ambitious Idol Team?]
Ready!
[Race-Start!]
-They're off!
-This is crazy!
Oh!  The pigeons are flying over there!
They're notifying us of the race starting!
[Race-start!]
[Idol's overwhelming speed]
[With the mike dangling around the neck]
[Touching off on the 2nd runner!]
[Flower boy Si Wan vs. Mr. Capable Jong Kook]
-Jong Kook!  Nice Jong Kook!
-He's so fast!
[Mr. Capable Jong Kook]
[With his fiery hair flying]
[Mr. Capable catching up
with the speed of lightning]
[He passed Si Wan!]
-Jong Kook is super-fast!
-He's caught up to him!
-He's passing him!
-He's passing him.
[Mr. Capable overcoming the gap from
the first runner and surpassing]
[Name tag baton touched onto the 3rd runner]
No!!
Gather up your strength!
[Gary running with his gritted teeth
to use the gap to his advantage]
[But... Stop grimacing...?]
Lee Joon really isn't very fast.
[With Gary's advancement,
the gap remains advantageous]
Gather up your strength!!
-Hurry!
-Hurry!  Quickly!!
[R4.  Eun Jung vs. Ji Hyo]
[Name tag baton hand off]
I'm getting so nervous since I can't see them.
[Curious about the next runners]
[Ace Ji Hyo's sprint]
We're winning?  We're winning?!
Are we winning?
Ji Hyo!
[Ji Hyo's fighting spirit in the race]
Running Man is currently winning!
Seriously?  No way!
[The surprisingly ever widening gap]
[Big-Nosed brother's baton touch off]
[3 runners remaining.
A serious gap for the Idol team]
[Doo Joon taking off like a rocket]
[The one jogging...]
Suk Jin, hurry!
[The one sprinting]
[Huh?]
Why is he so slow?  Hurry!
[The gap that is no longer]
[Kwang Soo vs. Yong Hwa]
Yong Hwa!  What happened to your promise?!
[What?  Overtaking...?!]
Yong Hwa!  Hey!
Kwang Soo.  Kwang Soo!
Kwang Soo!!
[Doo Joon and Yong Hwa
flipping the race around]
[Curious- What's going on?]
Kwang Soo!
-Kwang Soo!
-Hurry!
[Several meters in difference]
[Now the win is hanging on the last runners]
Yoo Jae Suk, fighting!]
[Good job!]
[Mere 0.5 seconds?
Touching off the baton within split seconds]
[Veteran Yoo-ruce Willis vs.
Ambitious Eun Hyuk]
[The race between these two
determines the winner]
What to do...?  I'm so worried.
For that last leg...
Eun Hyuk is way too fast.
[But Yoo-ruce Willis is doing
a decent job of following behind]
-Be careful.
-Jae Suk!
[The sharp corner of the course]
Jae Suk, fighting!
Don't give up!
[Eun Hyuk gaining more distance
since rounding the corner]
[Ah... The ever widening gap...]
[The winner seems pretty much decided...]
There's a big gap there.
It's Kwang Soo.
It's his fault.
Eun Hyuk, wait!
Hey, what's your blood type?
[Even able to tell him his blood type
as he races by...]
[Idol team wins!]
Idol Team!  Idol Team...!
Good job.
[Congratulating each other
on their best efforts]
It's a really long distance!
Wow... That was really far.
-If we had done a little better...
-You guys still did a great job.
[Idol Team relishing on their dramatic win]
Jae Suk, it's the same as winning for us.
What do you mean, win?
We just lost!
[Tiger, who lit a fire into his sprint]
-We almost lost this race...
-I've never run so hard on Running Man before.
There he is!
[Why is she headed this way in anger?]
Myuk PD!
-You!
-What?!
The person watching the show
told me that I weighed 53 kg!
-What are you going to do about it?!
-Ji Hyo... Ji Hyo...
[Ji Hyo's weight was #1 searched topic
after the broadcast of last week's show]
-Ji Hyo... We lost.
-Lost or whatever, I'm ruined, Jae Suk!
That man over there said...
That I weighed 53 kg...!
-Ji Hyo, you're not...
-Ji Hyo...
-You can just lose the weight.
-Myuk PD!
[For a while, no measuring of anyone's weight...]
Until we get to the next destination,
Idol team will ride on the first level.
-It's really nice in here!
-It's cooling off all my sweat!
The game got flipped around way too easily.
When you hear the back being slapped,
you should've blocked him.
Then the person that's coming
would have lost their tempo.
You seem very angry at Kwang Soo.
How could we have even thought about
getting in their way like that?
He could've blocked him!
It's all about the skills!
If he did, no matter how fast they are,
they wouldn't have been able to win like that.
I don't mind that we lost...
But I really don't think that we can
play sports with Jong Kook.
-Why?
-You scold too much!
How can you scold more than my dad does?
If it seems like they're going to the right,
then you go to the right.
[Endless coaching from Coach Kook]
Then they lose their timing.
What would happen if someone blocked
the way that you were going to go?
Then you won't be able to
keep running through like that.
[Everyone not being scolded hurries
to Coach Kook's side]
Even though this may sound like an excuse,
Eun Hyuk is just so fast...
All of them are fast!
Not one of them isn't fast!
It was just too burdensome,
and the corner was so scary...
What's so scary?
You don't think that he was scared by it?
You don't think that Jong Kook
is scary then?
Let's all just do a fighting once.
Everyone gather around.
-We'll just win the next one.
-Jong Kook... We can just win the next one.
If you're in a bad mood,
we all have to be in a bad mood.
And if you want to do a fighting,
then we all have to do it.
Let's win the next one.
Over or under?
Let's just do it under.
1, 2, 3, fighting!
Can't we at least pick if we want to
do it under or over?
He really should just go to London.
-What do you think the next game is?
-Oh! It's so nice in here!
[Defeated Running Man Team
moving up to the second level]
Good job.
It's time now to be with the Idols...
[Getting caught by Coach Kook]
But what I just realized today is that...
Running Man team shouldn't be taken easily.
No, they're not easy.
They just say that they're not good...
Of course, they're good.
How many years have they
been doing Running Man for now?
Since they've been doing it for several years,
of course they're good...
Even though we don't know
what the next game is...
[Without a doubt,
it's Coach Kook's coaching hour]
-We should all help each other...
-I'll be able to survive if you weren't here!
-If you weren't here, I can survive this!
I'm so mentally stressed out
that I don't think I can survive this!
This isn't the time for me
to live in fear of you!
If you weren't here, I can survive this!
-Yeah!  You tell him!
-You guys are older than him!
I don't think I can...!
-Hey!  You tell him!
-I feel so much better now!
[Even though he may feel better after
going off on Coach Kook...]
Jong Kook, I'm sorry.
[An immediate apology]
-What do you have to be sorry about?
-It was just a joke.
-Since we're taping a show...
-You were way too harsh.
[Feeling anxious after having stirred up
the tiger's anger]
-Jong Kook...
-Everyone stretch out your legs and shake them.
[In that case, resuming the lesson right away]
Why do we always listen to him?
It's so strange.
If there was no exercise in this world,
what would he ever have done?
[The ever untiring Coach Kook...]
-That is this?
-What is it?  Volleyball?
[The place they've arrived after
traveling for a while is...?]
-Is this it?
-I think it's volleyball or something like it.
-There's a mat too.
-What the heck is this now?
I think that's the mat
that they use for tumbling.
[The gathering of a crowd
after hearing the arrival of Running Man]
Volleyball!
[An overwhelming welcome from the crowd
at the appearance of the Idol Team]
We're not going to lose this time!
We won't lose this time.
-We're going to win this time.
-We can win this.
We're not going to lose even once.
Get your head on straight,
and accept it already!
[Trampoline volleyball.
First team to score 15 points wins!]
[Idol team first gathering for
a "Fighting" for the win]
1, 2, 3... Fighting!
[Running Man team shouting 'Fighting"
so that they're not scolded by Coach Kook]
[With the massive trampoline,
childhood memories of playing comes back...]
[...Huh?]
[Idol with a major in ballet...
Lee Joon's massive flexibility]
[His own personal stage?]
[Flower boy Si Wan also
showing off with his backflip]
[Idol Team displaying their
stunning skills to everyone]
Im Si Wan!  Im Si Wan...!
We can't keep jumping...
Only the one with the ball can jump.
[Without a doubt,
Coach Kook's lesson starts again]
[Trying not to be late for the lesson hour...]
The only person who should jump
is the person doing the spikes.
And everyone else, just walk.
[Tall giraffe jumping practice]
Flatten out your palms
and put it together like this.
And put these two fingers together like this.
[Private lesson from Coach Kook]
-Fighting!!
-Fighting!
We have to win this!
[Not a chance...!]
[15 point game-Start!]
[Lee Joon taking full advantage of
the leverage from the trampoline]
Jae Suk!
[Barely getting the ball over]
[Lee Joon flying up high... Trapping?]
[What the...]
[Too easily...
Running Man Team 1: Idol Team 0]
[After all, it is a trampoline,
so it's not easy to control the body...]
It's okay!  It's okay!
[Keep disorienting them by jumping]
[Idol Team utilizing
the special attribute of the arena]
[Blank Ji's serve]
[Running Man Team 2: Idol Team 0]
[Idol's Team's
strong pitfall candidate, Lee Joon]
[This is where the playing stops...!]
That's good!
Hit it!
-Hit it!
-Block it!
[Yong Hwa's spike!]
Running Man Team 2: Idol Team 1]
[Immediately following the mistake,
Coach Kook's one point lesson]
Yoon Doo Joon!  Yoon Doo Joon...!
Yoon Doo Joon!
[Eun Hyuk's midair return!]
[Accurately hits the blank spot!]
[The Idol Team evening out the score
within a matter of moments]
This is harder than I thought.
[...Huh?]
[The oldest member,
Big-Nosed brother's weak receive]
I can't believe that!
Don't you think you're aiming for me too much?
[Again?!]
[Another aimed serve succeeds!]
[Running Man Team 2: Idol Team 4]
Eun Jung...!
-Jong Kook...!
-That's good!
[Coach Kook's safe receive]
[He does seem to have the most advantageous
body type for volleyball...]
[Running Man Team 2: Idol Team 5]
You can just hit it the best you can.
[Giraffe's pathetic return...]
[Giraffe receiving tips from everyone]
[Giraffe]
We love Giraffe the best!!
[Running Man Team 2: Idol Team 6]
Great job!
[Coach Kook's shocking reflexes]
[Why did that ball have to go
towards the giraffe of all places?]
[Long giraffe getting in the way
just by being himself]
[Crowned as Running Man's Black Hole]
Kwang Soo...
[Even Kwang Soo's fans are keeping quiet...]
[Running Man Team 2: Idol Team 7]
[What was that?]
[Is that volleyball?]
Time out, time out!
[Ha Ha's explosion]
I want to do well too!
[To the spot the giraffe
is guarding with a blank stare]
[Idol team's
unilateral win is unfolding...]
[Running Man team feeling the urgency
when they can't even control their own bodies]
[Such bad luck...
Hitting the camera on top of the net]
[Inside the court!]
[Idol's Team's point is accepted]
Time!  Time!!
[Running Man Team 5: Idol Team 11]
[Idol Team's unilateral pace]
I think we need to strategize.
Kwang Soo... You haven't played
volleyball before, have you?
I'm good at volleyball.
[Firing down on Kwang Soo, the hole]
-You don't have to try to hit so hard.
-You just need to get it over the net.
There's no need to be greedy.
No need for that.
[Will the Running Man Team be able
to turn the game around...?]
Running Man!  Running Man!
[Ace Yong Hwa's miss!]
[Overtly ceremonious behavior]
Volleyball is all about team spirit!
[Blank Ji feeling bewildered on the trampoline]
Calm down... Be calm!
Kwang Soo, don't jump!
[Giraffe blocking himself?]
[How did that happen!]
[Volleyball is about team spirit!
Giraffe finally pulls one off!]
[Running Man Team 7: Idol Team 11]
Fighting!
[Why did it have to go to
giraffe again of all people?]
[Oh... How did the hole, giraffe
pull it off again twice in a row?]
They're doing well all of a sudden...!
Fighting!!
[Closely following behind!]
[Running Man Team 12: Idol Team 13]
Get it over the net!
[Doo Joon's fierce spike!]
[Could have been an epic scene...]
[At last, an even score]
[Running Man Team 13: Idol Team 13]
Let's go!
[Fast Jae Suk's 'Fighting' inducing play!]
[Running Man Team 14: Idol Team 13]
[Finally reversing the game!]
[Melting pot of excitement]
[If they score one more point,
an electrifying win for Running Man]
Leave it, leave it... It's mine.
[Is it over?]
[Ah...]
[Jae Suk getting caught in the net
along with the ball]
[Deuce!]
[Running Man Team 14: Idol Team 14]
[Rule: In case of there being a deuce,
the first team to score 2 points wins]
Nice.
[Different kind of nervousness than before]
[Giraffe?]
[Giraffe's attack a success!]
[The victory is right in front of their eyes!]
[Giraffe is finally loosened up!]
There's only a point left?
[Match Point]
[Running Man Team 15: Idol Team 14]
[Will this be their win?
Or will it be another deuce?]
[The nervousness is especially sensitized
for being in front of this huge crowd]
Let's do this right!
[Getting excited all of a sudden?]
[Just at that time,
the serve goes towards Lee Joon!]
[Idol Team is defeated in vain]
[Jumping up effortlessly]
[Flustered?]
[And that's how he misses]
What are you doing?!
[Unbelievable mistake by the ballet Idol]
[Game over!]
[Running Man Team's victory!]
[Disappointed...]
Lee Joon... It's such a relief that
Lee Joon is on that team...!
[I shouldn't have jumped...!]
[Defeated Idol Team once again
gets seated on the second level]
Thank you!
[Thanking all the fans that cheered them on]
We should've won that game!
I feel weaker because it's so hot.
We definitely can't take them lightly...
I think that we had some
serious teamwork going...
Our two years of working together
allowed us to work in sync.
We were really in sync today.
We can do this.
If this is how we felt for the first race,
we may have been able to pull it off.
Just acknowledge this...
That they're not easy opponents.
Of course!  I will admit that for sure.
Even though they are the best...
Our teamwork can't be taken lightly either.
Okay!  You're right!
The reason why is,
it's because I spoke to you all earlier,
and all of your superpowers came out
without you guys even realizing it.
[Superpowers...?]
I think we won just so that
we don't get scolded by him.
I'm being serious about this right now.
For the last competition...
At the final destination,
there are Sun-gong and Hu-gong.
When you find out what they are later,
you'll see how important they are.
And the team that wins this mission
will be able to take on that Sun-gong.
Really?
[Running Man Team-1: Idol Team-1]
[What will be the game to break the tie?]
-Third game is an underwater hurdle.
-Wow!  What is that?
If you pass a member through the hurdle
and cross over all three...
-All the members?
-No, just one.
-Just one member?
-Just pass over one member through...
The member that goes over the last hurdle...
And runs over here
to pull the flag is the winner.
-Then we got this!
-3 matches.
[Best 2 out of 3]
[A female to go over on the first game]
[First submerging in the water]
[Idol Team overflowing with excitement
at the sight of water]
The most important thing is...
Everyone gather around.
[Undoubtedly,
another of Coach Kook's lessons starts]
[First game's competitor Ji Hyo practicing]
That's right!  That was good!
[Strength of learning?
A smooth know-how's understanding]
Jae Suk... I think we can just
be ready for the next move over there.
Yeah, that... That...
What did they just say?
[After eavesdropping on Coach Kook's lesson,
gathering around for an immediate practice]
Hey, the Idols are copying us!
Eun Jung has a lot of fear...
[...Huh?]
[A free-fall]
It's okay, it's okay.
At the sound of the whistle,
we'll start the match.
Now, 1... 2...!
Hurry, hurry, hurry!
[Running Man Team moving in an orderly fashion
at Coach Kook's commanding order]
Step on me!
[Eun Jung succeeds]
Nice, nice, nice!!
[Ji Hyo succeeds the first obstacle
by throwing her body into it]
[Blank Ji being dragged through the water
now even before she knows what's going on]
[Flying like a bird...]
[Easily passing through the second obstacle
with time to spare]
-Nice, nice!
-Eun Jung, great job!
-Ji Hyo... Get on him... Step on him!
-Ji Hyo... We have to get to the last one!
[Feeling like death warmed over]
1...2...
-What are you doing?
-Hurry! We have to move it!
[The Idol Group is already ahead
by 1 obstacle]
Do it quickly!  Hurry up and jump!
Hurry up and jump!!
[Human jumping board giraffe
is feeling like death warmed over]
1... 2... 3...!
[Blank Ji succeeds with a scissor move!]
[Without even a chance to
get her mind back together...]
[her body is already dragged off
to the 3rd obstacle]
[This is their chance to catch up to
the Idol team while they're flubbing around]
[Eun Jung rising up to challenge at
the 3rd and final obstacle]
[Not so easy 3rd obstacle
with its' taller height]
[Just then!]
Hurry up and jump!  Hurry up and jump!!
1... 2... 3...!
[Succeeds by throwing her whole body into it!]
Run!  Run!  Run!!
[Eun Jung also succeeds
almost at the same time!]
[Now on the move to take the flag
at the finish line!]
[Like salmons trying to swim upstream...]
[Towards the flag at the finish line!]
[Eun Jung vs. Ji Hyo... Just who will win?]
Hurry up!
[Ji Hyo arrives first!]
[Running Man wins the first round!]
[Sapped of energy...]
[Wins through their teamwork]
This time,
the bar is going up a little higher.
[For the second round,
the hurdle height is raised higher]
-Running Man, fighting!
-We have to end it right now!
-Let's end it right now!
-Let's not drag this out longer.
-Let's do this, let's do it!
-Let's go!!  Fighting!!
[Second round competitors are...
Running Man's Kwang Soo vs. Idol's Si Wan]
You have to step on his shoulders...
On his shoulders.  1, 2, 3!
[Fails from dropping the bar]
Jong Kook, bend down a little.  Bend down.
1... 2... 3...!
[His heart is feeling the urgency,
and his body is so long...]
Kwang Soo, calm down.
1, 2, 3!
[During this time,
Si Wan passes through the 2nd obstacle too]
1, 2, 3!
[Diving as if he's a national swimmer]
[Submerging so dashingly]
[Now off to the third and the last obstacle]
Nice, nice... Okay!
[Running Man Team still on the first obstacle]
[Submerging again with the bar]
[Plummeting?]
-This is too hard!  This is just too hard!
-What the heck is this?
Seriously... Can we switch out the person?
This is too hard on me!
[Running Man already feeling defeated]
I told you that he won't work
because he's too heavy!
Just what in the world are we doing?
Hey, you...!
[Human jumping board, the tiger explodes]
I can do this!
[Submerging together]
I can do this... I can do this!!
[In the meantime, Si Wan easily passes through
the 3rd obstacle too]
-Si Wan, this way!  Come this way!
-Come on... Come this way!
[Anticipating the victory]
I'll do it!
[The giraffe is only practicing
on how to submerge a tiger...]
-I told you that he's too heavy!
-I can do this!
Yes!  Yeah!!
[Idol team wins the second round!]
-He just can't do this...
-How could you not have done it?!
[Current score:
Running Man Team 1: Idol Team 1]
[This time, Coach Kook does his practice]
You can't... You're too heavy.
You're just too heavy... You're too heavy.
It has to be a lighter person.
[Agony]
I told you that you're too heavy!
[Designated as the human jump board
for being tall]
[Feeling like death warmed over]
-1, 2, 3!
-Okay!
[Yoo-ruce Willis chosen
as the final competitor]
[Kwang Soo's shoulders...]
Hoist him up carefully.
[Competitor this time around is Eun Hyuk]
1, 2, 3!
[A shocking jump]
[A formidable flexibility]
[Already feeling like they've won]
-We have to win no matter what this time.
-This really is our last chance.
I really want to win!
-It's okay!  We can do it!!
-Let's win!!
Gather around!  Idol... Yeah!
[Underwater hurdle final round-Start!]
Hurry, hurry!
[Already!]
[Like how the last round should be?
Both teams at a lightning fast speed!]
[With the jump,
changing back to a classic hairstyle]
1, 2, 3!
[With formidable jumping skills,
succeeds the first obstacle easily]
[When did he get the swimming cap?]
[Within moments,
arriving at the second hurdle]
1, 2, 3!
[Succeeding the second hurdle in one shot!]
[Neck to neck]
[Now the final obstacle]
-It's higher than I thought.
-1, 2, 3!
[First?!]
[Flexible Eun Hyuk fails!]
[If Jae Suk were to succeed like this...]
[Ah... Fails]
[Seriously not an easy height...]
[A victory lost in a maze of chaos]
[Jae Suk rising to the challenge again]
[Eun Hyuk also rises almost at the same time]
[Jae Suk making the jump first]
[Will he...?]
[Wow!  Success!]
[How can this be?
The power of the swimming cap...?]
[Heading off to the finish line
with his hair plastered to his head]
[Eun Hyuk also succeeds at this time?]
[Ah... The bar...]
[Jae Suk heading off to the finish line]
[Running Man Team's victory
over the 3rd round!]
[The anger...]
[Running Man Team wins the underwater hurdle!]
We really were awesome!
Kwang Soo, you did a great job!
[Idol Teams devastated at their
defeat over 2 of the 3 challenges]
This really is disappointing.
[The long awaited final competition]
[Hansung museum]
-Are those hats?
-There are hats in front of the entrance.
[Will the defeated Idol Team
be able to reverse their situation?]
[Just what will be the last mission
for the Running Man's Olympics be?]
It's offense and defense.
[Shifting hide-and-go seek]
[Once the allotted time is over,
the offensive and defensive teams switch]
[The team with a surviving member wins]
I think we get to choose.
[The offense and defense switch time is
every 15 minutes!]
You can choose which one you'd like.
Either offense or defense.
-Let's go with the offense.
-I think hiding first would be better.
-The thing we're really good at...
-We know where good hiding places are...
-Then let's vote on it.
-Okay, okay...
-Let's vote on it.
-Those who'd like to be on the offense first?
[Show of hands
of those wanting to attack first]
-And that's a unanimous vote!
-A lot of people wanting to be on the offense.
[Only 4 out of 7 rose their hands,
and it's unanimous?]
But when you said unanimous,
not one person said anything.
[Even though it wasn't unanimous,
it's decided they'll be on the offense first!]
-Jong Kook...
-We can't... This place is too wide.
What's that?
[Idol Team's entrance]
Attack all you want...!
You guys just wait.
[Shifting hide-and-go seek]
[Once the allotted time is over,
the offensive and defensive teams switch]
[The team with a surviving member wins]
[Doo Joon being cautious
not to ruin his hairstyle]
Doo Joon,
the front of your hair doesn't move at all!
[The front of my hair is my pride!]
Is that his pride or something?
[The bells making their appearance
for the first time in a very long time!]
You'll get to know what Running Man is about
when you run into Jong Kook at a dead end.
[Running Man's required course]
[To see this man at a dead end hallway]
Seeing Jong Kook then is
what real Running Man is about...
[Soon the Idol Team members will
experience that theatrical terror too]
[Idol team who's on the defense first
is given 3 minutes to hide]
Hey kids... Be careful of this sound!
[Idol Team runs off to hide!]
Be careful of this sound!!
-This place is rather small...
-There aren't any places to hide!
Where should I go?
Seriously...?
This is scary.
Let's all move our right foot around a little.
Run, Si Wan...!
[Terror!]
Si Wan...!
Eun Jung, hurry up and hide!
Wow... This is really nerve-wracking.
I can feel my heart shrinking.
I really want to get going...
Since this shirt has Korea written on it...
Tearing off the name tag...
[Feeling as if name ripping pursuit
has become an Olympic sport...!]
[Feeling as if they've been chosen as
the national representative for the sport]
This is what a lot of people wanted...
This is the first time we've been united
on the same team like this...
I...never knew that you'd ever say unity.
[The icon of betrayal speaking of unity...]
-I don't do betrayals anymore...
-What do you mean, you don't?
-Let's do a "Fighting."
-Running Man time!
-1, 2, 3...
-Fighting!
[Running Man Team making their move!]
[Running Man Team with their combined
long time know-how and their pursuit skills]
[Full of confidence]
I'm really full of emotion over this right now.
[After all the time of betrayal,
being united is boosting up their morale]
[Offense team, time to attack.
Offense team, time to attack.
[Explosion of nervousness!]
What to do?
I feel like I'm going to go crazy right now.
[If there was such a marathon in the Olympics,
for Running Man, it would be the chase!]
[2 years of experience!
Indeed National Representatives in pursuit!]
[However...]
[Youth! Ambition! Idol Team's potential
that should never be taken lightly!]
[Time left until the switch]
Make sure to hide really well,
for I can see your hair strands!
[Big brother and little brother
out on a full-scale search]
Nice...!  I know one of you are in here!
[The sound of the bells ringing
getting ever so closer!]
I saw a shadow just pass by!
[Mr. Capable locking in on his prey
by the movement of a shadow!]
-No one came through here?
-Did you see someone?
[Running Man Team giving pursuit
in a calm and orderly fashion]
No one came through this way.
[Si Wan... Hurry up and make your escape]
[Lee Joon also making
his escape to elsewhere!]
Hurry!  Hurry!
[Lee Joon making a safe escape
towards the offices]
[As for Si Wan... You call that hiding?]
[Discovers Si Wan!]
Si Wan...
[Being discovered right away
from hiding so hazardously]
-Si Wan... Si Wan...
-Hello.
Si Wan...
[A confrontation with a wall in between]
Si Wan... No need to be nervous.
[What do I do?  What do I do?]
Where did everyone go?
[This won't do... Let's make a run for it!]
[Si Wan attempting to
escape from Yoo-ruce Willis!]
[Gary lying in await]
Gary!
[This is Running Man's distinction]
I got you!!
[It's a siege!]
[Si Wan, thwarting Gary
and continuing his attempted escape!]
[However...!]
[Wow Gary, relentless in his pursuit!]
[Captures Si Wan of the Idol Team!]
[Pleading]
I've barely had a few minutes...!
We felt as though we should tear at least
one name tag off to get started...!
[Even though he's dead,
Si Wan still not wanting to die]
-Si Wan, you shouldn't be like this.
-There's seriously no place to hide in here!
Whenever I watch the show...
There's always so many places to hide in,
but why aren't there any here?!
What am I going to do in jail by myself?
Alone?
You're going to get to see your friends soon.
[Idol Team, Si Wan-Out!]
You did a great job.
[Running Man Team-7 : Idol Team-6]
[Im Si Wan, Out.  Im Si Wan, Out]
-But Si Wan...
-We need to win that gold medal...
[Im Si Wan, Out.  Im Si Wan, Out]
[At last, the start of the real pursuit...!]
[The nervousness multiplying after hearing
that one of their teammates has been ousted]
This is no joke...
[Nichkhun trying to make his hiding place
even better by making a blockade]
If by any chance they come down here...
Come this way...
Turn off the light.
Yes, I like this!
This is perfect!
[How much time is left for the switch?]
Maybe we can hide under here for now.
[Two members of the Idol Team
cautiously treading around]
[The sound of the bells ringing!]
Oh!  Jung Yong Hwa!
There's Jung Yong Hwa!
[Ace Ji Hyo discovers
Yong Hwa from the Idol Team!]
2nd floor!  He's on the 2nd floor!
[But Yong Hwa will never go down easily!]
Hey!  Hey!  Yong Hwa!
[Yong Hwa fleeing for his escape
as he sees the net closing in!]
Get him!  Get him!
[Simply thwarting Ace Ji Hyo!]
Hey!
[This is what you call know-how!
Mr. Capable looking for the opposite door!]
[Ace and Big-Nosed brother giving pursuit
from the other end!]
Gary, where are you?
[Running Man pursuit basics:
Always laying a siege to the pursuit!]
[Yong Hwa, you're fast!]
He's so fast!
[But just then...
Mr. Capable Jong Kook gives chase!]
[When it comes to a pursuit,
Mr. Capable is the specialist!]
[Idol Team's Yong Hwa is captured!]
Yong Hwa!
[Idol Team, Yong Hwa-Out!]
[Running Man Team-7: Idol Team-5]
[Jung Yong Hwa-Out.  Jung Yong Hwa-Out]
Yong Hwa?!
[Yong Hwa, you too?
Already two have been ousted!]
Jong Kook, it's almost time for the switch.
It's almost time for the switch.
we have to find them quickly!
-Let's go in this way.
-Which way?
[Have to oust as many as they can
before they have to switch over...!]
Where does this lead?
[Idol Team's Doo Joon's attempt at escape!]
Doo Joon!  Doo Joon!
[Definitely comes from a soccer background!
He's so unbelievably fast!!]
[Mr. Capable Jong Kook is off!]
[Mr. Capable... Gets a grab of him!]
Doo Joon...
[Time to switch off.  Time to switch off]
[15 minutes have passed.
Offense and defense role to be changed!]
[Time to switch off.  Time to switch off]
[Idol Team that's been in hiding
can now attack to their hearts desire!]
I should have endured it another 2 minutes!
Wait, wait...
[Defense Running Man Team-7:
Offense Idol Team-5]
[Running Man now on defense has to
take off their bells and change their tags]
Look at Doo Joon's eyes!
Are you scared?
[Moments before the roles are to reverse!]
[Idol team completes switching tags to
mark their offense and attaching the bells]
I'm going to go catch them all like crazy.
Here I go making my move!
[Countdown to the time change switch off!]
[Time to run out of there!]
[Idol Team's counterattack is about to begin]
[Start!]
[Running Man banding together
and acting calm and cautiously]
Don't run.  Don't come any closer.
[Have to endure the fierce counterattack
from the Idol Team!]
[A lesson learned in the knowledge?
Doo Joon heading in the opposite direction]
[Totally different from the Running Man, who
were full of confidence during the attack!]
[Huh?  Lee Joon taking off
after seeing someone!]
[Lee Joon, locking in on
Yoo-ruce Willis as his target!]
[Lee Joon's fast!]
[How will the divine Yoo-ruce Willis fare?]
[Running Man Team-6: Idol Team-5]
That bell sound...
He's done too!
[Giraffe Kwang Soo captured by Doo Joon]
[Oh!  Kwang Soo attempting to thwart him!]
[But with Lee Joon's attack,
he's put in a dangerous situation!]
[The sight of giraffe
being captured by the 2 cheetahs]
[He thwarted them!]
[If he can just escape from here,
it's possible that he may remain alive!]
[Huh...?]
[Why did he tear off his own name tag?]
This... This was in my hand...
I tore it off, Jae Suk...
[Not something you want to brag about...]
Pretty soon,
we'll go back to being on the defense...
But I'm going to get them all
right now before that happens.
[Putting on his own enthusiastic bell show]
[Why go in the box that were put there
for the defense team to hide in?]
[Is there someone here?]
[I think I hear bells ringing...]
Aren't you on our team?
Who is it?
[The ringing bell sound heard
from within the box]
Who is it?
What are you doing in there?
[Was going to launch a surprise attack!]
I'll help you, I'll help you.
[How does he think that's a good plan...]
He scared me!
[It's got to be hot in there...]
Should we sit diagonally from each other?
How about like this?
-Have you been well?
-Well, I...
-Oh my, Ha Ha...
-Nichkhun!  Just come have a seat for now.
-We were just talking...
-Why don't we have a seat for now?
Nichkhun and I are...
Ever since he was little, I knew him.
I also know his parents.
And I even know all his younger siblings too.
Why else would I mention this?
I'm just going to walk out of here.
You can send me off.
I'm in no way running away!
I'm just saying that I'm going to leave...
You can tear it off anytime!
-I'll walk you out.
-Doo Joon, you can just stay here.
Why don't we just walk you out though?
-Let's go!
-Why don't you take the lead?
[Ha Ha taking the lead confidently]
I trust you guys.
I'll let you guys know where Suk Jin is.
Then it's even... Unconditionally.
[Ultimately, offering up Big-Nosed brother's
life to get himself out of danger]
Here.  Ha...!
-B... 2...!
[This is how Haroro...
How this man survives...]
Okay.  Let's go.
We're Ha-B-2.  Ha-B-2!
[The truth is,
Haroro is the master of betrayals]
Why don't you walk slower?
Over there... There.
[He's seriously showing them
where Running Man team members are hiding!]
[What should we do with him?]
[Should we just end it?]
I don't think Nichkhun
can be a part of Ha-B-2!
-Ha!
-B!  2!
Fighting!
[Ha Ha starts his escape!]
[Ha Ha, how can you
escape to a dead end like that?]
-Ha Ha...
-Doo Joon, take care of it.
I can't believe this is where I escaped to.
This is such a relief.
I want you guys to survive this...
[The ultimate swindler, Ha Ha-Out!]
[Time for the switch over.
Time for the switch over]
[Pure exhaustion]
I'm so hot!
I seriously almost passed out.
[Running Man Team-4: Idol Team-5]
Time to switch?  Okay!!
Okay...!!
[Able to breathe a sigh of relief
after being on the run for 15 minutes]
[Countdown to the switch off!]
[The nervousness is creeping up
on the Idol Team again...]
[Why don't you be a little nervous...?]
[Running Man team immediately heading out
to start their full-scale search!]
[Oh!  There's someone here!]
Lee Joon...!
[Gary showing his chasing skills!
Pursuing Lee Joon at full speed!]
[Lee Joon... Maybe you should've
just kept hiding in that box...]
[Anyways, a very satisfying pursuit!]
[But the ever widening gap between them!
At this rate, he'll lose Lee Joon!]
Lee Joon!
Coming... They're coming!
[Losing all the strength
in his legs automatically]
[There's one over there too!
Hurry up and come to me!]
[His mind is still out on an outing...]
What the heck...
He scared the bejeezus out of me!
Why did it have to be Jong Kook
of all people...?
I was shocked too!
Seeing Jong Kook spring out like that...
Jong Kook...
I was shocked seeing you there too!
[Whether you're on offense or defense,
this guy is sure to scare anyone...!]
All of a sudden, Lee Joon started screaming
as soon as he turned the corner!
So I was like, what the heck!?
And I saw him there with his mouth
opened up this wide!
-I just saw him collapsing to the floor.
-Yeah, he just collapsed!
[Mr. Capable, Jong Kook...
The pride of Running Man's pursuits]
Let's rest for just a little bit.
Let's take a little rest break.
[Idol Team exhausted from all the nervousness]
[The approach of the bells ringing
that won't even give them a moment's rest]
Let's get out of here for now.
Getting out of here would be best.
They're on the move!
[The Monday couple from the past
is on the move after casing them out!]
This way, we need to go this way.
Let's wait for them here.
-We just need to run from them right now.
-Hey guys...!
Where are you guys going?
[Wow!  Big-Nosed brother's surprise attack!]
[But... They're all escaping him...]
[Like water falling through a hole]
Hey!  Come back here!
[Splitting up and escaping
to 3 different routes!]
Hey, come here Gary.
[Of all places that Doo Joon escapes to,
it's a dead end!]
Doo Joon!
It's time to give in....
You don't even have anywhere else to go to.
[Even though he may be divine Doo Joon...
He's exhausted and at a dead end...]
Since we've got you here...
[Running Man Team-4 : Idol Team-3]
Suk Jin!
[Running Man on a roll...
Now discovered Eun Jung too!]
-Suk Jin...
-Eun Jung...
If you take too much time, I'm going to leave.
Ji Hyo, I can't.
I think you need to tear it off.
[Ace Ji Hyo, stepping up to handle it herself]
[Running Man Team-4: Idol Team-2]
By any chance...
Is there a way I can be on your team?
[Eun Jung-Out.  Eun Jung-Out]
I'm okay.  I'm good at escaping.
Someone's here... Someone's here!
[Mr. Capable Kim Jong Kook]
Suk Jin... Look over there.
[Coming up here with Big-nosed brother
to search the rooftop]
Start up from down there.
It's Jong Kook!
[But anyhow...
The time to switch is approaching...]
It's easier to hide out here...
Since it's dark.
[The siren alerting them of the switch!]
[What exquisite timing]
Hey!  Stop!
[Since it's time to switch over,
all the activities must cease]
[Time to switch over!]
Cease activity, cease activity.
[Running Man Team-4: Idol Team-2]
Suk Jin, are you ready?
You're going to oust me?
-Yes.
-No way... You can't do that.
You work out a bit, don't you?
What are you doing right now?
Seriously... That kid...!
-Get ready... Get ready...!
-Let's do this then.
[Im done... I'm done... It's Nichkhun...!]
[Countdown to the switch over!]
[Start!]
[Idol Team's attack begins!]
[...Huh?  Why isn't he chasing Suk Jin?]
[Instead of chasing after Suk Jin,
Nichkhun heads to the upper level]
[I wonder if Suk Jin made his escape?]
[Nichkhun, you're not... Eyeing Mr. Capable?!]
[Nichkhun challenging Mr. Capable head on!]
-Jong Kook, why are you running away?
-Huh?
-Why aren't you running from me?
-Because you came alone.
[Anyways, they're the only ones up here.
Nichkhun alone is easily to defeat?]
-I've got 15 minutes, Jong Kook.
-I know.
[Mr. Capable vs. Nichkhun.
Now that we think about it, these two...]
[At the special Thailand episode a year ago,
they have a history of another face-off!]
[Nichkhun, who made the divine Mr. Capable
break out in a sweat!]
[The two facing off again!
Just who will it be?]
[Strength vs. strength!
Will not be backed down!]
-I can smell the medicated patch.
-Where?
-You're not well, are you?
-Huh?
To me, the smell of medicated patches
is like scent of perfume.
[Nichkhun pretending to engage in conversation
but going for the name tag instead!]
I'm reminded of the time in Thailand...
Do you remember that?
[Someone else...is coming!]
[Idol Team's Eun Hyuk joining!]
[If this happens, it'll be
Mr. Capable vs. Nichkhun and Eun Hyuk!]
This is trouble!
[The tiger being surrounded
by 2 young cheetahs!]
You know this isn't right!  Guys... Guys!
[Ferocious attack!]
[Mr. Capable is flustered!]
[At last, his name tag is in his grasp!]
[Jong Kook-Out!]
Jong Kook, I'm sorry!
I had no idea that you'd come.
-How did you know to come?
-If it was Nichkhun alone, I could've done it.
Hey!  We got Jong Kook!
We got Jong Kook!!
[Running Man without Jong Kook...
Just who will the ultimate winner be...?]
[Kim Jong Kook-Out.  Kim Jong Kook-Out]
Kim Jong Kook is out?!
[Running Man, losing their focal point]
[It's essential to stay hidden
until the next time switch]
[Now spirited Eun Hyuk and Nichkhun
in a full search mode]
[With only a few survivors left,
the search has become more detailed]
Ah... So there are places like this around...
-Eun Hyuk, it's you.
-Yes, Suk Jin.
I had some business here.
-I have a meeting here.
-Oh, in here?
-Yeah, it's in here.
-Isn't it stuffy in here?
The reason I have to delay the
time here a little bit is...
But, Suk Jin...
[It's useless trying to fight him off...]
[Ji Suk Jin-Out.  Ji Suk Jin-Out]
[Running Man Team-2: Idol Team-2]
[Now remaining 2 against 2.
A toe-to-toe match]
Shall we go towards the theater?
[Approaching ringing bell sound]
[Panic...!]
Shall we try the hall?
[Even though I'm nervous,
I have to get on the camera]
[Where are Gary and Ji Hyo?]
[Oh...!  He's coming close!]
Please... Please...
[He's just leaving?!!]
[Siren for the switch off going off!
15 minutes are up!]
It's good.  It's good.  It's good!
[Cease all activities.
Prepare to switch over from your current spot]
Didn't someone hit it?  Didn't someone?
Oh!  That's crazy!
That's crazy!  What the heck?
When he hit the box,
I let my body get moved around along with it.
[He himself finds it fascinating
that he wasn't caught]
[Soon Nichkhun will become the prey
and Gary will become the hunter]
-You didn't know?
-No, I didn't know!
I thought my heart
was seriously going to drop.
You're ready to run, right?
Nichkhun!  I see you right there!  I got it!
You're ready to run?
[Countdown to the switch over]
[Start!]
Ji Hyo!  Ji Hyo!
[Possibly the last chance to catch Nichkhun]
-Ji Hyo!  Ji Hyo!
-Where is he?
Over there!  He's over there!
Hurry!  Hurry!!
[He's here!]
[Nichkhun escapes easily]
[Seldom able to catch up to his speed]
[Ultimately...
Idol Team's Nichkun succeeds at escaping]
Ah!  We almost had him!
It seriously has been so long
since we've done the bell thing.
It is fun...
-First of all, that sound... It's exciting.
-That sound is really exciting.
-Eun Jung?
-Yes?
Why don't you have one?
-But you already started eating it.
-There's some behind you.
You really thought that I would
tell you to eat this one?
Eun Jung, seriously...!
-Jae Suk treats us often to things like this.
-Really?
Didn't you know that he bought IU a car?
-Did you really buy her a car?
-Did you do it?
You weren't just talking about doing it,
but you actually bought her a car?
It's not that I bought her one...
Not that I actually bought her one...
I'm telling you that he's generous.
We're going to be moving
to a different dormitory soon...
-Refrigerators are nice.
-Refrigerator?  Refrigerator.
[He's about to become genie of the lamp today]
-No way.  You think he'll do it?
-You know those coolers with the ice in it.
Ok, in that case...
-Okay, in that case...
-Wow!!
[The atmosphere is as if
it's already been purchased]
I live at home with my parents...
And we haven't had an air conditioner
at home in more than 10 years...!
[This time an air conditioner...!]
-You picked a good one.
-Please buy me an air conditioner.
Okay, then an air conditioner.
Stand in line.  Form a line!
There are 9 of us living together
and the dormitory is very small.
-So...?
-A house?!
-Yeah!  A house!
-Okay then!
Jae Suk, you're seriously so cool!
I want a massage chair that
massages all the way down to my feet.
-How many times a week would you use it?
-I'd use it everyday.
Seriously, thank you so much, Jae Suk!
-Kwang Soo...
-I'm going to call my mom and tell her!
Can you lend me $200,000?
Let me borrow $200,000.
-If I'm to buy all this stuff for the kids...
-There's no borrowing money amongst family!
[There's now only 2 minutes left until
it's time for them to switch roles again]
[If they wait just a little bit longer,
the Idol Team will be able to attack!]
-Come and tear my name off, Gary!
-Oh, okay!
-Let's get one of them right now.
-Go after one of them?
[That's our Ace!
Proposing to catch one with remaining time]
Come on up here!
[The final four finally confronts each other!]
-There's not much time left now.
-We know that.
[It's now...!]
[Running Man Team starts their attack!]
[Who's the target?
Nichkhun? Or Eun Hyuk?]
[Ace Ji Hyo attacks Nichkhun!]
[But just then!]
[Gary got his hand on Eun Hyuk's
name tag somehow!]
[Gary succeeds at tearing off
Eun Hyuk's name tag!]
[There's no time left!
Need to hurry and get Nichkhun!]
[Eun Hyuk-Out.  Eun Hyuk-Out]
No, it was just Eun Hyuk being ousted!
Eun Hyuk is out!
[Announcement just now wasn't about the switch
but about Eun Hyuk being ousted!]
[They didn't move a budge thinking
that it was an announcement about the switch!]
[Both teams in desperation!!]
[Switch off siren goes off!]
[At full attention]
The odds are looking good...
But Nichkhun isn't someone to be messed with.
He has to get Gary right now to win.
[Gary even lost a shoe on one foot!]
You know that we're doing this
once he says start, right?
[Beating the hell out of here!]
[Only chance of survival is for them to run!!]
[Start!]
[Nichkhun eyed Gary right away,
but Ji Hyo gets in his way!]
Run Gary!  Hurry up and run!
[Nichkhun making his move
for Ace Ji Hyo first!]
[Ji Hyo-Out!]
[Now the final face-off!]
[Running Man's Gary vs. Idol Team's Nichkhun!]
I don't have a shoe!
[Ah... The sprint of a barefoot runner...]
-What the heck?
-We lost... We lost.
Kang Gary had to run for it
and leave his shoe behind...
He left one of his shoe behind...
-Really?
-That's really crazy.
Khun!  My foot is killing me!
[Will he be able to last on barefoot like that
until it's time for the next switch off?]
Someone's here!  Someone's here!
He's walking in with him in hand...
[The result is...?]
It's still on your back.
I... I promised him.
[Tearing it off in front of everyone
for all to witness!]
This isn't right!
[Nichkhun gets rid of
the final Running Man member!]
[Running Man Olympics-
Idol Team, the ultimate winner!]
Doo Joon... Congratulations.
[A real gold medal to the winning team]
-Thank you!
-You did a great job.
Let's go!  To London!
Representatives of Korea, Fighting!!
Subtitles by DramaFever