What is this?
You are invited onto a treasure ship.
Find the treasure hidden on the treasure ship and become its owner.
Take tomorrow's 8AM flight to Cusan and come to the following address.
Go to Busan?
That Busan in the south?
You didn't hang something on the doors this time?
Like that time in Hong Kong.
Is it an individual competition?
This is strange.
It's a treasure ship? A treasure ship?
Is this it?
I can just go back in?
There's no mission for me?
OK.
Never trust anyone...
Find the culprit
The culprit is...
I think the culprit is...
Among us!
No!
-It's you! -You are the culprit!
Nuna, hi.
It's a good morning.
I couldn't sleep a wink.
What are you planning now.
Your face is swollen.
What did you eat before bed?
A cup ramen.
Ah! This is ...
It makes me happy no matter how many times I look at it.
Why give me this on TV, making me embarrassed.
Hello.
-You all brought your invitations, right? -Yes.
Then we'll get going now, To the airport.
The airport is right there.
Then we'll get there. It won't even take 10 minutes. Please take your belongings.
-Wow, is this that... -Oh, this is here, too.
This is like Incheon Ariport...
Daebak! Daebak!
-It's the airport now. -Oh, it really is!
It's the airport!
This is amazing.
Wow, we're in Busan.
In the blink of an eye. It's Busan.
It's Busan.
Where will it be? I'm curious.
Oh? What's that?
Oh? What?
What?
-I was here! -Hey!
-Hey, get out. -Kwang Soo...
You can't stick yourself in here from the side.
And I had come out early.
Yes, yes, yes!
Please go that way.
-Yes. -Kwang Soo cut in from the side.
We're late, we're late!
Hey! I'm first!
Wait. Where's the car?
Ah, this will take a whlie. Where is it?
What is it? Which is it?
Where is it?
Come out! K.U.T.T!
It must be this one!
See!
Wait, wait. Please only one person press at a time!
It's here! I found it!
Wow, what luck!
Oh, it's right. It's my car.
It's this one.
This one, this one!
It must be this one!
It's this one.
Wait a minute.
What we got at dawn... I just need to go to this address, right?
Busan, Saha-gu, Cupyeong-dong 495-31 Orient Dockyard.
OK. Let's go! I'm going to leave first!
I think I'm the first right now.
Find a treasure ship? A treasure ship...?
Hey, what is this?
What will today be about?
What's going on all of a sudden? I can't get my mind straight.
It seems to be individual competitions today.
We haven't split into team, so it much be individual.
Maybe we'll be put into teams in the order we arrive?
You think we're being invited to a party? Like from the old show Detective Kim Jeon...?
We'll be invited and...
OK, I have a good record until now.
Wow, what is this?!
Wow, this is no joke!
It looks bigger than what we were on last time... Oh!
I'm first?
Am I first?
Buon Giorno (Good day).
Cuse me?
That ship you see over there is the treasure ship that came from Italy.
-Oh, really? -Yes.
First, wear this manteau.
Oh, really?
Wear that and you need to get on that small tugboat.
Ah, hyung, we'll go first!
Bye!
Ah,it's green again.
He's here.  He's here.
Ah! It's leaving!
Out!
Why do you get so started easily these days?
This isn't something that'll let us fly through the air?
I fell in water once...
But I was saved by this clothing.
Welcome. Mr Lee Kwang Soo, please go up first.
-Eh? Separately? -One by one?
Wow, there are 7 floors.
Marina.
Miss Blank?
-Careful. -Thank you.
Adlos!
Amigo!
Everyone, happy new year!
This is the 6th floor.
Kwang Soo, Kwang Soo.
What is this?
Oh! Chao chao!
Oh, if it's a Hao chao...!
Lee Seung Hwan, hao!
If we get all of this right, please let us go on Running Man.
-Would you like to try? -Please promise!!
Kwang Soo, Kwang Soo.
invitation?
The invitation is in my car...
Go back down.
-Eh? -Go back down.
GO BACK DOWN!
Do I have to get on the boat and go back?
Invitation is necessary.
What, I really... Really?
Really? But my invitation is really in the car.
What? We really have to go back?
We've especially readied brunch for you all.
Thank you. Follow me.
It was difficult, wasn't it?
-Yes? It was difficult, wasn't it?
Hey, you just here now Kwang Soo?
I really went back, hyung!
-Really? -All the way back? -Yes!
-Can we eat this? -Yeah, eat.
-Really? -Yeah, eat.
Oh, chao chao.
Hello! Hello! Hello!
Hello!
The Hao Chao team been invited onto Running Man!
Oh, but what is this?
-Oh, chao chao. -Chao chao!
Ah, the prince of dogs! Chao chao!
Is there something this chao chao is good at?
...Impersonation.
Oh, an Impersonation!
... Lee Gye In.
Oh, an Impersonation of the celebrity Lee Gye In.
Please show us!
Lee Gye In.
It's good!
Yoo Jae Suk.
-Hopper, hopper. -Oh, Yoo Jae Suk sunbaenim.
-He says you are a chihuahua. -Chihuahua, yes.
-Any personal talents? -Oh, he's asking if you have any personal talents.
I don't really have any talents.
Please show us something.
What should I do?
-The Dooly dance! -Ah, but that's been such a long time ago.
Grasshopper dance. Rabbit dance.
But I've done the grasshopper dance so often.
Do something already!
Why do you speak so much?
Quickly!
Quickly! Quickly!
Wow, he's dancing! Dancing!
You did well! You did well!
You did well!
Thank you.
-There's someone to celebrate. -Oh?
The two who the Entertainment Award, Ji Suk sunbaeinm and Gary.
This year's Entertainment Award...
Mr. Ji Suk and Mr. Gary.
-Congratulations! -Congratulations!
-You! You! -Me?
-You won! -Really?
But because we're the hubae comedians, if you could take a commemorative photo with us?
-Oh, but... the trophy you won... -Oh, the trophy? I bring that around with me.
Why are you taking that trophy around with you?!
-Because I do! -Really?
OH. oooh
Wow, tr-ro-phy!
OK, please come up here.
What? But the trophy disappeared...
What?
It disappeared?
But hyung, you had your bag with you the whole time.
-I did... -Look carefully!
Where did the trophy go?
Really?
It really disappeared.
Was it in there originally? When you received it?
-Of course it was. -Really?
-But it's really gone? -But, how could it disappear?
Then... We'll just take the picture with this...
Do that for now.
-Take it for now. -It's weird.
-OK. -Yes, yes, here.
-Thank you. -You're kind of cut off.
Originally, where...?
-Did you see it on the plane? -Yeah, on the plane.
-But hyung! You carried the bag nearly the whole time. -Exactly, I definitely was carrying the bag. Because it's precious.
Did someone take it? Was it you?
-I have my own! -The culprit is within us!
-In my mind, the culprit is... Kwang Soo. -You...
-Hyung! -Kwang Soo, it's you!
-But hyung! I went back with Gary hyung to get my invitation. -That's why it's you.
No. The culprit is... Ji Suk Jin. It's a self-fabricated scenario!
-What are you talking about! -Oh! So you could get another one?!
-You created this self-fabricated scenario to get another one, didn't you?! -Hey!
Look at his expression!
Why would I self-fabricated scenario?
But if someone took it, there's no way that absolutely no one know.
-You are the culprit! -It's you!
What? It's you!
-It's you! You! -It's you! You!
OK, then. There might be someone who has a grudge against Suk Jin hyung right now, so...
Exactly. Was that perhaps pure gold? Pure gold?
But that has no meaning. Why would anyone...
It's a bit more expensive than a regular daesang trophy.
See, it's expensive.
-But, who would. -It was very heavy, you see.
But how could that be more expensive than the daesang trophy?
-Yeah, but... -Oh!
-That's why it's you! -Yeah.
You are the culprit!
-Yoo Jae Suk! -I learned that fact just now!
I saw your facial expression darkening as you said that it was more expensive than a daesang trophy!
Why? Did you want it that much?
-But do we have to find this trophy? -Your eyes definitely shifted.
Can't we just forger it?
-Must we talk about the trophy for two, there hours? -Hey, find it for me.
-What did you say? -But hyung! The trophy...
-We came to find treasure. -Look all the doors!
...Great detective.
We know this would happen to we, the Hao Chao team invited a master detective.
Please come out!
-Oh! Do Hyun and Jedong Hyung! How...
Rock and roll baby!
Rock and roll!
Oh, seeing everyone here is very welcoming.
-Oh, but... -Hello.
-We came to find you your trophy. -Precisely.
-Sherlook Holmes? -Yes.
-How? -How?
Oh, you brought something.
-But it's the same colour as your clothes so... -What, you're detective, but you don't have a notepad?
-A detective must always have a notepad. -Is that so? -Of course.
Oh, a detective notepad...
Detective Rule No.1
-No.1 -Yes?
The crime.. crim...
At the scene of the crime...
procure the evidence.
I think we need to get some fingerprints.
-Fingerprints? -Yes.
With a brush...
-...The trophy case... -A brush?
-That part was what you had to do. -Oh, right.
-With a brush, did you say? -A brush.
-Oh, a brush! -Do we have one?
-You didn't bring it? -Yes.
What trophy will these people find for me?!
Go find the trophy quickly.
-You know where it is. -What are you doing? -I'll go find it.
-You know where it is? -Where it is?
I found it.
-Where? -Where?
It's in the chao chao's costume.
-What? -You found the trophy? -Yes.
-You found it already? -Is it OK for you to suddenly find it like this, hyungnim?
-It's really there! -Oh!
Oh, it's true.
When did it get in there?
See, I found it.
I'm a master detective.
Hey, Mr.Jesong Se Hyaop.
Why is Jedong just standing there not doing anything?
Say what?
I thought you would say something! Why are you not doing anything?
-Why are you squabbing? -Why are you getting angry?
-But... -No...
Never trust anyone.
Oh! Hyung!
Kim Jong Kook!
Noooo!
-What's this? -Quickly! Quickly!
Find the culprit.
We will now start the treasure hunt.
That's right.
-Treasure hunt. -The mission we received yesterday was a treasure hunt.
That's right, treasure. This is a treasure ship.
This ship needs set in February.
But the captain of the ship said he lost a treasure.
And he said he the person who finds the treasure can keep it.
Oh, really?
What?!
So, the captain is saying if we find the treasure we can...
Perhaps... the treasure is hid daughter? His daughter?
Oh, Chao chao!
-Chao chao! -Oh?
Chao chao!Chao chao.
Chao chao!
Oh, Mr,Do Hyun, you're going to the 4th floor.
Oh, you're 5th floor, Room 302. I think I shall go in first.
Oh, yeah, sure, do that!
Since you already know, I'll go now.
-And there are hints regarding this treasure hidden throughout this ship. -Ah, there are hints.
Is that so?
-It's a hint card looks like this. -Oh, the Death Note!
-And we'll confiscate all your cell phones. -What?
OK, you can get doing now.
Woow!
Let's go!
You have to follow them. Quickly now.
Now. Start!
Woow!
-Mine on the 6th floor. -Can we take the elevator?
-What floor is this? -What floor is this again?
We're on the 6th floor here.
-Oh, this is the 8th floor. -This is the 6th floor?
Wow, this is really long.
Hey, we might get lost here.
Is this it?
Oh! Kim Jong Kook.
Ah, my name tag is here.OK
Hints regarding the location of the treasure are hidden throughout the ship.
Acquire the hints and become the owner the owner of the treasure.
There can only on owner of the treasure.
Never trust anyone.
There are hints hidden throughout the ship.
Will you stick this on for me?
Please stick it well. So that it's hard to take off.
Wow, but this ship is really big!
I think... we may be around here right now.
I... I'm looking for the mission.
Wow this place.. There are so many rooms!
Ah, it's an individual competition.
You can't escape from my clutches.
Looking from the angle, it's a around here somewhere.
The angle is definitely pointing to here!
First. I lost this time as well.
-But there was no word about tearing off name tags. -There didn't need to be.
Mr. Do Hyun.
Talking about tearing off name tags... What are you two doing?
Both of you are very suspicions. Why are you acting like this?
There was no word bout tearing off name tags...
There's a movie that comes to mind after looking at you two.
Which?
Dumb and Dumber.
You're one to talk.
You just crashed into that while walking backwards.
You just look that way.
Wow.
Wooow
Why are you following me?
-I'm just passing by! -What...?
The structure of this ship is steady being stored in my mind.
Into my computer-like brain.
I'm thoroughly searching through this ship with my brain with an IQ of 250.
My eyes see in 4D!
I can see everything!
I cannot let this be! We must go back to where we were an hour ago.
The one who rewinds time!
The one who controls space!
Hey!
Wow, these lifeboats...
Hey! Mr.Do Hyun! I told you, we can't go around together like this.
What, no. I just came here myself.
Mr.Do Hyun! Try to look for it carefully!
Yes, yes...
I really like you a lot, Mr.Do Hyun!
Same here!
Wow, this is really breathtaking.
Hyung!
-What? -Did you find a hint?
No...
-Oh, but,,, -No, this isn't it.
You found something didn't you?
You're actually not supposed to be finding hints, Kwang Soo.
Hyung, we can work together.
With what?
You can share hints!
Because I have something very crucial...
-Really? -Hmm?
Let's get moving for now.
-And keep it a secret. -Hyung...!
Hyung, what do you have?
I... have nothing to fear.
Then why don't we ass our information together?
But hyung, why are you OK?
-What have, with what you have... -Hyung, what do you have.
-If you bring something... -Do you have something?
No matter what you find , you  need to have what I have .
-In the middle ,I... -Oh!
Suk Jin hyung!
Suk Jin out,Suk Jin out.
Hyung!
Suk Jin hyung!
Feel!
Kwang Soo! Kwang Soo!
Save me! Save me!
Kwang Soo, save me!
Noooo!
I'll avenge you... This one who did this to my hyung.
I'll definitely avenge you!
Kwang Soo.
Why are you running around for vengeance?
You were had, weren't you?
Hyung. What exactly are you, hyung?
Did you get to be the spy?
I'm not the spy, hyung!
If you're not, what are you getting vengeance for?
Suk Jin hyung was dragged off...
Go quickly. With your arms up.
Hyung, are you a soy?
Come up here when you find it.
It definitely feels like someone is following me.
How mysterious!
I think there will be something here!
Who is it?Who is it?Who is it?
You can't trick me!
Hyung!
-Hmm? -Hyung Suk Jin hyung was eliminated!
Suk Jin hyung was dragged off, with his mouth covered.
What did you say?
Oh, you scared me!
Hyung! Don't do stuff like this!
What? He was eliminated?
I was continuously with Jedong hyung. I was walking with Jedong hyung, but
Jedong hyung was never surprised.
-There must be something here! -You're saying that Jedong hyung was not surprised!?
Hey, we need to find these things quickly! What's going on?
-Jedong hyung looks like he's running around catching people. -What?!
He doesn't look like he's searching for things. He looks like he's searching for people!
-Who is that? -Shunsh!
-The two of them... -The two of them look like their working together...
Oh!
Hyung! Hyung, Jedong hyung is weird.
Why?
-He seems like he's trying find people. -Him and Hyun hyung, the two of them are acting weirdly!
Hyung! The two of them, they're coming here!
-Hey, is this a game where we're supposed to rip off name tags? -I don't know!
Before, Do Hyun hyung tried to tear off Jedong hyung's name tag.
-Ah, everyone...! -Mr. Do Hyun.
Ah, you...
-Why is everyone so not lively? -Hyung!
-The mission is... -Suk Jin hung was eliminated...
-So I heard. -You knew?
Oh, of course I knew.
-Then how are you so composed? -Why are you so composed?
Why are you so relaxed for your first guest appearance?
I'm not.
Suk Jin hyung was eliminated!
-Hey, for now, let's separate. -Suk Jin hyung was eliminated?
It's not something to be that shocked about.
Exactly...
I can't trust anyone.
704?
What is 704 2 degree piano?
Is it telling me to go to Room 704?
Oh!
You haven't left yet? Oh! Chao chao!
-Where are you going? -Yes?
You're going back up to Seoul with us, right?
-Yes, later we'll.. -Relax somewhere!
Take off the fur costume! It's hot!
What?
Ah, nothing, nothing.
There's nothing.
But it's room 704...
I think there definitely will be something here!
Huh?
Definitely. I think there will be one definitely!
Oh! See!
See, didn't I say?
Wow. Daebak, daebak.
As expected... As expected, I'm...!
Hao Chao. Hao Chao!
-Hao Chao! Hao Chao? -Hao Chao.
Hao Chao. Hao Chao.
What, what's going on?
It's here?
What?
No, nothing. Just curious about what you're doing.
-What? -Just wondering what you're doing.
Why are you doing that?
-Because I wanted to see you. -I'll tear off your name tag!
Hmm? Go ahead.
-What? -Go ahead.
You want me to rip it off? I really will!
If I say it in dialect, go ahead!
-What? -Go ahead.
Oh, please.
The hometown that I lived in
HaHa out! HaHa out!
You heard, right? The second I stared to sing.
You heard them say 'OUT', right? I'm going easy on you because it's you.
HaHa out! HaHa out!
What?
Hyung!
Ah!
Lee Kwang Soo out! Lee Kwang Soo out!
-Lee Kwang Soo out! Lee Kwang Soo out! -See!
What is this?
I don't know what's what at all.
Oh!
What is this?
What is this? See here.
What does 2,3 mean?
This is a symbol of Lupin.
Lu... Ah, this is that today, I see.
Lopin vs. Holmes!
Right?
This is a hint for the culprit.
This one is my hint.
What is this?
The culprit is among us.
As each of us gets eliminated, they're letting us know through these one by one.
Why are they still walking around?
Is this perhaps, from the Sherlock Holmes series... Baskers... Isn't there that dog?
Considering that Chao Chao came today, isn't it that?
Ah, it's been so long since I've watched the series, I can't remember.
Where is everyone?
Where is everybody?
It's Yoon Do Hyun sunbasenim.
Ah. What? Why are you locking the door?
Ah! Sunbaenim! Why are you doing this to me?
-No... -What did I ever do wrong?
-Why are you doing this to me? -But it's not like I'm a monster. Why are you acting this way?
Why are you doing this to me? What do you want?
Just.. that... you've been on the show for a long time, so I had a few questions.
You do think there is treasure?
Sunbaenim. It's not that I think there's treasure. I think you're the culprit.
-What? No. How could the guest be the culprit?
-You're luring us one by one, telling us you'll show us your green cards so you can tear off our name tags, right?
I wonder never play cowardly like that.
Then relax and come out later when you're comfortable.
Yes, sunbaenim. I'll see you later.
Gary, Gary! There's something strange!
-What is? -It's really strange!
Oppa! See! Hasn't Yoon Do Hyun sunbaenim shown you an A4 sized sheet of paper and asked you if you were searching for the cards?
I haven't spoken to him at all. I've been busy running away.
How could you just run away? You should have been searching for stuff!
-But there has to be cards! I was searching for cards! -Oppa, there's a chance there may be no cards left now!
None left?
I'm saying it may not be cards.
But.. then why did he show us his cards earlier?
This is not the time for us to be like this.
What's this?
Oh!
It's T-ARA.
Do these four have some link to Do Hyun hyung?
"First" "Floor" "Store" "Room"
Hyungnim!
You came to sing, right? Why are you going to the piano?
-No, no. -Huh? What's that?!
It's a bell.
-What is this? -What is that?
Hyung! Don't ring that! These could be a strange consequence!
Why would a bell that didn't exist before show up here?
Kim Joog Kook! Is that why it's a bell?
The hometown that I lived in
...that I lived in
-Why are you sitting down? -Don't tear off my name tag. -Hey, come here!
-Hyung. Why have you sat in front of the piano? -There's no use.
All of a sudden!
Why have you sat down?
Why have you sat down? Explain yourself quickly!
-Quickly! You're acting so strangely right now. -What is going on right now?
Why did you sit down there?
Don't keep looking at people's backs.
Hyung!
What's wrong with you? Why do you keep coming behind me?
Why is everyone like this? Everyone! Why is everyone like this?
Who plays the piano with their back?
Over there!
What is it?! Why'd you put the mic here?
-Gary! -Yes?
Why did you go?
Ah! It's so frustrating!
-Oppa! -Hm?
What's this Jingling noise?
What?
Ah, Mr. Do Hyun. What is your role here today? What is your role?
An invited singer.
What invited singer?
Find the culprit.
who is stealing your dream.
Even more than you think,
He is closer to you!
-Ni hao! -Ni hao!
Doesn't it feel like their telling someone our location?
What?What?
What?
Hey dongsaengs! Why did you come back again?
Ni hao!
No, why did you come back?
If it's hot, take this off!
Ice wa-ter!
Take it off. It's hot.
It's hot. Take it off.
Refreashing. Isn't it?
Why do you keep showing me your watch. Wait.
-Wait, wait! -...Expensive!
Something's strange.
I mean, why...
What?
They keep luring me...
Someone always is eliminated when they're with those two.
Why is he walking around with his watch off?
Here.
Hyung, this is the first time you've seen me wear a watch, right?
-Hyung, have you even seen me wear a watch? In the neighbourhood? -That's true!
Ni hao. Chao chao.
Ni hao.
Why did he show me his watch?
See! Room 704! See!
What? What? What? What?
Kim Jedong. Yoo Jae Suk, out! Kim Jedong. Yoo Jae Suk, out!
-Kim Jedong. Yoo Jae Suk, out! Kim Jedong. Yoo Jae Suk, out! -Huh? What's going on?!
Jedong hyung was eliminated?
What are you doing? Wait a minute! What are you doing?
Gary out! Gary out!
Come in quickly!
I found a hint.
474455668.
Page 474?
Ah, what is it?
What could this be? 474455668.
474455668.
It was put together like this because there's something definitely in this book, right?
I'm not sure how the hints are hidden.
I do think there will be something here...
What, two?
But.
It's in somewhere like this?
Ah, somewhere like this... These people are our staff, aren't they?
They're a part of the staff.
Where is this place?
It kind of looks like an engine room?
Ah, I was too focused on the outside decks.
Hyung, what are you doing?
What is that?
-You found one? -Yeah.
Let's see it.
There are not many people still alive now.
-See and you. -Yes.
-But hyung... -What are you?
-Eh? -What are you? You role.
And what are you, hyung?
Hyung! What is that? First show me. Everyone else has shown me, but you haven't, hyung.
I will never show you!
Why? Please show me...
-Hyung! -I will never.
What is up with that hyung?
-I will never. No. -Hyung, there seems to be no other answer.
I will never show you.
Hang on!
Sorry. Hang on! If I show you. I fell like it will be game over.
-Hyung! -Hey!
It's you, isn't it?!
-What am I? -He.. You! You're the culprit, the culprit!
Even more than you think, he is closer to you!
Why are you locking the door?
Ah! Sunbaenim! Why are you doing this to me?
We can't go around together like this.
What, no. I just came here myself.
Why have you sat down? Explain yourself quickly!
Don't keep looking at people's backs!
He.. You! You're the culprit, the culprit!
-You're the culprit! -I'm not!
-Hyung! -Hey, the culprit!
Ahh! No! You're the culprit! Ahh!
No!
-What? -He's the culprit!
I'm not...
Yoon Do Hyun, out! Yoon Do Hyun, out!
Ah, this is really...
Hang on...
Jong Kook oppa!
Kim Jong Kook!
-I found a hint! -What is it?
Oppa! And I found a truly crucial hint.
What is it?
I was at the root before, but while I was coming down, on the side where the piano, this was at the bar.
The Ricals of Sherlock Holmes.
And...
It was together like this.
Then we have to decipher this.
To me, this looks like page numbers, oppa.
Try to add all these up.
No, no. See, because it all falls perfectly.
-It splits into 474 Then 488, then 558. -Does it?
Then let's go to page 474.
474.
Page 466.
There's a lot of numbers on this page. Do you think it has to do with numbers?
1 minute before to 9:40.
...Chocolate...
-Page 558. -558.
558.
With this, there's just no answer.
There really is no answer.
-Oppa, let's try to clear our minds as much as possible and think simply.
You're saying it's all within the book? Within the book? Within the book...
Within the book...
Ah, we got all the way here, but we can't solve this, so...
Let's look at this.
Hang on...
Hey! 474,466,558?
Hang on, 474?
What is this?
The cuilprit is among us.
There definitely will be something.
You just have to be wary of everyone. No mater what.
Don't trust anyone.
What is it, oppa?
Suk!
Oh?
What is 2,3?
-No, no. -Huh? What's this?
A bell that didn't exist before no exists!
What is that?!
Crystal?
In this world, the one and only"Yoo Soo Jesong".
I love you forever.
Jin!
Suk Jin!
Ji Suk Jin!
Oppa, how'd you figure that out?
How'd you figure that out?
Oh, ah Meeting again like this...
-Happy New Year. -Happy New Year.
So, we thought hard and... Well, why don't you read this?
OK
You are the culprit. Without being caught by anyone, while using tricks, commit a perfect crime.
You succeed if you eliminate all of the Running Man.
-Because you said you wanted to become the protagonist. -Of course I do
Well, we are brainstorming, but
Yes, yes.
yoo Mr. Ji Suk Jin, must fill in the details.
-You want me to fill in the details? -That's correct.
I think that needs to be first.
Just from the feeling. How at ease I would fee.
Kwang Soo needs to stay a while...
I'll tear off Kwang Soo's last. Easily. With a light heart.
But the biggest problem is, if I'm alive till the end, they're get suspicious.
Why don't we do this?
I'll get eliminated first.
-You will yourself? -Just like always!
-Like always? -Yes, like always. Then they won't be suspicious.
-Very first? -Yes.
Suk Jin hyung!
Oh?!
The most important point is, when I get eliminated first, no one will be suspicious.
-Suk Jin hyung was eliminated? -Yes.
It's not something to be that shocked about.
Exactly...
Guys, I will show you what a perfect crime is.
I am the culprit!
Ji Suk Jin!
You have what you have to do, right? -Yes, I do.
Please do your best.
It'll be best if I get eliminated first, right?
I'll get eliminated and...
No one's coming, ahead.
Jedong!
Let's start. Cover my mouth, cover it.
-Hyung, what do you have? -If you bring something...
-Do you have something? -No matter what you find, you need to have what I have.
Suk Jin hyung!
-Hyung! -Kwang Soo!
It's started.
Where do we go? Do you know where to go?
Do you know where to go?
Let's go...
The first is a success.
-See -But.
-Who is that? -Jedong hyung is acting weird.
The two of them are strange! Both of them.
What kind of detective are you, really?
Oh, please.
Hyung, don't laugh.
Have you watched that anime, Metantel Conan?
Of course I have.
Why are you copying that?
-And I hear Suk Jin hyung was eliminated? -Yes.
Hyung!
No matter what you gather, just know that if you don't have what I have, it's useless.
What?
No matter what hint you find...
No matter what hint you find, just know if you don't have what I have, it's useless.
Don't confuse people with those strange speaches!
-I'm not ourlous at all. -Really?
You're just pretending.
Do you know what Suk Jin hyung was wliminated though?
Of course!
Why was he eliminated?
His name tag?
You don't even know that? You are pltful.
-Ah, everyone... -Mr. Do Hyun!
Ah, you...
-Why is everyone so not lively? -Hyung.
-The mission is... -Suk Jin hyung was eliminated...
-Then how are you so composed? -Why are you so composed?
I think I should rest.
Why are you resting?
What ... Did..What ... Did you do something?
I've done everything.
Hyung!
Ah, this is what I'm supposed to do! Act and get people confused...
This is a battle of the brains, I see!
Oh, you play piano well!
I think that hyung has something. He keeps following me.
Please continues to play, why are you leaving?
Hyung.
What are you doing?
If you play like that, how will I look?
What, what's going on?
Chao chao.
It's here? It's here?
Hey, come here.
Come in for a second.
Hyung, what's going on?
It's the all.
-What! Hyung! -Stay still.
This is my scenarlo.
Sure, speak.
Hyung, this was a self-fabricated scenarlo?!
Hyung! Your day had come this quickly?
Who's that?
Hyung!
-Catch him. catch him. -Hyung!
Hey! We need to catch him!
The hometown I lived in
HaHa out! HaHa out!
You heard, right? The second I stared to sing.
You heard them say 'OUT', right? I'm going easy on you because it's you.
Wait, wait.
-Wait, wait! -...Expensive!
...Gold watch. Expensive.
See! Room 704!
What?
Oh, Jedong was here, too? Jedong was here?
-What is this?! -I didn't see you, Jedong.
Hang on!
What's going on?
You are Sherlock Holmes. I am Lupin.
-It's all my soenarlo. -Room 704...
Search for Gary.
Gary, what are you doing? Let's see...
-Let's see. -Hyung, why'd you come in so suddenly?
Wow! Hang on!
Why are you like this? What are you doing?
I'm eliminating you.
This is my scenarlo. You are Sherlock Holmes. I am Lupin.
I don't know anything about these.
Killing two birds with one stone.
Parents and grandparents still living.
A total wreck?
Through hell and high water.
Hang on!
First floor storeroom!
I think that's right.
I should get to the first floor.
Hyung, what are you doing?
Hang on!
NO!
-What? -He's the culprit?
I'm not...
Am I out?
Hyung, the what is that?
Why did you tear my name tag off then?
-Bucause, hyung, before you...! But hyung! -We could have used this and found the treasure together!
-What? -Hyung, before, you...
Why did he rip my name tag off?
-Hyung, have you arrived? -Mr. Do Hyun!
Ah, hyung!
What are we doing?
What are you doing?
Joog Kook ripped my name tag off!
What?
Why did Joog Kook rip it off?
He ripped it off and said to me, 'Hyung, you're not the spy?'
Then... Then... Mr.Do Hyun, you don't know who the culprit is?
I don't know!
-Don't tell him. -Don't tell him. Don't tell him.
Mr. Do Hyun will find out what he watches this on TV.
You will be very surprised when you see the broadcast.
You will find it very funny when you watch the broadcast.
While he's eating he'll be watching the broadcast and go "Waht the hell!" and overturn the dinner table.
Hyung, you worked really hard today.
What id going on here?
-You don't know who the culprit is? -I don't.
I was going to show that to Jong Kook and search for it together.
You don't know, huh. Though it's in here.
-What does that mean? -I totally know it..
-Tis is the hint. -It's over for us anyway. For all of us, it's over.
He doesn't know at all.
Hyung, how do you decipher that?
-Right? -How do you decipher that?
This is "first floor storeroom".
-First floor storeroom. -First floor storeroom.
I said that before!!
When I found this, I said, it looks like there's a word in here... "First floor storeroom".
-That's right. -I really did think it was "First floor storeroom".
-I was thinking is it a storeroom on the first floor? -Why didn't you do that, hyung?
-Hyung, hyung! Do you think you were caught and brought here? -You were right with the "First floor storeroom".
-What? -Are you thinking you are here because you're caught?
The culprit was precisely.
you, Mr. Yoon Do Hyun!
-Candid camera! Candid camera! -You really didn't know?
We were all eliminated because of you,Mr. Do Hyun.
-Everyone, come out! -You still haven't figured it out?
-Jong Kook hyung! -I mean, really...
Joog Kook ripped your name tag off, right?
-Right? -Yes.
What? What are you talking about?
Hyung, you won. You can leave and go home!
You're trying to get rid of me and have a fun filming, aren't you?
-Because you won. -Hyung.
-This is the first floor storeroom. -Here?
Yeah. If you find your way here, you've completed the mission.
-Only the one person remaining loses. -That's right.
This is the first floor storeroom, look around!
-This is the first floor storeroom. -Hyung.
What are you doing, Gary?!
So you're saying that this place, where we are right now, is the first floor storeroom?
No, it's the 6th floor. The 6th floor!
Which side am I supposed to be a part of?
-What, exactly what is this? -Don't look at me like that!
-Ah, Golden Bell! -Wait! You said Suk Jin was eliminated.
Then why isn't he here?
Mr. Do Hyun, you're probably going to call us while watching TV going."Hey! All of you, come here!"
"Hey! You! How could you make someone look like that?!"
-Wow, this is deabak. -Oppa! Where are the words?
-You still haven't found it? -Yeah, where is it? where is it?
-You still haven't found it? -Ah, oh! Suk!
Suk!
I didn't see it because you had folded it down!
And while I was reading, I kept thinking, the sentences are continuations, so why'd they pick these pages?
Instead of page where sentences start anew.
...but it's a already been revealed, "JI".
It's just three words.
When I saw "JI" and "Suk", I...
-"Jin". -"Jin".
Then what's going on? Ji Suk Jin was eliminated before!
He was only pretending to be eliminated!
And he had kept saying he was being mistreated..
Tension, tension.
How is it over there?
They're there? They're there?
What about over there? It is safe? OK.
Escaping from him is escaping from him, but let's find the treasure first and lure him.
Then let's find the treasure first. First, the hints are...
See, we're here, but it could be outside...
-Do Wan was there and... -That's the engine room, isn't it?
It's the engine room.
Usually, machines, engines like these are in the basement, near the bottom.
And the celling is low, see?
First, let's go in that direction. Come.
Let's first try to find the engine room.
Keep me alive!
We have to stick together!
Keep a good lookout, front and back.
Today, I ,really...
Oppa, we won't betray each other today, right?
I'll use my whole strength today.
They'll come together from the place they were hidden.
The best method will be for me to hide here and...
I'll tear here off.
and the two of you will hold onto Joog Kook.
Oppa, engine room!
-Yeah, come down, It's down there. -Sorry.
Come! Ji Suk Jin is here!
Where?
What? What?
What!
Come! Ji Suk Jin is here!
Where?
What? What?
What!
No!
Wait! Hyung! Let's talk! And let me go!
Wait, wait.
Wait.
Let's talk!
Hyung!
It was perfect, wasn't it?
-No, we figured it out. -We figured it out.
-We figured out the pages. -What?
-We figured out the pages. -You figured out the book's pages?
Yeah.
But can the guards tear of my name tag as well?
They can't
-Oppa, right now... -Oh, the guards can't?
They're just not letting you come close.
Then those two can't tear off my name tag, right?
They can't tear off my name tag, right?
-Hey. -Right?
-First... -Oppa!
-First... They can't tear off my name tag... -Oppa! Oppa!
One of you come here!
-One of you, come here! -Oppa, quickly! I've grabbed hold on their legs!
You don't understand!
One of you, come here! One of you, come here!
- I've grabbed hold on their legs! -What don't I understand?
-One of you, come here! -What don't I understand?
Yes!
-We caught? -This hyung is really...!
How could you trick us about being the culprit like that?
-This hyung is really...! -I really elaborately crafted this plan!
What is this?
I shall give this to you.
Hyung, you really are ... dasbak.
Hyung, you are daebak.
-Wow -Wow
-Wow. -That's not small fry.
Wow
-Oppa! We did it! -Yes! We did it!
- We did it! - It's been such a long time!
You will see when you watch the show, but it was a perfect scenario.
Ah, but at the end... Eh!
No one actually heard the broadcast that he was eliminated.
-That's right. -We only heard through rumour.
-That's what I said. -I showed my elimination to two people.
Ah, you really spread that rumour.
-What is that? -How nice! It looks cool!
-You can use those name tags going forward. -Really?