-Two! –Is there?
Have you decided?
-Ah, it’s the first day of the new year.
–Space Controller, why are you wearing the same clothes as me?
Time controller, why are you wearing the same thing as Iam?
Ah, one person has to take it off, Space Controller
I’m seriously about to go crazy
-I’m seriously going crazy. – You really look identical!
-Why did I wear this jacket?-Are you jealous of Haroro’s character?
-No, Haroro... -Haroro’s very popular abroad.
He’s very envies after making me into this character.
That’s right, he’s trying to take everyone’s character...
The one who controls space.
Greedy person.
Ah, I’m seriously going crazy.
Ah, I’m seriously going crazy because of this Time Controller.
Time controller.
Space controller.
Sixth Sense.
Duplicator.
Tear it quickly!
when are you going to Europe,Europe
Ah, we're working that out now.
It’s really awesome.
Mong Ji’s going too?
He said he’s going alone.
He’s going alone?
Ji Hyo looks so lunxiuriou.
Is it the Serengeti, the Serengeti?
I put some effort before coming to the airport.
-Ah, is that so? – Blank Fashion.
Lollo! Lollo!
What are we doing now?
Why are we at the airport?
Before the race, we have to form teams.
-Ok. –Oh.
-There are a total of four teams today. –Four teams?
-What? –Four teams in all.
-Ok, this is the first team. – Ok.
Gary and Haha.
Hey, Lollol!
-Oh my god! – Hey, don’t you think the other teams will be equally weird?
Haha is going to be my ‘lollol’ today?
Don’t worry, if we lose we’ll just turn back time.
-Yes, Lollol! –Yes.
-The second team. –Yes?
The recent trend, the Easy Brothers.
Easy!
-Wow, he called them ‘trend’.-Feel! Touch! Cross!
Ok, this is the third team.
Yoo Jae Suk and Kim Jong Kook.
-What? –Wow, that’s too strong.
I’m with someone who can’t see 5m ahead of him?
No, we’re on the same team?
Jong Kook and I... hey.
They’re too strong.
If you can see 5m ahead and I control space, then...
Then we’ll definitely win.
Soon, arriving through the door, are five Korea’s hottest Hallyu idols.
SNSD?
-There will be one guest in each team. – Okay.
Also, Ji Hyo especially has two of them.
Ah, I hope they’re girls.
Give Ji Hyo two female guests.
Extremely young kids.
-The Hallyu idol on the same team as Gary and Haha will be revealed.
Oh, it’s a female.
Be my last love!
For a guy like me the answer is you !
I’ll love you forever!
-Oh, who is it, who is it? – Oh!
Sulli?
Sulli, it’sSulli!
Oppa, you’re tired right?
Where?
Oppa, we did it!
Who?
-Wow! –Sulli, Sulli!
Here
The answer’s me.
Ah, thanks Sulli!
Sulli, it’s been so long.
Why have you become even prettier?
Sulli, where are you going?
Sulli, we... where did you go after drinking the tea that other time?
Where exactly did you go?
-Ah, is Sulli in that team? –Ok, Sulli’s the best.
Jong Kook, let’s have a look at ours.
We won’t let your hands touch a single drop of water.
Who is it?
-Oh, it’s Sohee! –Sohee!
Oh, it’s Sohee!
It’s really been a long time.
Hello.
Daebak!
-You’re not welcoming her, you’re just like fans. –How so?
-Your welcome is seriously like a fan. – Oh, Sohee.
We seriously have not seen Sohee in a while?
Hyung, it’s too awkward, welcoming like this.
How can you let her feel out of place?
Have you prepared for transportation?
If not, we...
Come here Sohee.
Oh, I’m really nervous.
I haven’t done this for so long.
Come out quickly!
Oh, it’s Hyorin.
Hello.
Curious Who am I with?
It’s us.
Ah, it’s like this?
Ah, I ...
-Don’t be like this. Ah, we’re no joke recently. –We’re the trend!
-We even got first once. – Exactly, first.
Ah I’m the newble here, so I wanted to come out first.
I really didn’t want to be with oppas.
What are you saying when we’ve just met?
Hey, your voice is my age.
-I can only hear her voice. –Please look after me.
Thank you.
Ok, Ji Hyo’s alone!
-Our Sohee’s totally at ease. –Hey, seems like it’s two guys.
I think it will be two guys.
I really have, two of them?
It’s Min Ho?
It’s Min Ho, Min Ho!
Hey! Today, today we’ll definitely win.
Hi Si Won. Hello.
Hey, your expression’s really happy.
Get lost, all of you!
Hello.
Ah, Si Won!
Why are you like this to your dongsaengs?
Don’t be annoying, get lost.
I’m really touched.
Be on the same team as noona.
-What did Song Ji to be this lucky? – What, why aren’t you coming here?
You be quiet.
Sohee,Sohee!
-Hyorin, Hyorin!-Sulli, Sulli!
Oh, today’s really too daebak.
Now we’ll explain today’s race.
Today is the 1st of January.
To celebrate filming the first race of the year, a Math Race.
Pass each mission to get numbers.
Using the numbers received
the team who gets a final answer of 1 wins the Math Race
We’ll start the race immediately.
We start running from now?
Please set off directly for the carpark to receive your number cards.
The faster you reach, the more numbers you can choose from.
After choosing your number cards
go directly to the first mission location.
Ok, start!
Let’s go!
Where do we go, where?
Quick. Hey quickly, quickly.
Where do we go, where do we go?
The carpark’s on the right
Where are they going?
The direction is wrong?
Didn’t you say you’re good at running?
Ah, I can’t run because it’s too funny!
Run !
Let’s look over there.
Excuse me, the person in the fur coat, move aside!
I was the first
Hyung, it’s there! There!
Don’t be excited.
Don’t keep going straight. Look left and right.
Be careful, be careful!
Excuse me, sorry! Sorry.
Haha Hyung has already gone there.
Where exactly did Suk Jin Hyung gone to?
But this is amazing.
I was really hoping not to be with you and Suk Jin oppa.
What kind of words are these?
Found it! It’s there!
Faster! Faster!
Okay, okay, okay.
You guys are the first to arrive.
Just choose two numbers from here.
Let’s choose one and nine, hyung.
One and nine? Won’t that be too far for substraction?
-Friends? –Friends, friends. –Five, four, three, two, one!
-We’ve decided. –Friends.
Take it away, take it away.
I came alone, it’s okay right?
It’s okay, just choose on your own.
Five, four, three, two, one.
Three, six.
-Hyung, didn’t we calculate to get one? – We must get one.
Then let’s choose neighbouring numbers.
Four, five. Or, one, two.
-The minus method is also counted. – Death’s four.
-Why are yo so tough? – That’s too extreme.
-Death’s four and the first one. –Okay.
Why aren’t they coming? Thar team...
They there. They’re coming right now. They’re running.
You guys are quite a match.
-You chose already? –I ran here.
You did well.
That team is really awkward, really!
Talk to each other a little!
Jong Kook, look!
So you don’t know how we’ve become so close now?
Are you worried? Or are you not?
I’m very nervous right now.
Really? Don’t be worried.
-Okay, let’s go! Sulli, let’s go! – Go!
Go!
Let’s set off also.
Head to the "I" theme park in Bucheon and look for the Running Man flag.
Min Ho knows how to drive too?!
Yes I can drive a little.
-How old are you? – 21 years old.
-20 years old? - 21 years old.
How old is Si Won?
I was born in year ’87.
How old is noona?
Min Ho and I have a ten year difference.
-Liar! – Really.
Isn’t noona just in her twenties?
Noona is in her early thirties
Noona really doesn’t look like it, really.
When I think of coming to the show
I really wanted to be in the same team as noona.
-Really? – Yes.
In Running Man, it’s been a long
while since I’ve heard these typs of words.
Whenever I watch the show, I’m always very sad.
If you have younger brothers to take care of you,
All the oppas don’t look at me as a lady.
-It doesn’t matter to me now. –When?
Even when I see female guests, I also feel very happy.
We chose 2 and 8 right?
So we are going to get 1 later?
-We can add and subtract to get it done... -Is it? –Yes, it is.
-Maybe we can also use division... -Division.
Sohee,Sohee, Sohee.
There might be a square root sigh also!
What square root? I don’t like this, always being like this...
Perhaps you don’t know square root?
Of course I know it.
But I think better not to use that.
Want to try testing me using square root?
Stop saying square root, stick to the simple ones.
The one everyone can use.
But this is simple!
How’s it simple?
Do you know what Sohee is saying in her mind?
Can you be a little quieter?
It’s also been a while...
Why are you talking so much?
Just... like that.
Because it’s quiet, I feel more comfortable.
Oh, we’ve found it, we’ve found it!
-Where? –Over there.
I feel so happy seeing that thing.
Let’s quickly get off the car!
Oh! There isn’t anyone here yet?
What is this?
What is that?
-You see the airplanes here right? – Yes.
From now on, sit on the plane and go on a world tour.
-Because you are a Hallyu star. –I see.
-During the flight
you will pass by the miniature versions of Asia and the US.–Yes.
Use your arms to make a horse to carry the female member.
Quickly travel around the US and Asia,
And there would be a mission waiting for you.
Okay, then squat down.
I’m sitting. Sorry.
Min Ho, let’s go!
-One, two, three! – Why are you so light?
Noona, why are you so light?
It doesn’t seem to even reach 60kg.
Where are we going?
-Let’s go to the US first. –The US, go!
-Noona is really light. –Really light!
This is really good , you’re very light!
I’m so sorry, really.
This is really amazing, you’re really very light!
Oh, they are miniatures.
Great wall of China!Great wall of China!
-I’ve also seen the Great wall of China special! – Ni Hao
Over there!
We’ve found it!
That, right
Over there! Running Man.
-Where? –There, there.
Okay, please put me down now!
-Airplane landing! – One, two, three, swoosh
As expected, different from our members.
-You’ve just finish your Asia-USA tour, -Yes.
At the United States area you’ve just passed,
How many buildings were shorter than Haha?
What?
I’ll give you 5 seconds.
Five, four
White house!
Three, two,
-Quickly say it. – Two, two, two!
What are names of those two?
-Yes, what are the names? –Five.
-Four, -Wait a minute.
Three,
-Library? –Two.
-What is it? I even forgot the name. – One.
Head back to the starting point, set off.
Can’t be.
-Oh, look at this, look at this. –Sohee, Sohee.
Has the feeling come?
We’ve already arrived, haven’t we?
-Because you came with a Hallyu star. –Yes
Now sit on the airplane and travel around the world.
Even Sohee is laughing.
Private airplane?
-They have already arrived? –Where?
They have already arrived, we must hurry.
You guys have already gone and came back?
It’s not a joke, oppa.
These boys all still young. They carried me easily.
-Youth is life. –Ah, this ajummah, what you’ve said is so exaggerating...
Then let’s see how light Sohee is.
Really very light, surprisingly lighter than what I’ve imagined.
-Yah, we are... -Stop joking.
Really.
-Hey, is she really light? –She really is.
-Have a good look! –We will carry Sohee up to fly, take a good look!
Sohee, you must move around the wings like this.
After that, do this.
Ah, really...
-Our team, our team. – Ah, really...
Right, and then...
-What are you doing right now? –Ah, seriously.
Ah seriously, really.
One, two, three.
Let’s move.
Set off.
Oh it’s done, it’s done.
-Hey, we’re flying! –Sohee, is it fun?
Yes!
-Sohee. –Hey, this is totally flying.
This can totally fly.
Hey, we can see their legs shaking.
You’re lagging behind.
Hey, Sohee’s really very light.
It’s totally flying, flying.
It’s like taking a plane.
-Ah hyung, we have to hurry, hyung. – Oh, we can’t fall behind.
Min Ho’s tired.
No, that’s not it.
Ji Hyo noona’s very light.
Look at Jae Suk hyung’s legs now.
Jae Suk hyung’s legs are wobbling!
Jae Suk hyung’s legs!
Where is it?
-Why is it so far? – It’s really huge!
Over there.
Isn’t it here?
-I’m sorry. –No.
Hyung, we didn’t look around on our way here?
I didn’t see anything.
It’s over.
Ok. Should I give the questions or not?
Give it of course.
-You’re starting again. –No, you seem like you didn’t notice anything.
-In the US Zone... -Yes.
-How many structures are shorter than Haha? –Huh?
-Hyung, what are you saying? – You seem to have more muscles than Jong Kook hyung.
It’s done, it’s done.
Good.
-Ok, let’s go too! –What are you guys doing?
Min Ho, what are you guys doing?
What’s with you?
Now you’re, now you’re like this with guys when I’m not around?
-It’s Tuesday today! –Ah yes, I’m sorry.
-Do you know what’s our relationship? We’re friends. –Friends.
-Firstly, our mental age is extremely similar. –Five, six.
Jump around.
-Looks good. –Now do you hear the sounds of Haha’s short tongue?
"Hup, Hup!"Oh, I really can’t take it.
-don’t you know? I have a short tongue. –Omoomo.
-My back. –Don’t swing, don’t swing your legs!
Don’t do that!
-You went past Asia and US right? –Yes.
-In the US Zone, how many structures are shorter than Haha?
Shorter than Haha?
--Shorter than Haha? –Five...
Four...
-Did you see? – You should have seen it.
-Two... -I didn’t see.
-Iwas laughing. –Empire State Building!
Four
-That’s wrong –No.
Please set off again.
-Will this question remain the same? –Set off!
-Hey, he just won’t answer you. –He won’t answer.
Is this ok, like this?
-No. – How should I sit on your shoulders?
-That’s right, don’t move. –Like this?
Don your feet hurt? I think your shoulders must be aching.
Ah, just stop asking
-Ah, it’s hot! –Hey Sulli.
Yes, yes.
Sulli, your oppa can’t do it.
In the US zone, how many structures are shorter than Haha?
-No, this height now? –Three...
Two...
Three.
One. That’s wrong.
Please return to the starting point.
In the US zone, how many structures are shorter than Haha?
The same question?
Why are you asking it again?
One!
-Ah, hang on for awhile. –That’s wrong.
-Ah, why did you answer on your own?
Ok, return to the starting point again.
There are three.
Say it softly, say it softly.
The first one, the Grand Central Station.
Also, the Lincoln Memorial.
Also, the White House.
One is wrong.
What did you say?
You can’t land there.
-No, we were waiting! –Ah, yes.
Ah, how many, how many times have we been here.
Saw that?
-Saw that? –She watched our show, you’ll get shaken by the collar.
In the scene from the Battle of Hansan, how many Turtle Ships were there?
Oh my god!
-What’s that? –Two Turtle Ships.
-And then? –Seven... -That’s right.
Oh my god!
Sohee, how many?
One, two, three!
Two!
Correct.
We did it.
-Hey, what’s this? –You’re the first to pass!
-Do you see these numbers in front of you? –Yes.
Pick two, from these numbers.
We picked 2 and 8 earlier.
Yes.
Don’t we have to make ‘1’?
So just take 1.
What are you up to?
We have to make ‘1’.
-We have to get 1 but ... -We have to make ‘1’ so let’s take 1 and go.
No, but there will be some addition and subtraction or something like that.
-Ah, this is seriously... -7?
So 7?
3?
-How about a ‘2’? –Sorry.
Sohee, just pick whichever one you want.
-Hey, let’s turn around. –So we don’t know what Sohee does.
Ah, do what do you want.
Ok, 4 and 7.
Why did you choose 4 and 7?
This is because, we picked 2 and 8 earlier.
-If we subtract 7 we get 1.–Equals 1.
When we divide 4 we get 2.
-Seems like it’s not it?–Let’s go first.
-Hey, you don’t seem very satisfied? –Ah, what are you saying?
Math Race. Next, find the Running Man banner at the eatery.
-P Vietnamese eatery. –Let’s go.
Ok!
-Sohee, now you’re really... -My desire to win is burning now.
I can see it burning.
You’re gradually becoming more enthusiastic.
This is rather difficult.
-Seems like it’s something to do with eating. –It looks like it, an eating mission.
It’s all right.
Don’t be afraid. It’s all right, it’s all right.
-It’s all right. –Hello.
I’m filming.
It seems like we’ll be eating while filming.
Yes, it’s interesting.
What a relief.
-It’s my dad. –Ah, so it’s your father.
-Hey, he must also be, calling to see if you can eat well while filming.
That’s right.
Yes I told my father that I’d be filming today.
"Oh, I’m filming Running Man today."
-Dad wad like, ‘Oh, really?’ He likes it a lot. –Ah, really?
-My dad likes watching it a lot. –Ah, is that so?
Ah, even you father’s supporting us.
We have to work hard.
We must work hard to win.
I feel we should take 3 and 6.
-How about we take 1? -1 and 9.
So let’s take 1 and 9, 1 and 9.
1 and 9, I chose 1 and 9 too.
Take the smallest one, then take the middle one.
2,5,2,5*!
-Please choose. –What about 8 and 3, 8 and 3?
8 and 3. Because 8 times 3 is 24?
-We’re now going to an Italian restaurant. –Yes.
-There’s definitely an eating mission at the restaurant. –Yes.
-For instance memorizing, the order of food presented to us.
So we just have to remember everything then?
Firstly, we’re not just there for eating!
So that means we should pay attention until we leave the restaurant?
Min Ho’s tensing up
Noona’s really very light!
Oh, today’s really daebak.
Oh, it’s here.
-It’s here, here. –Running Man, Running Man!
-That’s right, so we’re the first. –Hurry.
Here?
Hello!
Oh, what’s this?
Hyorin, Sistar.
-Today’s the New Year special. –Yes!
-They’re messages sent in from international fans. –Ah, seriously?
It’s written for our members as well as the guests that have come on the show.
Hey, dumpling Sohee.
Show us the power of the Commander.
Hey, we’re seriously grateful.
What’s this?
Please think carefully before ordering.
-WhenIwatched, it’s about eating sequence.
Of course. Right, that could be it.
Just eat whatever you want to eat because it’s the new year
Wow, seriously? We can eat what we want?
So Hee was just on the phone with her dad.
She said there would be food to eat while filming.
Order something delicious, order whatever you want to eat.
Sohee, what do you want to eat?
This one and B1.
Ah, fried chicken drumettes with garlic sauce.
Don’t order that.
Why order chicken drumettes?
I got it. Ah, you’re seriously...
Ah, you’re just...
I just want to eat chicken wings, why must you interfere?
The team leader isn’t settled.
Ah, our stances are too different.
-Between us, it’s rather... -Our views are very different.
Yes, the way we talk is also different.
-Ah, his driving style doesn’t match mine too. –It doesn’t match.
Ah, seriously.
Oh, they all seem to be here.
All your dishes are here.
Yes, yes!
Ah man, so fragrant.
It really looks good.
Ah, thank you.
Chicken curry fried rice, spicy seafood fried rice.
And how about Ansung’s beef with rice noodles?
Did you say Ansung beef?
Anshim(tenderioin), anshim beef with rice noodles.
What are you doing continuing to order nonsense?
Three.
Ah, so tasty.
Ah, these are all foreigners?
Really?
She’s known as "Song Ji Hyo the Ace".
"Ji Suk Jin’s singing is not too bad."
"I nominate Lee Kwang Soo to be Spy."
I love you.
Oppa, look at this one.
"Yesterday I saw you as a person." Gary.
He said I look like a person.
Before both teams finish their food,
List the areas you hope the opposing team will change from last year.
-To each other? –Yes.
But is one team finishes eating, the exchange ends.
The more you say about each other the more advantageous it is.
We have to eat fast.
Do we start now?
-Yes. –I wish Jae Suk Hyung would get rid of everything but green.
-Iwish Jae Suk oppa would throw away his glasses.
I wish Jong Kook gets rid of his muscles.
I wish Jong Kook wouldn’t hit people.
I wish Sohee won’t be pretty ever.
I wish Sohee would get rid of that team
I wish Haha oppa would throw away his shoe lifts.
Hey, don’t you know I don’t wear them?
Hey, how old are you?
Hey, you’re so childish.
-But Sohee... -No Sohee, Sohee speaks very softly but they hit hard.
-I wish Jae Suk oppa wouldn’t make the clucking sound. –Oh, how...
-How did you know that? Oh!
I wish you wouldn’t stick your tongue out while eating.
-Iwish Jae Suk hyung wouldn’t pull his pants so high. –Oh, oh?
I wish Jong Kook oppa got rid of the velns on the back of his arm.
Ok Gary, I wish he’d give up his position as the Ultimates Survivor.
I wish Jae Suk oppa would get rid of the grain of rice on his left hand.
Where were we?
I want you to stop locking yourself every midnights to watch videos.
There’s no more hard disk space left to store them.
-I’m going crazy. –Throw them all away.
I wish Si Won, would get rid of his tendency to act cool.
I wish Min Ho wouldn’t be so noisy when exercising.
Ah, I didn’t do that.
Firstly, I don’t like Kwang Soo hyung’s dressing.
Someone said he wears leggings and short T-shirts.
How could you do that, Kwang Soo?
Why did you do that?
Hey, you’re on our side.
We’ve finished all our food.
Ok, this team can’t say anything about Yoo Jae Suk’s team anymore
Haha!
-I want you to stop your obsessing with beautiful stars.
if you get rid of yours first.
I wish you’d get rid of your mic.
You want me to stop talking? She’s really good.
I wish you’d remove one stroke from ‘Haha’.
Heehee?
I wish you’d throw away wet tissue after using it.
Ah, yes, I’m sorry.
Have you all finished?
We’re all done!
I’ll give you the mission.
Everyone, will write down everything the other party
said about you onto the memo notes and stick it onto yourself.
When the music’s playing, dance around to shake them all off.
Jae Suk has 16 pieces.
So Hee has 6 pieces.
Kim Jong Kook has 16 pieces.
-Why do I have so many? –All of them have to be shaken off to succeed.
I got it.
I have confidence in this event.
-Hyung, I’ll paste it for you. –Ah, yes, I got it.
-Ah, stick it on lightly!-Ah, yes, I know, I got it seumdwa!
Ah, why do I have so many?
There’s really ‘rice grain’.
Ah, what’s with this ‘rice grain’?
-Ah, you didn’t eat your rice.
Ah, didn’t I eat it when Sulli said it, why is it still being pasted on?
Hey, throwing away my passion, throwing away the ‘Grassshopper’, what do I still have left?
-Well, what should I do? – Live as a shell now!
I’m seriously going crazy.
Blood vessels.
Hitting people, eating fast.
Hey, protein...
We’ll start the music.
They’ve all fallen off right?
Ah, hurry up!
Ah hurry, hurry!
Ah, this won’t come off.
Ah, why can’t you get this off?
Hey, ‘pretty’ just won’t come off, Sohee.
Looks like you can’t change your face!
Truly, ‘chest up’ isn’t coming off.
Oh, seems like they’ve all come off.
Oh, like this, like this! Hey, do this!
There’s still one left!
Come off!
Please!
Please come off!
Oppa, there are three.
-Hyung, what are you...-Ok, done.
Hey, get off quickly!
Why won’t the one on hat come off?
Done.
Good one.
-Let’s, not stick them on glasses! –It’s done, it’s done.
Ah, this is seriously...
Are you doing a perm?
Hey, you’re giving me a perm!
-Are you getting a straight perm? –This is a straight perm.
Don’t do it, Haha.
It’s done.
Start!
Oh, it’s so scary.
Jong Kook hyung’s so scary.
Wow, Jong Kook hyung’s really scary.
There’s one under your cap, under your cap!
Where?
Under your cap!
Do it to the front!
Good!
I’m not going to be bouncing around, I’m really going to dance.
I’m going to have fun.
Ready, start!
Ah, these aren’t falling off! Oh, my shoe!
I got a shock!
Be careful, you might get hit.
Pass!
We did well.
We did really well.
Sohee, you’re happy, aren’t you?
Let’s choose the start and the end.
This is the mission.
I’m done.
Are we done?It has all dropped.
Success!
What shall we choose?
2,4.
-What should we choose? -5,6.
We choose 5,6.
Ok, we’re here.
What are you doing here, PD?
Use the numbers you have received so far to form the number 1.
You need to find at least 8 operations.
The cards on the arms can be stolen.
You need to find at least 8 arithmetic operations.
You get them by pasting them onto your arms, but
You must be careful because the other teams can steal them.
Okay, we’ll stick these onto your arms.
Where should we start searching? Where is it?
Here... we roughly know the way around
Since the stairs are like this...
I think there might be one at the waiting room at top.
-Right? –Yeah. The waiting room or the rehearsal room.
-You go take a look with Sohee, I’ll go somewhere else to search.
Oh! Here!
Square root, square root!
-We might need it. – Let’s just paste it first.
We can use it on 4 to change it to 2.
Don’t get it stolen.
They’re in filming.
-Oh hyung, hello! – How are you here?
I’m currently filming.
Have you seen the other members?
Like Jae Suk or Jong Kook.
He didn’t see them!
There isn’t any here.
-Did you go to the filming studio? –No.
Let’s take a look.
It might be on the audience seats.
Where’s Hwi Jae? I’m in the middle of filming Running Man.
-Oh, really? – Where’s Hwi Jae?
Over there.
Ah, hello, hello.
Ah, oppa is looking for this
I also know about it.
Oh! Yoon Jung, tell me.
Where is it?
I actually saw a few of them.
Where are they, just tell me.
I saw a few.
Don’t tell others...
Really?
But what will you do for me?
If I find it, I will credit the happiness of victory to you.
Can’t you sing a song for us?
I can’t do it, I don’t know any songs.
I need to go film the show.
Jae Suk!
Hyung, I’m filming right now.
-You’re here for the hint? –Yes, hint.
Hello.
-You’re here for the hint? –Yes.
-There is a large hint here. –Here?
-He is filming Running Man right now. –Yes, I am filming Running Man.
The hint is among us.
So , the hint , we’ll tell you, but...
You need to sing a song for us.
No matter what, rules are rules.
-If you get above 92 points we will give it to you. –But 92 points is...
92 points...
Everyone please cheer for Yoo Jae Suk, who would be singing a song.
-Song, what song? –That song.
-Which song? –Who failed Hong Kyung Min’s song again?
-Shaky Friendship –Ok, Shaky Friendship
Music, start!
I’m not really familiar with the song, it’s been a while since I sang it.
Above 92.
No, this shouldn’t be. Why do I keep liking my friend’s girl?
Why, as I tell myself I can’t do this inside my heart
Is this girl the only thing I can think of? –you’re doing well!
Why am I so anxious about this call
that I received from her without may friend’s knowledge?
I could just cooly refuse but why can’t I refuse this girl?
You already made an error!
I’m really going crazy. I don’t even know myself anymore
To question the friendship of a long-time friend over a girl
I’m so distressed
I’m so sorry my friend, for a moment I deceived you
Until now my friendship to you must still be lacking
Understand my friend, our friendship for a moment
It was just a test of someone who was jealous of our friendship
Please think of it like that!
92 points, 92 points.
-Ah... 92... -88 points.
Jong Kook oppa come up too, aren’t you a team?
Give us the chance to get 92 again.
-If Jong Kook can get above 92, we’ll give you the sign. -What?
What song are you going to sing?
- Something that you sing often, a classic. -Lovable.
- The next song is "Lovable" - Alright.
If it’s below 92, you have to retire!
Alright, let’s have Lovable!
- Music please! - This is a bit sudden.
Oh You’re lovable from head to toe
I feel proud with you as my woman
Waiting is fun now and even the air is sweet
I love you like this - Where is it?
Thank you!
Where is it, Yoon Jung?
- Need 92 points, 92 points. - You’re really going to tell us right?
Really?
Even if the world is hard, when I see you,
I can feel the wind in my heart
Is this life?
Or is this happiness?
Whatever it is, I’m feeling it now
From head to toe, you are... Lovable
And my affection comes naturally
Waiting is fun now and even the air is sweet
I love you like this - How many points?
Quickly please, quickly please.
One Cut!
- Quick give it to us! Quick! - But...
Isn’t it very easy for someone who sings their won song to get 95 points?
Fine, I’ll give it to you now.
It was hidden to this degree.
- I was nervous hiding it. - We don’t need a multiply sign.
Oh, sorry about that.
What are you going to do?
- They got a multiply sign! - Where?
- Jae Suk hyung got a multiply. - Really.
- Just take it. - Excuse me but is it alright if we search at the back of the studio?
- Yep, sure. - Just for a short while.
If this gets aired, the audience will be really shocked.
It’s fine, our program is let the viewers be relaxed in the morning, it’s alright.
Really, to the beloved audience...
- Really sorry, because of Running Man to suddenly appear... -Jae Suk hyung!
- Go! Go! - I have to greet first!
Ok, ok, cut!
- Thry found a minus. - Well done!
Then... If... So suddenly...
Everyone... Sunday morning... 2011...
One cut!
How did you find that
Good job.
Ending, ending.
- Have a happy new year! - Thank you!
- Then, we’ll leave now. - Thank you.
You worked hard.
Thank you. We’ll be going.
Is it okay to tear it off?
Ah, Director, hello.
Thank you, director.
Is there none here?
I really can’t find anything.
Hyorin!
Noona, come out for a while.
Who are you to tell me to go there!
- I can’t ask you to come? - What?
- I can’t ask you to come? - Unnl!
- You think you can order me? - Why?
- I think she has a lot. - There’s nothing here.
In her pocket.
Hyung! Ji Hyo is hiding them in her pocket.
Hyorin, just go,
Wait!
Quickly!
Ji Hyo!
It was mine.
Hey this is...hold on.
He ate it!
Don’t swallow it!
- The brackets are useful. - Exactly. The brackets are really useful!
It’s really important.
Brackets are really useful.
Sohee...
Sohee, how did you see that one?
- Kook Jong! - What?
I’m actually not good at finding these things.
But today...
I seem to be doing well!
It’s really big.
Jae Suk oppa.
Found it!
Good job.
- Sohee, where did you find that? - Here.
Hello sir.
Hello.
Can we look around?
- Come on in. - Thank you!
This is where they keeo their set equipments,
Jae Suk oppa.
- Sohee, you found one? - Yes.
Where?
Over there.
How do you find it so quietly?
Really?
- How many do you have? - Two.
- Hyung, you? - One.
I have four.
You’ve worked hard! Hello!
Hyungnim, perhaps have you seen any maths signs around?
Like this...
There was something behind the stage. A minus sign, but someone took that.
Ah really! We need a subtraction sign.
Everybody! This is the easy brothers!
Not only here in Korea but they are all over the world!
The one and only easy brothers!
Feel, touch, cross!
Thank you!
Can’t find any?
Did you know that Jong Kook hyung has taken all of them?
Let’s team up to snatch Jong Kook hyung’s!
Where is Jong Kook hyung?
Don’t know. Let’s look around.
- Hyung, I will go up. - Jong Kook oppa is too scary!
Si Won, they took all of it after the singing.
What are you doing here?
It is not a bad idea that we form an alliance with each other.
To be honest, we do not know how to use the square root sign.
Are you looking for a chance?
You aren’t looking for a chance to do something to us right?
How could I...
Hyung!
What do you need now?
Give me an plus sign.
We don’t have an plus sign.
We’re leaving first then!
Sohee, what’s that?
I don’t have anything.
- Don’t you have one right here? - I don’t!
It’s just below here.
Hyung, What are you doing? We don’t need brackets!
Swap with us for a plus sign then!
- I got it, give me the bracket. - Together, together.
One, tow, three!
Shy did you snatch it away!
You con artist!
Live your whole life like that!
Hey, these kids seriously!
What are you doing? Let us go out!
Sorry!
Why can’t we even snatch one!
Let’s go somewhere else.
Suk Jin hyung snatched mine away.
Ah, Jong Kook hyung really has a lot!
No, there isn’t.
Really! You can find them yourself!
Hey!
Our team does not even have a single person!
What are you doing?
Why are you suddenly like this after being so quiet?
That’s ours!
Wow, this is awesome!
You guys... Really!
You all are too much! Treating me like this...
What are you doing?!
Where is the rest of my team?!
Have you calculated it?
Nah, let’s just use 2 plus signs and 3 minus signs.
Dong Hoon, let’s not show the image of us trying to calculate.
You are my...
When we do not know how to calculate, who will comfort us?
Calculus.
What is this!
When you are lonely.
When you are lonely you have calculus!
Unnl, I was there.
What did you find?
I found this division sign.
What’s more important is that I found this minus sign.
We have three minus signs!
- There is 10. - Now we can move out!
- Both of us will protect noona. - Okay!
See, they are really fast!
They really wiped out this whole area.
Sohee, where are you going?
Where are you going?
You are going to steel from them? Sohee!
Why did you run out?
Jong Kook opp!
Sohee, this is great!
Many division signs?
- Huh? - Many division signs?
No division signs.
Isn’t that one!!
Jong Kook hyung isn’t here?
Huh?
We have 3 while you have 2...
- Jong Kook is right here... - Where?
Why did your expression change?
Hey, move a bit!
Ah, what kind of camouflage do you have, hyung!
- Why did Suk Jin hyung take mine away just now. - Why?
Didn’t he tear way those on my arms?
Hey, hey! Sohee found one! Sohee found one!
- Sohee found another one! - Really...
Hey, Sohee!
Go away!!
How are you so able to find so much?
- How did you find it? You are really great! - Where did you find it from?
You really can find these things!
- Ok, let’s verify if you’ve really got 8 pieces. - Let’s verify the number of pieces.
1,2,3,4,5,6,7,8.
Ok 8, you’ve passed. Now go to Paris Park.
Paris Park?
- Mok Dong! - Really?
First we use brackets, then we use this.
The we use the brackets around these, from 8 to 1, and then over here...
I said we must use brackets, but I don’t really know how to use the brackets.
Maybe we should have found 20 math symbols!
It’s okay, hyung, you just do it.
If it’s good you will be saved.
We must let Sohee smile once before she leaves.
Is it possible?
Not possible!
- Do you see your own team’s colour boards? - Yes.
Now do the sums on your own team’s board and get number 1.
You have too many minus signs.
Please do the sums on your own board and get 1 as fast as possible.
16, 4, 4...
Hyung, first, 8 plus 9 plus 7 will be 24 right?
Ah! It’s too complicated!
Why do you all have so many symbols?
Even if we didn’t find so many, as long as we do it right, we can also get 1.
If you minus 1 it will become 0.
Let’s use this, and add 1.
- Yes, yes. - Look, I’ll do this, and you calculate it again.
Look. 1, bracket 1.
That’s right, bracket 1.
Challenge!
If you pass, the lights will light up.
- Fail. - Why?
The answer you all have provided is -1.
Mlnus?
Just now we only used the numbers, then we use the brackets, right?
Divide.
That’s rights.
We’ve reached.
They’ve all reached?
We’ve come, we’ve come, we’ve come!
Let’s do it, let’s do it!
Oh? Quickly quickly! Dong Hoon, quickly! We can do it! There’s still time!
I’m doing it, I’m doing it!
- Just give us another minus sign. - We want a plus sign now.
We don’t have plus sign now.
Pass it to me. Minus, Minus...
No, no... It’s minus...
7 minus 2... Minus...
Minus?
There’s no minus?
- How can there be no minus? We had a minus! - Where’s the minus?
- Oh! It’s here! It scared me! - It almost spoiled everything.
- 3, 3... This must be first...3... - Then you add this, and add this...
What?
7 minus 2, minus...
7 minus 2, add here...
Add 2 and 4...
It’s done!
Wow, theirs is really simple. Really simple!
1, 2, 3, completed!
I said we aren’t the last! We aren’t the last!
What to do? That’s why I said...
I said we could be the first!
Actually blue team could have gotten 1.
Oh, really?
- If you move the brackets in front of the minus sign you would have won. - You see!! I was right!!
Ahhhhhh!!
What are you doing leading 2 children?
It’s the end? It’s now totally over?
Yellow team has won, everybody please gather in front.
We are unintelligent, so we won.
Calculus! Equations! We don’t need all of them!
Our mathematics just consist of plus and minus!
You want us to use square root? No! We just use plus and minus!
Today’s best Hallyu Star team is the last to arrive, yet using just simple plus and minus,
Calculus and equations are all not needed.
Sulli’s Team!
Happy Year 2012!
Who are they?
What mission must we do?
Please eliminate all the Running Man members.
Who is this betrayer? Does he or does she not exist?
Oh no, this...
It’s not possible yo have a reversal. It’s obvious there will be no reversal.
I almost died!
Faster, faster!
Other mission?
Before recording a special episode, you should eat something before coming.