Is there no one at all?
Here!
Save me!
Open the door!
Why am l here?
I know a secret!
I'm finally back after a year.
Why did you call me out at such a time at night?
Anytime now.
Huh?
You will know.
Where are all of them?
Today, it’s strange.
What's this?
Why did you call me out so late?
Will someone come to pick me?
What are we doing?
They'll come, right?
Is it a horror special?
What?
Myeok PD, you again.
Arrest him.
What?
Hang on. Why are you arresting me?
Huh?
Myeok PD, why am I arrested?
I'm now...
No, Hyung Taek.
I'm seriously...
We all know each other, keep your cool.
Well, it's not even the first time. I've been a Spy once...
What are you doing?
-Mr Yoo Jae Suk. -Yes.
Mr Yoo Jae Suk, has made people embarrassed with his tight pants.
You're also wearing them today.
-You've committed disorderly conduct. -Wow, I'm really...
And not just being obsessed with the colour green,
you've committed a crime for an obsess/on over perfection that makes people weary.
So?
-According to the Running Law, Article 14, Line 1... -How is there Running Man Law?
-Hey, do you really want me to grab your collar? -you aren't allowed to plead the Fifth Amendment.
I can't?
Starting from now, anything you say can and will be used against you.
-What did you say? -Understand?
So?
What do you want from me now?
-Ok, move him. -But, I...
Listen to what I have to say.
But, my pants...
Where are you taking me? Hey.
Hey, where am I going?
What's this again?
I'm going crazy.
What's going on today?
Huh?
What crime did I commit, according to what law?
The Running Law.
What Running Law, how is there a Running Law?
Where are we going?
To catch the other criminals.
I'm seriously...
What will it be? What will it be?
Why did they call us out so late at night?
Are they filming a scary show?
What? What?
Arrest him.
Why? Why me? I didn't do anything wrong, hang on.
Why, why?
I didn't do anything wrong!
Why? I didn't do anything. Why are you doing this?
It's so scary.
-Mr HaHa. -Yes.
During this period, each time female guests appeared...
-you would display your playboy act that humiliated Running Man. -No, I loved them!
I really loved them.
You just said you admitted it.
-No, I loved them! -For now...
-Mr HaHa is arrested for the crime of playboy act. -No!
-I loved them! Son Ye Jin's my woman. -According to the Running Man Law, Arficie 14, Line 1...
Ha Ji Won's my woman.
-Suzy... -You aren't allowed to plead the Fifth Amendment.
Why? I want to call my lawyer.
-Anything you say can and will be used against you. -I came from law family.
I know the chief judge.
-Take him away. -Let me make a call.
After I make the call it’s the end for you!
Do you know who I am?
I, can make you...
I’m an important person!
Come in, come in.
-Jae Suk hyung. -Time Controller.
Space Controller, what's all this?
Please give me your phones.
-What? -Give me your phones.
I don't have one.
It's here.
- It's here. - This is a gift from the Thai fans.
This cubic can't be lost, this.
You can't lose any cubic.
This is a present from the Thai fans...
Oh?
Why is he standing there wearing a coat?
What's this again?
-Arrest him. -What are you doing?
What are you doing?
No, what are you doing?
Have they ever told you when you ask what's going on?
You're just caught.
You're arrested for the crime of abuse.
What crime?
This is based on a tip-off from Mr Park Joon Gyu, the crime of abuse.
What's all this?
Also, the crime of overreacting whenever Yoo Eon Hye is mentioned. The Yoon Eun Hye crime.
How can there be a Yoon Eun Hye crime?
-Do you agree? -What?
-Get on. -Agree... you just asked if I agreed?
-What did you say? -Your handphone.
I'm seriously...
There's still one more right?
No! There isn't!
Hey, seriously.
Wow, you're nasty.
What's this, really?
-Just get in first, Jong Kook. -Oh, hyung!
Hyung, why were you caught?
What else could it be? What crime did you commit?
-What crime did hyung get? -You have too much muscle? - No.
What then?
Yoon Eun Hye crime.
What's all this?
Hyung is guilty of disorderly conduct, because of his skinny jeans.
Because of the skinny jeans they said it's a disorderly conduct.
Something's coming?
- Arrest him. - Hang on.
Why are you doing this?
Why?
You're ugly, right?
No!
You've committed the Ugly Guy crime,
-Huh? -you have to come with us.
Why, I'm...
According to the Running Man Law, Section 14, Line 1...
How can you charge someone because of his looks?
In my family I'm the most handsome!
Gary, what's your crime?
The Ugly Guy crime.
Seriously?
Arrest him.
Hang on.
What are you doing?
-You have to greet somewhat upon meeting. -For exceptional bad acting...
You always ruin the Running Men's plans.
We're arresting you for bad acting.
-Arrest her. -What are you doing?
Miss Song Ji Hyo appears for filming without makeup.
You've committed the Bare Face crime.
-Oppa, are we caught because of some crimes? -Thatis right.
That's right.
-Arrest him. -Hyung, hello.
Huh?
What crime did he do?
He has too many crimes.
Betraying Running Man members, twelve counts.
The crime of being scared, seven counts.
A streak of three counts of the crime of misfortune.
Plus the other miscellaneous items totalling twenty offences.
You're under special arrest.
-What? -Are we going to be locked in there?
Oh, what's that?
Why?
Ok, criminals. Listen carefully.
Criminal Lee Gwang Soo will alright first.
What, alone?
Please come out.
Gwang Soo is dragged away.
What’s all this, where is this place?
What's with these house shoes?
What's this?
What's this? Where are you bringing me?
Oh, it's so scary!
You have someone that you'll miss, right?
Jeez, really...
Like we won't see them forever.
Mr Ji Suk Jin.
Yes.
These are the house shoes I wore in middle school?
I really loved them.
We dated for real.
I'm being charged with green crime and you're giving me green clothes.
Here?
What is this?
Is this a real jail?
Sheriff!
Oh, it's really locked?
They really locked it.
We dated before!
Open the door!
I said open the door!
Why am I in here?
The colours of our clothes are different.
It's weird.
What are you doing?
Jeezr I'm really going crazy.
I want to go to the toilet!
Running Men.
Everyone has been sentenced to six hours of imprisonment.
What? Aren't we tearing of nametags?
You just want us to keep sitting here, for six hours?
Especially for Mr Lee Gwang Soo who has committed many crimes...
he will serve sixty hours.
Oh?
Before you serve your sentence, no one can even get out of here.
Gwang Soo has sixty hours?
How many days is sixy hours?
- Why do I get sixty hours? - Everyone has a sentence of six hours.
Mr Lee Gwang Soo gets sixty hours.
No!
Before you serve your sentence, no one can even get out of here.
If they're releasing us after six hours...
So I'll just stay here for six hours then leave.
Six hours isn't a very long time anyway.
So I'll just play around for six hours.
It's so simple. Oh, Running Man's extremely comfortable?
Ok, throwing us, into jail here...
they would expect us to try getting out, right?
Then there should be clues or something somewhere in this room?
Something for us to make use of to get out of here.
The room is locked...
so could it be numbers, numbers for the lock?
I can't hold it anymore.
-Give it to me. - Please be quiet.
I'll be quiet.
Give this to me.
Is this... Oldboy?
Who are you?
Give me some soy sauce and pickled radish.
Sir!
Give me some pickled radish!
Hey, isn't this Oldboy?
What's this?
Am I Chol Min Shik sunbae in Oldboy? Giving me fried dumplings...
Annoying.
Am I Choi Min Shik sunbae giving me fried dumplings?
Is it Oldboy now?
I'm hungry, I'll eat first.
Why couldn't you order seafood noodles for me?
Slieriff!
Pickled radish!
Give me some soy sauce, soy sauce.
I'm really going crazy.
I'll definitely find you.
Whoever locked me up here.
They might as well give me food for my wellbeing.
I'm trying to lose weight.
They don't even give pickled radish.
These fried dumplings, where...
Please escape from this room and flee this building within four hours.
Good luck.
Daebak.
But how do I get out of the room?
The pass code.
There must be a pass code.
Oh.
Escape from this room and flee this building within four hours. Good luck.
But, you have to tell me how to get out.
How do I get...
Are there clues in the room?
There should be a way out of this place somewhere.
Can't they tell me?
Right, no matter how creative they are, hiding it in dumpling is a bit... right?
These still have to be cooked, I don't think it's easy to put something inside.
Why these dumplings?
I just ate with my hands.
What?
Escape from this room within four hours and flee this building.
I'm eating now, you're making me uncomfortable.
The kids have all started.
They are starting to move, Suk Jin hyung too.
Ji Hyo and HaHa has started too.
Basketball, five players.
3 in 'Three Kingdoms'.
Six people, five people.
Two water bottles.
There are three 5s.
Ah, it‘s not it.
How frustrating.
Ok, there's no one now. Let's go.
I have to go, I have to go. It's now, it's now.
Find the building's blueprint hidden inside this building.
7th floor, 7tb floor. HaHa's room. He has escaped.
Prisoner number 2 escaped.
What?
-Prisoner number 2 escaped. Prisoner number 2 escaped. -What?
Already?
He escaped?
HaHa escaped, HaHa.
Stop!
Prisoner number 2 escaped.
If it's just six hours there's no point escaping.
Recording, performance, filming.
It has been too busy.
Right now, I want some time alone.
While eating dumplings.
I'm not going out today.
There's something written here!
I'm such a fool.
The chopsticks were like this so I didn't know.
But how do I get out?
I'm not leaving!
Why is there no crossword puzzle?
Me...
Merong.
Seriously, merong.
This is seriously pissing me off.
That's right. An 'R'.
Daebak.
8084!
Please find the hidden building's blueprints.
-Prisoner number 6 escaped! -Again!?
Prisoner number 6 escaped.
Ah, I was shocked!
-Did you get the mission card? -I got it.
- The blueprint? - Yes, the blueprint.
- Where is the blueprint? - I'm looking for it too.
The first and second floor?
We have to tell the members quickly.
Don't you know? Don't forget that it might be an individual battle.
Ji Hyo, seeing you here is making me really fond of you.
Oppa will treat you better.
Oppa, I'll be nice to you too.
Ji Hyo...
There must be a reason for these things.
They can't be placed here for nothing.
These things... really...
It's open. 3461.
Please find the hidden blueprint.
I didn't expect it to be here...
Oh, hang on.
Oh, scared me!
Oh, my heart is going to Jump out!
Oh! Why are these blacked out?
Which years do they want?
I need to go to the toilet.
Year 80... 7... year 70. 807.
807.
Hey!
Where did they go after escaping?
Oh.
There seems to be numbers written here.
It couldn't be.
Jeez, it's seriously unbelievable. It was written on the window!
Ah, it hurts my pride.
Prisoner number 4 escaped. Prisoner number 4 escaped.
-I'm going. -Go.
-Hyung, don't get eliminated! -Ok.
Gwang Soo, seventh floor! Gwang Soo, seventh floor!
Gwang Soo, 7th floor! Gwang Soo, 7th floor!
Lee Gwang Soo, seventh floor!
HaHa hyung's heading toward the roof! HaHa hyung, rooftop!
Is it the blueprint?
This isn't it. This is the construction plan for this room.
It's not the Running Man blueprint.
There should be a sign.
In the movies, it is usually in this kind of place.
Quickly.
Oh, hang on. Ah, what is it?
Oh hold on, what happened?
Why?
I Just came out, why do I have to go back in again?
I don't understand why I have to go back in again.
Please remember that’s my soul can't be tied up.
No, wait.
Can't I just go out for a while?
Why are you always following me? Are you in charge of me?
Even if my body is tied up, you can never tie up my freedom.
That's for you to know.
Come in, come in!
Is it Joo hyung?
Hey!
Myeok PD!
- No, why? - Did you escape?
Why are you catching us?
- Myeok PD, why did you catch us? - Please go over there quickly.
- Go where? Where? - Hurry, hurry.
-Quickly go where? - Go quickly and you'll know.
- What did you say? - Go forward.
Where Is he asking me to run to?
There's nothing ere.
Oh?
What is this?
I thought this was a closet. What is this?
It's not supposed to be like this.
This one is blocked off.
Is this an exit?
What‘s this?
What are you doing here?
-Hello. -I don't want to be a spy.
Do you know what day it is today?
- Today is 10th of April, right? - Yes.
Voomes Bond, do you remember the water gun episode?
Yes.
Secretly eliminate your team mates by spraying the water gun.
This!
Is it raining?
It has been exactly one year since that broadcast.
So?
So to commemorate the 1st anniversary, Yoo Jae Suk is selected to receive a special pardon.
-Do you know the Jail Breakers (movie)? -Yes.
You'll become a special envoy.
You don't have to serve the six hours prison sentence.
But, if there's a problem here or the prisoners cause any problem or escape the building..
Therefore, you have to make sure no one gets out.
If that happens you have to fulfill your sentence.
What should I do?
So, you have to return all the members to the cells.
That's the only way you can get out.
You'll get amnesty to get out.
No, now that you've let everyone out, you're telling me to put them back in again?
How do I catch them?
Jong Kook, how can I put him back into his cell?
So that why I told you earlier, it's the 1st anniversary of the water gun episode.
Yes.
This is a different story then.
I thought. I have to catch and put them back in their rooms.
- Is this it? - Yes.
Wait, please don't get too excited.
-I get excited when I see water guns. -Sit down first.
I missed the grip of the water gun. The water gun is already pulling me.
This is really making my palms sweat.
What's that for?
Since it's not litmus paper...
Put the colouring into the water gun to take them out.
You get one water gun.
You can pick from the different water guns.
Choose just one colour.
- If the colour... - If they are stained, they're out?
So, they're going to the jail spontaneously?
Once they're shot, the security team will force them back.
It's finally here.
After one year it's finally here.
Seriously, what's with this?
I choose this.
Green.
Of course it's that.
It's not 'of course'!
What's this I'm doing?
What am l doing with this green colouring?
I'm seriously.
I Didn't know they will give me this.
Why didn't they give it to me when l wanted it?
Looks like a carp bread filled with washable.
I'm already nervous.
I'm going crazy.
You be careful.
You're frightened too right?
I'm seriously going crazy.
Suk Jin hyung.
Why does Suk Jin hyung appear every time I'm at these moments?
I'm nervous.
Oh, it's nerve-wracking.
Oh, oh!
Ah!
Heyt you're really...
Oh, you shocked me.
Come quickly!
Hey, where did you guys go?
- We found the map, hyung. - Where?
If someone escape the building, you have to serve your sentence.
Hyung, there's no one here, hyung.
Hurry.
The blueprints, the blueprints.
Nothing here.
It will clearly be in this sort of place.
Gwang Soo, what's this?
This and the watch must mean something.
Oh.
Hyung's jjang right?
Hyung!
Kim Jong Kook, Kim Jong Kook!
The computer room, the computer room!
The third floor, the third floor.
What's that?
I don't know.
Because there's a watch I'll just wear it.
-I want something too... -Open it up.
Open it, quickly.
It's gold.
Hyung. Just in case something happen, I'll hold on to this.
Hyung, please trust me.
I can't trust you.
Where did you find it?
Hey Giraffe!
-Whatls there? -A key!
What key?
Hey, how did you find it?
Hey, where are you headed?
Where, where?
Hyung, come in!
Why?
Come in! Come in quickly!
Target, Lee Gwang Soo. Target, Lee Gwang Soo.
There must be a key here.
What did you say?
There's a key here in this room.
-In this room? -Yeah.
Find the key, quickly!
The key, it's a key.
There's a key here?
Hyung, according to the map we found, there's a key here.
Hyung, we don’t have to go to another room.
-They're all locked -They're all locked.
I locked the door. Hyung, I locked the door.
The key's here?
Hey, where Is it?
Look for It quickly!
The map said It would be here,.in the computer room.
No, why is the door open, who opened It?
- Who opened the door? - What, what?
What, what?
Hang on.
What?
Oh what, what?
Isn't Jong Kook hyung over there?
Oh.
Isn't Jong Kook hyung over here too?
Jong Kook hyung's also here!
Why are you just doing this to me?
Hang on!
Hyung! Hyung!
This is bad, Kim Jong Kook might have noticed something.
I forgot.
Lee Gwang Soo, jailed again.
It‘s all over.
Gary hyung!
Just tie it lightly.
That's it.
Ah really, they seriously don't give us a chance.
Work hard.
- Do a good job. -Yes.
Hyung, turn around. I'll untie you.
Hey, hang on.
I'll help untie you.
Oh, right.
Hey, ok.
Hurry, hyung.
Please help me too.
Ah, really... don't think about it.
Ah, hyung.
How do I untie this? Yours Is too tight.
Let's go.
I'm really... going crazy.
- Hyung, fighting. - Fighting.
I'm going crazy.
I did this once before...
The last time none of them had any suspicions, but...
This time it's different.
Oh, that scared me.
-That scared me. -They are everywhere.
Where?
They are all over the place.
Earlier... You survived?
How did Gwang Soo do?
Don't know.
Did you find the key earlier?
I didn't.
Come on in.
Hey, where are you?
Come in, come in.
I'm going crazy.
In the 3rd or 5th floor, we have to go to 520...
-Ah.. I'll show It to you. -What?
Where did you find this map?
325 is the computer lab we went to earlier.
There's a key here.
And the guards room...
They're here then.
520.
On the sixth floor...
Hyung Room 520 on the 5th floor.
Room 620, room 620....
Which floor is 620 on?
It’s Just downstairs.
Hyung, we've been to the 6th floor.
Because girls carry a lot.
Kim Jong Kook should have been dealt with at the start.
I'm going this way.
What are you doing!
Runny nose.
Hold it in.
They are right there.
I'm going crazy.
Hyung, don't open it.
They will see you.
They will see you if you open it.
Stay still, stay still.
Stay still, Hyung!
Move aside.
Hold this.
Wow, you're so amazing.
There’s no one.
Target, Kim Jong Kook.
I'll go first.
Hang on...
Who told you?
Kim Jong Kook, imprisoned again.
Sending Jong Kook back in is as good as controlling the ace.
Did you see me take it out and put it back in again?
What's this?
A watch...
Thank you.
Is it gold?
How do I do this? I'm going crazy.
It's a gold bar!
This is no joke....Today is seriously no joke.
- Hyung. - Jae Suk.
You found it, right? You didn't?
I haven't found it.
Let's go together.
-I found it. -What did you found?
-I found it. -Where did you find it?
Hey, you still haven't found it?
I saw what Jong Kook found.
-You saw it? -I saw the one Jong Kook found.
-Where did you find it? -Hey...
I already found it, but... right now...
I feel really bad for you...
What did you find?
Right now, you can just walk comfortably here.
Walk comfortably here.
-This is it. -What is this?
Oh, the patrol...
From 1:00 to 1:30 they are all at the 1st floor now.
We just need to avoid the 1st floor.
So that's why you must have the watch.
Why are you so slow today?
Jae Suk, you really...
So, hyung Is the shining ace today?
I am the ace.
Today, I'm so sharp...
Hey Yoo Suk, tell him.
-I'm like lighting today -Is Suk Jin hyung really like lightning?
When I saw him earlier, he was like this.
Hey, I'm not kidding. I hid myself, disappeared and appeared again.
-Hey, look at this. -Huh?
What time is it now, hyung?
It's 1:09 now.
It's here. Look at this.
Hyung, let's quickly split up.
Come here.
Meeting... Because it's time for a meeting.
Because it's time for meeting.
What?
It's meeting time, but why?
- But... - What's this?
Isn't it time for meeting??!
Isn't it time for meeting?
Hang on... These people really...
Hyung, didn't you say 1st floor?
-No, according to the plan, they should be at the 1st floor. -What is this?
Aren't you having a meeting on the first floor today?
Ah really...
Ah... what is this?
Where are we going? Huh?
It should be there.
- Hyung, where are you going? - Where am I going?
Suk Jin hyung!
What's happening?
Why am I going here?
Excuse me...
This... excuse me.
I'll give you this.
Gold!
Gold!!
Let me out!
Jong Kook hyung!
At least give me the gold!
Huh?
What's this?
Green.
If it's green then it‘s Jae Suk hyung.
Is Jae Suk hyung the culprit?
This is not the time for me to be like this.
I discovered the secret.
I should not be the one here.
Open the door!
Hurry, try contacting someone.
Let Gary or someone pass by here.
Oh! Wait!
Ji Hyo! Help untie me!
- Oppa, what are you doing there?? - Ji Hyo! I got caught. I got caught.
Why did you get caught?
Help untie me, quickly! Where have you been?
- Oppa... - Ji Hyo, thank you. HaHa is...
Oppa...
- HaHa Is really .. he's a complete traitor. - Oppa, HaHa oppa has a bunch of keys.
- Really? -Yes.
Oppa, where did you find the map?
Where did you find yours?
Hey, lets open it.
Just open it up, what do you think?
Let me see! Just let me see it!
Oppa, why are you here?
I got caught by the security guards and brought here.
Ji Hyo.
- It from the front, why did you go to the back? - That's right.
Ji Hyo, first lets escape from here quickly.
There is not enough time.
Where is everybody?
I am the hero of the day...
For sure!
Ye Jin... Let's live happily together with this gold bar.
What?
This is too heavy, I can't put it here.
Kang Gary!
- Did you find anything? - Nothing.
How can you be here?
I've been running continuously.
Oppa, what did you find?
I didn't find anything.
Look me in the eye and tell me.
Hey!
Hey! It's such a commotion.
Where did you find it?
There are more?
Your acting is too obvious.
- No. How do you... - So you hid the gold bar there?
Yes.
I'm afraid it would drop out.
-You look like a patient. -I have gold fever.
Please save me!
I know the secret!
Please give me steamed dumplings.
I want steamed dumplings.
Give me steamed dumplings!
Steamed dumplings...
I want steamed dumplings!
If not steamed dumplings, Just give me death!
Jae Suk hyuuung!
The others...
I'm going crazy.
To save energy, all lights out!
To save energy. all lights out!
Eh?
To save energy, all lights out!
What?
All lights out.
I must act fast during the lights out.
Now's the chance!
Where should we go, oppa?
-I don't know. Which floor is this now? - It’s the fourth floor.
-What floor is this? -The fourth floor.
Oh! This is terrifying!
Where did everyone go?
I can't find them.
Oh, scary.
♫ When mother went to the island shade ♫
♫ To pick oysters ♫
All lights in the building back on, with increased security.
All fights in the building back on. Increased security.
It's HaHa.
You scared me.
- Who are you? What’s your identity - I'm...
Here...
-What is this? -This is a map.
Could you be...
I am Scofield.
You say you are Scofield?
I am Suk-Sure-to-Fail.
You've worked hard.
Hyung.
-You will escape later, right? -Yes.
Let's get out of this place together!
Suk-Sure-to-Fall, Suk-Sure-to-Fail.
Hyungnim...
I am Scofield.
Target, Ha Ha. Target, HaHa.
Why are they suddenly chasing me? Really!
They keep chasing me!
Why are you keep chasing me!
No!
I am supposed to be the hero.
You’re making a mistake!
HaHa re-captured! HaHa re-captured!
Who told you?
What's this?
Is this it?
Three, four, six, one.
To save energy, all lights out!
How did you get out?
-There was another password. -I see.
I shook off guards...
when the lights were off and I turned on the radio.
Hyung, what did you find?
This security...
Oh, this. I saw the gold earlier.
Hey, you are really amazing.
I'm so surprised.
-What did you say about 2:30? -2:30 to 3:00.
-We can move around from 2:30 to 3:00. -Okay. I understand.
And hyung...
2:30 to 3:00.
Where are the guys?
2:30 to 4:30.
I have to hold for 30 minutes.
What's this?
Is this even possible?
It's Jong Kook's room, Jong Kook‘s room.
I can't walk around anymore.
I should just lurk here.
Oppa, how did you get out?
-There was another hint in the room. -There was another one?
Oppa, HaHa oppa has the key. HaHa oppa found one.
-I found the blueprint. Did you find the blueprint? -I found it.
-Did you find what I was looking for? -Where was it?
The third floor.
We didn't go to the 3rd floor.
-We didn't go there. -I know where it is. It's the 3rd floor.
Quickly, quickly, quickly.
Find the key. Quickly.
Hey, where were you guys?
-Hyung, what...! -Oh, you surprised me.
Quickly, find the key ."Quickly.
-What do I.have to find? -What are you doing?
Is it here?
Hyung, how did you find us?
Hyung, did you have the key?
-Did yo have the key? -You guys, be quiet.
-Did you find It? -I came here earlier, but where Is it?
-It's here. It must be here. -What is it?
- What are we looking for here? - Stop talking and find it. - The key!!
What key?
-Is it a set of keys? -Yes.
-Are they in sets? -It's a set of keys. A set of keys.
Uh, wait. What is that?
Where is it? What?
-What? -Check the monitors.
Check the monitor.
Where is the monitor?
How to check the monitor?
-Hey, does It mean to look at this? -Yes, you are right.
How do I turn it on?
Really. Only 30 minutes.
How do I turn It on?
Only 30 minutes.
How do I turn it on?
There's not much time.
There's not much time. Hurry,
There's not much time. Hurry.
Target Song Ji Hyo. Target Song Ji Hyo.
Do I have to press the power button?
What's going on? They are here?
Ow, ow, oppa. They are here!
Ow, I can't run anymore. Let's go.
Why did you come over here after running away?
Then what should I do? We have to find the key.
-Where were you? -Look at the monitor. Quickly.
Find it quickly, find it quickly!
This lecture desk?
Is this the lecture desk?
-Hey, open It and see. -Is this the one mentioned In the computer?
How do we do this?
Hey, hey, hey.
Hey, hey, hey
Gary, Gary.
What is it?
This is not a place for sleeping.
Let me sleep here for a while:
I am just tired.
Song Ji Hyo, Gary imprisoned!
-It could have been over if he was out. -Hyung, hyung!
Huh?
-There is a closed shutter door. It's strange. -So what?
-It's weird, that the shutter door is closed. -The shutter? -Yeah.
It's upstairs. Come here.
What is?
Look at this...
It's blocked off here, isn't that a shutter?
I'll go and look.
-What should we do If we don't have the key? -Wait a moment.
Let's calm down.
Really, calm down.
Calm down.
13, 21... there are so many numbers.
-What floor is this? -Hey, if we open this, we can get out?
I don't know.
Hey, my heart is trembling so much.
Calm down, calm down.
Oh!
-It is opened. -Jong Kook.
Hey, my heart is trembling so much.
Calm down, calm down.
Oh!
-It is opened. -Jong Kook.
-What are you doing? -Hang on.
What are you doing?
What did you do?
Target Kim Jong Kook. Target Kim Jong Kook.
You can't go anywhere.
Don't be ridiculous!
Jong Kook, we could all live together. Jong Kook, Jong Kook.
-What are you talking about? What’s this? -Kook Jong.
-If you're caught I'll be caught too. -What did you say?
If you get caught, I will also get caught, Kook Jong.
What's this?
I am sorry, Kook Jong.
-What? -Kook Jong, I'm sorry.
-Kook Jong, Kook Jong -You are sneaky.
Kook Jong!
What's this? A water gun? What's this?
-What's with the water gun? -It's the first anniversary of the water gun.
Ow, Really.
-Kook Jong, do you know how nervous I felt because of you? -Hey, seriously.
Gwang Soo.
How could hyung do this to me?
Gwang Soo, It's the first anniversary of the water gun.
What's that, hyung!
What's the first anniversary of the water gun?
Don't you feel its too much to eliminate me in the beginning.
I ate twelve dumplings.
-I have to explain, right? Do you know why you are here, Suk-Sure-to-Fail? -I got caught.
What the!
Ji Hyo, it's the first anniversary of the water gun.
-Ji Hyo! -Daebak!
Thank you.
-Thank you. -Hyung!
I won't be staying here for the rest of my life.
Oppa!
Yoo Jae Suk. I won’t leave you be.
What the!
How can hyung do this to me?
Good bye.
Hyung!
-Just wait. -Hyung!
-I won't leave you alone -Good bye. -Hyung!
There's an order, get the phone!
Who ordered the jjajiangmyun?
JYP, vegetable salad.