-I will identify today's Spy. -Enemies are everywhere.
I'm not the Spy.
What should I do?
Either way I'm alone, I'm dead anyway.
Hey, hey.
Hey!
-It's the best in history! -Wait. I'll tear it off later!
Hey. hey.
I'm seriously going crazy.
Who's next? Don't let me see you.
Where has Kim Jong Kook gone to?
Why is he so late?
Kim Jong Kook wouldn't be given some mission right?
-He wouldn't be with Yoon Eun Hye? -He could be with Yoon Eun Hye.
He could be with Yoon Eun Hye.
-Oh, is Yoon Eun Hye coming? -Really?
Hey really, Yoon Hye... hey.
If we start from the X-Man days that's twelve years of love,
-I hope they have a happy ending. -Right, we hope they have a happy ending.
I hope that couple has a happy ending.
Let's do "Dangyunhaji" later.
-Hey, then... -Please, let that couple...
Also, it's time we need a new love line.
It's still not over!
-Ah. Monday isn't over yet. -Look at this person.
-I'm the only one left. There's no one else. -You're most suited to be a playboy.
Then... I got it. Make a love line for Haha too.
-Yes. -With hyung.
-I want it to be with a female. -Hey. I love you.
Because I missed you I didn't sleep a wink last night,
-The love line has started. -I spent last night erasing your text messages.
-Your love line with me has started. -My heart's beating so fast here.
Hey, I'm about to go crazy.
My pillow's all wet.
Ah. I'm seriously about to go crazy!
-Your love line's already ended too. -Hey, it's just starting.
Your love line's ended too.
Get permission before coming!
Can't you feel how jittery I am?
Hey.
They've already broken up!
I've been drinking alone for three days!
Just drinking one cup after another!
I was in Hong Dae looking like this.
-I knew it would turn out like this. -I've was like this in Hongdae.
But, shouldn't we leave quickly?
-Ok today, the guests... -Yes.
Have been waiting in the car park.
Oh?
Does everyone see the three cars behind you?
Yes.
The guest are currently inside there.
Ok. starting from now. you'll be a team with the guest who alights from the car!
-You choose whether to stand in front of Car 1. Car 2 or Car 3 yourself. -Ok.
-Ok. set off. -Where, where?
-Which one is Number 1? -Number 1's here.
Number 3, Number 3.
-Oh, -Hey, it's Number 1!
I want Number 1 too.
I want Number 3.
That was weird right, earlier?
-Hey, do you want to be with me? -It doesn't matter to me.
We'll start from. Car 1!
-Shout. "Please come out." -Ok.
Ok, please come out!
What's this?
Ah. really.
Why are you applying lip balm?
It doesn't make sense.
Ah seriously, applying lip balm.
Why apply lip balm?
So today, the three of you are in a team.
-Huh? -Seriously.
Your fortune today isn't too bad.
-I so want to grab that person by the collar, -Seriously. I really want to do it.
-Ok, come over here to Car 2. -I'm trembling!
Oppa. I feel it's a pity too.
-A guy! -A guy, please let it be a guy.
Please come out!
Yeah!
-Ah, so it's the three of them? -What are you doing?
So. today the two of you are a team.
Hey, Gwang Soo.
You're seriously, going to have a nosebleed when you're at Busan.
-It's beneficial for you. -Oh, such stress!
Oh, I'm beginning to lose weight!
-Wow. I'm feeling very good now. -I'm anticipating it.
One, two. three.
Please come out!
-Pretty, pretty! -Hey,
Lee Da Hae!
Lee Da Hae, Lee Da Hae!
-Hey. -Aigoo!
Aigoo!
Get lost!
-Get lost! -Aigoo. Da Hae,
Hey. Gwang Soo,
Aigoo. aigoo.
Aigoo. I should have picked this car.
-Oppa. -What?
-She's not at oppa's. -Ji Hyo!
I should have picked this car.
Wow. Song Ji Hyo's face is super huge. Wow,
Hey, you... you're even shorter than, Lee Da Hae, compared to Da Hae!
Lee Da Hae and the Lollols, Lee Da Hae and the Lollols.
Ah, that's fine too.
I'm very close to Da Hae,
-Stop it! -Exactly.
-Don't be like that. -Her surname!
- Call her by her surname. - I'm very unhappy if you're like this!
Nice to meet you. Da Hae.
-Yes, nice to meet you. -Hello.
Noona looks so awkward,
Hey. who's older?
She looks much older.
-Ji Hyo. -Hey. hey.
Today we'll stay with the same groups the entire time.
Don't be overly upset.
There isn't a chance to change teams? I'm just curious.
-Do you watch Running Man often? -I quite like Jong Kook hyung.
Yes.
Who would you personally like to be on a team with?
-Ah. I like this team very much. -Oh my god.
Oh my god. oh my god.
You stop it.
There won't be changing of teams today.
Starting from here now. teams will board the plane holding hands.
Holding hands, those two.
Holding hands like this?
What hands have so many calluses?
- Linking arms or holding hands? - Because you're a little taller I'll just hold it in the reverse way.
Ok, when you come our of the airport you can find your cars in the car park
-Yes... -What, what?
Hurry, hurry.
- Let's go! - Get lost!
- Hey hurry, hurry. - Hey. get lost!
Where?
-Where? -Where?
It's fine, as long as there's Da Hae. everything's fine.
- We don't anything else. Hey. - It's enough, it's enough.
I swear, you're the most beautiful celebrities I've ever seen.
Oppa was very happy when you saw Son Ye Jin sunbae.
- You really liked her. - You have to know this about Ye Jin.
Her style is the sort that's rather easy to get tired of.
What sort of style does Da Hae's ideal type have?
For me...
- You wouldn't be so childish as to say the tall sort right? - Right.
It's too childish.
An understanding man.
-I can understand everything! -I understand everything!
I understand it all!
Also, he must have leadership qualities.
Hey, go this way!
I said go this way!
That's not it.
"Let's eat. let's do this, let's go there", things like this.
Good.
I like you.
Everything about you.
Oppa has money.
Go!
I don't need anything.
- He's a bit lost. - Could you try to understand oppa.
Beside us there. There, there.
- Gwang Soo. - There, there.
Gwang Soo, he's seriously very frightened.
The sound of the car's a little loud.
- Is there something wrong? - No, why is the RPM rising so much?
The car's gear is not shifting, that's why.
The car's sound is even louder that hyung's voice.
This car.,.
Why is this car like this?
You're in manual now.
Sorry.
- Why were there sounds? - Up till now the car has been in first gear.
- Is it? - A car this quiet...
Ah! It's the sea! The sea!
It's so pretty.
Oh. it's there!
This should be our first mission location.
- This should be our first mission location. - Really?
Yes. yes,
- Da Hael - Yes?
I really can't live anymore.
Please let me be alone.
Oh! Quickly, quickly.
Wah-
Oh, it's outside!
Why is it so cold?
It's cold!
What are we doing here?
Is there a mission?
Please kick the shuttlecocks in the cold bath.
-If the members kick a total of 10 times and above it is a pass. -Let's get going! Quickly quickly!
- Fighting! - Fighting!
1.2...
You can't do it like that.
Do we have to go in here?
Please step in.
Use this, use this!
A 3 man team is an advantage.
You should have stood in front of number 1 or 3.
I heard Da Hae's height is 170.
No, she's 175. What are you saying?
-She's 170 yet she's the tallest out of them. -She's 175!
-Then you're not 170! - I'm 170!
What's your height?
-170, -It's 175.
175.173,170. No, 169.
You are shorter than me!
Maintain your balance.
-One. only one. - Are you joking?
Joking?
-Only 1? -Tell him you're 175,
Da Hae. you are not a spy right?
There is a spy in this game too?
Her expression is weird.
Are you trying to make their team fail?
It is because the games are like these.
-We have to be alert in this game! -I really don't know anything.
You obviously know it.
It feels a little like X-Man now,
Standing like that,.. You are the X-Man'right?
You are the X-Man.
Yoon Eun Hye!
Don't do this! I'm really...
I asked you not to do this. Why are all of you like that?
I miss you, Eun Hye.
I must eliminate them.
I must tear them off. tear them off!
I am really going crazy.
This is the best in history.
The short one.
Oh...
-What are you doing? - What are you doing? What are you doing now?
The shorter this is, the less water it will carry.
Kim Jong Kook! Kim Jong Kook!
Your leg,..
Oppa, you will have a cramp.
No. it's okay.
1...
Ah. 2 times?
-I really can't watch this anymore. -It's really embarrassing! Really!
He stretched his whole body like that.
-Gwang Soo. what should you do? -Kook!
-Soo! (Kook Soo is noodles in Korean) -Eat!
-Kook! -Soo!
Slower, slower. Noodles, eat.
1!
It's our turn.
Well done.
I'm sorry.
Our VJ dongsaeng was like this just now...
Why are you like his?
Fighting!
I really hope I can hit twice.
Tok. tok. kick it like that.
Why are you holding him when Da Hae is kicking?
Let me wipe your foot for you.
-Done. -Gary oppa. you should stand there.
That's right.
-Like this! Not bad! -2! 2 right!
-2. -Fighting!
1,2...
4! 4!
-4! 4! -4! 4! 4!
Da da da da!
You just need to kick 4 more times.
-That'sit. -Fighting!
-Hyung, you see. .Never give up till the end. -Fighting! Fighting! Fighting!
Wipe it. Wipe your foot first.
Just use this...
4! 4!
I realize you are the very obedient type.
No...
Do it quickly!
This also looks like what we did in X-Man before,
Jong Kook, did you do all these to Eun Hye?
Ah! Why are you like this?
Like this...
-4! -1! Ah!
We have to do well.
Why can't I do it?
Can I kick 10 times in one go?
2! 3, 3!
Ah, you really can't do it.
You have to kick it well.
Gwang Soo, you have to say something.
Why can't you express yourself?
You saw how hyung did it. right?
You obviously can't do it like that, Gwang Soo.
Jong Kook, he didn't mean it. He made a mistake.
He didn't do it on purpose. Jong Kook, he didn't mean it.
Are you alright, hyung.
Jong Kook has the look in his eyes.
-Hyung, I will definitely do better next. -You come here first.
Our turn.
-Start. -Fighting!
1.2.3.4.
5,6.
7 times, then Da Hae and Dong Hoon kick only once and they'll fail.
Just do it. It's as good as done. Be at ease.
1.2.
-I only need to kick once. -Only 1.
-Only 1. -Maybe you can't even kick once.
We've won. We've won.
Dong Hoon!
1.
How did you kick 7 times?
What's that? It's cold, let's go quickly!
Bye.
We will definitely have no problems.
Get it? Kick confidently.
Yes, like that! 5!
-Oppa you are too good! -You all saw it right?
It's done! It's done!
Like this!
There's definitely no problem!
Yeah-We're done!
-Why can't I? -You just have to kick twice.
This is indeed a little difficult.
Ah. 4.
We can do 4 times,
Oppa. I'm sorry!
It's alright.
Ji Hyo. it's alright.
-You can do it. -I can kick 4 times,
Aja!
4 times! 4 times! You just have to-kick 4 times!
1,2.3.
1 more time!
We did it!
Let's go.
You saw it right, you saw it right.
Why didn't you do it with me?
What's with this? It's so strange.
Oh. it's too difficult.
What are all of you doing there?
-This is for Dae Hae. -Ok. I get it.
-Thank you. -You're really too much.
Break the falling balloons.
Hit more than 30 balloons to pass.
-Ok! Ok! -What?
We have to hit the thing falling from above?
Kim Jong Kook is very good at this.
Gary also did boxing.
-Fighting! -Fighting!
Oh, what is that?
-Are you all ready? -Yes.
Start!
Mother!
As expected, the boxing Gary.
Oh, I can't do this.
Two, one. Stop!
We're not bad,
-There should be 30. -Did we get it?
-Only 18? -Huh?
Seems that they hit a lot?
-They hit so many and only got 18? -This is only 18?
This isn't easy.
Ok, let's try it. 30!
Fighting!
-Ok, fighting. -Start!
Open your eyes! Open your eyes!
Aigoo. where are they?
Suk Jin hyung can't even hit one,
Suk Jin hyung keeps hitting home runs.
-How many? -Ah, so scary!
I think we done it,
-Wow, what a pity. -It was 26?
-You had 26, so its a fail. -What a pity.
Ok. I know what to do.
-Ok. are you ready? -Yes.
Ok. get ready. Start.
Hey Jong Kook. Jong Kook.
Hey. Kim Jong Kook.
Hey, they're not falling on this side.
-Hey, Gary... -He's no joke.
He's like a kangaroo.
Why are they always thrown to Gwang Soo?
Ok.
Gwang Soo. it won't do if you miss like this.
It's out, Gwang Soo. Gwang Soo. no.
It's out. Gwang Soo, Gwang Soo. no.
We'll reveal how many they got.
-Did they get 30? -They got 29.
Really?
Hey, you hit all 29!
Actually, Mr Lee Gwang Soo missed quite a few balloons.
They wouldn't break even after I hit them!
Gwang Soo. he even got in your way.
Exactly.
-He did this to you. -Not like that.
You guys are the ideal match.
-Ah, why were you like this? -Kook!
Soo!
Cross!
Start!
Oh, oh, there's still a lot of time,
-They haven't got any. There's no time. -You wasted the time.
-They didn't break. -Hey. Lee Da Hae's doing well!
Oh, Lee Da Hae's doing well.
-Da Hae's hitting all of them. -She's getting all of them.
-Good Job. -Da Hae's getting them all.
-It didn't break. -Da Hae, good job.
Come forward a little!
They didn't break,
I really hit a lot.
-I also hit a lot? -No. they didn't break.
Mr. Gary got 9.
Mr. Haha got. 16.
-Oh yeah! -Wow.
-That's already a lot. -They did it.
Miss Lee Da Hae hit 9 balloons, like Mr Gary.
Ok. success!
-A total of 34. -Yeah!
-Da Hae did well. -Looks like we can be first.
We did it.
-Please go to the restaurant on the third floor. -Go, go! We have to go quickly.
-Look, we must hurry. -Hey. looks likes we can be the first today,
-Oppa. I did well right? -Oh. it was the best, the best.
Wow. this is interesting.
Start!
Throw some this side too.
-Oh, oh, it's not working again. -Gwang Soo's not hitting them, Gwang Soo can't do it.
Oh. what's this?
Hey, Gwang Soo,
Gwang Soo.
Why is there so much water splashing on me?
Hey!
Hey, Gwang Soo's hitting the water towards me.
Hey. are you a kangaroo?
Why are you spraying water on Jong Kook. Gwang Soo?
Hey. why are you splashing me with so much water?
Hey. why you...
-Hey, what are you doing? -No, no hyung.
-Hey, you kept doing this. -No.
Hey, I'm completely drenched!
I was like that because I was focused.
-Ah, even if that's the case! -I hit a lot. I got a lot.
No, no. I hit a lot this time.
I really hit a lot this time round.
Gwang Soo was a kangaroo.
Ok. Mr Kim Jong Kook broke 18 water balloons in total this round.
Ah, Gwang Soo didn't hit them well, he didn't.
Mr Lee Gwang Soo broke. 19 and succeeds.
Hey. our teamwork is great, right?
-Seems like we'll be first. -Yes!
-Yeah. -Of course,
-It's here. Running Man, here. -What floor is it?
Here, here, it's inside.
We're here,
-Oh? -Mikes. -What's this?
Headphone karaoke speed quiz. Answer 5 questions or more correctly in 60 seconds to pass.
member from the team will put on headphones to guess the title of the song sung by the other members.
Hey, you sing with Da Hae,
What does it mean?
-You have it on while I sing? -It's a speed quiz.
So you have to know a lot of songs.
Ok.
-Ok, fighting. -I can't hear anything.
Pay attention to the motions.
The motions, got it? The motions.
60 seconds, start!
I don't want to hear sad songs...
-♫Crying, like this...♫ -Pass, pass.
Ah, how to do this?
Pass if you don't know!
Train.train.
Playing with Trains.
The East, the East Sea.
Hunting Whales.
-♫Gee Gee Gee Gee. baby baby baby.♫ -SNSD. Gee. Gee!
My darling
-The One and Only You. -Correct, correct.
-Ah, One and a Half! -Ok. ok!
Isn't it too easy?
-♫you and I...♫ -IU.IU!
You and I!
Why is it over already?
It wasn't even 30 seconds.
! can't hear, what happened?
-The time's up. -He didn't even know southbound Train'.
Guys... I came after a shower.
Ah. hyung.
Oh cold, it's very cold.
-Cold, oh cold. -Oh. it's cold.
Oh. it's cold.
Start!
My shirt got wet because of you.
You don't even know me
How would I ever know you?
-♫You were born naked and at least you got an outfit♫ -You have to name the title.
The title,
-Life... is futile. -The title!!
The title!
You don't even know me
-Tatata. -Right!
-♫I have a dream...♫ - Goose's Dream!
Flip it quickly!
Ah. my fingernails, my fingernails are too short.
I'm willing to do this ♫
The Clown Laughs at Me.
-The Clown Laughs at Me. -Do it like this,
The Clown...
Us, us.
-Whatever, pass. -The clown...
The Crying Clown.
When yon want to dance, then dance
Even grandfathers and grandmothers are dancing too
Age doesn't mean a thing
Everyone sing together
Like this
Bear with it. Bear with it.
Do I have to know to use chopstick we If to eat
Hey, smile.
Hyung.
Then what do we do. shall I go first?
-Look at my mouth, my mouth. -I got it. don't worry,
-Get ready! -Oppa. oppa just has to get five.
-Five, five! -Just five.
Start!
-♫Again and again and again♫ - 'Again and Again'!
We keep going around and around
Namee's 'Spin Spin'!
-♫I've totally become a bird♫ -'Bird'!
-'Bird'! -Yeah!
Looking for food. In the valley.
Leopard of Kilimanjaro!
Oh, friend forever
-Do 'I promise you' Ji Hyo. -Oh, my friend forever.
-♫Promise me♫ -Fin.K.L!
Forever Love,
We're done. We're doneiwe're done.
-We succeeded? -Hey, we succeeded.
Success!
-We passed it in one try. -One try!
The questions are too.easy.
But how did you guess 'Leopard of Kilimanjaro'?
Hey, how did you know 'Leopard of Kilimanjaro'?
Panicking to find something to eat.
Swishing in the wind,
I said 'looking for food' and he just guessed it.
-It's a come from behind victory. -Ah. we were dead last.
-From last to first. -I feel so good.
-Hey. this is important. -Hey. how many are there?
-This is really important. -First place is the best.
Hey. how can it be so small?
-Shall we have a look? -This isn't fair.
-Why is first place so small? -Do we open it?
-It's the best right? -Open it and see.
-Can we open it now? -What's this? Is it a present?
-Ours is the smallest. -Why is it so small?
-It's name tags. -Oh. it's name tags?
They are wings.
-What's with the wings? -They have wings.
Angels, you guys are angels.
-It's cute, cute. These are cute. -Hey. these guys.
What is it. what is it?
You're the best. The best comedy duo.
You're going to fly.
They'll fly,
-They'll be wearing wings. -Aigoo. my stomach!
-They'll, they'll fly. -Ah. my stomach.
Hey, you have to walk. You'll fly if you run.
It looks quite good.
-He's going to fly. he's going to fly. Ah. it's cute!
Like this, rip!
-No. oppa. -Hey. we can do this today!
-Oppa. put it on his shoulders. -That's not it, look at Jong Kook,
-Oh. really... -Jong Kookie's an angel.
Look at the wings on his shoulders from the side.
Ok. then we'II tell you the final mission now.
Today's final mission, is to find the Spy.
What?
-There's a Spy? -There's a Spy amongst you.
-What's this again? -Then, it's Da Hae!
Find the Spy before he succeeds in the mission and get him out.
-I knew it. -A Spy?
Ok now, Team 1 will enter the mission venue first.
What... who. who is the Spy? Huh?
Hey, it's really, really a;huge place.
But. what do we do now?
We can't tear off each other's name tags.
What's the mission?
They're working, even though it's a rest day. Hello.
They're here for work.
Do the people here have, some mission?
No?
What did you say?
-Please come with me. -But, why?
What is it? Are you making me the Spy again now? Huh?
I won't be the Spy.
I, don't want to.
But. why again...
Ah. this is seriously...
Ah, this again...
You want to make me the Spy now?
Why are you doing this, seriously? This is just...
Jeez, if you want me to do it again.
Well this once.... I'll do it again.
I'll just do the mission.
What is it?
Huh?
I have to find the employee with the R sticker on them?
Rendezvous with the employee with the R sticker on them.
And then?
Then when you find him. carry out a task.
You can't let the rest find out about the missions.
Hence, you have to complete three stages of missions.
I'm really going crazy.
What do I do?
Don't be like this, give me a water gun.
I can't do this.
If it's like this, I'll be exposed right away. I'll be exposed.
Today. I don't have the rhythm. I shouldn't be the Spy now.
They will suspect me right away.
They'll say "It should be Jae Suk hyung's turn to be the Spy".
When I heard it I thought I should be the Spy too.
Like what I said. Ok?
-Also, listen to what I have to say... -Ah firstly. I don't know.
Well. I'll work hard, I can't do anything if it doesn't work.
This is bad.
I'm not confident. I'm not confident about this.
Seriously...
You be careful, we can't expose ourselves.
Find the employee with the R sticker.
Someone with the R on them.
This is bad.
Why am I going in alone?
Oppa, when did you come?
I was the first person to come in.
-Oppa, I thought we'd come in together. -No. they made us come in. one at a time.
-Individually? -Individually.
-Oppa, do you want to tear mine off now? -Why would I tear yours off?
-I'm not the Spy, oppa. -I know.
Because you've been the Spy recently.
-Actually I suspect oppa. -Why?
Oppa hasn't been a spy. for a while.
You're saying that based on me not being a Spy for awhile,
Miss Ji Hyo. please come this way,
There's an exit here.
In the past, we really ran a lot in the emergency exits.
Omo!
Oh. oh!
You are the Spy,
From now on. rendezvous with the secret agent to accept the task you have to carry out.
Look for the employee with the R sticker on their body and recite the password.
Blooming flowers on Dongbaekseom
My heart is pounding again.
How do I act this out?
Oh. I'm very bad at this, what do I do?
Where is it?
I believe I can fly
Here?
I believe I can touch the sky
What's this about now?
Really, when I came in. my heart almost stopped beating.
You are a spy
Because the fast time was a shame
Although it was a shame, thank you
-We want you to do it again. -No one would suspect it.
The production team has the brain,
R sticker. Is it Running Man?
Ha Dong Hoon who a has good feeling is catching the spy.
It's definitely not me.
Why haven't you say anything? I have been waiting.
I have been waiting.
Thank you very much, teacher
What is this?
Like this. I'm in the middle of being a spy again?
I understand
I waited for a very long time.
I'll do my best.
The shadow is very cool, right? Looks like an angel.
The shadow looks like an angel
Mind control, mind control.
It's crazy.
I don't know what to make of all this. I can't think of anything.
I shouldn't make any mistake.
There seems to be somebody over there.
There is somebody over there.
Enemies everywhere
Because I live alone in this world.
I will eliminate all of them!
Hello
I didn't do something wrong, right?
Today's mission is different from the others.
You are not a spy. Eliminate all the spies.
How many people are spies?
Today. everyone is a spy but Lee Da Hae.
Then...
Da Hae wins if all the spies are eliminated.
How do I do it?
Rip their name tags.
All 7 people?
What to do?
Later in Busan. I will give separate instruction to the members to be spies.
Then they will think they're the only spies and do the spy mission.
Miss Lee Da Hae can eliminate them one by one to become the winner.
I can just tear it right? As soon as I see them?
This is really...
Can you give me a little help?
I'll do my best.
I'M.do my best! Fighting!
Enemies are everywhere
Since I live alone in this world. I will eliminate all of them!
Everyone is a spy, right?
When did you come?
I came last.
-This is making me crazy! -What are you doing, hyung?
Hey, Da Hae is very strange!
-She's very strange -But if Da Hae noona is a spy,
-It's very predictable. -It's very predictable!
Kim Jong Kook looks cool!
It's like you're really flying
-It's not bad right? -Oppa. it really suits you.
Hey. who is it today?
Oppa. today Gwang Soo is acting strange?
Gwang Soo is acting bit strange. Gwang Soo is suspicious.
-I think so too. -Gwang Soo is suspicious...
Gwang Soo is a bit strange.
-What about Lee Da Hae? -Lee Da Hae is a bit...
Anyway, you need to be careful. If you stay in one location, you might get eliminated.
I'm busy looking around,
-You are window shopping? -Yes. I am
l did a little too.
R sticker.
Do-you know the The flower Dongbaekseom?
How do I look for him in this huge place?
I think I have to just try.
Hello.
Blooming flowers on Dongbaekseom
Is where spring arrived
This is really...
Blooming flowers on Dongbaekseom is where spring arrived
I'm sorry.
Oh? It is Da Hae.
Da Hae.
Yes. oppa?
-Earlier, why did you do that during the game? -Doing what?
Earlier you look like a spy.
-Me? -Yes.
No?
What are you doing?
What have you been doing, oppa?
-I have been looking, of course? -Looking for what?
I heard there's a Spy here, so I've been wandering around.
There's a spy?
Da Hae is not a spy. right?
If you are a spy, you are very obvious!
Actually, I don't know what I have to do now.
You don't know what to do, Da Hae?
I don't know.
If you are a spy, you totally fail.
Why is that?
-Because you are very obvious for a spy. -Me?
-You are not a spy. right? -Are you a spy?
Of course I am not.
I'll see you later.
What is she now?
What is Da Hae?
Olivia, where are you going?
Just looking around.
What are you trying to find?
Where are you going?
Oppa is also that?
Then, you too?
Then from what I see, there are 2 spies.
Don't get caught.
Da Hae. you cannot be caught,
-We must quickly eliminate them. -Don't talk to me. just walk straight quickly.
Don't even look at me, understand?
We must eliminate them quickly.
Ok.
The rest of them.
Ok, We can't meet each other again.
-Try not to... The flowers bloom... -Oppa...
Just kill them.
Ok.
Will he kill them? I think he trusts me.
Wow... Really...
I was wondering, how can we be singing the same song?
Can I have a sheet of paper? Thank you.
I have to look like I'm not a spy. a little alibi,
Gwang Soo!
What are you doing?
I am doing some reasoning.
What?
I'm making deduction.
Reasoning what?
Spy.
Hyung. what are these's staff doing?
I also don't know! They wouldn't tell me!
Why are there so many staffs. There are a lot.
It may be real staffs.
But the strange thing is, there are also security guards and all.
Ah. really?
You go that side, I'll go this side.
Like this... Like this?
Like This... Like this?
You go that side.
I missed the timing!
I tried to do it but he stared at me.
Oppa!
What's the situation like over at your side?
Yes.
- Gwang Soo is over there. - Where where where?
Oppa!
We must quickly eliminate them one by one,
I can't do it myself.
Oh? Gwang Soo oppa!
You are a spy right?
I have something to say to you. oppa.
What?
There's no one here I guess.
Where is Gary hyung?
For me... Up until now, after observing everyone's glances...
The situation now looks like this, ,.
It seems like the spies are oppa and myself.
What?
You're a spy?
Quickly, quickly! Get rid of him!
Gary oppa. fighting!
Of course, he is a spy.
As for Gary oppa,
He thinks only the both of us are spies.
In the end. by my hand, he will also...
Get killed...
Next one...
Who is the next one?
Don't let me catch you.
I have confidence now!
Lee Gwang Soo out! Lee Gwang Soo. out!
What is this?
What is happening again?
Hey...
You should already know after coming here,
Then the filming for today has ended?
I am the spy.
Blooming flowers
Blooming flowers in Dongbaekseom...
Is where spring arrived...
Welcome!
Oh, yes!
On the wrist.
Yes.
Ok, I know. You've worked hard.
Ah! I am really going crazy!
After searching for half a day, I have to search again!
Find the staff wearing a red scarf. The rendezvous code is "The one who controls the password!"
Oh dear.
I already said I didn't have a phone.
Why did they give a mobile phone?
If Jong Kook knows of this I'll be caught.
If Jong Kook knows of this I'll be caught!
Why did they suddenly give a mobile phone?
I already told Jong Kook that I did not bring my mobile phone.
Can you see it?
Are you able to see it?
You can see it, right?
Ah, I'm going crazy.
Welcome.
Oh! It's correct?
Oh! Thank you!
This is really not an easy task.
If anybody walks towards me from the back. I will feel uneasy.
But how do I tear off 7 people's?
Oh, I'm going crazy.
Who should I make use of now?
I must go and look for Yoo Jae Suk senior!
I can't do this myself.
Sunbaenim!
Jae Suk oppa!
Oh?
-Why. Da Hae? - Oppa!
After walking around until now. I have discovered...
Oppa. you...
Oppa. you are a spy right?
I am a spy.
What did you say?
You are a spy?
The flowers bloom on Dongbaek Island.
You are also a spy?
But, hey, you are too much of a spy!
Everybody thinks it is you!
That's why!
Da Hae, everybody is suspecting you. isn't it?
They are all suspecting you!
-Are you the one who eliminated Gwang Soo? -We must quickly kill them.
Huh?
We must quickly kill them.
Quickly eliminate them?
-Are you the one who eliminated Gwang Soo? -That means we must quickly kill all of them.
What do you mean kill...
-No. Da Hae... -Oppa. aren't you a spy?
Yes. that's right.
That's why!
You are also a spy?
From when?
I am. of course, from the start.
Yes. I knew it would be like that.
I had to find one by one.
Really?
Are you the one who eliminated Gwang Soo?
Oh? It's not you?
You are... too much of a spy!
What, you are not a spy?
Oh, I'm going crazy.
Jae Suk oppa, really, really!
No, Da Hae...
You're a spy! Go further away!
What are you trying to do?
Look at her! This is simply suffocating me!
Shh!
Da Hae!
You can't do this!
Why are you like this?
You now,..
Do you want to see someone get eliminated by acting like this?
What are you doing?
Please go!
What is this?
Hyung! Hyung! Hyung!
Someone who is more obvious than me!
This is the first time we see someone who is more obvious than me!
This is the best I've ever seen!
Seriously, I...
I'm seriously going crazy!
I'm going first, Da Hae.
Oppa! You have to believe me
Oppa I'm not kidding around with you.
-Da Hae! Da Hae! -I'm being serious!
-It's not that. -♫Blooming flowers... ♫
-♫Blooming flowers on Dongbaekseom♫ -I'm going crazy! Da Hae!
It's not like that.
Although I am a spy too...
Stop calling me Oppa in front of everyone.
I did it on purpose. It's my plan!
Why?
-It's my plan! -What plan?
If this continues we're both done for! We'll both be out.
I'm so tired right now.
-Da Hae. although I understand what you mean... -We have to survive!
They'll want to kill us now.
This is because of you.
Because I'm with you. I'm being. suspected as a spy now!
Da Hae. that's why. You made the wrong move.
Be quiet!
Wow, really.
She wants me to be quiet,
I can't do this, now I have to be quiet.
Are you shushing me because you're scared of being discovered?
I'm going crazy.
I'll really go crazy soon!
-Da Hae... -Oppa, Oppa.
Oppa is a man.
I don't think I can do this myself.
Hold on Da Hae.
Oppa .we have to kill Jong Kook Oppa and everyone else!
Us sitting around like this...
Let's go!
Rather than waiting here...
Hey Da Hae!
-Why don't you just eliminate me! -Shhh!
That's not it.
Da Hae. stop following me.
Just eliminate me now!
Keep quiet!
Go quickly.
For now...
-Right now... -Da Hae.
If you see me pretend you don't know me.
But we're spies!
Da Hae...
So we have to go kill the others quickly!
It's not that, its not like that!
That won't work!
This will make both of us look suspicious.
We have to kill them quickly.
No no!
Why don't you listen to what other people say?
We have to get rid of the...
No Da Hae, not like this.
Please explain to him!
Why is it so hard for us to communicate?
I'm so frustrated! I feel sick.
Do you have any sedatives?
My heart is pounding,
Oppa and I, since the first moments... here, from here on something seems to have gone wrong.
Da Hae it's not like that,
-There's nothing wron... -Listen to me!
I've been listening to you this whole time!
I have to listen to yo again?
From now on.
Right? From there... we'll do that. But. the most important thing for us...
You're too funny!
You're too good at this!
The only way to describe you is very-Daebak!
Very Daebak!
Okay, let's go find Jong Kook Oppa!
What?
If we don't do that we'll die.
Do you want to die?
Da Hae. to be honest.
Before I met you. I wasn't suspected at all.
After I met you. things became like this.
-Okay, let's go for now. -Go for now.
Eliminate them,
Oppa. Fighting!
Don't do that!
-Don't do that. -Oppa, Spies.
What are you doing now!
We are on the same team.
Oh, so frustrating.
I got both of them on my side, right?
Seriously, this is called very-Daebak.
Da Hae's the best, just the best,
Gary, want to come with me?
It's tiring.
Let's just go look for clothes for my wife.
Me? How would I know what hyung's wife likes?
Just think about what your girlfriend would like.
How does this look?
-Just pick some. -Why am I picking?
-This type looks fine. -What?
-You scared me. -You surprised me!
Why are you here?
Really. Please, we're shopping right now.
Da Hae come here,
-You don't need to be like that. -What?
-Hold on. -There's only us here.
What?
Hold on. Why?
Oppa! Oppa!
Oppa!
Oh. what?
Wait a minute.
Hey. Da Hae,
-I'm sorry. -Dae Hae.
What's going on?
Hey! I'm the spy!
Gary is a spy too?
Goodbye.
Gary, out.!
What?
Ji Suk Jin. out!
The person who controls space!
Why is Kang Gary out?
Hey. Jong Kook was with you right?
Did you use your superpower again?
What superpower?
The person who controls space!
-Did you use your superpower again? -The person who controls time.
Hey!
Are you really going to be like this?
Because you do this. I'm going to be suspected.
I've been suspected!
I know you're not. hyung.
-Eh? How do you know? -You know I'm not either right?
I don't think it's you.
Looks like Gary being out had nothing to do with you.
I suspected that it was you at first.
And I suspected you. I thought it was you for sure!
Why?
Because you're talking with Da Hae.
Hold on! Who's that?
-What is it? -Gary hyung is escorted.
-Hey Gary! -Hyung, are you okay?
Hyung! What are you doing?
What are you doing? Come here first.
Come here first.
Please take care of him.
Come here first, hyung!
What's going on?
Sorry about that, Dong Hoon!
What is this?
What were you doing, hyung?
I thought you were a spy.
Come over here.
I'm speechless.
Ha Ha. just go to the jail. I'll tell you later.
He didn't see this, did he? That hyung.
What are we going to do? What should we do?
I've been running around like this by myself.
Why isn't Yoo Jae Suk sunbaenim helping me?
Why! Why!
Since he's on the same side as me.
HaHa. out! HaHa. out!
HaHa's out?
He's out?
Yoo Jae Suk sunbaenim!
He's giving me help though.
This is great!
Then. I'm more comfortable. This is good.
Good job! Yoo Jae Suk sunbaenim. you did well!
I'll tear yours off later!
Hyung! You've been too busy!
Why?
You've been acting like you're busy.
-Me? -Yeah.
I'm just wandering around right now.
Should I just sit back?
Hyung walk slowly. You might run out of energy.
Hyung is the most suspicious now. So you can't die just yet-
The longer he's suspected, the more it helps me.
I need to eliminate Jong Kook quickly. Better hurry now,..
We came here before.
Is that her?
Find the staff that's wearing a red scarf! Rendezvous signal is "Password Controller"
Hello.
The one who control the password!
Anything else?
Searching gain?!
It took me 2 hours just to find this person-
What is this!
Do you want me to kick your butt?
Really.
Where is he? Where is this person?
You don't know? Can you tell me?
It looks like a battery.
Usually.., when the battery is inserted... Shouldn't this work when I press it?
But if the battery is empty...
Da Hae!
Da Hae.
Oppa.
How is the mission going?
Da Hae come over here, You'll get spotted if you stand there.
Da Hae what are you standing"there for?
I'll be discovered here.
Forget it.
The each of us must eliminate someone now.
Because they have great suspicion on you.
I also said I was suspicious of you.
I have no choice.
This is teamwork Da Hae.
But. didn't say I suspected oppa or anything like that,
That's why l'm being suspected.
Because you didn't say that you suspected me.
But we are together.
Yes we are together.
I don't want to!
No.
We are together why must we be like this? Why must we slander each other?
Da Hae. haven't you watched Running Man before?
We are together so we must help each other.
No. that's not it.
Who should we kill?
- We must hurry. - Jong Kook is on 2nd floor.
It doesn't benefit us if we delay the time.
-Let's go to the 2nd floor first. -Catch him from the front then tear his name tag from the back.
Jong Kook cannot be caught.
I'll go look for Jong Kook first. Understand?
Jae Suk oppa is getting the table ready,
I just have to put the spoon down.
And just have to eat now.
Where did everybody go?
Hyung! Who's that?
Is that hyung?
Jae Suk hyung! Da Hae's at 1st floor!
Da Hae's at 1st floor!
Oppa. now is not the time.
Why...?
Why not?
Oppa. now is not the time.
-Me? Why? -Hey! Da Hae!
Where were you?
Oppa. the mission. Spy? I'm the spy!
What did you say?
Where were you?
I'm here.
But every time you're not around, one person will just be out.
Why are you being like this to me? I'm also very uneasy now.
Why are you avoiding me?
Where is Ji Hyo?
-Jong Kook where is Ji Hyo? -I don't know.
Oppa! I'm also a spy. I'm a spy.
Where is Ji Hyo?
Why oppa?
How can I tear it?
Jae Suk oppa.
Jong Kook calm down.
My heart is beating so fast now!
Good job!
That's how it should be done!
What about Ji Hyo unni?
Wait. Jong Kook is no more and there's only Ji Hyo left.
There's no need to hide anymore!
Oppa you go first. I'll catch on later.
In the worst scenario I'M tear your name tag in front of Ji Hyo.
What?
Team victory is all that matters!
The worst scenario is I'll tear your name tag.
Then just eliminate Ji Hyo will do!
No this won't do!
Oppa.
Hey! Hey! JI Hyo! Ji Hyo!
Ji Hyo it's Da Hae! It's Da Hae!
How did Jong Kook oppa get eliminated?
-I don't know. I don't know. - Hello.
Hello. It been a long time.
How was he eliminated?
It's Da Hae!
In the worst scenario, I'll tear your name tag in front of Ji Hyo.
What?
Team victory is all that matters!
The worst scenario is I'll tear your name tag.
Then just eliminate Ji Hyo will do!
-There's a criminal among us, a spy? -Of course there is! Of course!
Oppa. you're the spy right?
-Ji Hyo. -I saw it.
What?
Oppa tore it.
Yes I tore Gwang Soo's name tag!
Jong Kook oppa's too!
You said I tore Jong Kook's name tag?
Then I did it? I tore it off?
Really this acting! Who am I supposed to trust?
This is so confusing.
Da Hae you're the spy right?!
What?
You're the spy right?
Really, ,. Your reaction is too 1 dimensional!
Did you get anything? Did you receive any mission?
I didn't receive anything...
So you're just strolling around?
Just strolling around.
Then you didn't stroll?
Our aim is to catch the spies right?
Yes.
He's the Spy!
You know he's pretending.
Unni.
Trust me this time! Really!
I'll give up the number 1 spot to you! Really!
So if you tear it down. I'll give you the first spot!
Then quickly tear it!
Fantastic!
I almost fell into your trap
I almost walked past you.
Oppa. you're really too much.
So this is the end?
So simply like this?
How did you know, Da Hae?
-Oppa.♫-You really are a Fantastic kid.
Why do you always make me so confused
AH! Really!
Fantastic!
Yoo Jae Suk. Out!
- Yoo Jae Suk. Out! -What?
-What? He's out? -Hyung. who eliminated you?
-Lee Da Hae! -What?!
-Hyung, aren't you a spy? -I also got eliminated by Lee Da Hae.
-Hyung are you a spy? You aren't a spy right? -You're a spy?
Wow, I'm surprised.
So hyung and Lee Da Hae are both spies?
Yeah!
I only found when I came here.
-When I first came here they made me a spy. -Wow, he's a spy.
-It was like this since we came. -What I want to say is.
I told Haha earlier,
the atmosphere was weird
Under no circumstances, whenever there's a spy. I'm always being suspected,
I wondered what happened to hyung
What's that?
It's a mission.
What's that? What's the mission?
Rendezvous password is "Kick the butt".
That's why there were staffs.
Is that the last one?
-It's the last one. -Hyung, as the spy, shouldn't you be surviving till the end?
-Why are you eliminated -The result is out, please go to the 9fh floor.
Huh? It has ended?
-Has it really ended? -It can't possibly be that Blank Ji won?
Can everyone please make your way to the 9tfi floor.
Wait a moment, we just go to 9th floor?
Before we go. do you want to sing a song first?
No way, what about singing songs
1, 2, 3 . 4
Blooming flowers on Dongbaekseom
Together with the mates from the village
Playing together happily
Love you!!
We got scammed by the ladies!
We all got cheated! Hyung, we all got cheated!
-We were cheated! -You thought you were a spy alone?
-We're all spies!! -We all are!!
-What? -We're all spies!
-We've all been used! -We are?
What are you saying?
Together with the mates from the village
When she's doing this to hyung...
Da Hae was also doing this with me.
Ya! This is really...
So you guys knew it from the start!
It's Lee Da Hae.
Oppa! Faster come over here and chat with us!
Let's talk! Come here and talk! Faster!
Ji Hyo are you eliminated?
Daebak!
That's why I was killed.
Wow, really.
-Hey, Lee Dae Hae! -Hey! Lee Dae Hae!
-Eat well and live well! -But, how did you know about the song?
Eh?
-Right. -Just what I was saying..
-She overheard Jae Suk sang the song earlier. -Oh really?
Ah! Jae Suk!
Jae Suk hyung was the one that caused everything today!
I'm... really everybody...
The lesson learnt today is: Woman must be chosen very carefully.
It was all because of her acting! It's ail acting!
-Everyone here today totally got cheated by Da Hae! -I didn't even do one mission!
But whatever the case, Lee Da Hae. victorious! Congratulations!
Lee Da Hae had made a call
In the Busan Special, there is a bundle
-We've reached! -They all came
Where is it?
I found it!
Ahh! Don't come over! Don't come over!