[An X-man is amongst them!]
[Running Man vs. X-man...
the cutthroat mind battle]
[Just who is the X-man that is throwing
the competition into chaos?]
[Running Man vs. X-man starts now!]
[Incheon 'S' shopping mall]
[Overtly excitement]
Our biggest trouble maker!
Just how long am I going to
wander for?
- It's because it's Autumn!
- Look at Gary... look at Gary.
- Go stand over there by yourself.
- I really missed you.
- I love you.
- I love you, Gary.
I really like you.
- I love you.
- I miss you even as I'm looking at you.
- You're embarrassed, aren't you?
- Why am I so embarrassed?
Promise us that you'll never do it again!
This is a year's worth... a year's worth.
Just get it all out now.
I want this kind of attention too.
Anyways, to our viewers,
we're sorry for making you all worried.
He's returned.
The fact that he's returned
is what's important.
- Of course, it is.
- The one who was going to leave us.
- We're going to work even harder.
- The fans overseas were very worried.
- Is that right? I'm sure they were.
- I am sorry.
- What do we have today?
- What is this? Another Ddak-ji match?
Last week, I...
[Chuseok last week]
[The Absolute Ddak-ji that was created
with all their might.]
[In just one shot!]
[King of Ddak-ji, who didn't even get
the chance to try his hand at it...]
- It's because my team didn't get the chance.
- Why do you say that every single time?
All I seriously am asking for is one chance!
Seriously... I'm sure they set this up so that
we can have another Ddak-ji match today.
Seeing the wedding cake over here,
it looks like we're going to have a guest?
- If they go to these kind of lengths...
- They did this for Ha Ji Won the last time.
Yeah, they did something
similar to that back then.
And this is similar to when Ji Sung was
on the show too... maybe Ji Sung is back.
Our today's guest... please,
come on out!
Back up... I can't see anything
because of you, Kwang Soo!
[From inside the wedding cake?]
[Shocking the members of Running Man...]
[The entrance of that woman...]
[The ideal image of a woman...
Moon Geun Young!]
- Wait...
- What!
Appearing out of nowhere like magic...
- Moon Geun Young!
- Be careful!
- Help her down!
Hey, take off your coat and
cover up her skirt for her!
[The Giraffe carefully guiding her down.]
- Get out of the way now!
- What are you doing?
- Miss Moon!
- Yes...
It's so great to see you!
[The original Nation's little sister
has turned into a mature woman.]
What took you so long to come
on the show?
This is... our Miss Moon Geun Young!
- Your skin is really nice!
- She's seriously so cute!
- She's just glowing!
- She's literally sparkles!
Oh my goodness... look at her eyes!
- Geun Young, have you been well?
- Yes, have you been well?
What are you doing? Why are
you acting like you know her well?
I got flustered too.
This is actually my first time meeting her,
and my words just popped out like that.
- You got flustered?
- I got flustered!
She's just so sweet! So sweet and kind!
- This is my first time meeting her...
- Seriously?
- It's been awhile...
- Stop!
She has always been one of my
favorite female celebrities...
[A female celebrity that Kook likes?]
- I've always really liked her!
- I've never seen you acting like this.
I even mentioned in an interview in the
past that she's my ideal woman.
- Really?
- Geun Young is your ideal woman?
I never imagined
that she would be on our show.
We're sorry, but we need Geun Young
to speak up a little louder.
Yes...
[Everyone just keeps on
talking about themselves.]
But why is your MC'ing such a
mess today?
You should take better care of our guest.
You need to quit!
By any chance,
did you know about this incident...
- What do you mean, an incident?
- Why are you calling it that?
- Our incident...
- Do you know about Gary's incident?
Yes, I know.
Then does it mean that you have
some interest in me?
Yes, Gary is the reason why I
watch Running Man.
- Seriously? Because of me?
- Yes.
Yes... I really like watching him.
- Then you must have been shocked!
- I want you to quit!
I can't quit now!
- I can't quit now!
- He says he can't quit now...
I'm going to keep doing
the show for Geun Young.
It really has been awhile since Geun Young
has been on screen like this.
I heard that you're a big fan
of our show.
Yes, I really like it.
I make sure to watch it every week.
- Did you watch last week's Ddak-ji match?
- Yes, I saw it!
What are you doing?
[Muscle Boy with a lot of things
to show off today.]
Did you by any chance watch
the wrestling portion too?
You were the best!
[His self-confidence that's been crumbled
to shambles in front of Geun Young.]
With how the things are set up today,
aren't you reminded of X-man?
Why is this out here?
When we did our X-man thing,
this is what we used for dance initiation.
Yeah, I remember that.
[A hot opening for every show of X-man.]
[The memorable dance initiations.]
All the staff that we have now are the same
ones we had when we did X-man in the past.
Why don't we revive those old memories?
You know Jong Kook's moves for this, right?
The move that we couldn't stand.
Yeah, this move.
Whenever we asked him to get up there,
he'd get up there and do this...
[The same music from those times!]
- You start it, you start.
- I don't want to start it.
[Starting with Haroro who mentioned
he wants to relieve the memories.]
- You need to start it. Come on.
- Why am I the one to start it?
Having you telling me to do it
all of a sudden is making me feel burdened.
[Breaking out the moves!]
[Dancing as if he's been
waiting for this moment.]
He's doing great! These are
the moves that you needed to do.
[Busting out a move with his short legs.]
Kwang Soo... Kwang Soo!
[No matter what kind of a music it is...
the bendy moves come busting out.]
- Now, Ji Hyo!
- Blank Ji... Blank Ji!
[Blank Ji's turn!]
[No matter what music is playing,
Blank Ji always reverts back to Hot Issue.]
Gary!
[The Autumn man, Gary!]
[This is a performance dancing skills!]
- Gary!
- Suk Jin, it's Suk Jin's turn.
- I don't want to do it...
- No, you have to do it too.
[No matter what music is playing,
it's 'Woo-sa' dance.]
Okay, Kim Jong Kook!
[The heavy Muscle Man's dance.]
Ugh, that's gross!
Just go back to your shifting.
Miss Moon... Miss Moon!
- Miss Moon!
- Show us the wave!
- Wave?
- Wave!
Miss Moon, show us another wave!
[Geun Young's wave to melt any
man's heart.]
[Finishing it off with some popping!]
Yoo Jae Suk! Yoo Jae Suk!
[Dancing Machine, Jae Suk]
[Eyes ablaze... and a serious expression.]
- Take off your glasses! Your glasses!
- Look at you dance!
[Totally awkward]
- Shuffle! Do the shuffle!
- Nice!
[I'm the King of the shuffle!]
- He's really good! Look at his dancing!
- He's a really good dancer!
It looks like he's been practicing!
[Ending it with a lively shake.]
Why are you trying so hard to
dance well?
- Do your moves like this!
- Do this move!
You know, this move!
- I did all those moves too!
- No, you didn't! You were seriously trying!
It's because Miss Moon is on the show!
[The dancing spirit]
[Putting in an effort because
Geun Young is watching?]
Anyway...
it's been a really long time since
we've done the dance initiation like that.
That was really energizing.
- How are the teams being divided?
- Today's mission...
Is X-man vs. Running Man.
There's an X-man amongst us then?
What is X-Man vs. Running Man?
Do you all remember how an X-man
is selected?
'You are not the X-man'.
It's really been a long time!
- In the same method...
- Is Yoon Eun Hye not going to be on then?
[A rightful memory that follows
the theme...]
Hey! Jong Kook just said that he liked
Geun Young, which he never does...
it's the first time he's ever said
anything like that!
This is the first time he's ever said anything
about liking any of our female guests.
- Really?
- Yes, this is the first time.
I've really liked him too since
his days as part of Turbo.
- How old were you?
- How old were you back then?
- I was in Elementary School...
- An elementary student?
Only one person out of the eight of you
will be selected as X-man.
And the remaining seven will be
Running Man.
When we did X-man,
the guests were always X-man.
- Right?
You will be divided into two teams,
and will play games all over Incheon.
And each time a team wins a game...
they can trade one person they suspect to
be the X-man every round that they win.
- Ah... we can trade?
- The team that wins?
I bet we're just going to keep wanting to
trade for Geun Young without regards to X-man.
The team without the X-man in
the final round is the winning team.
Ah... the team without the X-man?
X-man has to carry out a special mission
that's given to them during the race.
And in the case that the X-man completes
the special mission by the final mission...
the X-man is the ultimate winner without
any regards to any of the teams.
By the end of the whole race?
In the case that the X-man fails the mission,
the team without the X-man will win.
And if the X-man succeeds the mission,
then X-man would be the ultimate winner.
I'm sure that the X-man will be given
something special then, right?
Ah! The selection process!
It really has been a long time.
Why don't we do it exactly the same way
as we did during our X-man days?
Okay... let's start the selection process.
- There it is... the phone's ringing.
- Dong Hoon...
[Starting with Haroro]
The one thing that's changed is
the phone has gotten much better.
Hello?
It's been awhile, Ha Ha.
Okay, I will give you the command.
You are...
X-man...
[Is he or not?]
- This is reminding me of the old days.
- Doesn't it?
- Okay, I will give you the command.
- Sure, sure.
You are...
X-man...
[Is the surprised Jong Kook the X-man?]
You are...
X-man...
[Is the astonished Gary X-man?]
You are...
X-man...
[Is it Jae Suk with the smile on his face?]
You are...
X-man...
Yes, thank you.
[What? A 'Thank you'?]
You are...
X-man...
I understand.
[Blank Ji with that meaningful expression?]
Really?
[Could it be Impala brother?]
- I've heard a lot about you.
- Ah, yes...
You are...
X-man...
[Is Giraffe with his
energetic reaction, the X-man?]
[X-man has now been selected.
Just who among this group...]
Everyone now change into your team
uniform and get in the car matching your team
and in it, you will find the location
where your first mission will take place.
- Everyone, please move on to the location.
- Yes! Let's go!
- Just who...
- Who is...
-Who is X-man?
- Who is it?
- Are you curious?
If you're curious,
it'll cost you 500 won.
Just who do you think X-man is?
It's me.
I'm your ex.
[X-man is ex-boyfriend?]
[X-man vs. Running Man - Start!]
[Go to Incheon Cultural Center and
find the Running Man landmark.]
- It's right next to this place.
- It's right next to this place?
Let's get this started!
[Blue team is on their way!]
So... is there X-man in this car or not?
Who do you think it is?
There's a good possibility that
it's you, Geun Young.
- That's right.
- Yes, I'm X-man.
[Acknowledging it so innocently like this?]
- You really are X-man, aren't you?
- Yes.
- I think you are.
- How am I supposed to do this?
Even if you are,
we're not going to trade you.
Right? Please don't trade me.
Even through to the end,
we're not going to trade you.
I'm just going to lose today.
Why do you think that you won't
get traded?
- It's because I'm not the one.
- It could happen, it could happen.
I'm not X-man, and...
I always work very hard.
In my opinion, the one that we think is X-man,
we should keep him around to the very end...
- That's a way to do it too.
- So that we don't get suspected.
- Geun Young... wow...
- You're pretty cunning too, aren't you?
- It's because I watch it all the time.
- No kidding.
What are you going to do,
since you said you like Gary...
- Are you disappointed?
- I'm going to trade for him later.
[Giraffe getting a feeling about his fate?]
So what he said was that we can trade
one of our members per game?
Is the other team going to take
one of ours?
Don't you think the winning team gets
the chance to trade one of their members?
- It's the winning team's chance.
- The winning team can kick someone out?
So the reason Gary passed out
this apple juice is because of that...
- Why? Why?
- Apple juice... (Apple=apology in Korean)
- Apple juice to signify his apology...
- Is that what it was?
- You didn't know, did you?
- No, I didn't know.
- I was wondering why Gary...
- Apologize to me too.
Apple juice because he wanted
to apologize...
That's why he passed out the apple juice
to everyone today.
- After talking with my managers...
- This is really cute.
Yeah, it is cute.
I was going to write letters...
- Geun Young, do you have a boyfriend?
- No, I don't.
Jong Kook is single too right now.
Stop it! Do you know how old she is?
- What does it matter?
- It's weird because you're overreacting!
Your overreaction is
what's weird right now.
- Her age and my age...
- Why is your face turning red?
Why can't you even look in her direction?
[Can't even look at Geun Young]
Why are you getting so embarrassed?
You should be making her feel comfortable.
You're the one who's acting
uncomfortable right now!
Why are you only staring straight ahead?
I've seriously been a fan of hers forever.
I seriously have always been your fan.
You know that movie
where you get married young...
- The Young Bride?
- The Young Bride, yeah!
I've been your fan
ever since I saw you in that.
Since you were even younger back then,
it's not that I liked you as a woman...
Are you not looking at her right now
then because she's of age?
I thought that it would be nice to have
a daughter like your character...
But then you started to see her
as a woman?
What are you talking about?
She is a woman. One glance and you can
tell that she's become a woman.
She's become a woman.
[Trying to open up a love line.]
Let's make her feel comfortable.
You like her! You like her!
Should we ask him a question where
he replies 'of course'?
- This is really reminding me of the past!
- I really used to like him...
She's saying that
she really used to like X-man!
- X-man really was a lot of fun, wasn't it?
- Yes, it was.
With you and Eun Hye...
[Gripping the wheel out of
embarrassment?]
Hey, why are you guys being like this?
That was so romantic!
- Of course!
[Ha-Kwang brothers immersed in their fun.]
- Stop it...
- Of course!
Don't think that I won't beat you
just because Geun Young is here.
Of course!
We're here!
Thankfully, we're here.
[Already having arrived at their location?]
Even his voice has become deeper.
[Mission location - Incheon Cultural Center]
They're walking hand in hand!
We're the first to arrive, aren't we?
All the races today will be played
team against team.
Please wait for them.
How many times have I told you not to
make her feel uncomfortable?
- Why, Jong Kook? What's wrong with you?
- Don't you think we're being casual?
[Barely containing his smile
from the happiness he feels?]
Just be casual and
make Geun Young feel comfortable.
Do you like Geun Young?
Of course!
I said, stop it!
Why is it that you can only
look in our direction?
Do you see how they're both standing
with their hands in their pockets?
I said, stop it...
No way!
Treat Geun Young comfortably
like any other time we've had guests.
We should make it fun for her...
Then shall we link arms
and shout 'Fighting'?
[No matter what he ends up saying,
those two pounce on his words.]
- She's like your little sister!
- Just do it!
- Let's just all do it together!
- Fine! She is like my little sister!
They were in each other's arms!
[Roro and the Giraffe having too much fun.]
[Red Team arrives]
- Miss Moon...
- Yes?
- Did you have a nice ride here?
- Yes, I did.
Things are going very well
for these two right now.
- No, no, no! It's not like that.
- Then are you my Sister-in-law now?
- They were even in each other's arms!
- Seriously?
- He still hasn't gotten over Eun Hye yet.
- Seriously!
- I said, don't do that!
- I said, okay!
Why? Are you embarrassed about it?
Do you know how he drove here?
He drove like this.
[Showing off his embarrassed driving style]
When did I do that?
I was about to make a turn!
That's why!
Your first mission is... Catch the tail.
- That sounds like fun!
- But...
This catch the tail is to rip off the
name tag.
The team with a surviving member wins.
Grab on like that?
Do we all have tails then?
Do we have tails or not?
I seriously don't get it.
[Impala's weakness to outdoors...]
- Geun Young...
- Yes?
[Each team's tails are Ha Ha vs. Jae Suk.]
[The key is to rotate as fast as you can
towards the other team.]
Geun Young grabbed me.
What am I supposed to do now?
[Big nosed brother with his eyes
on Ha Ha's name tag?]
[Haroro escaping with lightning speed.]
[Ha Ha taking this opportunity!]
[Jae Suk's name tag!]
[Desperately holding onto the name tag!]
[Red Team in danger!]
[Huh?]
Hey! What are you doing?
[Kook not able to see anything
in front of him.]
We can tear it off... it's almost there.
What the heck are you doing?
Listen... I think Kwang Soo is X-man.
- Why me?
- It's Kwang Soo.
- He covered me up on purpose with my hood.
Jong Kook, you didn't see it,
but Kwang Soo's expression was real.
[Stopping in the middle of the game
to point fingers at Kwang Soo as X-man.]
But this catch the tail game is pretty fun.
[Without regards to winning or X-man,
he's just having fun playing catch the tail.]
I've never played anything like this before.
This is so much fun.
This is one of game show basics.
I've never played it before though.
I've just heard people talk about it.
[That aside...
Is Kwang Soo really the X-man?]
- Fighting!
- Fighting.
- Grab him... just grab him
- Grab him!
Grab him, grab him!
[Tail Kwang Soo with his eye on
Jae Suk's name tag.]
He's got us!
[With his long arm!]
[Giraffe's long arm surprise attack!]
- Ji Hyo!
- That's right!
[Working with Ji Hyo to get out
of danger!]
Good, good. Bend the arm!
[Now Giraffe is the one in danger.]
[Help me...]
[Huh?]
[Jae Suk's name tag!]
[His name tag... is in Geun Young's hand!]
- We got it! Got it!
- When did you rip it off?
- We got it!
- Geun Young got it!
[Surprise attack that happened
in a span of moments.]
[During the moment that Jae Suk and
Ji Hyo were tangled up together...]
[With the speed of light,
Geun Young eliminates his name tag!]
[Amazing sense of competitiveness!]
- Fighting!
- That was the best!
- Oh goodness!
- That's crazy!
- That was awesome!
- Geun Young is awesome!
[Totally bowled over by
Geun Young's competitiveness.]
That's unbelievable!
Those name tags aren't easy to
tear off either!
Jae Suk is acting strange.
[Being cast suspicious as soon as
his name tag has been ripped off.]
- He showed his back to me.
- She said you turned your back on her.
- You kept turning your back towards me.
- See? She said you turned your back!
- Miss Moon, when did I do that?
- You were practically begging me to rip it.
I was so busy trying to fight off
these two!
- I think he's the X-man...
- Seriously...
[Is Jae Suk really the X-man?]
- Okay, let's go.
- Okay!
[Blue Team's 4 vs. Red Team's 3]
Please don't stare at me like that!
You think I'll go easy on you?
There's no way.
He's got him, he's got him.
Hold onto him!
[Blocking the lead right away.]
[Each team's tails are Ji Hyo and
Kwang Soo.]
Get him, get him!
[Blank Ji on the attack!]
[Going up face to face with the Giraffe.]
Ji Hyo, Ji Hyo, Ji Hyo!
That's right! Good!
What is this?
Wait! What are you doing?
[His hooded sweatshirt has been taken off...]
You can't take off my shirt!
Where's my name tag!
[Giraffe's deeply hidden sweatshirt.]
- Where is it?
- Where did it go?
- Here it is, here it is.
- Catch the tail is so much fun!
Here? Is it here?
[Blank Ji's definitive chance!]
[Damn...]
You're doing good, Ji Hyo. Great job!
[Normally impossible Man vs. Woman match.]
[How can this be? Geun Young
quickly rips off another name tag!]
She ripped it off again?
- You're a killer!
- You're totally a killer!
- She's a killer!
- This is unbelievable!
Moon Geun Young is not the X-man.
There's no way Geun Young is the X-man.
She really doesn't act like one.
Geun Young could be the X-man,
but she may just be overly excited right now.
Seriously...
how does she rip them off like that?
- This is really unbelievable.
- It is unbelievable.
This makes no sense!
Why do you keep picking games that
use strength lately?
How can you say that? Can you
say that when Geun Young's doing it?
What you're saying isn't right.
It's all strength based...
If you don't use your strength at something,
what is it that you're good at?
- Why don't you tell me?
- Look here... what did you say?
I said, if you don't use your strength,
what is it that you can do?
How old are you?
- What year were you born?
- I was born in '79. Why?
- Seriously...
- You're going to win for being old?
- Then I guess your team wins!
- Watch your mouth!
[Impala getting worked up over
the age talk.]
This is really exhausting.
Let's go grab him...
he's going down anyways.
[Plans to win by blocking the lead
and with Geun Young's speed.]
[Blue Team's 4 vs. Red Team's 2]
It's over once you grab onto him
using your strength.
[Cutting them off from their
ability to move.]
[Now it's Geun Young's turn
to rip the name tag.]
I can't get a grip on it because
it's being blocked!
- If we're stuck like this...
- Got it! We got it!
We got it!
[The Blue Team easily wins again!]
You said that it was fun, Suk Jin.
You liked playing catch the tail...
- I'm just going to have fun.
- End it quickly.
- Get it over with quickly.
- I'm going in.
Quickly... quickly!
How can your running be so slow?
Go the opposite way.
[A unique way to offer himself.]
Ji Suk Jin! Ji Suk Jin!
[Ultimately, facing them off head on?]
[Red team - Complete defeat]
- This is really hurtful to my pride.
- We did it! We did it!
Now it's time to move on to
the second mission location.
But before you do that, you have the chance
to switch out a member with the other team.
Ah, the winning team can?
Our team doesn't want to trade.
Can you tell that to the other team?
What should we do?
- Then... let's trade Jong Kook for Gary.
- Okay.
Seriously, you guys are...
Since the next round
won't be about strength.
Seriously, how can you guys... wow...
- We like it.
- Isn't this how it usually works?
Yes, I'm sure it is.
Lee Kwang Soo...
you're the X-man, aren't you?
- Why me? I'm really not!
- You keep acting really strange.
Why are you saying that?
No, you really are acting very strange.
- I seriously am not!
- I'm not kidding about this right now.
- Seriously, I'm not!
- No, I think you are.
[His expression is extremely strange.]
I knew it was him... it's him.
- You get that it's him too, right?
- This really isn't fair. It really isn't me.
[Behavior, expression, way of speech...
everything seems suspicious?]
- It really isn't me!
- I'm positive that it's Kwang Soo.
Isn't Jae Suk more suspicious
for acting like this?
- No, you're strange.
- You're acting strange.
- You just stand down.
- Why are you getting so worked up?
[Why... is he screaming so much?]
We're going to trade Jong Kook for Gary!
- Is it okay to be happy about this?
- Of course, you can be happy about it.
- Congratulations...
- Since you're not the X-man.
- You must be happy.
- I'll act as the ex-boyfriend today.
Geun Young...
you've hurt my feelings.
[Farewell to his ideal woman, Geun Young]
I'll see you later.
I was so happy about it...
[I guess I'll have to win...]
- My hair is a total mess.
- It's okay, you're always pretty.
Thank you.
The truth is, Geun Young said she came
on the show because of you.
[There they go again...
Roro and Giraffe playing matchmaker.]
The weather sure is great today,
and my mood is great too...
Don't Gary and Geun Young look
great together?
Of course!
[Are they by any chance planning on trading
him off after egging him on like this?]
[Go to Sorae Estuary and
locate the Running Man landmark.]
Why don't we go around saying who we
each think is the X-man?
- Right now, I think it's Jong Kook.
- Jong Kook?
- Yes.
- Why all of a sudden?
The way he drove like this earlier
is really bothering me.
- He really drove like this?
- That's right, he did!
[Could that possibly be X-man's
special mission?]
I was teasing him earlier
about him being nervous
but Jong Kook could possibly have been
carrying out a mission or something.
Jong Kook is most opportunistic
when it comes to things like that.
- Geun Young, you...
- Yes?
It feels like you've been doing this
with us for the past two years.
I really want to do it too!
- Do you want to join our cast?
- I really want to do Running Man too.
I want to come on the show often.
- We'll arrange it.
- Arrange it...
Monday Couple?
[If they arrange it, she wants
to be the new Monday Couple?]
Look at you! You look so happy!
[Arriving at Sorae Estuary]
[Incheon Namdong-gu, Sorae Estuary]
[A place always crowded with people in
search of fresh daily seafood.]
So it's another restaurant
mission today.
- You can just go ahead and eat.
- You're saying we can just eat this stuff?
[The mission can wait until after the meal.]
- Is it okay to just eat this then?
- Yeah, I think you can just go ahead and eat.
- Here, eat the pen shell. This is so good.
- Why don't you just eat it yourself then?
You just go on and
eat whatever you want.
- Hey, why don't you eat the pen shell?
- Why? So I can grow taller?
Eat lots of the pen shell.
Look at you eating the mackerel pike...
I guess you want to lose then.
This mission is to ferret out
the X-man in the sushi house.
Everyone write down a game
that they're most confident in.
That sounds good!
However, it has to be a game that
you can play within the restaurant.
- What should I pick?
- You don't have straps, do you?
Who wrestles inside a restaurant?
Everyone write down what you want,
and hand it to me please.
How about who can open the
drink bottle the quickest?
Hey, I'll do the bottle opening one.
If you do the arm wrestling,
our team is going to win for sure.
We're going to do arm wrestling.
- How about a staring contest?
- I'm good at that!
[Three wins out of five!
Going with the game that's drawn.]
The first game is...
[First game: Spoon zero?]
- Is this the one where... who wrote that?
- I did!
Ji Hyo, what is this game?
- You know, holding the spoon like this...
- Zero game?
The person who proposed the game
gets to make up the rules.
What do you mean?
For example, if you say three and someone
gets it, that person is out?
That's right...
that's how we do it, right Ji Hyo?
[Blank...]
- The person who gets it right...
- Ji Hyo hasn't thought that far ahead.
- No...
- Sorry for pointing that out.
- I didn't think that far.
- The way I see it...
Just like Kwang Soo said, if someone shouts
out three and that's what pops out
then that person will step back
from the rest of the team.
Then the team with
anyone remaining is the losing team.
- That's right!
- The team with no one left is the winner?
I think I'm slowly going crazy here...
[Difficult to even get the game started...]
If you feel that you don't really get it,
then just guess and watch others.
Ah... I see what it is!
I get it! I get it now!
- I'll start. Ready...
- Jae Suk can start.
[Jae Suk to start the game.]
Three!
We won!
I raised it because I got startled.
- Thanks... we got it!
- Okay!
But why aren't the two of you
stepping back?
[Big nosed brother is still lost
when it comes to the game rules...]
Four!
[Wins again]
- They won.
- We did it!
Next is Ji Hyo.
Four!
[I lifted mine...]
[An exquisite match]
- Hi!
- Why did you lift yours?
Because I had a feeling
that you would lift yours.
[This is the Monday couple's unity.]
Four.
[An unfortunate fail.]
Kwang Soo, why did you lift yours?
I was going to lift mine with Geun Young.
[What is this...]
[When he was hating the matchmaking?]
You think this is a lover's game
or something?
- Why are you pointing your spoon at her?
- I was going to lift mine along with hers!
Next is... Suk Jin.
Zero.
[Success...]
I knew he understood it.
I knew he'd be like this.
- He knew it from the beginning.
- This is how you play a game.
Making sure no one would
take him seriously...
- This is how you play a game.
- I knew it.
Kwang Soo.
Three!
[No followers.]
- This really is disappointing.
- That was really funny.
Are you guys not playing this
game with me?
Or is it because you were
all too lazy to lift up your spoon?
Is it me?
Two!
[Success]
What is this then?
Is this an X-man's play right now?
How can you play this?
There's no way to play this.
This isn't it...
[And here we go into the analysis.]
Okay, I got it.
Sorry I even mentioned it.
Forget it,
I won't mention anything again.
[Coach Kook analyzing everything
no matter what it is.]
When they have discussions,
do you join them?
- I just wanted to explain...
- You make things more complicated!
I was just trying to explain things
in case our team didn't get it.
- Okay, we got it.
- We're going to have to send him out.
I hope we win this.
One.
[Fail]
Geun Young saying one means that
she has no interest in you.
What are you talking about?
We both had ours down.
Oh, really now?
[After he told all the guys not to
make her feel uncomfortable earlier...]
Are you going to take part
in the love line or not?
I just said it to be funny!
Things like this are said to be funny!
- It was said too seriously for that!
- I just said it to be funny!
[His face has become too red for it to have
been a comment just to be funny?]
Two!
What the heck was that?
- What?
- It's just a nervous habit of mine!
- What about it?
- I saw it come all the way up here!
[Gary's spoon that was up above
45 degrees.]
- I didn't raise it.
- That was you raising the spoon!
- No, he didn't.
- He didn't lift it. He didn't do that.
[Letting it go this time, but from now on,
even if it moves, it's to be counted.]
We're going to count it from now on.
- Who is it this time?
- It's Kwang Soo's turn.
One.
Yes!
Pil! Chok-Cross!
[Huh? A cross all of a sudden?]
Is it my turn?
Two!
[Success]
I thought Geun Young was
going to lift hers.
[Geun Young's man?
Final match between Jong Kook and Gary]
- This is the deciding round.
- This is really important, Gary.
One, two!
[One + two?]
- I was meaning to say one!
- Do it over again.
- One, two?
- I meant to say one...
- Okay.
- Is it my turn then?
- No, it's me.
- You're going again?
Two.
[Gary's defeat...]
[Red Team: 1 vs. Blue Team: 0]
Yeah, this is just the beginning.
The second game is...
It's arm wrestling.
[Second game - Arm wrestling]
Our team's representative is
Moon Geun Young.
What did you say?
We'll switch the game then.
What kind of disgusting behavior is this?
Then we choose Moon Geun Young
to take the match.
[Jong Kook vs. Geun Young]
I didn't know that it was a game
between representatives.
Why are you taking your clothes off
when you're going up against Geun Young?
It's because I'm hot. I'm really hot.
He's trying to show off his body.
He's just showing it off.
- Hey!
- Don't take your clothes off!
Jong Kook, don't fall for their mind games.
Since it's Geun Young,
I'll do it with one finger.
[Jong Kook's one finger vs.
Geun Young's one hand]
- I really am sorry...
- It's okay.
I'm sorry, I love you...
- That's what he really wants to say.
- Just bend over his whole finger.
Just bend it over completely.
Should I do it with two? One?
What's with you asking if you should
use two after saying you'll only use one?
Ready... set... go!
- Why are you trying to hold her hand longer?
- I'm not faking this!
You can't even beat her when you lift
weights that weigh as much as her?
Ji Hyo must be really angry.
- Put some muscle into it!
- A little bit more!
[The one finger holding out...]
[When will this end?]
Whatever!
[Oh my goodness...
did he just throw in the game?]
- How can I use my strength on her?
- Why did you even write down arm wrestling?
We won! We won!
[Red Team: 1 vs. Blue Team: 1]
I'm positive that X-man isn't
on our team.
Is that what you think?
I'll tell you why X-man isn't on our team...
I didn't say anything about arm wrestling,
but everyone told me to write it down.
What does that tell me? It means
our team must win no matter what.
But it could've been because
X-man didn't have a choice.
- You again...
- I can't even say anything!
I don't think this is the place
for you to be speaking up.
Then when can I ever speak up?
Should I go home so that I
can speak up?
I can't even say anything anymore?
- Whenever we talk about X-man...
- I can only speak when I'm at home?
Give me a bottle of soju!
[Giraffe wanting to resort to drinking
from all the frustration.]
The next game is...
Spinning a pen on your hand.
With the hand... yes!
- Spinning the pen like this.
- How many?
The person who can spin it the most.
[A match to spin the pen as a team.]
Who knew I'd ever play a game
like this now?
This is the only thing I'm actually good at.
The other team can start the game.
- Jong Kook...
- Set, go.
Set, go.
[Breaking out in a smile just
from the sound of her voice.]
- Why smile from a 'Set, go'?
- The most beautiful 'Set, go' in the world.
- One...
- Yes, that's good.
[Jong Kook - One...]
Yes! That's what I'm talking about!
So we can't grab it like that, right?
Ji Hyo's next.
[Ji Hyo- Zero...]
I feel like I can win this by myself.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven,
eight, nine, ten...
[Wow! Nine...]
- So a total of ten?
- Total of ten.
- Do it how we've been doing.
- The same way?
One... two...
[Succeeds at getting two]
12 total.
Okay, we have 12.
Set, go.
[Fails right away...]
You should've done at least one.
- Dong Hoon, you should've done at least one.
- It isn't as easy as it looks.
[Cute Geun Young's turn.]
One... two...
[Huh?]
[Her method is a little...]
What is this?
- You know that's not right!
- Let's do it over.
If I do it like that, I can do at least 50.
One, two, three...
You have to do it with your fingers.
- She's doing a great job!
- Miss Moon isn't doing it right!
- She was doing her best!
- Three?
- Let her have three...
- Two, we'll give her two.
- Give her a break.
- We'll give her two.
- Two? Okay...
- Miss Moon has two.
- Geun Young has two, right?
- We may win with our 12 at this rate.
[The man casting the suspicion on
himself all on his own...]
- I'm not the X-man...
- You are the X-man!
- He really is the X-man!
- You should've at least gotten a couple!
[The Blue Team currently only have
two total!]
[Gary needs to get over
ten for the Blue Team to win.]
I seriously lost my grip on it...
I think we're going to win with our 12.
- You guys are seriously being so cheap!
- I'm really not the X-man.
If they are to win, Gary needs 11.
- He was able to do ten earlier.
- But I'm all nervous now.
Set, go!
- One, two, three, four...
- He's not looking while he's doing it.
[Succeeds in getting four...]
That's awesome!
- Awesome...
- Why did you want to do this game?
- We made him nervous...
- Why did you have to make me nervous?
I'm usually so good at this!
What kind of a game is this?
The next game is... staring contest.
- You can be the representative.
- I'm really horrible at this.
Do it with Jong Kook.
He's going to be shy doing it with you.
Jong Kook, don't hide back there.
The hard thing about Jong Kook is...
we can't be sure if his eyes are open or not.
Jong Kook.
[Red Team's representative - Jong Kook]
[The birth of a new sense star
on their show.]
I'm usually pretty good at
staring contests.
- I know, you're pretty good at it.
- But I didn't sleep much, so I'm tired...
But Jong Kook usually is good at
staring contests.
- I'm usually good at it...
- Even in the past...
Jong Kook doesn't get to
sleep much these days...
You'll be getting even less sleep
from now on.
- Because of thoughts of Geun Young?
- From what?
Why don't we do a round of 'Of course'
to loosen things up a little?
Why are you seriously being like that?
Ready...
[At last, the staring contest]
This feels strange!
They're too far apart! They have
to be closer for a staring contest.
[Making his best effort to calm down.]
Come here,
we have to learn things like this.
[Complete attention from the group.]
But wait... we don't have to stare into
each other's eyes, right?
- Yes, you do. It's a staring contest.
- we have to stare at each other.
[I want you to stare into my eyes.]
You just stay quiet.
- Just be quiet!
- I really want to do a round of 'Of course'.
- You have to stare at each other.
- Ready...
Set, go.
[Directly into each other's eyes...]
[One man bursting into laughter.]
[Jong Kook's defeat.]
- What the heck was that?
- The thing is...
- You must be X-man?
- Are you X-man?
- What are you doing?
- Let's do four out of seven!
- We don't have to stare at each other...
We haven't won once with you in these
matches starting with the arm wrestling!
- Stare at her eyebrows then.
- I can't be laughing like this.
She says she shouldn't be laughing...
Why do you keep laughing?
Miss Moon... why do you keep laughing
even though you know you shouldn't be?
Why? Why?
You should ask yourself that question.
Why don't you ask yourself
how you really feel?
I don't know...
She's laughing because this is
a funny show!
- It's because our show is funny!
- Look at her... 'I don't know'...
- It's because she's finds this funny.
- Seriously...
[Calming down again...]
People standing in the back,
please keep it down.
[The man who turned his head
away first.]
- Seriously, what are you doing?
- She laughed!
[If she laughs... you don't have a choice?]
Anyways, Moon Geun Young wins!
[Mr. Capable's weakness in front
of Geun Young...]
Jong Kook is the one who lost
both games for our team.
And both of them to Miss Moon!
Seriously though...
something's strange about that.
- That is strange...
- It is definitely strange.
Don't you feel it's a little strange?
Our team's lost twice and Jong Kook has
lost them both to Miss Moon!
And Jong Kook keeps throwing
off his suspicions onto me!
But he's still not as suspicious as you are!
[Still the most suspicious one is the Giraffe.]
That's not it... I'm just bad
at looking into a woman's eyes.
- What about Ji Hyo?
- You're good at staring Ji Hyo.
- You're good at staring at me.
- But she's family.
That's why I can stare at her.
[Moving the corn]
- What the heck?
- What was that?
- Moving 20 kernels the fastest...
- Ah, with chopsticks?
- A representative from each team.
- This is the deciding round.
- Go up against Kwang Soo...
- Can we decide who gets to represent?
- No, we get to choose.
- Why don't you choose Kwang Soo then?
Kwang Soo!
- Wait...
- You have to win this no matter what.
- All I have to do is win this, right?
- That's right, you just have to win.
- You can only move one at a time, right?
- Of course.
Kwang Soo... this is a very important
game to you too.
I understand, Jae Suk.
Jae Suk is really good with
his chopsticks too...
- You have to win this, okay?
- Of course.
Set... go!
Kwang Soo... you're quicker.
That's right, that's right.
Concentrate, concentrate. Don't get nervous.
You're doing fine.
That's right, Kwang Soo.
Get the big ones first.
- I said, get the big ones first.
- I'm not getting a good grip.
Good, good... you got this. You got this!
Kwang Soo... you got this.
You got this game!
- Jae Suk!
- Kwang Soo, you got this game!
[Three kernels vs. two kernels]
[Just who's win will it be?]
[Jae Suk's 2 vs. Kwang Soo's 1!]
[Kwang Soo finishes first!]
[Celebration]
- How could you have lost this game?
- You're not the X-man...
I'm not the X-man!
You saw this, right?
Ji Hyo, you saw?
- You saw how they were stuck together, right?
- No, I didn't see anything.
- Why couldn't you have done this?
- Two of the corn kernels were stuck together.
I really did work my hardest!
[Jae Suk losing at the game that
he himself suggested... is he X-man?]
[The number one suspect, Kwang Soo...
he's not the X-man?]
[Is Jong Kook who's been losing the
X-man?]
[Or is it Geun Young
with her bright smiles?]
[Or it could be someone that
no one is suspecting?]
[Who is X-man?]
Blue team... is the winner.
In the next two games, you have be given
a hint about who the X-man is.
And you'll get a hint as to
what special mission X-man was given.
We're going to have to win it
no matter what.
[The next destination -
Arriving at Sorae Estuary Station]
- What is this?
- Here.
You're at Sorae Estuary Station...
Everyone get to Platform number one
right now.
[Huh?
But Jae Suk is on the Blue Team?]
- Decide who you'd like to trade.
- Geun Young, you decide.
- Dong Hoon for Jae Suk.
- Me?
- You're telling me to go?
- Get over there.
- Me? Seriously?
- I said, get over there.
[Is X-man one of these two?]
- He said Platform One, 6-4.
- 6-4?
[Giraffe running as if he has a purpose.]
[With Geun Young on his tail...]
Here it is!
- 6-4! Here it is...
- Where? Oh, I see it.
- You've made it to 6-4, right?
- Yes.
- You did good.
- Excuse me?
[PD Myuk's hatefulness
that she's only heard about.]
I want to stick a name tag on him.
- What? A name tag?
- Yes, because I want to rip it off of him.
This mission is going to take place in the
subway station.
Everyone, please pay attention
to the yellow line over there.
You have to stay inside the line,
and you have to quickly get on when it comes.
You're going to take the train
and take it all the way to Hong-do.
You have to pick a representative for
each team before you arrive.
The time frame which the door will be
opened for is about 30 seconds...
and those two representatives will get off
and play a round of Paper-Rock-Scissors.
If you lose,
you can just stay as you are.
[The person who loses in the game
can't get back on the train!]
[The team with most members of the team
remaining at the end is the winning team.]
Then what happens to the person
that had to get off?
The person who had to get off
can grab the next train.
I see...
What if you win the game,
but don't make it back on the train on time?
Then that person can grab
the next train.
- He's not your average person...
- She definitely isn't X-man.
- Here it is, here it is!
- The train's here!
We need to win this game.
Fighting!
[Stay behind the safety line,
then quickly board the train.]
Then... if Gary and I do it, and he loses,
then he has to get off?
No, you'd get off. The person who loses
has to get off the train.
- Then what happens after that?
- There will be another representative.
Shouldn't we send those that we're
suspicious of off the train first?
[Place of first match - Incheon Nonhyeon]
- The one that we're...
- The most suspicious person.
Dong Hoon is going to go.
[Red Team's first representative - Ha Ha]
Kwang Soo, why don't you go?
[Blue Team's first representative - Kwang Soo]
[Match - Ha Ha vs. Kwang Soo]
[The train is coming
to a stop at the platform.]
[A single play.
If you lose, you can't get back on!]
[Playing Rock-Paper-Scissors right away!]
[Just who will remain here alone
by themselves between the two?]
[Just who...]
[Revelation...]
- Kwang Soo...
- Jae Suk...
- What is he doing? Seriously?
- I'm seriously not X-man...
[Giraffe, the biggest suspect...
loses here too...]
[Since he lost,
he's not allowed to re-board.]
- Kwang Soo, take care.
- Bye.
This isn't the end of me for the day, right?
- Think about what you're doing here.
- Take care, Kwang Soo.
- I'm seriously not X-man! I'm serious!
- Bye!
[For now, one member
of the Blue Team is eliminated.]
Why do you think that they won't
trust me?
Let's talk for a bit...
I'm being really serious right now.
Why? Why do you think they
won't trust me?
- What do you think the reason is for that?
- Because you betray them...
- Because I betray them?
- Because you betray them a lot...
[The truth even kids are well aware of...]
Fine... since it's always like this,
I'm going to betray them to the core.
[Does that mean... that he could be...]
- You're wondering what's going on, right?
- Yes.
This is nerve-wrecking though.
What is there to be nervous about?
- Right? Nervous because you're not sure...
- Are you nervous?
- Yes.
- Jae Suk's probably making you even more so.
[Get off at Hogu station!]
- This is seriously driving me crazy.
- You have to win this.
[The door is open!
Time for the second match.]
[A match between
two big brothers of Running Man]
[The result of the two that know
each other so well is?]
[Who is the winner?]
[Blue Team's Jae Suk eliminated!]
Hey, Gary... you have to remain alive!
Yes, I understand.
I should've thrown out scissors!
I should call Kwang Soo.
It's Jae Suk.
- Jae Suk...
- Kwang Soo, where are you?
Right now...
I'm standing alone at Incheon station.
- I got eliminated too.
- You did?
Yeah, I lost the Rock-Paper-Scissors.
- Then there are only two of us left?
- Only Gary and Geun Young's left.
This is really frustrating.
Hey, since it's just the tow of us now,
tell me. I won't tell anyone.
Yes, Jae Suk?
You're X-man, aren't you?
Jae Suk... it really isn't me.
- You're really not?
- I'm really not.
- You're sure?
- It really isn't me... it really isn't.
Why don't we meet up and
we can talk?
- Call me right away when the train arrives.
- Yes, Jae Suk.
- Yes, I will.
- Okay, good.
[Arriving at the third location -
Namdong interspike station]
[If Gary loses too,
she'll be the only one left remaining.]
[This time,
it's Rock-Paper-Scissors minus one.]
Gary, make sure to throw out
two different signs.
Two different signs, okay?
[Train has come to a stop.]
[A difficult match where they have to use
their brain in a short amount of time.]
- Hurry!
- Rock-Paper-Scissors.
Minus one!
Rock-Paper-Scissors, minus one!
Rock-Paper-Scissors!
[Wait... this means...]
Rock-Paper-Scissors, minus one!
[Blue Team's Gary wins!]
[Gary wins the Monday Couple match!]
You could've won...
- Bye!
- Bye, Ji Hyo...
Yes, Jae Suk.
I understand, Jae Suk.
[The next train for the ones
eliminated finally arrives.]
[The first to have been eliminated
is the first to get on.]
[Awkwardly standing alone.]
- Oh my, you're so handsome!
- Thank you.
- I feel so embarrassed.
- I watch you on Running Man all the time.
Looks like that's what he's doing since
he has his name tag on.
Really?
[All the crowd members slowly
starting to noticed the Giraffe.]
- Where's Yoo Jae Suk?
- You'll be seeing Yoo Jae Suk soon too.
[Yoo Jae Suk getting ready to
board the train.]
Please be careful going home!
[Second one to have gotten eliminated,
Jae Suk enters.]
- We...
- Oh, hello.
- Kwang Soo...
- Why are you so bad at Rock-Paper-Scissors?
Are you here because you're
good at it?
Why are you and I
so bad at these things?
Because this doesn't have
anything to do with skill.
This seriously is so frustrating.
[This time, it's Jong Kook vs. Gary.
Rock-Paper-Scissors behind the safety line.]
Rock-Paper-Scissors!
[There's a winner! Just who could it be?]
[Revelation]
[Shock!
Red Team loses twice in a row!]
- Jong Kook, take care.
- Geun Young... bye.
Bye, Jong Kook!
Geun Young!
[A common farewell scene from
melodramas.]
[Even though he wants to stop the train
from moving with his strength...]
This is seriously...
Yes, hello...
I can't believe... seriously...
There's only one stop left now.
The team that wins this round
is the winning team.
- Geun Young is going to play for our team.
- I will play.
[Blue Team Geun Young vs. Red Team's Suk Jin]
[Arriving at the final location which will
determine the fate of each team.]
It's going to be
Rock-Paper-Scissors minus one.
[The final game -
Rock-Paper-Scissors minus one.]
[Which team will be the winner?]
- We have to win this...
- The final game. Let's go!
- Let's do this quickly!
- Rock-Paper-Scissors!
Minus one!
The stop coming up is the last stop.
The team that's standing there
is the losing team.
How could it have come down to
two against two?
- That was unbelievable.
- It really is unbelievable.
The team that wins this round gets a hint.
- An important hint to the winning team.
- Only the winning team gets the hint.
- Something to stop the mission...
- If the X-man fails the mission...
Hey, hey, hey...
[Finally arriving at the station to see
who has been eliminated.]
[The team who's member is standing
at this station is the losing team!]
[Who's standing at this station?
Suk Jin or Geun Young?]
[Oh... a blue shirt?]
It's Geun Young.
- Geun Young...
I lost.
[The final match
at the station a little earlier.]
Rock-Paper-Scissors, minus one!
[Big nosed brother wins in an instant!]
[This is how the Blue Team was defeated.]
Then it means... our team is going to
get the hint then, right?
- That's right, the Red Team.
- Tell me what the hint is.
I bet Jong Kook will really
tell you what it is.
Jong Kook will tell Geun Young.
There they are, there they are.
Read Team won the subway
Rock-Paper-Scissors.
- You have to trade a member this time too.
- Oh yeah, we have to make the trade.
Whenever I move to a team,
that team keeps losing.
When I was on that team, that team lost,
not this team...
So it's you... now that I think about it,
you're the X-man.
Want to hear my opinion?
If I were to tell you my opinion...
there's something weird about Kwang Soo.
- Kwang Soo...
- Something is off about him.
Games aside, his reaction when we ask
if he's the X-man is really strange.
- I know...
- I've always been strange to begin with.
[Finally acknowledging that fact?]
You have a special thing
you do whenever you lie.
I think Jae Suk is really suspicious.
It's not him... he always shows a sign.
No, Jae Suk doesn't make
things like that noticeable.
You have to make your decision by
the time I count to three.
This is the last game here, we have
to get the hint and make the decision.
-Two... one...
- Hold.
We're going to stay as we are.
We will be giving this to the
Red Team only.
[X-man's mission hint to Red Team only.]
[Just what is the hint concerning
X-man's mission?]
Let's find out where we're going first.
[Go to 'S' apartment in Incheon Yeonsugu
and find the Running Man landmark.]
[What is the X-man mission hint
that they received earlier?]
[Moon Geun Young]
- What is that?
- Is it a mission hint?
Didn't he say we were going to get
something about X-man too?
This isn't about X-man but about
the mission.
So this has something to do
with Moon Geun Young?
So today's X-man has
something to do with Moon Geun Young?
So it's not Moon Geun Young.
So does it mean that Moon Geun Young
has to be told something?
Does it mean that the game
has to be lost to Moon Geun Young?
You've lost both games to her.
[Deducing that it may be like that...]
You're the only one who's lost
to Moon Geun Young.
When I think about it,
it does kind of sound like me.
- That's what I think.
- If I were to be objective about it...
And Kwang Soo...
he keeps high fiving Moon Geun Young.
Maybe the mission is to high five her.
- Maybe that's the secret mission?
- He kept doing that to her.
It's one of the three...
you, Jong Kook or Kwang Soo.
- There's Jae Suk too.
- It's not Jae Suk.
It really isn't Jae Suk... I'm sure of it.
It doesn't matter who suspects who,
but let's pay close attention from now on.
- Since we're the only ones who know...
- Let's seriously pay close attention.
- This is what's really important.
- Pay close attention to both teams, okay?
- This is the final mission.
- Okay, okay.
[Final mission- A park inside
the Incheon apartment complex]
[In the midst of a large crowd.]
[In this place...
Running Man makes their entrance.]
[The crowd gratefully welcoming them.]
[Feeling of boxers entering the ring.]
Jong Kook!
Ha Dong Hoon!
[But what is the long rope
in the middle of the field?]
[The Blue Team arriving soon thereafter.]
[Entering the competition ring while
gratefully being cheered on.]
[All the Running Man members arrive
at the final mission location.]
[Just what is the mission in this location?]
This is your final mission.
The team that wins this mission
will trade in their suspected X-man
and will receive an important hint
that'll help you determine who X-man is.
This mission is something for you to do
together with the crowd.
What you're going to be doing is,
as you can see behind you, jump roping.
[Gigantic jump rope]
It's not about how many times you can jump,
but how many people you can fit in.
[It's not about the number of jumps,
or how many people can they get to jump.]
What does that mean?
[The team that can get most number of people
to jump even once is the winning team.]
[Each team to recruit 10 members each.]
[Confused as to who they should recruit.]
The one holding the red cell phone...
And don't you think the one who just
swept her hair back would be good?
- The one with the black top.
- We have to look at their shoes too.
- Tennis shoes...
- We have to pick tennis shoes.
Thank you!
[Even recruiting an elder who will
be their center.]
Over there... that man.
[Recruiting two young men
overflowing with energy.]
[After a cheerful greeting,
they're now same team members.]
[Both team's in a critical scouting mode.]
[Blue Team completes recruiting
10 people for their team!]
Our team is all set.
[Red Team also completes recruiting
10 people.]
[Crucial to practice
jumping together as a team.]
We have to be in sync.
You have to stare straight ahead
and jump higher than you think.
You have to bend your legs like this too.
Are you good at things like this?
Then you should go up front.
Go up to the front,
and we'll go in the middle.
- The ones who are in good shape...
- The ones who are fit need to go in first.
The fit ones up front.
Sir, do you understand?
I think it would be best for you
to enter last.
No, I'm very energetic still.
Pil-Chok-Cross!
- Fighting...
- The our victory! One, two, three!
Fighting!
[We can't lose to them!]
[Each team gets three tries.]
[The team with most people
jumping is the winner!]
- Yoo Jae Suk!
- Fighting!
[Each team member
drawing energy from the crowd.]
You have to cheer us on, okay?
[Red Team is looking for
any sings of suspicion.]
[Concentrating on their suspect,
Kwang Soo's expression.]
- See? He keeps talking to Geun Young.
- He really does keep talking to her.
[Definitely suspicious... talking
to Geun Young at every opportunity.]
First round! First round!
[Blue Team's first attempt at jump rope.]
[14 members per team.
Just how many people will they get to jump?]
Trust each other!
[Jae Suk is first to enter the line.]
Slow... slow!
[Jae Suk is first to enter,
and second follows soon thereafter.]
[Number three, Gary.
Number four, a member of the crowd.]
[Geun Young's turn to enter!]
[Geun Young slipping and losing her balance!]
[Will she be able to jump over the rope?]
[With Geun Young hitting the rope,
the people up front end up stepping on it.]
[It was quite stable for the first four...]
[But fails in a moment with a mishap.]
It's okay! It's okay!
[Brightening up again through the cheers
of her team and the crowd after her mistake.]
[Red Team's turn at their first attempt.]
[Red Team overflowing with energy.]
[One more cheer for team spirit.]
Geun Young, don't be nervous.
- How many did we get?
- Five people...
- You're the fifth?
- Yes, I'm the fifth person.
Just watch.. and come in right away.
And when you do, just jump high!
Feel the rhythm, okay?
- What does that mean?
- You know, the rhythm!
- I'm so nervous!
- Don't be nervous.
You have to get over your nervousness.
[The way to victory is
to get over the nervousness.]
I think I went in too late,
and that's why I jumbled it up.
[Red Team's first attempt]
[Just how many members of Red Team
will they be able to get in?]
[Wow! So many people within moments!]
[Entering without hesitation!]
[Already seven people! Now the eighth!]
[Complete teamwork!]
Suk Jin... look at Suk Jin!
[Ninth Suk Jin almost caused big trouble!]
[Ah, Ji Hyo's entrance caused
the fumble.]
[Red Team's first attempt succeeds
at ten people!]
[But it's still amazing!
Nine people at first attempt!]
- You have to get closer to the front!
- Yeah, you guys have to go up more.
Everyone get closer to up front.
[Blue Team's second attempt!]
[Sufficiently chocked after seeing
the Red Team's performance.]
- Would you like to jump? I'll go in last.
- No, it's okay.
[Geun Young still feeling down after
the mistake she made earlier.]
- It's okay. Fighting!
- Fighting!
[Still watching Kwang Soo with
sharp eyes.]
[Blue Team's second attempt, Start!]
[Jae Suk is the first to enter again!]
[He's caught... is this how it ends?]
[Wow! A miraculous recovery!]
[With Jae Suk first, second
young boy enters without trouble.]
[Third and fourth with ease]
It's okay to go in with ease.
Kwang Soo is acting strange.
[Kwang Soo's turn to enter.]
[Stoic expression]
[Gritting their teeth to move as one.]
[At last, Geun Young's turn to enter.]
[Good job, Geun Young]
[Wow, seventh and eighth
entrance a success!]
[Now the ninth!]
[Ah... Blue Team's second attempt
succeeds at eight people.]
- How many people did we get in?
- We got a lot of people.
It's okay...
[Geun Young and the Blue Team
with big improvement.]
- It's not as easy as it looks, right?
- The rope was so short.
- What number were you? You were the ninth?
- Yes.
- We can do this.
- Yoo-ruce Willis!
[At the request,
each team's time to practice.]
We're going to practice
like it's the real thing.
[Blue Team's turn to practice first.]
We're going to practice like
it's the real thing...
[Seriously as if this was the real thing.]
[Already at four people within moments.]
[Five including Kwang Soo!]
With confidence! With confidence!
[Even Geun Young enters without trouble.]
[Nine people without a problem!]
[Tenth person!]
[Now eleventh!]
Why are they so good when it's
just practice?
That's awesome!
[Even though it's practice,
Blue Team has succeeded in 11 people!]
[Even the cool Dad succeeds in entering
as the twelfth man!]
[Awesome!
Even the thirteenth lady enters!]
[Just then!]
[Getting caught as the last
fourteenth person was making his entrance.]
[Even though it was only practice,
Blue Team succeeds in getting 13 people in!]
[At this rate, the victory is ours!]
Okay, here... everyone gather here.
The last person to come in just
get in wherever there's a blank spot.
- Just go in where there's space.
- You don't have to go to the back.
That's good, but it's important that
you guys scoot up as much as possible.
We will try to do that
but in case it doesn't happen
you don't have to go all the way to the
end like what happened to them.
So just go in wherever there's space.
- Are you okay?
- Yes, I'm fine.
You're really good!
[Blue Team with added confidence
after their practice.]
[Red Team's turn at their practice time.]
[Red Team's distinctive rush.]
[Practicing with members
overflowing with energy.]
[Numbers of members increasing
within moments.]
Jump higher!
[They're continuing to enter!]
[Red Team succeeds in getting 12
people in during their practice.]
They're rushing too much.
We're much better.
As long as Geun Young does a good job,
we can win this thing.
[I'm in trouble.]
[Red Team's second attempt.]
[Will they be able to do as well as
during their practice?]
[Number one, Ha Ha's entrance]
[The next one following right after!]
[Starting off the round with
their distinctive speed and flair!]
They really are so good!
[Eighth person succeeds in
making his entrance!]
[Even the Red Team's weak link,
Big nosed brother succeeds in entrance!]
Get in!
[The tenth person is Ace Ji Hyo!]
[10 people within moments!]
[Gets caught when Ji Hyo makes
her entrance.]
[Coach Kook encouraging his teammates
after their opportunity is over.]
[Blue Team's third and last attempt.]
If by any chance...
We got more people
than them during our practice.
The other team succeeded in
getting in ten people...
[If they don't break the opposing team's
record of 10, Red Team immediately wins!]
I know this is difficult, but everyone
relax and do their best!
I hope that you all think of this as a fun
jump roping game and do it with comfort.
[With more vigor than any other time.]
Everyone do the wave! The wave!
One, two, three!
[He really likes doing things like that...]
[It's a relief that
the crowd seems to like it too.]
Do you think that's a special mission?
[Is that X-man's special mission?]
[After doing that lap,
he's already drained of energy?]
[If the Blue Team fails to get in 10 people,
then it's the Red Team's victory!]
[Blue Team's chance to get everyone in!]
- Fighting!
I'm getting nervous.
[Entering with caution.]
[Number five, Kwang Soo...]
[Number six, a member
of the crowd also enters.]
[Number seven Geun Young,
this time?]
[She made it!]
[In this moment, everyone is as one...]
[That's too bad!]
[Fails with the ninth person's entrance.]
[The victory goes to the Red Team
with their 10 people!]
[To everyone that's helped out,
we sincerely thank you.]
[The only thing left now...
is the final judgment.]
[Just who is X-man?]
Jump roping with the crowd is
really fun.
We did it a few times in the past,
and it's really fun.
It's much harder than I thought.
I don't think there's anyone who
purposely made a mistake or anything.
- How can anyone have done that?
- Yes, there was.
- Really?
- Who?
Is it the person I'm thinking of?
- But if really isn't Kwang Soo...
- If it isn't him...
Then it means that Kwang Soo
really is bad at things.
Geun Young... who's the person that's been
acting the friendliest with you today?
Kwang Soo...
[Casting all suspicion on him thinking that
X-man's mission is to get close to Geun Young.]
[While Kwang Soo is
getting suspected more and more...]
You could've been luring her or something...
[The bus that they're all on is
taking them to the final place of judgment.]
[Arrives at the X-man's
final place of judgment, Youngjongdo.]
- It looks like the X-man set!
- Yeah, it does look like it.
[This is the final judgment stage!]
Why don't you give us a hint?
I wish we could get a hint too.
- What?
- I want to get a hint too.
More than anything else, the team
I've been on lost every game today.
[It was the definitive hint to reveal
who the X-man really is...]
- I think this is important.
- Come on, let's take it and see.
[Running so they could see
for themselves alone.]
What do they take us for?
Why don't you show it to us too?
We won't say anything.
Just tell us what the hint says.
We haven't even won anything today...
- It's initials.
- Tell us what the initial says.
- What's the initials?
- Want me to tell you what it is?
[Since they don't know anyways,
sharing it would be...]
- DB...
- What is DB?
- What's that?
- What does that stand for?
- Dae Bak (Awesome).
Who's the person that hit it big recently?
The name of your group is...
[It's Turbo, not Durbo...]
- Did you think it was Durbo?
- I thought that maybe...
[Without knowing what the hint is,
trading their suspect first...]
[The team with X-man on their side during
the final judgment loses.]
- Who are you going to trade?
- How about Gary?
Why? I could be X-man too.
- I don't think it's me.
- I'm X-man!
I'm X-man too.
I know you are...
[If they pick the wrong person,
they could bring X-man to their side...]
Hold!
[No change in team members.]
- What are the hints that you've received?
- Moon Geun Young and DB.
Moon Geun Young hint meant...
for the X-man to be on the same team as
Moon Geun Young at the final location.
[If X-man is on the Blue Team,
it'll be X-man's sole victory!]
[For now, the main suspect Kwang Soo and
Geun Young are on the same team!]
[Blue Team ascending to the
judgment stand.]
[If Kwang Soo really is X-man,
it will be his sole victory.]
[Kwang Soo, who's received a lot of suspicion
from everyone from the beginning.]
[The fact that he's been defeated in almost
every game is a given.]
[With plenty of action that can
earn him the suspicion he's received...]
It really isn't me!
I'm not the one!
[Could he... really be X-man?]
[Not a match.]
[Kwang Soo isn't the X-man!]
I told you that I wasn't all day!
Hey... it's not you?
I told you that it isn't me!
I've been telling you that all day.
The reason why I'm positive
that X-man isn't here
is because if X-man was here, then
he would've tried to go to the other team.
I'm sure you're right.
Then is it Kang Gary?
[Then... Kang Gary?]
X-man!
[With his peaceful expression...
could he be carrying out a mission?]
[Now that we think about it,
no one has ever suspected him today...]
[Could he have used his casualness as a
weapon to be on the same team as Geun Young?]
[Not a match.]
[Gary's not the X-man either!]
If it's not Jae Suk,
then it's one of your members.
Then we win, right?
If it's not you, then we win?
- That's right...
- If it's not Jae Suk, then our team wins!
X-man wouldn't have succeeded
either then.
[But if Jae Suk is X-man,
then he would win all by himself.]
Please, please... Please, Jae Suk!
[Could he be X-man?]
[Defeated in almost every game...]
[Jae Suk, whom Ace Ji Hyo has been
suspicious of all day...]
[Could he possibly be?]
[Match!]
[X-man is Yoo Jae Suk!]
Forget it!
[How can this be... Jae Suk is X-man...]
[Confirmed, Jae Suk is X-man.]
[You are... X-man for the day.]
[You are X-man.]
You have to be on the same team as Geun
Young at the final judgment for you to win.
[Acting as X-man
starting with the first event.]
[Turning his back towards her...]
[Even during the corn game
that he suggested himself...]
[He purposely threw a kernel of corn
off the plate.]
[Purposely acting disappointed at
having lost.]
Trade Dong Hoon for Jae Suk.
[This is how he came to be
on the same team as Geun Young!]
Every team that I join keeps losing.
I think it's Jae Suk...
No, it's not him.
He'd be obvious about it.
[Hint to the identity of X-man, DB.]
[If looked on the keyboard, 'D' equals 'o']
[And 'B' Equals 'y']
[Those put together equals 'Yoo'.]
[You are... X-man.]
[And that's how he succeeded his roll
and mission as X-man.]
Kwang Soo did such a great job being
the patsy for X-man...
Anyway... the gold is all mine!
Subtitles by DramaFever
[On next week's Running Man]
[The next day, they recruit
Asia's ultimate agents, DBSK!]
[On the grandest scale to date...
Land and sea's spectacle chase!]
[The bloody battle on the Incheon shores
that'll go down in history!]
[Catch me if you can!]
[The real chase drama with
love and thrill.]
[Incheon operation landing.]