We're wearing school uniform today. Hey, Ji Hyo's very pretty.
-Hey she looks like Sherlock Holmes. -actually this is..
The hand phone sticking out slightly like this is the highlight.
Nowadays, do kids wear them like this?
Oppa, kids nowadays, their skirt come right up to here
is that so?
Hey you were also like that
-no our skirt were.. -Jeez Ji Hyo's..
On the internet, that photo.
That photo with the sesame leaf hair.
-your skirt was still like this. -that's right
well today, who is coming today?
-Isn't today spring? -yes yes
so to usher in spring, we've prepared a Couple Race.
-It's been a long time. -see there?
Oh there are flowers
-wasn't it like that last time? -We also wore school uniform the last time.
If today's a paired Couple's Race, well this is..
-I'm anticipating it. -we'll be in chaos today
I'm definitely going for a date today, really.
-I'll let you see a meeting in variety followed by marriage. -It's already a year.
Well, our Suzy.
-Sulli Sulli -They should be returning actually.
-Then let's wait a little more for Sulli -Yoona.
-Suzy. -They should be wanting to come.
Luna and Suzy
I'm seriously going crazy, seriously.
Now the guests will come out passing through that floral door one at a time.
-shout for the guests to come out together and they'll come out one at a time. -I got it.
-Everyone! Come on out! -I love you. I love you.
-Miss A. It’s Miss A. -Oh it’s Miss A.
-Miss A, who? -Fei, Fei.
Who?
Wow, oh.
Yay... Oh?
-what are you doing? -It’s Miss A’s song, why is that hyung coming out?
So that music is then...
But what’s this?
Hyung. That’s what we’re saying.
-oh why are you here, hyung? -how can a hyung come out from a floral door?
Does that look like just a floral door?
Hyung, it was Miss A’s song, why did hyung come out?
It should be "Rustic Period" song. -No no.
That song was played but why are you guys here?
Why is hyung here today?
Our program’s concept has changed.
Won’t you get away from me?
Aigoo, why are you getting angry, the moment you’re here, hyung?
You made me angry!
If you saw us earlier, you would understand.
Hyung, he’s a dud.
Then, firstly...
-Joon Gyu hyung -wow!
Hyung we’re sorry.
We greatly welcome you.
But because they played miss A’s song, we thought it was miss A.
We expected it to be Suzy. -Jeez, it couldn’t be.
-ok, Joon Gyu hyung’s here. -Joon Gyu hyung, nice to meet you.
Ok our next person, please come out.
Oh!
KARA, KARA.
Seungyeon, Seungyeon.
-Goo Hara! -Seungyeon.
-Goo Hara! -Seungyeon
-it’s scary, suddenly. -what the?
But why is the response so bad?
-No it’s not bad. -it’s my first appearance today.
-Hyung. -Nice to meet you.
Why are you wearing safety goggles?
-the back of your hat seems to be torn. -Hello.
-Are the two of two friends? -Yes we’re old friends.
Really?
When we were in high school...
-We took Line 4 together. -Together.
Is that so?
We went to Haehwa-dong together, that line.
Why are you suddenly doing this to us?
You’ve been treating us well in the past, why is it like that?
-Exactly. -There’s still one last person.
There’s hope. Ok don’t lose hope!
-don’t give up! -ok now, finally!
-the production crew won’t let us down! -they won’t!
This can’t be it.
Ok applause!
Ok now, we..now..
Seriously
-oh. SNSD! -that’s right.
-Taeyeon! -Just one.
At least one person should come, just one.
Ok who is it?
Ok!
Please come out.
Taeyeon!
-wow daebak. -Daebak!
Daebak.
Hang on hang on.
Nice to meet you.
Aigoo, aigoo.
Why are you here?
Oh you’re so pretty.
Oh nice.
Oh you’re so tall.
It’s like the boss of a large company is here.
The head, the head.
I should come as a school principal, but I’m wearing a school uniform.
Please greet everyone...’Hello’.
Oh nice to meet you.
I’m 60 years old.
I don’t know why I’m on Running Man.
So there are no more guests?
Thank you very much.
But why did hey give me a hat?
What are you doing?
-why did you give him a hat? -Isn’t he already wearing a hat?
You want me to wear two hats?
Are you making fun of me?
Wearing two hats.
Wearing one fur hat is enough.
I agonized because of that!
He plays soccer a lot but when he plays soccer, he’ll wear a cap.
-of course. -That lightning header shot?
Take it off, hit it and put it on before landing on the ground.
The people...
They all feel that something is weird.
Because things are restored immediately, they can’t laugh.
I’m sorry, how are your ages ranked?
-He is the eldest hyung. -then he is next.
-Then next.. -You’re the maknae?
-Really? -Hyung’s the maknae?
You’re the maknae?
I’m the maknae. Isn’t Suk Jin the eldest here?
So what about you and Suk Jin hyung?
-They’re friends. -we’re friends.
-How many times do I have to say it? -You don’t listen to people!
Why do you get angry after talking?
-Didn’t I say it already? -You make everyone scared.
Inside these two hyungs..
-Anger. -They’re always filled with anger.
It makes one uncomfortable.
But your uniform are so cool.
There are the current uniforms.
Miss Ji Hyo looks very pretty.
Girl’s uniform.
Give us something like that, what’s this?
I want that too.
If I wear that I could be pretty too.
We have the three of them today, are we racing with the three?
Yes, just like we said earlier, it’s a Couple Race today.
-yes yes. -yes couples
-we’ll decide on the couples first. -yes.
Also, this side has three people, so there aren’t enough people.
-yes -From this side, err...
-the two people of similar age to them will come to that side. -Suk Jin, come here.
-Yoon Jae Suk, Ji Suk Jin, come here. -hyung looks very weird in this school uniform.
When I go there I’ll totally be..
-come here. -I’m young.
-I’m like a newborn baby if I come here. -Come here.
-Hyung’s totally like an idol there. -Wow, seriously.
Hey, I look younger too right?
-yes hyung. -You look young.
-ok, we’ll proceed according to age so Mr Lee Deok Hwa will begin the selections. -Is that Si?
The person chosen can refuse.
-refuse us? -ah we can refuse?
-if you’re unwilling to be partners until the end of the day.. -Jeez, it couldn't be.
Just say, "Ahjusshi, I’m sorry."
-What’s Ahjusshi? -Jeez!
-wow what’s that? -we should say ‘hyungnim’.
Hyungnim, hyungnim...
It’s fair and good..
-I’m sorry. -they can just comfortably refuse us.
But the rest of their filming careers may be rather tough.
After they say, "I’m really sorry hyung"..
Then, what are you going to do with my wounded pride?
Ok now, we’ll be choosing.
Haha, I like his mother.
Haha!
Please look after me!
Haha, please look after me!
Oh, he’s so bashful.
I’m sorry?
It’s nice to meet you, really..
‘thank you’? One, two, three!
I’m sorry.
Hey, give haha’s mother a call.
Call haha’s mother.
Hey, what did you choose?
Aigoo my stomach.
Give haha’s mother a call!
-I was joking. -That’s right.
Thank you sir.
-I like it. -Hey, Haha’s dead today.
Ok next!
Please look after me.
Yeah these guys are dead.
Ok!
Look at Gary, Gary.
Gary’s now..
Gary doesn’t dare look directly at Joon Gyu hyung.
Time, time.
I’ve told him coolly.
I’m.. I’m uncomfortable with him.
Why hyung?
He’s the scariest!
-oh why? -ok.
-gary’s not bad. -one two three!
Gary’s nice.
Gary hyung’s good.
-Oh Jong Kook. -Jong Kook!
Hyung, you’re not supposed to hold my hand first.
You can only hold my hand after I agree.
I’m the one choosing.
Seriously..
When I’m having a difficult time I always dream about you.
If you are there..
..I won’t jerk awake while sleeping.
And I can sleep well
-good. -one two three!
-thank you hyung -yeah.
My man!
Today’s my first time on Running Man.
Yes.
I’m a little bit burdened.
Because I’m not familiar with their styles, it’s better to be with someone I know.
-Just follow the rules. -I said I can’t.
-I said I can’t -Follow the rules!
My nickname in school was Holmes.
Why?
Larry Holmes.
I’m sorry.
-it's not Sherlock Holmes but Larry Holmes. -I want to be with Suk Jin.
With Suk Jin.
I don’t want to.
Why?
I don’t want to! Hey.
Suk Jin hyung!
Seriously.
Hey, kneel on both knees!
Brat, alright then.
Hey, what kind of guests are we?
Let’s have some dignity.
Mr Yoo Jae Suk will choose one person from the remaining members.
What do I do about this? This is seriously..
What do I do?
Gwang Soo.
-Hey, the Giraffe wants to be chosen. -I’m very anxious.
I will get slightly angry, hyung.
Hey if it’s like that..
There’s no other choice but this
-why don’t the two of you be together? -yeah!
Oppa I really don’t want to.
It’s a couple special today.
Have a last journey today.
Enjoy your last journey with Gary.
Have the last journey.
Have the last journey Ji Hyo.
Oh it’s raining.
The weather is extremely bad too.
Sir you have to be careful.
Do you want a hat?
Haven’t you watched TV recently? This much is fine.
Even with the wind..
10m/second is no problem.
These days, he washes his hair.
10m/second.. Oh my stomach.
Oh it’s really hilarious.
Diving is fine too
I hope the wind blows for once, hyungnim.
Ok.
Ok I’m revealing today’s mission.
Ok today’s mission is..
Since we’re in Cheorwon, a Fishing Race.
Get fishing equipments for the race.
Then head to the final fishing location to fish.
Also the team that catches the largest fish within the time limit is the winner.
Then the winning team will be awarded golden fishing floats.
Go to G Land and find the Running Man banner.
Where’s G land?
You should wear a wig or put on a hat.
What’s wrong with this?
Hey I have no benefits being with you!
Why?
I use banmal with you.
The audience thinks that I’m young.
Why.. Why do yo look so old?
I look, I look dirty?
You look old, old.
Oh I didn’t say it earlier,
When I chose you, you should have said "hey friend, good to see you".
Even if I knew it was a joke, did you have to ask me to kneel?
Hey you’re the one who kneeled down first. Did I tell you to do that?
Then you should have asked me to get up, but you told me to be on both knees?
Jeez, that’s why it livened up the atmosphere.
What atmosphere? Hey that sort of gag, what era is this now?
While I’m in Running Man..
How many years has it been?
About 1year and 7 to 8 months.
Isn’t it about time to quit?
Aren’t you out of line?
Actors can leave during a drama, when they die.
You know, Deok Hwa hyung and I acted in History of the Salaryman.
Right right.
Following my death in History of the Salaryman, the drama started to unfold.
It’s really similar to me, in Running Man, following my death..
..it signifies the start of the race.
We’re both the same.
-okay. For the win, fighting! -Good! Fighting!
Gwang Soo!
Yes hyung.
There’s hardly anything to talk about in the car.
With you beside me.
Hyung.
What, Gwang Soo?
Recently I’ve been, extremely sharp about, about what should be done next.
Talk about something.
Why?
-say something. -about what?
-talk about this or that, oppa. -why, why?
It’s too awkward.
-Why is it awkward? - it’s awkward.
I’m fine though?
Are we going to do it outside when it’s raining now?
You know, usually..
Two months ago I would say, "I’ll be your umbrella".
"I’ll be your umbrella, Ji Hyo."
That’s right, it’s good that we’re together.
Of course.
So, is there something to bond it?
There’s a medication to attach it.
It’s amazing these days.
Even diving as well?
Of course.
Really.
The medicine's very strong.
If I attach it with the super strong one,
If someone pulls it, the scalp might get torn.
I found it, hyungnim.
Good!
I got it!
Let’s hurry up a bit.
Those behind are catching up.
Really? Let’s hurry.
They have all kinds of rides here.
This is Deok Hwa hyung. This person, is out Collar-Grabbing PD.
He’s extremely good at pissing you off.
You can grab his collar.
Will he grab my collar?
No no.
You look here!
Myeon Sang hyung!
Hey run! Hey run quickly!
Hey I said run.
Hey why are you like this?
-why are we running? What? -this has to do with thee order.
Line up line up
I was first.
Why are you looking at ours?
-excuse me, ahjusshi -yes
-how are you doing with the chairman? -it’s great, why?
Chairman please say something!
Ji hyo, have you ridden a carousel before?
Of course I have.
Who did you ride it with?
-did you ride it with that person? -come quickly.
It’s funny, why?
Oh these two. Hey come together.
Hold hands.
Ok please be quiet.
The chairman is here and you’re telling us to be quiet?
The combined age of this couple here is over 100 years old.
Be quiet.
Ok choose a textbook that you like.
What do we choose?
-choose Korean language. -Korean language? Ok.
Korean language, we chose Korean language.
-this one, this one. -stop shoving.
Do it slowly.
There’s an order here.
Don’t push me.
The mission card is inside.
Come here to confirm the mission card with me.
I think I’ve picked the wrong one.
Ok Lee Deok Hwa’s team will take the aerial bicycle. Do you see it there?
Please go up there.
Go up from there.
Please check and show it to me.
How about us?
Please go that way.
Why did you choose the Science textbook? I wanted Geography.
Let’s exchange let’s exchange.
You can’t do that. Only one chance.
It’s because our lower body lack strength.
I have no strength in my lower body.
What do you get?
Aerial bicycles.
Follow along.
Ok I’ll explain to all of you once.
Starting from here until you return,
After you set off, these two friends will follow you right behind.
Just make sure they don’t catch you.
By these guys?
Yes.
Hey how are we going to do it with these legs?
But these friends are athletes.
I..
Now..
I’ve only rode amusement park rides 3 times in my sixty years.
It’s my first time on this thing.
Please be careful hyungnim.
-Hyung be careful. -if this goes above 10km/hour will it..
Don’t worry, don’t worry about my hair.
He can go under 10m of water.
-Gwang Soo! -yes hyung!
Because of you we’re here at the Viking, the Viking.
Each person sits at the ends of the Viking.
One person will describe a word while the other person guesses it.
We can do it right, oppa?
You’re describing? I don’t do it well.
Are you good at guessing?
Yeah not too bad.
-I got it, I’ll do the explaining. -I got it
I will do my best.
-If we don’t want to be caught by them.. -yes, we have to go as fast as possible.
Hyung.
Please take care of us.
Got it.
Set off!
-hey! -we’re off!
They’re coming, they’re coming.
-They’re coming already? -yes.
Hey they are very fast!
The string is tangled.
We’re tangled up!
Hey don’t do it!
Don’t do it, don’t do it. Don’t do it!
Jeez
it's over!
Hey what are you guys?
-since we’re caught, let’s conserve our energy. -yes.
Let’s get them to push us.
Hey you guys can push us.
-I can’t do it. Seriously. -seriously.
You saw it all right?
Push quickly!
Are they pushing them from behind?
Hyungnim is not doing anything now.
They’re really pushing them from behind.
I’m seriously..
Hey we were caught over here.
Oh chairman!
-chairman how are you? -we got caught.
We were caught right from the start
-yes -who are these guys?
You do something about them.
Haha, take good care of the chairman.
This is unfair.
Hyungnim, please come over here.
These friends, come over here.
-how can you catch us from the start? -what sport do you do?
I’m a mixed martial arts athlete.
Mixed martial arts? And you?
I’m a judo athlete.
-hey, call someone for me. -who?
-Shim Gwon Ho, at Taerung National Training Centre. -take it easy hyungnim.
Taerung National Training.
We just need to run away?
We really won’t be caught.
-we’ll go all out, hyung? -yeah yeah.
Immediately!
Ok get ready!
Immediately.
-start! -let’s go let’s go.
This is fast, it’s fast.
We’re going too fast.
Our legs.
But this..
Hyungnim, this is..
Hey they’re too fast.
Why are you going so fast?
Are we caught?
Yes.
They got caught, they got caught.
Even better, the end!
Out! Out out.
How did they catch up so fast?
How did you come so soon?
We were going extremely fast?
Ji Hyo, let’s do this in one try.
-oppa one try -one try.
Oh I don’t like this. Oh oh hang on.
But you two..
Both of you look like first loves.
Why did you put us so far apart?
Start!
-hurry! -Son Dambi!
Crazy?
No.
What comes after Friday?
Saturday! Saturday!
Next question.
Oppa, what do they call you?
Prince-like.
The opposite of that.
Sir Lee Deok Hwa!
Sharp.
Oppa, Lee Deok Hwa sunbaenim did it.
The ball he kicked.
Soccer!
But in front if it..
-foot volleyball! -no.
Soccer shoe?
No hey!
What is it?
-hey. -oh hang on.
Oppa, it’s a big fish, it’s a big fish.
A big fish, if you fish it up, wow it’s daebak
-big fish -no!
-no -what is it?
Hey!
A very big fish!
Daebak!
Hey.
-Daebak, you’re the daebak one! -oh hang on.
Hey hurry up.
It’s over.
Are they eliminated?
Gwang Soo.
Yes hyung.
Yes hyung
-we can do well right? -yes hyung.
I’m very confident.
Hyung, it’s harder than you think!
Ji Hyo, you were playing a bit right?
Why? Why oppa?
You’re too obvious.
What obvious, oppa?
Gwang Soo.
Yes hyung.
Do well.
Make sure they go as high as possible!
Gwang Soo go!
This is driving me crazy.
-oppa, it’s going to go totally high. -this is crazy.
The scaredy-cat pair are suddenly very nervous.
No don’t get us too high!
Start quickly, sir, I’m seriously..
Gwang Soo.
Gwang Soo let’s go.
3 characters.
-China’s emperor’s name, China’s emperor’s name! -Qin Shi Huang!
Ok!
Qin Shi Huang!
Jae Suk oppa’s good.
4 characters! Women’s kingdom.
-what? -4 characters! Women’s kingdom.
What did you say?
4 characters! Women’s kingdom!
-women’s world! -ok!
That, Park Joon Gyu sunbae’s nickname!
-when he raps! -what did you say?
Park Joon Gyu sunbae’s nickname!
-whose nickname? -Park Joon Gyu sunbae’s!
-who? -Park Joon...
I can’t hear!
Among our guests, our chairman, the chairman!
Sir Lee Deok Hwa!
Change the surname!
Andy Lau(Yoo Deok Hwa)!
-Andy Lau! -ok!
I said it? Did I answer it?
-panties, panties! -stop it!
What did you say?
I can’t hear!
What you wear inside your clothes?
What did you say? -you wear..
Ah ah.
-What did you say, Gwang Soo? -what you wear under your clothes!
-tell me the question! The question! -it is the question!
Gwang Soo, don’t close your eyes!
Tell me the question!
The clothes you wear..The clothes you wear..
-ding ding oppa, ding ding -it’s over?
Lee Gwang Soo!
Hey!
-hey Sang Myeon has something to say, say it. -hey you two.
You have to give us some space, then slowly catch up.
It will be more breathtaking for the viewers. Who catches people right from the start?
Fighting!
You don’t even know that much?
Weren’t they just caught?
-they were caught earlier. -exactly.
They were caught at the corner now.
Just do your best, do your best.
I got it.
-hey chase us slowly -we can go right?
We’ll go and they’ll set off. Right foot, left foot.
I’m not lying, you guys won’t even reach 10m.
Don’t say that sort of thing, hyung.
-hey Sang Myeon, 5m. -start!
Right leg left leg, Right leg left leg
-great! We’re quick! -they’re coming!
Let’s go.
Sang Myeon, we’re winning!
Go quickly. Go quickly
-hey great! Hey -Go quickly.
Hurry! Hey go faster. You, pedal faster!
We can do it, we got it!
What’s going on here?
Hey don’t come close!
Don’t come closer, aigoo
don’t come, don’t come closer!
Hey hurry. Right foot left foot.
Hey they’re here already.
Use some strength!
Hey Sang Myeon! Get a hold of yourself, hang in there!
Why did you choose this?
Ah really.
How can you get tired so quickly?
This.. I can’t do this.
Hey push us quickly.
Push.
We have to drain these guys’ strength.
Go quickly.
-there’s no use talking to them nicely? -yes yes.
-I wanted to say it with a smile. -exactly.
They think I’m funny.
Exactly hyung, this isn’t it.
Hey you should take care of him.
How old are you?
My child is already 34.
-Do well, yes. -help your father.
Hey whether it’s your father or grandfather, this is..
-ok let’s do it right this once -fighting!
Fighting!
Set off!
Ah they’re too fast, too fast!
-hey hey -what’s this?
-hey stay where you are! -stay where you are!
-these guys! -stay where you are, oh oh!
-hey hey! stay where you are! -stay where you are!
It’s your father, you brats!
Stop, stay where you are!
Stop.
He wait. Time!
-stop stop they’re still following us.
They’ve stopped.
They’re being scolded, they’re being scolded
they’re being scolded.
Telling them not to come over!
You, I told you that my child is already 34 right?
Listen up! You would not start after 10 seconds!
-we understand.. -alright? start after 10 seconds!
-are your parents well and healthy? -yes.
My greetings to them.
Start after 10 seconds.
After 10 seconds! After 10 seconds alright?
Hey you guys are starting too early!
Hey you guys stop!
Still not stopping?
You have worked hard, chairman!
These brats..
-hey you guys should apologize. -Joon Gyu, do something about them.
-you guys can’t be like this. -we’re sorry.
Even so, Deok Hwa hyung is really lousy at this!
But he’s not young anymore! He’s sixty years old!
This can’t go on, we need a different tactic.
-yes hyungnim! -I have no more energy.
Alright go go!
Young singers!
-idol! -ok!
-a cool man! 3 words! -Cha-do-nam(cold city man)
-flip the page quickly! -use the camera Ike this on yourself!
Selca, selca!
4 words to say "it’s so troublesome"?
Bothersome!
Taecyeon! An idol like Taecyeon! What do you call it?
-beast idol! -ok ok!
Ji Hyo, I’m having goosebumps now..
You did good! You did really good!
Ji Hyo, come to think of it, we really suit for each other.
-yay, Kang Gary! -Yay!
-you guys are really a match made in heaven. -I think we’re starting now hyung.
-you did well together, Ji Hyo! -oppa! Do well.
It’s nauseating! Be careful!
You succeeded?
-we succeeded! -oh yeah! We succeeded.
Succeeded!
Before forming a team with Haha, I wanted to join you.
I’m sorry but I went with him.
-and do you know this, Song? -what?
Teacher, our hyungnim, doesn’t do very well.
-Yoo! -Lee!
We missed you!
-Gwang Soo, let’s do this! -Yes!
Gwang Soo.
Expired man! Popular man! Hyung!
-married man? -no they are popular!
Taken man.
A man who looks nicer the more you look at him.
Warm men!
Movie.. A movie city
-busan! -nonono 3 words!
-what? -3 words! Next to Myeongdong!
-Chungmuro! -ok!
That thing you use for fishing! 2 words!
-hook! -no no!
Curved! Curved!
-fish bait! -ok!
Huh?
4 words! 1,2,3?
-4,5,6,7,8! -Park Sang.
Myeon?
Hyung’s favourite colour!
-Choroksaek (green) -ok!
Blank Na da la ma pa sa?
4 words!
Ka Na da la ma pa sa.
What?
Put them together, the 4 words!
-Samyeon choga? -ok!
So we choose?
It’s going to rain, hurry!
Ji Hyo, this one feels right?
This is good too.
There are 5 joints, 2 joints, it’s here right?
Let’s take the one that says 30.
We’ll choose this one
-please bring it with you. -ok.
Go to Hwa River and look for the running man banner
-everyone, you have worked hard! -see you!
A little harder!
Oh it‘s tiring.
Hey you guys pedal slower! Slower!
My legs have no more strength.
They were doing well, what’s wrong now?
What should we do? We’re sorry.
Hey don’t poke us!
Poke them!
Poke Poke Poke!
They got him.
We did it right?
Jong Kook hyung was poked.
Hey the chasing duo come over here!
You guys quickly get to it!
It’s your turn now!
Now the two, the other two, come over!
According to the rule, the next team is them.
The other two are ours! Come on, you have to go another round!
Hey go for another round.
Go!
Slowly, slowly, like this.
Oh it’s raining.
Good, the timing is good.
Ok slowly.
It’s ok if we continue like this.
They have already caught up to us!
Hey don’t come closer! Don’t come closer!
Why are they so fast?
Why do you keep missing your steps?
It’s raining! Oh the rain.
They are not breathing hard at all.
No water for them!
-why did you miss your steps? -it’s because it’s so slippery!
You know, right? Go slowly
-set go! -go go!
We must be careful. There’s no use pedaling too hard.
Why are they there already! Go go go!
-my legs are cramping! -we are close!
They might make it!
A bit more a bit more!
Haha!
They might make it!
We did it!
It’s a success, a success!
Hey hey!
We did it!
I can’t believe it.
These two are tired too.
Hey they are ours, ours!
-my legs are going to have cramp. -Mine too!
Alright come on.
Come on boys!
You were great chairman.
My wig almost came off.
At over 10km speed.
Please choose a fishing rod.
Is this one bad?
-I don’t really know much about fishing. -Once selected, that’s it.
I don’t really know much about fishing..
Go to Hwa River and look for the running man banner.
The successful team, please choose from the remaining fishing rods.
This is good.
This one? Ok ok. We’ll take this.
For fishing, skills matter more than equipment.
Because I’m so lonely nowadays, I should be able to catch a lot of things.
I got it from someone else.
Really?
The VJ told me to give it to you.
Because you looked very bored. Oh what is this?
Even if it’s just bread, we are sharing it?
-on the right -yes
I can’t see anything except restaurants.
I’m so hungry suddenly.
There’s a supermarket in front. Do you want to go in?
-shall we buy something to eat? -shall we?
Let’s go buy something delicious.
Ji Hyo, just choose anything you want.
Oppa, can I really pick anything?
Of course! But you have to start over with me!
Last stretch!
Success!
This is the worst one, right?
I’m really tired. I’m really tired.
It’s on the right?
-we’re going to the right correct? -yes.
But the lane is on the right..I’m a bit confused.
Is this England?
-if you’re not in your right mind now, let me drive. -no no.
It’s the right side. If the handle is on the left, you have to be on the right lane.
Hey we should have picked the Viking.
Hey I ride Viking well.
What’s the next again? What are we going to do there?
There will be something.
Didn’t we pick a fishing rod?
-hey what fishing rod? It’s a bamboo stick! -how do we fish with this?
There’s a banner here, hyung.
That’s it.
-we get off here? -yes hyung.
Ok oh who’s that?
Who is it? Hurry, let’s go quickly.
Jong Kook, Jong Kook hyung.
Hey you reached so quickly?
Hyung, in running Man, we have to go faster.
-isn’t it titled "running man"? -yeah, don’t stop, run.
Oh what’s that there?
Isn’t that a fishing outfit?
-hey it’s books again. -aigoo aigoo
-how about we stick to Korean language’ to the end, hyung? -alright.
We’ll just stick by one way.
Hyung seems like a mayfly went into your mouth.
A mayfly went inside.
Hyung, are you hungry? Why are you eating mayfly?
I’m hungry. let’s take ‘’Korean Language’.
Ok I got it.
Hey let’s choose world history
-of course -world history?
-the world is ours. -what’s up man? -All right, baby.
Oh when did you arrive?
Aren’t you the first team?
Oh Gary.
You guys look good together!
-you even took the Viking together? -that’s right.
We ate something nice.
Really?
-you ate? -yeah
-ji Hyo, pick one you like -this is daebak.
What?
-truly -oppa, you choose one
-are you trying to do what you couldn’t do before.. -then we’ll choose this!
Remove your gloves.
Oh.
Hey!
Hey Suk Jin, you choose.
What do we choose?
I hate Math.
Is that so?
Ok now, can you see over there? There are baits.
There are two methods of getting the bait.
Over here is the shallow path to go straight while piggybacking.
-we are all very heavy. -over there, is the canoeing route.
We have to grab a canoe quickly.
- Sir, if we fail into the water your wig wouldn't come off right? - Don't worry.
It's even intact 10m below.
Gwang Soo.
I'm personally, very fond of you.
But not when we're on the same team.
Ok, get your members and set off quickly.
Let's go. Let's go quickly.
Hey, we've been running the entire day.
- Hey Sang Myeon, are you ok? - Of course.
- Can you carry me? - I'll carry you, hyung.
Jong Kook.
What are you doing?
Our Joon Gyu hyung, he seriously chose well.
You guys are piggybacking too so don't laugh at us.
Where do we go?
I don't know.
Piggyback.
How can the last one be "piggyback"?
Aren't there three boats?
- Because of you really, nothing is going right! - No!
It's not like that, hyung!
- Hyung. - Seriously!
It's all because of you.
- Nothing is going right! - Hey, what are both of you doing?
Hey, are we ready?
Hold still, hold still.
- You won't fall in, right? - Hey, we can't just balance ourselves.
What then?
- Be more relaxed. - Be relaxed.
Relax.
Just like you. One.
One.
- One. - Two.
- Hey, it's going more to this side. - Okay.
- Hey, you. - One. Yeah?
You… that's right, that sides' correct.
- Two. - That's right.
Hey, be careful. Don't fall into the water!
- Hey Suk Jin. - Yeah?
- Paddle a little more to the right. That's right, ok. - Oh? Ok.
Forward. Forward.
- Do you know how to do this? - Ok. Ok, go.
- Oh hey, we're not too bad! - Ok, one, two.
One, two. One, two.
Hey, let's be careful!
Ok!
Haste makes waste.
Yes.
Woo!
Wow oppa, you're doing great!
- Straight ahead! - Hey, we're about to crash!
Relax, relax.
Hey, stop bumping into us.
- Hey, more on your side. More, more. - More, more.
Hey!
Hey, don't knock into us! Hey, stay clear!
Hey, where are you going?
Hey, it's going way off course!
How did you steer way off from there?
Hey, where exactly is this going? Hey.
Hey, where did Jong Kook go?
Jong Kook hyung went for a piggyback.
This water is too cold.
My legs are…
This game is the most suited for you.
Hey, let's get off quickly.
Get off, get off.
It has to be on this side.
The canoe has to be parked at the right place.
Ok, we're going to win.
- Hey, push it! - The opposite direction, Ji Hyo.
Like this, the opposite direction.
Hyung! It's cold!
- Hyung, what are you doing? - Hey, what are you doing? Hurry.
- It's the right direction, it's the right direction. - Sunbae.
We're here, we're first!
Seriously!
We're first, hyung.
- Which do we choose? - Ok, there are five types of fish bait right here.
Can we open them?
The first one.
- The best fish meal, paste bait. - Yeah.
The second one, earthworms.
The third, grasshoppers.
The fourth, fruits.
- What's this? - The last one.
Raw meat.
If you win at Rock, Paper, Scissors, you can choose one to take with you.
Sir, let's start from you.
Rock, Paper, Scissors!
- This guy! - A pity.
- Hey, change direction. - Hey, he's quite something.
- Hey, we have to go. - Get the signature before coming back.
You guys must do well at Rock, Paper, Scissors.
This guy. This guy!
Oppa, I'll go first.
- Of course. - You get your act together.
- The first one. - Yes.
It's a 100% win. Suk Jin, do it.
Rock, Paper, Scissors!
- Jeez, what? - We won right? - Please go back, yes. Get the signature and come back.
- No, isn't there still me for Rock, Paper, Scissors? - You try too, you try too.
Rock, Paper, Scissors!
You lost? You lost?
Why couldn't even one person win at "Rock, Paper, Scissors"?
Gwang Soo, hurry up.
Gwang Soo. Hey, please.
Why are those people sitting there?
Hey Ji Hyo, where are you going?
- Oppa, We lost at "Rock, Paper, Scissors" - So?
We have to go back again and come back.
You can take the bait if you win.
- Really? - Have done it or not?
Come down, we came first.
Hey, this is, a chance for us.
Rock, Paper, Scissors!
- Yon won? - Sunbae looks tired.
Do it quickly!
We're telling you to move it.
- Hurry. - Rock, Paper, Scissors!
What did you say?
What do you have?
Earthworms, grasshoppers, fruits, raw meat and paste bait.
Grasshoppers?
The Grasshopper's here.
Hey, do it quickly!
- Are earth worms good? - They're good.
Be careful, sir!
If it's good, why did he turn his head away?
- Hey, hurry up! - How about paste bait, paste bait?
That's good too!
Hang on.
All these carps like them!
- Four, three. - No, this raw meat?
Two, one.
- The best. - Yes, you picked the earthworms.
- Oh, the earthworms are good choice. - Next.
It's good right?
What about the paste bait?
The paste bait's good too.
The fruits?
You go eat the fruits.
Hyung! What colour are you wearing now?
- Gwang Soo. - What colour are these clothes?
Give me the power of green.
Rock, Paper, Scissors!
He lost.
Haha!
Rock, Paper, Scissors!
Hyung, seems like you have to go once more.
What are you going to put out? What will you show?
I'll show rock.
You clearly said "rock"!
Rock, Paper, Scissors!
Yay!
Quick, quick. Let's choose!
Sang Myeon, that meat is a good choice.
If you can't catch any fish, you still have meat to eat.
Seems like we still need to go back and forth five more times.
Ha... Ha… Aigoo.
- Paste bait! - Okay!
- Fish like this right? - Yes, paste bait.
- Go to Wasu Elementary School and find the Running Man banner. - Primary?
Let's go, hyungnim.
- Where are we going now? - Let's go, hyung.
- Gwang Soo! - Yes, hyung!
- Yoo! - Lee!
I miss you.
- There are three left. - Not much left.
Faster! Let's play Rock, Paper, Scissors!
- Rock, Paper, Scissors! - Rock, Paper, Scissors!
Hey, you can't even do this?
Yes, it's good that we broke up!
You two are very compatible.
Why can't you play Rock, Paper, Scissors well?
Rock, Paper, Scissors.
Collecting the power of green!
Green, give me your power!
Rock, Paper, Scissors!
Yes!
Jae Suk, the fruit isn't a bad choice.
Chairman, fishes don't eat fruit.
No, they might eat it.
In summer, we catch them with watermelons.
- Do we really have to take grasshoppers? - What's left?
Grasshoppers, fruit and meat.
- That's it? - Yes.
Haha, let's forget it.
- Would grasshoppers be the best? - Grasshopper?
What will they eat among the rests?
It's the grasshoppers.
Haha, we are in big trouble. We don't have much left to choose.
Hyung, it's a good sign.
Hyung is wearing a green dress holding the grasshopper.
- We will surely win today! - I'm going crazy.
Grasshopper, eat it yourself.
What do we do with these grasshoppers?
- Are those fried grasshoppers? - Yes.
Using it as side dish while drinking?
We… we are?
We are the controller of water.
- Controller of Water! - Controller of Water!
Controller of Water!
One, two, three. Rock, Paper, Scissors!
Yeah!!
Let's choose meat.
We'll just grill it.
If we fail to catch any fish, let's eat them.
It's the fruit, then?
Meat and fruits, this guy.
Then what do we have?
- Only the fruit is left. - Fruit, fruit?
What is that, school bags?
Every couple need to wear a bracelet and fish for the seafood name tag.
We get to win windbreakers.
The two of you need to wear a bracelet.
Put on the bracelet.
Put on the bracelet and move together.
Be sure not to get the seafood nametags removed by someone.
The seafood name tags are inside the bags.
Starting now, you just need to get the seafood name tags.
Is there really seafood inside?
Hyung, it's seafood name tags.
Hyung.
This is strange.
Oh?
- We came first! - Is that the headmaster?
We came here first!
Hyung, believe me this time.
- Okay, Gwang Soo. - I have a strong feeling.
Then you will choose!
What's this?
This one!
Is this a club? We are wearing a bracelet.
Ba ba ba bam.
Hyung, who still dances like this?
What is this?
Then what dance is trendy now?
Did you talk about club dancing in the car?
No.
We talked about our kids.
And their education.
- Which one should we choose? This? - Okay.
Let's go.
The bag suits you.
Carry it like that, on your side.
Hello, how are you?
We'll choose this.
- You can start once you put on the bracelet. - Where is the bracelet?
Looks like a race, a race.
I'm sorry.
- What to do? - I think we have to stick it on top of our nametags.
I think it will fall easily.
Stick it as tightly as possible.
Gwang Soo…
We're dead.
Why do you say that?
Did you tear it?
I didn't feel anything.
We're dead.
Why is the stingray so big?
Like this.
No, it's because I am bigger in size.
I can block it.
Let's go.
It's easily removed, so you need to stick it properly.
Mackerel?
Where do we stick this?
That's why it's small.
When we want to remove the nametags, we just tear it like this?
Of course, as long as you tear it off.
Mercilessly?
What if Jong Kook hyung wants to take off your nametag?
Jong Kook... next time, towards the others…
If Jong Kook hyung says "I'm sorry" then he starts to tear your name tag.
Then…
How dare you!
Hyung, we definitely must get the windbreaker.
Of course. If we fish without a windbreaker, it's the end of us.
No matter what, use your charismatic acting skills.
Charismatic act or cowardly act?
Back and forth to confuse them.
Why am I like this…
Gary.
Gary, Gary.
Do you know where he is?
Gary.
Who is on the second floor?
There is someone on the second floor.
This is Jae Suk hyung's VJ.
- Oh, really? - Yes.
Jae Suk.
How can you eliminate me already?
Grasshopper, how can you do this?
Chairman, do you know why?
Because we have to do it quickly to get the windbreaker!
Didn't we let chairman live?
Gwang Soo, come here.
Hey, he is not your sunbae. He's the teacher, the teacher.
Come here, nearer. Your sunbae is calling you.
Are you crazy?
Are you trying to rebel?
Do you need me to shout over a small matter like this?
Come here.
Are you trying to tear of the name tag?
No, I'm not.
I just want to take off this.
No, you can't kneel down!
Hey, you! See what you did!
Jae Suk, please same my face.
Wait.
- Gwang Soo. - Jong Kook hyung. Let's eliminate him first.
- Eliminate Jong Kook hyung together.
I'll take care of him.
Tear off Gwang Soo's name tag, then we'll form the alliance.
Let's do that.
He is the betrayer anyway.
Take it off, take it off.
Sir, please remove his name tag.
He will be the one that tears off your name tag later.
I can't rip it.
Why not? Mine's already torn.
- Seriously, I'll work hard. Really! - You are not a bad child.
But, he's the betrayer. I'm telling you.
Gwang Soo will be the one that tears off your name tag, hyung.
I've been turning my back towards him all the awhile.
- But he hasn't torn mine? - He won't tear it now, he won't tear it now.
At the end, there's only one winner.
- Look, if he wanted to tear it he'd have done so earlier. - Of course.
I'll just let you off once.
- Yes. - Hyung, thank you.
Where are they?
- Upstairs. - Alright.
Hey. Let it go, let it go.
Hey, what are you doing?
You can't have high blood pressure, that's what I do.
I will do it.
Let's act it together.
1…2…3!
This, this… this… rude one!
This!
We'll see you later, hyungnim.
My blood pressure is really going up.
Oh!
Are you okay?
Let's ambush them.
We'll go down and find Jae Suk first.
Let's go now.
Let's go this way.
Oh.
Oh, you guys.
They went there.
- Who? - We're hiding now.
I know that too.
- Are you tearing it off? - No, no.
What are you doing?
How do we pass?
What's this?
Whose is it?
- What are you doing? - Whose is it?
- Whose? - Yours, yours.
What are you doing?
What are you doing now?
This… Why is this so long?
You really caught a lot of fishes today?
But, we are together. Why was mine the one who got ripped off?
It's worse than the shark.
There's a shark?
Hyungnim was really scary.
Today is too funny.
- Why is your hand so weak? - I got my hand on it, but it won't come off.
Do you know how he was following them?
We usually follow them like this, but teacher was like this.
You…
Hey, hey. Stop it.
Hyung, I'm looking. You just stay here.
I'm looking and you are too…
He's lecturing his hyung too much.
I'm already looking and you still…
Let's go up first then come back down.
Stay where you are. Aren't I already looking?
I'm curious too!
If you are curious watch the broadcast.
Gary.
Gary?
But, is he keeping a dog in his house? He keeps on calling Gary Gary.
Gary is a person's name.
Gary.
Gary?
What? Found them!
-I like you. -Hyungnim.
-Gary? -Chairman.
Chairman, how did you come in?
-Let's agree to rip one. -Hyungnim.
-So, let us... -Let's unite.
Just tear one.
I promise.
How can you do that? One person is not enough to attack.
If I tear yours, he can do it. If I tear him, you can do it.
Then... Do we need help later when finishing?
Of course, when we get there I'll be the king.
-Because you won't be able to do anything. Fruits won't catch anything. -I know.
I'm sure. We eat meat and then dessert.
That's right.
I trust you guys.
I told you, I told you.
Tear mine, mine.
Let us just go now and if we meet again...
-There's no time. -There's no time.
-Teacher, let us off once please! -We just started over again now.
We have just started over again.
-She wanted to tear mine. -That's what I said. Don't be so soft-hearted anymore.
Is it usually like this?
I saw hyungnim earlier, when she's about to tear yours...
-Let's settle this first, teacher. -Let's just tear off one. Just one.
Just use your strength, why are you so weak?
How could I use strength among us, let's just tear off his.
Why are you so scared?
-Let's play rock paper scissors for once. -Why?
To tear...
-Just do it cleanly? -We'll do it cleanly.
I'm tired to death.
Hey, tear it.
Hey, you. Why did you have to suggest that?
I wore too much layers.
-Hyung, you're even wearing long Johns? -He's not kidding.
I wear more...
He keeps saying he's tired.
Let's do rock paper scissors once.
I really.
-Moo ji ba. -Tear it off nearly?
Mook ji ba.
-You have keep your side of the bargain. -Of course.
Then just one person.
-Yours is the right hand. -Rock Paper Scissors!
Paper!
Rock!
Scissors! Paper!
Paper!
Gwang Soo, go!
They're coming.
Behind, behind!
Why is it like this? Yoo Jae Suk is usually like this?
They're here.
Block them, block them.
-Hey, we are just left with one guy now! -Why?
I already got torn.
I'm already torn. You have to get Jae Suk's.
-He lost in rock paper scissors and still ran away. -Really?
We only have one person left.
Look at Sang Myun's face.
Jae Suk was too despicable!
We agreed that the loser would be torn but he just ran off.
Joung Kook.
-Joung Kook. -What are you doing?
What are you doing?
We're waiting for you.
Let's go up first.
What are you guys doing?
We were waiting here.
Where did Jae Suk go?
We tore Gary's.
You got Gary's?
Let's work together and tear off Jae Suk hyung's?
-They're coming. -Jae Suk hyung.
Hey Gary, block him.
Block him.
This won't do, Jae Suk.
Lock the door. Block him.
Hey, I'll do it, I'll use my strength.
-I'll use my strength. -These guys have no strength.
Hey, come in.
Hyungnim, come here!
Hyungnim, come here quickly!
They don't have loyalty.
They're going to run again.
They might run away again.
Wait, wait.
Jae Suk hyung! Wait, wait!
-Hey, come in! -Wait! Jae Suk hyung!
That's not it.
Jae Suk hyung's not ripped.
What about this guy?
Only the tail's ripped.
This is so weird, what's this?
Let's hurry and finish the Mook-Jji-Ba.
But, playing mookjjippa doesn't make sense.
There's still one try left.
-Hey, our four teams should rip off Joung Kook team together. -That's right.
-Please lead the way, chairman. - No, hyung.
-Chairman, chairman. -We have to tear off one of theirs.
They are traitors. We have to tear one too.
-Chairman! Chairman! -They are traitors.
They are really traitors.
Done! This is it!
Yeah, chairman.
-This will work too, this will work too. -Chairman, chairman.
Ok, let's do it fairly now.
Ok, from now on, we'll catch Jong Kook.
Jong Kook.
Hyung.
I can't hear! I cannot hear you, hyung. I can't hear you.
Joon Gyu!
I can't hear you!
I can't hear you.
Jeez, we won't hear it.
Let me see, what are yours?
What is it?
-I won't tear it. -A shark, a shark.
Oh.
How can only the tall came off?
The camera's filming that way, they may be there.
Hey, don't act like you're very sharp.
You're not going to, right?
We won't tear.
I don't believe you.
-What's the matter with you? -Jeez, hyung.
Hey, you really can't be like this.
Jae Suk hyung can't tear anymore.
I can't tear anything.
So what was that earlier?
Why are we walking around so noisily?
That shocked me.
Do you still want to tear this off?
What?
Nothing's wrong, it's fine.
Your hand can't reach your back?
See if there's anyone in the toilet.
Where are you going?
They're here!
Hey, they're here, they're here.
-Here, here. -Catch them!
Catch them!
Don't tear it!
-Didn't I say so? -Hey.
-This place is full of betrayal, betrayal. -Gwang Soo, this fellow...
Look at this, this.
Didn't I say so?
If we don't do this quickly, there will ebe no winner.
Gwang Soo, help me scratch here.
Oh, that's it.
Oh, but the clothes are too thick.
A little higher.
Right there. Put your hand in, scratch.
I'm going crazy. Hang on.
I'll loosen it.
You know this feeling, right?
Gwang Soo, do it quickly.
-Jeez, really. -Come here quickly.
-Hyung's style is to really troublesome. -Higher.
A little higher, higher.
-Scratch it, scratch it. -Why are you sweating so much?
Oh there, there.
A bit higher, higher, higher.
A little to the side.
To this side!
A little higher.
Oh there, there.
Come here, come here.
Hang on for a moment.
We'll just, confront them. We'll run over and I'll catch them.
As long as we sacrifice once the others can get first.
Just pass them by naturally and pretend we don't know anything.
They're coming, sit down, sit down.
I'll go in front.
I...I can't do it.
I can't do it.
Is this plan a good one?
Hurry! I'm supposed to block, right?
-Hey, hurry with this. -Can't you even do this?
No, I'm blocking, catch him.
Catch him quickly.
Hey, aren't I blocking him?
What's with Park Joon Gyu, tear Park Joon Gyu's off!
Hyung, grab this side, this side.
The bracelet, he bracelet.
-Where is your bracelet? -The bracelet.
-The bracelet. -The bracelet.
The bracelet, out! The bracelet. They're out!
Hey, let's go!
I didn't foresee this.
I knew it'd be like this.
-Hang on. -Aigoo.
This is the jail.
Yours was torn?
It was torn off earlier.
I will only tell you both.
Gwang Soo's a jerk, make a call.
He's always been that kind of person.
-No, he's the worst. -No, I begged hyung but you wouldn't listen.
When I was watching it...
"They're doing that intentionally for laughs." That's what I thought.
-When I come and see for myself... -That's why, hyung.
-It's really savage! - I even threw up the last time at Gyeonghee Palace.
Why?
I just ran around the interior and exterior of Gyeonghee Palace.
I didn't know what I was doing.
I just ran wildly.
-Hey, apparently Min Soo came again because he was too angry. -Yes, I've also heard that.
It's worth coming again.
I must come again next time.
We'll just come together with Min Soo hyung.
I thought I could just go, "Hey, come here!"
And that would do.
"Yes... ah yes, hyung", just like this?
I was planning to for a 3 set if I met Jong Kook hyung.
Shall we try it?
-The fist time. -We'll meet face to face.
-Jong Kook. - We've met.
Jong Kook.
Let me tear one.
Jeez, you can't do this on the show.
This guy!
Let me tear one!
I said you can't.
Oh, oh!
Ohm oh. Hey, hey.
Oh, tear it, tear it.
Haha, there's medicine in my left pocket.
We wanted to do this.
Hey, it's not bad.
Hey, you guys came at the right time.
-Feel. -Feel.
Cross.
What's this, who are you teaming with?
Are you jealous, hyung?
One more time.
-Myeon. -Sang.
Let's tear Ji Hyo noona's off together.
You hang on.
She's a girl so let her off.
If it's a 1-on-1 it's going to difficult to use strength.
Right, but how can we use strength on Ji Hyo?
-That's right. They're only left with one. -I feel Ji Hyo's too pretty, I can't even get close to her.
-One team will lure her, the other... -He's totally fallen for Ji Hyo.
Is that so?
Actually his heart has been leaning towards Ji Hyo.
Hey, do you think it will work out?
Hey, can't I like her in my heart?!
-In my heart... -Hyung, what's this about loving in your heart?
We're filming now.
You're saying you love her.
It's no longer a love in your heart.
Liking her in my heart can also be like loving my mother.
Why do you even bother about things like this?
-Even if it's loving your mother... -What do you mean bother?
Hey, you should protect what you have to.
-But, as Song Ji Hyuo's fan I can also like her as an actress. -Well, that could be.
Why do these issues of mine have to be...
Hey, should I break this?
-This won't do. -Did I say something I shouldn't have?
But what Myeon Sang hyung said was right.
Hyung, we'll leave first.
I got it.
Gary.
Are you here?
They're here, they're in here.
Hey, Gwang Soo's a really poisonous snake.
If he's given half a chance...
-Be careful of Gwang Soo. -Jong Kook's strength is really great.
How can you guys be so cocky?
Let's just use one floor and then disperse?
-Let's disperse. -We'll just use one floor.
-We'll just use the first and second floor. -Right!
We'll just use this floor.
-A battle to the end. -Ok.
Start. One.
Two, three, four, five, six.
Seven.
We'll just grab that and tear it off.
Ten.
I'm going to tear it off.
Omo. Omo, omo.
What are the four of you doing?
I can't tear, I can't tear.
Oppa, catch them quickly.
Catch them.
Catch them. Oppa, you can catch them.
Ji Hyo! That's it, that's it.
It's only the tail.
The head is here!
Match it first.
Match it, match it.
It's right, it's right.
Hey, Ji Hyo.
What?
Sunbae, I love you.
What do you mean love?
Hyung, 10 seconds?
-10 seconds? -Ok.
Where do we go?
-We'll go this way, -Right, we'll go this way.
Ok, one...
Yeah!
Thanks.
Am I really out?
Then what do I do?
Ok, one...
Hey, what's with you? Hey!
Hey, what's with you?
-Hey. -Hey, what's with you?
You kept betraying others!
Hey really, you're seriously... -Hey.
Hey, Song Ji Hyo.
Let's flight it out!
Gwang Soo, Gwang Soo.
Gwang Soo.
It's raining so heavily and it's so cold.
How do we fish?
-From now, the time limit given is one hour. -Ok.
Within one hour, the team that catches the biggest fish wins.
The species doesn't matter.
Oh, what is it?
Ok, everyone come over to this side, everyone to this side.
What is it?
Ok, all fishermen come over here quickly.
We're not fishermen, we're Running Men.
He fished for half a century.
There are 50,000 excuses for not being able to fish anything.
Teachers caught a shrimp.
But five would be enough.
But this is real today.
It rained suddenly so the water temperature dropped.
-I'll just let you see it. -What is it?
If you had won today...
So what do we do, about the golden hook?
Today, because there was no winner, we won't be giving out the prize.
Of course.
-All of you today... -Take good care of it.
Next time.
Well for me, I don't know if it will be six months...
Or maybe even three months if it's urgent.
-If I come again... -It's fine.
You're coming again?
We haven't had a situation with no winner.
No winners today. Hey, we have to remember this.
Let's give our hyungs a round of applause.
No!
Is there anyone?
Here!
Open the door!
Why am I here?
Never give up hope!
Fugitive 1 has escaped.
I've finally returned after a year.
A water gun.