Where did she go?!
We're going to have to chase her down.
[A tiger leaves behind its' stripes,
and the criminal leaves behind evidence]
[An endless flight, and endless chase]
[And that person's identity is?]
[One day in June]
[Seoul Children's amusement park]
[Full of children out on
a picnic on this cheery day]
Hi!
-Enjoy yourselves!
-Bye...!
[It's Mr. Grasshopper]
[Smiling at the children's innocence]
[Even the Tiger is smiling]
-Aren't they so cute?
-It really makes me want to have kids.
-Get married first, married first.
-I know.
What is this?
[But what is this hidden under the cloth?]
You want us to unveil it?
Both of these?
Wow!  It's gold!  It's real gold!
[Pure gold?]
Touch it.  It's real gold.
[Staring at it eye level]
Are these the prizes?
Even though it may have been small...
But we've been giving out
little bits of gold at a time...
So the owner of the jewelry store
that produced all our prizes
said he is very thankful,
and that he is an avid fan of yours...
so he gave those to us today to be given
out as the winning prize.
[The most radical prize they have
seen thus far]
The owner of the jewelry store?
This is the first time
I've ever seen anything like this!
-He gave these to us?
-That's so beyond generous!
Look at her eyes!
I can see you salivating over it.
How can I get my hands on this gold?
Now the competition among 4 teams will start.
-4 teams?
-The first mission is...
Is to find the guests.
Today's guests are hiding around
this place right now.
[The guests that are hiding around
in this wide open park]
[Once there are 3 members to a team,
then the team succeeds]
This is a team race.
I'll start by announcing the teams.
Yoo Jae Suk and Lee Kwang Soo are one team.
Gary and Ha Ha are a team.
Kim Jong Kook and Ji Suk Jin are a team.
-You must be happy to be on Jong Kook's team.
-I'm with Jong Kook!
-Everyone, please get started!
-Let's go.
[Find the guests that are
hiding in the large park...]
It's so unfair for me to be doing this alone...
I'm at a total disadvantage!
It's really been a long time since
we've been teamed up together.
Yoo...!
Kwang Soo...
It's because you said Yoo when I'm Yoo.
Yoo...!
-Lee!
-We miss you! (As in Uee, the k-pop star)
-Hi!
[Yoo-Lee duo saying hi to the children]
-Hello.  My name is Seo Yoon Seo.
-Huh?
-It's Yoon Seo.
-Ah, Yoon Seo?  Seo Yoon Seo?
-I saw you on the television.
-You saw me on the television?
-What did you see me on?
-On the television.
Have you seen me on television?
[Avoiding...]
Do you know this man?
-You know me?!
-Who is he?
-Mister stupid?
-Mister stupid...!
Mister stupid...!
-That's right...!
-When it comes to kids...
Kids always say things the way it is,
and how they see things...
But how am I Mister stupid?
That's hilarious...
[Bye, Mister stupid...]
Today's female guest...
[Only thinking of a female guest...]
Where are you?
-Guest!
-Guest...
Guest...!
[There's someone in the bushes?]
Who's that?
What the heck?
[The person that's
hiding in the bushes is...?]
Bum Soo!
[The God of singers, Kim Bum Soo!]
Bum Soo, you?
Bum Soo!
What's going on?
-I got the wrong person.
-Have fun here today.
-Gary...
-You must be here to have fun.
[The kids pretending like they didn't see him]
You should just go back to hanging out.
-Aren't you looking for me?
-We're searching for female guests.
[The condition for their teammate
is that it's a female]
-Have a great time since you're here.
-Seriously?
But it really is good to see you.
-Our Bum Soo...
-Bum Soo...
Did you come here with other people
from your company?
[Are they seriously trying to not take him in?]
No... I didn't come here for that.
You think I'd come dressed like this to play?
-Then a performance...?
-Running Man...
[Stop it... Stop it]
Bum Soo, we have to do this with a
female gust because it's been so long!
Just tell everyone that you came to film
Animal Farm... Hurry up and say that...!
You have me now.
It's our village!
-It's totally your village...
-It's my village!
This really is overwhelming...
-Hey, the Merry-Go-Round is spinning!
-What?
There's someone in there...
There's someone in there!
Who is it?!
[Who could it be?]
I see someone's hair!
-What are you doing?!
-Who is it?
-What are you doing up there?
-How did you know?
[The second guests that's recognizable
even by just seeing the back of the head]
[Funny Man, Yoon Jong Shin]
I almost didn't see him up there...!
Jong Shin!
Why are you spinning around like that?
Do we have to have him on our team?
-That's not very good...
-Maybe he won't come down.
-Isn't this game about finding me?
-This game isn't about finding you...
-You're not the main guest today.
-I'm almost good as Park Ji Sung.
If there are 12 guests on the show,
you'd be the last one we'd pick.
You know what?
If we don't like you after seeing you,
we can even just keep on going.
You're not the one in charge here right now...
You found someone!
What the heck?
[Jae Suk, sees Jong Shin]
Jong Shin, what the heck?
We fished him... We fished out Jong Shin.
I saw a hamster that kept spinning around
on the merry-go-round...
And when I went to check it out...
It was him... He was hiding in there.
Won't my character be overlapping his?
[Overlapping Suk Jin's character
as the weakest link]
He really is...
He really is overlapping the character!
I got teamed up with overlapping Suk Jin,
and the kid I don't like.
Totally... Totally!
You really are like a hamster today.
I'll see you guys later... Okay?
-Work hard!
-Okay... Okay...
Kwang Soo... Where are all the guests?
When are they going to find me?
What if this is it for me
by staying here like this?
It's really hot.
What?
Is something there?
[Someone in the bushes?]
Who's there?
-There's someone there?
-Yeah...
Who's there?
It's me...
[Return of the Rock star, Yoon Do Hyun!]
-What took you guys so long to find me?
-Do Hyun!
-Hurry up and get out here.
-How did you get back there?
How did you get in there?
[Jae Suk, Kwang Soo and Do Hyun are a team]
[Gathering of all the teams
that found their guests]
-R and B...
-The juror of all the ballads...
-Yes, the juror...
-Then who's Ji Hyo coming with?
-Who else is going to be here?
-It's gone!
Where did it go?
[The Gold... Has disappeared!]
Someone...!
[How did this happen?]
[Someone has stolen all the gold!]
[That is none other than... Song Ji Hyo!]
-Ji Hyo...
-Ji Hyo!
[I'm sorry, but I'm taking the gold]
[C-hun S-ung I-m]
[That's how...the gold disappeared]
[A little while ago]
Hello?
-Hello?
-Who's this?
-Running Man's Ace, Song Ji Hyo?
-Yes?
You will be given a special mission.
[Special mission request?]
Your mission is to steal the gold that's
up for the grand prize today.
If you can safely move
the gold to the final destination,
all that gold will become yours
for the taking.
So I'm to trick all the Running Man?
All by myself?
[Take the taxi to the Jamsil district at the
Civic Park by the Han River...]
[and meet with the secret mission personnel]
[Tactical approach: ]
[Question-Hello, my name is Song Ji Hyo
Answer-Ah... Miss Chun Sung Im]
[This is how CSI Ji Hyo started her
secret mission against all the Running Men]
Please take me to Jamsil district
at the Civic Park.
[The runaway with the gold]
[Chun Sung Im]
-The gold is gone!
-I bet Ji Hyo's team took it.
Inside these briefcases are position trackers
you can use to find Song Ji Hyo.
What is that?
Ah... this!
[Using the state of the art technology,
they're off to start the chase!]
[Chase preparation complete!]
What else is in the case?
[The CSI chase team that's been given
everything they need to chase her down]
Suk Jin!  Where is the place?
That's... Near the heliport that they met
Big Bang in the earlier episode?
That's the only place with a heliport.
That's right...
[Comfortable?]
When do we get to eat?
-How can we eat already?
How can you already be asking for food?
[Jong Shin already asking for food]
Come on!  Drive more carefully!
How are you driving with your father and
the hamster in the car with you?
We're going to the veterinary clinic.
-The hamster is a little sick...
-What kind of a hamster talks?
I'm going to get treated for heart worms.
Treated for heart worms right now.
-Mister!
-Yes?
Why don't you go and get
the breakfast ready already?
[That's how the CSI chase teams
got off to their start]
[Han River Jamsil Civic district]
Thank you.
[CSI arrives at her destination]
[The chase teams are coming!  Hurry...]
[In this wide open space...
How to find the secret agent?]
[Take the taxi to the Jamsil district at the
Civic Park by the Han River...]
[And meet with the secret agent]
[Where is the secret agent that
she has to approach?]
Hello, my name is Song Ji Hyo.
[If it was the secret agent,
undoubtedly there would be the response of CSI]
Hello...
Hello, my name is Song Ji Hyo.
Hello... Hello, my name is Song Ji Hyo.
[Running away from humiliation]
They're not it!
They're not it...!
Hello, my name is Song Ji Hyo.
-Yes, I'm a huge fan...
-Yes, thank you.
[The people that are cheering her on]
Hello, my name is Song Ji Hyo.
Ah yes... Hello.
-I think we're supposed to do something.
-Yes, I'm on a mission.
-Pretty?  Fat?  Skinny?  Ugly?
-You're the best!
You're tall, you're short, you're cute...
What is it that we can do for you?
No... No... No!
[Both getting frustrated]
This is driving me crazy too!
[There weren't any secret agents among
the kind strangers...]
[CSI heading toward the inner pier]
Song Ji Hyo... You won't get far.
What is Ji Hyo doing anyways?
Song Ji Hyo, we're almost there.
[Perhaps one of the people inside?]
Hello, my name is Song Ji Hyo.
Ah...!  Hi!
[All the people gladly welcoming her]
Please have a great time.  Thank you.
Ah... This is nerve-wracking.
Hello, my name is Song Ji Hyo.
Miss Chung Sung Im?
-Miss Chung Sung Im?
-Yes!
I found you!
Seriously...!
[Disguised as a secret agent...
Youngest PD, Lee Hwa Jin]
[Shh... This place could be wiretapped]
[Because of the risk of wiretaps,
being relayed in a message]
[Right now, the C.S.I. agents are coming
after you with a position tracker]
[It seems there's a position tracker on
the gold.  Please check to confirm]
[Position tracker?]
[Handing the position tracker that was
on the gold to the secret agent]
I didn't see that!
I didn't see it...
[I will deceive the chasers with the tracker,
so escape quickly!]
[There's a helicopter ready for you at the pad.
Go meet the secret agent at Misari cafe]
['S' cafe in Misari?]
[And...]
And this is...
[A mysterious black pad]
This is a very important clue for your
final destination.
You have to make sure to receive one from
every other location that you stop by at.
[Ji Hyo has to receive one from every
location that she has to go to]
A bicycle has been readied for you outside.
-To the heliport?
-You can ride it to the heliport.
I'll be on my way.
Please destroy the wiretaps.
[First secret agent approach is a success]
[Off to the heliport to move to Misari]
I had no idea at all that there would be a
position tracker in my bag]
It's about time the members got here...
[You have to hurry.
They're coming after you!]
[The target is CSI-Chun Sung Im]
[The helicopter ready for the move]
[The fugitive Ji Hyo,
running away with the gold]
[Simply thwarting the chase with the chopper]
I think we're almost here...
This is where the heliport is!
-Isn't it?
-This is it, this is it.
-Isn't that Song Ji Hyo?
-Where?
-Over there... There...
-That's Song Ji Hyo!
Let's get out first.
They're here!
What is she doing there right now?
Is she taunting us?
Song Ji Hyo!
Hey!
Mister, hurry!  Hurry!
[The gold is in my hands!]
[Bring that back!]
[You're going to hang onto the helicopter?
Of course, not...]
[Helicopter lift-off complete]
Wow... this is driving me crazy.
[The CSI chase team that let her
slip through their hands]
We lost her.
We were the first ones to arrive...
There it is.  They're running around.
They're taunting us right now.
Give back the gold!
Hey!  Tease Ji Hyo!
The chopper is off the ground!
She's already escaped!
-Suk Jin!  She's gone!
-She escaped?
That's Song Ji Hyo?
-Hey!!!  Song Ji Hyo!
-Where are you going?!
-Song Ji Hyo's gone.
-She's left?
We lost her right in front of our eyes.
-You saw her getting on it?
-It was almost a Hollywood movie.
[If they had caught her,
it could have been like a Hollywood movie?]
-You should've hung onto the chopper.
-You're saying we could've hung onto that?
There it is!
All those guys were glaring at me.
All the guys were glaring at me...
What to do...?
This is quite the spectacle.
Isn't it pretty decent?
[Was under the impression the show would be
the most cultivated out of all Variety shows]
-Since this is the CSI episode...
-At this rate, she'll be on a submarine next.
Where to now?
Since she's moved her destination,
we have to chase her down again.
-Let's all go now then.
-Off we go!
-I've started her tracker.
-Where is she then?
But it's still showing the same place.
It's showing the parking lot over there.
-Is she around here somewhere then?
-I think she may be.
Why is it showing over there when we
saw Ji Hyo leaving in the helicopter?
Huh?
Maybe she took the helicopter
and got off over there.
Somewhere within a 5 minute
walking distance from here.
Taking the helicopter to go over there...
No way...
What the heck is this?
[Han River Jamsil Pier right nearby]
There's no place around here...
For the helicopter to land...
[Following Ji Hyo's tracker to here...]
Hey!  Song Ji Hyo!
Bring back the gold!
[The chase team has no idea that she's
thrown away her tracker]
Bring back the gold!
[The beautiful view seen
outside the chopper window]
In the helicopter...
It only takes 10 minutes to get to Misari.
If you were to go in a car...
It takes about 30 minutes?
That's how long it would take.
[Catch me if you can!]
[Will she be able to
take possession of the gold?]
Have you seen Song Ji Hyo?  Song Ji Hyo?
[CSI chase team arriving at the pier]
There's no place for the
helicopter to set down around here.
Unless it's magic, there's no way.
But the tracker is showing this place.
[Everyone searching for Ji Hyo
with a sense of urgency]
Do Hyun!
Kwang Soo!
We don't have time for you to
walking around like that!
We'll work harder!
[Agent Yoon Do Hyun
pledging his determination]
I'm seriously about to go crazy here!
-We're the fastest ones right now, right?
-Fastest?  We're the slowest!
[The Green team is busy catching up,
let alone chasing]
-Hello.
-Ji Hyo definitely did leave though.
Jae Suk... Wait for me.
[In a relaxed pose,
wanting to go along with Jae Suk]
Why are you being so rushed?
-Over there...
-Hello.
Jae Suk.  I'm going to go take a look around.
You saw it, right?
Every time we pass by...
No matter who it is,
as soon as they see Jae Suk...
-As soon as they see Jae Suk, it's 'Oh my...!'
-Do Hyun!  Hurry up and look for her!
Seriously...!
[The tracker is definitely around here...]
[But Ji Hyo is nowhere to be seen]
Hey Gary, what are you looking for?
I don't know either.
I'm searching for the tracker...
What are you doing?
-What the heck!
-Hwa Jin!
[Discovered PD Hwa Jin disguised
as a kitchen chef]
Have you seen Ji Hyo?
-I haven't seen her.
-What's this?
[The mission card in the apron pocket?]
I can't tell you.
Does it have something to do with us?
-Who is he?
-Huh?
I think he's a celebrity.
Tell us!  Quickly!
-We can see it!
-You're hiding something!
[Who is he?]
Okay... Okay... Okay!
-Okay... Here.
-What's going on?
Follow me.
That hat really suits you.
What is this?
Can we go in there?
[Access denied]
-How do we get in there?
-Is this for limbo?
How are we supposed to do this?
-You're all CSI crime team, right?
-Yes.
This is the scene of the crime.
Really?!
[Scene of the crime?]
[Crime scene holding clues as to how to
go after the fugitive, Ji Hyo]
Are we not able to access it?
[But how to get into the crime scene?]
[CSI Crime Team-Site Monitoring]
[2 people in a row needs to limbo across in
order to succeed onto the crime scene]
They can't even bend forward,
so how can they bend backwards?!
We're not made to bend like that.
[2 worried middle aged men]
[Green Team's Kwang Soo challenge]
[Because even at this moment,
Ji Hyo is making her escape]
[Taking up the challenge
without any hesitations]
[Giraffe is bending with all his best efforts]
[This is what he can do...]
[Giraffe's whole body is starting to quiver]
I don't think I can do it...
If you can't do it, then get out.
We don't have time.  Hurry.
[Giraffe going in for another try]
Kwang Soo... Don't cry... Don't cry.
Kwang Soo, don't cry.  I'm sorry.
[Shaking all over again]
[Kwang Soo, just staring at the limbo bar
without saying a word]
I'm sorry for making you do this...
[Sad giraffe for being so tall
with such a long neck]
[Impossible to begin with...]
Why are my pants so tight?
It's because your thighs are so thick.
You're blaming the pants...
Not even thinking of your own legs.
And he always blames his shirt for being tight
instead of looking at his own arms!
Don't you think that's so silly?
You should wear the pants for a top.
[What the heck does that mean?]
Hey!  Where would I stick my head?
-What about my face?
-The zipper!
[Face inside the open zipper?]
You can just make the zipper a little bigger.
-Say something that makes sense.
-Then go around naked.
-This is hard!
-It's hard... It's not easy!
Ji Hyo is just getting further away, Jong Kook.
[Limbo, not easy for even Mr. Capable]
5... 4... 3...
[Mr. Capable fails!]
[Elated herbivores]
[Teasing the King of the Jungle for once]
[Ultimately restarting
the mission 5 cm higher]
During this whole time,
Song Ji Hyo is making her escape.
-Hurry!
-Do it, quickly!
-Bum Soo's nickname is 10:10.
-10:10... Why?
Do you see my eyes?
It's pointing to 10:10 right now.
[His eyes always pointing to the same time...]
Bum Soo is always angry.
Mom, feed me!
[He's always pointing to 10:10...]
I'm going to give it a go!
[The best challenger, Bum Soo...
His chances are?]
[Wow... success!]
[Agent Bum Soo's amazing flexibility]
Hey!  You're good!
You're really good!
It's because he's using his head.
Ha Ha, you can do it.
Why don't you just take off your pants
if you're going to do that?
[If this happens, then 2 successes in a row?]
[Back to original position...]
Not yet, not yet...
[If he can just pull the head through?]
[Success?]
I got it, right?  Success!!
Awesome!
[Blue team-Pass!]
[The blue team scored the case
from succeeding the mission]
[Chase down Ji Hyo that's getting
further away by the minute]
-The one in the middle.
The middle?  Let's go!
-Work hard, everyone!
-Fighting!
[The blue team to go off on the chase first]
My feet... It's so hot on the feet!
-Jae Suk...
-Yeah?
-Try doing this with your feet.
-Like this?
Put them like that, and instead of jumping,
shimmy gently like this.
-There you go... you got it.  A little more.
-You're almost there!
That's a fail... That's a fail!
-Isn't it hard?
-It's totally hard!
-I need to think about this for a second.
-I used to be able to do this.
Concentrate on it, and don't laugh.
-It was lower than this for me.
-Just concentrate on it real hard.
-I think I can get this.
-Don't laugh, don't laugh.
-What are you doing with this?
-What is this?  What is that?
-My hand just went out like that.
-What the heck is that?
-That's a Suzy Q style limbo.
-You know that's not it.
-Your legs... Watch your legs.
-This is my style!
[With Suzy Q's style]
You got it!  It looks good!
-Good, good!
-You got it!
[Fail...]
[The blue team is opening up their case]
What's this?
[Misari Cafe]
[Address:  Gyungido-Han Namsi, Misadong 314]
-Hurry up and type it in the navigator.
-Bum Soo, input the address in there.
[The destination where Ji Hyo is headed next]
[You just wait, Song Ji Hyo]
Huh? Seoul Pier at the civic district?
Then seeing how the location is still there...
Then she's left the tracker behind there.
-Don't you think?
-Ah, like in the movies?
So that she can buy herself some time...
She's a total brain... A brain.
[On the other hand, CSI is...]
[Arriving at the destination, Misari]
[This is where the cafe is?]
[Ji Hyo getting to her destination much
faster than had she been one of the chasers]
[Thank you!]
[She needs to quickly find the secret agent
in the cafe and approach him...]
[But right here...
is where a huge problem arose]
I got off at the wrong place.
[The helicopter landed somewhere else!]
It feels like it's going to be
more than a kilometer.
[Even though she is quite a bit ahead...
If she's not careful, she may be caught]
[Nothing else to be done... Let's run!]
-You do it.
-I think... I think I can do it quickly.
You really think you can do it?
[He falls down quickly...]
What the heck is all this?
-Seriously...
-Anyone else here that's done it?
I'll do it, I'll do it.
[Jae Suk up for the re-challenge]
[The unique form is still the same...]
[Bottom dance style?]
I seriously can't even watch this...
Your lips... What's with the lips?
What the heck is this?
-What the heck is this?
-That's just something I do!
[The poor concentration that he's feeling]
You!  Just go catch some fish
so we can have it for breakfast.
Fighting!
[Another try at the limbo with
the unique form again]
[Fail]
[The tireless hamster]
If you're going to do it like that,
then don't do it!
-You want it raised another 5 cm?
-Yes, yes.
[The relaxed Do Hyun passes with ease]
[Jae Suk up for a re-challenge]
[The neck...!]
[Success!]
[The Green Team succeeds]
-You can take one of the remaining cases.
-Which one shall we take?
-This one.
-Okay.  Let's go.
Raise ours just another 5 cm.
There's an address. Misari's 'S' cafe.
-Misari?
-Misari's 'S' Cafe.
What is Ji Hyo doing anyways?
[CSI Ji Hyo, what are you doing?]
[Through walking and running,
Ji Hyo's almost at her destination]
[Misari 'S' Cafe]
Where is he?
Hello. Hello, my name is Song Ji Hyo.
You're the owner, right?
[Approaching the secret agent]
[Earns another mysterious black board]
Thank you.
[We've prepared a red car for you.
The car keys are hidden somewhere in the cafe]
Somewhere in the cafe?
[Only once the car keys in the cafe are found,
will it be possible for her to move]
[Somewhere inside here is the key
for her transportation to the next spot]
[Even though she's feeling the urgency,
the keys are nowhere to be found]
[Since the time's been wasted for getting
off at the wrong spot, she must hurry!]
[The target is... CSI (Chun Sung Im)]
[Ji Hyo, moving to cafe's 2nd floor]
[Somewhere in this place is... The car key!]
This is a car key... Right?
[Where's the car?]
[A red car in the corner of the parking lot]
I don't think this is it!
[Trouble... The key she found is a fake!]
[The CSI chase team,
getting closer to the cafe]
[The real key is somewhere...]
[Discovered another car key!]
[It has to be the real key this time!]
[Luckily, it's the real key this time]
[Get a ticket at Sanbong Terminal
and hand it to the secret agent
disguised as a bus driver.]
[Open the passenger compartment]
[Off to the next destination]
[The chase team's car!!]
My mind that's sharp as a knife...
I trust in it.
-What the heck!  That's Song Ji Hyo!
-Where?
Bye guys...!
-Where?  The red car?
-That's Song Ji Hyo!
Where?
That's Song Ji Hyo, right?
Isn't that Song Ji Hyo?
I think that's Song Ji Hyo!
Hey!  Song Ji Hyo!
[Ha Ha on the chase]
[The Blue Team lets her slip by again
right in front of their eyes]
We keep losing her...
[To let her slip through their fingers
like that twice now...!]
We have to get the mission done quickly
and go after her.
Gary, Ha Ha, and Kim Bum Soo's team
keeps bothering me.
I bet they're all resenting me
quite a bit right now.
It's the first time these guests
are seeing me...
But they're just going to see me
as someone who stole the gold...?
I'm not that kind of a person...
[But even something that she doesn't know...]
[A phenomenal actor...
Next week, he'll be on the move!]
[Kim Soo Hyun]
So this is another crime scene?
-Captain... Do another limbo across.
-She always leave problems behind.
This isn't going to work.
[Anyways... Detective Kim, Captain Jang
and Investigator Ha, first to arrive]
[CSI Crime Team-Collect the evidence]
[Without leaving a mark or a fingerprint,
find the piece of paper...]
[However... 3 of you must move together]
[Inside the investigator briefcase
they chose first]
[2 pairs of shoe covers and a pair of gloves]
-1, 2, 3.
-This investigation is a pain.
[This is how the investigation is painful
for the person that has no shoe covers]
[How is this a scientific investigation?]
1, 2, 3!
-1, 2, 3.
-How is this CSI?
[CSI is an abbreviation for Chun Sung Im...]
[Into the scene of the crime without leaving
any marks or their fingerprints]
[Where is the evidence 'piece of paper'?]
-How about we switch off?
-Sit me down there first.
[Investigation or not, it's hard...]
It could be up here somewhere...
[Desperately trying to protect the
scene from being contaminated]
-I tried not to let my feet touch the floor.
-Your feet didn't touch... They didn't touch.
Seriously... Grab onto to me.
[Investigator Ha coming to
Detective Kim's rescue]
[First flipping over]
They're not touching,
they're not touching.
[Having touched everything
except for the feet]
[Blue Team investigators experiencing
all sorts of chaos]
-We're something else... We're pretty great.
-This is making things difficult for us.
This is hard.
[The Green Team on the other hand,
that followed not too far behind]
[Using the back light that was in the case?]
There's a good chance that
there's something written somewhere.
[Find the writing regarding the
evidence 'piece of paper']
[This cafe with
an unusual amount of white walls]
[There has to be writing somewhere...]
There's something here!
[This is a trail of clues!]
-I see something!
-It's a shadow.
I thought I saw something.
That is really pretty though.
Hey!  There's stupid written on here.
[Stupid]
[Wait...]
[This mark is definitely...
Something related to us!]
[Is the evidence 'piece of paper'
hidden here somewhere?]
[The Blue Team finds the evidence!]
-Yes...
-Set him down here.
[Opening up the piece of paper...]
[Sanbong city bus terminal]
[Address: Seoul Jungranggu Sangbongdong 83-1]
[So this is where CSI Ji Hyo
is headed off to next...!]
[Blue Team's investigation complete]
Anyways, the basic to any detective...
The bread is the best when it comes
to working undercover...
[Bread is the best at times
when working undercover]
Would you like this too?
This joy of eating after a day's work...
[That's right... We all work to eat and live]
-May I ask you one thing?
-What is it?
There is something I'm uncertain about
regarding this investigation...
-Yeah?
-The criminal this time is Song Ji Hyo...
Yes, what about it?
I've heard that
you dated her briefly in the past...
[The love story inside Captain Gae's memories]
-Okay...
-Okay?  Promise.
[Suspect Song Ji Hyo,
and the chaser, Captain Gae]
Gary is my man today!
[What kind of a play is this on fate?]
Is it okay for you to be investigating
with your feelings involved?
Back then... I was in love briefly.
There's nothing like that between
the two of you anymore?
-Of course not.
-I'm keeping my eye on the 2 of you.
It's like a movie... A movie.
A love affair of the criminals.
I wonder if she's making well
with her escapes...
What?!
-I'm just joking around right now...
-That's not very appropriate!
I'm sorry.
-I hope she got on that bus quickly...
-Come on, seriously!!
[Keep teetering back and forth
into the relationship?]
-You can't be doing that.
-I'm done, I'm done... Okay.
With my own hands...
I'll tear her name tag off.
So you can just keep that in mind.
[That's right...
Just forget about being the Monday couple]
I'm sure they're searching for me frantically.
I came all this way...
[The difficult and loneliness
of being on the run alone...]
[Constantly feeling parched...]
[Arrival at destination]
[Sangbong Terminal]
[Get a ticket from Sangbong Terminal...]
[And hand it to the secret agent
disguised as a bus driver]
Please give me all the tickets that you have
for this time frame, please.
-All of them?
-Yes.  Give me all of them.
[Since she doesn't know which bus it is...]
Thank you.  Have a good day.
[Ji Hyo buys a ticket for every bus
that's running for this time slot]
[Where is the secret agent
disguised as the bus driver?]
Hello, my name is Song Ji Hyo.
[By any chance... Is he the one?]
Oh yes... Hello.  Nice to see you.
['Nice to see you' isn't the right response]
You can get on.
-You can get on.
-Get on this?  Where...where is it headed?
-This is headed to Yeojoo.
-I can't go to Yeojoo.
-No, I can't go to Yeojoo... No, no.
-You can't go?
[This person is not a secret agent!]
Hello, my name is Song Ji Hyo.
[Perhaps disguised as one of the drivers
taking a lunch break?]
-What is this?
-It's nothing.  I'm sorry, sorry.
Hello, my name is Song Ji Hyo.
[Not in here either]
Sorry... Sorry!
Where is he?
I think we're almost there...
Song Ji Hyo... You can't escape us any longer.
[The Blue Team is almost at scene!]
Where is the driver?
Not much left, Song Ji Hyo.
Please... Please...!
Please... Hello, my name is Song Ji Hyo.
Ah... Miss Chun Sung Im?
[It's the secret code!]
I have been searching for you everywhere!
There's no one around.
-Just me...
-This is for you.
Korea's Institute of Science and Technology...
Go to KIST.
You can go to KIST and use
'Hello, my name is Song Ji Hyo' as a code.
Thank you!
[But the blue team is right in front!]
[Ji Hyo receives
another mysterious black tablet]
What is this?
[With my own hands...
I will tear off Ji Hyo's name!]
[But in the meantime, Ji Hyo is...]
[Heading off to KIST.
Escapes successfully!]
[CSI Investigative Team-Canvas the scene]
[Use a sketch to find the witness]
-Witness?
-Sketch?
There's a witness that just saw Song Ji Hyo
approaching a secret agent.
It's been confirmed that the witness
is still inside the terminal.
Draw a physical drawing of the witness
to find the said witness.
[Find the witness by drawing out
what the witness looks like!]
This is the description.
[Physical description of
Song Ji Hyo's eyewitness]
First, the witness is taller than 170 cm.
A darker toned skin.
Somewhere between the age of 20-30.
Wears glasses.
A busy head of hair,
and long and thin face.
Very average.
-Bushy hair?
-Bushy hair.
I'm already done drawing.
I didn't know that
the witness had facial hair.
It's not facial hair,
but the skin is just a bit dark.
A sketch is about drawing from your gut.
Why are you concentrating on it so hard?
But...
170... You have to indicate the height.
This is...like Picasso's work!
It's something.
[Bum Soo's sketch indicating
the witness' height]
The pass code to approach a witness...
To sing my song, 'Bogoshipda'...
[Blue Team's witness rendering]
[Where is the witness that witnessed
CSI Ji Hyo?]
The face is smaller and longer...
That could be him, but he's too clean.
Here, here... There he is!
-He is just like the drawing!
-He is just like it!
I think he could be the one.
Can you please stand up?
Excuse us.
-He is, he is...
-Nice, nice...
-Isn't he the same?
-He's the same!
[He does look slightly like it...]
There's no need to wonder about it...
It is the guy.
[The secret pass code...]
[Not the witness!]
I thought he was the one, but he's not.
I'm sorry.
-He really does look like it...
-He almost looks the same...
Let's see this...
The witness has an angular face.
-An angular face?
-And a fierce look on his face.
We have to draw this quickly.
This is our eye witness.
[The witness must be found in
order to find Ji Hyo's next destination]
Casual dress... Draw the casual dress too.
-So this is what he looks like...
-Then what about the secret pass code?
"Bingsoo, bingsoo, Patbingsoo...
Don't melt... Don't melt...!"
-That should work.
-Okay, okay... Got it.
Where are you going?
Okay... We have to be the first to find him.
We have to walk around the whole place...
This guy here... He looks similar.
He looks similar!  His has a high nose...
and a wider face!
Okay...
[Singing the pass code right away]
I'm sorry.
[He's not the witness]
Age is not identified...
And he has a very round face.
Draw a circle then.  A circle.
His face looks like a moon when he smiles.
His nose bridge isn't high or low...
So somewhere in the middle.
So about this much...
[Huh?]
And large ears.
-So draw them big like this.
-And the hair is tied into a ponytail.
So like this?
Hey...
But how can you draw the hair like this?
What is that?
[Doubtful that a 10 month old
baby is the witness...]
-Not sure about this.  A cute expression.
-Cute expression?
We can just draw
the lips puckered like this then.
[Cute expression means puckered lips?]
A smaller frame.
Is that a hamburger?
[So tiny]
What kind of a person is this?
This is a baby.
-This is totally a baby.
-I drew it just like the description.
It's just like the description.
I'll draw it.
[Jae Suk taking the challenge of sketching]
-I'll describe it.
-I'll draw it just like you call it.
A small frame.
Hard to tell the age.
[Drawing it just like the description]
What is that?
It's pretty similar.
Kwang Soo, you want to try drawing it?
[Ultimately Kwang Soo is...]
You must have some art classes.
You're drawing it like the description?
Let me see it.
You call that a drawing?
How is this...
How is this any different from ours?
How is this... How is this any different?
[Using 'Maybe I loved' as the pass code]
[Can they find
the witness with that sketch...?]
-There aren't many people with their hair tied.
-There won't be many...
[It seems there wouldn't be many people
with their hair tied in a single tie...]
[However...]
She's pretty similar...
I don't look like that... That's not me.
-That really isn't me...
-You kind of look like Kwang Soo's drawing...
[Right or not, the pass code...]
I have no idea what you're doing...
[Not the witness!]
-You're not the one, sorry.
-Why are you mumbling it?
[Do Hyun mumbling the words,
because he doesn't know the song]
I did place first for 5 weeks in a row...
-Someone who acts suspicious...
-The person that's not looking at us...
That's right...
-What about...
-His eyebrows... Look at his brows...
[By any chance?]
Can you come here please?
-Hello.
-He really looks like it!
[A match to the sketching!]
It looks like we traced your face!
Set, go!
[Witness confirmed!]
[All this is thanks to the spot on sketching!]
Where did our target go?
-Your target is headed to KIST.
-KIST?
[Confirmed Ji Hyo's whereabouts]
-Let's get first place.
-But let's act like we're still searching.
[The Green Team still searching with
their faulty sketch]
[By any chance?]
[Right away with the pass code]
[Bolting out of the chair!]
[Seems like the witness...]
What are you doing?  Why are you doing that?
You're our witness, right?
Where do we need to go?
Some man told me to tell you to go to KIST.
-Ah... Go to KIST?
-Thank you.
-Goodbye...
-Thank you!
[Fugitive CSI]
[CSI chase team on her tail]
Detective Kim...
-You cannot trust anyone within Running Man.
-Really?
-There could be a spy within us.
-Seriously?
[A spy?]
[Busy enough chasing...
But a spy...within the group?]
This person's behavior is a little strange
with all the bread that he's eating.
I will tell you this now...
If I were the spy,
everyone can tell the moment I start.
When I lie...
When I lie, I blink excessively.
I have a habit of doing that.
I see that you're the same as me then.
I wonder how Bum Soo and Jong Shin are doing?
About what?  What?
[Why Bum Soo and Jong Shin all of a sudden?]
-I'm a little worried...
-Do Hyun...
[Could it be...?]
You just worry about yourself.
[Korea's Institute of Science and Technology,
KIST]
[The future of Korea's science...
This is today's final destination]
[Fugitive Ji Hyo's car finally arrives!]
[She has to approach the secret agent
inside here too...]
[Just what will happen to her here...]
[Hurrying to find the secret agent]
Hello, my name is Song Ji Hyo.
-Ah, yes...
-Hello.
I don't think he's the one...
Hello, my name is Song Ji Hyo.
Hello...
[Just exchanging greetings...
Who's the secret agent?]
Ah... He's not here.
Just... Who am I supposed to approach?
[Just then... The CSI chase teams!]
Until now... The fugitive's...
[The photo tips of
fugitive Ji Hyo is passed on]
It's Ji Hyo.
-The chef!
-That's our PD!
[All the places that stopped by today!
What's the secret of these photos?]
-Look at this...
-What the heck is this?
[A clue inside these pictures?]
Is that a cell phone?
[Discovering the similarities in all the photos
of her receiving something!]
Since it's in the case... Earrings?
A necklace? Ring? Watch?
You can see this bit here
that it's not any of those.
[It doesn't look like an accessory?]
[I see...]
This is the restaurant we were at.
Look at the owner.
[CSI agents entering the building
while looking at the photos]
-What is this about?
-There's a conclusive clue in the photos.
So I think we need to figure out these photos.
-What is this about?
-There's a conclusive clue in the photos.
The members are here.
[Fugitive Ji Hyo feeling the urgency]
By any chance...
Has Song Ji Hyo been by here?
-She already stopped by.
-When?
[The information pouring out since
there are so many eye witnesses]
[In big trouble if she's discovered!]
[Must be more careful approaching the agent!]
[The CSI agents
are spread all over the building!]
Excuse me... Have you seen Song Ji Hyo?
Just... Who am I supposed to approach?
[Where is the secret agent that
she's supposed to approach?]
Hello.  My name is Song Ji Hyo.
Yes, hello.
[Huh?  A robot?]
[Humanoid, Keebo coming to life]
Hi.  I'm Song Ji Hyo.
Ah.  Miss Chun Sung Im?
CSI-Chun Sung Im?
[It's the pass code!
Then this humanoid is the secret agent?]
CSI Chun Sung Im.
The gold that you have is fake.
[What... What???]
[Just... Just what does this mean?]
[The gold that I stole and brought
all this way is fake?]
[An hour before filming this morning]
[The 3 guests that are gathered!]
[Passing over the secret case]
From the beginning...
It's not like we're the 3 stooges...
[They were gathered to be given a secret order
but this is...]
[All of you are criminals]
[Infiltrate the CSI Investigative team,
and steal the real gold]
In a little bit... At the opening location,
today's gold prize will be showcased.
But actually, that gold is fake.
The real gold is hidden at a secret location.
Your ultimate goal is
to find that secret location
and take the gold for yourselves to share.
You should've done this last year.
The price of gold last year was better.
The price has dropped a lot.
Now... Call a member of the Running Man and
give the fake order to take the gold.
And without even knowing, that person is
going to close in on the real gold.
Your goal is to infiltrate Running Man and
pretend to go in on the chase.
So you're making up a fake criminal to find
the location of the real gold for you.
That person is to find it for us?
Fighting!
[So this is how the 3 real criminals...]
Hello?
-Hello?
-Who is this?
-Running Man Ace, Song Ji Hyo...
-Yes?
You will be given a special mission.
Yes.
Your mission is to steal today's
gold winning prizes.
If you're able to move the gold safely
to the final destination
then the gold is all for yours to take.
Running Man's gold thief, Song Ji Hyo!
Please do everything in your power
so that you may take the gold.
Ah yes... I understand.
[Ace Ji Hyo receiving an order
from the mystery man]
[Ace Ji Hyo rushing to steal the gold
without knowing they're fake]
[But she didn't know...]
[That she was just a pawn
for the real criminals...!]
[My...goodness!]
The gold that you have is fake.
The real gold is hidden inside
the final location.
The real gold is hidden somewhere within
KIST, the final location!
You can find out the location with the
items that you have garnered so far.
Sprinkle water on top of them.
[The final location will be known once
water is sprinkled on top of them?]
[The acrylic pans that she's gained from
all the secret agents she's approached]
[Sprinkle water on top of these?]
[Da... There's a letter!]
[Gu...!]
[Na!]
['Da' 'Gu' 'Na'... These are still...]
I'm sure there are more to this...
This was fake gold?
[I guess I was happy for nothing...]
Then I was happy about over nothing...
[Since it's already come to this...
I'll have to find the real gold!]
Is this silver?
I think it's metal.
I see something like metal...
Is this around anywhere?
[Ha Ha showing the picture around to find out
the nature of the items]
So where can I find something like this?
-I think this building would have the most.
-Have you been to the experiment area?
What...!  I went there and they all
pretended like they didn't know!
Thank you. Thank you for your cooperation.
Thank you for your cooperation.
If you ever want to skip time,
you just let me know.
Excuse me... Excuse me, sir.
[CSI team member Ha Ha,
finding his way to the experiment room]
Something like this...
[Other CSI team members are also
making their way to the place]
No matter how I look at it,
I think that's it.
This is it.  This is definitely it.
[Similarly colored and shaped
metal, and acrylic plates are everywhere]
-Hey!  Hey!
-Did you find it?
Yeah!  Come here.
[Gary seemed to have found something?]
[That's...?  The same box that Ji Hyo has!]
Yes!  This is it!  This is it!
[Ha Ha and Gary discovered the black plate!]
[Here too!  Giraffe discovers one!]
-Jae Suk!
-What?
This is it, isn't it?
[CSI team getting excited over
finding the thing from the pictures!]
Isn't this an acrylic plate?
[Your eyes will get crossed...]
Your eyebrows are really thick.
And look at your beard.
[Become eyebrows on top of the eyes,
and becomes a beard on the chin...]
[Will the CSI team members be able to solve
what the acrylic pans mean?]
-Let's split up.  Let's go around separately.
-No we can't split up.
We can't split up because
we have to combine our heads together.
-Ji Hyo could tear the name off our back.
-Hurry.  Come quickly.
[This is driving me crazy...
I can't do my criminal things!]
-Shouldn't we move a little quicker?
-Don't you think he's a little suspicious?
-Jong Shin?
[Constantly saying they should split up,
and wanting to go on his own...]
[Just a quick glance confirms he's suspicious]
Why do you keep going around
by yourself like that?
-Do you have something?
-You got something?
[Totally obvious that he's flustered]
You're acting suspicious.
-You're a spy, aren't you?
-You're a spy, right?
-I'm not a spy!
-I don't know anything.
-You're overtly pretending to be oblivious.
[Jong Shin being too obviously weird,
and receiving all the suspicion]
-I'm just overwhelmed...
-You sure you're not a spy?
[At this rate, rather than finding the gold,
he'd be the first one ousted!]
-Confess.
-If you're a spy, then confess already.
[Criminal Jong Shin...]
[Will he be able to remain alive
and find the real gold?]
[The real criminals that are getting busier]
Did you find something?
[Do Hyun and Bum Soo's secret conversation]
[A quick secret planning meeting without
the other agents knowing]
[The 3 need to meet quickly to discuss...]
Where's Jong Shin?
-Jong Shin can't come.
-Where is he?
Jong Shin is totally being suspected...
Oh!  Someone's coming.
We can't be sitting here like this.
We're in big trouble.
[CSI agent, Ha Ha approaching in the direction]
Escape, escape.
[The criminals parting ways in
such an obvious manner]
Hey...
What were you talking about with Do Hyun?
Do Hyun kept holding onto me
trying to tell me something.
Hey... You're not going to rip off my name
off my back later, right?
-No... That's definitely not it.
-Hey... You're acting a little suspicious.
Why are you being like this right now?
I don't know anything right now.
I don't even know where I'm going right now.
[Bum Soo is acting strange...]
[Criminal Bum Soo rushing to
get out of his spot]
[Is there something with the guests?]
[Jong Shin rushing in
from the back suddenly?!]
[Was running with Ha Ha's name tag in sight...]
[Dropping the pretense]
-What?  Did I scare you?
-Gary!  Hurry up here!  Come here!
[Acting weird again so being suspected again]
You're trying to rip my name off?  Wow...!
Hey!  What's wrong?
What's going on?
[You should've kept a low profile...
Jong Shin going around being suspected]
I was looking for Do Hyun...
And I scared him while playing a joke.
Gary... He's definitely a spy.
Without a doubt, he's a spy.
I'm not... Bye.
[Just too hilarious because just even by
plain looks, there's something suspicious]
[Awkward]
I'm letting you go this time and
just pretending not to notice anything.
That's just too funny.
[Poor Ace Ji Hyo tired from
running around for nothing]
[Criminal Jong Shin...]
Ji Hyo...
-Jong Shin...!
-I didn't rip it... I didn't touch it.
[It seems like criminal Jong Shin
sought out Ji Hyo on purpose]
[The criminals need to use Ji Hyo until
she leads them to the final destination]
Ji Hyo...
Because the guests today are a bit bumbly...
Right?  The guests are to help me, right?
[Disillusioned]
[Ji Hyo not yet knowing the purpose
and the identity of the real criminals]
[She doesn't know anything yet...]
[I'll have to pretend to help her until
she finds out where the location is]
We almost got found out too just now.
I failed trying to tear Ha Ha's name off.
Ha Ha...has it.
Ha Ha has it?
I have to have that.
[Ji Hyo not even knowing in her wildest dreams
that the real criminals are the guests]
Who else has it?
[The criminals need to use her to the end...]
Who will the ultimate victor be?
Cloud cafe... Come there.
Cloud cafe... I got Do Hyun!
[Bum Soo's exclamation that he's got Do Hyun?]
-Do Hyun is caught?
-I didn't get Do Hyun.
-I heard that he's caught.
-Who said that?
Just now... Bum Soo.
[The criminals acting after being suspected!]
No matter what, be confident about it.
I'll go in like this.
Ha Ha!  I got Do Hyun!
I caught Do Hyun!
Don't be too eager about it.
If you're too eager, then you'll be suspected.
Tell him to come to that place earlier.
Coming, they're coming.
[Smoke acting]
[Did Bum Soo really catch him?]
[Since they're still suspecting him,
they're hiding for now]
-There he is.
-Oh, Ha Ha!
See?  I caught him!
[Even though he's saying he caught him...
That loosely?]
He and I are actually on the same team today.
-What are you talking about?
-We're actually on the same team.
What does that mean?
We're originally on the same team,
but he caught me like this.
[Why is criminal Do Hyun confessing
all of a sudden?]
[The criminals confessing that
they're on the same team?]
We received those orders.
To prove that I'm your friend...
Just what does that mean?!
You told me to rip off his name...
-But I can't rip it off myself.
-You just have to tear it off.
[Even they're getting their own words twisted]
Then you're saying that you were
originally put on the same team?
Yeah we did.  We're the real criminals.
You're not supposed to be telling me that!
-You're not supposed to be saying that...
-My name is going to get torn off anyways...
-Then what becomes of him?
-He's saying he's not going to do it anymore.
-He's basically betraying me.
-It's because I'm your friend!
Are you playing around right now?
I'm doing this because you think
of me as your friend...
[There's even a worse spy out there than me]
We just need to be friends.
[Bum Soo arguing that he'll give up being
a spy to remain his friend]
Just what the heck is this...?
I caught him!
Bum Soo... You're just too funny,
and Do Hyun is too funny too...
[The worst plan ever...
What are they going to do with that?]
-Are you strong?  You twisted my arm earlier.
-I totally twisted his arm earlier.
I caught him...
Then when I say 1, 2, 3,
rip off Ha Ha's.  1, 2, 3!
What the heck!  Gary!
What the heck? What the heck?
[With Bum Soo falling down,
it's Do Hyun in danger]
Hey!  Kim Bum Soo!  You stupid!
[Deception operation failed.
The 3 criminals now a real active target!]
[Running Man's worst plan ever?]
That stupid...!
He should've torn it off right away!
[Criminal Yoon Do Hyun-Out!]
Yoon Do Hyun, out.
Bum Soo!
[Bum Soo escapes to the basement that
Jong Shin's been hiding in]
I've totally been found out.
[An irreversible situation from
their botched plan]
[All the CSI agents out to get the criminals]
All of them are so quick to notice things.
-They're all experts and we're...
-It's not that we're quick...
Our members are quick in a way...
But we're not good either?
I don't know why the heavens...
You have to protect us.
It's really a miracle that I got out of there.
Look at how I'm sweating right now.
They were breathing down my neck!
First...
Isn't that Ji Hyo?
-That looks like Ji Hyo...
-The one with the bag looks like her...
-Ji Hyo!  Come here!  I have something for you!
-Ji Hyo!  Come here!
-Ji Hyo!  I have something to tell you.
-I have something for you!
-Where did she go?
-It's not her... I thought it was Ji Hyo.
Didn't it look like Ji Hyo?
I totally thought it was her.
[Everyone looks like Ji Hyo because
they've been searching for her all day]
[Jae Suk and Kwang Soo discover Ji Hyo!]
Ji Hyo...
Where have you been?
What are you searching for?
What are you searching for so hard?
This is really hard.
-Ji Hyo...
-What are you searching for, Ji Hyo?
Let's meet up and talk.
We've been searching for you all day.
Ji Hyo...
Then let's meet up one on one.
I'm not going to meet up with both of you.
You're searching for these, right?
Yes.
-Why are you looking for these?
-I have those too though.
I have one and Jae Suk has one.
I don't have just one...
-So there are several?
-Of course.
In that case...
That's why... That's why I have no desire
to meet up with both of you.
Kwang Soo, come down here.
Come down here and let's talk.
Ji Hyo... How about this?
-Let the 3 of us become a team.
-No, I don't want to.
-Can't the 3 of us do it together?
-I don't want to.
-Why?
-I can't trust you and Kwang Soo.
Seriously... If you're going to say that,
then you're the one we can't trust!
-Then you're not going to meet up, right?
-I'll meet you.
-I'll go see the other teams then.
-I'm coming.
Why are you talking so rashly?
-I'll apologize to you in his place.
-Come down quickly.  Come on.
Kwang Soo... You're saying you're going down?
But look at the situation...
[Ji Hyo asking to meet one person at a time...
What are her intentions?]
Ji Hyo...
Ji Hyo...!
I came alone.
-I have it here.
-I have mine here too.
What have you decided to do with them?
I thought that we should meet with you first.
[But Ji Hyo is the only one who knows
the secret behind the acrylic plates...]
-I don't know...
-Ha Ha has one too.
Really?
-I see...
-In that case...
Let's exchange them.
[Since she knows what's written on her plates
she's trying to earn other people's...]
I'll show you the 3 I have for you to choose.
-You can just give me whichever.
-No, I can't.
[But why is she slowly inching backwards
into the room?]
[Where do you keep going off to?]
[Criminal's ambush!]
[Ji Hyo lured him in!]
[They're not criminals...
They're more like zombies!]
[2 criminals attacking Kwang Soo!]
[What!  Both at the same time!]
[Criminal Kim Bum Soo and
CSI agent, Kwang Soo out at the same time!]
What happens now then?
Lee Kwang Soo, Kim Bum Soo-Out.
-Kim Bum Soo...
-Kim Bum Soo, out...
[A relief for now that
one of the criminals has been ousted]
[The problem is, the criminal is a criminal...]
[But to get the real gold,
you have to oust your own team members]
I think you were just eyeing my back.
[Jae Suk has lost all his team members]
[The perfect scenario for Ha Ha and Gary]
-This is perfect being on the staircase.
-This is 2 against 1 again.
[Even though they can catch all the criminals,
real validity comes from ousting other teams]
This is 2 against 1...
[Blocking his escape]
[The 2 kids slowly eyeing the victory]
Two against one like this again...
Like when Kim Hee Sun was here...
There are a lot of things that I've been
harboring feelings against you about...
[The 2 kids with a lot of grudges against him
during last week's 100th episode special]
[Huh?  Ji Hyo?]
[Is she to save Jae Suk?]
Hurry.  Aren't you going to oust Jae Suk?
-What are you doing?
-Aren't you going to oust Jae Suk?
-Then rip it off, Ji Hyo.
Jong Kook!!  Why are you picking on me?
[Ousting Jae Suk a success!]
[Jae Suk-Out!]
Yoo Jae Suk, out.
Earlier... Earlier...
I should've ripped it off.
[Now the biggest enemy is the Blue Team]
Ji Hyo... We really have to know.
[Sharing the plates they each have]
I'll give it back after taking a look.
[You don't even know what you're doing]
I know this is of some value to you.
[Ha Ha wanting to know the meaning
of the plates]
That's what I want to know.
If you solve the riddle of these plates,
you'll know where the real gold is at.
[Huh?  Faintly...]
[Hey... Take a look at this...]
[I got it]
[I have to check the other plates quickly]
I think I kind of know.
It's a secret.
[Gary's found out
the secret about the plates?]
[In that case...]
If I knew the location...
[Where is Ji Hyo going all of a sudden?]
-I think I got it...
-Why did she leave this behind?
Hey, where are you going Ji Hyo?
[She's not leaving... Shutting the door?]
What are you doing?
Hurry up and come out,
so we can tear them off.
-What the heck?  What's going on?
-Hurry up and come out.
[Someone else is in the room?!]
[Just who is the cohort that
Ji Hyo's joined hands with?]
[Could it be Jong Kook?]
[Jong Shin!!]
[Zero shock]
You want to fight?
You're going to use him to fight us?
-I'm speechless...
-You're supposed to be scared when you see...
I thought it was going to be Jong Kook.
I got you.
[He's the one to get scared himself]
You can't even tear that off?
[Anyways, 2:2... An even score]
-Fine, let's do this...
-He's doing it like in the movies.
[Weakling Jong Shin using useless tactics]
-Let's get out of here and do this.
-Okay.
Let's take this outside.
This is...
[Just then!]
[Ha Ha slyly taking Ji Hyo's plates]
[Ace Ji Hyo, not noticing anything]
But the thing I'm curious about is...
Even in this situation, the first person
to arrive at the location is the winner?
[Really??]
[Ha Ha flashing out of the room!]
You didn't take my things, right?
[Gary and Ha Ha, with all their stolen plates]
[Ji Hyo's acrylic plates have vanished!]
[Realizing that it's related to water,
Gary heads to the bathroom!]
I can see it clearly.
['Reum']
Jong Kook!  Jong Kook!
Ha Ha has all 4 acrylic plates!
He even has all of mine right now!
'Ri'.  It says 'Ri'.
And this one says 'Mu'!
I can see them all so clearly!
Cloud bridge?
-There's a cloud bridge!
-There was that cloud bridge cafe earlier!
-I had 4 but he took them all.
-So where are they now?
-The final location!
-They went to the final location.
-The gold that I have is fake.
-They're fake gold?!
That's right!!
[We're ruined...
Those guys are going to take the real gold?!]
What about this?
Should we try shouting out the words?
-Cloud bridge...
-Cloud bridge...!
[Why not just yell out 'Open sesame?']
Hey!  Ha Ha!
We have to do it quickly...
Why is this split like this?
[The wooden door!
Is this what 'Cloud bridge wooden door' means?]
This is opening!
[It opens!]
[Will the real gold be behind this door?]
What is this?
Is this a treasure chest?
[A gold safe!]
Come, come!
[My gold!]
[It's my gold!]
-Open, open...
-Hurry.  1, 2, 3!
[At last... The real gold is discovered!]
[Blue team, Gary and Ha Ha
are the ultimate victors!]
[Thrilling emotion]
[Coming in late after seeing the open door]
-What?  What?
-Are you crazy?
Why did you take my things?
How can you be so low to steal
them from me like that?
-What's your deal?
-I don't know anything even to the end.
[Pretending not to be the criminal
even to the end]
Let me check.
Are you a criminal or what?
He is a criminal!
You're a criminal
and you denied it to the end.
[The 3 criminals sending Ji Hyo on
the hunt to find the real gold for them]
I told you that you were a criminal.
I knew it from the beginning.
What the heck happened today?
These 3 are the criminals?
They really are something...
They're the worst!
-I now know Running Man.
-Know what?
It's a good program.
[Even though they may be off kilter,
thanking the 3 guests who gave their best]
[And...]
Hello?
You failed?
You're seriously saying that the gold
went into Gary and Ha Ha's hands?
This is very disappointing.
I don't even want to look at you...
So just keep your back turned
for the time being.
I guess I'm going to have to step in.
[Next week's Running Man...
The new chase begins...]
Subtitles by DramaFever