Guest mission.
[The last guest of 2012.
Hallyu Goddess, Choi Ji Woo.]
You are a spy.
Oust all members of Running Man.
[A spy more glamorous than any other.]
[But there is one bit of truth
that she isn't aware of!]
[Running Man's mission.
Deceive Choi Ji Woo!]
[Between the truth and lies.
Most secretive plan yet, starts now!]
[Choi Ji Woo vs. Running Man.]
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Closing on end of 2012.]
[Busan's Maritime Museum]
[This is Running Man's
New Year's Eve Party location.]
[Shining guests of honor on
the red carpet.]
This is our New Year's Eve party.
- What is it?
- There are eight settings!
- Two, four, six, eight...
- We have a guest?
- Do we have a guest?
- Let's all lift up our glasses.
[Starting off with a toast.]
- Cheers to the world.
- Everybody!
- Cheers!
- Thanks to all for your hard work.
- Happy new year, everyone!
- Here's to everyone's health!
[Thanks for everyone's hard work,
and for all your running this past year.]
[Mm... grape juice.]
[New Year's Eve in Busan.]
[In the place where they filmed a show
with all their big brothers.]
This is our final show for the year 2012.
[2012's final show filming.]
We have a great guest here today for
our New Year's Eve show.
[The ultimate guest for
the New Year's Eve show?]
- Is that car headed here?
- Is that a limousine?
[Limousine?]
- Here it comes, here it comes!
- It's headed this way!
- It's a limousine!
- Is it headed this way?
[A full size limousine headed their way.]
- It's coming this way!
- Who could be in there?
Whoever it is,
they're coming here on a train.
[A powerful entrance.]
Gary, go open the door and
see who it is.
[Today's top guest is...]
You startled me!
[The ultimate Hallyu Goddess,
Choi Ji Woo.]
[Heart beating wildly in surprise.]
It's Choi Ji Woo!
- Hello!
- You look so beautiful!
[An actress truly befitting
of the red carpet.]
Choi Ji Woo!
What are you doing here?
- What brings you here?
- Wow...
- I can't believe you're here!
- Hello.
[Happily greeting everyone first.]
- I can't believe she's here!
Look at how tall she is!
- Are you naturally that tall?
- Yes.
[So... tall.]
I thought you were going up
to kiss her.
I feel like we're at a
film festival with Choi Ji Woo here.
- Our guest is so beautiful!
- Our guest truly is beautiful.
But isn't your back a little cold?
- I'm a little concerned about your back.
- Can we help you with that at all?
[Afraid of her back getting cold
with the low cut dress?]
- What? Why are you guys yelling?
- Ji Hyo... just cover up Ji Hyo instead!
- I was going to cover her up with this.
- No, it's okay. I'm fine.
[Elegantly refusing with both hands.]
This means, never.
She's adamantly refusing with both hands.
- Do you not like us?
- No! No, it's not like that.
Today... with our
top rate Hallyu star, Choi Ji Woo...
and with the rest of our average rate
Hallyu stars, Running Man members...
Come on, you didn't have to
put it that way.
With it being the end of the year...
we're doing a special New Year's Eve show,
called 'The battle of the stars'.
All eight of you will be going around together
and performing these missions individually.
And to the person that wins the round,
that individual will receive a star.
And the first person to end up with all
seven stars at the final location
will be the ultimate winner.
[However...]
[There's something suspicious about
the glint in Ji Woo's eyes.]
[An hour before
Running Man's New Year's Eve party.]
[Oh? Ji Woo?]
[What is Ji Woo doing here?]
- Welcome to Running Man.
- Hello.
By any chance, have you
ever watched Running Man before?
Yes, I'm a fan of the show.
We usually ask to meet in a setting like this
if there's a special mission to be given...
No! I don't like anything
special like that!
I just...
So this is what it feels like.
Don't walk. Run.
Guest's mission.
One vs. seven...
[One vs. Seven?]
[The battle against the Running Man.
You are a spy.]
[And one of the Running Man members
is the spy's partner.]
[Find your partner and
oust all the other members.]
[If you oust everyone without
getting caught to the end, the spy...]
One against seven?
- And you have to oust everyone.
- How am I going to do that?
How am I going to oust Mr. Capable
and everyone else?
If you somehow end up getting caught
for being the spy...
- Then the show's going to stop recording?
- Yes, then this show will stop recording.
- Then this show ends immediately?
- Yes, it'll end immediately.
It's going to end right away
when I came all the way here?
[And that's her secret mission which was
handed to her before the show started.]
A grand prize is waiting for the winner
with it being the end of the year.
We understand.
You are all going to get on Busan's city
tour bus to move to your next location.
- Wow!
- The tour bus?
Please change your clothes,
and gather in front of the bus.
Wow... we're going to do the show with
Choi Ji Woo today!
Ji Woo's been on variety show's before,
so you can see how she knows to fist pump.
- Look at her fist pump.
- Why don't you say something?
Choi Ji Woo, why don't
you show us how it's done again?
[Her reaction that they'd all
like to see one more time.]
Come on, Ji Woo.
Why don't you do it again?
- Let's go!
- Yeah!
[Spy Ji Woo...
Will she accomplish her secret mission?]
[However...]
[Earlier, when Ji Woo was
making her entrance...]
- Is it an actress?
- If it's an actress, I bet she's top rate.
- But all of us are here...
- Let's all commit to this.
[Their conversation is a bit suspicious?]
[What? They already know?]
[They were all... watching her?]
[All the Running Man members were
watching and listening... in that case?]
The glint in her eyes right now...
she's totally committed to this.
- She's totally into this right now.
- You know that expression, don't you?
The glint in her eyes right now...
she's totally into this right now.
How am I going to oust Mr. Capable
and everyone else?
She's asking how she's going to oust
Mr. Capable.
This says that I have a partner.
Does it mean it's one of those seven?
As you've all just heard, her mission is to
find her partner to oust everyone else.
As for the spy's partner...
The way I see it, I think we
need to determine who that'll be.
[It seems to be the wiser choice
to choose who that should be?]
- How about Gary?
- Me?
[Not such a good idea?]
[Whenever he's given a special role,
his expressions always gives him away.]
In my personal opinion, the ones Ji Woo
will feel most relieved about
and feel reassured having as her partner while
being the spy would be the two of you.
Either Ha Ha or Jong Kook.
One of those two would be best.
- Ha Ha's usually good with the female guests.
- We're best at reassuring the female guests.
It's because you're always
scheming something.
Okay then, leave it to me.
[Female guest specialist?
Haroro chosen as the partner.]
[Choi Ji Woo vs. Running Man.]
[Deceive one another.
Just who will be today's ultimate victor?]
Is that it?
[Today's mode of transportation,
City tour bus.]
That's going to be freezing!
[We're not going to be on the top level
in this weather, are we?]
It's the middle of winter!
It's just a relief that Ji Woo isn't
going to be riding this in her dress.
[Just a relief Ji Woo won't be riding
the bus in her dress?]
- Hello.
Let's go!
[To the heart of Busan.]
- It's totally freezing up here!
- It's so cold!
[Getting slapped in the face by
the frigid winter air.]
The drama you did, 'Winter Sonata'...
Didn't your character meet her love
for the first time on the bus?
- Yes, you're right.
- You did, right?
[The lead characters on 'Winter Sonata'
had their first meeting on the bus...]
- That's right! We know all about it.
- We all remembered.
And your face hasn't
changed a bit since then!
[Really?]
Is it okay for me to treat you
like my little sister?
[Look at him acting like a fool...]
He asks if he can treat her
like his little sister...
- Let's just speak comfortably to each other!
- Yes, let's just do that.
- You can lower your speech to me first.
- Okay, I will.
- Really?
- Yeah, let's.
- Ji Woo!
- What is it?
I got the ball rolling!
I can't do it. I'm too big of a fan.
Ji Woo... I can call you that, right?
Yes, Suk Jin.
Hey! You guys always just sit together
so naturally now, don't you?
It's Monday today,
so what choice do we have?
Then does Monday's mean that we're on?
Should I be logging back in?
[Monday Couple, we welcome you.
Please log in or out.]
[Forgetting about the cold
in the midst of all their laughter.]
[Arriving at the mission location.]
There it is.
[No matter what happens,
this is where the first star will be given.]
[Busan City Tour - Songdo Beach.]
- Everyone, off the bus!
- I don't want to get off!
Why are you asking us to get off?
[The ultimate beach in Korea,
Busan Songdo Beach]
Next year will be its' 100th year anniversary
since it opened to the public.
Okay, this will be the first game to
'The Battle of the Stars' mission.
We have a three course relay
that we have prepared for you.
You have to pass through the tire course
behind you and roll down the balance beams.
And once you pass through the line,
you win the race.
The race will be a one-on-one
tournament.
Choi Ji Woo looks so worried...
[Somehow needs to win the race to get
the star... what to do...]
- The Tiger against the Giraffe!
- Fighting!
[First round, Jong Kook vs. Kwang Soo.]
[In order for me to get the star...]
[I need Mr. Capable to lose...]
We're really going to have to win this
if we want the star, don't we?
Coming in second would be the same
as coming in last.
We need to get the star.
[They need to make sure to behave
so that Ji Woo doesn't get suspicious.]
[Huh? Why isn't he going through this one?]
[The Giraffe is always asking for trouble.]
[Using force to make him move over.]
I don't want to go in there!
[With his monstrous strength,
he forces the Giraffe inside the tire tubes.]
I can't believe he forced him in there.
[Huh?]
Get out!
I hope you die of old age in there!
[Their teamwork causing some concern...]
[Now off to the balance beams
for the second leg of the course.]
Pants, your pants!
My button fell off!
[It seems as though it fell off while
he was forcibly dragged over to his side.]
My button fell off!
- What do I do about this?
- Just hurry up!
- Just take them off!
- Hurry up!
Yours is that one!
[Must do two flips to pass.]
[His pants...]
[Welcome to hell...
Being forced in the water.]
[Now just need to pass through the loop.]
[What? Around the Tiger's neck?]
[The Tiger's ultimate revenge.]
[Kkuk is in the process of
passing through the loop already.]
[Running close to the finish line first?]
Your pants!
[They're falling...]
[Pants falling down automatically...]
- Are you crazy?
- You have to pull them up!
Kwang Soo won.
- I can't fit through this at all!
- Kwang Soo won.
[Um... if he runs like that...]
[Kwang Soo wins...]
You really are a piece of work.
[A battered victory.]
[The curse of his wide shoulders.]
I can't I believe I lost to Kwang Soo.
What are you going to do later
if you don't have your pants on?
[People that look like Kwang Soo
has no sense of shame?]
[On top of that,
quite a crowd is watching...]
Seriously though, Ji Hyo...
I'm going to win.
[Ha Ha wins the race against Gary.]
- You're at a disadvantage. You may not pass.
- Even so, I'll still be faster than her.
Ready...
[Jae Suk and Blank Ji's fierce competition.]
[Blank Ji may actually be faster?]
[Flip over twice on top of the
balance beam.]
[You dare get in my way?]
[Blank Ji's power!]
[Bending his leg over to
force him down.]
That's just a basic move on
the show now.
[Jae Suk coming back for more
of Blank Ji's power!]
[Again?]
[Another flip onto the ground.]
Song Ji Hyo... it's only because where you're
standing is higher up than where I am.
[Neck to neck competition.]
[Off to the ocean for the final leg.]
Ah! That's so cold!
[On the other hand, Blank Ji
goes in without any hesitation.]
[Nice going...]
[Waist deep...]
[Passing through with ease.]
You're almost there!
- Hurry up and put your shoes back on!
- Great job!
[Song Ji Hyo!]
- Ji Woo, you've gotten awfully quiet.
-  No, I'm not.
Song Ji Hyo,
you're really good at the leg flips.
Leg flips are my specialty.
[The final race.
Ji Woo vs. Suk Jin.]
She's not letting him go easily.
He's not giving her any breaks.
[Passes through the tire tunnel
at an amazing speed.]
What is she doing?
[Don't you dare come out!]
[What?]
[Is she trying to pull the tire out?]
Go in... get back in there.
[Merciless Big-nosed Brother.]
Wow, Suk Jin... he really is something.
She's not fooling around!
[I'm going to make sure to
get my star!]
[I know that you're doing all that
to get your star...]
[Now for the two flips...]
How do you do this?
Ji Woo, what are you doing?
- I'll flip you over.
- Suk Jin, I'm scared.
You have to be careful!
[What got into the Big-nosed Brother
to be so helpful?]
[Figured as much...]
Why don't you help her out to the end?
[Trying to take the loop away
from her...]
Ji Woo, hurry!
[Passing through the loop
at lightning speed!]
[Passes through successfully!]
[Wow! Ji Woo succeeds!]
- Will you be able to do it like that?
- I'm fine. Everything's covered.
[They need to get started on the race
between Ji Woo and the Giraffe...]
- I'm okay, seriously.
- He can go to the playoff level.
- You think you can do it?
- You're moving up due to your lack of dress.
[He's going to keep playing like that?]
- How are you going to play games like that?
- What's going on right now?
[Thing that's been prepared for him
in this case of emergency is...]
Okay, just play then. Play.
What the heck is that?
[Unbelievable.
Using a bathrobe as pants...]
Hey, they're like baggy pants.
[Bathrobe have now been transformed
into a pair of baggy pants.]
Why did you have to ruin my pants?
They totally are a pair of baggy pants.
I can't play against him!
[Finished with the preparations?]
- He can do it. He can totally do it.
- They're just like baggy pants.
He's like a fashionista.
- Whenever Kwang Soo's  like this...
- Ji Woo!
Ready... set...
[Ji Woo in a rush to win the star.]
Why are you so slow?
They haven't said start yet.
Why are you trying to go to my side?
I have noticed that beautiful women
tend to get annoyed easily and pout.
I have noticed that in all the
beautiful women.
Ready... set... go!
[As guessed,
showing his tendency to cheat.]
Sorry. You were just going where
I was headed!
[Baggy pants boy entering the
tunnel of tires.]
From the back,
Kwang Soo looks like a roasted chicken.
[Baggy roasted chicken
almost out of the tire tunnel.]
- Your pants!
- Put your pants on!
[Baggy pants reformed into
a pair of loose pants.]
- Put your pants on!
- Kwang Soo, put your pants on!
- Hold onto them if they keep falling.
- Ji Woo, get up to the side!
[Showing surprising skills when
it comes to her body gags.]
- Ji Woo, your physical gags are the best!
- They're awesome!
Ji Woo! You can win this!
[Succeeds with the two flips!]
Choi Ji Woo, you're the best!
[Oh no... the Giraffe...]
[The giraffe show.]
[The pants once again pull a
disappearance act.]
[A fierce battle in the water.]
- Kwang Soo, just give up!
- Just put your pants back on!
Kwang Soo,
just go grab the other one!
My neck already went through the loop!
[Ji Woo having taken over the loop.]
[Passing through it in a flash.]
[She's good.]
[Wow! Ji Woo moves up to
the playoffs!]
- She's not looking so good though.
- One pass through the race, and she's done.
[Heroine of tragic love stories
falling down in exhaustion.]
Ji Woo, are you okay?
You have to play in the final round.
Choi Ji Woo, come on!
I have to do it again?
- Against who?
- Me. Me!
I don't want to!
This is for the win!
[Final Round - Ha Ha vs. Ji Woo.]
The winner of this round wins the star.
[The so desired star hangs on
this one race!]
For each game played,
a star will be given to the winner.
Once you get to the final location
with the stars
you'll be given a hint about
your partner.
[A hint regarding the identity of
her partner will be gained!]
She has to gather the stars and
get to the final location.
- Stars?
- Yes.
[All the members of Running Man who
are already aware of the truth.]
[No matter, they have to stop Ji Woo
from getting the stars.]
- The star is mine!
- The star belongs to Choi Ji Woo!
-Ready!
- Fair play, okay?
[Asking for fair play before
the start of the game?]
Set...
Set... go!
[A race where the star hangs on
the balance - Start!]
[Engaging in fierce physical battles
right from the get go.]
[Breaking out the leg flips?]
[And there she goes.]
[Ro-Ro trying to realize his goal
by resorting to his leg flip moves.]
[Where do you think you're going?]
[Oops! My leg is too short.]
- His leg...
- His leg is too short!
[Finding the leg flip too difficult
with the difference of their height.]
- Ji Woo, you have to go through it too.
- Just go through the other one.
Ji Woo really is putting
a lot of effort into it.
[Oh my... more physical gags.]
- Look at her... she's a total airhead!
- Are you getting stuck?
Ji Woo's a total airhead!
[Cruel Ro-Ro...]
He's so cruel!
It has to be somewhat of a competition
for the game to be any fun.
[Oh? Lending out a helping hand?]
[Figures.]
[Pulling the leg flip on her
once more.]
I will be the victor!
Ji Woo!
What if she doesn't do the flips?
[Fine...]
[Ro-Ro in the process of making
the pass through the loop.]
Don't come! Don't come near me!
[The ultimate ending...]
- Come here.
- Why?
Come here!
[Retreating backwards.]
- Here, pull this up.
- Why? Why should I do that?
[Pull off the loop that he's already
passed through halfway?]
- Why are you pulling this off!
- Hang on a minute...
What do I do...
what should I do now?
Go Eun!
Ji Woo keeps putting her
arms around me!
[Trips him over with her leg.]
No!
[The music indicating that ultimately,
they will end up running.]
[In the end, they will end up running...]
[Desperate Ji Woo.]
What are you doing?
[Ro-Ro ultimately succeeds at
passing through the loop.]
What are you guys doing?
Let me go, Ji Woo!
How in the world are you this strong?
Let go of me!
[She's almost through the loop?]
[I don't think so!]
[Ro-Ro stretching out his arm
past the finish line.]
[Ro-Ro wins]
- Why did you have to go that far?
- You should've been more gentle with her.
- She's a Hallyu star, after all.
- Is the star that important to you?
[Good job...]
[You didn't give any indication,
and that sounded good.]
[This is my specialty.]
[In the end, Ha Ha wins the star.]
I won!
- Good for you.
- I trampled Choi Ji Woo!
- Look at how happy is to have beat her.
- Seriously...
- Here is your star.
- Can't we share it?
- Can we share it? Let's share it.
- What's the big deal about that star?
- That star, seriously...
- The star truly does belong to Ha Ha.
[Choi Ji Woo vs. Running Man.]
- Ji Woo... hey, I can't believe...
- I almost lost to her though.
She was working so hard at it.
I thought she was just going to give
half the effort she did and quit.
I'm so jealous of people that can pull off
physical gags without trying.
Kwang Soo...
seriously, he's unbeatable with that.
- Are you okay?
- You can lower your speech with me.
Okay, Kwang Soo.
Stop acting so bashful.
I've watched the show in the past.
- I noticed you do that with all the ladies.
- No, I don't.
[Ji Woo's spot-on monitoring.]
Kwang Soo likes actresses.
[Is Ji Woo the perfect woman who embodies
everything Kwang Soo wants in a woman?]
You have everything he's looking for.
An older woman who's also an actress.
This is why I can't date anyone.
[You don't? Or you can't?]
By the way, you're ugly.
Don't you think that he's
being too harsh?
Kwang Soo... being ugly
is actually kind of a trend lately.
That's right. That's nothing
to feel bad about right now.
- It's not a trend!
- It's a trend, Gary.
Ji Woo, which one of us
do you think is best looking?
- Out of you guys?
- Not counting the popularity.
Ji Woo, don't feel bad about it, and
tell us who the best and worst looking is.
Should I tell you in the order of
best to worst looking?
- Yeah, start with best looking. Who's first?
- Starting with best looking?
First place would be...
- I pick Jong Kook.
- Thank you!
- Okay, then how about second?
- Second?
- I don't even care about the first place.
- You can't count the age either.
- Then Ji Suk Jin would be second.
- That's just absurd!
Come on, Ji Woo!
You know that's not right!
- Maybe she's just trying to be funny.
- I just look weirder on screen, that's all.
- Okay, it's been funny so far.
- I see that you have a funny side to you.
Then you want me to tell you the third?
Ha Ha!
[Third place is, Ha Ha.]
Ji Woo!
[The lower rank people
desperately calling out Ji Woo's name.]
Starting with fourth,
you guys are all pretty much the same.
[Calling fourth through sixth a tie.]
Ji Woo!
Gary! Why aren't you even
saying anything?
It's the same thing I hear
all the time!
- Kwang Soo, seriously...
- I don't know how I feel about this.
You know what this means, right?
You're in seventh place.
[Then he's voted to be the least attractive
out of all the Running Man members?]
- She says that you're not that attractive.
- I used to be really popular.
I know that you're popular.
I've heard people saying that
you're attractive before.
Really? Where? Where?
- Don't you think you're being too much?
- Wait, calm down.
- Don't you think you're all being too much?
- This is great comedy!
Ji Woo... I really
didn't take you to be like that.
- Wow, this is great. You're hilarious.
- It's getting hot in here.
[Climbing up the steep road...]
[All the beautiful and
colorful homes everywhere.]
[A village reminiscent of the colors
in traditional hanboks.]
- Doesn't it have a certain feel to it?
- It's so beautiful.
Thank you for all your hard
work to get here.
[Busan's Gamcheon Cultural Village]
This place is so beautiful.
I never knew such beautiful place
existed in Busan.
- It's just so beautiful!
- It looks like a European village.
This place makes me think
of Santorini in Greece.
This place is referred to as
Santorini of Busan.
I was thinking this place
looked like Santorini.
Is there anything you don't know?
I'm getting the same feeling I did
when I was in Montpellier in Europe.
What did you say?
You're thirsty?
[In this beautiful village...]
[Battle of the Stars - Second mission.]
We have prepared something special for
you guys to wish you luck in year 2013.
- This is 'The Amazing Quiz'.
- Amazing Quiz?
You know that we're not good
at quizzes.
The category of the quiz is,
Choi Ji Woo.
What the heck does that mean?
[Is everyone ready?]
[Second mission - Choi Ji Woo Quiz.]
[Everyone was already aware of it...]
- So we're already going to know what it is?
- We'll be prepared for the mission.
You just need to make sure that
Choi Ji Woo comes in last in the mission.
If we know the answers to difficult questions,
I bet that will really fluster her.
These questions are going to be
simple for Choi Ji Woo.
- And I'm sure you can see that for yourself.
- Yes, you're right.
- But you will... already know the answers.
- We'll already know the answers, right?
The first thing Choi Ji Woo says to
Bae Yong Joon on the bus in 'Winter Sonata'?
'Just what were you doing
not waking me up?'
I don't know if I can be natural
when I say things like this.
Who's the writer that wrote the drama
that became really popular in Japan in 2006?
Watanabi Muziki!
[Who?]
[I bet she'll be flustered...]
But if we're too good with the answers,
I bet she'll get suspicious.
Don't you think she'll get suspicious
if we answer too many questions right?
- She may not know some of these herself.
- We have to act dumb on some of these too.
- She may not know all of them herself.
- We have to act like we're stumped too.
[Will they be able to pull it off?]
But wouldn't that put Ji Woo at too much
of an advantage if they're all about her?
[Ji Woo feeling energized knowing
that the questions are about herself.]
Listen carefully to the questions
and you have to break these bowls
on your head and shout out 'This is awesome'.
[Break it on your head,
and shout out 'This is awesome!']
And to those that pass the quiz,
a running ball will be given to them.
- Running ball?
- Instead of a star?
First place will be given
seven running balls.
Second place will receive six,
and the fifth place will receive five.
And the person who comes in last
won't receive any.
Then all the balls will be put in a drawing,
and one will be chosen at random.
Is that why you're giving us the stars?
Wow, you're not making it easy for us
to get those stars.
I really do know quite a bit about
Ji Woo personally, though.
- I know quite a bit too.
- I think I know a good bit too.
- Since she's been in so many projects...
- I know more than you'd think too.
There could be things that we know
about her that she may not know herself.
[We're going to knock her socks off...]
Since she's just so famous to begin with,
we can't help but know a few things about her.
- I even know what your first commercial was.
- What was it?
I can't tell you that right now.
It could end up being one of the questions.
Okay, here comes your first question.
In the drama...
Beautiful days...
Where did Lee Byung Hyun and
Choi Ji Woo share their first kiss?
[Where did Lee Byung Hyun and Choi Ji Woo
share their first kiss in 'Beautiful Days'?]
[It seems as though Ji Woo
also knows the answer?]
- I know this!
- No!
[Fortunately, Jae Suk is first to arrive.]
[He needs to remember the answer...]
Who in the world doesn't know
the answer to that question?
Who wouldn't know the answer to that?
I saw this!
I saw that drama!
- Beautiful days... I know I saw it.
- You know the answer, don't you?
- Choi Ji Woo, it was...
- I'm just a little unsure...
This is pretty tough.
[Will he be able to remember correctly?]
You can answer the question
once you break the bowl on your head.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah, I'm okay.
That really startled me.
[And the correct answer is...]
- You have to get it right.
- I'm a little confused with the scene.
[Does he know? Does he know?]
[He remembers, doesn't he?]
[Answer: Inside a car by the ocean.]
Inside a car by the ocean!
- No, he's wrong.
- Inside a car by the ocean!
No, he's wrong.
[What? It's not?]
It's not?
- No, it's not. It was at the other place
- Wrong. He's wrong.
[Then was the answer on the
sheet wrong?]
- That's not the place.
- Then where was it?
Where did it take place?
[Let's verify.]
[Main leads of 'Beautiful Days', Ji Woo
and Lee Byung Hyun's first kiss scene.]
[Whew! Inside a car by the ocean
is the correct answer!]
- No, it's not.
- Then where? Where was it?
I'm sure she's right.
[Inside the car by the ocean
is the correct answer!]
[That was the right answer?]
Which scene are you talking about?
That was much after the kiss scene
we had in front of the recording scene.
[Ah... I guess there's that
kiss scene too.]
I'm talking about the scene in the beginning.
The other one is practically a bed scene.
- Come on, that's not a simple kiss scene.
- There was a bed scene?
- In 'Beautiful days'?
- Bed scene?
- There's a kiss scene before the bed scene.
- Let's make this one a practice one then.
- I took the later one as the main kiss scene.
- You're right.
You're right. You're right too, but
the record store scene is prior to that.
[Even though he's right, the record store
scene earlier is the real first kiss scene.]
Come on. It was my drama.
I'd know.
- Am I not right?
- You may be remembering it wrong though.
Once she starts arguing her point like this,
there won't be an end to it.
[I guess you're right.]
- Is there proof of any kind?
- What happens now? Wasn't I right?
After checking into it,
by the ocean is the first kiss scene.
So Yoo Jae Suk had the
correct answer.
You're the weird one here.
How in the world did you know that?
- How did you know that?
- You've got a dirty mind. That's what it is!
I sort of had an idea,
but I wasn't sure.
- I wasn't sure.
- What was it about?
What was the drama,
'Beautiful Days' about?
- What's the drama about?
- It's about their love, what else?
'Beautiful Days' is about their love.
- Then how does it end?
- What do you mean? It doesn't work out.
- It doesn't work out?
- It doesn't work out.
- No, it has a happy ending.
Wait, which drama were we
talking about?
You're confused about the two, aren't you?
It's understandable to get mixed up.
And if he only watched it sporadically,
it's understandable to be confused.
[A risky joke being played out.]
- You kissed one too many times.
- I kissed way too many times.
It's so confusing at times.
Dramas can shoot their scenes
in reverse at times, right?
- It could be confusing.
- Yes, it's confusing.
Ji Woo has tendencies to argue her points
a little strongly, doesn't she?
Her style is a bit...
Okay, Jae Suk just gained
seven Running balls.
- Here's your second question.
- You have to be run quickly.
- You have to run up there quickly.
- Really?
In the drama, 'Winter Sonata'...
- In 'Winter Sonata'...
- There it is! I saw the whole drama!
- I saw the whole drama!
- Who in the world didn't see that drama?
I saw that drama twice!
What is the piano song that Bae Yong Joon
plays for Ji Woo in the auditorium?
I know that one!
I know the answer to that one.
- I know that one.
- I know the answer.
[Oh? It looks like she remembered?]
I just have to break this
on my head now, right?
- Okay, this is awesome.
- Wait. Ji Woo, what's your answer?
I know the exact answer to that.
I'm such a huge fan of 'Winter Sonata'.
[Winter Sonata's fan, Gary.]
The piano song that Bae Yong Joon
plays for Ji Woo in the auditorium.
Trumerei (Reverie)... Trumerei...
[The piano song in question is, Trumerei.
A difficult title to even pronounce.]
['Winter Sonata' fan working hard
to memorize all the answers.]
Trumerei!
- Why do you want to know that?
- What did you say?
- Trumerei.
- You're wrong!
- No, that's not it.
- No, you're wrong.
Trumerei!
Trumerei. Tru... merei.
- You're wrong. You got it wrong.
- There's no way I got that wrong.
You have no idea how much
I love that song!
In that scene, Bae Yong Joon says he can't
play the piano and then he all of a sudden...
Ji Woo...
[Is he right?]
[The song Bae Yong Joon plays for Choi Ji Woo
in the auditorium in 'Winter Sonata'.]
[Schumann's Trumerei. (Reverie)]
But in that scene... doesn't Bae Yong Joon
tell me what the title of the song is?
When I ask towards the end, 'What is this',
he tells me what it is, doesn't he?
I see now that your memory is
starting to come and go, doesn't it?
I... I don't know...
I don't think I know anymore.
- What are you doing?
- I don't know... I don't know.
Trumerei.
- Trumerei?
- I can't believe he's right!
How did you know that?
How did you know it was called, Trumerei?
- You really do like the song, huh?
- Of course, I do!
He starts playing the song on the piano
after telling her that he can't play.
Who's the composer of the piece?
Come on... the composer isn't important.
What the heck? What's her problem?
How does she not know anything about herself?
What did you think it was?
I don't remember.
You have just won six Running Balls.
What do I do?
You guys really don't know
enough about Ji Woo.
How... how did you know that?
- I'm a total fan of that drama.
- Show me, which song are you talking about?
[If anyone is caught,
the filming stops right away.]
I don't remember it at all.
[But... that's...]
That's the Godfather!
That's the Godfather.
[She wants to hear Trumerei...]
I guess I got the shows wrong.
[Even I know that's from The Godfather.]
No, no!
- You look good against the backdrop.
- Yeah, you do.
So what's the third question?
Five Running Balls hang on this question.
- I have to get it done this time.
- Ji Woo, you have to do better this time.
How can she not get any right
when they're all about her?
- In the drama, 'Winter Sonata'...
- 'Winter Sonata'!
Aren't there going to be any questions
about 'Stairway to heaven'?
In the scene where Choi Ji Woo and
Bae Hyung Joon first meet on the bus...
- I... can I answer this one?
- I know this one. I know it.
[A scene that's been remade
several times over!]
I know exactly what the answer is!
[Even Jae Suk remade
the same scene in the past...]
Why don't you...
take your glasses off?
[That won't be pretty...]
I made a remake of that drama scene.
I know the exact answer!
The color of the coat and
the headband Choi Ji Woo
is wearing in the bus scene
where they first meet?
[The color of the coat and headband she
wears in the bus scene where they first meet.]
[A scene from 'Winter Sonata'.]
[White and yellow.]
[And of course,
there's Jae Suk's parody.]
- I know this one!
- I know the exact answer!
Why are you so late in going up there?
[While everyone's jumping over themselves from
knowing the answer, Ji Woo hangs behind?]
Since the show's gotten so
many re-runs...
- I know this one!
- You know this, don't you?
Why don't you tell me?
Do you know this one?
- The color of the headband...
- The headband...
This is awesome!
[Unable to break the bowl.]
Get out... get out of the way.
This is awesome!
I  don't think Ji Woo's right
this time either.
- She doesn't know.
- No, I do know.
- You looked so pretty back then!
- I know that, Suk Jin.
[Her unchanging beauty
even with the flow of time.]
I watched it over five times
because you looked so pretty.
- Suk Jin, thank you!
- I'm being serious.
The headband was white,
and the coat was canary yellow.
Yes, he's right.
- Ji Woo knew the answer too.
- Wow, that really is amazing.
Ji Woo, you have to get up
there quicker.
[Don't you find any of this strange?]
[This is unbelievable!]
- Ji Woo, you have to start doing better!
- You have to place something.
I really don't remember any
of the dramas!
How am I supposed to remember something
that happened over ten years ago?
[It seems like she's finally
starting to get angry...]
She's really annoyed right now.
I have done so many more dramas
since those ones!
But when you keep talking about
ones from over 10 years ago...
[My... throat...]
[Why bring up something
from over ten years ago?]
Even though she is annoyed,
she's annoyed in a relaxed way, isn't she?
She actually looks very pretty
while annoyed right now.
Okay, here's your next question.
'Winter Sonata'...
'Stairway to heaven'...
'Air City'...
'Star Lovers'...
and 'Can't lose'. Tell me the names of her
characters in the order of dramas mentioned.
[The names of the characters she played
in the order of the dramas mentioned.]
[Oh no!]
[Ji Woo is the first one to arrive.]
Repeat them again, please.
'Winter Sonata' and...
Jung Woo Jin in 'Winter Sonata'.
I'm right. Jung Woo Jin.
In 'Winter Sonata', I played Jung Yoo Jin.
[She forgot to break the bowl!]
You didn't do that! You didn't do that!
- You didn't do that!
- Ji Woo...
I can't believe you didn't do that.
My head... my head is killing me!
I bet you're upset.
[Almost shaved ten years
off their lives.]
My head! There's no way he'd
know them all.
You have to hold her in the back.
I don't want her to overhear what I say.
- Keep her turned around.
- You're right. She shouldn't hear you.
But this one here...
'Air City', 'Star's lovers', 'Can't lose'...
memorizing all these names in order...
[Even though they did everything
they could to memorize them...]
[Will they be able to answer correctly?]
Her name in 'Star's lover' is Lee Mari.
And in 'Can't lose',
she plays an attorney named Lee Eun Jae.
- Jung Yoo Jin...
- I'm going to say I know the answer.
And the correct answer is?
- 'Winter Sonata'...
- He's not going to know the answers.
- 'Winter Sonata'... Yoo Hae Ji.
- How is he going to know the answers?
One of the answers is Mari.
- Yoon Ji Ae...
- You can't listen in.
'Stairway to Heaven', Kim Ji Hye...
[Ha Ha fails.]
- This is awesome.
- You can't watch. You can't watch.
- It cracked... it did crack.
- Did you hit someone?
Jae Suk... this really hurts.
- Choi Ji Woo would know this question best.
- Jung Yoo Jin?
Han Jung Suh. (Stairway to Heaven).
You can't listen. That won't be fair.
Lee Mari. (Star's lovers).
Lee Eun Jae. (Can't lose).
Did I get it?
- We've got the results.
- What is it?
[Ji Hyo is their only hope...
Did she succeed?]
[Correct answer.]
- You got it right?
- How did you know all that?
[She got that right?]
- You got it right?
- How did you know all that?
Why don't you say them again
from the beginning?
[Again?]
Jung Yoo Ji... I mean, Jung Yoo Jin.
- Get your head on straight.
- Yeah, get your head on straight.
But the thing is this.
Ji Woo, when you memorize things...
[Memorize things?]
[Crap.]
[Huh?]
- Don't you forget things after you're done?
- Yeah, I do. I forget after I'm done.
I'm telling you, I forget once I'm done.
Jung Yoo Jin...
- What were you thinking?
- How can you already forget the names?
[Luckily, she didn't seem to
notice anything.]
[Now the only two left are
Ji Woo and Ha Ha.]
[The person who answers this one right
gets one Running Ball.]
But even if we only get one right,
don't we still get to pick later?
- That's right.
- You're right.
[Since the person who comes in last doesn't
get any balls, they've no chances at a star.]
Why don't you concede to me?
You have one already.
- You have one already. Seriously!
- Choi Ji Woo is the problem now.
- How is this happening?
- This really is upsetting!
Ji Woo, what's wrong with you?
I bet this is really embarrassing for you.
- I'm really embarrassed.
- She's really embarrassed.
We're all standing up here
because we all answered a question right.
The important thing is,
these are Choi Ji Woo related questions
but the fact she's still standing there...
- That really is absurd.
- But it really is making me feel happy.
[Huh?]
[Goddess with a positive attitude.]
Choi Ji Woo!
To be honest, this really
isn't something to be upset about.
- No, it's not.
- This is really making me feel happy.
- Are you getting them wrong on purpose?
- Maybe I am!
So that we can answer them?
- I'm just testing you guys.
- I guess you are.
- Here comes an easy question.
- Is the question related to me?
Of course.
They're all related to you.
One of the songs on
'Stairway to Heaven's soundtrack...
When Kwon Sang Woo hears
this song...
[When Kwon Sang Woo hears this song from
'Stairway to Heaven's soundtrack...]
[The song that made them run
in the drama...]
[This isn't a question that would
even demand any hesitation!]
Ave Maria.
[Big problem]
Ave Maria... that one?
- But that song...
- Wait, this.. I hope it's awesome.
[Huh?]
[Ah! She got the saying wrong!]
[Scrambling for the bowl.]
This is awesome!
Ave Maria!
- I won!
- This is awesome... this is awesome.
This isn't going to do.
Come... come here.
Ji Woo, your face is beet red!
She stopped just like this.
What is 'I hope it's awesome'?
Ji Woo... how can you say,
'I hope it's awesome'?
[Because of saying the phrase wrong
even though she had the answer correct...]
- That was so easy. Ave Maria...
- I hope it's awesome? What was that?
I once said 'Jujube head' when
it should've been 'Mugwort head'.
This is seriously...
As I've already told you,
there's only one to be picked.
So the star will be given to
the person who picks the right one.
- This is it! It's mine!
- Are there any duds?
Except for one person,
they're all pretty much duds.
He says they're all duds
except for one!
- Watch this. This is pretty fun.
- This used to be so much fun back in the day.
- It really has been awhile, hasn't it?
- It's like the lottery drawing.
- Okay. It can't be opened anymore.
- Everyone, this star you see is riding on it.
- Please! Please!
- Please!
- I always had such bad luck with this.
- I used to hate getting chosen in the past.
[Who will be the winner of the star?]
- Here we go...
- One, two, three!
We have one!
[And that name is...]
[The end of the year man, Gary.]
[Opening up a ceremony for himself
with the theme song from 'The Godfather'.]
I can't believe I didn't get it
when I had seven balls in there!
- Yes, thank you!
- What to do!
- How can I be so unlucky?
- You should've let it spin around some more.
[So jealous...]
[Choi Ji Woo vs. Running Man.]
[The final mission location -
Horse themed park in Busan.]
- This is the final round of mission.
- Yes.
[The person to gather all seven stars
is the ultimate victor.]
- Then what about the person who has no stars?
- Then they have to go out and find them.
[I was given a secret spy mission...]
[I just need to find my partner to
secretly oust everyone.]
- Should we get started then?
- Yes.
- You shouldn't be in such a rush.
- Go find your stars.
[Not even realizing in her wildest dreams
Running Man cast already knows everything.]
I need to find them quickly.
[I need to start by finding my
spy partner first.]
- Did she leave?
- Not yet... not yet.
What are we going to do now?
Do we have to get ousted by Choi Ji Woo
so that she doesn't catch on to what we know?
- Yeah, that's right.
- So we have to get ousted?
We have to make sure that Ji Woo
collects all seven of the stars.
Since Ha Ha has to be the spy,
I'll get ousted first with my star.
We can't get ousted since
we don't have a star.
Suk Jin, you have to be careful.
- You and Kwang Soo have to be careful.
- What if she comes for me first?
- Let's all rally first.
- Do we really have to do it that way?
One, two, three... fighting!
- Come on, I wasn't even there yet.
- You should've moved faster.
Jae Suk, I'm going to get going.
[Whatever the case, precise planning,
and spot on acting is crucial!]
Then let's do it a little later.
After we find some stars first.
[Spy partner, Ha Ha's role is crucial to buy
the team members some time to find the stars.]
Since you haven't found a star yet,
you need to attach this under your name tag.
Deceive Choi Ji Woo.
[If they get ousted by Choi Ji Woo
before they find a star...]
[Then the whole thing will be blown!]
I have to find a star.
You have already gained a star
from the previous mission.
- You don't need to put this on your back.
- Then I can get ousted with ease?
[Choi Ji Woo vs. Running Man.]
I'm so cold!
[That's the signal she'll be using to
approach her partner during her search!]
Is that what I have to do?
That's too much. Can't I just do one?
[To approach her partner -
Wink and do the chicken dance.]
[Worried people may think
that she's a weirdo.]
[Should I do a practice round?]
How am I supposed to do this?
It's not like... I can say that I'm cold
since we're on the inside now.
I need to use my brain a little.
How am I to do this?
[Spy Ji Woo is on the move!]
I'm going to start
approaching them one by one.
[Who is my spy partner?]
[Is the ultimate deliverer,
Mr. Capable my partner?]
[Or could it be, Ace Ji Hyo?]
[Gary with his serene face?]
[I need to start my approach tactics.
Wait a minute...]
[Should I try approaching
Jae Suk first?]
Ji Woo, did you find any?
Are you coming towards me to
try to rip off my name tag?
- Come on...
- No, come here.
No, I'm not going to.
Why? Did you find one?
Look.
[Ji Woo starts her
approach tactics on Jae Suk.]
[Ah... I guess this is
the spy approach signal.]
[Breaking out in laughter
out of embarrassment.]
Jae Suk... if I joke around a little,
you should be more receptive.
Ah, this?
- Where? Where did you find it?
- I didn't find any yet.
I have to go find one.
Be careful of Jong Kook, okay?
[Jae Suk taking his leave after
pretending not to be aware of anything.]
It's not Jae Suk.
When I did this...
[Since there weren't any special responses
even though she did her approach tactics...]
He had no idea what it was about.
That Ji Woo... how can she make it
so obvious?
[Difficult to play dumb when she
makes her approach so obvious.]
Do I really have to play dumb
to everything?
Who knew I'd ever be looking for a star
just so that I can get ousted in ease?
But I feel no burden today.
Since getting ousted is the goal.
[The 'R' mark!]
[Could there be a star inside
the envelope?]
What is this?
[But there's only a piece of paper
inside the envelope?]
[A mission?]
[Put on a step counter and walk at least
100 steps in a squatted position.]
So you're not just giving it to us?
[They're not just given out, but must
complete the mission before gaining the star.]
I have to walk at least 100 steps?
So how do I get the star?
When I complete the mission first?
[With the count set to zero,
and while being prompted by Coach Kook.]
[Will Running Man's weakest link,
Big-nosed Brother be able to do it?]
So this is how it counts?
Good. Good...
What are you doing?
Training me right now?
- Come this way... this way!
- Okay.
- Can you just go away?
- Hurry up and come on.
I feel like you're pressuring me
right now.
We have to work fast to
find more stars.
I have to do 100 of these?
My legs...
- Come on.
- Let's see if I've done 100 yet.
You haven't done it yet.
You've still got long ways to go.
[If the count is below 100 when it's
checked, then the mission is a failure!]
- I'm telling you, you're not there yet.
- And I think I am.
[Will the count be over 100?]
- 88.
- You failed. You have to start over now.
- See? You have to start over now.
- I can't just do 12 more?
Instead of walking, how about jumping?
- Just jump instead.
- Let me get some rest first.
- We don't have the time for that.
- My legs are killing me right now.
I need to get some rest first.
[How is he going to do 100
with those legs of his?]
Just what in the world is all this?
What am I doing?
[Ji Woo starting to make her way
towards their direction.]
[What's Suk Jin doing?]
Suk Jin!
- Did you find it?
- What?
- Did you find one?
- I haven't found one yet.
- You haven't found a single one?
- Did you find any?
No, I haven't.
- I've been playing around.
- Doing what? Why do you look so tired?
- I was just playing around with Jong Kook.
- Ugh, I'm so cold.
- Are you that cold?
- Yes. Yes, I am.
[I guess it's not Suk Jin either...]
At last... I'm going to start
my approach.
[Ha Ha starting his approach strategy
in his role as the spy's partner.]
[He has to be resourceful and act right
in order not to raise Ji Woo's suspicion.]
[Finally runs into Ji Woo.]
How many did you find?
- I can't tell you that.
- Tell me.
- Why?
- Just because.
- Come on.
I'm... working on finding them
right now.
No?
[Okay...]
[Watch carefully.]
[Ha Ha's response signal is
to act like Rambo.]
[Haroro responding to her signal with
one of his own with his whole body.]
[So sorry...]
[Ha Ha even breaks out his emotional
acting for having found his partner!]
Leg flip cross!
[Spy Ji Woo not suspecting a thing,
and feeling relieved at having found Ha Ha.]
[Checking once more.]
[Anyways, spy and her partner find
each other successfully.]
Lets go find who has a star first.
[Of course...]
[Gullible Ji Woo... Feeling relieved
at having found her partner.]
[Lol... nice!
So it's up to me now, isn't it?]
[Discovers Ji Woo and Ha Ha
who have now found each other!]
[Okay... time to get caught...]
[Haroro convincing Ji Woo they should
go up and capture Gary.]
- How many have you found? Give me one.
- I only have this one.
- Why aren't you looking for any?
- I am looking, but haven't found any yet.
[Everyone has to be on the ball
with their acting skills now!]
[Gary has to let Ji Woo get him
without giving her any signs of anything...]
- Why are you walking back there alone?
- I'm afraid of someone ripping mine off.
Jae Suk is acting suspicious though.
[Just then!]
[Gary leaving his back wide open!]
[Spy Ji Woo on the move!]
[Ji Woo succeeds in eliminating Gary!]
[Top billing acting! Realistic expression!]
[I'm sorry, Gary.]
[Rushing off to jail before
breaking down in laughter.]
[Gary succeeds in getting ousted by
Ji Woo without indicating anything.]
That was pretty difficult.
That one scene...
[But the mission of having to not give
anything away is more difficult than thought!]
- Gary, Out. Gary, out.
- So it's begun.
It's begun.
Gary, Out. Gary, out.
Gary... Gary, nice job!
Thanks for your hard work!
I wonder if Kang Gary acted okay?
Jae Suk... will you count for me?
- What's your mission?
- Step counter.
I have to take 100 steps in
a squat position.
Your knees just made a crackling sound.
[Mission aside,
may have to head to the hospital first...]
[In such plain sight like that...]
Did you find one?
[Of all things, to get caught having
to do a mission like that...]
Why are you doing your
new year's greetings already?
To all our viewers,
I wish you a happy new year.
[While he's already down there,
saying a humble new year's greetings.]
- You really are so humble.
- Yeah, you really are.
[Maybe he should take some training
from Coach Kook in the new year...]
What are you doing?
[We're in big trouble!]
[She can't figure out that
there are missions involved!]
[Did she notice anything?]
[And then she just walks on by...]
[Rushing off to a spot where he can't
be seen to avoid her suspicion.]
[Just how many squatted steps
did he take earlier?]
If it's 88 steps again this time...
Crap, 93 steps.
[This time, 93 steps.
Fails at 100 squatted steps again!]
I almost had it...
I'm about to go crazy.
Only 93 steps when I did all those?
[Will Big-nosed Brother be able to
complete his mission?]
[On the other hand...]
[Giraffe in the process of
checking out the studio room.]
You haven't seen any envelopes
around, have you?
[Oh! Discovers an 'R' envelope
underneath the keyboard!]
[Jump up and stick five pieces
of paper on the ceiling.]
This is it.
This mission is tailor made for me!
Who else but me would be able to
get this mission done?
[Will the Giraffe be able to
beat this mission?]
- I found one... I found one.
- Hurry up and do it here.
- Hurry.
- Do it quickly.
[Stick five pieces of paper on the ceiling.]
[It stuck!]
[An impossible mission had it been
Ha Ha who found it.]
[Total of five pieces of paper.
Time to stick the second piece!]
[Kwang Soo's height at last
becoming useful at something!]
[He did it!]
[Lee Kwang Soo succeeds in his mission
to win himself a star.]
[Doing a pose after pulling off
the mission.]
[Now he can be ousted by
Ji Woo with ease.]
- Here's your star.
- Thank you.
[Now... should I start
making my move to get ousted?]
[On the other hand, Blank Ji starting to get
nervous from not having found her star.]
[Discovers an 'R' marked envelope!]
[Just what is the mission contained within?]
[Approach Choi Ji Woo's name tag and change
it to' Choi Ja Woo' without her knowing.]
[Must change the 'Ji' to a 'Ja' with the
pen in order to gain her star!]
I can't even get close to her name tag
now that Gary's been ousted!
[If she gets close to her at all,
Ji Woo is going to try to oust her...]
[Time to request backup.]
- Hi, Ji Hyo.
- Ha Ha...
I just found an envelope,
but the mission that I have to do...
I have to approach Ji Woo's name tag and
change it from 'Choi Ji Woo' to 'Choi Ja Woo'.
[Asking for him to distract Ji Woo while
Ji Hyo changes the name from the back!]
- You're with Ji Woo, aren't you?
- Yeah.
- I'll come to you right now, okay?
- Okay.
[May be able to pull it off with Ha Ha's help!
Time to put spy partner to work.]
[Ji Woo trying to approach Big-nose Brother
to oust him this time.]
[No... he doesn't have his star yet.]
- What?
- What are you doing, Suk Jin?
- Did you find a star? Did you find one?
- What? No, I haven't found one yet.
Where is it? Let me see.
You hid away your star, didn't you?
[If he gets ousted without a star first,
she's going to see 'Deceive Choi Ji Woo' sign]
- Want to walk around together?
- Shall we?
Why don't we join forces for now?
Why work with Suk Jin?
Leave him out of it.
[Leave Suk Jin out!]
[A scratch on his self-esteem.]
[Even in Ji Woo's eyes,
he's the weakest link.]
- Did you all find a star?
- What about you?
- I don't have one.
- I don't have one either.
Suk Jin,
come back after you find one.
- I understand. I'll be back.
- You know what I mean, right?
- Yeah, I got it.
My pride seriously took a blow.
[Ha Ha, what do I do?]
This is seriously driving me crazy.
I have to fix her name
with my marker right now.
[Whispering their plans to one another
while Ji Woo is out of sight.]
[Just then!]
[Ace Ji Hyo's name tag
is right in front of her!]
[I will end it!]
[But Ji Hyo doesn't have a star!]
[If she's ousted, then it's
over with Running Man's defeat!]
[Ji Woo attacks Ji Hyo!]
[Ji Hyo in danger!]
[Ha Ha needs to act fast and rescue
Ji Hyo without getting caught!]
[Oh! Ji Hyo's name tag!]
[Barely escapes her demise thanks to
Ha Ha getting between her and Ji Woo!]
Where are you? What are you doing?
Are you going for my name tag now?
[What's wrong with Ha Ha
all of a sudden?]
[Everything will be blown if Ha Ha
doesn't handle this right!]
- Wait..
- What is this?
[But thankfully, kind hearted Ji Woo is only
concerned for her partner at the moment.]
- Just go, just go!
- What is this?
- What's going on right now?
- Don't touch me right now.
[Transform 'Choi Ji Woo' to 'Choi Ja Woo'!
Will Ji Hyo be able to get it done?]
- I don't have any right now.
- I'm seriously going to get mad if you do.
I really will...
[Just then! Kwang Soo attacks Ha Ha!]
[Even though they look like they're
fighting, if you look closer...]
[It's a plan of distraction so that
Ji Hyo can complete her mission!]
[Too bad!]
[What's wrong with them
all of a sudden?]
- What's going on with you two?
- Are you two working together?
No, we're not.
What are you talking about?
Be careful... both of you.
I'm just telling you to be
cautious of me.
Because I'm going to oust all of you.
But anyways, this isn't the time
for us to be sitting around like this.
What do you mean, this isn't the time?
You're the one who's acting weird.
That's what I'm saying.
We can let Ji Hyo go for now since
she doesn't have any stars.
But for now, how many does
Jong Kook have?
He doesn't have any stars.
What about Gary?
But Gary's already been ousted.
- Really?
- Who ousted Gary?
[Playing it off like she doesn't know.]
Then why don't the four of us go
to oust someone right now?
- Yeah, that's a good idea.
- Let's do that.
I can't trust any of this.
Whenever I watched the show,
you guys oust each other after saying that.
- Let's go get Jong Kook first.
- Let's wait until I find a start first.
- Then let's go get Jong Kook.
- You're with three most trusted people.
You're the one I trust the least!
- He's actually pretty loyal.
- No, he isn't.
- Jae Suk is the problem.
- Really? Then let's go.
- Fighting. One, two, three...
- Fighting.
- See? You're acting strange.
- Should we do it again? Okay, let's redo it.
One, two, three... fighting.
Forget it. Let's not even do it.
[Truly innocent and gullible Ji Woo...
not even the slightest bit of suspicion.]
Seriously!
[You're still at it?]
[Doing a year's worth of leg workouts
in one session.]
I have to make movements like this
for the counts to go up.
I feel like I'm shooting
a documentary by myself.
A documentary about a dad making it.
[Instead of that, how about a middle aged
man not getting enough exercise?]
I'm going to jump over there
and check the counter.
Please...
[What... what is he doing?]
[Is that a special dance to bring up
the count on the step counter?]
Gangnam style...
[Anyways, he really is working hard
at getting it done.]
What is that?
Who's crawling around over there?
[Ji Woo! Big trouble!
He needs to make his escape quickly!]
[Running away at top speed!]
I can't... I can't do it anymore.
Just leave me out of it.
I'm not doing it.
If I failed again, I'm not doing it anymore.
231...
[Succeeds with 231!]
[Side effect - Having done
too many has paralyzed his legs.]
[Why was Suk Jin squat walking?]
- Why do you keep doing that?
- No kidding. What are you doing?
What the heck?
Why are you doing that?
- I'm trying to work out a cramp.
- Are you by any chance...
[Suk Jin, are you by any chance...]
Suk Jin, are you by any chance
sitting on top of a star right now?
Are you sitting on top of a
star right now?
Lift up your butt.
- Why are you asking me that?
- I think you are.
[Ha Ha working to get her away
to move to another location.]
[Almost got into big trouble
after barely completing the mission...]
Okay.
[Suk Jin finally gets his star!]
[The sign is now removed from his back
ensuring his safety!]
All set.
Let's go get ousted and go to jail.
[My legs...]
This is so embarrassing.
- I have to find a star quickly.
- Come here, come here.
- The thing we need to do is... come here.
- We can't go around in a group like this.
[Ha Ha trying to distract her so that
Ji Hyo can complete her mission.]
Why don't we make a tiny mark on our
name tag to indicate we're on the same team?
[A sign of alliance?
A mark on their name tags?]
Why don't we make a small mark
on our name tags?
[Ah... use that opportunity to change
'Choi Ji Woo' to 'Choi Ja Woo'...]
[Turning their heads so that Ji Woo
can't see that she's laughing.]
We need a marker or something.
Hey, do you have a marker of sorts?
[Ji Woo not even realizing in her
wildest dreams that this is Ji Hyo's mission.]
Ji Woo!
[No choice but to follow since all the
others are saying they should do it...]
[Adding a mark to Ha Ha's back first
to show that they're working together!]
[Changing Ha Ha to Hya Ha.]
[Changes Lee Kwang Soo to
Lee Kwang Shu.]
[At last, it's Ji Woo's turn.]
- Ji Yoo?
- No, change it to Ja. Ja Woo.
Ja Woo.
You have to mark it more.
You can't even tell it's there.
That's too light.
[Done. Choi Ja Woo!]
- Song Ji Hyong? Ja Hyo?
- Ja... do a 'Ja'.
- Okay, all done.
- Done?
- Okay, fighting.
- One, two, three... fighting.
[Even a cheer to close the deal.]
But why did we all come in here?
Just so we can do that?
We came in here to mark our names?
Why did we do that?
When we all recognize who we are.
[Ji Hyo rushing off to escape far away.]
[I seriously thought...
I was going to die of laughter.]
- You succeeded your mission.
- Okay.
[Succeeded in changing
'Choi Ji Woo' to 'Choi Ja Woo'!]
[Now she can get ousted
to her heart's content!]
Ji Woo... I'm sorry for
turning you into Choi Ja Woo.
[Running Man's victory is slowly
approaching closer.]
Ji Woo! Come in here.
We have three stars between us, right?
[I need to get ousted without
making it seem obvious too...]
[Kwang Soo all of a sudden is in need
to re-tie his shoe lace!]
[Kwang Soo... you're a genius!]
[Signaling to her immediately
to oust Kwang Soo!]
[The glint in Ji Woo's eyes
changes in a flash!]
[But... his shoes don't even have
any shoelaces at all.]
[But Ji Woo doesn't suspect a thing.]
- What are you going to do without your tag?
- Ji Woo, you're awesome!
[Must move him off to jail before
Kwang Soo burst out in laughter!]
[Lee Kwang Soo, out!
Lee Kwang Soo, out!]
[On the other hand,
Yoo-ruce Willis has yet to find a star.]
[Scream out 'Ji Woo' and
it must reach over 125 decibels.]
[Noise measuring device!
It must be done here!]
[If he screams out the name,
Ji Woo is sure to run over to him.]
Ji Woo!
[Must be over 125 decibels.
Fails from registering at 121.8.]
- What are you doing?
- This is my mission.
[Rushing to do it again
before Ji Woo comes over.]
Choi Ji Woo.
Ji Woo!
Choi Ji Woo!
Who was that?
Ji Woo...Choi Ji Woo!
[Too bad...]
[Ji Woo starting to head over
his way after hearing the shouts.]
- She can't know this is a mission...
- No, she can't find out.
- Who ousted Kwang Soo?
- I did.
- You did? Really?
- Yeah.
- How?
- I just did.
- Wasn't I supposed to just rip it off?
- Yeah, you are.
That's what I did.
- Ji Woo... Choi Ji Woo!
- Yeah?
[Jae Suk! If you do that,
she may get suspicious!]
Yes?
[Even though he's doing that right in front
of her, not the slightest bit of suspicion.]
- What is it?
- Did you really oust him?
[Sensible. Continuing his conversation
so that she doesn't get suspicious of him.]
[Amazing wit and improv skills!]
Yes, I ousted him.
- Why?
- Jae Suk, just let it all out.
- Just turn to the wall, and let it all out.
- Ji Woo...
- Ji Woo. Choi Ji Woo!
- There you go. Good.
- Choi Ji Woo! Choi Ji Woo!
- Good! Get it out!
[Just what in the world is going on?]
[On the other hand, one final person
who has yet to find a star mission.]
[A suspicious room with the door ajar?]
I didn't think there was a door
to this place.
I thought there was a door in the back...
[At last, Mr. Capable finds
a mission envelope!]
[Find a member to play the peppero game
and leave only 2cm behind.]
Who's still left alive? Jae Suk...
[Then he's going to play
the game with Jae Suk?]
Ji Woo...
Choi Ji Woo!
[Two members without a star!
If Ji Woo ousts even one, then Ji Woo wins!]
Ji Woo.
Choi Ji Woo!
You think this is the time to laugh?
You can still laugh about this?
How can you laugh right now?
- Choi Ji Woo!
- Ji Woo, forget him and just come here.
I think I'm just going to oust him.
He's being way too loud.
[This is trouble...
Jae Suk doesn't have his star yet!]
[Screaming again with all his might.]
[It seems as though the rating goes up more
when he screams at a higher octave.]
Ji Woo... Choi Ji Woo!
Choi Ji Woo!
[Choi Ji Woo is closing in
on him from behind!]
[He finally succeeds but if he's caught now,
then everything is over!]
[Jae Suk avoids elimination by a hair!]
You startled me.
I could've been in trouble.
[If he escapes too fast, she may pursue,
so he calmly starts walking away.]
- Why are you so startled?
- Of course, I'm startled.
I was going to flutter in like a butterfly
and sting him like a bee.
[Anyways, he did scream out
Ji Woo's name above 125 decibels.]
[Jae Suk succeeds his mission!]
- Here it is.
- Yes, give it to me.
[Jae Suk finally feeling reassured
after gaining his star.]
That could've been trouble...
She almost ousted me. That was close.
[This time, it's Big-nosed Brother
right in front of her.]
[There's no one around watching, right?]
[Target locked.]
[Ji Woo succeeds in eliminating
Suk Jin's name tag!]
[Big-nosed Brother's perfect
acting skills!]
Ji Suk Jin, out!
- What is it?
- Come on... hurry.
[Must play the peppero game with
another person to leave behind 2cm!]
What the heck is that?
[Kind of creepy and weird
between two men!]
Then should I call Ji Hyo over?
Seriously, am I supposed to
call Ji Hyo over instead?
I was so afraid that you were
already ousted.
- Then I'd have to find Ji Hyo.
- You should go get Ji Hyo. You have to.
Just do it!
[Like it or not, it's man on man!
Just 2cm behind...]
Look at him biting that end so that
he doesn't have to eat the chocolate.
[Mr. Capable abstaining from sweets.]
[So he lightly bites down the end.]
Seriously... just to stay away
from sweets.
Seriously...
Come on... what the heck is this?
I don't like this either!
It's because I don't have a star.
I'm doing it to earn a star.
Seriously... you're so ugly.
Do you know how ugly you look up close?
- Seriously...
- I'm being serious.
- It's not like I can even oust him.
- Why would you want to do that?
Just hurry up and do it.
I can't believe I'm doing this
just for you to get your star...
[But why are you holding onto
each other's shoulders?]
- Don't look, don't look.
- Just do it. Let's get this over with.
[Slowly...]
[Closer...]
[Come a little closer...]
I can't do this!
- You have to come closer!
- No, you move in.
- You have to move in since I'm holding it.
- What's the length?
- That won't work.
- There's way too much left.
Since I'm biting it down,
you have to move in.
One person bites down,
and the other one moves in.
Ji Woo is heading this way right now.
[There's no time!
Ji Woo is headed their way!]
[Big trouble... big trouble.]
[Moving right into their second attempt
with no time to waste.]
[Enduring it all in order to
succeed the mission.]
[If it's less than 2cm, mission is a success!
Just what will the results be?]
[2.3cm. Fails again.]
[While that is all going on,
Ji Woo is approaching even closer.]
[Even though it's annoying,
they're jumping into their third attempt.]
[More drastic now?]
[Yuck!]
[Holding down their bile
for the success of the mission.]
Hurry!
[Will it be less than 2cm this time?]
[2.5 cm. Fails again!]
Hurry up!
[Their facial expressions are starting to
get darker and darker.]
Watch who you're spitting at!
You come in. This time, you come in.
- You make the move this time.
- Let's just keep doing what we've done.
He doesn't want to eat the sweets because
he's thinking about himself and his muscles.
He's afraid that it's going to make
his muscles smaller or something.
[Ji Woo is getting ever so closer...]
Just shut your mouth and
bite down on it.
[There's no time! Must get it
done quickly to get the star!]
Bite.. bite down on it.
[It does look pretty short... could it be?]
Seriously, Kim Jong Kook...
- If that didn't work, I'm leaving.
- You can't leave!
[1.8 cm. Success!]
Seriously...
are you seriously going to be like this?
What do you mean, be like this?
What else could I do with the mission?
- You could've just moved closer.
- You could've just ate a little chocolate!
[Anyways, Jong Kook finally
earns his star.]
- What? What is it?
- There he is!
[All they have left is to get ousted now
without raising any suspicion!]
[Quietly agreeing to Jong Kook
getting ousted first.]
- Why are you doing this?
- Jae Suk, what's going on?
[Acting as though they're unable to
trust each other.]
- Ji Woo, hurry!
- Come on!
[Ji Woo finally makes her move!]
[Heading towards Mr. Capable
caught in their grasp!]
[Realistic acting.]
[Ji Woo eliminates Jong Kook's
name tag!]
[Just then! Moving onto
Ji Hyo's name tag right away!]
[Amazing, nonetheless.
Eliminates Mr. Capable and Ace Ji Hyo!]
[Acting bewildered even as
they're being dragged away to jail.]
Ji Woo... Ji Woo!
Good job... good job.
Kim Jong Kook, out.
What the heck?
Hey... how can you oust
Ji Hyo like that?
Why not?
- Why not? Seriously...
- Ji Woo...
It's not that, but I almost got ousted
by Jong Kook because you took so long.
I almost got ousted.
Then shouldn't you be grateful to me
for eliminating Jong Kook for you?
Shouldn't you be grateful?
[Jae Suk and Ha Ha's perfect
acting skills!]
[Ji Woo eliminates Jae Suk's name tag!]
That was too easy.
Maybe I'll put it back and do it again.
Yoo Jae Suk, out.
Ha Ha, it was you?
Look at how happy she is with this.
[Running Man succeeds their mission of getting
ousted by Ji Woo without raising suspicion.]
There are no eternal friends of enemies
on Running Man.
[Ji Woo and Ha Ha heading
towards the final star platform.]
One, two, three... leg flip cross!
[The seven stars that used to belong
to the other members!]
- Look at how happy Ji Woo is right now.
- You know how good winning feels.
- What to do...
- What do we do?
[Running Man members feeling bad
for having won the mission.]
Okay... Ji Woo!
[And lastly, Ha Ha's star.]
[As soon as all the stars are lit up,
fireworks lights up the sky!]
[Beautiful fireworks to mark the
last night in year 2012.]
[Right behind the happy lady...
a flag drops down from the sky...]
[Huh?]
We've been watching you down here.
[What is that?]
[Still unable to comprehend this situation.]
- I'm a spy, Jae Suk.
- You're not a spy...
[Even on Choi Ji Woo's back...
'Deceive Choi Ji Woo' sticker!]
What the heck is that?
[Now finally getting what's going on.
[On the brink of a mental breakdown.]
Why is Running Man all about
deceiving people?
[Game with 1:7 odds where Ji Woo would've
won if she ousted anyone without a star.]
I'm sorry,
but there was a game like this before.
Traumerei...
Was that what it was called?
We were together during the whole race,
and with just the two of us walking around
and with everyone else getting ousted,
I'm sure she must've suspected something.
No, I didn't suspect a darn thing!
I really thought... I was just that good.
I just thought that I was that good.
Seriously.
[Choi Ji Woo is so beautiful!]
- So sweet and innocent!
- I really did think that.
I thought that my steps were
light as a feather.
[Ripping off every name tag
that crossed her way.]
- You were amazing at ripping them off.
- They were so fun to rip off!
- You really were something else.
-I could see Ji Woo getting bolstered by it.
- So when I asked, 'Isn't this too much?'
- She replies, 'Why?'
[Her one word, 'Why?' came after gaining
confidence playing the game.]
[Just what is the winning prize that
Running Man won?]
[Digital cameras!]
- Ji Woo, I'm so sorry!
- Ji Woo's not getting one, is she?
If Ji Woo had won,
would she have taken them all?
All seven would've been
hers had she won.
Then what about me?
I don't get one?
[It seems as though Ji Woo just gave the
Running Man members end of the year gifts.]
- Ji Woo, thanks.
- Sorry about this, but you get nothing.
[This is what happens due to
her unsuspecting nature...]
To all our faithful viewers, we sincerely
thank you for watching us throughout 2012.
And as for everything...
all the negative things that
happened in the past year...
Please erase them all from your memory
as Ji Woo joined us on the show today.
[Erase all the unpleasant memories
from your memories- 'Jiwoo'= Erase.]
- Erase them completely...
- Erase them.
And we will work harder to bring you
more laughter in the year 2013.
I have become a fan of Choi Ji Woo today.
Our beautiful Choi Ji Woo.
[Making a fan out of all the members
with her pure and kind heart.]
Please allow us to wish you well
in the year 2013.
Everyone...
we wish you a happy new year!
[We all wish you the best 2013!]
Subtitles by DramaFever
[No... no... this can't be.]
- Ji Woo, it's okay. Calm down.
- This sucks!
[Changing 180 degrees with
vengeance as her goal.]
[Our Ji Woo has changed.]
Happy new year!
This is a new year's special,
12 signs of zodiac race.
Let's get started then!
This is really making me nervous.
[12 powerful spirits protecting the land...
please guard me in my quest!]
- Help me!
- Is that one the snake?
You're not the snake?
[Just who will become the
king of the zodiacs?]
[Signs of the Zodiac... Battle of the Gods.]