You failed?
You're saying the real gold fell
into Ha Ha and Gary's hands?
I don't even want
to have to look at you...
So keep your back turned for the time being.
I guess ultimately,
I'm going to have to step in.
[There was a larger-than-life actor that's
planned everything from the beginning]
[Boss Kim Soo Hyun]
It seems that ultimately,
I'm going to have to step in.
[The trio failed in the operation]
[This time, the boss himself is
stepping into the gold hunting game]
[Gimpo yacht harbor]
[Parting through the water...]
[Making an appearance like the
main character in a movie...]
[Boss Kim Soo Hyun]
Hello.
[What is the reason for him showing up here?]
[A little while later]
[The emergence of
the nation's first class thieves]
[Mission:]
[Steal the gold turtle
that's been hidden here]
[The 7 thieves eyeing the ultimate break]
To the left.  A sniper to the left.
[Jae Suk.  The legendary water gun sniper]
[One shot, one kill.  God of water guns]
[Taking out the security within seconds]
[Now to the interior of the building]
[Interior with an even tighter security]
[Huh?]
[Getting rid of the security guards
with the poisonous darts]
-We don't have time.  Open it quickly.
-Hurry, hurry!
[Suk Jin- Veteran lock specialist]
-Come on!
-Hurry up!
[Penetrating into
the heavily secured interior!]
[Jong Kook- The legendary invincible fighter]
-Let's go!
-Come on!
[Flying in like a bee...]
[And suppressing them within moments!]
[Operating in Hollywood style]
Wake up!  Don't you recognize me?
[Ji Hyo- Laser transmission expert]
[Checking for hidden laser beans
with a spray]
[Starting to break through the laser beams]
Watch your legs!
My legs are too short!
[Agility]
[Ultimately completing
with the old faithful method]
[Completes getting rid of the laser]
[The next step is a time bomb]
Where is cutter?
[Gary- Explosives expert]
[A flustered expert...]
[The awful lot of Hollywood style jargon]
-No time, no time!
-There's no time!
Red or blue?  Red or blue?!
No green!  No green!
-Cut it!
-Maybe... Cut the red?
No time no time...!
[Going with the gut instinct...]
[Defusing the bomb is a success!]
[Doing a roll without any reason]
[Thief giraffe stepping up
to crack the safe combination]
[Kwang Soo- Safe expert]
[Will the gold turtle be in the safe?]
-Wait... Wait...
-Come on, come on...
[These are the 7 gold turtles!]
Pack them, pack them, pack them...!
Quiet!  Quiet!!
Hey, get your mind together.
-Sorry, sorry...
-Hey!  What are you doing?!
Come on!  Let's go!
[The thieves succeed
in getting all 7 gold turtles]
[Now the only thing left to do is to flee
the scene of the crime without getting caught]
See you again!  See you again!
[Huh?
Where is Ha Ha headed to all of a sudden?]
-Ha Ha!  Ha Ha!
-Ha Ha!
The one who controls the wire!
[Ha Ha- Wire expert]
-Ha Ha!
-Ha Ha!  Ha Ha!
[The wire expert who takes longer
than those that are walking]
[Wire expert Ha Ha,
who holds wire safety at highest priority]
Ha Ha!!
Thank you mommy!
[The 7 thieves safely escaping the building
through the use of their own special skills]
Go!  Go, go, go!
[Heading to the yacht in the harbor
in hopes of a quick escape]
[However... A man that's been watching
this whole time...]
[Boss Kim Soo Hyun]
-This boat?
-This boat?  Let's go.
[Soo Hyun not missing their single move]
[What is his purpose of coming here?]
[A little while ago...]
Why did you come on Running Man?
Last week...
The gold that was taken from me,
I came here to take it back.
Didn't you leave that to the 3 criminals?
Yes... They were
associates of mine that I trusted...
[But who knew they'd be that clumsy...]
I think I'm going to have to step in.
Since it was a difficult mission
even for 3 people...
So there's one thing that we have prepared.
Shall we open it?
[High performance water gun]
-It's a water gun and special solution.
-Yes...
-Special solution?
-Here is our proposal.
While Running Man members are
carrying out their mission...
Take your shots at Running Man's name tags.
Once you do...
Once the member that's been hit
gets to the final location
they will be automatically ousted
after an hour.
[Automatically ousted?]
-If I shoot everyone...
-That's right.
The more targets you shoot,
then more of your opponents will diminish.
It would be best if you attacked them secretly.
That isn't just any water.  If you look...
That's your special solution.
Even if that gets on the name tag
after a certain amount of time,
it evaporates from the name tag.
[It's hard for other to catch on
because the signs of it disappears]
-Any opponent that you find overwhelming?
-Mr. Capable.
[Now it's my turn to step up]
Running Man, just wait...
The gold turtles are mine!
[A showdown with the veteran Running Man...]
[Will Soo Hyun be able to recapture his gold?]
[Not a single one of them had a clue
of Soo Hyun's existence...]
Ji Hyo... Don't steal this gold.
It really has been a long time.
[The thieves drink on their success]
It's moving... Moving.
Where is this headed to?
Where are we going?
[Even though they may not know the mission
or where they're headed...]
[But they're feeling good...!]
[But for now, a boat party
to celebrate the thievery of gold turtles]
[And I have you by my side...]
[Teacher Gae teaching the rail dance]
[Yes, you are the blue sea...]
[Dancing machine Jae Suk's stage]
You guys were the best today.
[What is this?]
-I used to play video games with these on.
-Back in the day...
-Aren't these 3D glasses?
-Can we watch DVD's with this?
-Should we put them on?
-I can see something!
[Mission images shown through
state of the art equipment]
[What?  This is...?!]
[Chairman Lee Duk Hwa]
-Hello Chairman!
-Chairman, we see you!
It's nice to see you.
Running Man...
It's been awhile.
[What is the Chairman doing on here?]
The gold turtle that you guys stole earlier...]
Unfortunately... Only one of those are real.
What the!
You have to place the real gold turtle
on top of the reader at the final destination.
If...
You were to place the fake one up there...
The reader will end up exploding.
I have prepared a way for you to figure out
which one of the ones you have is the real one.
The one that wins at Sangam...
And the member that wins the mission at
Ilsang market will get the chance to find out.
And...
Kwang Soo, you!
Don't even dream about betraying!
I understand, Chairman.
Oh yeah...
We have to do the second round
of fishing soon?
[He hasn't forgotten...]
Running Man...
I make this request!
What the...!!
[A surprise cameo by Lee Duk Hwa]
[Now time to divide the 7 gold turtles
among the members]
[Just one of these is a real gold turtle]
[Just which one of these is the real one...]
But this is pretty yellow too.
The most important thing is,
we can just melt everything.
[On the other hand...]
[Soo Hyun, who's been listening to everything]
At Nanji campground...
[Sangam Nanji campground...!]
[Already studying the structure
through a 3D image]
[Today's gold is... Mine!]
Everyone be careful today.
[Not even dreaming of the existence of the boss
and thinking it's a rivalry between the gold]
[Nanji campground]
[The black troop
that's entering the campground]
[Among that team... Is Soo Hyun]
[Receiving the help
of the campers to infiltrate]
[And...]
[The giant ice blocks placed
throughout the campground?]
[Then this is... The Running Man's mission?]
[Oh... So if those were put to use...!]
[The ice block in front of the tent...!]
[Good... In that case, that's the place.]
[With the intense summer sun,
inside of the tent is a sauna]
[Okay, from here... I will get rid of them]
[Will Soo Hyun's plan succeed?]
-We're almost there.
-Do you remember Nanji camp?
[Running Man arriving at Nanji camp]
It really has been awhile.
[Nervous]
Since the ice bock is right out front...
As long as they stand there
with their back turned...
[It sounds easy... But the heart is pounding]
They're not even here yet,
but why am I so nervous?
Since this is the first location...
The target is... Gary.
And Mr. Capable.
[Preparing the special solution]
[Soo Hyun waiting for the
Running Man members with confidence]
Hey... There it is.
-Wow... It's been awhile.
-It's now starting!
[They're here...!]
[A familiar location
that they've been to before]
-It was really cold back then...
-It was totally freezing.
Oh!  It's ice!
[For your first mission...]
[There are ice blocks
placed throughout the park]
[The mission letter is
placed within those ice blocks]
So we have to break them...
The first person to break the mission free...
only that person will be able to determine
whether the turtle they have is real or not.
Go!
[Start!]
There's ice... There's ice over there!
It's ice!!
Is that it over there?
[Thief Big Nose,
who was the first to discover an ice block]
Hey, this is...
Hey this is... The ice is...!
How are we supposed to break this?
Why is this toy hammer even here?
-What is this toy hammer?
-How are we supposed to do this?
[Rather pathetic tools around the ice...]
How can we do this?!
[Jae Suk and Ji Hyo running madly]
[The place they're headed to is
in front of the tent #C-17!]
[They're here!]
[Jae Suk and Ji Hyo!]
Where else is it at?
[Ji Hyo who was one step late is
headed towards another location...]
I don't know if this is going to work.
If I concentrate all my strength and hit
the middle, it'll split right down the middle.
[Chattering away while not even knowing
the danger that he's been put himself in]
If I concentrate all my strength and hit
the middle, it'll split right down the middle.
You didn't know that, did you?
[But Jae Suk's facing the tent...]
[How will he shoot in this situation?]
You'll be surprised when it splits in half.
Hold on tight to that.
[He has to turn around!]
Gun Yul... Make sure to get this.
Why did they put the toy hammer here?
[Please... Turn your body just a little!]
I'm sorry!  I'm going to borrow this!
I'll borrow this for a moment.
[Just then... Ha Ha grabs a hammer...?]
Thank you.
You're dead!
[It's a hammer!]
[He left...]
[The ambitious dreams of the first attack
flies out the window...]
When I would watch the show...
it just looked like so much fun...
[My luck...]
[Is no one coming?]
[It can be so easily over
if only someone would show up...]
[Anxiety ridden Soo Hyun...]
[Surprisingly cute and clumsy Soo Hyun]
Are you making any progress?
-Where did you get that?
-I'm taking care of it.
How can you say that?
I don't think this will work.  I need a hammer.
What are you doing?
[Blank Ji Hyo with a hammer and
a tent pole out of nowhere]
-I'll do it.
-No!  I'm going to do it.
I'll help you. Come on.
[Gary helping out of affection from the past?]
Move!  You're going to get hurt!
Ji Hyo!  Not yet!
[Helpful Gary making an extortion attempt]
Ji Hyo, wait...
Okay then.  You can have this.
Kang Gary!  It's not out yet!
Bring the hammer back here.
[Completely immersed...
Shooting the water gun out of anger]
[Gary is headed this way...!]
Just keep doing what you're doing!
[He's finally here!]
[Motivated boss...
But now that it's time, heart is pounding]
The mission card...
There's a hole in the mission card!  Wait...
[Gary's back is unprotected]
[This is it!]
[Soo Hyun's aim out the tent]
[The target is Gary's name tag]
[Attack complete]
It hit...
[Gary gets his hand on the mission card]
[His name tag...]
[Has been hit with the special solution!]
...They'll be automatically ousted.
[Boss Soo Hyun...
Succeeds at shooting Gary]
Gary is a little...insensitive, right?
[Very...insensitive]
Thanks for the treat.
[One person for now... Ok!]
I got it.
I got it, I got it.
Find the gold wan?
What is gold wan?  Gold wan?
[Now that he's got a hammer,
making simple issue of the situation]
Huh?  What does 'Find the gold wan' mean?
Who is Gold wan?
[Running Man's first mission is
to find the gold wan!]
Gold wan!
Where is gold wan?
Hey!
Gold wan...!
[The evaporating special solution...
Already gone!]
Does it have the number one
written on it in gold or something?
If I tell you this...
To the end...you have to...
[Giraffe with sharper sense these days...
Is he sensing something?]
-What is that?
-Go Dong Wan.
[Gold Wan= Go Dong Wan?]
Dong Wan PD?
For example,
Dong Wan could be dressed in something gold.
Hey, that's a guarantee.
Hey, you've gotten so much better.
[The giraffe's keen reasoning]
Let's go look around the tents
over here first.
[Bingo.  Gold Wan's identity is...]
[Dong Wan PD that's been adorned in gold]
Is he hiding in here?
[Searching for the PD in disguise]
[Over here!]
There he is, there he is!
[Sensing danger,
Gold Wan breaking off into a run!]
[Jae Suk joining on the Gold Wan chase]
Isn't that Jae Suk?
Why is Jae Suk running?
He's running!  Running!
There he is!
[The giraffe following the crowd for now]
[With something seeming stranger,
Mr. Capable and Ace also breaking into a run!]
What is it?
[Why are they running?]
[Gold Wan doing a good job of evading them]
Hey!
Getting out of here is the bigger problem...
[Mr. Capable Jong Kook]
[Tiger Jong Kook chasing after Gold Wan
like a beast of prey]
Come here.
[The tiger captures Gold Wan]
-Hey!
-Is it Jong Kook again?
I knew about it first!
I got him first!
-I figured it out earlier too.
-I knew about it first.  I found Gold Wan!
[Arguing over the capture of Gold Wan]
-Jong Kook...
-I knew it as soon as I saw it.
[Transporting to Gold Wan's hideout somewhere]
[Huh?  Jong Kook's bag?]
[Thief Jae Suk stealthily searching
through Jong Kook's bag]
I knew about it before you did.
Hey, Dong Wan... Hey...
Why don't you let me take you in?
[Stolen Jong Kook's gold turtle!]
Do you want me to set you free?
-Dong Wan, get out!
-Hurry up and run!
[Trying to set Dong Wan free?]
[However the tiger
isn't letting go of his grip]
[Gold Wan becoming a joke]
Run, Dong Wan!
[The tiger keeping a firm grip on Gold Wan]
-Run!  Run!
-Run away!
Run away!
[Mr. Capable...
Succeeds in finding Gold Wan!]
Since Kim Jong Kook was the quickest
to bring Gold Wan here...
We will give him the chance to check
to see if his gold is the real one.
Let him.  His is not real.
-Let's go.
-Can't we all go?
You have to let us know for sure.
They can only find out if they take out
the gold they have themselves, right?
But if they don't have one, it doesn't matter?
Gold Wan?
[Mission's 1st place winner, Jong Kook-
Entering Gold Wan's chambers]
That little...
He only knows to use his strength.
-He's still just a foolish young man...
-He can't even take care of his own things.
Please give me your gold.
Where did the gold go?
Did the gold fall out?
Where did my gold go?
[Flustered]
I know I put the gold in here!
Here he comes, here he comes.  He knows.
He's mad, he's mad.
I know without a doubt
that I put it in here earlier.
-Is Jong Kook angry?
-I'm sure that he is.
[The gathering of herbivores
watching the carnivore warily]
Anyways, it's his fault for not
taking care of his own things.
I think someone took it!
Someone took it out of the bag
when I wasn't paying attention earlier.
[Bingo!]
Who took my gold out of my bag?
What do you mean, who took it out?
When you're the one who couldn't take care
of your own thing, how can you blame...
Someone took it out when I was
dragging Dong Wan, right?
[The tiger seems angry...]
-Stop right there...
-Don't come here.
[Collectively cringing]
There are 6 of us right now!
Keep your manners.
[Just raising their voices while
remaining seated out of fear]
This show is just full of thieves...
-What is that supposed to mean?
-All you guys do is steal...!
Don't you remember earlier?
All 7 of us are thieves!
[I guess calling you thieves is right...]
You're a thief too!
Look here...
Since you're at fault too
for not being more cautious...
Let us listen to it too from 3 steps away.
-3 steps away...
-Yeah, let's do that.
-How does that sound everyone!
-Great!  We like it!
-Just 3 steps away.  It's 3 steps!
-Fine.  Let's do that.
-Everyone, let's go.
-Since it's already in this situation...
[Now they're all about to find out whether the
first place winner has the real gold or not]
Let's pretend that I never stole it.
-Wait...
-Let's see what they say about it.
[Hand over the gold.  It has to be put
on the reader to know if it's real or not]
We'll just stay out here,
so go in and find out first.
Right now... I'm going to start
tearing through all you guys!
Yoo Jae Suk stole it!
-Captain Yoo did...
-Wait... Jong Kook, let's do it this way.
Let's just two of us hear it.
All of you, go!
[The world of herbivores that attacks
the carnivore whenever they get a chance]
You're the thief!
-We didn't do it...
-You suck the blood out of everyone.
Jong Kook.  I picked this up for you
when you were being careless with it.
[Ultimately, Jae Suk admits to being a thief]
No, this is mine.
-Jong Kook, shall we...
-Who told me that it was Jae Suk earlier?
I was the one who told you!  It was me!
You were being too hateful earlier.
[Excluding Ha Ha for telling on Jae Suk]
-Since Gary's shirt is gold color...
-Yes, I understand.  Thank you, sir!
[Ultimately, it's decided
that only Gary will enter]
Gary and I will find out then.
If you hadn't said anything,
we all could've found out!
[Sniping out of embarrassment.
The lucky star, Gary]
I will measure it now.
What are you guys doing out there?!
What are you doing?
I told you not to come up here!
Jong Kook!  Don't worry.
I'll get rid of them all for you.
Everyone get out of here!
-I didn't know that someone was in there.
-I'm really curious...
-I'll measure it now.
-Yes, I understand.
[Will... Mr. Capable's gold...]
[Be real or fake?]
[Green means real, red means fake]
[Fake!]
-The weighing is over.
-Mine too please...
[Refusing to weigh anymore]
[You've been ousted anyways...
What's the point of finding out?]
[It's gotten pretty quiet...]
[Boss Soo Hyun leaving the tent while others
are involved in weighing the gold]
[Bending his head to hide his identity
from the other campers...]
[Please don't spread any rumors...]
[Now, just like a silent shadow...
Moving to the Wondang market]
[Running Man still unaware of the boss]
Let's not betray each other over
such little things anymore.
Even the Chairman told us not to earlier!
Gary... All you did was reap the benefits
of my hard work...
I've seen the kinder side of Jong Kook.
[Complimenting the tiger]
-Gary, you know don't you?
-No, I don't know.
[Tsk Tsk... I guess you don't know that
you'll be automatically ousted later either]
This is Wondang.
[This is... The last chance of
water gun sniper attack]
[Wondang market]
[Interior of the market that's much
busier than the campground]
Those girls recognized me!
They recognized you?
[Seemed to have recognized Soo Hyun's car]
They recognized you just from the car?
[Extremely nervous]
Running Man is nerve-wracking.
See? They're not leaving.  Not leaving.
[Extremely nervous Soo Hyun.
Concerned about every eye watching him]
They're following... They're following.
They're following us.
[Oh?  They do seem to be following...]
[Panic]
[What to do?]
Why do I have to hide out in here like this...
[Miserable boss's life...]
They're texting.
They're calling their friends.
[Really?]
[We're at the entrance to Wondang market...
They're shooting Running Man, so come quickly]
I don't know... I'm sure someone will show.
Bring everyone.
I think that's what she's texting.
[The boss sure has an imagination...]
[This is big trouble...]
-Maybe we'll get to eat something good.
-It's been a long time since we've been here.
Hello... Hello.  Hello...
[Gladly greeting all the shoppers
and the workers at the market]
[What is the mission at this place?]
First... Why don't everyone
weigh themselves with me?
What?
[Weight?]
Don't be like this...!
[0.1 ton.  Measure of total body weight
with Hwa Jin PD]
[Jae Suk + Hwa Jin PD = 167.05 kg]
[Ha Ha + Hwa Jin PD = 166.10 kg]
Ji Hyo, get up there...
[And Blank Ji Hyo...]
Ji Hyo, we can just delete 100.
So just get up there.
[Ji Hyo+ Hwa Jin PD = 153.55kg]
-You weigh 53 kg?
-53 kg...?
Now... This contains $10 for your activities.
The one who comes back the quickest
with an extra 1 kg will win this mission.
[Mission-
To be the first to come back 1 kg heavier]
[At the same time...]
[Soo Hyun looking for his chance at
the opposite entrance to the market]
[Hat+mask= A total coverage]
[Infiltrating into the busy market]
Excuse me.
[As previously planned,
Soo Hyun spies from a clothing store]
[Now... As soon as
a Running Man member comes around...]
Then you can buy this,
and I'll buy the fish cakes.
But this is...
[Delicious looking acorn jelly noodles...]
-I'm about to go crazy... Here it is!
-Here it is!
[The king of snack foods, spicy rice cakes,
tempura fried foods]
I'm so happy that I'm about to go crazy.
Thank you so much.
[Happiness isn't that hard to find...]
-I'll enjoy it!
I'm going to gain 1 kg.
[But this is...]
[Inside the clothing store
by the snack stand...]
[Sniper boss, Soo Hyun!]
Jong Kook...
[Ji Hyo also heading to the same spot?]
-Hey, this is awesome.
-Is it good?
[3 people...]
The broth!
This time, at Wondang market...
I think I'm going to have to
get Jong Kook's back.
[And that back is
right in front of his eyes...!]
[On top of that, Ha Ha... And even Ji Hyo!]
[Okay... Here I go!]
[I will get rid of at least one person!]
Ugh... I'm so full.
Thank you... See you again!
[Huh?  They're done eating?]
[Now they're leaving?]
[Leaving already?]
[Tsk Tsk... For a young man...]
-Good luck selling.  Thank you.
-We enjoyed it.
[After carrying out the mission,
going to receive the verdict]
[While not even dreaming of
Boss Soo Hyun's existence...]
[They left...]
[Soo Hyun showing us the charm
of his clumsy behavior in the market...]
[Fortunately he was able to
hide his identity...]
[He failed to shoot!]
I should have moved a little quicker.
[Without a doubt...
Running Man isn't easy...!]
[Soo Hyun rushing off
to the final destination]
Yes!
167.20...!
[Ha Ha wins the mission]
What are you talking about?
[The same goes for the 2nd mission winner...
A chance to weigh out their gold]
Gary... Where's Gary?
[He can't possibly still...]
[Zero anxiety or worries]
[His peaceful meal]
This food is really good for you.
For some reason,
I have a good feeling about this.
Please take care of me, Mr. Gold Wan.
[Ha Ha's gold turtle being set
atop the scanner reader]
[Will it be real?  Or fake?]
I'm seriously about to go crazy!
For the first time in a long time viewers...
[Reading is over.  What will the result be?]
[Real??]
[Fake?]
[Fake!]
You're a hustler, aren't you?
There's no way this could be!
I picked this one out carefully!
[The final battlefield]
[SBS Ilsan Production Center]
[To make up for the failure at the market,
Soo Hyun speeds to the final location]
[The ultimate showdown with the Running Man
now starts at this place!]
Is it okay for me to go in?
[Inside a busy studio]
[Soo Hyun just leaving the place]
I feel like I'd get caught.
[Looking for a place to hide before
the Running Man's arrival]
Hello, sir!
My name is Kim Soo Hyun.
[Actor Sohn Hyun Soo who plays
the role of Bak Hong Suk in 'The Chaser!']
-What are you here for?
-I'm on Running Man.
I like that show...
-Have fun.
-Yes, thank you.
[He wouldn't...
Tell them that he met me, right?]
You can't see me, right?
[Dubbing Room]
Why you...!
I just tried dubbing.
My head...is going completely blank...
I preferred it earlier when I was
imagining my plans alone...
But I keep sweating right now...
What to do?
[Surprisingly nervous Soo Hyun...
Will he be able to take back the gold...?]
[Running Man finally arrives!]
[Of course without knowing that
Soo Hyun has been awaiting their arrival...]
What is it?
[The final mission for the Running Man]
[Find the final destination by finding
the bouillons hidden throughout the place]
[The person to put the real turtle up on the
reader at the final location is the winner]
Now, you will enter the place one by one.
[Running Man's final mission is individual]
We can go in there in the order of
the number written on the turtle.
[The Mr. Capable will be the last to go in,
since his turtle is #7]
I don't think I've found my hiding place yet.
[It doesn't seem like Soo Hyun
has found his hiding place yet!]
[Witnesses Running Man's arrival!
Now must hurry!]
[Ha Ha keeps trying to make
an anti-Jong Kook alliance]
Don't you know that we're not with you?
Let's go!
-Running Man!
-Jong Kook, fighting!
-Kim Jong Kook! Kim Jong Kook! Kim Jong Kook!
-Kim Jong Kook! Kim Jong Kook!...
-I'll see you all in there.
-Goodbye, first to be eliminated.
You'll be out with 3 minutes... 3 minutes.
Everyone, don't change your expression
and just keep looking forward.
We're going to have to get rid of him first.
[Talking about him as soon as
he's further away]
Everyone... Cheerily lift your right hand
and wave to him.
Are we going to get rid of him first?
-Is he out first?
-Don't get any blood on your hands. I'll do it.
[Not even knowing
what they're saying behind him...]
-Fighting!
-Bye.
[Giraffe makes his entrance]
-Kwang Soo! Find out Ha Ha's location first.
-Yes, Jong Kook. I'll call you.
[Compliant so there's no talk behind him]
Bye!
Since Ha Ha's good at hiding,
if not him then that one first...
While looking for Ha Ha, if I see Suk Jin,
I'll take him out first.
[The person that's not with the team,
will be plotted against behind their back]
So if we see Ha Ha first while searching
for him, then he'll be the first to go.
[Suk Jin's utilitarian role
for starting the race]
[Now Gary's turn to enter]
Since this is an ultimate rotation too...
Gary has always placed either first or second.
So we can't let that happen.
[He's going to be automatically
ousted soon anyways...]
Let the 3 of us just take care of it.
-Guys... I'll see you later.
-Okay.  Go ahead.
-We'll see you at the end.  Fighting.
-Okay.  Fighting.
-Don't say anything else either.
-Okay.
-We never will.  Don't worry.
-We'll stand here like this.
-Don't say anything!
-We won't, we wont...
-Ji Hyo, fighting!
-Don't talk about me!
You're not talking
out of the side of your mouth, right?
I've never even learned how to do that.
-You know that she has the most gold, right?
-She has too much gold.
Is she takes the gold too...
She can open up her own jewelry store.
Let's share the gold between us.
Jae Suk... It's always you and me.
[Running Man's two power house demonstrating
kindness and friendship]
-You know that, right?
-Just eliminate Ha Ha first.
And if Suk Jin happens to be in the way,
there's nothing I can do...
[Anyways, the two parting in a good mood...]
-It wouldn't be fun for you to talk alone...
-I'm not going to do that.
[Jae Suk-Jong Kook,
Will they maintain their decree to the end?]
He's won way too many times himself.
[Where's such a thing as coalition?
You live your life alone]
It's not like there are several...
There's only one gold turtle.
[Ruthless Running Man when
faced with the possibility of winning]
They all went...
They all went up to the second floor?
Kim Jong Kook, your turn to enter.
Fighting.
[But Running Man still doesn't know...]
[That right here...]
[The boss that they'll have to
go up against is in the premises...]
[And that boss...]
[Is really nervous]
I think I've lost my way.
Yeah, I remember this place...
[Ilsan SBS was where the very first
Running Man strongest held its' stage...!]
[And... This long hallway...]
This hallway...
[I remember...
What happened in this hallway back then...]
[Running Man's first survival!
Running Man's first ultimate rotation...]
Hey!  Kim Jong Kook's there.
Kim Jong Kook's there!
[Mr. Capable-Jong Kook!]
[The scene where he had terrorized them!]
[Do you remember!
That long hallway of terror?]
[The terror you felt back then...
I'll make you feel it again!]
[Mr. Capable's number 1 target, Haroro]
[What just...passed by?]
[What is that monstrous sound?]
Even though I may be like this...
A little while ago...
I played the role of a King.
But this is what I'm doing now...
[What to do...
The King's confidence is shaky...]
[All we see in front of us now...
Is a nervous...and good looking young man!]
Even if they were to see me...
They can't even see my name tag.
And I can...like this...
[Turning off the light for now
because voices can be heard outside]
It doesn't matter to me
whose name gets torn off.
Because I did it by myself the last time.
[Oh!  Soo Hyun's in there!]
[If he's discovered already,
then everything is over!]
[Was the door somehow locked?]
[Locked the door right away earlier
when it seemed like someone was approaching]
[Thank goodness...
If it hadn't been locked, game over!]
[Soo Hyun averts a crisis
with an instantaneous wit]
I almost screamed out loud...
[On the other hand, Mr. Capable searching for
Ha Ha with fire in his eyes]
[Ha Ha!]
[You're caught...!  Why you!!]
What the heck?
[He has been awakened in the same hallway!]
[Mr. Capable, Jong Kook]
Ha Dong Hoon! (Ha Ha)
[Just like mentioned,
Ha Ha escaping so that he can survive]
[Even escaping into the costume design room!]
[Ha Ha... Ha Ha!]
[There's only one target... Ha Ha!]
I'm so scared...
This is a variety show...
A variety show...
[Lately feeling terrorized...
Just what is his fate?]
[On the other hand,
Jae Suk is shopping in the wardrobe storage]
Gun Hyul...
We need to get a fall suit.
[Even though he can't buy it,
indulging in some window shopping]
A nice suit...
[Wow... Tightly packed costumes!]
Isn't this pretty?
[Huh?]
[Discovers a box with 'R' sticker!]
[What kind of luck is this
during shopping?]
[If you combine the words written
on the bouillon
you'll find out where the
final destination is!]
I just opened it, and look at this!
[He just randomly opened one,
and right in there...!]
'So'
[Jae Suk- 'Byul', Gary- 'So' discovered]
[Does Ha Ha know someone in the green room?]
[Actor Sohn Hyun Joo that met
Soo Hyun earlier!]
I'm shooting Running Man right now, sir.
[Greeting Ha Ha warmly too]
I've been watching your show...
And I'm so mad it's about to drive me crazy!
Thank you...
For watching Running Man on your busy schedule.
I mean, I guess you're watching
The Chaser, not Running Man.
But the feeling of it is somewhat similar.
We're always chasing each other too.
[But... He could tell Ha Ha about
seeing Soo Hyun earlier...?]
-Running Man is really fun these days.
-You should come on the show sometime!
[Perfect score for his senses!
Purposely saying something else
and pretending not to have seen Soo Hyun]
This is the prize...
This is gold...
if you win, this is what you get.
Really?
[It sounds good...]
-Good luck escaping.
-Yes.  Please come on Running Man.
You're the best!
I'm really enjoying you on your show!
-Don't get caught.
-Yes, sir.
[He doesn't reveal Soo Hyun's identity
through to the end]
[And this is how Soo Hyun
averts crisis once again]
[Thank you, senior...!]
[On the other hand, Yoo-ruce Willis is
looking for another bouillon...]
[He opened the door... But it's blocked?]
What is this?
Just what the heck is this?
If Kwang Soo or Gary had been here...
[If they had been here, it would have
been great to have seen their expression]
[The truth is,
they're fake doors made for drama shootings]
[They do say that a giraffe will come
walking in if they're talked about...]
Where are you going?
Did you find anything?
[Without hesitation,
searching each other's bags]
-You really haven't found anything?
-No...
-Jae Suk...
-I was just searching your back...
Why are you looking around like that?
-I'm just searching around.
-That's worse than insulting my parents!
-Jae Suk...
-What... What?
-Your jokes are a little too severe...
-Why?  I was just searching.
The last time... My grandmother just went
into her room during the 100th episode.
All the family were gathered
to watch the show and have dinner...
-I'm sorry.
-And they just went home.
[All of Kwang Soo's family were gathered,
but went home when he got ousted]
You shouldn't have let me get so close.
You should always be careful of your name tag.
Kwang Soo, come here.
Will you go in there for a moment?
[Huh?  The construction is...?]
-Welcome!
-You scared me!
What is this?
Welcome.  I welcome you to the magic room.
-Welcome...
-What is this?
-Who are you?
-It's magic.
-Where did Jae Suk go?
-Kwang Soo, come here.
[Jae Suk having fun at pranking Kwang Soo]
What is this?  Is this a dream?
[This door...]
[Working his magic...]
[...Or pretending to]
No matter how you try to open it...
The doors are everywhere...
Who are you?
What did you do with Jae Suk?
Who are you?  Just who are you?
Is this a dream or reality?!
[These two shooting a short within seconds]
Do you finally know?
-Stop!  Please stop!  I'm so dizzy!
-Do you know now?
Do you know where you are now?
The place you are at...
is a place where you can no longer escape.
-You can't escape...
-I have to get out of here!
No matter how you try to escape...
You can't...
[Slapstick's new expert, Giraffe Kwang Soo]
-No matter where you go...
-I'm going to get out of here!
Try and see if you can escape this place!
What!
Do you finally realize it?
[There's...a magic door?]
[Naive Gary arrives]
Go in there.
Slowly, slowly... Open it slowly.
[Naive Gary is 100% surprised]
Gary, it's a magical room.
[The only person that believes
that it's a real magic room]
-Did you find something?
-I haven't found anything.
What do you have?
[An awkward expression...]
-You found something, didn't you?
-What do you mean?  Found what?
[Gary's expedient face that betrays him
whenever he lies]
[Without even seeing it,
it's obvious that Gary's found something]
-I didn't...!
-Don't do that.
-Let's at least see what it looks like.
-Just show us what it looks like.
-I really shouldn't be doing that...
-Let us see it just once.
Just show us the back then.
I'll show it to you real quick.
-'So' is written on there.
-'So'?  What's that?
'So's written on there...?
[You saw that?]
[How did he see that?]
How did you see that?
[On the other hand...]
[Huh?  Soo Hyun looks frozen in place]
Oh!  Hi Jong Kook.
Oh... I'm here because I have a meeting
for a drama today.
[Is he meeting with Mr. Capable?]
I'm here because I have a meeting
for a drama today.
I'm really enjoying Running Man.
Ah, the water gun?
Well because I'm a fan of Running Man...
[Practicing for the moment that
he faces Mr. Capable]
Running Man...
I'm seriously a big fan.
So I go around with
a name tag on my clothes too.
When will I be able to come on Running Man?
There's no way this is going to work.
What do I do?
[Popular Kim Soo Hyun's weakness revealed...
His nervousness]
[Blankly staring...]
Jong Kook hasn't seen you yet?
Have you found anything?
How could you do this to me?
-You don't think I heard earlier?
-What did you hear?
-You said I should be eliminated first?
-Who did?
You did.
My people...
I didn't say that we should...
But I said there's someone who was going to...
-My people...
-Listen you.
You're crazy.
[Embarrassed]
My people...are going to call your people.
It would be nice if I could see you
with a smiling face next time.
I don't know.  Will a day like that come?
Why don't we have a meal together sometime?
I don't have the time.
I'm going to study abroad.
[The easy brother gathering this way]
Where have you been?
[Everyone gathering to share information
after being scattered looking for bouillons]
You find anything?
[Mr. Capable Jong Kook!]
[If he's caught... He's dead!]
[Mr. Capable chasing at full speed!]
[Looking as though he will chase
after him to the end!]
[A real chase that we haven't seen in awhile]
[Since Mr. Capable is only chasing Ha Ha,
the rest of them are safe...]
[Mr. Capable slowing down]
Hey... You watch yourself.  Ha Ha...
[Escaping to the costume design room again]
Dear God...
Please hear my prayers.
Is this really a TV show?
Or is this a reality?
I can't seem to tell the difference.
Please show me the way.
Is it Kim Jong Kook, or...
Or is it going to be me?
[Now... He's figured out all the places...]
[Now shall we seriously start the hunt?]
[A darkened office...]
How about here?
[Soo Hyun, finally found a hiding place]
[The bait is also complete to lure them in
from outside with this!]
Okay!
Next... If you'd stand over here.
[Telling the camera where to stand so that
it's not seen from the outside]
Please turn your light off too please.
[Gary earnestly searching for
the bouillon by himself]
[Oh!  There!]
I found it, I found it!
['Gwan']
['Gwan'?]
Jae Suk had 'Byul'...
I just found 'Gwan'...
and also have the 'So'...
Byul Gwan...? (Annex)
How does it all fit in?
Something in the annex...
The prop room? (So-poomsil)
[Oh... Not bad...!]
[To be more sure, looking for more bouillons]
[A really lucky day, Kang Gary!
All the hard work is paying off in his search!]
['Poom']
I think it's the prop room?
[Is it really the prop room as he thinks?]
[Huh?  The producers are approaching
Gary all of a sudden?]
Gary-out.  Gary-out.
[Why me?]
Why me?
What the heck...?
[All panicking at
the sudden news of Gary being ousted]
[Do you remember?
The secret to Gary being ousted...?]
[A few hours ago at Nanji campgrounds]
[Target Running Man's name tags!]
[The members that has been shot...
...will automatically get ousted after
a certain amount of allotted time]
[No one knew that he has been shot due to
the evaporated special solution]
Even if they've been shot,
no signs will remain of the solution...
[Gary being dragged away without even
knowing that he's been shot earlier]
[Everyone and even himself are all lost]
-He still has his name tag.
-Why is he ousted when he has his name tag?
He's being dragged away
because he's been ousted...
What the...
What is this?
-Why in the world is he out?
-But he still has his name tag...
Suk Jin, don't go!
[Since they don't know the reason,
the nervousness is at full force!]
Come out!
Just what is going on today?
Hey this stage...
Do you die if you get up there?
Why don't you try going up there?
[A ridiculous reasoning...]
[Easy brothers' explosive conflict]
[Competing at crucial times
when neither one of them dies]
[As if he's throwing around luggage]
How can you do this?
Wait... I don't think you get ousted
even if you get up there.
[Huh?  Gold Wan?]
[What is Gold Wan, the one that reads
the real gold for you, doing here?]
We have to get him!
Tell me if it's real or not!
[Easy brothers' full chase!]
-You can't go outside!
-You can't go outside...
Come here.
[Easy Brothers capture Gold Wan]
-I'm so glad to see you!
-You know that I really like you, right?
[The chance to find out if the gold they have
is real or fake]
-I think something's going our way today!
-Pil-Chok-Cross!
[On the other hand, Ace Ji Hyo is
searching the editing room]
[A real mental breakdown]
What's wrong Ji Hyo?
Why are you so shocked?
I drooled...
[So shocked that she even drooled...]
-You scared me so badly...
-Why did you get so scared?
-Why did you follow me?
-I didn't follow you.
I just came here to look too,
and you just happened to be here.
But you tag... If I pull on it even slightly,
it felt like it was just going to give.
Let's just get out of here.
There's nothing in there.
Let's go get Ha Ha... Ha Ha...
Let's go get Ha Ha...
At this rate, I'd rather just die.
[Mr. Capable Jong Kook]
[Target in sight]
[Just how many times is it today
that he had to go sprinting?]
Jong Kook...
I'm about to go crazy because of Jong Kook!
Where did Ha Ha go?
[Mr. Capable's shadow drawing closer]
[Uh... That dark room is...!]
You scared me!
Who are you?
Huh?  Kim Soo Hyun!
[Ha Ha really being shocked
from seeing Soo Hyun]
Look at the goosebumps I got!
I'm just so shocked!
Jong Kook is outside... Jong Kook.
[Pretending that he's shocked too
and hiding his identity]
Are you here for Running Man?
-It's really nice to see you.
-Just what is going on right now?
Why are you just coming on now?
-Actually, I've been on it for awhile.
-Really?
[Ha Ha getting excited
without even knowing Soo Hyun's identity]
So what's going on here?
If you could help me...
[Readily agreeing without suspecting anything
after being panicked by Jong Kook]
-If others find out about me, then it's not good.
-Really?
[Soo Hyun's intention is to trick Ha Ha
into helping him out]
-Without being caught, to the end...
-I'll help you with whatever I can!
Jong Kook knows that I came in here.
Since he knows I came in here, when I open
the door and he comes in here, rip his tag off.
You're the only one who can get Kim Jong Kook.
Even if I were to end up getting ousted,
you make sure to rip Kim Jong Kook's name off.
Do you think that I can do that?
[Time to carry out the plan!]
Hide... Hide.
[There you are... You little...]
[Mr. Capable advancing in his chair]
[Ha Ha succeeds in luring him into the room!]
This is a TV show...
Why is it that you're so angry?
[Just waiting for his chance...]
You're someone
who's really needed in Running Man...
And this isn't sweat from being hot,
but cold sweat from fear.
Therefore...
I will treat you to a meal sometime.
Goodbye.
I will just leave...
[He's coming out!]
[Huh!  It didn't come off!]
[It didn't come off!  Is this the end?]
[Soo Hyun doesn't let go to the end,
and succeeds in ousting him!]
[Nice, Soo Hyun...]
[Jong Kook-out!]
Sir... What I did...
What I did was very wrong.
But since this morning, Kim Soo Hyun...
(A real fan) Soo Hyun, you can stand up.
Soo Hyun, please stay with me.
I just ran in here because I got so scared
when I heard your voice...
And then Soo Hyun scared me by being here
and asked me to help him.
-What I did was wrong...
-Let's go.
Jong Kook!  You know that there's
a dinner outing after we're done, right?
Kim Jong Kook, out.
-Kim Jong Kook, out?
Who ousted him?
He just said that Kim Jong Kook is out, right?
[The shocking news
of Kim Jong Kook being ousted]
Did Ha Ha oust him?  He's the only one...
No way...
The truth is, we've succeeded.
I've wanted Jong Kook out...
[Ha Ha and Soo Hyun succeed at
helping each other out for now]
Even though what we all want is to win...
You should win since you're a guest...
And I will become your helper,
and as a prize take the turtle's back...
[He wants the turtle's shell as a prize]
[This is good since it was too difficult
to do on my own...!]
If you'll keep your promise, we can do this.
[It sounded like Ha Ha's voice...]
[Ha Ha's unfair trade negotiations]
[Huh?  the door's not opening?]
What's this?  Why isn't this opening?
Jae Suk!
Why were you doing out there?
[Ha Ha casually luring
Jae Suk into the room too]
[So it's Jae Suk this time...]
-How did you tear his tag off?
-Look at this...
-How did you oust him?
-What do you mean, how did I oust him?
[Target within range!]
-Do you know what this place is?
-What is this place?
You're getting a strange vibe, right?
[Ha Ha targeting Jae Suk first...]
Soo Hyun... Soo Hyun!
[The time has come!]
[Boss Soo Hyun mobilized!]
Hello.  Hello.
[Totally shocked Yoo-ruce Willis]
What is this?  What is this, Ha Ha?
[Jae Suk can't even talk from the shock]
Can I pull it off slowly?
[Another successful trade
between Ha Ha and Soo Hyun]
[Soo Hyun succeeds in getting rid of
Jae Suk's name tag!]
-He's been with us all day.
-When?
He said he's been going around with us all day!
Ever since you were on the boat in Gimpo.
-I didn't even know!
-You said you two were close.
Ah... Soo Hyun...
He always acts like you guys are close,
and whenever you're on TV,
he says 'There's Soo Hyun...'
I think this is the first time I've seen him
since he became a huge star.
How have you been, Soo Hyun?
[The way you call his name and your behavior
is all awkward, so how are you close?]
Whenever you're on TV,
he acts like you guys are so close!
I really had thought that you two were close!
He says stuff like
'Wow... Soo Hyun's really doing well!'
You have no idea how close we are...!
I knew something felt a little off today.
-Right?
-But I had no idea that Soo Hyun would be on.
[But seeing Soo Hyun is a welcome sight]
[Anyways, Jae Suk-Out!]
[You're really good looking...]
[Gold Wan's room where they can find out
whether their gold is real or not]
Here it is.
[Reading Kwang Soo's gold turtle]
Okay, I will let you know.
Your turtle is...
[Green means real and red means fake]
[Kwang Soo's turtle is real gold!]
[What luck is this...!]
Thank you...
[Now if I can only figure out the
final destination, I win!]
[Searching through as if it's his own]
-Tell me honestly...
-It's fake.
-What?
-It's a fake.
[The wall of distrust is back up
between the Easy Brothers]
-Yours is real.
-It's a fake.
Then why are you so territorial over it?
Look at this.
The tail on my turtle is bent.
[Suk Jin's turtle with the bent tail]
The tail on yours is still intact.
Yours must be real.
[The difference in shape of the tail
is what separates real from fake?]
-See?  The tail is dead on mine.
-What do you mean, it's dead?
What are you doing?
See?  Mine has the tail down right now
because it's fake.
See?  The tail on yours is still alive!
If yours is fake, then switch with me.
-Trade with you?
-Trade with me.
-If it's fake, then switch with me.
-Let's not switch or things like that.
[It's becoming even more obvious that
it's real from not wanting to trade]
-Yours is real...
-It's a real fake.
[What is the fate of the real gold turtle
that's in Kwang Soo's hands?]
[On the other hand, the unfair trade coalition
between Ha Ha and Soo Hyun...]
[Oh!  Soo Hyun disguised as a VJ!]
[Soo Hyun is slowly getting more and more
acclimated to the show!]
Ji Hyo!
[In order to eliminate,
approaching Ace Ji Hyo!]
I think they're trying to trick us...
Come here.
[Luring Ji Hyo into a dead end hallway...]
[She's passing by!  If she recognizes him...]
[She doesn't know!]
Then the Pil-Chok-Cross team is
deceiving everyone right now?
[Venturing even closer]
[She's close!  Close enough to touch
with an outstretched hand!]
[Ace's instinct!
Putting her back to the wall from a weird vibe]
[What a loss...]
-Let's go, let's go...
-Let's get rid of them first.
-Seriously... Promise me.
-I really promise.  Until they're out...
-Until it's all over... I promise.
-Really?  You have to promise.
[Again...!]
[Fail again with Ji Hyo moving!]
I really promise...
[If he loses this chance, he may never...]
-Really?
-I seriously promise.
[He slipped]
[Ace Ji Hyo discovers Soo Hyun!]
That's Kim Soo Hyun!
Why can't you tear it off in one shot
like a fool?
[Just then, Ji Hyo's counterattack!]
[Ji Hyo's counterattack!
Gets rid of Ha Ha's name tag!]
[Ha Ha-out!]
[Beating out of there
without even a backwards glance]
[The formidable Ace...]
[Boss Kim Soo Hyun's last ditch effort]
Ha Ha, out.
[The two who still doesn't know
about Soo Hyun's existence]
[Big-nosed brother getting greedy for
the victory since everyone's ousted]
Suk Jin!
[On the other hand, barely escaped
Soo Hyun also comes this way]
[Discovers the Easy Brothers in a fight!]
[Why are those two being like that?]
[Easy Brothers ripped away
by the greed to win]
So you're saying we'll fight to win right now?
Let's go.
[Easy Brothers' culminating conflict]
[I don't think I even have to step in...]
Tell me honestly... Your gold is real, right?
My gold is real.
[Oh... Kwang Soo's gold is real...]
[The two off to their desperate fight]
[The Easy Brothers'
not detecting Soo Hyun to the end!]
[Easy Brothers' battle]
[In terms of friendship,
The Easy Brothers' is the tops in Running Man]
[Today... I will beat you!]
[A desperate battle between two men]
[To play footsie between
two grown men is a little...]
[No matter who wins...
You're saying they have the real gold?]
[Big nosed brother who hates to be hurt]
[Even though it's funny to watch,
these two are pouring all their power into it.]
[The real gold turtle... Is mine!!]
[Not even leaving
mixed martial arts to be desired]
Hey!
[A total chaos]
[Soo Hyun slowly closing in]
[Tsk Tsk... Not even knowing that...]
[Big nosed brother in danger!]
[What tragedy is this?]
[You've worked hard... Here I come!]
Great job!
[Easy Brothers discovers Soo Hyun!]
[Soo Hyun seemed like
he was stopping for a moment...]
[But a surprise attack at the chance!]
[Drastically... And quickly!]
[Succeeds at getting rid of Kwang Soo's name!]
-What happened?  Soo Hyun!
-Hello.
Moon that Embraces the Sun?
[Without even knowing about the existence
to the end, ousted the moment they meet!]
We had a guest today?
[Finally the confidence befitting a boss!]
Race start!
[The boss is back.  Kim Soo Hyun!]
[Now if he can only take the gold
to the final destination...]
[Putting all the bouillons
that members had gathered together]
[Prop room in the annex]
[Now he just needs to make it to
the annex prop room]
[Gold reading device set in the middle]
[If it's the real gold... The lid will open]
[The real gold turtle...
Coming up with the lid open!]
[Boss Soo Hyun,
The ultimate winner takes the gold!]
[Cautious but thorough win for the boss!]
[Soo Hyun, finally facing everyone]
[Ha Ha taking the lead,
and acting as if they're close]
[Soo Hyun facing off with Running Man
in a really cool way!]
[Jae Suk acting especially at a loss]
Then give him a hug or something.
Soo Hyun...
Just come spend the night at my place.
And you can come to my house for dinner.
[Now the official close to the filming]
[With Soo Hyun's hands hitting the slate,
the filming comes to a close]
1, 2, 3.
[Giraffe being jealous of popular Soo Hyun?]
One more try with the slate.
1, 2, 3.
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Descending of a Princess-Shin Se Kyung]
[Descending story?]
[By dedicating your life...
Take care of the Princess!]
[What the heck?]
[The attack of the beast eyeing the Princess]
[What is he eyeing to come here suddenly?]
[Stop the lightening fast
attack of the beast!]
[The beast's identity that leaves no trace]
[The nation's husband, Yoo Jun Sang?]
[The beauty and the beast]