Let's go!!
Let's have a showdown!
Hey!
Quickly!
If we want to stop them...
No!
What we need now is,
Quickly, stop him! Stop him!
I must eliminate them ail.
It's 2012. The year of the dragon has started. We're wishing everyone...
Happy New Year!
Hey, after doing this, immediately everybody bends over on the ground.
Currently our viewers are celebrating the new year.
Actually we should dig a hole in the ground first before bowing.
- Hey, HaHa seems very prepared to be funny today. -Why, why why?
Your hairstyle! Hairstyle!
About that... Why did you perm your hair?
-No, it's only just a new image. -We are not interested.
What? Didn't you ask me?
Hyung!Hyung!
It's because Yoo Jae Suk hyung keeps copying me, so I wanted to have a new style.
Ah really, I am going crazy.
Look, isn’t he still copying me now?
Next week you'll also come with your hair permed!
If this hyung does perm his hair, it‘s really look very funny.
Really.
Why don't we perm our hair together? Together...
-Jae Silk oppa's hair, wearing HaHaioppa's glasses. That... -Shall we make this the punishment hairstyle?
Try wearing it now. Now!
-No, no thanks. -Just try wearing it once.
Isn't it just changing glasses?
- Just try it. -That... This isn't very difficult.
I can never wear this again, this.
Cute! Cute!
How did your eyes turn out to be like this?
No, what's wrong?
I knew it would be like this.
Which is why I said only my own glasses are suitable for me.
This is really hilarious.
No, isn't it New Year's today?
Last year. Year 2011...
Yes.
Once again, we want to express our gratitude towards our viewers.
- That's right, we are really very grateful. . -This year, we will work even harder!
Yes!
We will work even harder on the show.
Congratulations on the Daesang award.
-We-sho'uldhave received it together. -Also, that... Ji Hyo also...
We all went through the same hardships, why didn't we all receive?
Congratulations to you.
Congratulations to all of you... HaHa as well.
Hyung! Let's turn around too! Let's turn around too!
Let's turn around too! Let's turn around too!
We have also went through hardships!
Like you have mentioned, last year all 7 of you went through the same hardships.
For the anke of JI Suk Jin and Gary, who did not manage to get an award.
We have prepared our own award for you.
Thank you.
- Now, we will invite presenters to give the prizes. -Ah, there are award presenters?
Hello.
Ah, Lee Beom Soo and Hong Soo Hyun.
That's great, that's great.
Oh my god.
Hey, you stand over that side.
Hey! You really...
Do you like Hong Soo Hyun a lot now?
Today's guests are Lee Beom Soo and Hong Soo Hyun.
It is said that you will run into your worst enemy at the worst time and place.
Wake up!
This is my first time doing an outdoor prize presentation for a show.
I will not say anything special.
Why is this prize presentation conducted outdoors?
- Because it's too cold, we will immediately announce the results. -Yes, yes, yes.
SBS's Performing Arts Daesang for this year.
Soo Hyun will be announcing.
There is no need for that. Senior, you shall announce.
That's really modest.
-You are making us all so nervous. -It almost scared me, really!
Then, shall I be the one to deliver?
Yes.
SBS's Performing Arts Daesang for this year.
Ah, I’m really nervous.
Running Man's...
Ji Suk Jin and Gary. Congratulations!
-You got the award! You got the award! -Me?
I didn't hear it clearly. What did you say?
Is it really me?
Who would have such unnatural expression?
This year's Daesang.
Wow, it's the Daesang! Daesang!
Really, even the flowers are sent by our authors.
Good! Now let us listen to the winners' speeches.
-Firstly, how do I say it... -Thank you everyone.
-First, we received the prize from Beom Soo and Hong Soo Hyun. -Yes, Hong Soo Hyun,
Yes, because this is live now, so...
This year we even rode a boat. We did everything!
Ok, please give the two of them a round of applause.
It's a new year, and I will really, really work harder.
The path which we must take is still very long.
-It has already ended. -Ah. it has?
Firstly, we have to invite the two guests to the centre.
Hyung, we should invite them to the centre.
That... it has already...
Usually isn't it the prize winners who get to stand in the centre? Isn't it?
Why are you so stubborn about the centre?
No. these two are also very busy. We still have a recording to do with them today.
Today will be Cho Han Ji's race to conquer the world.
After splitting into teams. first we will curry out the frontier battle.
Let's go!!
See you at the frontier battle!
Then it will be the reconnaissance battle.
Don't you have that?
Just kill me!
Didn't you ask me to introduce her to you?
Me?
Lastly. world war.
Faster! Hey kids!
Stop Beom Soo hyung!
No!!
Please... Really.
-And the final team which conquers the world.. -This time the scale is very big.
That's right.
-Will he this episode's race winner. -Although I interrupt you every time you speak.
But there are still some friends who don't understand what is Cho Han Ji is.
That's right, that's right.
I am at least a little more knowledgeable than Mong Ji
Why? Why?
-Maybe they thought it is related to window papers. -Window papers...
-Cho's overlord Hang Woo is Kim Jong Kook. -That's right!
Leader, that's right!
Han's overlord Yoo Bang is Lee Beom See.
This, this, this, this,
You people who are immediately going on the battlefield, what clothes are you wearing?
-And even wearing a hat! Look at that curly hair! Really.. -What's wrong with curly hair?
Let‘s meet in the battle fight!
By then, don’t be afraid!
What is "meeting in the battle fight"?
It's not "meeting in the battle fight", it's "meeting in the battlefield".
This is just a variety show, why are you shouting your throat out like this?
Just wait for your death!
Weekly?
Just wait for your death in the hattle!
Then, we will begin the hattle now.
-The winning team can choose a member from the opposite team.. -That＊s good, that's good!
-To cast away. -That's right.
-How can you do this? -If it's like this, it will definitely he me on this side!
Hyung! Don't cast me away!
We cannot lose!
Can you see the hay over there?
You must run there quickly, as fast as possible.
-Following the chess board, the red flag represents Hun. -Ah, Cho Han Ji is chess?
No... It’s not  like this...
Don't we have to write Cho and Han on the chess board?
I didn't even know there was a Cho.
-Isn't Cho blue in colour? -Right.
Ok, if you guys go quickly, you will know what to do next.
When everybody has ranched, please verify.
-Ok. set off! -Let's go!
Here, here, here!
Is it here?
Oh my god, must we read this?
Find your country's flag in the heap of hay and hang it in front of your opponent's camp.
Must find the flag in the heap of hay! Flag!
Quickly, quickly!
-Do we do it like this? -Where is the flag?
There's no flag.
-Hey! Hey! -Ahhh!!
There isn't any...
Lee Beom Soo is the best!
This is the best!
Here! Here!
Hyung, grab him!
Hey! Hey!
Kwang Soo. what are you doing?
Kwang Soo, grab hold quickly!
Oh, why are you doing this?
Look for it, quick!
Where should I look?
Hey! What are you doing?
-Hey! We lifted Kim Jong Kook up! -What are you doing?
Set the flag up, quick!,
This is the first time feeling like this!
Take a picture!
It's over there!
No! No!
Hey! Kim Jong Kook!
Hyung!
Why are you doing this to me?
Ah, Soo Hyun!
Soo Hyun, wait a minute!
You can't do that.
Oppa, hurry!
Quickly guard me!
Move aside!
We won!
-They've got it wrong. -Why? Why?
It's upside down!
Quick, hit the drum! Ji hyo!
Yeah!
I can't read Hanja characters.
-I already said you have to have knowledge about Cho Han Ji. - How can you be so clueless!
No, why. Can't you read it like this?
-Ehem, so tired. -Soo Hyun.
Was it Soo Hyun? *Cough cough!* Aiyoo. I'm so tired.
* cough cough*, I'm so tired.
Because  Chu lost, please discuss who to eliminate.
You've worked hard!
Ah, really.
Do you feel apologetic to your team?
Hey, you really.
Why is he like that?
Hyung. please think about it carefully.
Hyung, you decide.
Hyung, come over here. Please decide quickly.
Poor thing, Gary.
Hey!
Oh, Ji Hyo!
-Have you decided, hyung? -Ah?
Who is it?
Him.
-Yeah! -Oh, really!
Gary will drink the poison!
We will provide the poison.
What should I do after being eliminated?
Looks like there's something. Where are you taking him?
Let go of me! First, tell me who you are? Tell me who you are!
Seriously, where are you taking him?
-Where is he taking him to? -Where is he going, really?
Look's like there's something.
Oh! We re here!
Where is this?
A school? Isn't this a school?
What are we doing here?
Ah!
What's that?
Look's like there's something there, hyung.
-It's food. -Chocolate.
-It's bread, bread. -Really?
-Do we have to eat this? -What is this for?
-That's for Cho. -And what's that for?
The food is only prepared for the winning team.
Only for us?
Wah! I really like this!
It mustitaste good!
Ji Hyo. what are you gonna eat? Here, eat this.
What's this?
Here, eat the bread.
Oppa, can we take these away?
Why can't we have some?
Seeause you tost.
This is too much.
-How can they have something to eat? -Just give us one.
-Have one. -For real?
Oh, thank you, hyung!
It's for Soo Hyun.
Our king is so cool.
-Other than the King, there's only 2 of you? -Why?
-That's a joke. -Why!
They look so pitiful.
After this game ends, there may be only two of us left.
What are you saying?
This second game is a reconnaissance.
Each team member goes against a member of the same ranking. The team vvhose members wins the most will win the game.
Yoo Jae Suk, you come out! You have the same rank as I am.
What rank are you?
-All of it! All! -Alright, I got it.
Let's officially start the first round, shall we?
Don't you think you have many returning students?
We also have someone who studies late and teacher, too.
I was born in the year 66! What of it!!
You guys don't have students born in the 60's, right?
None.
The first round is a battle of wits.
Ahh! My dongsaeng!
Me? Ahh... I'm the first one.
-Today, we finally meet one another on the wooden bridge. -Jae Suk hyung waiting!
Fighting!
-I'm not worried about you, even for a bit. -I can beat him easily.
The battle of wits is of course a battle of knowledge.
Wait a second! Wait a second!
What's this?
I'm guessing they are letter scrolls,
answer 3 out of 5 questions correctly to win.
-Victory is in our hands. -We'll win for sure! 100%!
No matter what question you choose, I'll sure answer it correctly. There's nothing that I don't know.
This one!
I really took it randomly.
Woorimal Quiz.
Is there such a word?
-5 words? -5 words.
-What kind of question is this? -It's too hard.
It's too hard. How is this a Woorimal Quiz?
Is the answer "The elders"?
Entertainment room. Entertainment room.
The elders in the entertainment rooms!
The elder Arisu!
We'll give you a hint, it's a propur noun.
It's a proper noun?
-It can be a name of a place or a name of a person. -That's right.
Oppa! Our member's name !
Ok!
Couldn't be...
Yooruce Willis!
Right!
- Yooruce Willis! - Right.
That's right! Yooruce Willis! What were you thinking?
Ji Hyo gave me the hint. I was right! I guessed it right!
Why did you give him the hint?
It's alright! it's alright!
Our member's names.
Hey, Ji Hyo. Thank you.
Hey, when can we win?
I already said it was the name of our members.
Ahh... Seriously.
Hey, I've only lost one round
What?
- General knowledge! - Oh yeah! I'm good at this.
A category I'm good at.
For 4 years, I studied... general knowledge.
The general knowledge was passed down from generations! _
General knowledge, the house rules of my home.
General knowledge is the name of my son.
My Sang Shik hyung's lifestyle. General knowledge.
He who lived well, Sang Shik hyung. General knowledge!
I won!
I love you, general knowledge.
Please be my last love! General knowledge!
It's general knowledge.
If you wear underwear. you can achieve 3C of thermal warmth,
If the whole nation wears underwear. how many percentage of thermal energy can we save?
3%?
15 percent.
-20 percent! -That's right.
Oppa. waiting!
No doubt! Quiz down, quiz down.
The great house rules of our home, general knowledge!
- Were you guessing? -He must he.
I already knew the answer.
- 20%. -Don't lie!
Don't you watch PSA's?!
1 to 1.
I'll choose.
Luck is on our side today.
I don't know which is which, it's driving me crazy!
There's definitely a nonsense question in this one.
Ahhh... Nonsense.
Do you think nonsensical questions are easy, Dong Hoon?
If you want to look then open it!
Fine, just open it up and look at the question.
Really? Then it’s onsense.
Is that so? Is this nonsense then?
Ah, hold on.
Okay.
- Oh yeah! Nonsense Quiz. -Really?
I'm really good at this.
- It's really nonsense quiz. - Oh, not nonsense quiz.
Ok! Nonsense Quiz.
Our family slogan, is Sense Sense Nonsense, which started 3 years ago.
For grooming me to a son who has such a great sense.
Thank you for all that you have sacrificed for me. Thank you mum.
My dearest grandfather and grandmother,
Who always says that I'm someone who has sense, thank you for bringing me up.
Thank you.
- What are they doing? - My sense uncle who is currently overseas..
Sense uncle, thank you!
I'm HaHa, you are Sense. Goodbye. See you next time.
Stop playing! stop playing! Let's reveal the question.
Please listen to the question.
If a lion falls into a country?
-If a lion fulls into a country? - A lion falls into a country?
-If a lion fulls into a country? -Kookie!
- Oh Kookie. -Kookie Kookie!
- Kim Jong Kook! -Kim Jong Kook!
It's not, it's not.
Please hurry up.
A lion falls into a country.
Lion soup.
If a lion falls into a soup, it must be dry.
Ryan needs to be rescued.
-5 words. -5 words?
Is it the number, 4?
Lion falls into a country.
OK!
Please answer.
-This is... -What is it?
It's nonsense right.
- Dong Hoon! - Animal Kingdom!
Right?
Lion is the King of Animal!
You saw it? You saw it?
Do you like Oppa?
- It is impossible for HaHa to lose. -It's too childish.
Guess the next one. The next one.
You saw it? You are shocked right?
It's ok. It's ok.
-You're really clever. -He's really clever.
-Is that really a clever person? -It's really clever.
Really clever.
The score is...
2 VS 1! I'm 2! This old man is 1!
This old man?
I'm 1! This perm is 2!
1 VS 2
Yoo Jae Suk please choose the next question.
It‘s too hard.
-Really didn't expect the answer to be animal kingdom. -Really didn't think of that.
-This is your last chance, Hyung. -Common Sense Quiz!
-Common sense quiz is my favourite! -Common Sense Quiz.
We'll will certainly win this round. Surely win!
Recently, most of the hanphoes have 3G 4 G.
-What is the meaning of the G? -Generation.
-Please answer it in English. -Shouldn't I answer first?
Generation!
-Right? -It＊s correct!
The Generation came from the world wrestling competition.
-X-Generation! -But I said generation.
-The generation is in English. -You must say it in English.
-But you didn't say we must answer in English. -That's why you should listen to the question until the end.
Please go there! I won!
You are the king of quiz now!
-I'm sorry. -This is crazy.
Hyung, you didn't want to be eliminated right?
The next battle will be the battle between the generals.
-If it's the battle between the generals... -Then you will he competing again!
-How many times do you want to compete? - There are still two generals there.
I'm going crazy!
Let's compete again!
-Two of you please come out! -2 people?
Really?
Is that Gary?
But, where's Gary?
Where exactly did Gary go?
Where did Gary go?
-Is this a kneecap? Kneecap? -Please open it.
What is it?
-Isn't that a barbell? -What are they going to do?
Everyone takes turn to drink the water.
-Water? -The weight will increase after each successful try.
You will be eliminated if you don't manage to finish the water.
-Only Jong Kook Hyung can do this. -I'm really not good in sports!
Me too!
You will be drinking this much of water each time.
We need to finish it?
How can we finish it?
It will be more advantageous to start first right? Or will the 2nd one have more advantage?
Pour it all in?
-Hyung, it will be more advantageous to start first. -It's good to start first?
-This is really a lot. -Is this drinkable?
-You have 10 seconds to go. -10 seconds? Wow!
-Fighting! -10 seconds right?
This is too hard. It's really hard.
Dong Hoon, you can do it!
-It's impossible. -Just do it like how you normally do. It's the same.
Just do it as per normal. It's nothing! it's nothing!
-That's right! Good, good! -Good.good!
Dong Hoon!
-Dong Hoon did it seriously. -Fighting!
-Fighting! -Fighting!
I didn't know you could do it.
-Fighting fighting! -Fighting!
-Hyung, be careful of your waist. -Don't worry.
Lift it up lightly.
-Not bad not bad not bad! -It's over.
Use your strength, use your strength! '
Use your strength, Ji General.
You can do it!
Ji General, use your strength!
Hyung, just a little bit more, a little bit!
Stop!
I won, I won!
It's over, we won!
Ji General.
-He＊s good. -I'm sorry.
What should I do? I'm sorry.
I'm sorry to you. Let's eat together next time alright. I'm sorry.
-You must be very happy right. -No I'm not. Really sorry.
This is making me crazy!
The battle between the two pretty girls from each tearn.
-Ji Hyo. -Fighting.
Ji Hyo you are too cool! Fighting!
The third match is beauty trap.
-Beauty trap? -We won! We won the beauty match!
This match is a disadvantage for me.
She's thinking to herself that she is pretty!
Hey, hey you he careful!
You are chubby! You're chubby!
You're a bully! A bully!
Other than your wide forehead, the rest is very pretty.
Ladies. choose any male members from the other team. You will win if you increased their heart beat.
-Hey, HaHa come out! -Me?
Hey, HaHa come out!
-Hey you come out! Come out! -I'm coming.
Just let him be angry!
Ladies. you have 1 minute to complete your mission. Because Ji Hyo picked first, she will start the mission first.
-Ji Hyo - Kiss him!
HaHa is very easy to deal with! He's a easy man.
Oppa, I won last time!
- An easy man? -Totally.
You are shorter than me!
Hey! Take off your hat first then talk.
-Are you wearing insoles? -Hey!
Hey! Our King Beom Soo has something to say to you.
What ?
You...
Cheap guy!
I'm seriously going crazy!
Make him angry!
Choose Ji Suk Jin or Lee Kwang Soo.
Kwang Soo.
Lee Kwang Soo! Kwang Soo.
-You know right? -Look elsewhere, just look elsewhere.
Kwang Soo seems weak!
Please wear the heartbeat sensor.
The current heartbeat of HaHa now is 100 and Lee Kwang Soo 109.
Kwang Soo is already imagining things with Soo Hyun!
-I'm your fan! -What did you say?
Ji Hyo, please start now!
Hey! You gave me a text during Christmas and New Year eve right?
You gave me a text. Do you think I would reply you?
What did I send?
-Love! -ME?
Ji Hyo! Ji Hyo!
It's right here, right here!
I swear on my life, I didn't!
-It's here -I swear on my life!
Here, look, look!
It's right in here, look.
I swear on my life! Seriously!
Dong Hoon!
Did you think I would consider you as a man if you sent that to me?
I heard that in the past, HaHa oppa asked a mutual acquaintance to set us up?
Really?
Is that true?
Why didn't you mention anything during the year and a half we've been doing Running Man?
Seriously, this is so unfair!
Isn't that why you talked to Jae Suk oppa about it?
Me. telling Jae Suk?!
I heard about it, too.
You're saying I told you about it. hyung?
I couldn't bear to say anything to Ji Hyo.
-Is that why you sent that SMS at the end of the year? -Me?! Sending you that SMS? I just wanted to tell you to eat a lot!
I'm sorry but I've never thought of you as a man.
I don't care!
Not at all, not at all.
Good job. good job.
Not at all.
HaHa's highest heart rate is...
149!
Me. telling Jae Suk?!
-I heard about it, too. - You're saying I told you about it. hyung?
Heart rate is 149.
Good job. Ji Hyo!
It's because I couldn't stand how unfair it was!
This is seriously so absurd.
If Soo Hyun doesn't raise Kwang Soo's heartbeat over 149, her team vvill lose.
Of course.
Just believe that she‘s playing you.
Kwang Soo. Ji Hyo has set up everything for you, you just need to simply kick it down.
Ok...start!
Hello, Kwang Soo.
-We're in big trouble. -We're already in trouble.
-Don't meet her gaze. -Come closer.
You mustn't meet her eyes.
Geez, it's already at 120.
Seriously, what is wrong with that kid?
You have to make eye contact when talking.
Hang on. I'm seriously going to go crazy!
Don't raise your voice.
-Do you have a girlfriend? -No.
Kwang Soo, Soo Hyun has no intention of dating you.
-Just believe that she's playing you. -No, that's not true. Soo Hyun said that she liked Kwang Soo before.
She's just toying with you.
Fix your posture.
Call me 'Soo Hyun.
While looking at me.
Soo Hyun.
Tell me.
What is this?
Hurry up and do it.
Hurry up.
Soo Hyun.
You know she's faking it, right?
Oh, Kwang Soo, look how much he likes it.
I'm so happy right now!
You guys look really good together.
You match very well.
Hey, hey. Kwang Soo!
Hyung, I want to go to the bathroom!
Give me your phone number.
She's serious.
Enter it into my phone. ^
It's not for real. It's seriously all pretend.
What are you looking at?
Give her your mother's number.
- Look how happy Kwang Soo is. - Hey, Lee Kwang Soo! Get a hold of yourself!
Yes, of course.
When?
Tonight.
Hey, Lee Kwang Soo! What are you saying, you'll call her tonight?
He's acting like an adolescent boy!
Ah, Kwang Soo.
Ok, stop. We won, right?
Lee Kwang Soo's highest heart rate is...
One hundred forty....
One hundred forty...
Give me your phone number.
She's serious.
Yeah!
Can't you give us 30 more seconds?
I guess I'll have to delete the number.
What are you saying?
She's not your average girl, Hong Soo Hyun. Definitely not.
The score is 2:1. The last facs-off is worth 2 points!
Of course!
Oh, daebak!
The Kings, please step forth.
- You can do it. - Fighting!
Fighting, fighting! Sunbaenim. fighting!
Lee Beom Soo is a hyung I really like but...
A win is a win.
I'm about to go crazy. Ah, really.
Why are you like this!
What is it, what is it?
It's slap-match.
Ah, so it's this.
We've won, we've won!
You can do it!
Fighting!
Here I go.
It‘s not going to turn over.
He doesn't know how to play slap-match!
Hyung!
End it this time!
Good! Hyung, make this your last try!
Beom Soo hyung, hit it strongly!
Ah, this is too thin.
Ah. this is too thin.
That's too thin?
I thought you were going to say something impressive. "This is too thin,"
Fighting, fighting.
Why doesn't it flip over?
- Yeah, maybe it is too thin. -I wonder why this doesn't work.
We lost.
Jae Suk hyung is really good at slap-match.
You're pretty good?
Ah. you should have done it like that.
- Why were you so bad at it? - If you hit right at the centre, it flips over immediately.
See?
The King has to now choose someone to eliminate.
Fortunately it’s not us.
It really is a relief.
Why are you acting like that?
Hyung, to be honest it's uncomfortable to be around someone older than you.
There's a lot to learn from older people.
Even so. it's still uncomfortable.
You know you're dead.
We just can't seem to stop laughing.
Ah, so much fun, so much fun.
Ah, seriously. So I can choose anyone?
We should.have won.
Kwang Soo.
Wow, really?
It's uncomfortable.
Ah, so it's because Beom Soo thinks it‘ll get awkward if he drops him.
Ah. so that's the reason.
Kwang Soo, you've worked hard.
I'm sorry, hut this is too dirty to handle anymore.
-I can go by my own will! - Bye, Kwang Soo.
I'll call you.
He's probably going to cry.
Hey, what is this?
Are we supposed to stick something on here?
What are these? We look like Robot Taekwon V.
Yeah, you seriously do.
Today's final mission location is Th is shopping mall.
The first team to find all of the hidden pieces of the Royal Seal and compile them wins.
How many?
Nine.
-That＊s a lot. -Stick the pieces that you find on your shoulders.
- Can we steal them from the other team? - Each team needs to find nine?
It becomes one seal if you collect all nine?
Ok, set off!
Hey, let's go the other way.
Yes. that's right. Ji Hyo.
Hey, let's go upstairs.
Oppa, we have to go upstairs.
Is the escalator working? Oh, it's not on?
Let's search through the second floor.
Ok, let's do that.
Doesn't seem like anything would be here.
- Oppa, are you looking for it? -Yeah, aren't there any around?
If you are just searching like that, of course you can't find it!
Hey. look at the clothes.
Oppa, can I look at this?
Of course, look at the clothes.
It's a calculator.
Thought it was the seal.
How can we find it when we don't even know what it looks like?
Who is it?
Him.
Drink the poison!
Kwang Soo...
What? Really? It is so disgusting I can't carry on with this anymore.
Kwang Soo.
VVe are giving the both of you a chance to get revenge on your team mates.
Do you want to accept this chance?
Of course! Of course!
Sure! Sure!
You are too close!
Ah, really,
It is too interesting,..
We'll do well.
We can definitely do this.
Please give us the mission.
I have been waiting for this moment for the past 6 hours.
I came after sleeping, eating and resting,
The members are currently searching for pieces of seal to he put together to win
I will now give the each of you a piece of the seal.
Then what am I?
I thought of it first...
Ah... I get it.
Oh, and...
We still have to carry out the secret mission.
What is our final goal?
Help any one of the teams to win and you can propose to share their reward.
Or get an apology for abandoning yon.
This is definitely necessary.
If you don't want any team to win...
You can dealy them till the time limit is over and win shopping vouchers for yourself,
If the both of you perform well, you will receive shopping vouchers as your reward.
We have to last till the end?
Yes.
We are the Ji team of Cho Han Ji.
Hmm? The Ji nation?
I get it.
Ji...
Suk...
Eh
We are going to complete the mission.
Oh, what is that?
That kid with good eyesight! She's going up again!
Hurry and go back down.
I came to take a look.
- Go down. -What's wrong? What's wrong?
What? I came here first.
Oh!!
You are even acting now!
Hey, where will the pieces of the seal be hidden?
Oh, a royal seal?
Oh, Oppa you found it right!
Huh?
You found it right?
No, I didn't.
You found it.
Where was it?
Hey! Ji Hyo!
No! No!
- What are you doing? -What is this?
No!
Hey, where did you go?
What?
Oh, did you find it?
No.
Ah! Ah! Look at him!
- Hyung, there's nothing. -Let me see.
-I don't have anything. -Let me see.
Let me see.
Search for it carefully, you should be able to find it.
Oppa, please let me take a look.
Hyung, they found one.
He sticks it on his left chest.
Hide it properly!
It was well hidden but I saw it because of Soo Hyun.
Tell me, it was found out because of Soo Hyun ssi.
Hyung.
The garden is like this, and it was placed at this area.
What, a soap?
I got a shock.
Oh, it's here.
Wow, this...
Should we hide? No one knows we are here.
Someone's coming.
If someone comes over, pretend we are shopping.
Hey! Who is that? Kwang Soo! Gary!
There must he something going on since they are running away.
Come here! Come here!
What's happening?
Oh! It's Gary's voice!
Where is Kwang Soo?
You guys!
Hey Kwang Soo!
- What's happening? - What are you doing!
What's with them?
Hey! Where were the both of you?
Oppa! Gary oppa's shoes.
What's inside?
There's nothing.
In the shoe?
No, there's nothing.
We were here less than a minute ago.
- What are you trying to do? - That hyung...
What did we do wrong to have this happening at the beginning!
He tried to catch us the moment he saw us!
Take out your foot, quickly!
What?
Take out your foot!
What are they doing? What's wrong?
Give me a moment!
Stop moving!
Oppa, there's something in Kwang Soo's pocket.
No, it's just a pocket.
Noona, how did you do this? It is stuck there on purpose?
My name tag is on your hair!
Ji Hyo, what are you doing?
How did it end up on your hair?
- Ah... It hurts... - What is this?
- Hey, Ji Hyo. - Look at this.
- This is possible? - What is this?
Ow, it hurts.
- Hey, what are you doing? - Take off your shoes and socks.
- We just got. here. - Quickly, just take off your shoes and socks.
- Why would 1 take off my socks? - Take them off.
Where did you come from? Where were you?
We just got...
Do you really want to see me go crazy?
- Hey. -Hyung.
- Take off your socks. - Hyung. I...
Take off your socks.
Hey!
He really bit me!
Hey, you really...!
- Noona, I'm sorry! Sorry1! - Ji Hyo...
Oppa! Look, he really hit me!
- Hey! How could you really bite me! Where are you going? - Hey!
You..!
He really hit me!
See this?!
Not only does he put me in a armbar...
Come in.
Please help me check if my scalp is bleeding.
Please stick on my name tag.
It's a habit, ripping off my name tag.
- Kang Gary! -Yes?
- Where were you? -What?
- Do we have to find this? - Hmm?
Do we have to find this?
- What are you doing? - I'll find it for you and give you the victory!
- Really? -Yes!
Why?
What do you mean, why? That team betrayed me, so I'll help you out, hyung.
- Do I have to find this, hyung? - Yeah.
- I guess I gotta start looking. - But what are you doing?
I've come here to help you, hyung. As a phoenix lollol!
Hey!
- Hyung! If you say, "lollol" I'll come. -I think you're acting, hut I'm not sure what you're acting.
What acting?! I’m, hyung.,!
He's acting, but what...?
Find the lollol! Lollol!!
What is he up to?
Hyung, no one's upstairs?
Yeah...
Just what is he up to?
Lollol!
It's dangerous,
-So instead of where people can go on two feet, let's go to the higher floors. -Yes.
Why... why is he...
Why are you running away?
- Why are you running away? - Noona.
Yes?
I＊ll call!
I received your text.
Before, when we exchanged numbers...
I saw he had sent a text.
I saw you sent a text with a heart?
I saw you sent a text with a heart?!
What are you doing? What are you doing?
I don't know. I just came here.
I just came.
Soo Hyun. Come quickly and let's talk with him.
- No, no. Please don't concern yourself with me. - Yeah.
- Please lift up your shoes! Your sole. - Yeah,yeah.
- Let me see. - What will you do for me if 1 do?
-You shoes, quickly. - A phone call! Tell him you'll call him
Tell him you'll call him. You can call him now. can't you?
I want to pick it up here by myself.
Oh, noona!
Where are you?
I think I‘ll be a bit late.
I... I'm Tate, aren't I?
I'm tired of waiting here.
Wait a little hit longer.
I‘ll wash up and go.
Your unmade face is more manly.
The way you are is good.
Noona...
I'm sorry.
Don't change your socks.
I won't.
Just come. I want to see you.
It's OK even if it's just a minute. Please.
Please, really.
Let me smell your feet for just one minute!
Where are you? I think he ran away.
-He what... Where did he go? -He went upstairs.
Ah... Seriously...
-He must have something on his feet. -He does, he does.
He has something.
Something on his sole.
Yes, noona...
Where are you?
I'm., in front of my house.
Let's talk for a bit.
Something wrong?
No, I have something to say.
Then I'll be waiting at the place we met.
I'm here.
You really are a bad man.
It's so hot.
-Did you find something? -No...
Well, I found one.
You found one?
Oh? Yeah...
It's OK. I'm already...
I'm not your enemy. I won't hurt you.
Well continue to meet as we continue to act and since we've exchanged our contact info, we'll get along, right?
If we want to improve our relationship, you need to tell me, right?
For you only, noona... I'll show you.
Ye..aah!
-Will you keep my secret? -Okay.
Please give it to me.
-What, no., this isn't... -What is it?
I have to hold onto this. This is my only weapon.
Gimmmmmme...
Quickly, give me!
This feels weird!
Wait!
It feels like we're the only two here in this space!
-But if I give this to you. I'm done. - Why? Why are you done?
-I only have this one thing. But I don't need this at the end. -Why? Yeah?
I'll give it to you later.
-Later when? -Later, I'll definitely give it to you, noona.
Promise.
-Can you do that just once more? - What?
That...
No! Quickly!
Aaaaang- Quiiiickly!!
Quickly!
-Before it's over, I'll give it to you. -OK, now promise!
We're like this right now...
Before you get married...
-When you go to purchase... -You think?
Do you like massage chairs?
Massage chairs... are good.
Do we need a massage chair?
I'll be your massage chair for the rest of your life.
Do you want a son? Or a daughter?
While we were searching for this.
Do you think Gary and Kwang Soo are doing something?
That level of deduction, hyung, do it mysteriously.
That level of deduction, hyung, do it well.
Ah, this, really...
These items...
These women's clothing...
-It＊s so hard to find it! Because it's hidden in weird places... -They made it too hard. While we search for these.
What?
-Where was it? -Hey, it was right here.
Where was it?
-Did you search here? -Yeah.
I passed by here lots of times.
Are you sure you're not a fool?
-Why? -It was right here.
It was here?
Hey, Kwang Soo.
You hid it well?
-I nearly got mine stolen. -Me too, me too.
What are you going to do?
I have a girl I like.
Soo Hyun?
How could you trust someone at your first meeting?!
-The truth in her eyes... -It's the 80th episode for me and Ji Hyo!
It's the SOth episode.
Don’t be shaken by a girl now, understand?
What do you want to do?
Do you want us to win?
We definitely have to go together. Hyung, we're definitely...
But, before, honestly...
Gary hyung!
Yeah?
- Hyung, why aren't you picking up your calls? - Dong Hoon.
I sent a text, Kwang Soo.
Gary hyung!
I'll leave first!
Hey, Kwang Soo!
Kwang Soo!
-Hey! - Yes, hyung?
Get a hold of yourself!!
Just a bit... I got an important text.
Hey!
I can't win.
I don't have anything. I can't even win.
If I had something.
I'd give it to you.
Why? Why is it like this?
- It's because my leg is in pain. - I got it.
You have to believe me, Dong Hoon.
Ah, why won't you let me see?
There is! Inside.
There's nothing.
Go back.
Did you see Kwang Soo?
Hey, l really like you.
There's obviously something inside.
He shoved it back in to conceal it.
I'm asking you what this is.
It's swollen. I hurt it it, during the games earlier.
It's right here.
This is ours...that's, nothing at all.
It's my money, my emergency funds!
- It's my emergency funds. -Hyung.
Before anyone finds out, hide it under your sole.
I got it.
You got it?
Aren't you admitting it by saying that?
Hey Dong Hoon, keep it a secret.
Ah, of course.
Hey, let's hurry.
- There's no one. - This won't do.
- Because of.this... -Huh?
I'm so stressed trying to hide it.
Ah, what sort of concealment is this?
Ah, please hide it properly. Iiyung,
I thought nobody would be able to find this, who would know?
Who would have known, it's too funny.
Hey, I already let you see it.
Don't laugh, this is so important.
That's why.
But tell me honestly.
Earlier, my country betrayed me.
So I'm going over to that team to offer my help.
- Help me to get over.7- Ok, ok.
-Hyung. - This is really a secret.
Ah, of course.
You... agree, right?
- Ah hyung. I'm unconditionally... - For me, I won't even be able to benefit anyway.
Ah. exactly.
I'll just, let you win, honestly, so we can split the prize.
Ah, definitely. I'll give you all of it.
Ah, not all of it.
I ll give you everything.
Look, there are nine pieces in total, ok?
If there are nine pieces, this is just one of them.
Exactly.
Without mine, they just can't win.
Of, of course.
- Do you know what I mean? -I know,I know.
Although I have no way of winning, they still need me.
Ah, of course.
- So you have to treat me better. - Ah, definitely.
Jeez.
Don't forget.
I got it, ok.
- Fighting! - Fighting, fighting.
There is still 30 minutes before the mission ends...
Gary and Kwang Soo, they seem to have something to do before the given time.
It seems like whoever outlasts the other will just win.
Then would there be something else?
Do they have to carry out obstructions?
- If the country isn't unified then they'll win. - Not unified. If we're not unified.
They'll just win. they'll get the reward.
It seems like this is it.
-I really don't have it. - You must have it.
Hyung. I don’t have It. I was wrong.
Let's discuss it.
- Huh. Idon't have anything. - No, just once...
Don't do this. Get rid of the suspicions around you.
- Get rid of what, hyung? - The suspicions.
Ah, this is so weird, hyung.
Go in, go in.
- Ah, I really don't have it. - Go in.
- Jeez! I really don't have it. - Hang on, Take it off quickly.
-I don't have it, I don't have it. - Give it quick.
Oppa, now take off Kwang Soo's...what's nearest, nearest to oppa.
Some, some hidden areas, near the mic, the mic.
There's nothing.
The mic area, check the mic.
This humiliation, I‘ll definitely avenge it!
Gary hyung!
Why isn't there anything?
Kwang Soo. weren't you really holding on to it?
Take it out for hyung to win this once.
In here?
Oppa, it’s here.
-The water's all finished. -No!
No!
The water's been drunk!
Hey, so it's here.
Ah, it's here.
-It's here. -Found it, found it.
Hey, seriously.
-There is something,pppa. for real. -It's been snatched away.
I promised Soo Hyun noona.
Sorry, Kwang Soo.
You really look like a ghost.
I don't need anything else!
-Seems like hey got another one again. -Jeez, it couldn't be.
Hey.
Hey, what are you doing?
Get it.
-Ah, my shoe... -Hey. get it quickly.
Where is it?
We're very curious about your feet now.
I didn't do anything.
-There's something here, there's something here. -Get it quickly!
-Hyung, I said I'd really help you! -I got it, I got it.
There's still one more, where is it?
-Oppa. -There's still one more.
One more is still with Gary oppa.
Right, that's right.
-Hyung, I said I'd really help you! -I got it,l got it.
Hurry, find it quickly.
This smell...so why, why are you helping us?
-Ah. I'm really in it for the reward so I want you to win! -No, doesn't seem like it.
But we...oppa, I'm curious about what we do after we find this.
So what do we do after we find this?
We have to do something for sure.
-But where to go with this... -Hey. we don't know this.
Now you treat me like this.
You'll clearly regret it.
Hey, hey, then what do we do?
You were holding on to it.
You had one with you.
Hey, hey Kwang Soo, this is really true.
-If you were holding on to it, what would you do now? - Hey.
Why would I let you go, like a fool?
He's truly the hyung.
Ah. it's a, it's a famous quote.
Oh, hyung has already apologized so many times.
Haha...
A person's greed seriously, knows no bounds.
As a special allowance. I'll give you a chance for revenge.
-Ok. - Will you accept this chance9
-We accept, we accept. -Of course, of course.
-Sure. sure. -We accept it.
Also.
This;
If you think you're in an extremely important situation, open this.
This might turn the tables of the battle for you guys.
-Turning the tables of the battle. -It's an advantage.
Turning the tables of the battle.
-This is too advantageous. -This is a reversal of the battle.
This is totally important.
Gae!
Gwang!
Cross!
Ok, now...
The final mission location, an ice rink.
Do you have a pocket?
You won't be separated from me right?
Never, lose this important item.
Come here, Kwang Soo.
-Hey Kwang Soo. -Come here.
Jeez, going here and there. What's all this, hyung?
I'm a free man, I can act freely!
-Kwang Soo. come here. -Come here, come here.
Cool off before you go.
-Cool what off? -Come here.
-Ah, after my pants were taken off. what's there still to cool off? -Come here, come here.
There can't he a division between people.
You're on our team.
-Come here. -This, this team?
Huh?
Wherever you go that won't change.
What colour clothing were you wearing in the morning?
Red.
-You see, you see. -That's right.
-Kwang Soo. why are you like this? -I'll give you that thing, that thing.
-Thinking about it. I... -It's a misunderstanding.
-Whatever happened in the morning... -Right.
It was just a happening.
Ok?
We're really sorry about earlier.
Well. Beom Soo hyung too...
We just wanted to get the upperhand.
That's right.
-I didn't know. - Ji Hyo, you too.
Kwang Soo, I'm sorry.
That's right.
The K word, the K word.
That's right, I should take this.
Huh?
Take this to the third and fourth floor.
These are...
-So. this is 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6... -Are you sending me on an errand?
You're so funny.
Was Tom Cruise an errand boy in that movie? Hey, seriously.
Do you like doing that? Who will like it?
Ah, so you felt that way.-That's what you felt.
Really...
It's quite cool to be an errand boy then.
Got it?
-You're so cool today. - Hey. you're really...why are you so cool?
Do this action, like this. It's looks the same as 007.
Your face has the feel of a missionary.
There is no need to go to the fifth floor.
Because...
You phone is ringing. Have you been on the phone?
No, there was a recent phone call. It's Soo Hyun noona.
-There is a call now. -Pick it up, pick it up.
Noona!
Oh...
Where are you?
I am currently at...
First floor, first floor...
I am with the red team.
Why are you there? Come here, quickly.
Where, where?
Third floor.
The way noona is speaking... Third floor-' I like it a lot.
I will go to the third floor immediately.
This kid is already trapped. Trapped in love.
I remember a line.
Fall in love with the enemy's spy...
In the end, did the spy succeed?
Died!
-This is too much. This is really too much. -Kwang Soo, that's only a movie, only a movie.
I just need to complete the mission.
-That is only a movie, only the contents of the movie. -It is only the contents of the movie.
In 007, it is the bong-girl that will land you in trouble.
Today. Hong Soo Hyun is the Bbond Girl.
It's Bond Girl. What's Bbond Girl?
-Isn't it understood? -Kwang Soo, fighting!
-Kwang Soo. there is not much time. - Feel.
Feel.
Cross
Now, we found all that should be found right?
-Did it get stolen? -No, no...
Really?
Kwang Soo, you have been moving around secretively.
It's as if you are hiding from us.
You saw wrongly. It has nothing to do with me.
Why did we see it wrongly? Do you know how unnatural you are?
This is the better one...
'It has nothing to do with me.'
Kwang Soo is like that right now, just like that.
What should we do?
-Stop the fight. -During the call, where were;you?
What are you going to do? Quick.
Did you see that?
-I know something. -What?
-I know something. -What do you know?
I want to know which team is more advantageous before helping that team.
If you snatch it, we will give you the prize.
Quickly go snatch it.
It is easy for you to go there. Snatch it within 5 minutes.
-Then hyung, I have to bring something there. -Quickly return after snatching it.
Bring Soo Hyun's heart there.
Wait a while.
Stop recording first.
Is it obvious?
Is it obvious? It's not obvious right?
Now we need to snatch those over, really.
We need to know the final location.snatch those over and rush over there.
Those two persons seem to know the final location.
Give Gary 50 percent of the prize.
To"let him reveal the final location.
Let‘s ask.
Gary! Come here for a while.
It's really tiring.
Gary.
We will give you a bigger share of the prize.
If you tell us where we should go this game will end immediately.
We are helping you too. What do yon think?
Ah, I get it.
Let's go to 'a place where you will slip on the iceT
Are there-a?iy here?
There should be.
A place where the ice is slippery.
Ice rink!
What are you doing up there? Come down!
We are making a decision now.
So, just like what we were saying just now.
We need each other.
Let's make a bet using the piece and decide using flip the paper game.
So the two teams are ending it here once and for ail right?
Good, come down.
Quickly pass it to him.
Let go. 1,2,3.
There are 10 minutes left to the end of the mission.
Let's go straight away now.
Quickly, quickly.
Kwang Soo, come quickly.
They ran away.
Hey, hey hey!
Soo Hyun, quickly stop them! Soo Hyun, quickly stop them!
Kwang Soo! Run quickly!
Where are we going?
Where is it?
Do you really know?
Ah, really! Making use of others' trust!
It seems like we know the final location!
We know it.
You know it?
Hey, hey! Where is it?
Come here quickly! Come here quickly!
Hyung, what about that paper?
Soo Hyun, hold on to them.
Where is the key? Take it out quickly!
Hey, take it out quickly!
It's with hyung! Search Gary hyung! Search Gary hyung!
Do you prefer a son or daughter?
It's funny.
Isn't it this?
Oppa, come here quickly!
Oppa, quickly!
Quickly paste them!
How do we do this?
Why did you do that?
Here, here!
It's done! It‘s done!
Well done, well done!
-To put it accurately, there is another person who helped us. -That's right.
The prize for the team who won is superior grade Korean beef.
The team that won just needs to take it.
-if you recognize their contribution, you c.1 n transfer the prize. -Ah, no.
Thank you!
-Ah! This... -Ah, we did that to let you all in!
It's fine if Ji Hyo eats it with me.