This is Absolute Ddak-ji.
[Without regards to the bad weather.]
[Searching for the method to win
the Absolute Ddak-ji battle.]
[The battle within the family.]
[Running Man Ddak-ji race starts now!]
[One rainy day in September.]
[Seoul Jung-gu 'A' Hotel]
Hello.
[Kwang Soo,
the first to arrive on location.]
Mrs. Go Dong Wan?
[Huh?]
[Mrs. Go Dong Wan family gathering.]
Hello.
- The third son, Lee Kwang Soo.
- Why am I the third son?
- I'm the third son?
- Yes, you're the third son.
[Mrs. Go Dong Wan's third son,
Lee Kwang Soo.]
Where is... Mrs. Go Dong Wan?
[The main character, Mrs. Go Dong Wan
is nowhere in sight.]
Where is my Mother?
[Jae Suk and Gary arrive soon thereafter.]
Mrs. Go Dong Wan's family gathering?
Brothers... you've arrived.
- What is this?
- Gary is the second son.
I'm the second?
I'm not the youngest?
[Mrs. Go Dong Wan's second son,
Kang Gary.]
The older cousin, Yoo Jae Suk.
I'm the second son's older cousin?
[Second son Gary's older cousin, Jae Suk.]
Where's my Mom?
First born son, Kim Jong Kook,
take your seat.
I'm the first born son?
[Mrs. Go Dong Wan's first born son,
Kim Jong Kook.]
How is Jong Kook the first born son?
All of you, keep it down.
- Hey you...
- What do you mean, hey you?
[Arguing about the authority within
the family from the moment they meet.]
I'm your older cousin.
Seriously...
Jae Suk, I'm sorry... I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
It's because we all look alike.
[Is it because it's been so long since
the last family gathering?]
I was just confused because everyone
looks so similar to one another.
How can you tell us to keep it down
when this is a family gathering?
Let me get this straight,
you're the first born
and he's the second born, and the third...
you're all brothers then.
The three of you are brothers.
- The three of you are...
- Brother! Brother!
- Brother!
- The three of us are brothers?
Why can't we recognize each other though?
- We're brothers...
- Mother is Mrs. Go Dong Wan...
- and the three of you are brothers...
- Then we have the same Mother?
- Your Mom...
- Mom, where are you?
- Our Mom...
- Wait a minute...
[Third born Son, Kwang Soo's
older cousin, Ji Suk Jin.]
[First born Jong Kook's younger cousin,
Ha Ha.]
And there are three Daughter-in-laws!
Jong Kook,
I think we all have wives today.
- It seems like it.
- Wait, then this is my wife's seat?
- My wife?
- Huh? Then one of the Daughter-in-laws...
Wait! There's Ji Hyo here... Ji Hyo...
- Then her seat is over there for sure!
- We've been over for a long time!
- It's already all over!
- Ji Hyo's seat is over here.
[The person to resolve the question
at stake arrives.]
- Ji Hyo! Sister Ji Hyo!
- Where is her seat? Where does she belong?
I was never married to that woman!
- Hey, Kwang Soo...
- I've never had a son like you either!
[Seems like she wants to play
the role of the Mother.]
I never had a son...
I mean, a husband like you either!
- You're the second born son's wife.
- Okay!
[The atmosphere of a family in mourning...]
We're already divorced!
[An explosive outburst]
What kind of a thing is that to be saying
at a family gathering?
So you guys are back together then.
This table is ruined...
the second born son is ruined.
- Why did you guys divorce?
- The love battle team.
You guys shouldn't be
like that at a family gathering.
[Extremely upset older cousin]
Then it means that
this table has no female guest.
This seriously is upsetting.
This is so disappointing... seriously!
Why is the older cousin lusting after
the Daughter-in-law?
[Older cousin Jae Suk...
lusting after the Daughter-in-law?]
This family just won't do!
Since we're divorced anyways...
why don't the two of you date then?
- That's not it...
- What kind of a family is this?
This family is just like a korean drama!
- Why are you after the Daughter-in-law?
- I told you, that's not what I meant!
If you're the first born of this family,
then you should act like it!
What do you know about being
the first born?
[Fault of workout-obsessed first born for not
paying enough attention to the family?]
It has to be chaotic like this
for it to really feel like the holidays!
Now that I think about it, why are all of our
last names different when we're brothers?
[The secret behind the different last names.]
This is an outrageous drama family.
[The hateful younger cousin.]
We're all still family...
Ji Hyo, I'm your older Brother-in-law.
So what do you want me to do about it?
[The second Daughter-in-law who's already
figured out the family atmosphere.]
You're just a middle-aged woman now.
Our family has come to a ruin because
of the second born son's family.
- What did you say?
- You heard me.
Why are you being like this?
We can just get back together then.
[Second born son declaring a reconciliation?]
The first Daughter-in-law has just arrived.
My... my wife?
That's Jong Kook's wife, right?
Jong Kook's wife...
- Honey!
- Sister-in-law!
Come on in, Sister-in-law!
[A vivacious entrance]
[The first Daughter-in-law
is none other than...]
[City woman actress, Yeom Jung Ah!]
[The husband and the younger cousin-in-law
bowing down in greeting.]
I'm the first Daughter-in-law.
The head Daughter-in-law of the family...
[The head Daughter-in-law overflowing
with her dignified majesty.]
I did good to protect my family.
The glint in her eye to begin with...
it's not your average glint.
It looks fierce.
Our older sister-in-law is
the one that leads this family.
- This is your husband... your husband.
- Yes, I like that.
[Satisfied with her husband
from the first meeting.]
- Jong Kook... your wife is here.
- I'm so very happy.
- I'm not a scary person.
- Yes.
She is a very nice person.
All of you are dead now.
Look at how fierce she looks.
Next... what about next?
Then the third Daughter-in-law
must be really young, isn't she?
Idol, Idol...
This is so funny...
Why is it funny?
Don't you think it's a given? Between
the first and second Daughter-in-laws...
[Getting curious about
the third Daughter-in-law...]
The third Daughter-in-law has just arrived.
She's here?
[Getting a bouquet of flowers ready.]
Honey!
[The emotional moment of a
couple's reunion.]
[She is none other than...]
[Cute lady actress, Jeon Mi Sun!]
[Both of them in shock.]
- Hello.
[Awkwardly greeting one another.]
He doesn't look very thrilled...
[Totally caught?]
No, it's not like that!
- That's not what I meant...
- You were so happy about this!
That really isn't what I'm thinking!
- But why are you the third...
- You're the one who dated her!
You dated her because you loved her!
You're the one who wanted
to marry her!
You went against the family's wishes
because you were so in love...
Remember how much beating you took
from me because of all that?
- I took a beating?
- Yeah!
[The love that beats against
all the odds.]
Since the third Daughter-in-law
has also arrived...
we need to greet our family's older cousin.
Brother!
[Second son Gary's older cousin's
entrance.]
Please come on in!
[The identity of the older cousin is...]
[None other than Yoo Hae Jin!]
[Shouts of joy?]
[Extreme welcome]
- I'm a huge fan!
- Thank you.
He's the most popular.
[Older cousin, Hae Jin receiving a more
enthusiastic welcome than the female guests.]
The first Daughter-in-law
is very angry right now.
She normally gets jealous over women...
It really sounds loud and noisy
even from outside.
[Now all of Mrs. Go's family has gathered.]
[Really look to be blood relation to Gary?]
- They really look alike!
- They really do!
His eyes... his eyes are so slanted...
- It's so good to see you, brother!
- Our eyes really do look alike!
Then... with Hae Jin today and
first Daughter-in-law, Yeom Jung Ah...
and Jeon Mi Sun make up our family?
The reason why all of Mrs. Go Dong Wan's
family has gathered here today...
will be revealed by legal counsel Attorney Go
from Mrs. Go's 'Go corporation'.
What attorney?
[Attorney Kim Hyo Jung -
Go Corporation's legal counsel?]
- Attorney...
[The entrance of a real attorney which has
never happened in history before.]
I will reveal to you the reason for asking
all of you to gather here today.
Sit down.
- What is that now?
- There's something.
[Mrs. Go's reading of will and testament.]
Mom!
No!
[Shock?]
What I can't get over is...
we're her kids and we didn't know?
This is a reading of her will and testament
before she passes.
- Oh, that's better!
- Doing this ahead?
It would've been really heartbreaking
for me...
Because she had an urgent meeting today,
I'm here for her in her place.
Mother is still living young,
for her to be in a meeting.
[I guess...
anything's possible with this family.]
I will reveal her will and testament.
My beloved sons, listen carefully.
Your Mother doesn't have
many days left here on earth.
It seems the time has come for me to inherit
everything I've worked for down to you.
As you all know, I have dedicated
my whole life into making Ddak-ji's.
What did she say? Ddak-ji?
Whether it rained or snowed, all year
round, my life revolved around Ddak-ji.
And just in time,
through my own secrets...
[After countless number
of years and failures...]
I came up with Absolute Ddak-ji that
can't be found anywhere else in the world.
[Absolute Ddak-ji]
Pass through the various gateways today
and return to the final location
and I will pass down my greatly cast fortune
to the son that wins the Absolute Ddak-ji.
What kind of a Mother is that?
- Ddak-ji? The ones you flip over?
- Yes.
What kind of Ddak-ji is she
talking about?
The person who flips over the Ddak-ji...
This is the will and testament that I've
just read to all the sons...
Depending on the method used for it...
[Professional vernacular...]
And this will is to be followed
exactly the way it is written and stated...
Now that we're getting the legal jargon...
[Since she really is a real Attorney...]
She sounds so natural and comfortable
saying all that...
What are you saying that we're
supposed to do with the Ddak-ji?
When it comes to Ddak-ji, it's me.
[The first born son's provocation?]
When it comes to Ddak-ji,
you know it's me.
Why is it you when it comes to Ddak-ji?
Did you not see what happened
the last time?
[The King of Ddak-ji, Jae Suk who lost without
even having to play once previously.]
- Ddak-ji...
- As it is stated in the will...
the family that passes all the obstacles
and beats it at the final location
will inherit the fortune.
- We're playing this as a team, right?
- Yes.
Here is the letter that Mrs. Go has prepared
for the representative of each family.
[My beloved sons, go to the flea market in
Sin-Sul-Song and obtain a good Ddak-ji. - Mom]
[Chuseok special, Ddak-ji Race - Start!]
- How do we get there? By bus?
- I think we have to take the bus.
[The rain is pouring down...]
Wow! It's raining down so hard!
[Following the wishes of Mrs. Go
who's lived frugally all her life...]
[Using public transportation all day.]
[Checking the bus route to the flea market.]
- Is that the route?
- I can't see... maybe because of my old age?
- There it is! Right here!
- Off! There it is!
- Number 421...
- I should've brought my glasses.
[Mi Sun surprisingly not being very good
at spotting the signs...]
[On the other hand...]
- Shouldn't we be running instead of walking?
- No, it's okay.
I know this is plain to see,
but you've joined the best team.
- Our team is most likely to win...
- Okay.
Yoo Hae Jin and Jeon Mi Sun don't
seem to be very good at things like this.
I get the feeling that Hae Jin won't be
very good at things like this.
- He can't do it.
- He has no competitive streak!
- Oh my... it's really raining down!
- Oh my goodness!
We should be wearing rain boots like
Ji Hyo on a day like this.
- But... it has an appeal of its own.
- I know.
[Hae Jin leans more towards romanticism
than competitiveness as others guessed?]
We can share a conversation...
I don't think I'm totally getting the program.
The way I see it, you and Gary are
very similar in so many ways.
The way neither one of you really
understand the nature of this program.
It's been two years for me,
and I still don't really get it.
- Just walking around is nice...
- And run when we're told to run.
Yes.
I don't know if it's because it's Autumn...
but look at all the bank on the ground.
[Bank= Gingko?]
- There are even seats open!
- This isn't going around in a circle?
Hello.
There are enough seat in the back.
[Huh?]
[Kwang Soo and his family have missed
their stop for the flea market.]
[And the gusts of wind with rain...]
Oh no!
[Giraffe's destroyed umbrella.]
- Hurry up!
- What's wrong with you?
- Let's hurry up!
- Let's just get going.
Here, I'll share it. Here.
[Sharing the umbrella with
his wife, Mi Sun.]
You really are a married couple.
[Kwang Soo and his wife walking together
under one umbrella in the rain.]
Wait... why don't we rest here for a bit?
Let's rest for a bit.
[As long as they're together,
even weather like this can be a memory...]
- Jung Ah...
- Yeah?
This is the first date you and Jong Kook
had in a while...
Why don't you hold his hand
or something?
- Do you want to hold hands?
- Excuse me?
[Holding his hand after asking
him for his opinion.]
Of course, I do.
[Since they're a married couple for
the day, this much is...]
Hey...
- This is the place.
- Where?
See? That's the place.
Seoul Flea Market.
[Even in this situation,
sighting the signs perfectly.]
[Immature little brother looking
for romance.]
- Here it is.
- Ha Dong Hoon, seriously...
Since you're getting rained on,
I'm going to do this.
- Why is he...
- Since you're getting rained on...
Since you're getting rained on,
I think I should do this.
That's just so beautiful!
- Is this the place?
- I think this is the place.
You look so cute together!
[Haroro feeling jealous
of Jong Kook and his wife.]
- You look so awkward!
- No, I'm fine!
This is how you're supposed to do it.
I know that you're pretending otherwise,
but I'm sure you're a little embarrassed.
Look at them taking care of one another.
You guys have always loved each other.
[Arriving at the Flea Market.]
[Seoul Folk Flea Market]
Mi Sun's not here yet?
- I thought she would be here by now...
- I bet they're out walking around.
- You're the first ones to have arrived.
- Seriously?
No way!
Let's open it up and take a look.
[My Sons,
I see that you've made it here.]
The sooner you succeed the mission
that I give you here
you can obtain the better Ddak-ji.
For the first mission,
family teamwork is very important.
[While riding in the boxcar together,
go buy the items listed in the time allotted.]
[Detailed explanation will be given by
Driver Kim on site.]
[Flea Market with so many things to
be looked at and bought.]
[The mission to go out and find the items
that are hidden within the site!]
[Family teamwork is essential while
moving around in a boxcar together!]
Do you see the Jae-gi on the table?
You have to spin around in a circle
ten times and kick the Jae-gi.
And wherever the Jae-gi lands
after you kick it, that's what you earn.
- Where's the boxcar?
- This must be it.
- We're all supposed to ride this together?
- What the heck?
[The latest model to be rolled off
the line as of this morning.]
How are we all supposed to
get in this together?
You have to get the items that you
land on within the time allotted.
You have to get the item that
Jae-gi lands on.
I bet roller-skates would be good.
We can find those quickly.
- The direction...
- Why don't you kick it?
Why don't you just try kicking it once?
- Don't try to make it look funny.
- I wasn't.
Kick it... you can just kick it.
- I have to kick it onto something, right?
- Yes.
[Fooling even the camera this time...]
[The Jae-Gi not as easy to kick
as first thought.]
- Jung Ah... Jung Ah...
- Stop trying to be funny.
- Jung Ah, don't try to make it funny.
- Why do you keep sticking up your arm?
Let's do this.
- Fighting!
Set, go!
[Starting with the ten spins.]
- Four... five... six... seven...
- What do I do?
[Losing her sense of balance
more and more.]
- Nine... you have to stop now.
- You have to kick it now.
- Jung Ah! Over this way.
- Jung Ah, come this way.
- Jung Ah... Honey!
- I don't think I can get up.
[Kwang Soo and his family
arrive at the Flea Market.]
They're already here?
They're here already!
- You guys are already here?
- They're here now!
- You guys took a taxi here, didn't you?
- I'm going to take my turn now.
[First born son, Jong Kook's challenge.]
One, two, three, four, five, six,
seven, eight, nine, ten!
Hurry... you have to do it quickly!
[Ten spins making it difficult to get
a sense of balance.]
- What is it?
- 'Love me once again' videotape.
['Love me once again' VHS tape]
- Where are the wheels? This way.
- This is way too small.
[Jong Kook's team getting in the boxcar.]
Okay, good.
- Okay.
- Do you see the hourglass?
You have to be back before the sand
in the hourglass runs out
and ring the bell after you have
been checked out by me.
- Okay.
- Go!
[Jong Kook's team - Go!]
We have to get up there... up there.
[According to Jong Kook and Ha Ha's memory
from having come here previously]
One, two! One, two! One, two!
Right foot, right foot, right foot...
[Jong Kook's team matching their
footsteps.]
-Where do they sell videotapes?
- 'Love me once again' tape!
- 'Love me once again' tape...
- Watch your steps.
[Could it be this shop?]
- There's an 'R' sticker on the item.
- Seriously?
- They have it hidden, I bet.
- How are we going to find it?
[Somewhere hidden amongst these
countless number of videotapes?]
It could be down below too.
There are so many erotic ones here.
[Kwang Soo's family's
Mi Sun taking the challenge.]
- Just one more. There!
- Mi Sun, you have to kick it now!
Kick it!
[Lands on a slinky]
Jeon-Kwang-Suk-Cross!
This is what you're reducing
Mi Sun down to?
- She said she wanted to do it.
- And making her carry the bag like that...
- I was afraid of losing it...
- She is my wife!
You should at least carry
her bag for her.
Okay, the Yellow Team's time
starts now!
[Kwang Soo's family - Go!]
Do you know who sells slinky's here?
- Please give us a slinky!
- Do you have any Slinky's?
- Where...
- I don't' think it's around here.
We can barely walk around in this thing.
[Kwang Soo's family with too varying
differences in height.]
What to do...
I didn't know that this would be
a challenge for our team.
- It's okay. I'm lifting up my feet now.
- You're lifting them up?
I'm walking on my tiptoes now.
[Walking hard to walk on her tiptoes.]
[For my wife...]
- Mother, do you have a cutting knife?
- A cutting knife?
- I do have one.
- Can I please borrow it?
The slinky... I don't see it anywhere.
Thank you.
Careful, careful.
[Cutting a hole in the boxcar?]
I can use my hand to do that.
- That's good.
- We can totally speed up now.
- Thank you for letting us borrow it.
- Thank you.
Here, give it a try.
[A window for Mi Sung is complete.]
- You can still see the camera, right?
- Yeah, I can see it.
- Let's hurry.
- This is so much faster!
You can see, right?
You can see where we're going?
This is so much more comfortable now.
- Slinky... how do we find it?
- Where's the slinky?
[But anyways, where's the slinky?]
- Slinky, slinky...
- They said they don't have it.
- One, two, three...
- Hae Jin, even she can go this fast.
- You're saying I wasn't even this fast?
- No, you weren't!
Your speed was about this fast...
- Seriously?
- She's still spinning?
- Ten!
- Ji Hyo... Ji Hyo...
Kick it!
[Kicking it right into Gary's embrace?]
You're expressing
your feelings for me this way?
[But you said you two were divorced...]
Just what is the deal with you guys?
Why are you guys being like this?
A woman like you, seriously...
Oh my... I'm so dizzy!
[Jong Kook's family - Fail]
Straighten up a little...
- Eight... Nine...
- You're standing up too much, too much!
Ten! Okay.
[Fail]
We can't even get started...
[Their wish is to get on the way.
Time has stopped for Gary's family.]
[Fail...]
What the heck is this?
Why are you so weak?
[Gary's family spinning around
for 30 minutes now...]
- Bend down a little bit more.
- Ji Hyo, spin!
Spin!
[Second Daughter-in-law Ji Hyo
with a hot temper.]
Move!
[Mis-step...]
Ji Hyo...
[What the heck!]
[Gary's family's wish is for the Jae-gi to
land on one of the squares just once.]
- You haven't landed on anything once?
- We haven't gotten anything even once!
- Isn't Hae Jin good at this though?
- He's really horrible at it!
As of now,
the ladies will spin only seven times.
Set, go!
[Third Daughter-in-law,
Mi Sun taking the challenge again.]
- She's so good!
- Five, six, seven! Done!
[Seven spins complete!]
- Good, good!
- There it goes!
We did it!
['The Geek's Bottom Line' book]
[Gary's family spinning again.]
[At last... in the final round?]
He did it!
['The process of a late bloomer' book]
[Look as though they're going to
have to get to the books.]
I think we're going to have to
get up the ramp for now.
I'm happy enough with the fact that
we're able to move on at this point.
[Kwang Soo's team having done it
a few times is moving at lightning speed.]
- Come on!
- Wait, wait!
[The boxcar ultimately breaks down.]
Here it is!
[Kwang Soo's family having
arrived at the bookshop.]
Let's take a look.
- Here it is.
- Here it is!
[Huh? 'The process of a late bloomer'...
This is Gary's Family's...]
No, this isn't it.
[Instead of finding their 'Geek's Bottom-line',
they only found the one Gary's family needs.]
Kwang Soo really looks like
Kwang Soo.
[Fascinated with Kwang Soo
looking like Kwang Soo?]
- It's weird for him to have that name, right?
- Yeah, you're right!
- Dong Gun doesn't suit him.
- That's right!
Kwang Soo... that's perfect.
[Gary's family having found their way
hearing all the noise going on.]
At least take the one you found earlier.
Do you have the book,
'The process of a late bloomer' here?
Mother, we'll take this one.
[But Kwang Soo and his family
are buying it in the meantime?]
Jae Suk! It's that one... it's that one!
- Give it to me, give it to me!
- We're going to buy it!
- Give it to us!
- We already bought it.
[Obstructing so that
Gary and his family can't win.]
- This is our book!
- This is ours, we bought it.
- No, we bought it!
- But it's ours!
- What are you doing?
- Give it to us!
- Don't be like that!
- Wait... wait!
That tickles!
Why did you have to say something?
You should've bought it quietly!
- Thank you!
- Give us our book!
[At last looking as though
they're going to work together?]
[Having bought it for 2,000 won and
selling it to them for 20,000 won!]
[Hurrying back to the starting line.]
[We didn't have to get caught...]
We could do this if we hurry back.
One, two! One, two! One, two!
[Gary's family matching their steps
to speed up their pace.]
One, two! One, two! One, two!
One, two! One, two! One, two...
- Curve, there's a curve!
- One, two! One, two! One, two!
- Curve, curve, curve!
[Did Gary's team make it back on time after
having brought back their item?]
[Their time isn't over yet!]
[Gary's team - Pass!]
Must be nice... I'm jealous.
Blue team, please gather up here.
What is this?
These are all Ddak-ji materials.
[This is none other than...]
[The material they would need...]
[To beat the Absolute Ddak-ji!]
You need to choose
a material and take it with you.
Since you don't know what the other is
made of, you have to keep that in mind too.
You have to choose very carefully.
[Caution - Since the identity of
the Absolute Ddak-ji is still unknown...]
When we hit, it's got to make it flip.
- Box would probably be best, right?
- Box?
We're going to choose the box.
[Gary's family chooses the cardboard box!]
- We can only make one?
- Yes, you can only make one Ddak-ji.
- I'm really good at making Ddak-ji.
- Will this flip others over easily?
Yeah... if you make it right.
[Gary's team starting to make their Ddak-ji
with experienced hands.]
[King of Ddak-ji,
Jae Suk making it with ease.]
After that...
after that, you have to stomp on it.
[Hae Jin carefully stepping on it.]
[Gary's team's Ddak-ji is complete!]
[Did you obtain a nice Ddak-ji?]
Yes, we did.
[Since once isn't generous enough,
I'll give you one more chance.]
[Head over to the Market Square
right away.]
[Kwang Soo's team looking for
the Treble Clef.]
- The one hanging up there?
- Let's go, let's go.
[Jong Kook's Team on the search
for a metal pipe.]
- Here it is! Here!
- Where?
- Here it is!
- Okay!
[Discovers the one with 'R' marker!]
- We can do it! We can win!
- We've got plenty of time.
[Jong Kook's team succeeds!]
Yes!
[Jong Kook's team's turn to choose
the Ddak-ji material.]
You have to make one Ddak-ji on the
spot with the material you choose.
I've made Ddak-ji's before...
we should just lay down several layers of
the newspaper and...
fold it over to make one gigantic one.
Enough for people to wonder how
a Ddak-ji can be so big, you know?
[Huh?]
- We have to fold it...
- Do it like this...
[What?]
[Not even able to make a Ddak-ji...]
- We have to fold down this part...
- And bring this part over.
[Ultimately getting tutored on...]
Okay, the shape of it... this way.
Have you never made Ddak-ji before?
- You have to fold down that part there.
- No, this isn't right.
- Here, let me see it.
- I'll press down the part here.
[They did complete it somehow...]
I don't think that Ddak-ji will be any good.
Jung Ah, this Ddak-ji is the best.
Aren't we supposed to flip over
the other Ddak-ji with these?
How did you make yours?
[Jong Kook's newspaper Ddak-ji
is complete!]
Step on it... hurry, Suk Jin!
[Kwang Soo's team chooses
the cookie box.]
- Step on it, you have to step on it.
- Go ahead, and step on it.
This... this is a good Ddak-ji.
[Kwang Soo's team's Ddak-ji, complete!]
[Will those Ddak-ji's..]
[Be able to turn over the Absolute Ddak-ji?]
[Gary and his team arriving
at the Market Square.]
- Jae Suk, I think this is the place.
- This is it.
[A market full of delicious food.]
Over here...
[Huh? This is?]
What is this?
Hae Jin, come here.
[My sons, you're all working so hard.]
[The sooner you complete the mission here,
the better Ddak-ji you'll be able to obtain.]
Wrestling match...
[Wrestling match!]
[Gary's team having been the first to arrive
automatically moves up to the next level.]
That's much better.
[Arrival of Jong Kook's team.]
He really is walking towards here
so confidently.
- It's wrestling! Wrestling!
- What is this? Are we wrestling?
- This is a sure win.
- It's wrestling?
We won! Wrestling!
Why are we wrestling? It's so extreme!
He used to wrestle!
- I think we're the first to arrive!
- Maybe we are from having took the taxi.
[Positive attitudes...]
What took you guys so long?
You guys took so long!
He's so tall!
He really is like a giraffe!
We've already been moved up
to the next level.
It's until all three members
of the team are ousted.
- Then you're at a major advantage.
- Yes, it's advantageous.
- Who's the first one up for the Red Team?
- Me!
[Jong Kook's team's first player up
is Haroro.]
- Yellow Team, who will it be?
- I will go up.
Lee Kwang Soo!
[Ha Ha vs. Lee Kwang Soo]
Lee Kwang Soo! Lee Kwang Soo!
[Inducing the crowd's cheer for himself.]
[Having no choice but to
accompany by clapping...]
Lee Kwang Soo!
Warning!
[Warning for inciting the crowd
to cheer along for him.]
Stand up, stand up.
[20cm? 30cm?
A great difference in height.]
[Start!]
Dong Hoon, you can do it! It's okay!
[Giraffe showing some force these days.]
Nice... that looks nice.
[Quickly pulling up the legs and..]
[Giraffe's lightning fast attack.]
[Flipping Ha Ha over right away!]
[Giraffe wins!]
[Giraffe's lightning fast attack!]
Lee Kwang Soo! Lee Kwang Soo!
Your self-confidence must be dashed from
having lost to Kwang Soo so often lately...
[A switch from Giraffe's usual stance
of being the symbol of weakness.]
- Let's seriously win this.
- It's okay.
- It's okay... it's okay.
- Let's win this!
Kim Jong Kook!
[Finally...]
[The Tiger's entrance!]
Lee Kwang Soo! Lee Kwang Soo!
[Giraffe's showing his fighting spirit.]
Kwang Soo has gotten stronger.
[Surprisingly anticipating the match.]
[Kim Jong Kook vs. Lee Kwang Soo]
Kwang Soo, you can do this.
This is too suffocating.
I feel like my ribs are about to shatter.
[Overwhelming one-sided fight...]
I really hope he wins.
Show him what you have, Giraffe!
[The first born son vs. the third son]
[Start!]
Beat him!
[Tiger's easy expression]
[But the Giraffe is able to defend himself
using his great height as leverage.]
[Danger]
No, no!
[Escaping danger through dazzling footwork.]
- He really is a Giraffe!
- Look at his legs!
He's our Giraffe!
[Giraffe holding out by using
his long legs.]
[Could this somehow be...]
[Oh?]
[Being pulled by the Tiger's attack!]
[Astonishing power!]
[Will he be able to thwart it off again
using his long legs?]
[Not this time!]
[This is the Tiger's power!]
Are you okay?
I'm so humiliated!
[Undoubtedly, Big-nosed brother
coming to a ruin as well.]
[Kwang Soo's team with only
Daughter-in-law Mi Sun left standing.]
- Jeon Mi Sun, please step forward.
- How am I to do this? Seriously...
This is an absurd match.
Women can decide whether they're
going to win the match or not.
- If you lose, then we win.
- Losing is wining in this case.
[Mi Sun chooses losing the match.]
[Kim Jong Kook vs. Jeon Mi Sun]
The whole crowd is agitated right now.
- No way!
- They're saying that this is absurd.
There's no way... no way.
[In this match,
the loser is the winner.]
Wait a minute...
[Start!]
[Just sitting down on the spot?]
[Huh?]
[Completely immobile.]
Just hurry up and sit down.
[Tiger as immobile as a stone.]
[Even though they're in a different situation,
both are clueless as to what to do.]
[Only the desire to lower herself
onto the ground.]
Sit down! Little... little bit more!
Mi Sun, little bit... little bit more!
I can't... I can't!
- Just sit down!
- Sit down right now!
- He's way too strong!
- But we have to win this...
Of course, we have to win!
What are you doing right now?
What are you doing?
[Outburst of criticism.]
- I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
- What are you doing?
[Tiger sprawling out on the ground.]
[Jong Kook wins!]
Mi Sun, you could've just sat down!
What are you doing right now?
Are you playing around with her?
What are you taking her for?
The Red Team moves on to the final round!
[Red Team moves up to the final round.]
[Final round
Gary's Team vs. Jong Kook's Team]
[Song Ji Hyo vs. Yeom Jung Ah]
Sit down.
[Charismatic first Daughter-in-law, Jung Ah]
[Ji Hyo vs. Jung Ah.
Wrestling for the win.]
She's really strong!
A round of applause for our two ladies!
[Our team is the winning team.]
What do I do?
[Women's match with no conceding.]
[Start!]
Oh my goodness...
she's not even budging.
[This is the power of our
Running Man's Ace.]
Ji Hyo, Ji Hyo...
[This is no joke.]
[Jung Ah's attack!]
[Will she?]
[The attack just ends with a
hint of danger.]
- You have to be careful now...
- Those girls...
[This time, Ji Hyo is...]
[Catching the outer leg perfectly!]
[Ji Hyo's single victory!]
[Lightning fast skills!]
Ji Hyo!
You got her outer leg perfectly!
It could happen... it could happen.
You can finish this up for us.
[Her next opponent, nervous Ha Ha.]
I feel like I'm going to lose this
even if I really give it my best try.
You saw what she did earlier, didn't you?
She knows what to do with her legs!
- Ji Hyo, just beat him.
- I don't know, Suk Jin.
[Ji Hyo vs. Ha Ha]
[Going with the option to lose the match
this time around.]
[Start!]
[Huh?]
[Sprawling down at a lightning fast speed!]
[Ha Ha not even having the chance
to use any of his strength.]
[Wow! What a sight to see!]
Ji Hyo... that was perfect!
[Jae Suk filled with admiration.]
That was the perfect move!
[Admiration plus laughter.]
Jae Suk...
When someone pulls that move,
they usually end up dangling in the air.
But her butt totally just touched the ground.
- Why do you think that is?
- He's trying to attack you with his words.
Most women's butts wouldn't touch
the ground like that.
[She's good at kicking too!]
There are a lot of people here, Ji Hyo.
[If Blank Ji beats the Tiger,
the game is immediately over!]
[But her opponent is
an all-round player, Mr. Capable.]
[Song Ji Hyo vs. Kim Jong Kook]
But her plan is known now...
She should've used that move
on Jong Kook.
[Opting for the losing match this time again.]
What is she doing right now?
Everyone... both teams,
let's give them a round of cheer!
[The final round
overflowing with apprehension.]
[Will she be able to beat Mr. Capable...]
[and win with a three win streak?]
[Start!]
[Going to for sprawl out
on the ground move again!]
[And lifting her right off the ground.]
[A move that won't fly with
Mr. Capable.]
I don't feel really good about easily
holding her off the ground right now.
Hey!
Hey! Don't do that!
Should I end this quickly?
Hey!
[Blank Ji's strong resistance!]
[Jong Kook wins!]
Ji Hyo, you did good.
[Blank Ji having beat two people.]
She really is very strong.
Jong Kook, how are you going to beat
all three people?
She seriously is very strong.
I'll go this time.
[Jae Suk finally makes his entrance.]
[Yoo Jae Suk vs. Kim Jong Kook]
[All throughout the history of the show,
they've been lifelong rivals.]
[The humiliation from
Chuseok special a year ago.]
[Having lost without even having been
able to exert his strength once.]
[That shameful match...]
Jong Kook's the winner!
[Will he be able to pay him back
for that shame today?]
- Isn't this going too fast without break?
- We have to do this quickly!
[Huh?]
[Rubbing his body up against
him all of a sudden?]
What are you doing right now?
- What are you doing?
- I'm trying to grab onto the straps!
- What...
You are the weirdest man!
[Even if he can't win the match,
doing what he can to exert the Tiger.]
[Mr. Capability's power that can be felt.]
[Start!]
[The history of shame that's being
repeated again this year.]
Throw him!
One more time...
let's do it one more time.
Set... go!
[Defense in depth.]
[Immediate apology.]
[Right back in the air again...]
[Time?]
- Why? What do you need the time for?
- My straps are too tight.
- Just a little bit...
- Okay, I got it.
Loosen it up a little bit.
It's really pinching my skin.
Grab it right here.
[Just then!]
[Using the moment
his defenses are down to attack!]
[Will his plan actually work?]
[Huh?]
[The handiwork?]
No, no...
- What are you doing?
- It's because of these straps... the straps.
[Using every ounce of strength he has
until the very end...]
[The Tiger made of stone
isn't budging an inch.]
- What?
- Jae Suk, that's too ugly of a sight!
Do you really want me to flip you over?
[Flip... flip him over?]
[No way...]
[Gulp...]
[Jae Suk flipped over...]
Seriously...
[Upside down Titanic?]
[A rare pose to capture on film.]
[This year's Chuseok
is also passing by in shame.]
This is so humiliating...
[Jong Kook wins!]
Jae Suk... just come back here.
It's okay!
- Jae Suk, that was so...
- I've exerted him a lot.
[After the loss of Gary,
Hae Jin is the only one left.]
[The loud battle cry.]
- But I'm so scared.
- It's okay.
He's really exerted right now.
[The final wrestling match of the day.]
[This is the match that will
determine the winner.]
[Yoo Hae Jin vs. Kim Jong Kook]
You can do it... you can do it.
This is the last match... the last match!
Fighting! Let's give them a round
of applause!
[Start!]
Hae Jin, you're really strong!
My blood pressure...
[Seems as though he may have
overdone it.]
[Tiger's gigantic and overwhelming wall.]
[He does have his leg wrapped around...]
This is so upsetting!
[Seriously upset older cousin.]
[Extreme entertainment to
everyone watching.]
Hae Jin...
Hae Jin is so upset right now.
He's so upset right now.
Only those who've lost know what that's like.
What's wrong with you?
[Reserving his energy...]
Finally a move!
[Wow... but still not budging...]
Jong Kook is sapped of his strength
right now.
[But he looks even more
depleted of his strength.]
Please just end it now!
- Just end it now!
- I can't watch this any longer!
- Just end it...
- I'll try it just one more time.
If it doesn't work,
there's nothing I can do about it.
[The inner leg?]
[Not being able to do as one wants...
His name is, Mr. Capable.]
[Depleted]
[Jong Kook's team wins!]
[Triumphant Jong Kook's Team]
[Second Ddak-ji chance!]
[A little more diverse material
this time around.]
[Jong Kook's Team chooses the
cardboard box.]
- Jae Suk, the calendar.
- Definitely the calendar.
[Gary's Team chooses the calendar.]
- I can't believe those guys left this.
- Without a doubt, that's what we should get.
[Kwang Soo's Team chooses
the hardboard.]
Here's your next mission.
[There will be no more
chances at any more Ddak-ji.]
[I'll give you a nice chance
at the next mission.]
[Choose the picture of the food you like,
and go to the address written on the back.]
[Picture of grilled meat?]
[Discreet and thorough Jong Kook's Team.]
[Jong Kook and Gary's Team
chooses the same picture.]
[Seoul Jong-nogu, Jong-no-guga]
- This one's ours?
- It looks good.
[Seoul Jong-nogu]
- Thank you!
[Thanking all the crowd for having
gathered and cheered them on.]
Thank you!
[A feast of veritable kind
everywhere they look.]
- Hello.
- That looks so good!
Jae Suk, that looks so good!
I think I need to re-energize myself.
Mr. Yoo Jae Suk...
[Happily greeting those that he's
seeing again after a year has passed.]
I have to get going right now.
It's been a year since we've been here.
Oh yes, hello.
Hello, Mother.
It's been a year since we've been here.
[Bountiful Chuseok!
Endless banquet at the traditional market.]
I want to buy everything...
Look at this...
[As if the bountiful banquet of feast
goes on all year long...]
Spicy rice cakes are good too,
but there are variety of pancakes too.
Look at the chicken feet...
and the pig feet too. It's no joke!
[Heading to the grilled meat restaurant
within the market.]
Come this way.
[Discovering the next mission location. Go!]
Here it is! Here's the sign!
Hello!
[Having arrived after enduring the hunger]
[Just what is the mission that
awaits for them here?]
Should I take off my socks too?
[I'm going to judge your concentration
during this mission.]
[You have to eat all the meat on the grill
within the allotted time to succeed.]
[It's a fail if there's even a piece left,
so concentrate and make sure to eat it all.]
- If it's eating...
- Eating is no problem!
[Will it be such a simple mission as that?]
- The meat isn't to be eaten comfortably.
- Then what?
- We're going to enjoy it, right?
- We're not eating it raw, are we?
Hae Jin wants to know if we can enjoy it.
- And Jong Kook...
- Yes, Jae Suk?
Hae Jin's pride got really destroyed earlier.
I feel like my body is still shaking.
You're not just going to be eating the
meat. If you look behind you...
[Tie up the hand holding the chopsticks
with the rubber tube...]
[and finish eating the meat on the grill pan
within 30 seconds to succeed!]
I'll let you know when
the meat is done grilling.
Hae Jin just said that
his arms are still shaking.
[Gary's Team first to take the challenge!]
Here, you come and try it.
[Bursting out in laughter from
the absurdity of it all.]
- It's pretty funny, isn't it?
- How does it feel, Hae Jin?
I'm being made to feel very
pathetic today.
- This is...
- Ma'am, can we get some napkins?
- Eat lots, Hae Jin.
- I really do want to eat a lot.
Is this all cooked?
- It's done cooking, so get ready.
- I think it's done cooking.
Set, go!
[Beat the pull of the tight rubber restraint
and eat the meat!]
[I will for sure eat it!]
[Jae Suk's hidden strength!]
[Hae Jin barely getting in a
bite in his mouth!]
[I'm hungry!]
[I should give Gary a bite.]
Ouch! That's hot!
You just burned me!
[But you have to eat quickly...]
[Hae Jin using every ounce
of strength he has!]
- Turn that pan around.
- Turn it... turn it.
[Ah! In an effort to turn the grill pan!]
That should be grounds for elimination!
[Disqualified!]
Gary, I'm sorry.
I was aiming for your mouth.
[Even if we failed,
we should eat what we can.]
- Tastes so much better to eat like this.
- This is really good.
If I had only put
this much effort into acting...
- If I had some soju to go with it...
- Jung Ah said she wants some soju.
I'm sorry,
but I think you need to get her some.
She's pretty on edge right now.
We're going to have a drink of soju here.
If you put it down there,
Jung Ah will reach out her arm to grab it.
[Without an issue even if her arm
is tied up with the tube?]
Then someone can pour the drink here,
and you can take the drink from this side.
- Okay, we're going to grill the meat now.
- Everyone, enjoy.
[Now Jong Kook's Team's turn
to take the challenge.]
[Tasty looking...]
[Setting it up high where they can't reach]
It has to finish cooking first!
The fire is hotter over on this side.
[Succeeds in setting the meat
in an out of reach spot.]
It's okay if I finish eating it all
in a short period of time, right?
[Tiger brimming with confidence.]
That looks really good.
This would be really good with rice.
[Rice thief, spicy marinated pork.]
- I think it's done.
- Get ready to start.
[Will Jong Kook's Team be able to
succeed within 30 seconds?]
[Start!]
[Jong Kook's chopsticks closing in.]
[Grabs it precisely!]
[Succeeds in grabbing a piece
within 1.2 seconds.]
That's just not fair!
Just look at him!
Yeom Jung Ah can't even get a bite.
[Carnivorous Haroro's surge of power!]
[And this person...]
Grab a piece for Yeom Jung Ah!
Hurry up and give me a piece!
Me too!
[So hot...]
[All the time slipping away
between the laughter.]
Fail!
[Failure with three pieces
of meat left to go!]
[That's so hot!]
You have to eat this
while scalding the roof of your mouth.
The unfair thing about this game is
that it's all about using your strength.
It's not really like that, Hae Jin.
- If you had gone to the other place..
- That would have been even worse.
The other team has to sit there
without swallowing anything.
Seriously? At least we get to eat!
[At least these two teams get to eat meat...]
[Kwang Soo's Team...]
[Succeed the mission if they don't swallow
any spit until the meat's done cooking.]
- Miss Mi Sun, I think you swallowed.
- No, no... no, I didn't.
That's just her habit.
Don't flip it over, please don't do it.
[Danger! The meat is being flipped over!]
I'm about to go crazy. Don't flip it over.
[The moment that the
ultimate top sirloin gets flipped over!]
[Stimulating the appetite 10,000%]
[Fanning the scent of grilling meat their way
to make them lose their composure.]
[I won't forgive you for this...]
Would you like to smell it?
[Giraffe swallowing way too noticeably!]
You've failed.
[No excuses can be accepted
for the way he was caught.]
[The grilled meat goes to
the VJ's and the staff.]
[Giving a bite to Big brother's VJ,
Yoo Suk.]
[Awesome!]
[Since it was a big piece of meat,
everyone gets to have a bite.]
Is it good? How is it?
[And of course, a bite for PD Myuk.]
Don't eat that in front of us!
Hey, why did you swallow?
Ddak-ji... think of Ddak-ji!
[So... hungry...]
Ji Hyo...
- Ji Hyo...
- There's no way that they can do this.
[Concentrating all their might
on their chopsticks.]
Just look at Ji Hyo...
[Angry Ace for not having things
go the way she wants when she's hungry.]
[Hae Jin losing all the strength he has left.]
[Huh? Ah...]
[Hae Jin doesn't even know...]
[Where do you think you're going?]
[Grabbing a piece with
his whole body quivering.]
[Not much time left on the clock]
- Hae Jin, are you eating?
- I'm totally zapped of strength.
Wait... what are you doing?
- Variety!
Variety mentality!
What is this with the hands?
[Anyways, failing again with
Jong Kook's playing around.]
Here, eat... eat.
Here, eat all of it.
[Jung Ah grilling meat for the opposing
team since they lost their mission.]
[Taking the pose of the head Daughter-in-law
during the holidays.]
Hae Jin looks like he's settled in his seat.
A bottle of soju over here, please!
Why don't you get up now?
Our program really does
make you hungry, doesn't it?
I think Hae Jin is finally done eating.
Thank you... thank you.
This really was an
entertaining drinking table tonight.
- What?
- Housewarming party? Housewarming party?
[Monday couple's housewarming party?]
I think they must run a restaurant.
You should have put out some more food.
I told you that we were having guests.
This is barely enough to cover anyone's
nose with what we have here.
I put it up your nose earlier.
[Start]
Jong Kook, one at a time!
Give me some too, Jong Kook.
[Almost done eating...]
Let's go!
Hurry up and set it down! Hurry!
[The last piece!]
[He ate it, but the time...]
[Jong Kook's Team succeeds at
29.82 seconds!]
[Mr. Capability's tenacity
has paid off in this round!]
[First team to pass the mission
out of all three teams.]
The one I used is probably
a bit stretched out, so use that one.
[The rubber tube seemed to be stretched out
after having him use his strength against it.]
We have to keep doing this until we pass.
Set... go!
[All the chopsticks easily going in
for grabs.]
[After a few uses,
the rubber seemed to have stretched.]
I don't want it to be too difficult
for them to eat it.
[The meat disappearing the moment
he lays them on the grill.]
I'm so hungry!
- What the heck?
- They're doing really good.
[Gary's Team succeeds with ease.]
[Hae Jin always making sure to eat
all the side dishes.]
[Mm... so good...]
Jae Suk, the place we have to go...
[You still have one more chance.
Hurry on to the pancake shop.]
- Myoungrhyun intersection?
- Myoungrhyun intersection.
Then that would be in front of
Song Ryun University.
[It's not very far from here...]
Then let's take a taxi over there.
[Gary's team dividing up into
two taxis to move to their next stop.]
[Ji Hyo and Hae Jin getting in the cab first.]
- Let's move quickly!
- Thank you!
Thank you, sir.
I ate so well.
You look like a foreigner.
- Excuse me?
- You look like a foreigner.
- Are you referring to me?
- No, the lady.
You look totally native though.
[Jong Kook's Team being directed on
which way to go at the police station.]
Thank you so much.
[Fully comprehending which routes to take
and where they need to go.]
- Thank you so much.
- Have a great night. Thank you.
Bus route number eight.
This one here.
Three people.
- Thank you.
Do you know this area very well?
[Kwang Soo's team on the other hand...]
Do you know this area well?
Around here?
[After barely having passed the mission,
heading off to the pancake shop.]
We have to right now...
let's see here...
[Asking direction to the location while
looking at the map to the destination.]
- Then you need to get off right here.
- Get off at this stop?
[Kindly and patiently
explaining it all to them.]
Thank you... thank you so much.
- It's where a lot of young kids go.
- Ah, young kids?
Then you and Mi Sun shouldn't go.
I'm sorry.
Thank you!
[Each arriving at the location.]
[Locating the pancake house
at the Myungryun intersection.]
This way... here it is. Here.
- We fit very well...
- We fit and work very well together.
[Jong Kook and Ha Ha head over heels
for Jung Ah's motherly image?]
- But I think I'm really bad at the games.
- But that's not what's most important.
- But you really are horrible.
- Fine! I'm horrible at it!
[Finally arriving at the pancake house.]
[Just what Ddak-ji related mission
awaits for them here?]
[To Jong Kook's team that won
first place at the restaurant earlier...]
[Is given the first chance to swap
their Ddak-ji with an opposing team.]
[Not allowed to re-trade the Ddak-ji
they've already traded for.]
I see how it is...
We remember exactly what we all have.
- There is one that we'd like to have.
- Yes, there is one.
Since you've won first place,
you can either hold onto one you have...
or you can trade it with another team.
If they lock one of theirs down,
that one can't be touched?
- If they do, you can't touch it.
- Then just lock yours down.
We shouldn't have won first place then.
[The privilege of being first place
not sitting well with Mom Jung Ah.]
- Listen to what Yeom Jung Ah says!
- She can beat us up.
- I saw it...
- What?
[It's a huge power to be able to protect
one of their own Ddak-ji's...]
- Then tell them to go first.
- Tell the other team to go first then.
- What's the use of being first place?
- Okay then, we'll go first.
But they can't touch the ones
we made, right?
Why can't we touch it?
Why are you doing this?
This is seriously about to drive me crazy!
- Explain it to Jung Ah in detail.
- I'm not explaining it to her!
Her understanding is correct!
How did you guys all get here so quickly?
[How are you guys so slow?]
Mi Sun is really pouty right now
for being last all the time.
[Now that we think about it,
Kwang Soo's Team has been last all day.]
She says that her son is useless.
He pout is big as a trumpet right now!
[To trade and protect,
put out all their Ddak-ji in possession.]
[Offering the opportunity to hit
the opposing team's Ddak-ji.]
Then we're going to give it a hit!
Seriously... she's really angry right now!
Second place... I just
want to get at least second place.
Don't complain it about it so much.
We have the pride of being in last place too.
Her skills are totally our level.
The opportunity to hit others.
Just once... hit it just once.
[Jong Kook's Team's extremely powerful
newspaper Ddak-ji.]
[Not even budging]
Let's keep it...
let's keep our newspaper Ddak-ji.
- Keep it, keep it.
- Let's keep this one.
- Since it's good for attacking...
- That's a piece of art right there.
- Then is it our turn?
- Yes.
Take that one. That's a good one.
[Jae Suk testing out
Kwang Soo's hardboard Ddak-ji.]
[Immoveable]
Keep on hitting it.
For us...
[Taking Kwang Soo's Team's
hardboard Ddak-ji.]
When it comes to Ddak-ji,
Jae Suk's good.
The last time... when
Yeon Jae and Tae Hwan were on...
Ddak-ji!
[He thought that when it came to Ddak-ji,
he ruled the game...]
[He was forced to face failure without even a
chance to hit with Mr. Capable's entrance.]
What's the point if I'm good at Ddak-ji
when I don't even get the opportunity?
Chance?
Chance, my butt...
[Just wait and see...]
Please come up and take a letter
that your Mother has written for you.
She sure writes a lot of letters...
[My sons, you have all made it.]
[Upgrade your Ddak-ji through this mission
and challenge the Absolute Ddak-ji.]
[Everyone has to flip over the coin
by placing it on the frying pan.]
You have a total of five chances.
Starting with number one,
one, two, three, four and finally five.
[All five have to succeed in procession
for them to succeed the mission.]
- No practices.
- No we have to practice too.
No, we have to practice too.
Let them practice once.
Even when Mi Sun first came on the show,
she had a fresh baby looking face...
But as the day wears on,
she's starting to revert to her age.
Her scary Mom voice even came out.
- Kwang Soo...
- This is too hard!
What is this?
Hurry up and practice.
[Each team gets two tries.]
[Ace Ji Hyo easily succeeds in one try.]
[Number two Gary also succeeds.]
[Number three Jae Suk's turn.]
[Will he...]
[He didn't flip it over...]
I haven't even gotten to do it once!
[Gary's family's second attempt.]
- Fighting!
[Ji Hyo succeeds on first try!]
- Ji Hyo's really good...
- Ji Hyo's so good at it.
[Didn't flip over!]
[Diffusing the situation with laughter.]
- Hae Jin's not good at anything.
- This is pretty difficult.
[Now that we're thinking about it,
he hasn't won a thing today.]
Hae Jin, come here.
Stand over here.
Jong Kook... kneel down over there.
- Kneel down on both knees.
- I don't want to.
- Why do I have to do that?
- You have to kneel down.
[The older ones not being able to mutter
a sound when the younger one starts talking]
You can rest your arm like this
since it's difficult to stay like that.
- No, I have my own method.
- Really?
That's a first. That's the first time
Jong Kook ever let anything go.
[Jong Kook's Team's first attempt.]
- There you go.
- That's right!
- That's right...
- He did it!
[Number one Ha Ha succeeds.]
[Mr. Capable's failure bringing
so much joy to everyone.]
[Switching their spot and
making their second attempt.]
[Taking their spot and positions...]
Lightly... lightly to the back.
Seriously... Jung Ah... she has a temper
and is very bad at the games.
What have you done today, Jung Ah?
Yeom Jung Ah is getting angrier
by the minute.
- I got it, Jung Ah.
- What do you know?
- What do you keep saying that you know?
- I got it, come here.
I got it, Jung Ah.
I figured it out exactly.
You can't be like this.
We can't lose our teamwork!
[Kwang Soo's Team's first attempt.]
Lee Kwang Soo!
Kwang Soo!
[Second attempt after
switching out their seats.]
Jeon Mi Sun!
- Jeon Mi Sun!
- That looks good!
Who was it...
- Jeon Mi Sun!
- That looks good!
Who was it...
You can't do that!
[Fail from Jae Suk's shouting?]
- You can't shout while we're doing it!
- Did you see Mi Sun's stare?
[Frigid...]
[Sae Young's Mom showing her true nature.]
I can do it during practice,
but I can't do it during actual try.
Ji Hyo does it as if she's cooking.
- How do you do that so well?
- I'm good at flipping fried eggs too.
Then do it with confidence...
with confidence.
[Number two Hae Jin also succeeds.]
[Number three Jae Suk also succeeds.]
- They figured out a method.
- No!
Gary won't be able to do it.
[Wow! A success!]
[A total of five times.
Now Ji Hyo has to flip it one more time...]
If she gets the yellow tab,
then we win?
[Their hopes once again ride
on Ace Ji Hyo.]
[If she flips it over to the side with
the yellow sticker, they win!]
[Will she...]
[It flipped over!]
[Gary's Team succeeds in flipping them
over five times in a row!]
[Ji Hyo is definitely Running Man's Ace!]
- Even during wrestling, you took out two!
- My wife is the best!
[A reunion for the holidays?]
That's my wife!
Wow seriously... that was great!
It's a lot easier than I thought.
Mi Sun... I think Mi Sun is pissed off.
The winning team can just relax
and enjoy the food now.
Yes, we'll enjoy it. Thank you.
We're just going to eat some pancakes then.
[Now competing for the second place.]
Jong Kook... give it a little snap.
You can't do that?
Try flipping it like you would flip an egg.
Why make it so hard?
I'm getting to eat the pancakes and
even see a side show now...
- It's a dinner show.
- This place has great dinner shows.
[Jong Kook's Team takes the challenge.]
Okay, let's go!
[Number one, Ha Ha succeeds]
[Number two, Jong Kook succeeds]
- Jung Ah won't be able to do it.
- Don't be nervous and do it calmly.
[Number three, Jung Ah succeeds]
[Whew...]
[Now flip it back so that
the yellow sticker is back in view!]
[Oh no...]
[Number four, Jong Kook fails.]
[You were almost there...]
This dinner show is making my
palms sweat!
The dinner show at this place
is pretty decent!
That's pathetic, just pathetic...
All three of them need to get
the feel of it together...
But since only one of them
is trying to do that...
[Acting like he's better than anyone.]
It's okay, it's okay.
You really don't know until it's over.
This is the first time
I've seen her like this.
Hae Jin, just think back to
when you were wrestling.
- Who? Me?
- What about him when he was wrestling?
- Me?
- Yes, Hae Jin!
I did it very confidently.
[His look of confidence...]
You lost by a margin to Jong Kook earlier.
Yeah, it was really too bad.
- I was so close.
- Yes, you were!
[Jong Kook's team regroups to do it again.]
[Number one, Ha Ha succeeds]
[Number two, Jong Kook succeeds]
[Number three, Jung Ah succeeds]
[Now they just needs the yellow sticker
to show for their fourth and fifth try!]
[Number four, Jong Kook succeeds]
[Now final number five, Ha Ha!]
[If he flips it over, they
complete the mission in second place!]
[Will he...]
[Jong Kook's team succeeds in flipping it
over five times in a row!]
[All the built up stress, gone!]
- Yes! Yes!
- Thank goodness!
[Kwang Soo's Team in last place again.]
You can't think about this...
no hesitations, and just do it.
Your team doesn't even need to do it
since you're in last place, right?
Are you trying to upset them
even more right now?
There's the Ddak-ji match later anyways.
- You did really good.
- I did good, right?
[Supplies to upgrade the Ddak-ji's.]
[Just what are the supplies to
help upgrade their Ddak-ji?]
Okay, I'm going to reveal them.
One, two, three!
[Masking tape, glue stick, stapler]
- Tape... let's get the tape.
- We just need one of the two.
[The first place winner gets the option
to make the first selection.]
[What shall they use amongst these...]
Come on, do it quickly.
[Gary's team's selection]
We'll go with the tape.
- Why is there only this much?
- There's not much there?
That's right.
They shouldn't be giving you too much.
What the heck is this?
[Barely enough left to go around the roll
maybe three to four times.]
Look at the tape!
- That's all of it?
- What kind of a deal is this?
[We're in trouble...]
We can use that glue stick a lot.
Ours is made of newspaper...
newspaper sticks very well together.
I'm really sick of it...
so totally sick of it.
If you were going to be like that,
why didn't you just become a scientist then?
- Save everyone the trouble...
- Kwang Soo, Kwang Soo...
[After getting it all off his chest,
apologizing immediately.]
The stapler may not even be able to
go through our newspaper at all.
[Through Mr. Capable's needling,
they choose the glue stick.]
- Okay... look at this!
- Think about it, it's a good choice.
Hey, we originally wanted the stapler
for ourselves anyways.
[Kwang Soo's Team automatically
gets the stapler.]
[But there doesn't appear to be
enough staples.]
- Show Mi Sun, show it to her.
- No, don't show it to her!
Don't show it to her!
She's going to get annoyed!
Take a look! See for yourself!
What the heck is this?
[Gary's Team,
upgrading their cardboard Ddak-ji.]
[Complete after all the effort
put in with the tape!]
I think this is good.
We got ourselves a good one.
It sticks very nicely.
[Jong Kook's team
upgrading with their glue stick.]
[Is that Ddak-ji, or a land mine?]
Let's staple this part.
One, two, three.
[Kwang Soo's team making theirs stronger
with the use of the stapler.]
- It keeps coming back out though.
- That's not going to do.
[Envious...]
You're jealous, aren't you?
- We're going to slate once.
- I'll do it!
I'm going to hit the slate.
One, two, three!
[The final location. The place
where Absolute Ddak-ji lies in wait.]
[To Sam-choen-ggak.]
[All the teams pulling everything out of
their pockets to take the cab!]
Sam-cheon-gaak in
Cheon-buk-dong, please.
The important when we get there is,
not beating the other team's Ddak-ji...
- but the Absolute Ddak-ji...
- Flipping that over, right?
[They have to flip over the Absolute Ddak-ji
with the ones they have in possession!]
[All three teams arrives
almost simultaneously!]
[Jong Kook's team is the first
to enter the place!]
Go! Go!
[What awaits for them inside?]
- What is it?
- What is this? It's scary.
- It's not scary, Jung Ah. Come in.
[A set of doors blocking their path.]
[Past those doors...]
[This is... Absolute Ddak-ji!]
- See? It's scary!
- Mom!
- Mom! Mom!
- Grandmother!
[This is the Ddak-ji creator,
Mrs. Go Dong Wan?]
- That's my mom. Oh look, there it is!
- Hello.
What you see there in front of you
is the Absolute Ddak-ji.
[Taking turns between the teams to try
and flip over the Ddak-ji.]
[An extraordinary inheritance will be
given to the family that flips it over.]
I will reveal to you my legacy before
you start the Ddak-ji match.
- What is it?
- What could it be?
- Is it a beef rib set?
- My legacy is this.
[Solid gold plaque]
- It's written in gold!
- It's gold!
Wow... that's really cool!
[Run, don't walk]
Once a family fails after trying
with both their Ddak-ji's...
then the opportunity goes to the
next team.
We get to try out both of them?
It's not just one?
- You get to try them both.
- But we just need to flip it over once?
- But we just need to turn it over once?
- That's right.
- Talking down...
[Letting it go since he's playing his Mother.]
Even though that Ddak-ji is great at defense,
I don't know about attacking.
[Attacking first with
the monstrous newspaper Ddak-ji.]
[It's gigantic enough,
but it's been upgraded with the glue stick!]
[Mega-monstrous newspaper Ddak-ji!]
[Challenging the Absolute Ddak-ji!]
- Wow, they're even beating the drums!
- Wow...
What's so significant about Ddak-ji
that you're even beating the drum?
Is this some sacred Ddak-ji or something?
[He's making his move...]
- I think he's going to flip it...
- Just shatter the ground. Shatter it.
- Shatter the ground!
- here I go!
Here I go!
[Do you know the danger of
Absolute Ddak-ji?]
[Simulation...
158th attempt to flip it over.]
[Number of times it's been flipped over...
zero.]
[Do you think you'll be able to flip over
this Absolute Ddak-ji?]
[Wait...]
[What... the...]
[Wait... what...the heck...]
Did that really happen?
- Did that really happen?
- Seriously... did that really happen?
[It flipped over... in one shot...]
How in the world did that happen?
[Oh crap...]
[The writers and
members are all frozen in place like ice.]
How is this Absolute Ddak-ji?
[Who knew it would flip over like that...]
- Here, try to flip it over.
- Try it.
- What the heck is this?
- Flip it... try and flip it over.
I'm speechless right now.
Look at PD Myuk's expression right now!
No one had been able to flip that over...
[Jong Kook making another attempt
with his newspaper Ddak-ji.]
[Again!!!]
[The whole staff has a mental breakdown!]
This Absolute Ddak-ji really is made well...
- It is made really well.
- His is more like a boulder... a boulder.
I never got the chance this time either.
What I would like to say to you is this...
stop talking about Ddak-ji.
[The declining Lord of Ddak-ji?]
Seriously... this is unfair.
[Jong Kook's family is passed down
the legacy.]
[Jong Kook's family, the ultimate winner!]
We give you the Absolute Ddak-ji, Mi Sun!
- Yes, here.
- Thank you...
Thank you.
We wish all our viewers an
enjoyable Chuseok.
Thank you!
[Happy Chuseok to everyone!]
Subtitles by DramaFever