[Marine Boy Park Tae Hwan.]
[Rhythm Gymnastics Fairy, Son Yeon Jae.]
[They are here!!]
[Running Man's training camp that's
difficult even for the Olympic heroes.]
[And...]
[Training camp mission -
Find the magical potion]
[If the blue potion is found, the name
tag is transformed into a giant size.]
[Being made into an
easy target to be chased around...]
[On the other hand,
the effects of a red potion?]
[Pitch- hitter out.]
[An enormous weapon power in which
even if your name tag is ripped...]
[someone else gets ousted instead.]
[Ha Ha chooses Jae Suk to be
ousted in his place.]
[Jae Suk, already wise to the truth.]
[A surreal name tag battle
swirled around in magic.]
[Just who will be the ultimate victor?]
I bet you'll be really mad by next week.
I bet you'll be really fired up
when you see this broadcast.
[I knew that he'd do this.]
Let's sit down and talk.
[Ha Ha relaying what just happened
to his teammates.]
- There's good and bad potions here.
- Kwang Soo must've gotten the bad one.
That's why his name tag got big.
But look at my name tag...
- Yoo Jae Suk will be eliminated.
- If someone tears yours off?
[Pitch hitter out - If Ha Ha's name tag
gets ripped, Jae Suk is out]
Don't make it obvious and let other know.
Just act casual.
Don't even smile about it,
and don't even talk about it.
That's why I really hope that Jae Suk
rips off my name tag.
[Ha Ha plans on luring Jae Suk
to rip off his name tag.]
Then while Jae Suk is watching,
you can rip Kwang Soo's name tag off.
[Planning on ripping Kwang Soo's name tag
off in front of Jae Suk to lure him in.]
[The evil scenario]
[Definitely getting excited
over political plays.]
You really are the best!
- Just tell Yeon Jae about it
- Okay.
That's awesome.
[But the problem is...
Yoo Jae Suk is watching all this]
[A little while ago]
Yoo Jae Suk.
[Ha Ha choosing Jae Suk to be ousted in his
place after finding the red potion.]
[By chance, Jae Suk got to witness
this event.]
[He probably won't just sit by
and wait to be had.]
It'll probably be good to oust a member
of the blue team first, right?
[Even if they attack the Blue team,
they have to avoid Ha Ha.]
Either Suk Jin or Ji Hyo.
One of the two.
The scenario that Suk Jin
mentioned is the best.
- There's Jong Kook and...
- Where?
Hey, hey... there's Kwang Soo.
There he is.
[Kwang Soo stepping into the trap of
the Blue team as Jae Suk planned.]
Someone is running up there right now.
He's following someone right now.
Right? Wait a minute... come here.
Come here and squat down.
- There's Kwang Soo.
- Kwang Soo to the right?
[Within moments, all of Running Man
are targeting Kwang Soo.]
[The injured Gary is keeping
watch up high.]
[Just where is Kwang Soo heading to?]
The other way! The other way!
[Kwang Soo approaching
Green team's Gary!]
[Kwang Soo eliminates Gary's name tag!]
[Gary - Out! Gary - Out!]
Jong Kook!
[Even Jae Suk gets flustered over
Kwang Soo's move!]
Kwang Soo!
Jong Kook!
[Green Team's Coach Kook and Athlete Park,
on full on attack mode for Kwang Soo.]
[Since I let you go once,
this time, I will get you!]
[Escaping into a dressing room
in the corner.]
I'm going to stay here for a moment.
Stay here just for a moment.
[The siege has already been
set up right out front!]
Go in there.
[Heading inside to get Kwang Soo.]
- There you are.
- Wait, Jong Kook... wait.
You can tear it off.
I heard that you ripped it off.
I heard that you did.
Who?
- Gary.
- I didn't rip Gary's off!
There you go lying again!
Hurry up and rip his off!
[Tae Hwan eliminates
Kwang Soo's name tag with a force.]
- That's not it...
- You ripped it off.
[Huh? It seems like
Kwang Soo has something to say?]
- You ripped it off, right?
- No, this...
[Huh! This is!!]
What is this?
[Park Tae Hwan - Out!]
[Jae Suk searching for
the water bottles on his own.]
[Red team also discovers the
red potion.]
[Heads off to the witches' house
immediately.]
Choose who you'd like to oust.
[Cheering after realizing the secret!]
[The member that they chose
to oust is Tae Hwan.]
- Who would you like to have put this on?
- Kwang Soo.
[Park Tae Hwan- Out
mark put on Kwang Soo's back!]
[Park Tae Hwan - Out! Park Tae Hwan - Out!]
What did he say?
Wow! This is crazy!
[Park Tae Hwan - Out! Park Tae Hwan - Out!]
What is this?
Kwang Soo!
Did you do it?
- That really is something...
- Tae Hwan...
- And Kwang Soo's not out?
- No, I'm not.
You stay alive?
Seriously... at the end,
he does stab me in the back.
[Park Tae Hwan realizing what Running Man
is about with his whole being.]
Month of August really is
turning out to be something else!
Tae Hwan!
Wait... this is just a game.
[This can't be how it ends...]
[The next day]
[Marine Boy's counterattack]
[The God of competition, Park Tae Hwan
bringing Running Man down to their knees.]
- Running Man really seems like a lot of fun.
- Isn't it fun?
- It really brings out the competitiveness.
- Of course.
When people watch it on TV,
they think 'Oh, that looks fun'...
but when they actually get to come on,
it really brings out your competitive streak.
[On the other hand...]
[The lonely tiger after losing
both Tae Hwan and Gary...]
What?
[Left alone with his gigantic name tag.]
- I asked, what you were doing?
- I was just resting for a bit.
Is he hiding?
Are you hiding out right now?
- No, I was just resting.
- What is Mr. Capable doing?
- Why are you here? What are you doing here?
- Are you tucking in the sides to protect it?
[Stuffing the wings in his arm pits so
that they don't get ripped off.]
Can you oust one member
of the blue team for us?
Why are you asking that of me?
When I'm in this situation?
Come on, just do it.
Why would I?
Why would I in my situation?
- Oust just one member for us.
- Who?
[My life is on Ha Ha's back...]
[If Jong Kook tries to rip off Ha Ha's name,
I have to protect him...]
[All members of the Red team and Blue
teams are headed in that direction.]
Let's just finish off the one team first.
Seriously, these people...
That way, that way.
[Red team and the Blue team
need to cooperate in this situation.]
[Huh?]
[Not able to wait it out,
going head to head with one another.]
[A chaos where your enemy
and ally frequently changes.]
[It didn't fall off!]
[Just the wing got ripped off,
but the name tag remains fine!]
Rip his off first. Rip his off first.
[Since he already used his chance, if
his name tag gets ripped off, he's ousted!]
[Easily eliminates
Kwang Soo's gigantic name tag.]
This is what got ripped off.
- Let us the blue team just end it all here.
- Okay, let's go.
Yeon Jae, go!
Yeon Jae, go.
[Ha Ha trying his best to get
Jae Suk to tear off his name tag.]
You two battle it out.
[Yeon Jae pretending to run away...]
[And attacks from behind!
Eliminates Big-nosed brother's name tag!]
[Attacking with a distinct agility!]
Yeon Jae, great job! Yeon Jae...
[The Red team's mood shifts
from despair to success!]
Let's go for now.
Do you know how scared I was earlier
thinking Jong Kook may oust Ha Ha?
So that I can survive, I have to...
Ah! I'm so angry! Seriously...!
[Jae Suk's fate of having to protect Ha Ha
so that he can survive...]
[Miserable winged tiger being chased
by both teams.]
Ha Ha...
I need to oust Ha Ha.
[Jong Kook not aware that if he eliminates
Ha Ha's name, Jae Suk will be the one ousted.]
Let's just oust one person.
Just one... I can do it.
[Red Team headed in his direction.]
[Totally caught...]
[You found him...]
[Everyone gathering in front of
the tiger's cave for now!]
Is he in there?
[The women staying behind due to danger
and the men approaching closely.]
[We saw the shoes?]
[He's appeared! The winged tiger!]
- Let's fight! Why are we running away?
- Don't go in there. You stay back.
[But why is he always so scary?]
- Even though we knew...
- Knowing that he's in there, it's still scary!
I saw you guys approaching...
Listen...
A girl has to rip it off.
It has to be a girl that rips it off.
- Jae Suk, come in here.
- Come here, come here.
I won't rip yours off.
A girl has to approach him.
[Ha Ha taking the lead on purpose
so that his name tag gets ripped off.]
Hey, you get out of the way.
[Jae Suk trying to protect
Ha Ha no matter what.]
Let's do it together, do it together.
A girl has to take the lead.
Wow! It's still not easy!
When there are four of us here.
When there are four of us...
[Ha Ha, you brat... deliberately trying to
get your name tag ripped off.]
- 1... 2...
- Wait, what are we doing?
Hey, hey, hey!
[About to age a thousand years
trying to protect Ha Ha.]
[Ha Ha not feeling burdened since even if
his gets ripped off, it's Jae Suk who's out]
I don't care if I get ousted!
[With all his might, Jae Suk protects Ha Ha!]
[Ha Ha's purposely tries to get ripped off,
but Jae Suk keeps getting in the way...]
Hey! Rip mine off! Mine!
[Screaming at him to rip his name off.]
I told you to rip mine off, mine!
Why aren't you ripping it off?
[Danger! Protect Ha Ha!]
[Just then!!]
[In the moment that
Jae Suk is protecting Ha Ha!]
[Yeon Jae takes the chance!]
[Yeon Jae, in the midst of all the chaos...]
[...suddenly grabbing the opportunity!]
[Eliminates winged tiger's name tag!]
Kim Jong Kook - Out. Kim Jong Kook - Out.
[You all just wait and see...]
- Then we'll start attacking Son Yeon Jae now.
- Fine.
- But what is that red potion?
- What about you?
[If Jae Suk rips off Ha ha's name tag,
he himself is out. Just how will it all end?]
I know.
[Dramatic battle of the glares.]
Do you have something?
It now, Ji Hyo!
[Jae Suk attacking Ji Hyo first!]
Now, Ji Hyo! Rip mine off!
If you have rip mine off now!
[Just then!]
[Jae Suk eliminates Ji Hyo's name tag!]
[Ha Ha trying to rip off his own name tag
out of sheer desperation.]
[Ha Ha, it'll never go the way you want!]
[Okay, Yeon Jae.
I got him now so rip my name tag off!]
[Huh? Yeon Jae's
tearing off Jae Suk's name tag?]
[What kind of a plan is this?]
[Yoo Jae Suk, you're out.]
Yoo Jae Suk's out?
- Why?
- I tore his name off.
[Aha! Since Yeon Jae
already ousted Jae Suk...]
[The power of his chance in invalid.
Therefore, Ha Ha is just out.]
When I have Ha Ha in my grasp,
somehow I'll hold onto him...
then you'll oust me first,
then rip off Ha Ha's name tag.
Okay? I'll hold onto him.
What have you done, you idiot?
I thought I had it!
[The end is totally opposite of
what Ha Ha had dreamed of.]
[Red team's victory!]
[This is how Running Man training
camp day one ended.]
- We will start at 7 o'clock tomorrow morning.
- At 7 o'clock?
[Training camp - Day 2]
[Lodging out of a fairytale book.]
[7 a.m.]
[Starting with Cinderella's attic room.]
[In that room...]
Yoo Jae Suk? Jae Suk?
[Cinderella Jae Suk?]
- It's morning.
- Really?
The sun has already risen.
[The morning of a
difficult training camp's day two.]
[Putting on his glasses which are
as necessary as underwear.]
[The antennas making their rare appearance.]
Aren't you going to wake Kwang Soo up?
- We have to wake him up.
- He's sleeping in a princess' room.
[Inside the Cinderella's
pumpkin carriage room is Kwang Soo]
He's so pitiful.
[Looking like a giraffe that's escaped
the tiger and is now in hiding.]
Kwang Soo!
Kwang Soo... out.
[In the Little Mermaid's room
across the way.]
- Hello.
- Did you sleep well?
- Are you up?
- Yes.
- You got up early.
- Yes, I got up early.
- We have to get going right away.
- We have to go?
- Do I just go?
- Yes.
Miss Song Ji Hyo.
Please get up.
[Even sleepy-head Blank Ji gets up.]
Park Tae Hwan...
Please get up and go to
the living room.
[A difficult early morning
even for the Marine Boy.]
- Right now?
- Yes.
It would be more advantageous for
you to get there quickly.
[His heavy footsteps.]
- It's Ji Hyo.
- Blank Ji Hyo, you're up early.
[A torturous early morning for the beauty.]
Tae Hwan! Did you sleep well?
[And lastly, Gary's arrival.]
You're already up?
- What is it?
- Why is he like that?
[A blemish...]
- Let's see it.
- It's huge.
- It's not big.
- It's okay.
[Gary's sensitive skin...]
You have to take better care of your face.
[Having to pay more attention to taking
care of his back and his skin.]
We were going to do our morning mission
at the elementary school...
But with the hurricane,
it's temporarily closed.
[This was the day that the whole country
was in fear of the big hurricane.]
There's going to be
fierce gusts of wind and rain.
All the schools in the country will
be closed down tomorrow.
So since we can't do
what we had originally planned...
we're just going to do
a very simple game here.
Please write down one subject that
each of you feel confident in.
This mission will receive an advantage
for the final mission.
[Tae Hwan's already decided that
swimming is going to be his pick.]
It has to be a game
that you can do in this room.
And if the person needs a prop,
it has to be available in here.
Otherwise, you can't play the game.
Something we can do without props.
We will pass out 10 marbles per person.
Once it is decided which one of the events
that you wrote down will be played
then the person who feels confident to play
that game will bet a number of their marbles.
[Props prepared in a rush this morning]
Ddak-Ji!
Everyone scatter and write it down.
[Writing down Ddak-Ji right away!]
[Everyone's writing down something
without hesitation.]
[Time to announce the first event.]
The first game's event is...
[Gong-Gi]
Is Gong-Gi. (Similar to Jacks)
Is Gong-Gi.
[A game of Gong-Gi!]
How are we going to do this?
- Who wrote down Gong-Gi?
- Me. I wrote it down.
In the condition my body's in,
that's one thing I can do well right now.
[As long as there are 5 pebbles,
Gong-Gi could be played.]
Everyone gets only one chance.
You have to try to beat Kang Gary.
[The person who plays it the best wins.]
- I'll start with the first level.
- Everyone bet their marbles.
- Why don't you all place your bets?
- Will they think I'm easy and all place a bet?
This seems simple enough, right?
[Ha Ha bets one.]
You're entering? Okay.
- Yeon Jae also enters.
- Enter!
Why don't you bet some more?
- I'll bet two.
- You must be good at this?
- I'll bet one too.
- One.
I'm going to bet all five.
No, no... two.
[Confidence disappearing all of a sudden?]
- I don't want to take too much on right away.
- We're all entering except for Ji Hyo.
Ji Hyo can't do things like this.
- She has to do more rough things.
- That's right!
- Like playing horse or something.
- Horse!
Here I go.
[Ha Ha takes the challenge.]
Not everyone can play this.
You never know.
[Fail...]
[Haroro crumbles with Jae Suk's 'Hey!']
[Speechless.]
- Can you say 'Hey'?
- Of course, we can say it.
- It's just noise that we're making.
- We could've been cheering you on.
Hurry up and give them to
Yeon Jae.
[Looks as though he probably would've failed
without the interruption anyways.]
You can't even catch it.
- I could have done it.
- Forget it...
As long as I can get past Yeon Jae,
I could do this...
I think Yeon Jae is going to
be really good.
She's like the dark horse here.
- She's really good.
- And it hasn't been long since she played it.
- She's like the dark horse here.
- She's really good.
And it hasn't been long since she
would've played this game.
She's the best when it comes to throwing
something in the air and catching it.
- That looks dangerous.
- Pick this one over here.
- No, you have to make a play for it.
- Listen, teacher...
[The flexibility.]
- She's the best!
- She's good at throwing things and catching.
Yeon Jae's going to win this. She won this.
[Even level 3 is no big deal]
[The last level. Kkuk-ki]
This is what I'm bad at.
[Sadly fails at Kkuk-ki]
Yes! Yes!
I really can't do that part.
My wrist hasn't loosened up.
My wrist...
[Yeon Jae succeeded up to level 4!]
Is it my turn now?
[Jae Suk takes the challenge.]
- That doesn't look good.
- I don't think he'll be very good.
Or he could be oddly good at it.
- That was a little touch and go.
- He's better than I thought.
- He's good.
- Forget it. He's done.
[Fails immediately at level 2!]
Yes, yes, yes!
This really... this isn't really working!
I should have gone further.
Hey, Suk Jin bet 2.
[The biggest bet.
Suk Jin betting 2 marbles]
If he wins, then we're all in trouble.
- This is dangerous.
- It's dangerous.
- Those things are really light.
- Can I move them to my other hand?
- Of course, you can't!
- What are you talking about?
It's actually not as bad as I thought.
He really is good at the girly things.
[Elegantly spreading out the pieces.]
What is that? What is that?
Splitting them up. Splitting them up.
What... what is this?
This is the way to scatter them
for the second level.
- Suk Jin, you really are something...
- Grab the middle one!
- This one?
- No, the pink one.
- Okay.
- You can't coach him like that.
Sorry.
[Girly Impala brother's chaotic play.]
Since guys are normally bad at this,
I kind of hope that he does well.
[Even Jae Suk's 'Hey' isn't working!]
He's really good at things like knitting.
[Elegantly splitting them up again.]
Did you see that?
That's good.
You can grab three.
- Drop it!
- Wow... awesome.
[Easily passing level 3 too!]
[Huh?]
[After doing so well,
what are you doing on level 4?]
[4th level should've been done
the way Yeon Jae did earlier]
[Splitting them up like he's
been doing...]
He does have the skills,
but he doesn't know the rules.
- My turn.
- Okay.
[Muscleman, Coach Kook's turn.]
He's going to play this with those muscles?
- Just look at him!
- He really isn't good!
[Heavy handiwork.]
My hands are getting sweaty.
[Fail...]
Yes! Yes!
- He's really bad!
- Who do you think you're coaching?
It's not working because
my hands keep getting sweaty.
Yeon Jae got furthest with it.
- This has to be heavier for it to work well.
- Right?
[Marine Boy, Tae Hwan's turn]
Who scatters them out like that?
He's good.
[He's good?]
- I didn't think that he'd be good.
- That's hard. That looks hard.
The red one.
You should go with the red one.
[Wow?]
[Fail...]
[Even though he's shown us his quick
handiwork, he also fails]
If he doesn't get to Kkuk-ki,
then Yeon Jae...
Even if he can even get to that part,
he'll win.
I can't get comfortable.
You can lean forward a bit more.
If you end here when you're the one
who picked this event...
He actually is pretty good.
Yeah, he's good.
[Easily succeeds level 1.]
- He's making me nervous.
- This is nerve-wrecking.
[Gary tries Big-nosed brother's method.]
- He's good.
- No.
[Fail...]
Yeon Jae, Yeon Jae won it all.
[Top winner Yeon Jae, doubles
her win and gains two marbles]
- Yeon Jae right now...
- What a loss!
Then why don't we go on to
the next event?
I hope it's what I wrote down
for the next event.
[Ddak-Ji]
Ddak-Ji!
Oh my goodness!
- Ddak-Ji!
- Oh my goodness.
[It's Ddak-Ji...]
Jae Suk, Jae Suk...
[The legendary King of Ddak-Ji, Jae Suk]
[If he holds onto a Ddak-Ji and
gathers his energy...]
[The opponent's Ddak-Ji
ultimately flips over]
[This is Jae Suk's game of specialty.]
- We're screwed.
- What happens if no one bets?
- What if none of us bets?
- Then I can bet on myself, right?
I'm not going to enter this.
- What the heck, Gary?
- I'm not entering.
I'll bet one.
Tae Hwan is the dark horse here.
- I was going to see what he does.
- What are you going to do?
- I'll bet one too.
- Do we have to beat him then?
[Jong Kook, Suk Jin, and Kwang Soo
each enter with one marble.]
[It's King of Ddak-Ji, Jae Suk's turn to bet.]
I think betting two would be too weak.
- Four... bet four.
- Four?
[Following Yeon Jae's suggestion, betting four]
I'll bet four!
- I'm going to stay out of this.
- Okay, stay out of it.
You're not good at Ddak-Ji?
Jae Suk is way too good at it.
- There's no reason to even try...
- He's like a God when it comes to it.
I don't know, you never know.
There aren't many participants.
[The game to be carried out the way Jae Suk
makes the rules since it's his game.]
- Can I make the rules then?
- You'll move up to play the winner.
[Kwang Soo, Suk Jin, Jong Kook and Tae Hwan
playing in a tournament to beat Jae Suk.]
Then as for the matches...
We can't play like this.
- Why?
- Me against him?
- Jong Kook and I...
- You think this is too much?
[Ever unchanging strong composition
when it comes to this game playing.]
We can play Rock-Paper-Scissors
and decide.
Why do you guys make it seem like
we're not good at Ddak-Ji?
Why do you think we can't play this?
In that case...
I'll write down all of your names
down here...
- And we'll pick it that way.
- This is important.
- Yes, this is important.
- Of course, it is.
I'll announce the first match up.
Ji Suk Jin...
Park Tae Hwan.
[The first match is Suk Jin vs. Tae Hwan]
- You can do this.
- Of course, I can.
- I'm not going to give you a break.
- You never know how it'll turn up.
You have to win this!
- If you think you can beat him...
- Look at Tae Hwan swinging his arms.
How do you loosen up your arms
like that?
[The roar that shakes up
the whole living room.]
Rock-Paper-Scissors.
[Tae Hwan wins the Rock-Paper-Scissors]
- Why even try to beat him?
- Put it down here.
[One single game where it's hard to
guess who the winner is going to be.]
- Do I just go?
- Yes.
[Ah... a missed throw.]
Even though he's strong,
he misses his throws!
[Believing it's all about the power,
Tae Hwan misses the mark.]
- You have to hit it just right.
- You never know... you don't know.
Suk Jin, show us how it's done!
[Impala's miracle?]
[Ah! A full flip!]
It did a complete flip.
[Tae Hwan's turn again]
That's right!
[Easily flipping it over...]
Park Tae Hwan, wins.
What are you doing?
Suk Jin...
Lee Kwang Soo, Ji Suk Jin... I mean,
Lee Kwang Soo and Kim Jong Kook.
What... what are you doing?
- I'm going to use that one.
- What a joke!
[A fight over the ownership of Ddak-Ji]
Referee...
- Please make the call here.
- One who wins Rock-Paper-Scissors...
Why?
- Since he's the referee...
- What a weirdo, you are!
- The person who wins...
- It's a conspiracy here!
- This isn't right.
- There's a conspiracy?
Where? Where?
[Hates conspiracies.]
Rock-Paper-Scissors!
[Even losing the Rock-Paper-Scissors]
After all those years of working out,
all to play Gong-Gi and Ddak-Ji.
[Years of working out just in preparation
to play Gong-Gi and Ddak-Ji.]
- It takes just one good hit...
- You never know.
[With just one hit!]
[Giraffe losing
his opportunity to even hit it.]
- Who is it this time?
- Park Tae Hwan and Kim Jong Kook!
[Park Tae Hwang vs. Kim Jong kook]
- The person who loses this...
- Tae Hwan is like my little brother!
Why are you two so close all of a sudden?
It's seriously driving me crazy.
Tae Hwan, you go first.
[Cleanly conceding
to his famous little brother.]
And Tae Hwan really is going to go first.
[Confident little brother Tae Hwan doing
what his older brother tells him to do.]
- You can go first...
- No, that's okay. You go.
- It's okay.
- See? Ultimately, he's going first.
Since Tae Hwan has the flag behind him.
[Ah... a full rotation.]
You have to do it right.
This is trouble.
- Jong Kook, I'm okay. I'm fine.
- You're okay?
[Flipping it over right away.]
Why are you working so hard at this?
The one who travels through time!
[Facing embarrassment because of his
Tiger brother who shows no mercy?]
- You have to do it again.
- No, no... it's okay.
It's because I want to
go up against Jae Suk...
- I'm sorry, Tae Hwan.
- Fighting.
- Why are you taking that?
- It's mine.
Let's just do this.
Rock-Paper-Scissors!
[Jong Kook wins the Rock-Paper-Scissors,
with the victory hanging on the line.]
- I'm in total trouble.
- Is this such a good thing?
Am I supposed to be this happy
about this?
There should be at least one person
like this in every game.
What are you doing?
- You really are a weird person.
- Why are you getting so mad?
You're not supposed to keep stepping
on it like that. Fine, we're good.
Please, please, please...
You can't flip it over right now.
One shot... you have to get it done.
[It flipped over...]
[Over in just one shot.]
[Tiger's self-confidence crushing roar.]
He didn't even get to throw a single one.
[The one who chose the game didn't
even get to throw a single shot.]
- Best out of three?
- Okay, let's do best out of three.
- Best out of three wins, okay?
- Best out of three wins.
- Rock-Paper-Scissors.
- Rock-Paper-Scissors!
[The all-important Rock-Paper-Scissors.]
[The tiger wins again.]
[An undeniable roar again this time.]
- No way... no way.
- Yeon Jae, this is the kind of man he is.
[Jae Suk desperately wishing
for a missed shot.]
[The end...]
[Jong Kook wins.]
[Hasn't been able to throw a single Ddak-Ji.]
This is hard.
Why don't you throw it at least once?
[What...]
You're not good at Ddak-Ji, Jae Suk...
- I should have bet too!
- I should've bet more than one!
- Yeon Jae, we should've bet, right?
- Just one, I just bet one.
I need two then. I didn't even expect this.
I didn't even expect this to happen.
I just didn't... wow,
I'm glad I did this.
Don't even say that
you're good at Ddak-Ji anymore.
[Let's chalk it up as
having played the game.]
[The third event is...]
- What is it this time?
- It's stretching.
Ugh... stretching?
[Stretching!]
- I can guess who wrote this down.
- This one is definitely...
[Tying her hair?]
- Why are you tying your hair?
- How are we going to do this stretching?
Like I undoubtedly told you,
you just have to do what you're good at.
Then just show us a demonstration
as to what we need to do.
If we can follow the three moves
that Yeon Jae shows us... then we win.
- So you're trying to beat Son Yeon Jae?
- Yes, then we beat Son Yeon Jae.
Show us a little taste...
Well, the most basic thing is...
[That is?]
That's the little taste?
- This is the most basic stretch.
- That's the little taste?
Yeon Jae, what are you doing
this morning already?
- Yeon Jae, that's the most basic thing?
- Yes.
To us, that's like our life-long dream.
- Then... you can stretch forward like this...
- You can touch your toes?
[2nd move - Bend your upper body
and stretch over your lower body.]
- Touch your toes with your hands?
- If that's the 2nd, then what's the 3rd?
- What's the 3rd one?
- Stand up and do like a back-bend?
- Can you do that?
- Can you do it?
- She needs to warm up first.
- Can you do it first thing in the morning?
On my stomach...
I don't think I can do it either.
[A difficult move even for Yeon Jae
this early in the morning.]
Yeon Jae, don't do it. Don't do it!
Yeon Jae, don't do it.
- We thought you could do all that, sorry.
- Sorry, Yeon Jae.
- We thought anything was feasible...
[So the 3rd move is...]
[Stand up and do... this move.]
[Oh my...]
[This is the 3rd move.]
- So these are... the basics...
- Why are you being so shy about it?
No one is going to be able to do that!
Yeon Jae needs to bet something.
I'll bet... four? Five?
[Four or five?]
Yeon Jae!
Only the way she speaks is nice...
- Betting four or five?
- Sit down.
[Yeon Jae bets 4 marbles]
You're really betting 4?
I'm going to pass.
- You're good at it, aren't you?
- Tae Hwan, aren't you going to bet?
So I just need to do one of the three moves
that Yeon Jae showed us?
- Can't you do this?
- Tae Hwan, can't you do this?
- If Son Yeon Jae agrees to it...
- Then make it where the chest has to touch.
- Yes, like this.
- Was that what it was from the beginning?
[Her words are a bit different than
what she said earlier...]
- You said we just had to touch the toes.
- Isn't that what you said earlier?
- Yeon Jae, are you changing your story?
- I'm afraid that Tae Hwan can do it...
Wow... you changed your story?
- Then the chest has to touch?
- That's really going to hurt.
I guess Yeon Jae
is just going to take them all.
Why did you do it? Why did you show her?
In that case... we'll finalize the rules now.
- We'll finalize it now.
- To see who's going to enter.
- First...
- Can I change what I said earlier?
- Yes, you can change it.
- Really?
- You can change it.
- Then, you need to do 2 moves out of the 3...
[Immediately changing to succeeding
in doing 2 moves out of the 3.]
[Yeon Jae rushing to change the rules
in fear of Tae Hwan's abilities.]
- How can we...
- Bet. Make your bets.
What do you take
these marbles for to be doing this?
When Tae Hwan touched his
chest to his legs...
Then Yeon Jae, how about if we collectively
followed 2 of your 3 moves?
- All of us combined to do 2?
- Okay.
Then Yeon Jae... show us the 3 moves that
we're supposed to follow one last time.
- Okay, this is the first move.
- This is the first move.
- Bend forward like this.
- The chest has to touch completely.
- Now the second?
- Yeon Jae, it wasn't that bad earlier...
- Then... do it like this...
- And your arms, lift your arms.
[Second move-
Do the splits and raise your arms?]
Why did you add the arms?
- The third move!
- Well that one is like this...
[Do the vertical splits while standing up.]
So if you're going to do it, then do it.
Otherwise, don't do it.
[It is up to the individual on whether
they want to participate or not.]
We have to do two moves out of
the three?
- There's another solution. You...
- Should I rip his legs apart?
Just rip them apart.
[The way to beat Son Yeon Jae is to
forcefully rip Giraffe's legs apart?]
Ji Hyo, you can't do the splits?
- Are you going to participate?
- I'm really bad at stretching...
Just try it.
It may be better for Ji Hyo to do it.
- Give it back! Come here!
- I'm placing the bet for her!
- She's entered!
- Okay, Ha Ha has entered the game then.
- It's her marble.
- Okay, Ha Ha's entered.
But you entered the marble yourself.
Ha Ha, give a marble to Ji Hyo.
I didn't know you were so active about it...
I had no idea you were so all about it.
I'm going to pass.
- But if no one participates in this...
- No, you can participate Ji Hyo.
And I was told that I've already
entered this game.
- Other than Ha Ha...
- Anyone who else wants to do it, throw it in.
[Actively participating in it as if he's
been waiting for the stretching game]
[If just watching the replay of the scene,
like a person who's bee eagerly waiting...]
I never knew that Ha Ha was so
active about stretching like this.
Since everyone's putting their effort
into it, I'll participate in it too.
- Good, good.
- If we plan this right, we can do this.
- Kwang Soo...
- It's Yeon Jae against the rest of us.
We have to beat Yeon Jae.
If by any chance we win this,
everyone who entered wins?
Then starting with Song Ji Hyo.
The chest has to touch completely.
- And like this...
- And raise the arms too. The arms.
[Second move - Make sure to raise the arms]
[And for the third move-
Just stand and do the splits.]
Ji Hyo, show us your skills.
- Maybe the splits?
- You can try the splits, maybe...
- Ji Hyo...
- You might be able to do it!
- You can do it!
- Challenge!
[Blank Ji taking the challenge to touch
her chest to the legs.]
[Fail...]
- What was that? What are you doing?
- Fail. You failed.
Ji Hyo fails. Next up is...
the one who most actively...
[Stretching loving man, Ha Dong Hoon.]
Please shout out, 'challenge'.
- 1, 2, 3.
- Challenge.
You've got three seconds.
1, 2, 3!
[Fail...]
Okay, you failed.
[Sudden stretching's agony that can be
felt throughout the whole body.]
Okay, he failed. Next move.
[The third move-
Doing the splits while standing up.]
You can do it!
You have three seconds after
you say 'Challenge'.
You have to pull it off within
three seconds.
- Challenge!
- Challenge.
Challenge. 1, 2, 3!
- Okay, you can do it!
- That was a fail.
[Challenge that leaves only agony behind.]
His legs... his legs are too short.
[His love for stretching that
only leaves behind the pain.]
Next is... Lee Kwang Soo.
- Jong Kook, help me.
- There's not much time left.
- You have to help me.
- I can help. Tae Hwan... let's help.
Tae Hwan and I can help you.
- Which one do you want to do first?
- Do the vertical splits.
I just have to
stretch my legs out straight, right?
- Try it, just try it.
- He really is so tall!
- How should we do this?
- He looks like a giraffe.
[Forcing him to become flexible.]
- Isn't it done yet? Isn't this good?
- You have to stretch it out more.
[Forcefully put into the position,
will he be able to pull it off?]
[Zero flexibility.]
- You should've stretched it out.
- Okay, the next move.
Let's do the splits.
- You have to push him down from behind.
- Wow... he's so long!
Kwang Soo, if you can pull this off,
Tae Hwan can touch his chest to his knees.
You really are long though...
[After completing the chaotic warm-up,
ready to take the challenge!]
1... 2... 3!
[The Giraffe's explosion.]
You really kicked me hard!
Why did you kick me?
You asked me to help you!
Lee Kwang Soo, fail.
Our last surviving hope, Park Tae Hwan!
- If he can do two of the moves, we win?
- Of course.
Do the chest touching thing first.
He was really good at it.
It was just one in the beginning,
but she switched to two after seeing this.
To be honest, it wasn't even
the chest touch to begin with.
At first, all we had to do was to
touch our toes with our hands.
Yeon Jae changed the rules about 3 times.
She made the changes little by little 3 times.
Okay, I'm going for it.
[Succeeding the first move within moments.]
- Success. That was a success.
- No one else could do even that.
- You just need to do one more. One more.
- You just need to do one more.
How about the splits?
Don't you think that would be best?
Do I need to do it all the way
to the floor?
He just needs to raise his arms, right?
He doesn't need to go all the way down?
Okay.
- Really?
- Just do the splits, and raise your arms.
- I can just use my strength to hold it?
- That's right.
- Just don't fall over, no matter what.
Nice... nice!
Nice, nice, nice!
[Wow! He did it?]
[Just what will Yeon Jae's judgment be?]
How can you say that it's no good
just because I didn't touch the ground!
- Yeon Jae, you tell us.
- Well, the thing is, originally...
[Originally?]
Originally, this is what you had to do...
[Then you're not acknowledging it
because he didn't touch the ground?]
- You were supposed to touch the ground.
- That's what it was originally. Originally.
Yeon Jae says this was what it
was originally.
[The judgment call is that it's to be
what it was originally supposed to be...]
Since it had to be done
the way it was originally shown to us...
Beating Son Yeon Jae was a fail.
Son Yeon Jae wins!
There's no way for us to beat you.
[4 marbles times 2= 8. Wins 8 marbles!]
Don't you think it's funny?
What she should do...
[Tae Hwan's flexibility
even Yeon Jae was surprised by.]
[Thought she was going to acknowledge his
win, but pulls out 'actually, originally...']
Since she feels too bad to say that it's not,
and she can't say that he didn't win...
Since Tae Hwan is so much better
than she expected...
[Even though he did great,
originally, that wasn't it.]
- Originally...
There was no way we could've beat her.
[I shouldn't have played...]
It would be nice if it was something
that I could participate in.
- Put as much water in your mouth as you can.
- What is that?
[Put as much water in your mouth
as you can?]
[Quickly raising up his hand.]
Hey, how can we measure the amount?
- Open up a full water bottle...
- With a full water bottle?
To see who can pour most water
in their mouth without swallowing.
- Then this will be over in just one try?
- Ah, hold it in your mouth?
[All the participants to do it
all at once.]
This is really weird.
But Yeon Jae just said very quietly,
'This is really weird...'
What's so weird about it?
- Everyone drink it at the same time...
- This is really weird...
[Yeon Jae unable to understand this game.]
Yeon Jae...
this isn't a game that we usually do.
- This is our first time playing this too.
- But games like this can happen routinely.
We'll make the judgment
after the count of three.
- Okay.
- But we can't hold our hand to the mouth?
No, you can't do that.
Even if the slightest bit of water
slips out, then you're eliminated.
If the water even slips out,
then it's elimination. Keep that in mind.
- Really?
- I'm going to bet four.
If you swallow any water, or if any
slips out, then you're disqualified.
Song Ji Hyo...
I'm going to sit this one out.
I thought you were deciding to go for it
when you took your glasses off.
- I'll take the challenge.
- You keep participating in everything.
Of course.
- I'm going to have to do this one too.
- One thing I do is participate.
- Son Yeon Jae?
- I'm not doing it.
- You're not doing it?
- Just do it, Yeon Jae. Please?
No... it's too weird.
- She says it's too weird!
- What are you saying is so weird?
I'm going to participate.
You have to participate in things like this.
- How much is everyone betting?
- I'm going to bet one.
- It's just water.
- I have a very small mouth.
- I'm going to do it and bet one.
- Tae Hwan says his mouth is too small.
Song Ji Hyo, please be the referee
and be very fair about it.
And Park Tae Hwan and can from his side.
Son Yeon Jae can help with it too.
[The weird game of putting as much water in
your mouth as you can is one simple round!]
[Overflowing nervousness.]
Why am I getting so nervous?
This is nothing!
Seriously, why am I so nervous?
Why am I getting so nervous
over these silly marbles?
I think this is going to hurt
my self-confidence if I lose.
Set, go!
Go!
Kwang Soo swallowed it.
Kwang Soo!
[The swallow that can be seen
by his bobbing Adam's apple.]
Kwang Soo's Adam's apple moved.
[The water is dribbling out.]
His water...
[Gary also poured in the water in excess.]
Someone save me!
[Impala brother also explodes.]
What the heck is this?
Why are we doing this?
- What is this?
- 1, 2, 3, 4, 5.
[Time over.]
Put your water bottle down.
The people left remaining can
put them down.
I'm eliminated, right?
- Is he eliminated?
- Yes.
Yeon Jae... seriously...
I was pretty good at it too.
- You lost!
- Didn't I win?
- I think Kwang Soo swallowed a little.
- I think he really did swallow some.
- How was Kwang Soo?
- His Adam's apple moved twice.
[The referee rules that
his Adam's apple moved twice.]
No, no, no!
My Adam's apple didn't move!
[Video replay]
Kwang Soo swallowed, Kwang Soo.
[And one more time.]
No! It just moved! I didn't swallow.
- Yes! I won!
- You're saying it moved not once, but twice?
- Your Adam's apple moved twice.
- It was worth the challenge.
Okay!
That was a beautiful challenge for you,
whom always participated in the games.
You just need to give me two.
I haven't won a single one yet.
Why don't we play a final round?
Yeon Jae has the most right now,
and we...
- Even if I bet it all, it's not enough.
- Even if we bet everything, it's not enough.
Then... let's pick the best one
out of these.
It's time to choose.
Chicken fight.
I don't think this is good.
[Chicken fight recommender]
Seriously...
you have no conscience, do you?
When we have Son Yeon Jae
and Ji Hyo here...
You were going to play chicken fight
against Yeon Jae?
I doubt Yeon Jae would've participated.
Seriously... not this one.
Guess who's face it is
while blindfolded?
[This is definitely...
Experienced Blank Ji...]
- Holding breath.
- Don't do it, it's Park Tae Hwan.
[Definitely wrote in what they're
good at.]
- Tae Hwan, I'm sorry.
- I can't do it.
- How can we do the breath holding?
- Tae Hwan, I'm sorry.
Seriously... Yeon Jae's stretching,
and your breath holding.
[They both proposed the one thing that
they're the best at in the world.]
Draw a line and see
who gets closest with their marble.
- Let's go with this one.
- Let's hold onto that one.
- Then let's go with this one.
- Everyone can play this game.
- Then... let's go with this one.
- Cola Cider.
Okay, I'll explain the rules
of the game.
If you are touching the line, it's cider.
And if you're right on the line, it's cola.
- Does that even happen?
- But... if you go over, then it's out.
Then since I'm the referee,
I'll stand here and make the calls.
Please tell us the order
of who's going to go first.
First up is Yoo Jae Suk.
- Why am I the first to go?
- Because you're the first one.
Is there a need for a different reason?
[Jae Suk, the first to take the challenge.]
Foul!
- We can't kneel down like that?
- He gets a foul for being so ugly.
Do it with a nice expression
on your face.
- With a nice expression.
- Then I can't play?
[One more time with a nicer expression...]
Don't try to do it too well.
Why are you trying so hard?
[Throwing it towards the line...]
[Cola? Cider?]
[Out...]
Out!
- I'll do it again. I'll do it again.
- Why?
Please let me do it again one more time.
Let me do it one more time.
- You can't do that!
- You can't let him. No way.
[Jae Suk - Disqualified]
- Okay, disqualified!
- Disqualified.
Give me back me kneeling down
to you earlier.
- What?
- Give me back my kneeling down!
I didn't accept it!
- Give it back. Give it back to me.
- I didn't accept it!
Since you owe me a debt,
give me your knee later.
You have to give it back to me.
You can give it to me later.
- Even when I look at it...
- The next up is Ji Suk Jin.
- Why is it me?
- I shouldn't have gone first!
This isn't easy.
It's nerve wrecking because
you only get one chance.
[Suk Jin's pebble stopping
a way's before the line.]
I want to do it again.
- Suk Jin, you have to give a little force.
- I didn't want to go over the line.
The next up is... Lee Kwang Soo.
If you go past the line, you're out.
[Pretty close!]
- Next... Kim Jong Kook.
- Yes!
You have to be daring, Jong Kook.
Did you just call out your own name?
- Why would you call out your own name?
- Why?
- You're making Yeon Jae feel embarrassed.
- You have to pep yourself up sometimes.
[Just what will Coach Kook's skills be?]
I think it's going to go over...
What the heck is that?
- What the heck?
- Ugh, seriously...
I told you that you have to be
somewhat bold.
Kang Gary.
- You just need to hit this one.
- How can he do that?
Hit it, hit it.
I have to be somewhat bold...
Hey, are you copying me?
[Copy? Isn't that Coach Kook's
self-mantra?]
You have to be bold.
You have to be somewhat bold with this.
You can't be too weak with it.
[What the...]
- It's not easy to be bold.
- Song Ji Hyo.
[The next up is Blank Ji.]
- Go for it.
- That won't be good.
[Throwing it with a little force.]
[Currently, Jong Kook is in first place.]
[Ah... unfortunately, it's out!]
You should've hit it!
- Why should she have hit it?
- Ji Hyo, you should've knocked it out!
[Not wanting to see Mr. Capable
place first even in a game.]
Son Yeon Jae.
- Yeon Jae, Yeon Jae...
- Why am I always the last one to go?
- Don't throw it, but shove it.
- Like this?
Yeah.
[Just what will happen?]
[Sliding towards the line.]
[Will it shove Jong Kook's pebble out?]
[Or will be it out on its own?]
[What! That is?]
[Yeon Jae's pebble touching the line!]
- It didn't go out?
- No, it's touching the line.
This is cider. Cider!
[That is cider.]
- Yeon Jae...
- Wow!
[Yeon Jae climbing up to first place.]
Jong Kook is arguing
that it went over the line.
Originally...
originally, this isn't what it was.
- What do you mean? This is right.
- I told you originally, didn't I?
And lastly, Park Tae Hwan.
With him being the last,
I'm getting really nervous.
But Yeon Jae...
wow... Yeon Jae really is something.
He is seriously envious of her right now.
- Will it be better to do it like this?
- Shove it on the floor.
If he does this and it doesn't work,
he's going to ask for a do over.
He is totally your style then.
[The power brothers with so much
in common.]
They really are so similar...
[To where all the pebbles
are sitting gathered.]
If you had put a little more force behind it,
it would've pushed mine up.
- Ha Ha is the last one now.
- Ah, Ha Ha is still left to go.
- Ha Ha still has to go.
- You can do it... cola.
[he did hit a pebble out of there!]
- He didn't get anything.
- Did you shove mine out?
[Jong Kook's pebble that's been
pushed out.]
Jong Kook... disqualified.
The winner of our morning's indoor games...
Yeon Jae!
- She really did great.
- She's pretty good!
[The battlefield inside the hurricane.]
['D' high school in Pocheon!]
[Yeon Jae with most marbles earned from
the morning mission is first to enter.]
- You need to choose a card.
- Just one?
This is your final mission location.
[Why a card all of a sudden?]
[Just what is the meaning behind
these cards?]
[Enter in the order of winning earlier,
and choose a card.]
[A number on the cards...
just what is the meaning behind them?]
This kind of looks like my old school?
Is this not it?
That's me.
This is my alma mater.
Mike testing...
I can hear something.
[We would first like to thank all the students
and participants for helping with the filming.]
I will now tell you the rules of the game.
[Today's mission is...
to rip off the numbered name tags.]
Rip off numbered name tags?
You have to rip off the name tags
in the order of the number you picked.
[The hunt starts by the numbers
that they've each chosen.]
[This is the secret behind the
card's numbers.]
[The first target is...]
[Number 9!]
[Find the number nine tag,
and oust the person.]
[Just moments prior]
I feel an energy emanating from this one!
[Mr. Capable choosing card number 9.]
You need to oust number 9.
Why is number 9 first?
[This target hunting starts from number 9
and works its way down to number one]
Once number 9 is ousted,
your next target is number 8.
[Big-nosed brother with number 8.]
It should be 1, 2, 3, 4...
The person who's become the target...
can rip off someone else's name tag
and switch out your numbers with them.
[If you become the target,
take someone else's name tag!]
[Also... there's a secret opportunity that'll
be revealed once the allotted time is up.]
Thus, do not let your guard down.
Then we have to eliminate number 9
first no matter what?
But number 9 can target me too?
[However, number 9 can come
gunning for you too!]
[I will announce your first target,
number 9.]
He's going to announce who it is?
[Revealing of target number 9,
Kim Jong Kook]
[Target hunting - Target number 9.
Attack Kim Jong Kook]
[Cheers of joy!]
[The opportunity for all 8
to get Mr. Capable!]
- Nice, nice...
- He's the first to go to jail for once!
- Get Kim Jong Kook!
- Get him!
But we have to go around together since
Jong kook can get one of our name tags too.
If Jong Kook gets one of ours,
then we're the ones to get ousted.
This is awesome.
- This really is awesome.
- Awesome... wow! Awesome!
[Target hunting.
Target number 9 - Kim Jong Kook]
[Even though he's Mr. Capable...]
[Will he be able to survive against eight?]
[Nervousness...]
I just need one person to walk in here.
If I can just get one person...
[He needs to rip off someone else's name tag
and switch out the numbers to survive longer]
I'm really... nervous right now.
What?
- Why don't you show this to me?
- What?
- This project.
- What is it?
Betrayal.
[A textbook-like project to the Giraffe,
the king of betrayal]
[Can't let their guard down!]
[In search of number 9, Kim Jong Kook]
[Just then...
a very passive Big-nosed brother...]
[Since if number 9 Jong Kook is ousted,
him being number 8 is the target...]
I need to look for an
opportunity to ambush someone too.
[I'm next...]
[Number 9, Mr. Capable not able to
step out like he did earlier.]
[Target number 9,
Jong Kook in extreme danger!]
[Tae Hwan just passing by without
checking out the inside of the room.]
[He has to catch someone to escape
his predicament of being the target...]
I have to somehow get someone
no matter what.
Did he just go home?
You have to protect me.
Thanks.
[Second round of danger.
This time, it's Ha Ha and Yeon Jae...]
What if he's in here somewhere?
[Target number 9 Jong Kook
flees outside!]
[Number 9 Jong Kook the beast
eyeing others!]
- Over here! Over here! Third floor!
- Third floor!
What? Where?
[Others are headed to where the fight
is after hearing all the noise!]
Where? Gary!
[Spectacular scene of number 9's hunting!]
[Definitely Mr. Capable.
A target not easily giving in...]
[If Jong kook can tear the name off of
one of them, he can live too!]
Over here!
[Just then!]
[Third floor!]
I'll go get them.
Yeon Jae, hurry up!
You can't walk slowly like that.
Over here!
- Up, up. Upstairs!
- Where? Where are you?
[If you take too long, someone will
be had. Hurry!]
- Is it over here?
- This is where all the noise came from.
[Next target, number 8 Suk Jin,
no longer following behind them.]
[Escaping to somewhere
far away from the action.]
I think I'm...
[Mr. Capable still holding out.]
[That stamina! That strength!]
Hurry up and get here! Hurry!
He's here!
[Finally all the members have
gathered at the hunting ground!]
[But he's somehow still holding out...]
[Finding himself at a disadvantage,
Mr. Capable sticks his name tag to the ground.]
[All the attacking hunters!]
Do it quickly! Do it quickly!
[Oh my goodness...]
[Marine Boy Tae Hwan stepping up
to get the name tag!]
[Number 9, Kim Jong Kook, out.
Kim Jong Kook, out]
But... where did Mr. Ji Suk Jin go?
The next target is number 8,
Ji Suk Jin.
[Big-nosed brother escaping the
danger early.]
I'm seriously about to go crazy.
The next target is number 8,
Ji Suk Jin.
This is seriously driving me crazy.
I seriously don't want to
just lose easily today.
[His personal VJ in the hideout too?]
[Continuing to film from
the closet from across the room.]
[Will he... be able to
survive for long in there?]
Why has everyone become so relaxed since
number 8 Suk Jin has been announced?
[Everyone looking so relaxed after it being
revealed that Ji Suk Jin is number 8.]
So that why when we were searching earlier,
Suk Jin wasn't really being serious about it.
When we came up
to the third floor earlier by ourselves...
He kept opening and closing the door
to the same room by himself.
I bet he's in there. Let's go.
[Obviously hiding out in that room.]
There's no reason for us all
to even go.
[But... wait a minute...]
[The number that I picked earlier...]
[Number 7!]
[I'll be up next... what do I do?]
There's no way you can film me
in this situation.
You're filming me?
You can see me?
[Just stay in there quietly...]
[The search team working with
a lot of ease.]
[Ace Ji Hyo heading to the costume room
where Big-nosed brother is hiding!]
[Huh? Did she not see?]
[It's a camera!]
[Ace Ji Hyo discovering
Big-nosed brother's camera by chance!]
He's in here... he's in here.
[Do you see the camera over there?]
[Searching out a suspicious spot!]
[Where is he?]
[Target number 8, Suk Jin's ambush!]
[Even though he jumped out eyeing Ji Hyo,
Tae Hwan is there to protect her!]
[Target number 8, Ji Suk Jin, out!]
- Target number 8, Ji Suk Jin, out.
- I should've torn his name off.
[The news of Suk Jin being ousted
which doesn't come as a surprise to anyone.]
[Now...]
[It's time for me to become the target.]
[The next target is number 7...]
[It's number 7, Park Tae Hwan.]
[As soon as the target is announced,
Tae Hwan attacks Ji Hyo right away!]
[He ripped off her name tag?]
Are you okay?
[Song Ji Hyo, out. Song Ji Hyo, out]
[Wow... wow!]
[As soon as he became the target,
he attacks as if he's been waiting for it.]
[Tae Hwan gains Ji Hyo's number 1!]
[Number 1,
the very last to become a target!]
[The next target is, number 6, Kang Gary.
The next target is, number 6, Kang Gary.]
The next target is, number 6,
Kang Gary.
[We should've eliminated Tae Hwan
when he was target number 7...]
What do we do?
If Gary could...
[If only number 6 Gary could
eliminate Tae Hwan...]
If Gary doesn't get him right now,
then you, Yeon Jae and I...
We may not even be able to get him
with all of us ganging up on him.
[The big burden is that
Tae Hwan is number one right now...]
Gary?
[The simpleton only thinking of
catching Gary right now.]
[An extremely suspicious looking place.]
Hey!
[Discovers Target number 6, Gary!]
- Are you okay? Are you okay?
- Stand still. Just stand still!
- What are you doing? Get away from me!
- Come on! Come on!
Already?
[No! If Ha Ha ousts Gary,
it'll be too hard to oust Tae Hwan!]
- Ha Ha!
- Dong Hoon!
[The children's cutthroat play.]
[Anyways, neck and neck. Seems as
though one of the two will be ousted.]
- Ha Ha... Ha Ha... wait.
- Hurry!
Listen to me.
[Gary, rip off Tae Hwan's name.]
Why are you so fast?
[But Gary who doesn't notice the signs...]
[Seems to notice Jae Suk's name tag...]
[Stupid...]
[Yoo Jae Suk, out. Yoo Jae Suk, out.]
That's not it...
What the heck is this when I
just came to explain out plans?
You should've told me about it sooner!
[Of all people, tearing off number 5
Jae Suk only to become the target again.]
Why? Why again?
I have no other solution than here.
[Going back to his previous hiding place.]
[The next target is number 5, Kang Gary.
The next target is number 5, Kang Gary]
Where did Gary go earlier?
Gary...
[Tae Hwan searching for his target in leisure.]
[Wait...]
[Use Gary this time to oust Tae Hwan?]
- You startled me.
- We're supposed to oust you right now.
- But Tae Hwan... Tae Hwan is the problem.
- I know.
I will bring Tae Hwan down here, okay?
And, look... look.
- Make it seem like you're in here.
- But I can't go in there.
Kwang Soo, come here.
- Tae Hwan's on the third floor. Third floor.
- Third floor? Come here.
[World class when it comes to strategizing.]
[Gary's hideout complete.]
[Time to lure in Tae Hwan!]
1, 2, 3! Tae Hwan! Tae Hwan!
[In front of innocent Yeon Jae...
These adults teaching her such nice things.]
- Tae Hwan!
- Over here!
[Tae Hwan rushing to the rescue
without knowing anything.]
Where are you?
Tae Hwan!
[Tae Hwan being lured into their trap.]
[Ha Ha and Kwang Soo starting to act
as though they've found Gary!]
Go take a look.
[Tae Hwan, I feel so bad...]
[Getting ever so close...]
[While Ha Ha distracts Tae Hwan's gaze
so that he doesn't turn his head.]
[Gary's preparation to attack
Tae Hwan is complete!]
[Now's the chance!]
[He was tricked into being ousted
in place of Kwang Soo yesterday too...]
[Even though he did want to
get his revenge on it...]
What happened? What happened?
[Park Tae Hwan, out.
Park Tae Hwan, out]
[Tae Hwan's number 1 is now Gary's!]
I told you yesterday that
you can't trust anyone! I'm sorry!
It really is something else.
[Ah... is this really the end of it?]
- Anyways... we succeeded.
- Success.
[Running Man's political plays that
put the world wide star away!]
It was like a movie... a movie.
From now on, it's war.
We just have to oust each other in order.
- Who's number 4?
- We don't know.
I'm sure it'll be announced.
- Isn't it you?
- It's you, isn't it?
Gary's was number 5 just until
a moment ago.
- It's got to be one of you two...
- [The next target is...]
- It really isn't me.
- [Number 4, Lee Kwang Soo!]
[Target Hunting.
Target number 4, Lee Kwang Soo.]
[The hunting begins right away!]
- Wait! Listen to me for a second!
- Why would we listen to you?
It's right now, rip it off!
It's now. Yeon Jae,
hurry up and tear it off!
[Running away quickly down the dead end!]
[Oh! The giraffe's counterattack?]
What do we do about them now?
Hurry, Yeon Jae.
You have to go and tear it off.
But I'm number 3...
[New groom, Penguin vs. One-sided
love mania, Giraffe. Dream match!]
[The Giraffe's long arm attack!]
[Kwang Soo eliminates Ha Ha's name tag!]
[Ha Ha, out! Ha Ha, out!]
[Now Kwang Soo moves up to
number 2...]
Ugh, I'm so pissed.
If they can't oust Tae Hwan,
there's no way that any of them can win.
Ha Ha kept pointing me to some weird place,
like a closet or something...
[If the penguin hears himself
being talked about...]
What? What about me?
Ha Ha, let me just ask you something.
You lured me into a trap, didn't you?
- You lured me into a trap, didn't you?
- No, we all did.
I knew it.
You know why you were lured in?
Because you only think about yourself.
- Because they already have it figured out.
- Hey, what is that?
[Huh? Reappearance of the cards?
By any chance...]
I really wish that either Jong Kook
or I can come back to life.
I think there's a way to come back to life!
There's a card here that gives you
another chance at life from jail.
Do you even have any conscience or not?
Just two people out of all of you...
have a possible chance at another life.
If Jong Kook and Tae Hwan get it...
[This is the identity of the secret chance
that they've been told about earlier!]
[Time out. Time out]
A resurrection card
has been activated in jail right now.
A resurrection card?
A resurrection card
has been activated in jail right now.
Where did they get the resurrection card?
- In moments, two people will be resurrected.
- Two people?
[A strike of lightening.]
Who?
- How do I trust you guys?
- No, don't worry.
Since the order goes this way for now,
let's trust each other and work together.
I doubt that Tae Hwan will get
back out here.
[Come on... no way...]
- Yoo Jae Suk can choose his card first.
- At this rate, our chances aren't low either.
[A pretty high chance if it's
two people out of the six present.]
- Can someone else first...
- What did you say?
- Just go ahead and pick one first.
- Please just do it already.
You're going to have to pick
sooner or later.
[Yoo-ruce Willis chooses his card!]
- Oh my God!
- Is it a resurrection card?
- Is it a resurrection?
It's a dud.
But it has the R sticker on it!
I thought it was a resurrection card.
- But it has the 'R' on it!
- But it looks the same front and back.
[The card that looks the same front
and back is a dud card.]
- Seriously... that really is so...
- It's not a resurrection, but a resuRRection.
I have to get out there right now!
- Please pick the resurrection card!
- If both of you get it, that's huge!
- It would be nice if one of you got it.
- Just one of you should go, not both.
But if Jong Kook gets out there,
it's over!
Did you see that it's different?
But if you do get the resurrection card,
we'll be cheering and it'll be hell out there.
- What?
- What is that?
- They're in big trouble!
- You're saying I got number zero?
What does number zero mean?
It means that you've been
resurrected as number zero.
- Then what happens?
- You're on top!
[Even above number 1...
The last of the last target!]
Kwang Soo!
Please do something about Kwang Soo!
If it's number zero,
isn't it after number one?
- It's the last one.
- Right?
[100% real! Kim Jong Kook
resurrected as number zero!]
Okay... I've got another life.
I should hide somewhere and wait.
[The ones left alive still don't know
about my resurrection...]
[I will get rid of them all one by one.]
- Now... there are four cards left.
- It'll be fun to see who gets it.
There's only one of you
who will get resurrected.
Since there's only one card in here,
all four of you will pick at the same time.
Jong Kook doesn't know which one
of you is going to be resurrected either.
- I'm going to pick this one.
- If Ha Ha gets it, it'll be so unfair.
[Each picking a card of their choosing.]
- You have to take the one you pointed to.
- Really?
I'll take this one.
Okay then, I'll take this one.
And I take this one?
Okay... only one of
you is going to get a number.
That number is number 4.
- If it's number 4...
- Jong Kook picked the best one then.
If you get the 4, that person becomes
the target the moment they walk out of here.
- The moment they walk out of here...
- It's not such a good thing then.
It may be better to just stay here than
be the target as soon as you get out there.
No, that's not the case.
That's not true.
The person could get out there and gather
everyone and oust Jong Kook.
You can rip Jong Kook's name off too.
[Anyways, the person who picked
the resurrection card is?]
- Let's see who it is.
- You can't see off the camera reflection.
Okay... 1, 2, 3!
[Oh... my goodness...]
Put your arm down first.
You just stay here.
[Park Tae Hwan resurrected as number 4!]
How can things go so well like this?
- Come here... come here...
- Tae Hwan...
- You can do this... you can do this.
- Tae Hwan... fighting.
This is really awesome.
Tae Hwan was the last to pick, right?
[Almost like a lie, Mr. Capable and Marine Boy
have both been resurrected!]
[The next target is number 4,
Park Tae Hwan.]
The next target is number 4,
Park Tae Hwan.
[Tae Hwan being more calm
after becoming resurrected.]
[Avoiding the main paths
and listening carefully.]
I wonder if they're
searching for me right now?
[If anything, the hunters are
the ones being more cautious.]
Hey, why are we walking around
in so much fear anyways?
- Why are we being so afraid?
- There are three of us here.
[The three not knowing anything else other
than Tae Hwan's resurrection.]
[Searching in earnest for number 4,
Tae Hwan.]
[The Giraffe's nightmare.]
[The sinner who most actively worked
to lure Tae Hwan in earlier.]
Aren't you going to get Gary?
He's number one.
Gary was the one who ripped your name off.
Gary is on this floor too somewhere.
- But you lured me into a trap.
- I didn't lure you in.
I objected to it the whole time.
[It's Tae Hwan! What do I do?]
Did you see?
- Yeon Jae. Yeon Jae, come out here.
- Yes?
- Come here.
- Where's Gary? Gary's number one.
If you don't get him now,
you won't be able to get him.
Let's get him together. Tae Hwan...
I don't know what I should do...
- Yeon Jae, you can just stand over there.
- Really?
Yeon Jae... just because he tells you to go,
you're really leaving right away?
I can't fight.
Of my goodness!
Oh my goodness!
[Discovers Mr. Capable,
the other one who was resurrected!]
Who is it? Is someone there?
Is someone else there? Who is it?
Who's standing over there?
[Can only laugh out of shock...]
Is this even allowed?
What is it?
Can't I just go on ahead to jail?
This is too scary...
it's too bloody out here.
[Shaking after seeing that
Mr. Capable has been resurrected.]
It's either you go, or we go, Tae Hwan.
Listen to carefully...
Tae Hwan, Tae Hwan! I'll just lie here.
I won't do anything and just lie here!
I'll just lie here!
[Gary in danger!
Kwang Soo also in danger!]
[Just then, the Giraffe springs
a surprise attack on Marine Boy!]
[With that turn of events,
Gary's name tag is eliminated!]
[Number 1, Kang Gary, out.
Number 1, Kang Gary, out!]
Lee Kwang Soo!
Hey! Lee Kwang Soo!
[That... that person's been
resurrected too?]
It's not me... Jong Kook is a
better target in this instance.
[The next target is number 3, Son Yeon Jae.]
Who?
[It's me!]
[As soon as she becomes the target,
she attacks Kwang Soo!]
[The best thing for the Giraffe to do first
is to escape the situation.]
[Even the struggling Gary is imprisoned.]
- Does your back hurt?
- We've decided that your back doesn't hurt.
It hurts.
Even though it hurts, I got a little greedy.
I got greedy as soon as the game started...
It hurts...
Do you know who else has
been resurrected?
- How did you know?
- I saw him.
I saw him on my way down here.
But why aren't they announcing
Jong Kook's resurrection?
Because he's number zero.
[Because he's number zero, him being
a target hasn't been announced yet.]
There's even a number zero?
- You're saying there's number zero?
- He becomes the target after number 1.
Don't you think it'll be fun?
Then I'm glad that I've got mine ripped off,
because I was number one.
- You were number one?
- Yeah!
- This is much better to be in here.
- Tae Hwan's number one now?
- Tae Hwan's number one?
- Then it's Tae Hwan against Jong Kook?
Can't we go out there to watch since
we haven't done it in a long time?
Can't we go watch this?
[Coach Kook and Park Tae Hwan,
a dream match!]
Tae Hwan is really worked up right
now because of me.
But Yeon Jae is
the unknown variable right now.
Because Tae Hwan won't be able to
rip Yeon Jae's name off.
- But there's Kwang Soo...
- Kwang Soo will tear hers off.
[But the traitorous Giraffe
won't care who he rips the name off of.]
[Number 3 Yeon Jae,
going to catch easy Kwang Soo.]
[Where did he go?]
[Will she be able to become the dark horse?]
[The Giraffe's surprise attack!]
[Closing in on number 3, Yeon Jae!]
[Number 3, Son Yeon Jae, out.
Number 3, Son Yeon Jae, out.]
You really startled me...
Ah, ultimately... Kwang Soo...
[The next target is number 2,
Lee Kwang Soo.]
Anyways, it's me again.
The next target is number 2,
Lee Kwang Soo.
[I have been waiting a long time...
for this moment to arrive...]
The hunting finally begins.
The next target is... Lee Kwang Soo.
[The Giraffe is sure to come up
with another ploy... What will it be?]
Jong Kook... Jong Kook...
- I'm going to get Tae Hwan right now.
- What?
I'm going to get Tae Hwan right now.
- You are?
- I think I'll be fine against Tae Hwan.
- It doesn't matter to me...
- Jong Kook...
He's coming up here.
He's headed up here.
[Target is number 2, Kwang Soo...]
Why are you running away when you said
you were going to oust him?
How can you be running away when you
said that you're going to rip his name off?
[Huh? After saying that he's going to
oust Tae Hwan, he's going after Jong Kook?]
[Totally caught.]
[A born double spy.]
Jong Kook...
- I knew that I shouldn't have let you lived.
- No, Jong kook...
I shouldn't...
have allowed you to live.
I shouldn't have let you live. I...
Being deceived by you like this...
It's not like that.
Tae Hwan...
[Jong Kook and Tae Hwan can't attack
each other since neither are targets now!]
You really aren't right...
- Jong kook... I can't even move right now.
- Why? Huh?
I know that you can't move.
- Let me at least put my arms down.
- Why?
Jong Kook...
[The Giraffe's counterattack?
Is Kwang Soo really determined today?]
I'm sorry, Jong Kook!
I'm sorry! What I did was wrong!
What I did was wrong! I was wrong!
I'm really sorry, Jong Kook!
[Tiger with no intentions to forgive.]
[The Giraffe goes for another try!]
[Attacking with his long arm!]
[A real battle with no concession!]
What is this?
[The final blow].
[Number 2, Lee Kwang So, out.
Number 2, Lee Kwang Soo, out.]
Pause time... pause time...
The next target is number 1...
the next target is number 1.
The next target is number 1.
[The next target is number 1...]
[Park Tae Hwan.]
[As soon as it's announced that he's target,
Tae Hwan attacks Mr. Capable right away!]
[The Marine Boy did it!]
What a sight seeing you like that
after playing me like a toy!
What did you say?
So this is why they're
all afraid of Jong Kook...
[The winning prize that
the winner Tae Hwan gets is...]
- That's really big.
- What is that?
What is it?
[Pocheon's specialty...]
[A set of ribs!]
A set of ribs! The specialty of Pocheon...
[Envious]
That's really delicious stuff.
[We sincerely thank Park Tae Hwan and
Son Yeon Jae for being with us.]
Anyways, todays winner...
Park Tae Hwan!
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Beautiful port city, Busan...
Full of youth and romanticism.]
Seeing the flowers adorning that,
it's girl guesting today?
[This time,
it's with flower middle aged men!]
[Im Ha Ryong]
[Son Byung Ho]
[Lee Jong Won]
[Shin Jung Geun]
[And the youngest? Go Chang Suk.]
[Busan vacation - Off to the diamond step!]
[Excited Running Man becoming one
with the passionate citizens of Busan!]
[While taking in the sights of Busan,
clear the first morning mission!]
[Stimulated senses...
The world's most dynamic vacation!]
[Middle-aged Flower men's Busan vacation.]