[Hot tempered Santa who likes to yell.]
[Grumbly Santa who gets sensitive over food.]
[Five different Santa's!]
[They're here on Running Man
with bags full of laughter!]
[This is what you call, Santa's dignity!]
[Cut throat Christmas race that takes
place on top of a snowy mountain!]
[A Christmas special that
everyone will find shocking!]
[Running Man - The Christmas special.]
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Gyunggi-Do 'G' Resort.]
[A place full of joy to chase even
the chilliest of the weather away.]
Jingle all the way!
You better not cry!
- Santa's Claus is...
- Why? Do you have something to cry about?
Aren't we going to have some female guests
on today since this is a Christmas special?
This is the perfect place to bring them
if it's a female guest we have today.
- The snow will give some cushion.
- I'll be able to trip them properly today.
Han Hyo Joo said that
she really appreciated being here...
She also said that she thinks she'll be
reminded of you tripping her over.
- She texted me several times.
- Really?
Anyways, who's going to be
our guest today?
We have some very lovable guests on the
show since this is a Christmas special.
Our guests who are like Christmas gifts are
waiting back there behind the cake right now.
Our writers knows how to
take care of us!
If all of you shout out, 'Come on out',
they'll make their appearance.
- Who could it be?
- Our lovable guests!
I can't wait to see who it is!
Our Christmas gifts!
Just who could be waiting back there...
just which angels are waiting back there...
- Our angels...
- Come on out!
- Who could it be?
[Who could be waiting to spend
a sweet Christmas day together...]
[Who could be the guests that
they'll be presented with?]
[Could it be girl group members
that the Giraffe wants?]
[Or could it be Geun Young
Kkuk is thinking od?]
[Could it be Jung Ah that
Big-nosed Brother wants?]
Give us a round of applause!
Merry Christmas!
[Who...]
[Is that?]
Give us a round of applause!
[Big brother Santa, Park Sang Myun.]
[Unwelcomed Santa, Jung Hyung Don.]
What kind of a reception is this?
[Ryu Dam, Shin Dong, and Juvie Train.]
[This is... what you call a gift?]
- What the heck is this?
- Juvie? What the heck?
What the heck is this?
Why are you playing a joke on us?
[Big boys who are taking their time
to climb down the steps.]
Why are you doing this to us?
- Are you pulling our legs?
- This is the holidays! What is this?
Sang Myun... what the heck is this?
Why is it taking so long for them
to come down the steps?
[Greeting them cheerfully for now?]
[Or... maybe not.]
[Greeting each other
forcefully from the get go.]
[Big brother protecting his little brother.]
[Futile kicks into the empty air
trying to find his footsteps.]
- What are you doing?
- Take care of him!
- He hit me!
- How dare you touch me?
How dare you touch me?
[Santa Hyung Don showing his unhappiness
by throwing a temper tantrum.]
- Come here...
- What the heck is this?
What the heck was that about?
What are you doing to Hyung Don?
Seriously... this is such a surprise!
What kind of a Christmas is this?
- What is this?
- Why are you doing this to us?
Why are there so many fatties here
as our guests today?
What do you mean, fatties,
you scoundrel? Fatties?
I should just throw all of you
down onto the ground!
Hey, should we show them?
Show them what?
[Show them what?]
What are you going to show us when you're
already tired from coming down the steps?
- Hey, Shin Dong!
- Yes?
I thought that you were chubby,
but you're actually very slim.
I think I'm the skinniest out of
all of us here today.
[But...]
[There's one unfamiliar Santa.]
[A rapper from the group,
Buga Kingz with Bobby Kim.]
[The master of Hongdae, Juvie Train.]
I thought you were one
of these guys' managers.]
The top performer in Hongdae...
still clubbing even after you got married.
How dare you!
[A flammable situation that blows up even
with the smallest bit of instigation.]
[A Christmas that's hotter than ever!]
You're Kim Jong Kook only on
Running Man!
[But this is Running Man...]
This is Running Man!
- Give it a rest.
- Just leave him alone.
[Finishing off by throwing
his arms up into the air.]
Isn't Hyung Don really funny?
He tells Jong Kook that he's only
Kim Jong Kook on Running Man
when this show is Running Man.
[Oh yeah...]
I think Hyung Don was confused
for a moment.
I think he mistook this show
for a Saturday night show.
[This is Running Man with Kang Gary,
whom he wishes he could have.]
Wait, everyone... stop stepping up
to just look around at the scenery.
Step back into your spot.
Just look at how
they're staring at you right now.
[Staring at them as if they're looking
at something wondrous.]
They're staring at us like
they're looking at celebrities.
They're looking at us like they're
seeing celebrities for the first time.
Hyung Don...
just stay quiet until you have to leave.
- In front of all these people?
- I'll just see you Saturday.
Anyways, these five guests that are here...
they're here on Running Man.
More than anything else,
I think it's going to be a lot of fun.
The writers didn't tell me who the other
guests were going to be when I asked.
- And I was the first one to arrive...
- Yes, but what?
And when I started seeing them arrive one
by one, they all pretty much looked the same!
[All the friends that started to arrive
we're all pretty much in a similar shape?]
That's when I realized,
'Ah, this must be the special today'!
- And what is this special?
- You know what this special is!
- And what is that?
- This kind of a special.
That's how I knew
what kind of a special this is.
Today's Christmas special is...
Snow fight race.
[Christmas special - Snow fight race.]
I'm going to give you a snowball
each time you finish a race.
What kind of an evil game is this?
[Conclude the missions that are
placed throughout the ski lodge.]
[At the end of each race, they will be given
snowballs depending on where they placed.]
The team that wins the final snow fight at
the final location is the ultimate winner.
For the first time in a long time
for this Christmas special...
the team that comes in last will have
to face a severe penalty.
- Wow, we haven't seen that in a long time!
- I really don't want to have to face it!
[A festival of men in long johns gliding
over the snowy hilltops.]
[This is the penalty that awaits the
team that comes in last today.]
So I hope that all of you put
in your best effort today.
- But, Kwang Soo...
- Yes?
- I bet you're really comfortable today.
- Why?
You have Hyung Don to take
over your role today.
That's why I have nothing to say today!
[Giraffe in danger of losing his role
that's taken him two years to cultivate.]
I'm better at things like this than he is!
Get out of here!
[Giraffe being disgraced.]
[Merry Christmas...]
[Snow fight race - Start!]
[Yellow Team: Jong Kook, Ha Ha,
Ryu Dam and Juvie Train.]
- Do we have to get on this?
- This is so cool!
- In one row?
- How can we all fit in the same row?
This is such a tight squeeze!
- This is too tight!
- This is too tight of a fit!
- Seriously...
- Sang Myun...
- We succeeded!
- Our team succeeded the mission!
We all fit in the same row!
Are we on the show for two weeks?
Why don't you just worry about
this week?
- Just worry about this week!
- You guys are total scammers!
I was really shocked to see you come
on our Christmas special show.
[I bet Hyung Don is feeling
pretty much the same?]
It's been eight years...
Eight years since I've made
an appearance on a Sunday program.
Then why did you come out?
You should've just stayed home instead.
- Ugh, it's so tight... so tight!
- It's tight because of you.
Let's move it!
I feel like I'm suffocating here.
[This much weight is a first
for the little train too.]
Why did we even get on this train
if we're going to be moving so slow like this?
Because it's still faster than you guys.
[Bingo?]
- It's giving you a ride.
- No, this is nice to get a ride.
I never knew a place like this existed
so close to Seoul like this.
I know...
only an hour away from Seoul.
[Blue Team taking in
the beautiful sights of scenery.]
[Now off to the slopes!]
[The blinding snow.]
What is that?
I see a flag over there?
- Over there.
- Where?
[In the midst of the white slopes...
a single flag flying in the breeze...]
Even though you're all wearing the
same clothes, the difference in your size...
You have two layers of coat on, don't you?
[Suspecting them to be wearing
a second layer of outerwear?]
Are you sure that Juvie isn't wearing
another coat over there?
Sang Myun, how many layers of
clothing do you have on?
- How many coats are you wearing? Seriously?
- I'm only wearing one coat.
Here's your first mission
for the snow fight race.
The ultimate duo that you think of when
the word Christmas is mentioned...
This is the Santa and Rudolph game.
This will be two people per game.
One person will be the Rudolph,
and the other one will be Santa.
If you look up behind you,
you'll see the starting flag.
Everyone will wait there,
until I give my signal.
Do you all see the small cone that's
a little below the flag?
You'll find that a sleigh is tied up
to the cone up there.
You have to dig out the tube sleigh
and ride it down the slope together
and Santa has to change into the Santa
stockings down below to win the game.
We have to change into the stocking?
We have to take our shoes off to
change and put the shoes back on?
You're really making all this
pretty annoying.
[Inducing a vomiting reaction?]
He's just trying to get some attention.
[The meaning of his dry heaving
that's been caught by his friend.]
I suddenly felt short of breath just from
thinking of having to walk up there.
But... how can the Rudolph lead
the sleigh?
Rudolph can ride up front
and Santa can ride in the back.
Why don't you listen more carefully when
he's explaining the game to us?
I'm listening to everything he's saying.
- That's how we start?
- Then who's going to pull the sleigh?
You can pull it! You!
We told you, Rudolph gets up in the front!
[A violent physical conversation
at every chance they get.]
I was just lightly asking you...
lightly asking.
Why don't we all climb up there first?
[Yellow Team moves up to the second round.
Red Team vs. Blue Team.]
Kang Gary!
I can't believe I missed...
Hey! Why are you trying to hit me?
- What the heck?
- This slope is really steep.
This isn't just snow!
I'm already exhausted.
- No, you're not exhausted... you can't be.
- But I'm... really tired.
Fighting!
[Red Team- Santa (Gary); Rudolph (Ji Hyo).]
Blue Team- Santa (Shin Dong);
Rudolph (Kwang Soo).]
Set... go!
[Run!]
Wait! Wait!
[Sprinting down the slope.]
[Sliding down on their bellies.]
[They need to dig out the tubes quickly!]
[Swimming through the snow?]
- Ji Hyo! Hurry!
- Hurry!
[Ji Hyo and Gary succeeding on
digging up their tubes first.]
[Gary and Ji Hyo are first
to head down the slopes!]
[Isn't it fast?]
[Coming down the slope!]
- Hurry up!
- What's taking you so long?
[Giraffe and Rudolph going
at the slowest speed.]
[Now the Santas just have to change into
the stockings and pull out the flag!]
[What? A drop kick?]
[Santa Shin Dong stealing the stockings!]
[Rudolph Blank Ji's full on chase!]
[Santa Gary waiting with his socks off.]
[What? Barefoot?]
Take off your shoes!
[A full on chase in the snow
while barefoot.]
[Bet they're really cold...]
[Santa Shin Dong with his socks
finally off.]
- Put at least one of them on for now!
- Gary!
Put it on!
- Put at least one of them on!
- Gary!
[Santa Gary also succeeds in getting
one of the stockings on.]
[With an urgent heart on the
cold snowy slopes...]
[Snow massage on his barefoot?]
Gary! Give me your foot!
[Revenge.]
[Getting one of the stockings
back in his possession.]
[Rudolph Kwang Soo's attack keeps
getting more forceful.]
Okay... I got it...
[The never-ending snow massage.]
- Don't let it get taken away!
- Give it to me!
Give it to me!
Put it on... put it on.
[Definitely our Ace Ji Hyo.
Taking on two of them at once.]
Wow! It's two against one!
Two against one!
- You're making this difficult!
- Sorry... please don't do this!
Just throw it to me!
Kwang Soo, gather up your strength.
[In the end, with the
Giraffe forcefully stopping her...]
[Santa Shin Dong heading to the flag
with both stockings on his feet...]
[Firmly rooted flag...]
What are you doing?
[Blue Team wins the first round!]
But... Ji Hyo... she really took care of you
with all her effort and devotion.
[Blank Ji taking care of Gary
with all her devotion.]
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry you met a man like me...
Get away from him!
What are you doing here?
- Let go!
[I'm sorry.]
- My hands are frozen.
- Are you a gazelle?
[The same gazelle that's said to come down
the mountain to help out the human beings?]
Are you sure you're not a gazelle?
What do you mean, a gazelle?
My nickname is the giraffe.
I'm not a gazelle.
[Then we'll go with the giraffe...]
Kang Gary...
- You really are so high maintenance!
- Why can't you put it on yourself?
I can't put it on myself...
I normally can't put socks on
by myself...
[Seriously high maintenance man
who can't even put socks on by himself.]
He really is...
he's so high maintenance.
Okay, the other two teams,
please go up the slope.
I feel like we're climbing
Mt. Everest right now.
[Just what's the big deal
about all this snow?]
[Why do we have to walk up there
when we could just take the lift?]
Fighting!
[Santa Sang Myun frequently dry heaves
from physical exhaustion.]
What have you done so far to
be acting like that?
[This is hard...]
You can get started once
you hear me sound the bell, okay?
- Ready...
- Fighting!
- Set... go!
- Do you think running will be faster?
[Start!]
[Taking it upon themselves to start off
doing physical gags.]
[Rudolph unable to control his own body.]
- Hey! Where is it?
- You're doing great!
- Hey!
- You're going great!
[Starting to dig up the tube sleigh.]
- Where do we have to dig?
- Where is this thing?
Okay, we got it!
- You can't get them separated!
- Slow... slow down.
We can't have them separated.
We have to tie them back together.
[Having to tie the tubes back together.]
[Trying to disturb them in the meantime.]
[Santa Sang Myun working hard to
dig up his sleigh.]
Move!
[Oh! Blue Team succeeds in
freeing up their sleigh!]
You got it! You got it!
Let's go... let's go.
- I'll get up front.
- Let's go.
- Okay, let's go.
- You have to ride up front.
[Riding the tube sleigh down the slope.]
[Wow... just how far are they going down?]
Over here!
They're coming down really fast!
[Both teams luckily coming to a stop
thanks to the cushioning walls.]
[Oh no! The camera...]
Hurry! What are you doing?
[Forget it... just head to the stockings!]
[The Blue Team also gets on their way
towards the stockings!]
Where are those two headed?
You two are being so slow!
[Santa Jae Suk starting to
take off his shoes.]
You can't take those!
[Santa Sang Myun with his quick moves!]
[Slowly starting to make their approach.]
Hurry! Hurry!
[Red Team succeeds in getting
one stocking on!]
[Blue Team also succeeds in
getting one on!]
[Now it's time for the stocking war.]
I'm sorry, Sang Myun.
- It's so cold...
- Be careful!
[Succeeds in stealing the stocking?]
My foot is freezing!
[The agony of being barefoot
that he can no longer endure.]
- Put it on!
- Put it on.
[Rudolph's strong defense work.]
[The Red Team wins!]
Yay!
My feet are freezing!
[Depleted of energy.]
[On to the third round with a tie.]
Hyung Don...
Why don't you be the Santa
and come up there with me?
Yeah, why don't the two of you go up?
- I feel like I'm going to throw up right now.
- You feel like you're going to throw up?
Then I bet it would be even funnier.
Go on up there.
- Is it the two of you?
- Yes.
[Red Team- Gary and Hyung Don vs.
Blue Team- Suk Jin and Kwang Soo.]
- Fighting!
[Make sure you win!]
[Easy Brothers quick on their feet.]
Okay! Let's pull it out!
Good job!
[Digging out their tube sleigh
within moments!]
Sit down... you have to sit down.
[What got into them?
Easy Brothers working well together.]
[Getting a good head start.]
Backwards... we're going backwards!
[Sweeping the stocking along with them.]
[Gary and Donner's chase is
a step behind.]
[Easy Brothers trying to go for the win.]
[Gary and Donner refusing to lose?]
[Throwing themselves into the mix.]
- You have to take off your shoes!
- I can't reach with my hands!
[Blue Team with one stocking already on.]
[Red Team not backing down easily.]
That's a Santa's hat!
[Santa Big-nose with
the Santa's hat on his foot.]
[The unknown location of
the disappeared sock...]
Where did it go?
Why are you taking my socks off?
[Gary dreaming of his revenge for earlier.]
Just stand still!
[An eye for an eye!]
[Santa Hyung Don getting a
snow massage on his belly.]
[Embarrassed at having
his belly button exposed...]
[Total chaos.]
Just give it to Kwang Soo.
Gary, just give it to him.
[Succeeds in stealing the other stocking?]
[Getting back his revenge...]
[All he needs now is to pull out the flag!]
[Stealing a stocking the moment before
he can pull the flag free!]
Why aren't you putting it on?
- Why aren't you putting it on?
- Then I'd have to go through all that again!
[Donner not wanting to get
into another battle for the win.]
I don't want to go through it again!
This isn't the time
for you to be acting like this!
You just wear it!
[The name of the game is about to change
into 'Get the stocking on the other person'..]
[Protecting his bare feet.]
We don't like to win.
We don't want to win... here!
Don't put it on... don't put it on!
Put it on!
Wait...
[Even delivering the flag to him?]
[Gripping onto it tightly.]
- We lost.
- We lost?
We lost... we lost!
[Blue Team wins!]
We lost...
- You did good...
- Kwang Soo...
- I can't believe you guys actually won.
- We did it... we lost the game.
So this brings the Yellow Team and
the Blue Team to the final round!
[Final round- Yellow Team vs. Blue Team.]
Us two will do it.
Why did we have to win...
Fighting! Fighting!
- Hey, keep it down.
- Why?
I said, keep it down. Your
team is nothing without Jong Kook.
- So you'd better keep it down.
- Just a bunch of kids.
They won't let us cheer just because
Jong Kook isn't here.
[Yellow Team- Jong Kook and Ryu Dam vs.
Blue Team- Sang Myun and Shin Dong.]
Look at Dam... look at Dam.
Look at Jong Kook doing
everything on his own.
Dam, get on.
I said, get on.
You have to sit in the back
since you're Santa.
[Sang Myun and Shin Dong getting
on their tube sleigh at the same time.]
[Sang Myun and Shin Dong picking up
more and more speed.]
[Crash!]
[Already battered up and bruised.]
[Forceful Mr. Capable.]
[Blue Team capturing Ryu Dam first.]
[Attacking his foot with the snow.]
Why are you taking my shoe off?
[The popular thing to do on the snow now
is to take each other's socks off.]
Hey! Why are you taking mine off?
- Hey, why are you taking mine off?
- Hey! Stop it!
I told you to stop it!
[Refusing Santa Shin Dong's advancement
with his beastly power.]
[Huh?]
[Why is he getting on his back
all of a sudden?]
What are you doing?
My feet are too cold.
This game isn't supposed to be
played like that.
I don't think I can do this anymore.
[Giving up?]
I know how you feel, Shin Dong.
I'm too tired,
and I don't think I can follow.
[Yellow Team's Jong Kook and
Ryu Dam win!]
- This game is fun!
- I know how you feel, Sang Myun.
Jong Kook...
I didn't know that you had a nice
little lady on your team.
[A nice little lady?]
[A lone mother taking a rest
on top of the snowy hill...]
Where are all your kids?
Mother... did you come to ride the sleigh
all by yourself?
I see that it's a couple vacation.
Look... they're a couple!
[Is this the father?]
Honey!
Why don't we bow down to them?
Aren't you the couple that went off
to the jungle a while back?
That's so funny.
Mom!
We're all done!
The show is already over!
Fighting!
[Second round of finals]
[Yellow Team- Juvie and Ha Ha vs.
Blue Team- Suk Jin and Kwang Soo.]
I don't think Sang Myun is just going to
sit by if the other team wins right now.
- Yellow Team, fighting!
- Fighting, Blue Team! Let's go to the finals!
Finals! Finals!
You have to cheer on Kwang Soo to lose.
You have to want Kwang Soo to lose!
How can you grab me like that?
I'm a celebrity!
He's not very good at joking around.
- Yellow Team, fighting!
- Yellow team!
Yellow team!
Blue Team! Blue Team!
Blue Team! Here they go.
[Start]
[Is this game going to be another
overwhelming one?]
No!
[Oh no... the tube sleigh is heading down
the slope all by itself...]
[My tube... stop right there!]
[Juvie throwing his whole body into it?]
[That was a 100 point worthy body gag.]
There! Over there!
[Rudolph Ro-Ro on top of the slope
all by himself.]
You have to take me!
I'm not on it!
[Mismatched partners.]
Suk Jin!
I'm not on it!
You have to redo it.
[This is not acceptable-
Must head back up the slope.]
You have to leave the stocking down here.
Hurry up and get back up there.
Will they be able to get back up there?
- Kwang Soo...
- It's sliding back down.
[Oh.... no...]
[Tube going on numerous sleigh rides
all by itself.]
[In the meantime, the Yellow Team
is ready to slide their way down the hill.]
Kwang Soo!
[Blocking their path with their bodies?]
[Fails]
[Easy Brothers' finally gets on their way.]
Careful! Be careful.
[Always heading down towards
the same direction...]
Put it on... put it on.
Here, put the other one on.
[No way he'd leave them alone...]
[Predicting total chaos to ensue
with Kwang Soo's interference.]
Let go. Let go!
[This guy, who will stoop to any lows...]
Pass it back to me.
I don't know whose feet are whose!
Whose foot is this?
[In a contorted martial arts position.]
My foot is this one!
That's not my foot!
Are you just giving up like that?
[Will the Yellow Team win?]
[Juvie has both stockings on his feet!]
[Heading towards the flag!]
[The flag not getting pulled out easily.]
[Giraffe using that time to
steal a stocking.]
[Trips him over.]
[Still unsure of what's going on.]
[If I can't steal the stockings...]
[Huh? Where are they headed?]
[Running barefoot through the
snowy meadow...]
[Juvie and the Giraffe continuing
with their runaround.]
[Shocking spin they're taking
barefoot in the snow.]
[Juvie going along on the run without
even knowing the reason behind it...]
Suk Jin! Hurry up and
steal the stockings!
Hurry up and take it from him!
My feet are freezing!
[Ro-Ro running to Juvie's side after having
held onto the stockings all this time.]
[Big-nosed Brother helping to get
the stockings on Juvie's feet.]
[What everyone wants is not the victory,
but for the game to end quickly.]
[Yellow Team wins!]
So cold... so cold.
I don't think I can do this anymore.
[No longer allowed to frolic
through the snow anymore...]
Yellow Team wins!
[Yellow Team wins the
Santa and the Rudolph game!]
Yellow Team takes the win
for our first game today.
[Yellow Team to take the win.]
[Four snowballs given out to
the Yellow Team for winning the game.]
[Blue Team gets two snowballs
for coming in at second place.]
[Red Team gets zero snowballs
for coming in at last place.]
[Second mission location-
A swimming pool in the snowy lodge.]
Hot... this feels hot.
The water is mine.
[Sang Myun feeling confident
over water?]
I can swim like a fish.
Jong Kook...
did you bring your mother here?
[Kkuk here on a vacation with
his mother?]
This mission takes place in the pool,
and it's called 'Christmas in the summer'.
- They're so clever with their ideas...
- That's a good name they came up with.
That has a bit of romanticism to it.
If you look behind you,
you'll see a balance beam in the pool.
I bet we have to get up on that thing.
All four members of the team
will have to get up on the beam.
So when I call out the numbers,
number one will have to move number four spot.
And number two will have to move
down to that person's spot.
- We have to move our spots?
- You have to change your spots in this game.
The allotted time you will have...
is one minute.
It's hard enough to do that
while just standing here.
How are we supposed to get past him?
- Why don't you try moving over here?
- It's not going to work because of this!
What are you saying is wrong with it?
Why don't you try, Ji Hyo?
[Just like this...]
But I... normally can't even walk
straight on regular streets.
So how am I supposed to walk on
such a narrow thing like that?
We'll start with the Yellow Team
since they won the previous game.
[Yellow Team to start off the game
from having won the first game.]
The water is nice and warm!
[Hyung Don in the water...]
As I've mentioned to you before,
you've only got one minute.
Are you all ready?
We're going to start right away.
That's really tight.
It's tight just from even looking at it.
[Looking especially cramped for these two.]
Do you think you can even climb up here?
I don't think they can climb up there.
[Belly getting in the way...]
What are you doing right now?
If you keep that up,
Jong Kook is going to scold you.
There may be chieftains in the jungle,
but on Running Man, we have Jong Kook!
Use your knees!
Use your knees to climb up here!
[Unbelievable...]
Stop frowning so much, Jong Kook.
[Struggling to just even get up
on the beam.]
- This isn't working!
- We're going to win this game.
Use your knees to get up here!
[Several times getting only his belly
up on the beam already.]
That's right... your leg.
Pull up your leg now.
[Time's up.]
- Is it over?
- We haven't even gotten started!
[Fails without even having all
the team members up on the beam.]
He's like the sea lion.
[I want to sit upon a rock
and just rest...]
Dam... what happened?
No way... that's not possible.
[Blue Team's turn at the challenge.]
It's not easy!
[Big-nosed Brother not being able
to get his body to cooperate.]
[Sang Myun, first to make a move...]
[Throwing him off?]
That felt too weird!
[Everyone ultimately falls
into the water.]
How can you just throw me into the
water like that because it felt weird?
[Making another attempt.]
Hold on...
everyone, just hold on to me.
You need to hold on to me too.
[Why is everyone getting angry?]
[Finally passes by one person.]
This isn't too hard.
[Sang Myun and Big-nosed Brother
making a move simultaneously.]
That really does feel weird.
[Just how will Shin Dong...]
[Unable to work around the bulk...]
[Fail]
This isn't going to work...
Oh my stomach...
[Hurting the stomach of the bystanders
from making them laugh so hard.]
How much time do we have to
get this done?
[We told you that you only had
a minute just a little while ago...]
[Everyone getting together
to start practicing.]
[Red Team feeling disappointed
from their disinterest.]
[Aqua ballet dancing team..]
This team is pretty slim.
[Feeling too reassured because
of their slimness.]
[Slim Team? Moving at a fast speed.]
[Easily passing by skinny Ji Hyo.]
[Oh? Passes by Hyung Don too?]
[Gary starting to make his move
right away!]
[A strange atmosphere?]
Are you two dating?
I want to go through that again!
Hurry up!
[A hot embrace.]
[Red Team's chance at a win in danger!]
Okay, got it. Got it.
Okay, Ji Hyo!
[Slim Ji Hyo passes through them
quickly with ease.]
[And lastly, it's Hyung Don's turn.]
- I don't think I can make it...
- You can do it!
Get yourself together!
Hurry!
[Time's up]
[Slim Team almost made it to victory...]
[Yellow Team's plan is to get
Dam up on the beam first?]
Are you all ready?
There's no way they can get it
done with Dam.
He's going to fall, he's going to fall!
[Succeeds in getting Dam up
on the beam as planned.]
[Got everyone up on the
balance beam.]
Get down... lower yourself, Dam.
Lower yourself to pass.
[Halfway to victory as long as
they can get Dam to pass through.]
[And today's main event!]
[Ryu Dam and Juvie Train are
about to pass one another!]
Quickly! Do it quickly!
[Total chaos ensues.]
[- Hold your breath.
-You too.]
[Are these two dancing the waltz?]
[Convulsing with laughter.]
[Ryu Dam and Juvie having become
one belly to belly.]
[Ultimately falling into the water together.]
[Causing a small wave pool by
falling into the water.]
[Like a piece of seaweed
floating in the water.]
Now that I've gotten to know Juvie a bit,
I realized that he's guilty of a crime.
[My crime is always having a full belly...]
Juvie is cracking me up!
- It's G-Dragon!
- He looks likes G-Dragon!
G-Dragon!
[I'm Juvie-Dragon.]
Dam and Juvie together is hilarious!
[The birth of a new comedic duo!
Ryu Dam and Juvie Train.]
I should've gained some more weight
before I came on the show.
You really are very slim these days.
[If you think you can catch up to me,
give it a try.]
[Blue Team's turn.]
[Blue Team showing off some
new moves.]
[Shin Dong's strong skills.
Lifting them up and moving them aside!]
That's your biggest hurdle!
You move him, then we can win this.
[Going back to his original stance.]
[Shin Dong now has to move Sang Myun.]
[Succeeds in moving the large boulder!]
[Blue Team in good spirits.]
[20 seconds left on the clock!]
[Will the Blue Team be able to feel
the joy of winning?]
[Second person,
Kwang Soo also passes through!]
[No way...]
[If only Big-nosed Brother
can pass through...]
[Huh? There's no room for him to go to?]
[Spot on comedic move.]
[Why do these things always
happen to this guy...]
[Sorry.]
This is why I do variety shows!
[This is the reason why the nation's MC,
Jae Suk can't quit doing variety shows!]
- This is what variety show is all about!
- This is what it's all about!
- That was exciting!
That was sweet!
That was just delightful!
[Easy Brothers' piling on
the laughter for Christmas.]
Should I go first?
[Red Team follows up with their turn.]
I don't think I can do it.
- Get yourself together!
- You can do it!
There's no place for me to set
my foot down!
- Right here!
- Where am I supposed to step?
- Hurry up!
- Get yourself together!
[When they're already running
low on time...]
[Giving it another try after
checking for some room.]
Hurry! Get yourself together!
Get yourself together!
[Scaredy cat Hyung Don finally succeeds
in passing over one person.]
Hurry! Hurry!
[Easily passing by slim Ji Hyo once again.]
[Will this succeed this time around?]
[Monday couple also getting plunged
into the water amicably.]
Why did you guys fall in the
water on purpose?
Dam and Ju are next!
Dam and Ju!
[Dam and Ju duo that bring laughter
just from the thought of them alone.]
[What kind of laughter
will they give us this time?]
[Yellow Team's turn.]
[Dam now easily getting up on the beam.]
Hurry up!
It's the criminal! It's the criminal!
[Ryu Dam is making his move!]
Dam and Ju are back together again!
[Dam and Ju back to facing one another
on top of the balance beam.]
Dam-Ju! Dam-Ju!
[Dam and Ju's fan club shouting out
together in a unified voice.]
Suck in your stomach!
- No, they can't make a move.
- They both have to move together.
Suck in your stomach a little!
Both of you, suck in your stomach!
Why don't you try moving
your foot over?
[Huh? Taking the pose of a cobra?]
[Kerplunk]
[Dam and Juvie duo giving free
wave service to the bystanders.]
Mom! Mom...
[I have no way around it, my son.]
[Blue Team's turn once again.]
[What does the Blue Team's Brain,
Shin Dong have up in his sleeve this time?]
It's a new method again.
[Plan is to climb over
the person sitting down.]
[Even though it looks a bit funny,
already succeeded in passing two people.]
[Now if only Sang Myun can
pass through...]
[Blue Team's bad luck,
Sang Myun and Shin Dong.]
[Climbing back up to give it another go!]
[What is that?]
[Sang Myun getting crushed
under Shin Dong.]
[Those two bad luck charms
barely get passed!]
Hurry... we don't have time.
[Everyone falls into the water
no thanks to Sang Myun's move.]
This isn't going to work either.
[I feel like death...]
[Next up is the slim Red Team
who's favored for the win!]
They have the best advantage.
[We're going to win it this time.]
[Red Team definitely starts off
faster than any other team!]
[Jae Suk passes by
two people in the blink of an eye!]
[This isn't going to work.]
[Passing Hyung Don
through the front this time.]
What are you doing?
Are you posing for a picture?
[A sexy couple pose for the picture.]
[Second one making the move, Gary.]
[Safely bypasses Hyung Don.]
[Slim Ji Hyo bypasses
three people in one move!]
[And now, the final obstacle for the win-
Hyung Don's turn.]
[Barely passes by Gary.]
[Now if only Ji Hyo and Hyung Don can
switch their spots, they win!]
[Will the Red Team be able to win?]
[Mission complete!
Just what time did they make it under?]
58 seconds!
[Red Team succeeds!]
Give us our balls! Give us our balls!
Since you came in first place,
you get four snowballs.
[Red Team wins four snowballs
for coming in at first place!]
[Moving on to the next location
of the race.]
A restaurant?
[This fancy restaurant
is their third location?]
I guess they are going to
feed us after all.
Hey, do you think this mission is one
where we have to eat a lot of food?
- Even just the thought of it makes me happy.
- Then we'd definitely take first place.
- We're not much worse than the other teams.
- I don't think so either.
[A lively Christmas atmosphere
on the inside.]
[But what are these numbers on the chairs?]
Pull out one of the spoons in front
of you and show it to the camera.
One of these?
- Number three.
- Go take seat number three.
[Gary's seat for having pulled number three.]
- Just show it to the camera.
- You're supposed to do it like this.
This mission... a is Christmas feast.
[The third mission- Christmas feast.]
- Do you all know the game, '31'?
- Yes!
- Yes.
- So you do know the game?
[The thirty first person to get caught loses.]
[Rule: First, choose the dish
that you'd like to eat.]
[Eat as many bites as you'd like,
then pass it to the person next to you.]
[The person to eat
the thirty first dish is disqualified.]
And those disqualified can leave their
seats and sit over here on the sidelines.
This one sounds like fun.
For some reason today,
I can't understand a thing that's being said.
All you have to do is just
eat the food.
I can give up to five dishes per person.
And the person who can last to the end
until the last dish is the winner.
Okay, Shin Dong...
which one are you going to choose?
[The first dish is... steak.]
[Starting the first round with
such a delicious dish as this one?]
- Steak? How do you eat that? Cut it?
- That looks delicious!
- You can just be seated.
- That one should be mine!
You really know how to pick it!
- Hello.
- You are so beautiful!
- Thank you.
[Bite sized dishes. Enough for 31 bites.]
[Number one seat's Shin Dong
to start the eating.]
- Wait, don't just eat, but think about it.
- You have to calculate as you eat.
We're on the same team.
[Have to think carefully about how many
bites to eat before he starts eating...]
- One or two doesn't really matter...
- You can have up to five bites each.
- Three!
- I think this dish may end right around me.
- I think it's going to be one of us.
- They're all going to eat five bites.
Four bites. All done.
- Only four?
- Have another bite.
Hey, why are you eating like
a vegetarian?
[Now only 27 bites left of the steak!]
- That looks really good.
- I don't care if I lose, let me just try it.
[Next one up is Sang Myun]
I think I know who's going to get caught.
Think a little before you eat.
I'm thinking about it while I eat.
I'm not that stupid.
But you keep eating without thinking.
Shin Dong is doing the thinking for me.
- Two.
- You're done at two?
No, I'm saying I finished my second one.
[I'm not done yet...]
Why are you getting mad? Go ahead, eat more!
- He really scared me just now.
- You think that's going to be enough?
[Section in danger of being eliminated.]
We're in danger, aren't we?
Sang Myun just ate four.
- Okay, four bites.
- Four.
- Are you counting in your head?
- I'm not done. I'm going to eat one more.
Normally, I...
- I don't normally eat very much.
- Breathe a little while you eat.
[What are you saying?
That's already your fifth plate...]
[Carnivore Sang Myun finishes off
his fifth plate!]
[Now 22 dishes of the steak left!]
If I could, I'd have all five bites
since I'm so hungry...
Wait... if Gary does what he says,
then that will be 10 dishes.
[At that rate,
Jae Suk is in extreme danger!]
Then that puts me in danger...
I'm in danger.
- No...
- No, you don't think so?
- I'm going to eat all five.
- You can't eat a lot.
- It's okay, Gary... eat all five.
- Gary, eat just one.
I really want to eat one more.
Gary, you can only eat one.
Survival is more important right now.
- Just go ahead and eat!
- Gary, just eat one.
Okay, I'll just eat one. All done.
[Now 21 pieces left.
Hyung Don's turn next.]
- Hyung Don, you should only eat one too.
- What did you say?
[Hyung Don has to eat as little as possible
for Jae Suk to remain alive.]
Stop!
- Hyung Don, stop eating.
- Hyung Don, eat all five bites.
No, you can't.
Then I'm going to be ousted!
- Then I'm going to be ousted!
- He won't be ousted.
Stop it! Stop eating!
[Drunk on the taste and
beyond reason.]
If you keep eating like that,
I'm going to get ousted!
- No, you're not!
- I'm going to get ousted!
You think he'll eat four or five?
Eat if you want. There
will still be three survivors left.
Stop, stop, stop.
- Hyung Don, stop eating.
- Just eat one more.
We're still going to get more food.
So stop eating for now.
[Too alluring of a taste to stop eating...]
- Isn't it good? Eat one more. One more.
- Stop. Stop eating.
You have to stop eating right now.
[Just one more?]
That's enough. Say you're done!
How could you have come up with
such an evil game as this?
This is an evil game to these guys!
[An evil battle between reason
and desire.]
- Stop eating.
- I know you like meat. Eat one more!
I'm about to go crazy!
- Done. I'm done.
- You're done?
[Strong regrets even after
shouting out that he's done.]
Okay, it's my turn.
[Next up is Jong Kook.
Four plates down within moments.]
- How does he chew so fast?
- He does everything well.
- That's amazing.
- He's not human.
[Jong Kook finishes his five plates.
Now only 13 plates left!]
Fighting!
If I eat five here... and five for him...
[Red Team's Jae Suk in extreme danger
of being eliminated.]
- I need a bite of that too...
- There's not going to be any left.
You can't just think about
eating right now.
- Is it good?
- It's unbelievable. Just unbelievable.
I was hungry too.
Three.
Don't fill up just yet.
There's still a lot of food left.
Four. All done.
- Suk Jin, you should have one more.
- All I needed was four bites.
[Passing the baton off to Kwang Soo
with four plates left.]
Kwang Soo, just eat one.
Kwang Soo, when do you ever listen
to what other people say?
Kwang Soo, you should just stop there.
[Almost a guarantee that Jae Suk is the
one eliminated if Kwang Soo eats five bites.]
If there's one thing I can say,
you really... have gotten really cool.
[Do you take me for a fool?]
That's the biggest lie!
I have a young friend... and she
wants me to introduce her to you.
Hey, I saw her.
She looks like Jae Suk.
[A blind date?]
I'll introduce you to her.
- Don't stop there.
- Everyone just be quiet!
Can't I just do what I want
with the food that's in front of me?
You should eat... let the boy eat.
[Is it Jae Suk's blind date proposal, or...
the delicious steak in front of him?]
Make up your mind!
- Done!
- That's right!
[Kwang Soo announces that he's done
after just one bite.]
[Eight bites of steak left.
Battle of the minds starts again.]
Juvie, you can only eat one bite.
You can only eat one bite.
It's for our team.
[If Juvie eats only one, that
put Red Team's Ji Hyo in danger!]
- Hey, you have to eat just one.
- Aren't you hungry?
- You have to think about this!
- Juvie.. Juvie!
Even if Jae Suk eats five...
And if Dam only eats one...
[Red Team's Ji Hyo in danger!]
Juvie, stop eating.
Stop eating and hand it off to Dam.
Come on!
You have to think about this.
[What will Yellow Team's Juvie decide?]
- Done!
- That's right!
[Teamwork.
Juvie Train stops after one bite!]
[Whether Jae Suk eats one or five,
his teammate Ji Hyo is in danger...]
- If I eat just one...
- You should eat just one.
Then Dam would eat five.
[The outcome is pretty much decided,
so let's just get to the eating part.]
- Ji Hyo... it's going to be her.
- The end is pretty much written in stone.
If Ji Hyo is going to be eliminated anyways,
don't allow Dam to eat all the meat at least.
I'm going to make you go hungry!
[My meat...]
- No! Our Dam worked really hard!
- Jae Suk, eat it all!
[Jae Suk scarfing the food
down as he stated.]
[Finishing off three plates
in the blink of an eye.]
- No, that's Dam's steak.
- Jae Suk, you're a really good eater.
Dam! Just eat two plates and
oust yourself.
- Done!
- I know you're hungry. Eat both.
[If Dam only eats one,
then Ji Hyo will be ousted.]
Dam, just finish it off.
[But... the last
remaining bite of the steak...]
[Should I just eat it?]
Snap out of it, you dummy!
Look at all the food over there!
- Hey!
- Isn't it good? It's really delicious.
[If he eats it, he ousts himself.
If he endures, then Ji Hyo gets ousted.]
[So hungry...]
[I feel you.]
Is this something you even
have to think about, you dummy?
- Hey! Stupid!
- Dam, that steak is just too delicious.
- Eat it, eat it...
- Get yourself together!
- Smell it. Smell it.
- No!
[Beyond reasoning.]
You've worked too hard in the jungle.
Just go on and eat it.
[Will be he able to shout out
that he's done?]
Done!
- Done!
- Yeah!
[Red Team's Ji Hyo is eliminated.]
- Can I eat it since we're done?
- No, you can't!
[It's mine!]
I thought that you were
going to eat it.
- There was so much shouting!
- Our team has to stick it out!
- Our team has to win this game.
- That wasn't easy.
- I'm not eating it... not eating it!
- Here... eat it.
[Even though it's too bad,
Red Team loses one of their members.]
Kwang Soo, I really do appreciate it.
I'll introduce you to that friend I mentioned.
- Thank you, Jae Suk.
- She has a very pretty face.
- Then what's the problem?
- She's 39 years old.
[11 years his senior...]
[He tricked me again...]
- Please make your selection.
- Number one!
[Round two's selection is...]
I bet it's something good!
- It looks delicious.
- What is it?
- Tofu wrapped rice!
- Wow!
[Second round selection is
tofu wrapped rice.]
Okay, let's pass out 31 plates
of the tofu wrapped rice first.
[Serving up 31 plates of tofu wrapped rice.]
[Yellow Team's Ha Ha to start
eating this round.]
I'm really impressed with
all this food!
- Three!
- Think before you eat! Don't eat so much!
- Four!
- Hey!
[I want one too...]
Let's end this, Hyung Don.
[Game or not,
beyond reasoning once again.]
Ryu Dam stole a piece!
Five! Done!
- Ji Hyo, the other way.
- Here. Ryu Dam...
- No, you have to go the other way.
- No, I guess it's not you.
Why? Why?
[Next turn goes back to
seat number one, Shin Dong.]
- Why are we going this way?
- Hey, think about it before you eat.
[Battle of the words heating up again.]
- Just eat one each.
- No, we can all eat five.
Hey! You can only eat one!
- Whatever, one!
- Hey! You can only eat one!
Hey! Think about it before you
start eating!
- Shin Dong is a pig!
- You're going to turn into a pig!
[Shin Dong finishes his five already!]
[At this rate, either Suk Jin or
Kwang Soo will be in danger!]
- What are they doing?
- We're going to be ousted!
[I'm just hungry.]
They're crazy!
[Sang Myun also finishes his five
in the blink of an eye!]
They really are pigs.
[Not a care about the fate about
their own teammates!]
Very cool... Sang Myun
and Shin Dong are very cool.
They really are very cool.
- How did you stuff all that in your mouth?
- Drink some water with it.
[His know-how of eating fast.]
Why don't you try calculating it,
Sang Myun, you fool.
Five, five, then...
Hey... we didn't eat that right.
Five. All done.
[Gary also finishes eating five.
Next up is Hyung Don!]
- Here.
- Let us eat some too.
[Wow! Two pieces at once!]
[Somehow finishes five already.]
This really is such a suitable
game for them.
Yes, it suits them perfectly.
I realize that if I don't eat all five,
that would leave my team in danger.
Let's just eat one.
Let's just eat one a piece.
[Fate of it all rests on Jong Kook's fork.]
- Jong Kook... why don't we just eat one?
- Yeah, let's just eat one each.
- Why don't you just eat these?
- Jong Kook...
- Why don't you eat as much as you want?
- Just eat to your content.
Hey, do you see how you separated these?
Then only you'll survive.
- You're trying to kill me?
- No! That was a mistake.
I miscalculated. Here, just eat two.
- Two.
- Okay, let's just finish at two.
- And also...
- Three!
Just eat all five.
I'm sure you must be hungry.
- Just eat all five!
- Why don't you stop at four?
- Four...
- Stop there.
Whether it's Kwang Soo or Suk Jin,
it's one of our team members that dies.
- It's because of you!
- It's your fault!
[This all happened because of
Shin Dong and Sang Myun.]
- Really?
- You still don't know this is because of you?
[If he eats it, Suk Jin is out.
If he doesn't eat, then Kwang Soo is out!]
Done!
[Suk Jin's happy as a clam
to be left alive.]
- I'll be really good to you.
- Suk Jin could eat two since he's hungry.
What an absurd thing to say.
Suk Jin...
[What is it that Kwang Soo would
like to say?]
What is it that you want from me?
You're telling me to eat two?
[Telling his older brother to eat both
and back out of the game?]
Why are you calling me your brother?
You and I ended five minutes ago.
- Why don't you eat one first?
- Okay, we can talk after I eat one.
Kwang Soo... done.
[Blue Team's Kwang Soo is eliminated!]
[Easy Brothers, my butt...]
It's because of you two.
We told you to stop eating.
Couldn't you calculate that in your head?
[We were just hungry...]
- Number ten.
- Ten.
[The third round food is...
[Fish cake skewers!]
I can eat a hundred of those!
- A hundred?
- Yeah, I can eat a hundred.
- That's my favorite.
- Just eat one.
[31 skewers of fish cakes!]
[Yellow Team's Juvie starts.]
Why don't we keep it fun and
just eat one each?
- This tastes unbelievable.
- Two.
- Nice.
- He's a good eater.
Can't you give us some soy sauce?
- That'll make you fat.
- This is already seasoned.
[He's already...]
- I'm already fat, didn't you know?
- They're really sharp witted aren't they?
Three.
If you add a little milk to the fish cakes,
they won't make your face swell up.
[Sang Myun concerned about
the size of his face.]
It's better for the face to appear
smaller on screen.
[Yellow Team's Juvie
finishes eating all five.]
- Five.
- I really love this stuff.
[If Jae Suk eats too many, it put his own
team members, Gary and Hyung Don in danger!]
Jae Suk, I'll take care of it!
Just eat one!
Once you start eating though,
you can't stop just at one.
[Starting off by eating one first.]
- One more. Eat one more.
- What looks really delicious.
Jae Suk! Stop!
- Just let him eat all five.
- This is just so good.
- Just go on and eat one more.
- Jae Suk, you can't!
- You can't eat anymore!
- I just saw the face of an angel.
I looked over this way and,
'Just go on and eat one more'.
Just eat one more.
You know how angel's voice sounds
in movies? 'Just eat one more'.
- You really have to think, Jae Suk.
- Done!
[Jae Suk is finished after eating
one piece of the fish cake skewer.]
[At last, Ryu Dam is up next.]
Just eat one each. One each.
[Can't hear you.]
He didn't really get to eat the steak, and
he didn't get the tofu wrapped rice either.
[Already scarfing down two.]
Dam! Dam, stop eating!
Dam, stop! Stop eating!
[Whether he can hear or not...
He finishes his third one.]
Two more. Eat two more.
Dam, you have to stop eating!
You're putting us in danger.
[Beyond reason at his state.
Finishes his fourth piece.]
You're so cute when you eat.
You seriously look adorable.
Dam, you can't be doing that.
Dam, listen to me.
He's not done.
Dam, stop eating. You don't
even have any room to fit that in.
[No matter what other say,
he ultimately ends up eating all five.]
- He can't hear a word you're saying.
- Dong Hoon, just eat one.
Give me some water.
- It's really delicious.
- He can eat one more, couldn't he?
[The taste which makes it impossible
to stop after just one bite.]
[Finishing off his second.]
I want you to stop eating.
[Can't hear you.]
Is it all over for them?
[Fourth one!]
Nice! Eat one more. Get one more.
- One last one.
- Eat one more.
[Ultimately eats all five.]
[If the other team members eat a lot
of the skewers, then Jong Kook is ousted.]
Eat five. Eat all five.
- You look like you're really deep in thought.
- Three.
[Fish cake deep in thought.]
You have to eat all five, okay?
[Jong Kook is most likely to get ousted.]
This is going to leave me in
a tough spot.
Look at him drinking up
the broth first.
It's too salty.
[Making the dish bland since he
doesn't like his face bloated.]
[Self proclaimed fish cake mania.]
- One.
- What a good eater.
[Swallows after
chewing it up only three times?]
Chew at least four times
before you swallow it.
He really is like a pig!
[Finishing off four pieces of
the fish cake in a flash.]
You have to keep me around to
make sure the show stays funny.
[In the meantime, Gary
already finishes off his third one.]
- Done.
- Why don't you eat one more?
I will pass this off to Hyung Don
and let it rest in his hands.
[Passes it off to Hyung Don
with three left on the plate.]
[Depending on Hyung Don's decision,
either Jong Kook or Suk Jin will be ousted.]
- It's really delicious.
- Let me at least try it first.
You and I could do
the game together for a while.
[Trying to convince him.]
- You didn't see that? He did it.
- I didn't do anything.
[If Hyung Don eats that,
then Jong Kook is ousted!]
- How can you allow him to live instead?
- So this is the ultimate fish cake?
[The ultimate fish cake.]
[If he eats it, Jong Kook is out!
If he doesn't, then Suk Jin is out!]
Are you allowed to use
your strength like that?
My will when it comes to food is
stronger than most other people.
[I'm going to eat it!]
[The two willful people's fight!]
- Give me my fish cake!
- Hyung Don..
Jong Kook's strength
isn't what you're used to.
Hyung Don... think about it. Think.
- Hyung Don...
- This is like back in the day.
Hyung Don... Hyung Don.
[There's one more...]
Great job, Hyung Don!
- Great job, Hyung Don!
- Just stop now!
How about I just eat both
and oust myself then?
[Huh? He's going to self-terminate?]
- I'll be considerate of your team next time.
- I'll just eat both and kill myself.
This is seriously delicious.
I'll eat both and kill myself.
[The fish cakes are delicious enough
to kill himself over?]
No, I really will just kill myself.
- With the steak earlier...
- He's been full all morning.
[Eating one for now... done.]
Done!
Great job!
[Yellow Team's Jong Kook is
ultimately eliminated.]
[Eliminated players starting to
pile up one by one from the game.]
[Food for this round is... huh?]
One came alone.
Two came together?
[This time, it's not food,
but a mini game.]
[Giraffe Kwang Soo transformed
into an Assistant.]
We will now start the game,
One came alone. Two came together.
The game is very simple.
He really is so ugly.
If I shout out, one person came alone,
then only one person will stand up.
And when I shout out, two came together,
then two people can stand up.
We will now start the game,
One came alone. Two came together.
- Okay.
- Starting with Jae Suk. One!
- One came alone!
- One.
One came alone.
- One!
- One came alone.
- One.
You only keep saying one!
I guess I'm going to have to
teach you a lesson.
This is Running Man!
- Remember that you're on Running Man!
- He's not an easy opponent.
- We will start with Jae Suk.
- We understand.
- One.
- One came alone.
- Two.
- Two came together.
- Three!
- Three came together!
- Two!
- Two came together!
- One.
- One came alone.
- Three!
- Three came together!
- Four!
- Four came together!
- Three!
- Three came together!
- Two.
- Two came together!
- Five!
- Five came together!
[Since 'Five' was shouted out,
Hyung Don should be getting up too...]
[Red Team's Hyung Don is out!]
Running Man really is hard.
[Now four survivors in the eighth round.]
[The food in this round is...
orange juice!]
- I can't drink juice.
- Why not?
It's because I don't really like juice.
Ah, because he doesn't like it?
- But you can drink it though?
- Of course, I can drink it.
- You like carbonated drinks, don't you?
- Yes, I do.
I don't like fruit.
[Who will be the one left with the last
glass of orange juice out of 31?]
Look at them eating all day.
- Done.
- He really must not like it.
[Drinking as much as they want
in the beginning.]
This is really good.
- I just had two.
- He can't stop right now.
Okay.
[Quickly disappearing juice glasses.
- Look at him thinking so hard.
- Done.
They should just drink one each
to see how they're going to end up.
[Staying cautious without drinking
too much.]
Done.
[13 glasses left at the moment.]
- I think I'm getting the picture.
- Okay, let's start the countdown.
Five, four, three, two...
[Since he has to have a drink,
he drinks one for now...]
[Ha Ha also cautiously drinks one.]
- He hates this stuff.
- You drank one?
- I know he doesn't like that stuff.
- Shin Dong, you hate this stuff.
- He doesn't like juice!
- I know you don't like this.
- Three!
- It's actually tasting pretty good now.
[In that case...]
- I'll leave it up to Suk Jin.
- Five!
[After drinking all five,
passes the baton off to Suk Jin.]
[Depending on how many he drinks,
it'll determine who will be eliminated.]
[If he leaves only one,
then Jae Suk will be eliminated!]
[But if he leaves two,
then Ha Ha gets eliminated!]
You should really stop drinking.
[Drinking without any hesitation.]
Suk Jin, you can't be doing this.
Come on, you know better!
- Suk Jin... think about it carefully.
- Give me a break, Suk Jin.
[Now... there are only two glasses left.]
[If he ends it here, Ha Ha is ousted.
If he drinks one more, Jae Suk is ousted!]
I wish that Suk Jin would get honest
about this game right now.
What?
Which one of the two are you
going to kill?
You have to think about
the next game.
- You have to think about the next game.
- Which one are you going to choose?
[Final mission is the snowball fight...
In that case!]
You have to be careful.
[If he drinks it, Jae Suk is out!
If he doesn't, then Ha Ha is out!]
- Done!
[Yellow Team confirmed
as the last place holder.]
Okay! We did it!
Okay then. We know who
the death note will go to now.
- We got it now.
- Am I included in that death note?
[In the order that they placed,
each team is given their share of snowballs.]
Thank you!
It feels really good to be in first place.
- There's something up there.
- Something's already been prepared for us?
There's something up there.
Is that something for us to wear?
They're vests.
Why do we have to wear these now?
[Oust other members by throwing your
snowballs. Last one left alive is the winner.]
You remember that the team that
comes in last gets punished, right?
- We just have to make sure not to lose.
- Just make sure we don't come in last.
- Jong Kook isn't very good at throwing.
- It's not about strength but aiming right.
That's right...
remember the baseball game?
Kim Jong Kook isn't good at baseball.
- I'm sure they're going to aim for us first.
- We don't know that.
[Yellow Team in most danger
with only four.]
[Snowball fight - Start!]
Let's go! Let's say fighting.
[Gathering around for a shout out.]
One, two, three, fighting!
It feels like we're going off to battle.
Why is the Yellow Team standing over there?
- Red Team!
- What?
[Yellow Team with the least amount
of balls proposes a coalition.]
Shall we work together?
Since this isn't about ripping off name tags,
we're not afraid of Jong Kook.
Come on!
[Yellow Team staying cautious from
having only four balls in their possession.]
Yellow Team only has four balls.
That's right, they only have four.
And the Red Team has six.
We have to keep our eye on the Yellow Team.
You know what Yellow Team is waiting for?
They're waiting for our teams to fight
since they only have a few balls.
[They're close... now's the chance!]
If you're going to it so weak like this,
why even bother throwing it?
[Blue Team gains one more from
Juvie's weak throw.]
[Crap...]
[Yellow Team now down to only three balls.]
I felt good about it...
I didn't count on the wind.
[They were already at a disadvantage,
and now they're even more so...]
- We're seriously...
- Why did he throw it?
[Giving up on attacking,
and now just trying to survive...]
[Red Team's Jae Suk on the attack!]
[Red Team vs. Blue Team first!]
[The imminent face-off!]
Sang Myun, corner them!
[Yellow Team watching the other
two teams battle it out first.]
We really don't have enough arsenal.
Over here!
Get Sang Myun!
[Misses his aim!]
[Red Team uses this moment to attack!]
[Gary's attack succeeds!]
[Jae Suk also succeeds from the back!]
[Within moments,
Sang Myun from the Blue Team is out!]
[The remaining Blue Team members
start their counterattack!]
[Heading towards Hyung Don!]
No! No!
[A stand-off.]
- We are...
- This is just making it easier for Jong Kook.
- Seriously...
- We have to think about this.
- Jae Suk!
- We just need to make sure we're not last.
Since they don't have many balls,
let's all oust them first.
- Okay.
- Let's work together first.
[Both teams agree on targeting
the Yellow Team first.]
We'll wait down there then.
The bottom line is for both our teams
to abstain from coming in last.
- Okay... then go on down.
- We'll see you later then.
[A coalition without any trust.]
- Should we forget about our trust?
- I've had a lot of experiences like this one.
I've been doing this stuff for
seven and a half years now.
Let's go.
Wow... here they come.
[Enemies starting to close in on them.]
[Yellow Team fleeing to
even higher ground.]
[The allies closing in on the Yellow Team!]
Here they come!
Dong Hoon is cornered.
[Ha Ha getting captured from
trying to defend his team on his own.]
You can only kill one of us, okay?
- I'm serious.
- We only came to get one of you.
[The wall of enemy line closing in.]
You can't keep climbing up forever.
[Climbing up into the mountain?]
- I'm going to throw this!
- Go ahead and throw it.
- I'm being serious!
- Go ahead!
Let's just have a snowball fight.
Why are you climbing up the mountain?
- How far are you going to go up?
- Don't come any closer.
How far are you going to go up?
[He really is climbing up the mountain.]
- You trying to disappear into the mountain?
- You don't need to put your life on the line!
[This is all for some laughter,
no need to endanger your life.]
[Finally finding even ground to
make his getaway.]
Just what is the punishment that awaits
us for him to do all that?
Do you really have to go that far?
[Rendezvous with the Yellow Team
from making it back to safety.]
We have to get up higher.
Let's ambush them.
Hurry! Run!
- Hurry!
- Come on! We have to catch them!
[The enemies start the chase!]
Run!
Come... come all the way up here!
Ha Ha, come here.
[Juvie Train in extreme danger!]
[Just then!]
[A direct hit at Jae Suk's vest!]
[Yellow Team's Ryu Dam, nice play!]
[Jae Suk - Out!]
[Gains the snowball that Jae Suk
threw at them!]
Nice! Nice!
[Ryu Dam coming through at
a critical moment!]
[Yellow Team still maintaining
their high ground.]
[A method of protecting their vests
from being hit.]
[Making it difficult for anyone
to attack one another.]
- There's Jong Kook...
- We're even numbered right now.
[Jong Kook succeeds in evading
the snowball!]
[Attempting to grab the thrown snowball
to use as their own weapon.]
- Let's all attack at the count of three.
- One, two, three!
[All movements ceased.]
- What do we do?
- Throw it, Ha Ha. It's okay.
[Gary blocks the ball Juvie
throws at him.]
[Stuck together?]
[Just then!]
[Gary hits Juvie directly on his vest!]
[Juvie Train - Out!]
[Gary ceases his movement and
targets Jong Kook! Bull's-eye!]
[Gary ultimately ousts the big fish!]
Who was it? Awesome!
[Kim Jong Kook - Out!]
[We're ruined...]
[No clue as to where the
battle now stands.]
We're the club of traitors, aren't we?
- He's really making me want to get him.
- We no longer have Jong Kook.
- It's pretty much over.
- Gary, watch out!
Watch out for what?
They're all just standing there.
Wow... that team is
really tightly banded together.
[The trick not working to his satisfaction.]
[I've been waiting for you.]
[Hyung Don eliminates Ha Ha
of the Yellow Team!]
[Ryu Dam's throw is a direct hit
on Hyung Don!]
[Getting too greedy after ousting Ha Ha...]
I've been crouched down here
for 30 minutes!
- What did you do that for?
- I just wanted to oust you!
[Starting the blame game on
one another!]
Why did you have to come and kill me?
Why did you come?
Today was my chance!
Let's just die together!
Dong Hoon, what do I do?
[What is the fate that awaits Ryu Dam
for being the sole survivor?]
[The enemies are already
starting to close in on him!]
[Target locked.]
[Nowhere to run to,
and hard to run in that body!]
Are you going to climb down?
[Heading toward Ace Ji Hyo?]
[Blocks... and blocks again!]
[Blocked them all?
This is Ace Ji Hyo's skills!]
[Ryu Dam now down to
zero snowballs!]
[Enemies start on their attack!]
[Shin Dong sticks a snowball
on Ryu Dam's back!]
[But just then!]
[Kwang Soo locks in on
Ace Ji Hyo as his target!]
[A direct hit!]
[As soon as Yellow Team is ousted,
the alliance is over!]
[Blue Team's Suk Jin, Kwang Soo,
Shin Dong vs. Red Team's Gary!]
- How may snowballs do you have?
- One.
[At times Mr. Capable, Gary attacks alone!]
[Gary eliminates Suk Jin of
the Blue Team!]
[Blue Team - two snowballs;
Red Team - three snowballs.]
[Gary never backs down at
times like these!]
This is a man's battle!
[Blue Team closing in on Gary
from both ends!]
[Gary fails at his attack!]
[Succeeds in deflecting
Kwang Soo's snowball!]
[Now... in this case!]
[Kwang Soo has no snowballs left.]
[And Shin Dong has one left!]
[Gary starts his chase!]
I don't have any balls!
[Shin Dong - Out!]
[Down to one last one!]
[With the final snowball...]
[Hits Kwang Soo on his vest!]
[Gary does it!]
[For two years in a row,
the man of Christmas is Gary!]
Gary Christmas!
[With Gary's skills,
the Red Team is the final victor!]
[Gary ousts six players on his own!]
- Christmas is my show!
- At the end of the year, you really...
[The man of the year!]
- Your prize is behind you.
- What are we getting?
Is someone going to jump
out of there?
Cookies? Here, you eat it.
Is it a trip or something?
[Delicious cookies filling up a large box!]
[Since Christmas is about feelings,
rather than gifts...]
[Then what is the final punishment?]
[Could it be... that?]
[Red long johns.]
[You can guess what it is, right?]
[Night skiing in red long johns!]
I'm going to tell my mom on you.
- Let's go!
- Merry Christmas!
[Long Johns ski, go!]
[Unbelievable speed thanks to
the added weight on the skis!]
[Is the new groom rushing to get home?]
[I have style.]
[The show and these skis...
they both scare me....]
Merry Christmas!
Let's go home!
Subtitles by DramaFever
Guest's mission.
One against seven?
Who is it?
[Last guest of 2012.]
[Hallyu star, Choi Ji Woo.]
This isn't going to work.
Come here, come here.
[The original Goddess showing
her surprising hidden skills.]
[Rogue Ji Woo... you're all dead!]
[One against seven.
Choi Ji Woo vs. Running Man.]
[A psychological game of betrayals
and deceit.]
[However... the truth
that they're not aware of yet!]
[Just what will result from this drama
that no one can believe?]
Who? Who's that?
[Choi Ji Woo vs. Running Man.
Truth and lies.]