Subtitles by DramaFever
[Nine Elite Secret Agents]
Since you're all gathered here now,
I will give you your secret mission.
[The command from headquarters]
[After you clear the mission,
gain your license to oust someone.]
[Just who will be the top secret agent?]
[007 Water Sniper]
[Seoul, Republic of Korea]
Why did you call me out so
early in the morning?
Is this for a mission?
I'm not going to be the spy...
I'm not doing it.
I'm not...
Why do you think you're the spy?
When you call us out on our own,
that's what it's usually for.
[Find all the members that are scattered
about and gather at headquarters.]
- Yoo Jae Suk...
- Yes?
That's your first mission.
[Have you forgotten? Yoo-ames Bond...]
What is this?
[Find your fellow Secret Agents
who are in hiding!]
[The moment you find them, place
an 'R' sticker on them to gain a point!]
- Do you see the mission on the card?
- Yes.
[All the other agents are currently
preparing for their own missions.]
- You are a secret agent...
- The day has finally arrived!
Complete your first mission...
Because you mentioned that your favorite
number out of seven is one
you're number one.
What the heck is this
first thing in the morning?
I'm on my way.
Then I wonder who number two is?
Okay, we're here.
[S- Group Headquarters,
Gangnam, Seoul]
We will give you three minutes
to complete it.
[Only three minutes given for the mission!]
[Starting the mission simultaneously with
an agent who's inside the building.]
[And the other secret agent who's already
gotten started on the same mission?]
Hello.
There's someone else in here
besides me, right?
There is, right?
[Who could it be?
Which agent has infiltrated this building?]
38 years...
My Father and my Grandfather were
both secret agents too.
[Ah... is that right?]
That is why I'm going to succeed
my mission today!
I will score two points!
[You're a secret agent!]
[Transport the secret 007 case
to the house phone.]
[Find the secret number there to unlock
the case and blow the whistle for two points!]
[Agent Giraffe in search of the phone
with the secret number hidden by it.]
I have to find them quickly.
Gwon Yeol...
You saw how Shin Soo did it, right?
Mr. Choo? That's how we need to do it.
We have to get it done quickly.
By any chance...
is that a house phone too?
- Is there an envelope?
- No, there isn't.
I haven't been noticed by anyone yet.
Have you...
Have you seen anyone else who's
here for the Running Man show?
[Giving him the answer with
their laughter...]
[The perfect disguise...]
[Agent Giraffe coming down to the
lobby in a very drastic fashion.]
[Where is he?]
Hello. By any chance,
is this a house phone?
[A scream?]
[He's downstairs...]
Is that a house phone?
It's not...
[Agent Jae Suk heading down
to the lobby.]
- Hello.
Excuse me.
By any chance, is there a house phone?
[Oh no! It's Jae Suk!]
[Could that be...]
Lee Kwang Soo!
[Escape!]
[If he puts the sticker on Agent Giraffe,
then his mission is a success!]
[Urgently fleeing to the emergency
stairway!]
[I've got you!]
[Jae Suk chasing him down
like a speeding bullet!]
- Kwang Soo...
- Jae Suk!
Jae Suk...
What are you doing?
Kwang Soo, listen to me.
- Kwang Soo...
- Don't come near me. What's that?
- Come here.
- No!
[The sticker is issued!]
No!
[Huh?]
[Giraffe attempting to destroy the
sticker that's been stuck on him.]
Lee Kwang Soo, you're eliminated!
[Agent Lee Kwang Soo-
Consumption complete]
Kwang Soo!
I now declare you my underling.
Jae Suk, aren't you going to give me
a jacket like yours?
What?
[The Giraffe is jealous of the look
that Jae Suk has going for himself.]
Jae Suk, you've gained one point.
If Lee Kwang Soo had succeeded,
he would've gained two points.
- Kwang Soo, that's not what's important.
- I almost completed my mission!
How is a point or two important
between us?
- Kwang Soo...
- I have zero points.
It's okay. How is that
different than any other time?
You've got seven minutes
to complete your mission.
[Which agent has infiltrated this place?]
[Could it be...]
[The female student who seems
to be in search of something...]
Hello.
[That's right, she is...]
[A woman we're all very familiar with...]
[Jae Suk and the Giraffe who have started
their mission at the same time as her...]
- Nothing, Jae Suk.
- Have you searched in there?
Jae Suk... this is my area.
Don't you trust me?
[Maybe I'm wrong?]
[Huh? Another secret agent?]
[Oh no! She saw Jong Kook?]
By any chance, have you seen...
[Misunderstanding Jong Kook to be there
also to capture her and making her escape!]
There's someone there.
[Running away as fast as she can
after sensing the danger.]
The woman that just passed by here
looked like someone very famous...
[Whew... I should be safe now, right?]
Song Ji Hyo!
[Seeing a suspicious woman...]
[And chasing after her
like a bolt of lightning!]
Run, Ji Hyo! Run!
Run!
I stuck it on her... I got her.
- I got her... wait, who is this?
- Hello.
What? You're not Song Ji Hyo!
[Wait... this is...]
[Special Female Agent, Park Shin Hye]
Jae Suk, why did you twist her
arm like that?
You're really making big mistakes
so early in the morning!
Wait... Park Shin Hye...
- Where did you stick it on?
- I stuck this one on her.
It must've fallen off.
- So you didn't get me?
- No, I stuck one on!
[Escaping right away?]
[Jae Suk gains another point!]
[While Special Agent Shin Hye's
being recruited, who's the next agent?]
[The secret agent in this location...]
[Coming down the stairs while hiding
his face with the newspaper...]
It's so great to see you!
It's been about six years since
I've seen you last?
[The Secret Agent here is none other than...
The Crowned Prince, Lee Seung Gi!]
I thought I'd never see you again...
but here I am, seeing you again!
I've been keeping up with this show,
and really enjoying it!
You're a secret agent today.
[All the Running Man are in the process of
recruiting agents at the moment.]
- They're going to come to get you at the end.
- They're coming to get me?
They're not coming to greet me?
- No, they're coming to capture you.
- They're coming to capture me right away?
Yes, right off the bat.
I wanted to catch up with Jae Suk since
it's been forever since I've seen him.
But we're not doing any of that,
but jumping right into it?
You can catch up with him
after the mission is over.
Mission first, greetings later.
Yes, I understand.
- Here's your first mission.
- Ah, so this is it.
You are a secret agent.
Transport the secret 007 case to a locker.
If you find the secret code there to
open the case and blow the whistle
you'll gain two points.
You've got about five minutes left
to complete the mission.
What? I only get five minutes?
What is this then... there are only
eight minutes for the whole mission?
Wow... this is...
Wait, in that case...
I'm sorry, but actually since we've worked
together in the past on other programs
can I put my manners aside and ask
you if I can borrow your jacket?
[Asking the VJ to
exchange his jacket with him.]
This is a jacket I'm sponsoring,
so you have to be careful with it, okay?
Would you like for me to
carry your bag for you?
[To perfect his disguise,
requesting for the bag too?]
The bag...
This is heavy.
Maybe I should just take it off.
This is way too heavy.
You have to carry this around
while you film?
I don't think you worked this hard
in the past, did you?
[I can't believe him...]
I really don't think you worked this hard
when we worked together on the other show?
[A comfortable affection passing through
in their conversation?]
Where are you?
[Many members of Running Man who's been
recruited during some time.]
[Mission start!]
Seven minutes for the mission?
[The Giraffe just whizzing by!]
Giraffe! Stop!
- Hey Giraffe, stop!
- There's no stopping in this game!
Run! It's this way!
What are you doing?
[Miss Blank having discovered
Gary's car.]
[Discovers someone!]
- Gary!
- You've got the wrong person!
[Shin Hye issuing out a sticker]
Hello!
[Catches Gary in 45 seconds!]
Is it already over?
How did you know it was me?
I even have glasses on!
[Even at a quick glance,
it's obviously awkward Gary...]
Even from a quick glance,
I could tell it was Gary.
[While all the Running Man
are being recruited...]
[Another agent who's still
trying to perfect his disguise.]
[Infiltrating the stationary store.]
Hello.
[With his characteristic affinity,
greeting the person brightly first.]
Yes... hello, it's nice to meet you.
Something to help... oh, here it is.
This one... I'll just take this one.
Can I try on the helmet?
Look, it's been taped up over here.
[Agent Seung Gi, trying to
disguise himself as the delivery man.]
They probably won't recognize me,
right?
You can't tell either, right?
You can't tell, right?
You really can't, can you?
[A perfectionist?
Trying to find delivery invoices...]
And the box over there.
- It has carbon copy.
- Really?
[Wow... an invoice too?]
I'm using this as a hint for
the members.
[An even kind hint for the members.]
[No one has succeeded
in this mission thus far.]
I don't know what I would've done if
I hadn't borrowed this helmet.
All the other members
have failed this mission?
This is suddenly starting to
make me nervous.
Of all songs, it's
'Catch me' by DBSK playing?
What if I get caught?
Who turned that song on?
Did you do it?
It wasn't?
This is a bad sign...
All the members have just arrived.
- They're here?
- You're going to start now simultaneously.
[Agent Seung Gi's mission - Start!]
Hello?
[Surprising ability to camouflage himself.]
Perfect... this is perfect.
[Seeming very pleased with
his disguise.]
If I seriously get caught like this,
I'll just give up.
[Catch me?]
[Gangnam Station Street, Seoul]
[Agent Seung Gi entering his mission.]
[While no one seem to recognize
who he is in the streets of Gangnam...]
[Infiltrating through exit number five]
There's only one person left now.
[At the same time]
I understand.
Let's go!
[Curious about who the other
agent could be.]
[The members and Agent Shin Hye are
entering through exit number three.]
[I wonder where the lockers are...]
I'm nervous... I'm so nervous.
[Even though there are so many people
inside the train station like this...]
[No one seems to recognize him...]
Shall we get started, Kwang Soo?
[Agents having made
their way down to the station.]
I'm ready.
Look far and wide...
Everyone, keep your eyes out.
[Running right away in the morning.]
I'm so out of breath...
why are we running already?
I think it's around here somewhere?
[Looking for more props for his disguise?]
There's no mark...
I don't think it's that far out.
I think it's in the other direction.
[Agent Gary passing by without
noticing anything!]
I need to get the point...
[Agent Seung Gi's feeling just
as anxious...]
I think I'll find something
if I just keep following you.
[Huh? The Giraffe suspects
something?]
[Is Agent Seung Gi in danger?]
I got you!
[Issues out a sticker!]
Who is it?
He's good looking! Who is it?
I got you...
I already got you with the sticker.
[Agent Seung Gi is caught!]
How did you know?
[Agent Seung Gi fails his mission
after all he did to prepare for it...]
It's so great to see you...
it's been like six years...
[Clothes and the bag from the VJ
he hasn't seen in a long time...]
[And he even got to borrow a helmet
from the owner of the stationary shop...]
[He was really feeling ambitious after
hearing how everyone else had failed...]
[But he's been caught...]
How did you know with all this?
I really prepared a lot for this!
- But you really stuck out.
- I never dreamt that it'd be Seung Gi.
- Have you been well?
- Yeah, have you been well?
It's really great to see you!
- It's really been awhile.
- It's been too long!
[And thus, all nine of the agents
are finally gathered together.]
[Seeing him again for the first time since he
was a High School Student on X-Man.]
[His 'Usher' dance that he used to
dance for the audience?]
[His moves used to be a bit stiff.]
- He's not much of a dancer.
- Can I take my helmet off?
[Resuming the filming,
time to do the slate...]
Would you like to hit the slate,
Seung Gi?
- Seung Gi, why don't you do it?
- Kwang Soo, you stay out of it.
- Don't do it.
- But he's younger than me.
Running Man, it's great to be on here.
Our guests today
are Seung Gi and Shin Hye!
[Lee Seung Gi, Park Shin Hye - Welcome!]
[Shin Hye appeared in Jong Kook's
music video when she was in high school.]
I have no idea how long it's been since
I've seen Seung Gi after X-Man!
I've really been enjoying following
your show.
Really? You watch our show?
- He really keeps up with...
- I understood Hong Gil Dong's feelings.
Even though the show's really funny,
I couldn't exactly come out and say it...
I always felt like...
My friend texts me every week
to tell me how funny the show was.
What is this all about anyways
so early in the morning?
- How many points do you have?
- I have four points.
I have zero points.
[Remember the points you've each
earned during your morning mission.]
You'll find out how those points
are going to work for you.
- Really? What is it?
- I think it's a mission.
- That looks like the Korean flag...
- It's a tiger with the flag.
- Who is that?
- Who's that back there?
[The person inside the screen is...]
[The one in charge of MI-6, 'M'!]
Agents... have you been well?
He looks like her!
I'm your superior officer,
the one in charge of all of MI-6, M.
M?
Since you're all gathered now,
I will give you your assignment.
I have prepared a field agent
evaluation for all of you today.
[Field agent evaluation mission?]
You have to pass this mission before
you can earn the title of being a 007 agent.
I have already chosen the
teams for you.
Yoo Jae Suk, Lee Kwang Soo,
and Agent Lee Seung Gi on one team.
Kim Jong Kook, Ha Ha,
and Agent Park Shin Hye on one team.
And the rest, Song Ji Hyo, Ji Suk Jin
and Kang Gary on the last team.
Take the train to get over to the
next location as quickly as possible.
I wish you all luck.
Then our team has
five points right now, right?
[Team Seung Gi:
Jae Suk- 4 points + Kwang Soo- 1 point]
- Three points.
- We have three points.
We have zero points.
How can you team us up like this?
The quicker you clear the mission,
better advantage you'll have today.
As for how the points are
going to work...
The team with five points will
be the first team to leave...
and the second team to get started
will be the team with three points.
[Just how will this order work out...]
[To be the top secret agent, you
have to acquire the license to oust!]
- Do we just get going then?
- Of course.
I came on the show not knowing
anything.
What is there to know? We
never know what's going on either.
- We're on the same boat.
- So we're all the same then?
Wow... it really has been a
long time.
- It really has been a long time, Seung Gi.
- I know. I'm really glad to see you too.
It really has been a long time
since I've seen Seung Gi.
You two are talking way too much
amongst yourselves.
[Giraffe feeling left out...]
I forgot Kwang Soo's on our team too.
- I'm just saying it's been too long...
- I'm really disappointed here.
- Isn't he the Ace right now?
- Who?
- Kwang Soo...
- Ah, Kwang Soo?
- Why aren't you saying anything about it?
Now that I realize it, you pay
no attention to me at all, do you?
[Seung Gi's team - First to get on board]
- Second team isn't getting on.
- Then it's just us?
- Hello.
- Have you ever taken this before?
- My Mother has taken it by my house.
- She said it's really nice.
- You can see everything from here.
Really?
I had no idea that Running Man started
filming so early in the morning like this.
Running so early in the morning
may not be so good for your health.
Talk to him for us.
No matter how much I try to talk to him,
he never seems to listen.
No matter how I talk to him... and even
though I tell him my heart's pounding...
[Even though it's been awhile, falling
right in sync with their conversation.]
- When you run first thing in the morning...
- Oh yeah, Kwang Soo...
You've totally turned your back on me.
You've just turned your back on me.
It's just been so long since I've seen him.
You have to be a little understanding.
- You really are very tall.
- That's like the given line with everyone.
Didn't you film X-Man with Seung Gi too?
[Happily reminiscing about old times with
many previous staff members of X-Man.]
Can't we stop talking about X-Man?
Let's just talk about Running Man.
We're talking about Running Man too
but it's just been so long since I've seen him
so we're just trying to catch up.
I get that it's been a long time.
- It's because we used to be so close.
- What? Aren't we close?
- Yeah, we're close.
- You two seem like a good fit together.
- Seung Gi and I...
- You mean, Kwang Soo?
Did you call me Seung Gi just now?
Your head is just full of
Seung Gi thoughts right now.
Actually, it's not just my head,
but all my body and all my heart...
everything I am is just full of
thoughts of Seung Gi right now.
- Where do we have to get off?
- I think we've got two more stops.
- How do you know there are two stops left?
- Do you see the blinking light here?
Ah... this is how it's moving?
You don't know much, do you?
I thought this whole section
was where we are right now.
Since Seung Gi doesn't get a chance
to get downtown much...
Are you a little country or something?
Wait... or is it that he just doesn't know?
He could just be a little unaware
instead of saying he's country.
- But that's a little...
- You're too harsh with your words.
Why are you talking to Seung Gi
like that?
Jae Suk, it's me!
I'm getting tears in my eyes.
- What is this?
- Is that a car wash?
- The car wash must be our mission.
- Wait... but why the car wash?
- Do we have to do something physical?
[What kind of a mission could it be?]
What is this?
Your mission...
That startled me.
[What are M's orders this time?]
[A required condition for the
most elite secret agents...]
[A mission to test your agility.]
Agility...
Have you ever seen a car shootout
scene by a 007 agent?
Yes, of course...
Attacking his enemies from his car...
Shooting the targets from a moving car
with accurate aim from the water gun...
I have prepared a water target practice
to test my agents' agility.
You will be expected to shoot
the target precisely.
And you'll have to roll the windows back up
quickly so that your clothes do not get wet.
So we have to shoot the guns, but when we
roll down the windows, we're going to get wet?
- When we roll down the windows...
- When it's this cold out?
- Seriously...
- What are we supposed to shoot?
That's why we've prepared
rain gear for all of you.
The water is going to be fired at you
about every five seconds.
But are we really going to become
007 agents after we do this?
I had no idea that 007 agents did their
training at a car wash like this.
So this is how they get their training.
If you're ordering us to do it,
we'll have to work hard to get it done.
So this is why I was told not to
bother getting dressed up for the show?
- Why did you put mousse in your hair?
- I used a whole can of hairspray on my hair.
I was afraid of it getting messed up
from all the running.
Agents... let's go!
My hat is a little...
[Agent Seung Gi as same as
his reputation that precedes him.]
- What are we supposed to shoot?
- We're supposed to shoot those?
If you shoot four of those within
40 seconds, then you pass the mission.
[If they can knock down four empty cans within
40 seconds, then they pass the mission!]
40 seconds, wow...
Your first mission, you have
40 seconds.
- Fighting!
- No, not yet!
[Being startled into opening the
car door.]
You scared Seung Gi.
Oh, you were saying 'Fighting'...
okay.
I was just acting out instinctively...
- Get in! Get in!
- Kwang Soo! Shut the door!
[A totally chaotic start]
[If they let their guard down even in
the slightest bit, they'll be soaked.]
[If you're going to shoot,
you have to lower the windows...]
Lower the window!
[Shooting distance falling short
from not having pumped the gun enough.]
I'm not getting any distance!
Ah, this is how it works...
- Where's your water gun?
- Give me my water gun!
Give me my water gun!
[Just then, Seung Gi!]
[Taking an attempt at shooting
the targets!]
[Fail]
I figured out how to use the water gun
after 30 seconds elapsed.
[I see...]
Why didn't I get a water gun?
- Kwang Soo...
- Why didn't I get a water gun?
- Give me a water gun!
- I don't have your water gun!
[While the Giraffe was screaming
for his water gun...]
[Here's the water gun?]
[Give me a water gun too...]
Seung Gi, why were you sitting on
my water gun?
- I'm sorry!
- Why were you sitting on my gun?
Also, why weren't you closing
your window?
- Why weren't you rolling up the window?
- Please shut the window, it's way too cold.
- You need to roll up the window.
- And that's my fault?
- Of course, it's your fault!
- You two are full out against me today!
Shut the window. Seriously...
We have to be quick with the water gun.
Seung Gi, you have to shoot right away.
[After having tried it once,
seeming to have gotten the hold of it?]
Instead of aiming,
I think I'm just going to pen fire.
Just start shooting.
- Oh my goodness!
- It's so cold!
So cold! So cold!
Shut the window!
You have to shut your window!
It's so cold!
[Giraffe being doused
with the water full in the face.]
Shut the window! Kwang Soo!
[Concentrating their shots to the right!]
[We told you, you can't be slow to shoot...]
[Fail]
- What are you doing?
- What are you guys doing?
- This game is no joke!
- It's totally awful!
[What to do?]
What are we doing?
[Blue Team also finally arrives]
Is it a water fight?
Why are we doing a water fight
in the middle of winter?
Of course!
Hey, we all...
we all have to work together.
- We have to work together.
- Let's try a simulation.
- We get in the car and shut the door...
- And Kwang Soo hands over the water guns.
And I'll start by rolling up the windows.
[A simulation which will be
no different than the real live action.]
- And when the windows are rolled up...
- Just do it!
Why are you talking so much?
- He can't even take a joke...
- Seriously...
[Mr. Capable having exhausted his patience.]
All of us are standing around here
waiting for you guys right now.
Yes, we understand!
Ready... set... go!
Go! Go! Go!
[The speed of getting in the car
seem to have gotten quicker?]
They're late... they're being too slow!
[Succeeds in handing out all
the water guns.]
[After feverishly charging up their guns...]
[Giraffe getting shot in the face.]
That's our Kwang Soo.
[Just then, Seung Gi takes his aim.]
[Oh?]
[Seung Gi takes down one target!]
[And the target right next to it too!]
[Fall over...]
[If you take too long,
it's time to get soaked!]
[And the right side who hasn't been
able to knock a single one down yet.]
I'm seriously going to end up
drinking all that water!
- It's not working!
- You're not hitting anything.
[Fail]
- Were you just gargling?
- What were you doing that for?
- I see that you're gargling.
- Do you need some toothpaste?
- Aren't you just so clean?
- I drank way too much water.
Can't you put some more water
in the guns for us?
What are you going to do if I end up getting
a cold when I'm already not feeling so good?
You're going to have to keep working
with your cold then.
- What did you say?
- A show does have to go on...
Ready...
Go! Go! Go!
Move! Move!
[Total chaos out of the blue.]
[If you hesitate,
you'll get soaked right away!]
- He's so ugly!
- He really is so ugly.
You're very unattractive.
[A straight shot into the ugly face!]
[Kkuk only worrying about
defending himself.]
[Facing the mission head on out of rage.]
[Oh?]
[Oh? He knocks down both of his
targets!]
[Switching his target to
the left immediately!]
Look at Kim Jong Kook!
[Kkuk shooting at his targets
very passively.]
[Fail]
I was aiming at the targets,
but my stream won't reach.
Ha Ha did really well.
[Battling head on - Sharpshooter, Haroro.]
Hey, that was cool! You look sexy!
[I did good, right?]
Really?
Put your water guns back.
You can't take it out of the car.
Whether we take it out of the car or not,
we've already seen how it's done.
How could I not when the people before
us left looking the way they did?
- Take a look at them right now.
- Why? We're fine.
- No, I'm not okay.
- It's really fun.
Ready... set... go!
They're late even with opening
the door.
[Getting soaked right away without
even being able to shut the door.]
That's so funny!
[Oh? Facing it head on?]
[The force of the water not even
allowing him to open his eyes.]
[Rolling up the window even when
the water attack is over?]
He rolls up the window
after getting soaked first.
[Leaning out to shoot precisely at the moment
that he's being attacked by the water...]
[Rolling up the window again]
Suk Jin, that's not how you do it.
You have to do it the opposite way.
[Timing it at the same time
as the water attack again.]
[Rolls up the window again...]
All he's done is get soaked in
the face.
[Just then, Miss Blank...]
[Wow! Knocks one down!]
[Without hesitation, one more!]
[Will Miss Blank...]
[Fail]
[Rolling it up again?]
Wow... he really is so bad at this.
- Ji Hyo's the best at it.
- The other two awful, aren't they?
I didn't know that Suk Jin
would be that bad.
[Agent Big-nose's eyes have turned red.]
He sticks his head out the door
when he's being shot at with water
and he rolls up the window when
he's not being shot with the water.
I'm going to do it the right way
this time.
[You know him, right? Yoo-ames Bond...]
- Let's go! Let's go!
- Go! Go!
- Muba! Muba!
- Fighting!
Ready...
I think the speed of
my movements have improved.
Do 007 agents really do these
kind of things?
Do they get this kind of training
in England too?
Ready... set... go!
[Huh? In the back?]
Move over! Make some space for me!
Give me my water gun! My water gun!
Water gun!
[Seung Gi opening his window
with lightning speed.]
[Knocks one down!]
Seung Gi's really good!
Why isn't any water coming out?
[Help me!]
Give me the gun!
[While the other end is struggling...]
[Seung Gi shooting at his
remaining target.]
[Hit]
[Wow! Seung Gi knocks both of
them down!]
[Targeting the other side immediately!]
[There's not much time...]
[Fail]
- The water gun is a little...
- Look at them.
Wait... seriously, wait...
He looks just like the stone statues
on Jeju Island, doesn't he?
[Big-nosed statue?]
- Doesn't he look just like them?
- Yeah!
And look, here's Yoda.
[Confirmed to be in the sequel?]
Go!
Jong Kook, you're too slow!
Jong Kook needs to get something.
Fine! Fine!
[Facing off head-on without any
hesitation.]
[Knocks one down]
[Oh! Agent Shin Hye also knocks
one down!]
[Gets attacked by the water.]
Hurry! Hurry! Hurry!
[Pumping up her gun while avoiding
the water.]
[Haroro knocks the second one down!]
[If they can knock just one more down!]
[Will they be the first to pass the mission?]
You have to pump the gun more!
Pump it more!
[Shin Hye eyeing the last remaining
target.]
[Hit]
[Agent Shin Hye hits the target!]
[Yellow Team succeeds
during their second attempt!]
They didn't go over with their time?
Dong Hoon, I'm stuck!
I'm stuck, Dong Hoon.
Open the door for me.
I'm stuck.
[Agent Kkuk with his body stuck
in the window.]
Wait, roll down the window.
Just rip the door off and
get out of it!
- I know you can tear that door off.
- What are you doing right now?
I got it.
My body was stuck in there.
You need to shrink down your
body somehow.
[The window is busted...]
The window isn't going to shut
like that now.
We did it!
Look at this! You ruined the car!
The window won't...
Hey, we can't even shut the window now.
Really?
- What are we supposed to do now?
- What was I supposed to do then? I was stuck!
You have no game etiquette,
no etiquette.
- Fix this up before you leave.
- I'll try to fix it.
Fine, I'll just fix it then.
Why are you getting so angry over this?
This isn't so bad!
See? It's going back in its place right away.
See? It's all set.
[Agent Kkuk,
even able to do car repairs.]
All set!
The first team to have succeeded
may move on to your next location.
[Yellow Team - To their next location]
Mission card.
[Go to 'P' swimming pool.
Address: Bundang Seohyundong, Number 89.]
- A pool?
- Water again?
- Yay! It's water! It sounds like fun!
- It's the pool!
- Don't we have great teamwork?
- It's totally the best.
It's because Shin Hye's putting
her best effort in without any hesitation.
I really feel like we're filming a
Bond movie.
- Let's give it a shot!
- We need to get second place!
We have to get the second place!
- Second place isn't yours!
- Second, second...
There's not even a need to
roll up the windows.
Ready... set... go!
Why does Kwang Soo keep going in
through the back like that?
- Why does he keep doing that?
- Give me a gun!
[Hits one target!]
Seung Gi's good... he's good.
[Enduring being shot by the
water in the face.]
[Hit]
[Agent Seung Gi knocks two down!]
[The other side gets their target too!]
[Success!]
- Success!
- You guys have succeeded.
Red Team, success!
[Why is he getting out that way?]
- Kwang Soo...
- Yes, Jae Suk?
[Carrying their fellow Agent Giraffe
to their next location.]
A pool?
- What?
- I'm already freezing right now.
Seung Gi... you're really cracking me up.
Running Man is no joke.
The show is really deflating me of
all my energy right from the get go.
The most important thing to remember
is that we've only played one game.
- Oh... over there!
- There it is. I see the sign.
[Arrives at the mission site.]
['P' Sports center]
What is this now?
[Huh? This is?]
[Flying Chair]
What are we supposed to be
doing with that?
Huh? What is this?
Isn't that the flying chair?
- That's the flying chair...
- What are those chairs doing here?
They say that as long as your keep your
wits, you'll survive the tiger den.
I'm going to test your ability
to concentrate.
If you can read what's given to you perfectly
within 15 seconds while sitting in the chair
then you pass the mission.
If you go over the time
or if you slip on the words
you'll be immersed immediately
in the water...
Stay sharp.
I seriously had no idea that I was going to
have to take my socks off on this show.
We're going to start the mission.
What to do!
I'm nervous to see how this
is going to be!
Ready...
Set...
[Carefully pronounce the tongue-twisters!]
A rare animal American Mu...
[Terror]
[A refreshing flight]
[This is the power of the flying chair!]
[Are you okay?]
How are you doing, Shin Hye?
You okay?
We have Ji Suk Jin,
who used to be an announcer.
I used to be an announcer,
and was an MC for many different shows.
I'm scared! I'm really scared!
- This is really scary.
- This is no joke!
We're going to start off with Gary
reading. Ready, set, go!
No! You have to start with me!
We're going to start off with Gary
reading. Ready, set, go!
- Me?
- No! You have to start with me!
The 007 mission this time is to start off
from NeJuni Bugorov in Russia
start off from NeJuni Bugorov in Russia,
and go to Sang...
[Off!]
[Satisfied spectators]
[The power to strip them of
their ability to speak.]
This really is scary...
- Seung Gi... bye!
- Bye!
I normally am bad with
any types of amusement rides.
I hate them to begin with.
As for our position...
sit comfortably like this.
And take all the tension out
of your body.
Okay, starting with Kwang Soo.
Agent Seung Gi found an important
document where Golden...
[You need to read it correctly...]
Kwang Soo...
[An ostrich?]
[A experience that leaves you gaping.]
I knew that we were going to get thrown into
the air about two seconds before it happened.
Let's do this if we get thrown off again.
[Thinking of ways to pose
while being flung off?]
Ready...
Starting with Ji Suk Jin, start!
Start!
[Agent Big-nose, who comes
from an announcer background.]
[Is this the type of exams that
you took?]
From the very first word...
he got it wrong from the very first word.
My mind just went totally blank.
Suk Jin has no hair up top!
Look, he has no hair up there.
I left it at home.
[Is he swimming?]
While one person is reading out loud,
the others can quietly practice to themselves.
[Seung Gi's plan: Those waiting for their
turn can practice reading silently.]
- Seriously...
- Seung Gi, let's do this! Kwang Soo!
- Fighting!
- Lets do this!
We'll start with Lee Seung Gi. Ready...
[I will get it done this time!]
Set... go!
[The Ostrich practicing his lines]
[And there they go flying in the air.]
[That wasn't right?]
[There they go...]
- What was it that you said?
- Ae-In-Bba-Kko-Dae?
- Don't you think this is too hard?
- This is impossible!
I think saying just about anything
will be difficult right now.
This really is too difficult for us.
If you were going to be doing this,
why not just do this by the ocean?
[But this is an urban variety show...]
Even my clothes are feeling
too heavy on my body now.
It's making my shoulders droop.
This shirt that I just took off
weighs six kg.
That's true... what Seung Gi said is true.
This is way too heavy.
Look at this.
I can use this as a weight.
[Perfect to use as weights]
Yeah, we can really use it for that.
- Seriously, let's get first place for once!
- Yeah, let's do it.
Ready...
Set... go!
[Fly...]
No, that was right!
- We're telling you, that was right!
- That was my mistake. I made a mistake.
- He said he made a mistake...
- You can't do that!
PD Myuk!
Are you seriously going to be like this?
What? PD Myuk heard it wrong?
What? He heard wrong?
[Why dunking himself in the water?]
[He really is... a high maintenance man.]
Why did they make the ledge
so narrow?
It should be out a little bit more.
- Why did you push Suk Jin?
- I didn't push him.
You didn't push him?
Then how could that have just happened?
- Song Ji Hyo!
- I didn't push him!
- You shouldn't have done that!
- You shouldn't be doing this!
He said he heard us wrong...
[Red Team trying to go for the win.]
Let's go for it! Let's do this!
- Ready, set...
- Do I start?
Who's starting?
Starting with Lee Seung Gi.
Ready... go!
[In an upright posture...]
[A flying Seung Gi]
[A flying ostrich]
[All in their own distinct poses...]
We'll give you an easy
novice-level one.
Starting with Gary.
Ready... set... go!
How is this one easy?
[Is it hard?]
[Blue Team getting it wrong
with a gusto.]
That team is the funniest.
Ready...
starting with Ha Ha, set, go!
[If Shin Hye can get it done...]
[The last sentence!]
[Oh no...]
[Out of time]
Oh my... too bad!
- Oh my, that's too bad...
- Oh my... how disappointing...
I thought they were going
to succeed.
- Kwang Soo...
- Yes, Jae Suk?
- Let's get it done with Seung Gi.
- Fighting!
[Red Team with their overabundant
flow of cheer and energy.]
We're starting with Lee Kwang Soo.
Ready... go!
[If he can say the last sentence,
the team can succeed the mission...]
[Oh! Did they succeed?]
- You passed.
- Pass!
[Diving into the water to celebrate.]
I feel like we've just been freed
from incarceration.
I feel so happy to be in first place.
The next location is a cafe...
[The next location is a cafe,
perhaps there will be food there?]
- Some brunch or lunch would be nice.
- Yeah, it would.
- Doesn't your arm hurt at all?
- No, it doesn't. Why?
It was the first time
I had to pump a water gun.
Pumping the water gun like that...
[The Blue Team also succeeded.
Yellow Team is the only one left...]
[You got it wrong...]
[Mommy...]
You idiot!
Why can't you say it right?
How could you have gotten that wrong?
What to do...
[Oh my goodness...]
[Need to concentrate some more...]
[Finally succeeds!]
Oh my goodness!
Shin Hye, where are you going?
[Red Team arrives at
the next mission location.]
This is the place.
[What kind of a mission awaits them
inside the cafe?]
[Blue Team follows behind and
arrives soon thereafter.]
They beat us here.
I'm going to check how well you agents work
as a team when you're faced with danger.
It's very simple.
You just need to pass through
the rig within 15 seconds.
Okay... show me how well
you guys can work together.
[Just what kind of a rig
do they have to pass through?]
- Physically...
- What?
How can we do that within 15 seconds?
[Tennis racket. A landing net.
A wire hanger.]
- There's no way Kim Jong Kook can do this.
- It's over for them.
You can't try it now.
[Looks as though he may be
good at this mission?]
- This is actually better than the other two.
- The three of us have good teamwork.
- Let's go!
- This is what worries me the most.
[Just then, the Yellow Team arrives.]
[The other team is to mix-up the tools behind
them and the person up chooses randomly.]
Okay, we're finished.
- Tennis racket would be good for us, right?
- You want the tennis racket?
- Should we pick now?
- One, two, three!
Two!
[Red Team chooses the tennis racket!]
[They did get what Seung Gi wanted...
but will they be able to do it?]
- Number three would've been the best...
- That would've been better?
- We can do this... I'll go first.
- Okay. You go first.
- You really think you can do it?
- Yeah, I think I can do it.
[Seung Gi looking confident]
- Are you seriously going to be okay?
- I think I'm going to be okay.
[Needs to pass within 15 seconds!]
[M's mission to test their teamwork skills.
How will it turn out?]
Ready, set, go!
[Oh... Seung Gi, going as planned?]
You're fumbling here too,
aren't you?
Wait...
Just stand still.
I said, stand still.
[He really is stuck!]
- I can't see how to undo this...
- Seung Gi, can you not get yourself out?
Hey, you're acting like Kwang Soo.
[Children and immature adults,
Please do not imitate!]
- Why did you want the tennis racket?
- I thought it was going to be easy.
[But ultimately, he wasted time on his
own and failed the mission!]
- I guess that's not going to work.
- 35 seconds passed already.
[This is definitely Seung Gi's style...]
We get to mix it up this time, right?
- I'm sorry, but I think our team is a bit...
- If you're sorry, then just keep quiet.
What did you say?
Why you, seriously...
Hey, Kwang Soo... hey...
[Agony?]
They said, no practice!
- There's no practicing!
- I won't do it!
[Tiger's sense of humor
which isn't actually all that funny.]
What kind of humor is that?
[It's the Blue Team's turn at the challenge!]
[Red Team trying to
raise their level of confusion.]
You're not going to move anything
after causing all that noise, right?
- I get it, I get it...
- Okay, I think I get it.
One, two, three... number three!
Number three!
[Chooses the wire hanger!]
You really did leave it just
the way it was.
That one's not easy either.
You have 15 seconds.
[All three members of the Blue Team have to
pass through the hanger in 15 seconds!]
[Start]
[Targeting the hanger
as soon as the buzzer sounds!]
Wait... wait!
[Show!]
Wait!
Wait! I'm stuck!
[Kang Gary is flexible!]
Wait... my pants are falling down!
My pants are falling down. Wait!
[Keeping at it without even knowing
the time is already up... warning!]
[Pausing the game due to
pulled down pants!]
Kang Gary... you're wearing yellow
underwear! I saw it!
- Why did you have to...
- Did you see it?
- Seriously...
- It's a color you like, isn't it?
[Ugh, my head...]
[Hanger challenge showing us
that it's possible to win.]
Tennis racket is the worst, right?
The tennis racket?
[Needing to come up with a good plan
after seeing what the other team did.]
[Carefully formulating a plan]
[Yellow Team's turn to choose their tool.]
[Yellow Team chooses the tennis racket]
[Will Mr. Capable be able to get
it around his body?]
If I can't get through it,
then we fail, right?
I will show all of you that I'm
slimmer than what all of you think.
Ready... set... go!
[Shin Hye passes through it
with ease.]
Shin Hye's really skinny!
[That's amazing]
[And how will Ha Ha do?]
[Even Haroro passes through it
after having lost some weight!]
[And finally, it's Mr. Capable's turn!
Will he be able to do it?]
[Time over! Fail.]
[Just as predicted,
it gets caught at the shoulders.]
It won't go through!
What the heck...
What the heck is this?
[A funny scene for those
watching him try.]
[It's obvious that Mr. Capable will
be the worst at this mission?]
[Those muscles are just useless!]
[Body parts that are caught:
Trapezius, triceps, rear lat back muscles.]
And it was caught over here too.
[This is a game
where we can beat Mr. Capable!]
[Red Team's turn.
Yellow Team mixing up the tools.]
- It's number two. Trust me.
- Number two?
- Okay, call you on number two.
- Number two!
[Red Team chooses the wire hanger!]
[Tennis racket was a fail!
Will they succeed with the hanger?]
Ready... set...
- You got it!
- There it is!
[Did the Giraffe build up some
chest muscles?]
Hey...
[Time over! Fail!]
[Is he pulling down the hanger
or his pants?]
[Having no other choice but to
pull it back up towards his head.]
- You have to relax.
- That's right. Don't tense yourself up.
[Why is his expression changing like
that after being told to relax?]
Don't you think that the three of us
are getting a little too close?
[Next is the Blue Team's turn
after having chosen the landing net.]
- Wait...
- Ready...
Suk Jin, hurry! Hurry!
[Slim Ji Hyo passes through in a flash!
Next up is Suk Jin!]
[Anyways, Suk Jin also passes!]
[And lastly, it's Gary's turn!]
[Too bad!
The time's up and they fail!]
[Much easier than the hanger!
The landing net is good!]
[Excited at having discovered
a new tool to work with!]
[Seung Gi starting to whisper
his next plan.]
[Will everything go according to
Seung Gi's plan when it's their turn?]
[Next up is the Yellow Team.]
[Listening to the sounds...]
- Okay, we're ready!
- One, two, three... number two!
Number two!
[Yellow Team picks the landing net!]
Ready... set... go!
[Shin Hye passes through in a flash!]
[The foot!]
It's caught! It's caught!
[Now only Mr. Capable is left to go!]
[Landing net with the possibilities...
Will it work this time around?]
[Time's up! Fail!]
Just rip all this off! Rip it off!
[His muscles that are
rendered useless all day...]
[Next up is the Red Team who
ended up picking the tennis racket.]
[Brain Seung Gi with another good idea.]
[Will they succeed as he foresees
in his plan?]
Ready... set... go!
[Ah... lowering the
one shoulder to pull down...]
[This is Seung Gi's good idea?]
[The tennis racket
undoubtedly getting caught!]
It's caught on your shoulder.
It's caught.
[Change of plans!
Working from bottoms up?]
[Time's up! Fail!]
I thought that Seung Gi was really clever,
when I saw Kwang Soo doing this.
You helped me come up with the plan.
[This is the plan that they've been
whispering together about?]
Wow, don't you look stylish! Gary...
Your legs look so long right now.
[Simple Gary... not even
knowing that he's being teased...]
[Blue Team chooses the landing gear
and starting the challenge!]
[Start]
[Suk Jin passes! Gary's turn!]
[Now if they can get
Blank Ji to pass through...]
[Plenty of time! If she passes,
they place first for this mission!]
[12 seconds!
Blue Team succeeds the mission!]
- How many seconds was that?
- 12 seconds.
[Great teamwork!
Succeeding in mere 12 seconds!]
[Seung Gi getting upset because
things aren't going according to his plans.]
[Blue Team heading to the final location
since placing first with the mission.]
[The final location - Art Center in Yong-In!]
- We're in first place!
- We're in first place right now.
- Wow... this is awesome.
- Yong-In?
[That's the only sound they can think of
to cover up the sound of tools being moved.]
- Are you done?
- We're done.
Jong Kook... want to pick number two?
- Okay, let's do it!
- Which number?
- Wait, wait...
- No, you can't. Number two!
Number two! It is, isn't it?
[Bingo]
[Mr. Capable did it!]
[Shin Hye does it with ease.]
[Now only if Ha Ha can get it done!]
[13 seconds!
Yellow Team succeeds the mission!]
It just went right through!
[After all that planning,
ultimately ending up in last place.]
Oh my... you're in last place?
[Since they're already in last place,
trying it out as they had planned...]
Ouch! Wait...
It's not working. It's not working...
[Ultimately, Seung Gi's plans
are rendered useless...]
- It wasn't working.
- Ah, seriously...
And we were wrong with our
train of thoughts.
- To think that it would be so simple.
- I'm sorry for that.
To be honest, my strategies have
never really worked during games.
I'm sorry, but can you just stay
quiet then?
I knew it...
you really are a bumbly.
I was going to act like the brain of
this operation on the show today...
But it sounded feasible
when I was talking about it, right?
- Yeah, it totally sounded plausible.
- Yeah, I fell for it.
- I thought your plans were going to work.
- I thought that way too.
- Hey... this is our last chance at a win.
- To lean over like this...
We will do whatever it takes to make sure
that you take home the gold today.
- Really?
- Yeah, don't worry about it. Gold!
Gold medal...
[The final mission location-
Yong-In Art Hall!]
- I have a very good feeling about today.
- We're one step closer to victory.
[A gigantic screen...
M to give out another order soon?]
Your final mission.
[The final passage for the secret agent
to pass their skills exam...]
[Water gun fight!]
Water gun fight.
It's water to the end!
So starting now...
Find the water guns that have been
hidden around here for the agents
and target each other's name tags.
The team with the last surviving member
is the ultimate victor.
- Suk Jin, we can do this.
- Yeah, we can do this.
Since we're the first ones to arrive here,
let's hurry and find the water guns.
[Need to hurry and find the
water guns.]
I'm positive that...
[The problem is...]
[There are a thousand water guns here!
But less than 10 of them are operational!]
Nothing's coming out.
So we just need to find working
water guns and shoot?
[Even though there are a lot of guns around,
only about 10 of them actually work!]
The front part of it is blocked.
There's no water in here.
[It's like trying to find
a needle in the haystack!]
What is it? What is it?
- It's a dud, isn't it?
- I know.
[Useful when it comes to bluffing
each other with fake water guns.]
We can't work in alliance, right?
- What?
- We can't be in alliance, right?
- We don't know that, Seung Gi.
- Really?
- Betrayal is always an option, right?
- Of course!
Betrayal is a given.
What fun is a variety show
if betrayal wasn't allowed?
- Want to work together?
- Hey, what if...
[Shin Hye working hard
to find the real water gun.]
There's no other way but to
try out each one.
[It shoots!]
[Yellow Team's Shin Hye
discovers a real water gun!]
What the heck!
Hey! Shin Hye!
Hey! What are you doing!
She found one?
Kwang Soo, run!
Why? Who is it? Who got one?
She found a water gun!
I can't believe I lost him!
[Agent Shin Hye who's able to attack
after having found a water gun!]
[Will she be able to survive to the end?]
[Not knowing if the other's gun is working,
both being cautious with each other.]
I can see that your water gun
is blocked!
Want to trade with me?
[Mr. Capable in fear thinking
that he was going to be shot at...]
Oh... you have to push it open.
By now, someone could've
discovered a real one.
Are we allowed to take their
water guns?
Can we swipe the gun away
from them?
[If you think you can do it...]
[The doors are locked?]
Ah... this is how you open it.
Please, let me find just one.
[He's tried out every one of them he sees,
but they're all nonfunctional.]
There's some over there too.
That water gun looks good.
I wonder how this door opens?
It says I need to put 200 won in there?
[Huh?]
[Oh my... that was the product number...]
[Just as the rumor states,
Seung Gi is a bumbly who talks a lot...]
Wait... this one opens up like this.
Ah! This is how it works!
[Five minutes just to open up
the cabinet...]
The game is going to end before
I can find a working water gun.
[Hard at work,
going in to search the next room.]
This is actually hard. I can't
pump anymore after earlier today.
[His left arm getting sore from having to
pump the water guns to check them.]
[It seems as though a real water gun
is missing from this location as well.]
[I wonder if I should just give up...]
[Huh? That's...]
I wonder if this is a water gun too?
Is this a water gun?
[No matter! An ultimate weapon that is
like none other than a cannon!]
[Anyways, Red Team's Seung Gi
discovers a real water gun!]
Please just one...
Let me find just one.
Just once so that I can fight.
[Blue Team's Suk Jin
also finds a real water gun!]
Please...
[Water gun Master,
Yoo-ames Bond also discovers one!]
[One by one, real
water guns are being discovered.]
[The real fight begins now!]
- Oh my... Sir!
- Oh, so you were targeting me?
What are you talking about, Sir?
[How Yoo-ames Bond-like!]
[The skills of being a secret agent
has seeped into his bones...]
We'll see where this goes later.
[Now is my chance!]
- Am I out?
- Out.
[Clear evidence of a watermark!]
My water gun has never
missed its target.
[Ha Ha, out. Ha Ha, out]
[Whatever...]
[On the other hand,
Agent Seung Gi with his new weapon...]
Seung Gi...
[Mr. Capable, Ace and the Giraffe
all gathered in one place.]
Kwang Soo doesn't have a water gun...
[Seung Gi approaching slowly with
confidence with his weapon in hand...]
[Mr. Capable holding both Kwang Soo
and Seung Gi immobile with his hand!]
[Danger is imminent!]
- Ji Hyo... Ji Hyo...
- I'm useless right now.
[Pumping up his gun in this situation...]
You really are something else...
Kwang Soo, why did you
let him see that you had a gun?
[Jong Kook not letting go of Giraffe's gun
that he has inside his front pocket?]
[Just then!]
[The one in front is a fake! Giraffe
had his real one hidden in the back!]
[The chance to eliminate the Tiger
who's completely fallen for his ruse!]
[Now is the chance!]
Jong Kook is out! Jong Kook is out!
Jong Kook is out!
This keeps spraying.
How do I stop this?
[Still haven't figured out
how to make it stop...]
[Shot by the Giraffe's water gun
and is ousted!]
[Kim Jong Kook, out!
Kim Jong Kook, out!]
I think it would be better
if we oust Ji Hyo right now.
Let's just finish her off right now.
- Ji Hyo, you don't have a water gun?
- No, I don't have one.
I told you that earlier.
I don't lie like you.
- I can't lie either.
- Don't lie. That's your specialty.
- Why are you lying to me about that?
- Say that to my face one more time.
You think I'm going to beg you
for that?
- Say it one more time.
- Go ahead and kill me.
If you shoot me like this now,
you really are a coward.
- You really are a coward.
- Ji Hyo, I shot you.
[Shameless Seung Gi?]
Seung Gi, you suit me very well.
[Red Team's shameless duo]
Fine... have a nice life, you two.
[So far, Red Team is the only team
where all the members are left alive.]
- Two people... we got two people.
- Awesome. That's a great weapon.
- That's the best!
- I finally figured out how to use it.
[Now that we think about it,
Yoo-ames Bond has used this weapon before.]
See how this bends?
Then you can shoot someone like this to.
- Okay?
- Yes. What do you have? Does that work?
- Does it not work?
- No, it works.
Oh, it does work.
[His nonstop bumbly charm]
You know... I really do
realize how bumbly you are now.
Who is that?
That's just our staff member.
[It's our staff member...]
Wow, he's really fast.
[The fascinating world of Running Man...]
Wow... so fast.
Since we've all been running for two years,
even the staff members are pretty fast now.
If this plan succeeds...
The victory will be ours.
[The last surviving members from the
three teams that are gathered in the lobby.]
[Giraffe sneaking behind
Blue Team's Gary...]
[This is how a secret agent
infiltrates a situation!]
[Gary, you're dead...]
[Huh?]
[He's been exposed!]
[He's ruined! Running
is the only way to survive!]
[A barrage of fire from every direction!]
[Has water touched Kwang Soo's
name tag?]
[There's plenty of it...]
[If I go to jail....
Jong Kook will be waiting...]
Kwang Soo is here.
[Deleting the brutal scenes...]
[Currently: Red Team's 2 vs.
Blue Team's 2 vs. Yellow Team's 1.]
Seung Gi...
[Yoo-ames Bond being available
to be relied upon for a chase down.]
[Yoo-ames Bond lying in wait,
while Seung Gi advances forward.]
Who would hop out?
[Big-nosed Brother hiding out of sight
behind the door!]
This isn't easy.
[Amazing teamwork for Blue Team's
Suk Jin and Gary!]
That was a good chance to get him...
[But anyway, where is
Yellow Team's sole survivor, Shin Hye?]
[Waiting to ambush!]
[Running Man members and their first time
guests are all veterans at the chase!]
[Blue Team's Gary closing in
from behind...]
You've slipped through my fingers
several times today.
[Just then!]
[Seung Gi sneaks up from behind!]
[A breathtaking moment where a
sneak attack is happening back to back!]
You've slipped through my fingers
one too many times today...
[Did he get Gary?]
[Bulls eye! Blue Team's Gary, out!]
No! Can't be! Can't be!
[A short battle showing
how deadly teamwork can be!]
[Gary - Out!]
[Gary - Out! Gary - Out!]
[Blue Team's sole survivor,
Big-nosed Brother.]
[Seung Gi's on the chase again!]
[Red Team's Yoo-ames Bond heading
off to offer his assistance!]
[Just then! The one person
who's been eyeing his back!]
[Yellow Team's sole survivor, Shin Hye!]
[Amazing!]
- Shin Hye...
- Where is she?
- Jae Suk, what happened?
- I had no idea she was in there!
- How in the world did that happen?
- Wow... I can't believe that she got me!
Seung Gi... take care of it.
So I killed one person, right?
Seung Gi... use it when you're in danger.
[Yoo-ames Bond gives him his gun
with one shot left.]
- No, it's okay to give it to him.
- Jae Suk...
- Jae Suk, you just wait.
- Seung Gi...
[Please make sure to win for our team!]
[Now that we look at the scene,
there is one survivor per team!]
The way I see it, with number of people
ousted already, it's Suk Jin's time to go.
Time to go? You're too harsh with
your words.
[Big-nosed Brother reacting to
Seung Gi's psychological provocation.]
Let's you and I... I'm not kidding.
I'll let you take the win after.
- Why can't you trust me?
- Of course, I can't trust you!
Look at that temper...
Why can't you trust me?
[Where did Seung Gi go?]
[Red Team's Seung Gi
springs an ambush attack!]
Seung Gi! Wait... Seung Gi...
[Nice... then shall I attack from
the back?]
You really are too much.
[Men are corralling her from
both ends!]
Why are you doing this to me?
- Come on, Seung Gi!
- I have no other choice, Shin Hye.
Seung Gi, listen, we...
- Let's just kill Suk Jin first, okay?
- No, that's not right.
That's not right.
You know that's not right.
Don't come near me!
[Park Shin Hye - Out!
Park Shin Hye - Out!]
- Seung Gi, did you shoot me?
- Show us your back.
- Did you shoot her?
- She's out.
[A bulls eye on the name tag!]
- You can't blame me, okay?
- There's no blaming around here.
I don't blame you. But I'm
going to tell the Director everything.
That you betrayed me even after
being in the music video together with you...
- She's really mad.
- Come on, don't be like that.
You really lasted a long time,
you know that?
- Shin Hye...
- Bye!
Jong Kook, would you like to come over
and spend the night at my house tonight?
This guy's loyalty is a problem.
Why is he so angry again?
- I did something again...
- You betrayed him again?
I bet tomorrow really is
going to be an interesting show.
- Tomorrow may be your last day...
- You should just skip tomorrow.
You should just run.
Make a run for it...
[Gary's advice to him
is to make a run for it?]
It's because I can see how tormented he is...
he looks like he's having a hard time.
And I was hoping that I could
be of help to him.
[Fine... I'm not doing it, I'm not.]
Stop it now.
Shin Hye...
[The Yellow Team finally reunites.]
- Good job, Shin Hye.
- Good job.
How could you have died first?
[Shin Hye having kept the hope
of victory alive for her team.]
I've been hiding there for about
five minutes.
I didn't have a water gun.
- What the heck?
- What happened?
[Huh? Suk Jin and
Seung Gi walking in together?]
[Who won and who lost?]
[Agreeing to a duel since they're
both already exhausted.]
[The gullible kid...]
[Attack after the count of five!]
[Promising each other
to each take five steps!]
One!
[I'm a bit of a coward
while I'm playing games...]
[You, seriously!]
[He really is shameless Seung Gi!]
[With Agent Seung Gi's actions,
Red Team's scored a win!]
You did good! Great job!
[Huh? Something is being carried in?]
I bet this is something
for tomorrow's mission.
Good work, everyone.
To the first and second place team
of today's mission...
you will be given a pc and a smart phone
which will come in very handy tomorrow.
And unfortunately,
to the team that came in last today
you'll only be given a cell phone.
Don't despair, and I hope that
you'll work even harder tomorrow.
Then each team member take a case
that's been brought in front of you.
You're all dismissed.
[Each team taking cases with the
order of winning written on the case.]
[How are we supposed to use
these tomorrow?]
It's something Jae Suk can't even use
even though he has it in hand.
What do I use this for?
That's a relief. Because I
don't know how to use it either.
What do we use this for?
[Anyways, the agents who've been
given supplies by M...]
[all went to each of their homes
in peace for the night...]
[The next day]
[In front of Agent Jae Suk's home.]
What brings you here?
[Heading out for the day with the
case he's been given in hand...]
Hello?
[A phone call they all receive
from Director M...]
[You've all been issued a
license to oust...]
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Running Man Secret Agents, your
real intelligence operation starts now!]
I've been given a tip that the gold
inside the prism vault will be detonated.
I heard that he's still alive!
[Without regards to any method, acquire
any information you can on your opponent!]
[Their enemy -
Spine tingling being of darkness!]
You have to be honest with me.
[No one can be trusted! Division
and confusion amongst the team!]
007... I'm putting my trust in you.