Subtitles by DramaFever
[Running Man:]
[Running Man]
[Mission Impossible]
[Republic of Korea: Seoul]
[The people are busy leading their lives]
[There are 7 secret agents
with hidden identities]
Welcome.
[Gary 35 years old]
[Working undercover as an employee
at a Chinese restaurant]
You came to the right place.
How would you like me to do your hair?
[Song Ji Hyo - 32 years old]
[Working undercover as a hair designer]
What's your size?
45?
[Ha Ha -34 years old]
[Working undercover at a shoe store]
Just give me $450 for it.
$450 cash.  No discount.
That's too expensive.  Thank you.
Miss... $45.
[Selling one pair a day is his wish]
[Ji Suk Jin -46 Years Old]
[Currently searching for an undercover job]
[No one knows what's about to happen today...]
[Lee Kwang Soo - 28 years old]
[Working undercover at a pharmacy]
[This man hard at work ironing...]
[Yoo Jae Suk - 41 years old]
[Working undercover at a dry cleaners]
[And lastly...]
[The secret identity of the person
surrounded by all these beautiful flowers...]
[The imposing biceps]
[Kim Jong Kook - 36 years old]
[Undercover taking care of the flowers]
Oh, so pretty...
[Tiger buried under the flowers... Awkward!]
If I live among the flowers everyday like this,
I'm going to become a flower myself.
[Tiger Flower?]
The phone's ringing!
[Just then, the phone rings]
Hello?
[R-Central's adventure for the agents
that crosses international boundaries?]
[It all begins with this one phone call...]
Yes, this is the Running Pharmacy.
Have you all been well under your
hidden identities?
You have been called to the R-Central
on an emergency call.
An emergency call, you said?
It's already been 10 minutes
since I started working...?
I don't think this is right to the boss when
I've already started working...?
Right now?
-Yes, sir.
-I understand.
I got it.  Over.
It's been 40 years since there's been
an emergency call like this.
At last...
It's time.
Ma'am...
I think I'm going to have to quit.
I've got an urgent call from the central.
After working for only 10 minutes...
I have to return to Central.
It was a good job...
-This is sad...
-How sad...
-I'll see you again next time...
-I hope next time...
But you're not even upset and being so casual
about it when I told you out of the blue...
[After spending time with the MC,
she's well versed in ad libbing]
How can you say that so naturally?
[Prepping for takeoff]
[Their identities... Revealed in the name tag]
[The agent's equipment that were
hidden in the metal carrier]
Long time no see...
Everyone has their own materials...]
[The giraffe's awkward movements...]
Let's go!
[The 7 secret agents heading to R-Central]
[Suspicious even at a quick glance...]
[Move to the Central without being
detected by the civilians]
[We told you not to do things like that!]
[R-Central entrance]
What's this?
[Retinal recognition program]
Agent Yoo Jae Suk. Access accepted.
Welcome home.
[Welcome to R-Central]
[Stealthily arriving secret agents]
Agent Gary.  Access accepted.
-Take a look!
-Agent Ha Ha.
-Agent Ji Suk Jin.
-Agent Song Ji Hyo.
Agent Kim Jong Kook. Access accepted.
Hey.  Don't act like a brat!
[All but Agent Kwang Soo access granted]
[Lastly, Agent Kwang Soo]
Access denied.  Access denied.
[Scalp scan?]
[It seems even the scalp is faulty]
What the heck?
[R-central's main office]
What is this?  Is this our central?
I don't know. Come in.
Hey! Kwang Soo! How did you get in?
What are we doing today? Seriously?
They're going to tell us through the monitor...
[And the steel case in front of the agents]
Hey! That's going to explode.
[The fearless Tiger takes care of it]
Why is the muscle boy doing that?
[A secret device in the steel case!]
Wow... That really is like a movie!
[Maybe there's person under there...]
No, no... There's no one under there.
Isn't this going to
self-destruct in 3 seconds?
[The screen image when
the button got pressed...?]
What's this?!
-Man...
-Isn't that Manchester?
[Manchester United?]
[Could it be...?]
-Is it Park Ji Sung?
-Yeah, it's Park Ji Sung.
All the Running Men...
Hello, this is Park Ji Sung.
This is Manchester United Training Ground,
where I'm currently residing in right now.
[Real... Park Ji Sung!]
I got it wrong.  I'll do it again.
I'm so glad to be greeting you like this.
Crew Yoo Jae Suk, have you been well?
-Of course!!
As of right now...
I will give you your new mission.
The name of the mission is...
Running Man.
First, find the 8th Running Man,
and complete your mission.
The location is... Here.
[Jaegidong Medicine Market]
[The target password]
[Sparrow - Tweet Tweet]
[Chick - Chirp Chirp]
[Giraffe - Betray Betray]
Giraffe - Betray Betray...
[However, you cannot reveal your identity]
[Time given 1 hour]
R-Central's secret mission...
A total of 7 members...
Yoo Jae Suk  Ji Suk Jin. Kim Jong Kook.
Gary.  Ha Ha.  Song Ji Hyo.
And lastly, Lee Kwang Soo.
I advise that the team doesn't allow a split
within the group due to betrayals.
Especially... Be cautious of betrayals' icon,
Lee Kwang Soo.
Don't worry.
-Don't worry.
-Why are you laughing?
[The adorable side of him that you
can't see during the matches]
In a situation where you are suspected
of being the spy, or you're ousted,
we will deny any knowledge of you.
This message will self destruct in 5 seconds.
Then... Good luck.
[No way...]
[It really exploded]
It's a real explosion!
[A strong reaction]
[Park Ji Sung does not lie]
We almost got hurt!!
What if we had been standing here?!
[We knew that you were going to run for sure]
Hey... Things have been so crazy lately!
[The trend of late...]
[If you're shocked by this mere event,
we're going to have some problems...]
[Two-hearted Park Ji Sung]
[Find the 11th Running Man]
Are you ready, Mr. Capable?
Running Man... Out.
[Park Ji Sung vs. Running Man]
[Personal vehicles at the ready]
What is this?
-What is all this?
-This really is a spy vehicle...
I guess this is where we disguise ourselves?
I will give you your new mission now.
Your location is here.
[Herbal Medicine market that has 50 years
of operating history]
[Over 1000 Herbal Medicinal doctors,
and herbal stores]
Find the 8th Running Man
and complete your mission.
[The 8th Running Man is here]
[Working at the Medicinal Market while
hiding the true identity...]
[8th Running Man... Find that person]
The secret code word?
It's tweet, tweet of a sparrow.
Chicks Chirp Chirp.
And the giraffe's betrayal betrayal.
Just one hour?
-What's all in there?
-There are some camouflage pants...
I can't tell it's Suk Jin!
From the back, I really can't tell!
[The miniature sized mask for the Tiger]
Why are ours so small?!
[Huh?  Ha Ha's mother?]
Oh!  It's mother!  Ha Ha's mother.
-I hope that it's a huge hit.
-That's crazy!  Even the speech...!
I really can't tell...
[Arrived at the target location]
[This mission has to be completed
without being detected]
If one person gets caught,
then all of us are going to be suspected...
Not a single one of us can be suspected.
[Someone is approaching]
-Everyone... Hello.
-Oh, hi!
I'm the Intel from Kangbuk District.
Here we go again!
Everyone...
[What could be the command from this Intel?]
I will tell you about the rules.
[R-Central Intelligence Divisions]
The 8th Running Man is quietly working at
this market with his identity hidden.
Find that 8th agent... And say the code word,
for you to complete your mission.
[Time allotted is one hour]
I'm heading off!
[At last, the secret agents head out]
[Huh?  Suk Jin?]
Fighting!
He's going first?
If by any chance a civilian or a merchant
shouts out your name,
or if more than 5 people start chasing
after you from recognizing you,
you'll have to forfeit your rights as
a secret agent and the mission is over.
[A neighborhood young man?]
[No... It's Gary]
I think he'll get recognized.
If by any chance a civilian or a merchant
shouts out your name,
or if more than 5 people start chasing
after you from recognizing you,
you'll have to forfeit your rights as
a secret agent and the mission is over.
[Ostrich?]
[Kwang Soo's suspicious disguise]
Not everyone can succeed anyways...
Someone has to get ousted.
[Already gave up on the giraffe?]
There's nothing we can do about it.
[Suspicious person walking the streets
of the Medicinal market...]
[Unstable Agent Kwang Soo of R-Central]
[Secret agent Ji Hyo's turn]
[Casually strolls into the location]
That suits you... It's fashionable.
You have any idea who it could be?
[Secret Agent Yoo Jae Suk]
[Secret Agent Jae Suk enters the scene too]
[Lastly, Secret Agents Jong Kook and Ha Ha]
[Slowly approaching the scene]
You can't tell it's me, right?
They have no idea it's me.
[Where could the 8th Running Man be?]
[Secret agents starting the search]
[And the stalking ostrich...]
Our 8th Running Man is quietly working inside
this market while keeping his identity hidden.
You have to find that 8th spy,
and say the code word before
the mission is completed.
[The mission to find the 8th agent]
[Somewhere among these numerous places...]
Sir... Sparrow?
Chick...
You want me to repeat it?
You don't know the code?
-Have a great day.
-You have no idea who I am, right?
-No, I have no idea.
Thank you.  Have a great day.
You have no idea who I am?
[Kindly answering the strange questions
posed by weird Jae Suk...]
Sir...
-Sparrow?
-What?
He's looking for a sparrow.
Have a great day.
[Where is that sparrow?]
It's really hard to be mindful of my manners
when I can't reveal my identity
I should be paying my respects...
Sparrow?
Please enjoy your meal.
[Just a minute!]
Excuse me?
-Please take the dishes.
-Ah... Take the dishes?
[Mistaken as the delivery man...]
He told me to take the dishes...
[Suspicious neighborhood's ostrich...
and neighborhood young man...]
Gary.  If you go that way,
you're not going to find anything.
They're going to think that you're
just some kind of a strange person.
Everyone that looks at you is going to
think that you're a suspicious person.
But you still look very natural.
[Agent Gary fitting in
as the neighborhood young man]
Sparrow... Chick...
I think the heat has gotten to me!
Sparrow...!
-Sparrow.
-Tweet Tweet.
[Huh?]
-Chick.
-Chirp Chirp.
[Could it be?]
Giraffe?
[Now the last secret code...!]
[Not it...]
Giraffe?
That's not it!
Hello.  Sparrow?!
Chick?!
-Sparrow.
-Sparrow!
Sparrow.
Chick?
How can you be so blatant about it?
Jae Suk!
How can you call out my name when
this is a secret mission?
-I'm sorry, bro.
-Don't even call me brother!
If you scream out sparrow,
everyone's going to suspect something.
[Really suspicious looking two]
This way, this way.
[Walking as if he's out to get a drink]
Sparrow.
[Those kids...!]
Let's settle it with rock-paper-scissors.
Sparrow.
[Agent ostrich feeling nervous
about something]
[Did they recognize me by any chance?]
[If his identity gets revealed,
he loses his rights as a secret agent]
[The Herbivore giraffe goes to stand by
the tiger for now]
That's Kim Jong Kook.
[Ha Ha... He's caught]
Hey!  I thought I was going to pass out.
[All the secret agents are hiding out]
Just what are you wearing?
[In midst of analyzing
Kwang Soo's obvious disguise]
How could you have worn that?
-It's because I'm trying to remain a secret.
-Try bending down.
-Try nodding.
-This is your secret?
This is rather better.
[This is better?]
Try walking.
This is better.  This is safer.
We've got problems.  The kids are coming.
[The kids are coming in a group]
[Approaching with their phones in hand!]
-There's only one way for us to escape here.
-What?
It's Yoo Jae Suk!  Yoo Jae Suk!
[The lowest scheme...]
I just saw Yoo Jae Suk!
I saw Yoo Jae Suk!
[You can't trick the kids that way...]
There's no doubt, it's him!
[Approaching with the kid in front]
You have to run!
Hurry!  They're coming!
[The 3 cornered secret agents]
-1, 2, 3.
-Hi kiddo.
Oh!  It's Yoo Jae Suk!
[The secret agent that's announcing the
other secret agent's name neighborhood wide]
[The other two agents'
danger has been avoided]
I'm being chased by a bunch of kids right now!
If the civilians or
the merchants yell out your name,
Or in a case where 5 or more civilians
recognize you and chase after you...
You'll be stripped of your secret agent status.
[Agent Kwang Soo...
Stripped of his rights as a secret agent]
I haven't been recognized...
I got ousted because of you guys.
Really?  I'm sorry.
So tall...
[Seems envious of Kwang Soo's height]
Are you guys leaving?
[Agent Kwang Soo- Paused]
[Kwang Soo...]
[Just where in the world is the
8th Running Man?]
Yoo Jae Suk...?
[Jae Suk's name?]
[Asking for his signature...]
Sir, I'm...
[He's on a secret mission...]
How did you recognize me?
How did you know it was me?
-I recognized you at first glance.
-I didn't think you'd be able to.
[Asking for a signature for his daughter]
I didn't think you could see my face?
How did you?  I covered up my face?
As soon as I saw you,
I recognized the grasshopper face.
Yoo Jae Suk...
Since your identity has been revealed,
you've been paused.
[Jae Suk... Identity compromised]
But he was asking for my signature...
I was just...!
-How can you write down your name for him?
-No... That's not it...!
But he was...
-Sir... I just... Thank you.
-Running Man, Fighting!
Sir!  Tell him!
Tell him this isn't right!
Sir!
[Agent Jae Suk... Paused]
I don't know what just happened.
This is because Kwang Soo and Suk Jin
made it all weird!
I shouldn't have signed it for him...
[Secret mission is not so easy...]
[A fascinating scene for the passersby]
I've been caught right now...
[Ultimately surrounded by the civilians...
Mission failed]
-Sparrow.
-Who is it?
-Are you going around volunteering?
-Sparrow?
-But why are you shooting pictures?
[Secret agent being caught on camera!]
[Caught on many pictures...]
This really is daunting.
This really is daunting...
Just how far does this place go?
By any chance... A sparrow?
Sparrow...?
I'm sorry.  I'm sorry.
Sparrow...
Tweet Tweet.
Chick.
Chirp Chirp.
Giraffe!
Giraffe... Giraffe doesn't make any sounds.
[Neighborhood young man staying in hiding]
[They just ousted Kwang Soo!]
[The most dangerous element...
Neighborhood kids]
Can I hide in here for a little while?
I'm a secret agent right now, and too many
people are starting to recognize me...
So I have to hide for a bit.
Please allow me to for a little while.
[A flabbergasted business owner]
I apologize when you're in the middle
of playing your instrument.
I'll just hide out in here for a while.
Who are you?
I'm a secret agent.
I'm feeling so nervous right now...
I would like to request a performance
that could help calm me down.
-I'm not very good...
-It's okay!
[She really is performing for him!]
[Singing along]
[Alert]
[Gathering of civilians after hearing
the singing]
[It's Gary]
Thanks for the strength!
-Your identity has been compromised.
-Huh?  What are you talking about?
[Gary's identity has been revealed]
From here?
Here?  From here?
I got caught because of you!
-It wasn't me!
-You've been standing here the whole time!
[Agent Gary... Paused]
My secret is out.
It wasn't here?  Not here?
[Of course,
Ha Ha's identity has been compromised]
I want to be alone.
[Agent Ha Ha... Paused]
[Is it really Mission Impossible?]
[Only secret agents left-Jong Kook and Ji Hyo]
[If it's this hard to find the 8th member,
will they be able to find the 11th?]
Be careful.  Someone's walking by.
[Mr. Capable and Ace staying in touch
to warn one another]
[That looks like Song Ji Hyo...]
Jong Kook.  What should we do now?
Have you looked all over this side?
I didn't go to the end over there.
I stopped midway.
People are purposely out looking for us.
We've got a big problem.
I'm out on the streets for now.
Jong Kook.  I checked that side already.
Go in the opposite direction.
Go the opposite direction, you say?
-Hello... Sparrow?
-Tweet Tweet.
-Chick?
-Chirp Chirp!
Giraffe?
[The last code word, giraffe?]
-Lee Kwang Soo?
-I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
[Secret code failed]
Hello.
Sparrow...
Excuse me?
I'm searching for something right now.
I'm sorry.
[The time is ticking]
Sparrow?!
[Just where is the 8th Running Man?]
By any chance, sparrow?
[If they had divided the area from the start,
it wouldn't have been this hard...]
I've been all over the place,
and I still don't know.
Hello.
Hello.  By any chance... Sparrow?
Tweet Tweet.
-Chick.
-Chirp Chirp.
Lee Kwang Soo... Oh my, why did I say that?
[Out of nervousness, Agent Ji Hyo slips]
That was a mistake... Giraffe?
Betrayal Betrayal?
[Found it!]
[Finally the 8th Running Man has been found!]
Thank you!
Since you succeeded the mission,
I'll give you this case.
Thank you!
This is the case, but I gave you another one.
[But there's another case...?]
-And this is your next mission.
-Next mission?
[A black case containing the next mission]
Thank you!
Thank you, sir!  I found it!
-Let's set it down for now.
-I thought I was going to die!
[Checking the next mission]
What is this?
Something just came on.
If you've found the 8th Running Man,
the next mission is to find your 9th one.
Here is your location.
[Mistake!]
He slipped just now?
[College]
Especially for this mission,
be cautious of Ha Ha's fastness.
This message will self destruct in 5 seconds.
Throw this outside!
[The next location... 'x' college]
[This is Park Ji Sung's Alma mater]
[Find the name tag for the 9th Running Man
that's hidden in the library]
Yes?
[Moving on to the next mission location]
All of you have barely passed the mission
through Agent Jong Kook, and Agent Ji Hyo.
-It's the same thing...
-It's team work! We're all as one.
The second mission is...
To go to 'X' college's library,
and find the name tag for the 9th Running Man.
The name tag?
But we were told to be
careful of Ha Ha's fastness.
-What does that mean?
-I think the opponent is a girl.
-Ah... That's right...
-I think that's why we were told to be careful.
Who could it be?
Remember what he said about Kwang Soo?
Be cautious not to get separated.
[The journey of hardship to find
the 11th Running Man]
Ah... Ji Sung... Why didn't he call me?
Stop it!  Why would Ji Sung call you?
You are going to be shocked if you
run into Park Ji Sung sometime in the future.
Stop it....!
[Everyone's going crazy claiming they know him]
-Because it's the middle of the season...
-What about the season?
It's just too bad that I can't just call him.
I'm not going to say anything...
I'm not saying anything.
Don't, Suk Jin.  Don't.
It would be awesome if Park Ji Sung
came on the show once.
To come on the race and have a race...
['X' College]
[Front of the library is a full of crowd]
[This place... Where Park Ji Sung attended...]
[Entering the library where
9th Running Man is]
[The agents not letting go of their wariness]
This is nice in here.
What is this?
-We have to find the member here.
-This is the library?
Do we just have to rip off their name tag?
Why are you warning me of my fastness?
[Suddenly attacked by a security team]
-What are they doing?
-Our feet?
What are you doing?
If you do this,
we won't be able to catch anyone.
Why am I the only one going barefoot?
Why am I the only one...?
[Tightly binding Agent Jong Kook]
-This is too much...
-Seriously.
-I'm sorry.
-Let me put my shoes on!
[Secret agents faced
with their greatest challenge]
[These people overlook the scene
with ease...]
Let's just quietly go little by little.
Let me move a little bit!
Go slowly!
[Huh?  they're moving!]
-Hello!
-What's that?
[A familiar voice?]
-Hello!
-What's that?
Isn't that Hyo Rin?!
[Sistar's Hyo Rin]
What are you doing there, Hyo Rin?
[Idol Sistar with the top singing talents]
[Sistar's Sexy Hyo Rin's here?]
You just wait right there!
[Is Hyo Rin the target?]
Hello!
-Who is it this time?
[Sistar's Da Som]
Da Som!
[Sistar's So Yoo]
It's So Yoo!
Hello!
[Sistar's Bo Ra]
[The 9th Running Man is one
of the Sistar members?]
Ji Hyo!  Long time no see!
There she is!
[Sistar with tons of ease...]
Hey!  Wait!
You can't go off on your own like that!
[Roaring laughter]
You come here!
[Bo Ra's provocation]
[But even Kwang Soo's long arm can't reach]
But how are we supposed to catch the 4 of them?
That's why we have a handicap too.
We can only walk.
-If we run, we're ousted.
-Really?
-No... They won't walk too slowly.
-Just walk?
We're great at heel-to-toe walking.
[You stop right there!]
I'm seriously going to go crazy!
We could have gotten one of them!
I don't think there's any way
they can get us?
How are they going to get us
when they're walking like this?
-We could have grabbed one!
-Who was it?
[But will it... Really end like this?]
10 minutes have passed.
Because 10 minutes have passed...
we can untie one of the ties.
[Rule:  If 10 minutes pass,
one of the ties can be undone]
[Become 2 teams of 3 and 4 members]
And if another 10 minutes pass,
another tie will be undone.
[4 members will become 2 teams of 2]
Nice... Nice.
After that... We can't untie any more.
-Let's untie it here.
-I'm scared of the retribution.
[Now it begins]
We're in big trouble now.
[Separated into a team of 3...
The Kook-Lee-Ji Brothers]
Guys!
[The speed!]
Hyo Rin!
We can't go this way... Not this way.
This way!  Come this way!
[Da Som's been cornered]
Corner her!
Da Som!
[Da Som barely escapes up the stairs]
[Feels like 10 years of her life
have been shaved off]
-1...  1... 2.
-No.  This has to be 1.
On 1, you have to step up.
Why are you stepping up with that?
Suk Jin, I'll take care of it.
Let's not get annoyed with one another.
[The easy brothers going at it at each other]
But you're getting angry with me!
It's because when I said 1,
you're stepping with 2!
-Let's all apologize to one another.
-I just got angry...
-I'm sorry Suk Jin.
-I'm sorry too.  Please understand.
-Suk Jin, I love you.  I'm sorry.
-I love you too.  Let's hug it out.
Let us not fight.
From 1. Let's start.
1, 2.  1, 2...
-What are you doing?
-It was 1!
[The truce doesn't even last a minute...]
What are you doing?!
You have to go up on the step together!
Everyone needs to get up on the same step,
but we're all going on different steps!
-Suk Jin!  Let's apologize.
-Okay... I'm sorry.
-Kwang Soo... I'm sorry.
-Yes, I'm sorry too.
-Let's hug it out again.
-I love you!
Ready, set, go.
1, 2.  1, 2.  1, 2!
You guys look more at ease!
Let's go together in the elevator.
[Slowly getting used to their steps]
10 minutes have passed.
[4-man team become 2 teams of 2]
[Emergency!]
[Sistar running frantically running away
after being at ease]
[Ha-Hyuk brothers running at top speed!]
[Gary and Ji Hyo are pretty fast too!]
[Agent Jae Suk and Agent Ha Ha
approaching at a scary speed]
What do I do?
You guys come to the history section quickly.
-We have to rip it off right now.
-No!  Don't rip it off!
Hyo Rin!  Hey!  Hey!
Hyo Rin!
Run!  Quickly, run!
1, 2.  1, 2...!
[Gary-Ji Hyo.  Jae Suk-Ha Ha rallies!]
What do I do?!
[Hyo Rin stuck at a dead end]
You can't...!
Nothing?
[Huh?  Someone...?]
Oh my... So Yoo!
[Soo Yoo's hiding place discovered!]
-So Yoo!
-I'll rip it off.
[Suk Jin's master hands at ripping off
the name tags of Idols]
[So Yoo's name tag is off]
It's a dud!
-It's not So Yoo!
-The real one is still out there!
[Da Som secretly getting in the elevator]
[Ha Ha and Jae Suk seen on the other side!]
-Press it.  Press it from below.
-Look!  Jong Kook is over there!
Jong Kook.  Press 3rd floor.
Press 3rd floor.
He wants us to press 3rd floor.
We got her!!
[Da Som can't escape anywhere]
-Good job!
-Great job!
It's Bo Ra, right?  I thought so.
[Da Som is also a dud]
-Da Som, good job.
-Thank you.
With her name tag off like that,
she looks so innocent.
Without the name tags, they're so innocent,
and sweet... Look at her pink cheeks!
You're a little into Da Som now, aren't you?
-She's really pretty.
-Seriously.
I'll be your last love for you.
[9th Running Man is the Musical Major
of this school, Bo Ra!]
[Quietly evading Running Men
from the emergency staircase]
[They're right out front!]
The roof on the opposite side.
[She went down...]
2nd floor... 2nd floor.
[Gary and Ji Hyo who's already on 2nd floor,
ready to grab]
Gary and Ji Hyo went down to the
2nd floor earlier...
[Bingo!]
What do I do?
Please...!
[Bo Ra ready to get on the emergency elevator]
Why isn't it up here yet?
We found her!  Found her!!
-Don't come out!  We've got you!
-2nd floor!  Come to the 2nd floor!
[Bora fiercely resisting]
[Swift couple also arrives]
[Escaping at this moment?]
[Captured by Ace Agent, Ji Hyo]
-9th... Running Man!
-No!!
[Mission success]
The image is going to come on like earlier.
Look.  Here it is again.
-What's this?
-I feel like I'm on friendly terms with it.
Now... Go find the 10th Running Man.
Here's your location.
[DMC Advertisements]
Mr. Capable... There's not much time.
You need to hurry.
This message will self destruct in 3 seconds.
Put it down right now.
It really does explode.
[Now if 1 more person is found,
off to the 11th mission]
[10 Running Man location, Sangamdong]
[The agents have arrived]
[What's that large guitar case?]
Can we open it?
[Water guns]
-It's water guns!
-They're back!
Here it is again.
[A reliable support weapon]
There are only 4?!
[What is the mission they've been waiting for?]
[Protect the only woman, Song Ji Hyo
until Song Ji Hyo scored her goal!]
[However, if Ji Hyo's ousted,
then everyone is ousted]
What is it that we're supposed to do
until she scores a goal?
[Protect the only woman, Ji Hyo!]
Is Ji Hyo getting protection from us
for the first time?
[Protect Song Ji Hyo from the snipers]
[Song Ji Hyo to safely arrive
at the final destination...]
[And if she scores in the net...
Mission clear]
[However somewhere along the road,
the 10th Running Man Assassin is...!]
[Switching to paper name tag
for the water gun]
Aren't there any tools
for me to protect my back?
We'll protect you!
Come on...
[Somehow, can't be trusted...]
I think it'll be much easier
for me to just get hit.
[Anyways... Getting this ball in the goal
means that the mission is a success...]
-Let's go.
[Mission:  Protect the only woman,
Song Ji Hyo. Start!]
[Just in case the water
gets on the name tag...]
[Even if hit by the same team, as long as
the water gets on the name tag, OUT!]
-Be careful.  One drop of water, it's over.
-Ji Hyo.  You can't be out like that.
Put your back up against me like that.
Just like that!
It's because I can't trust you!
Even if I end up giving you a back hug,
I can't do anything about it.
You have to understand it.
-If you back hug me, then you'll die.
-You'll die then.
-Even still, I have to protect Ji Hyo.
-Come on.  Let's move!
[Everyone moving as one since no one
knows when and where they'll be attacked]
[Quiet streets before the chaos]
[Just who will come to attack Ji Hyo...?]
[At last, entering a full-scale battle]
Look carefully and keep your eyes peeled.
Look to your left, to your left.
Be careful of those areas...
More, more...
You have to go up a little bit more.
[A total chaos]
We have to protect Ji Hyo!
[Just then... There's a man watching
them pass on by...]
[The assassin with the water gun in hand...]
Go up a little bit more!
You have to go up more!
You have to protect Ji Hyo!
Watch her back!
[The assassin that's
approaching closer and closer...]
[His identity is...?]
[MBLAQ's G.O]
[One hour ago]
[Those that came here in secret]
[The ultimate assassins... MBLAQ]
[The secret mission
that they've received is...]
[To rid of Ji Hyo by using the water gun]
[It's war!!]
[The 10th Running Man... MBLAQ]
[G.O. as the first assassin to come up
on Running Man on their mission!]
-Go up a little bit more!  Up more!
-We have to go up a little bit more!
-Ha Ha.  Come up here.
-Protect Ji Hyo!
-Ji Hyo.  You stay back.
-Don't run!
[Close proximity]
Behind us.  He's behind us.
I'm saying he's behind us!
[Ace Ji Hyo is the first
to notice the assassin]
He's over there! There!
I'm the first to see him!!
-Over there. He's behind the car over there!
-Where?
Where?
[G.O. notices something is off]
Guys... They're on their way!
They're on their way!
Okay, I got it.  I got it.
[Clumsy...]
What... What do we need to do?
[First... Let's hide]
Ugh.  I'm so nervous.
Wait... Hang on a second.
Protect Ji Hyo!
[Since seeing the assassin,
first priority is to protect Ji Hyo]
-Over there... Jae Suk...
-Where is he?  Where?
He's at the end down there.
Where?  Where?
Ha Ha keeps staring at me.
[Can't wait forever...]
[Go!]
[The goal is just one person... Ace, Ji Hyo!]
[Assassin G.O. makes up his mind to attack!]
[Ambush attack from Mr. Capable!]
I'm hit?
I've been hit?
Am I hit?
[Yeah... You've been hit quite a bit]
He's out.  I ousted him.
[Mr. Awesome's one shot]
-I was right?  Someone was there, right?
-Who was it?
Who was it?
[Assassin G.O. reveals himself]
It's G.O.
G.O. out!  G.O. out!
[G.O. can't win against
the Running Man's know-how]
What are you doing here?
Were you hiding behind there?
I'm really sorry.
[Know-how that's built up over 2 years]
We have quite the knowledge with water guns.
[Parting as soon as they meet]
Great job, G.O.
I'm sorry, G.O.
[The assassin looking to ambush
got ambushed...]
What do I do?
Being on the same team with you...
Is really satisfactory and exciting.
I came up from behind him...
As soon as it started... I didn't kill anyone!
Guys... I'm dead.  They're going on ahead,
but be careful of an ambush.
Who is this?
He's dead, he's dead...!
[Shocked and flustered MBLAQ]
[After the 1st engagement,
on full vigilance!]
-You have to keep an eye above too.
-They seem to be coming up from behind a lot.
Wait, wait...
And instead of going so fast,
pause for a minute and then go again.
Pause and then go...
Keep your eyes open.
Gary... put your back up against mine.
-Then I have to walk backwards?
-Yes.  Keep an eye out on the back.
We really need to be careful of the 2nd floor.
Roger.  Roger.
What the heck is with Roger?
[Slowly getting close to a showdown]
Hey!  Ji Hyo... I think there's someone
at the pizza place over there.  Wait a second.
Wait, wait.
[Something feels off and suspicious...]
Get behind me.  Hurry up, Ji Hyo.
Put your back up against mine.
[Around the buildings... Could it be?]
Up there.  He's up top.  Up there!
[It seems Jae Suk's seen something...?]
You have to take a look below too.
[MBLAQ's Lee Joon discovered!]
It's Joon! Joon!
It's Lee Joon!
[The agents discovered
the location of 2nd assassin]
He's inside the building!
[Location's been compromised.
Lee Joon escapes the location]
[There's no hesitation about
protecting Agent Ji Hyo]
Here!  Come here.
Come over here.
Get up against the wall.  Up here.
Be careful.  He's above us.
Get right up against it.
This is the best spot.
If you go up, he may jump out behind you.
He's in hiding for now.
[Offense team:  Jae Suk, Ha Ha and Kwang Soo]
Carrying a water gun around the neighborhood...
I'm so sorry.
We're being a lot more serious
than I thought we'd be.
[At last, the offense team enters]
Be careful.
Go up there with your back against the wall.
[Assassin Lee Joon
that escaped up to the roof]
I wonder if they're down there?
This is #2, Lee Joon.
I'm situated here right now,
but go help #3.
If we can come up from behind right now,
we can get all of them.
Lee Joon, I'm scared to go out there.
Chun Doong, you can do it.
Don't be afraid and come out.  Got it?
I'm being serious.  Trust me just this once.
Where did Ha Ha go?
Ha Ha is with Kwang Soo and Jae Suk.
[Something's happening up on the roof?]
What's going on?
Hey Joon...
[A very easy attack]
[A total ambush]
Did we scare you?
[A crumbled 2nd assassin]
Joon, did we scare you a lot?
-You look like we really scared you.
-I told you to come here quickly!
Look at how scared he looks.
-Why are you so scared?
-Why are you so surprised?
[The agents are comforting the assassins]
-When did you get up here?
-Why are you so bad at it?
And why... did you get so scared?
I didn't even think of it...
I was supposed to be the sniper.
[Feeling the loss...]
[Also an immediate parting with Lee Joon]
Joon, good job.
-We'll see you later.
-That's 2 people out.
Hey!  I told you to hit them from behind!
I can't! I'm out!
Hear me out... If they came from behind and
I came down from here, it would be game over!
[We would've won this game!]
[Not much left to the finish goal line]
Keep a good eye out
up high and down below.
Don't go too fast.
Ji Hyo... Watch Ji Hyo.
-Hey be careful of places like this.
-Awkward places like this.
Be careful of open spaces like this.
[Be especially careful of open spaces,
or a crowded space]
The feeling is a little...
That car is a little suspicious.
[The car is heading towards them]
Hey... That car is a little weird.
Get close to the wall, Ji Hyo.  Careful!
[Could it be the 2 remaining assassins?]
-No, it's not.  It's not them.
-It's not?
-I think I see a camera?
-No, it's not.  It's their navigation.
[They're starting to suspect everything]
It's not easy for them
to just pop out of anywhere.
It's not easy.  Not easy.
-They have just one shot...
-That's right.  Just one chance.
Should I oust them?
[Seung Ho is in hiding]
-Is no one here?
-No one's behind us?
-No one's back there?
-Be careful right here. This is weird.
This is too open.  Look down that alley.
Someone's in there right now.
[Seung Ho is hiding behind
the vending machine]
[Seung Jo in perfect form for ambush!]
Someone's behind there right now.
Over there.
-Up there, up there... Up there.
-Someone's up there.
To the back...
[Seung Ho runs after the attack]
[Suk Jin is...?]
-Did you get hit?
-I got hit.
-I'm hit.
-It's okay.
[He's been hit]
[Suk Jin, out!]
He totally got hit.
-I'm out.
-Now the race starts!
[As always, today's true race starts
with the ousting of Suk Jin]
He was hiding in there?
I didn't even see that.
-Suk Jin...
-He did a good job of hiding.
Has our cover been blown?  Has it?
Yeah.  I've been found and I've run out to
where the goal post is.
-Isn't that it?
-I think that's the place.
[This is where the finish goal post is]
[Undoubtedly, there would be assassins
waiting to ambush by the goal line]
[Chun Doong, launching raid!]
[Seung Ho also charging!]
[The assassins' attack noticed!]
[Now... It's a head to head battle!]
[Both concentrating on Ji Hyo as target]
[Just then!]
[Mr. Capable zeroes in on his target]
[Mr. Capable launches a surprise attack
on Chun Doong and shoots]
[Chun Doong - Out!]
[The only assassin left is just Seung Ho]
Corner Seung Ho!
I just need to get the ball in the goal.
[If Ji Hyo scores the goal, mission succeeds]
Is it all set?
[No matter how, Seung Ho has to stop Ji Hyo]
[Gary protecting Ji Hyo to the end]
To the right.  Come to the right.
[Seung Ho, the final assault]
[No!]
[Ace Ji Hyo succeeds the mission!]
[The device that starts automatically
as soon as the mission is completed]
[As before, 2 steel cases
and a reference device...]
[If you're seeing this message, it means
you've found your 10th Running Man as well...]
[Did the Easy Brothers do a good job
following along too?]
[I've heard that all you members
like to receive gold as a prize]
If you succeed the mission,
you can expect something good.
Especially... Song Ji Hyo?
If you've found the 10th Running Man,
now...find the 11th Running Man.
Here is your location.
[Sangamdong "P" Building]
[8th Running Man]
[9th Running Man]
[And 10th Running Man]
[Now 11th Running Man]
[We are off to meet that person]
[The stand for the last battle]
[Sangamdong "P" Building]
[The cases procured so far- 6]
What are we going to do in there?
[Just what is the purpose for them?]
What could it be?  What could it be?
[One person will get off at each floor
that the elevator stops on]
-Who do you want off?
Just any one of you can get off.
I'll get off first.
[Gary gets off on the 3rd floor with a case]
You want to switch your case with me?
Shall we?  This one is heavy.
[One by one,
they each get off at their own floor]
[Kwang Soo and Ji Hyo both
wanting to take the last case]
-It's because I earned it...
-What do you mean, you did?
[Ultimately, Ace Ji Hyo takes one]
Did you just hit me?
Hello?
[All Running Man...
I will reveal an important truth]
I will reveal to you an important truth.
It's that there can only be just one person
that can meet the 11th Running Man.
Just one person, you say?
If you combine the items from
the cases that you acquired,
you'll be able to find out the final location
where the 11th Running Man is at.
[The 6 cases that they acquired thus far!]
I'm going to give you this case.
The 9th Running Man!
[Combine the items in the cases]
[And there can only be 1 person
that can meet the 11th Running Man]
[Therefore, from now on...
Everyone is on their own]
[Become the top agent,
and find the 11th Running Man]
[First, look inside the case in hand]
[Jae Suk picked an empty case]
That Ha Ha...
Ha Ha did ask to switch the case with me
before I got off the elevator...
This is... Seriously!
[And Ha Ha...?]
[Books that Bo Ra was holding?]
What is this about?
[Art History book
that's completely in English]
[Suk Jin picked the running shoes
after being attacked by MBLAQ]
Why are there lifts insides?
[Gary's case is also completely empty]
There's nothing in this case?
How can this case be empty?
[Ace Ji Hyo also has an empty case]
[Mr. Capable has...]
It's herbal drinks...
[Mr. Capable has the herbal drinks
that he received from the 8th Running Man]
I think my items...are something that
Park Ji Sung probably likes or something.
[#8-Pear juice.  #9-Books.
#10-Running Shoes]
The way I see it... This is really important.
-Don't you think?
-Pil-Chok-Cross!
[Kwang Soo attaches himself to
Suk Jin with Pil-Chok-Cross]
I'm not going to betray you.
I'm seriously not going to.
Then let's see.  Let's hide this somewhere.
[Suk Jin showing his item]
[Running shoes...!]
[What is the hint hidden inside the shoe?]
[The lift hidden inside the shoes]
Do you remember last time?
[Huh?  A cell phone?]
It's not even turning on...?
[A cell phone without power]
What could this be?
There's no battery!
[The battery is not even in there.
Just what could this be...?]
You must have the phone...
and the battery must be somewhere else.
We should put something else in here,
and take the phone out.
Something that doesn't even make sense...
[Newspaper?]
Instead of just putting this in here...
Let's erase some of the words.
-Okay...
-Like it's a hint!
[Not bad, Kwang Soo]
Hurry.  We don't have much time.
[Even the R-sticker that was
stuck on the shoes!]
[No matter who sees it, it looks like a hint]
They're probably going to go nuts
trying to analyze this.
[The Easy Brothers using their brain!]
Let's have it taken from us naturally.
[Perfectly hiding the real hint,
the cell phone]
Seriously...
Hiding and being hidden is the best.
[#10 - Cell phone]
Where do you think they are?
[Itching to use up their deception]
-Let's go up.
-We have to make it seem...
[The tiger that's always around the corner]
It's Kwang Soo and Suk Jin!
[Mr. Capable and Ace
chase after Easy Brothers!]
[The 2 that followed the Easy Brothers
according to their plan]
-Open it!  Let's all share it.
-I've already opened mine.
-I have nothing.
-We've already opened ours.
-Get rid of him first.
-Are you going to send me away?
Why don't you leave?
Suk Jin told you to go.
Why am I being sent on
a wild goose chase all day?
[I'm acting... Just go]
[Showing the tennis shoes
to Ace and the tiger]
-You have to show me yours too...
-Lee Kwang Soo...
You're fitting right in there.
-You have to show me yours too.
-Here, look.
-It's medicinal drinks.
-Isn't this pear juice?
Why don't you open it
in case there's something in there?
[Slowly showing the newspaper hint]
Ah, this must be it!
This must be the real hint!
[Jong Kook-We just need to find out
what's been erased!]
I'm sorry, but can you give that back to me?
[The tiger fell for the ruse]
Okay... But just sit down for a minute.
Then let's trade!
-Fine.  Let's trade.
-Can I just take this?
-You took something out, didn't you?
-I didn't take anything out.
-I told you, there was nothing in there.
-I'm going to take this then.
What are you doing?  If you take that,
you have to give us yours.
-Then give me the pear juice.
-What kind of a rule is that?
What are you talking about?
I told you to just take that one.
[Leaving with light footsteps]
They totally fell for it...
[Feeling good!]
Don't be happy.  Don't act happy.
[Easy brothers easily fool
Mr. Capable and Ace]
[On the other hand...]
[Ha Ha gets a hit on a wall
with his difficult book]
I can't even get a grasp of it.
Driving me crazy... Oh you scared me!
-You scared me.
-Sir... I came to get my case.
-But you traded with me earlier.
-But still...
-Let's go up there and make the exchange.
-Fine.
-After checking the items.
-Okay.
You can follow me.
I don't want to feel like I'm being dragged.
These 2 were in the case.
Baroque... Baroque?
Baroque is an art form...?
Ah... Baroque is an art form?
How can you not even know that
Baroque is an art form?
[Ignorant]
Want some Chinese?
[What is he talking about all of a sudden?]
Baroque Chinese?  Korean?  English?
[Korean word 'Ignorant' sounds like a form
of cuisine, like Chinese, Korean, etc]
-I've even shuffled through like this...
-You've done all that?
Yeah.  I did it all, and there's nothing.
[Even though he's done several things,
nothing is found within the book]
This isn't anything too crazy.
[Whenever they get a chance,
they fight over it saying it's theirs.]
If you keep being like this,
I'm going to call Gary.
-Give you what?
-You're going to make this more difficult.
Just give it to me.
It doesn't matter anyways.
We have to find out the information.
[Huh?  Gary?!]
[Ultimately... Gary also joins]
Suk Jin.
[The more that gather around,
the hint is shared and it's disadvantageous]
-Gary... What's inside there?
-Why don't the 3 of us share?
What's the deal with the books?
[Huh?  The paper is peeling off easily?]
[So rip off the book pages carelessly]
[Ha Ha feels as though he may have something]
No, that's probably nothing.
[No matter what others say,
Ha Ha continues on...]
Since we all agreed to join,
let's do it together.
[Huh?  The paper is peeling on the front too?]
I think someone stuck this on there?
[Something is
a little suspicious at this point?]
Something on here.
Something's been stuck here.
I'm sure that wasn't originally there.
That's not something that was
originally on the book!
[Inside is the real book cover!]
[On the back,
the real book cover is also on the inside!]
[By this point, it's a guarantee
that something is in the book!]
Something is in here.
[There's something inside
the real book cover!]
[Something is in there!]
[As soon as Jae Suk takes it,
Ha Ha bites his hand!]
[The 2 kids that won't give it up]
-Ha Ha... Hang on.
-You took this from me.
-You shouldn't have taken it from me.
-Okay.
Okay.
[But first, what is it that they found?]
[Cell phone battery!]
It's a battery.
Hand this to me.  Give this to me.
There's a cell phone around here somewhere.
[Bingo!  Suk Jin has it]
But why are you holding on to this?
You know I can't give it to you.
I can't let it go right now!
Then let's do this.
Give it to me right now.
Calm down Ha Ha... Don't be like this.
Let's do it this way...
Did you fart or something?!
Are you going to keep following me?
I wasn't following you,
but I'm here to get my things back.
This was mine from the beginning.
No!  Shall we do it the legal way?
Even though you had it first,
you undoubtedly exchanged it with me.
-In that case...
-You want to do this the legal way?
-Yes.  Let's do this the lawful way.
-The lawful way?
Do you even know where to go?
I used to work in the law force.
-I'm asking if you know where to go first?
-Yes.  We can go to the complaints department.
Then we can go to the criminal appeals court.
-Criminal appeals court?
-That's right.
You're going to become a criminal.
This is a civil case!
-This is a civil case!
-Criminal case!
Is it because I'm your hyung?
(a play on Korean words)
-Is it because I'm your hyung?
-Yeah... That's right!
If this isn't a civil case,
it goes to criminal court,
and it gets passed up to the supreme court!
Do you want to get shackled up in there?!
Hand it over then!
-Give it to me!
-Why would I give it to you?
[On the other hand, Mr. Capable and Ace
who have pear juice in their possession...]
Since there's no solution...
Let's drink all this up for now.
-Let's drink it.
-Okay.  Hurry up and drink it.
-Everyone take one and drink it.
-Hurry up and drink it.
This is medicinal.  It's really good for you.
This is good for you.
Everyone take one.
Hurry up and drink it.
You've been having a hard time chasing
after me these days, right?
[No matter what the reason may be,
the staff members have their windfall!]
-There's nothing in here...
-Something got to be...
Come here.  Everyone drink one more each.
Ugh, so bitter!
What if there's really nothing in here?
[It can't be just pear juice.
I'm sure there's something in here!
[A little while later]
[That many pear juices annihilated?]
There was nothing?
[But as for the hint...]
There's some more here!  Oh!
-Seriously Jong Kook!  I drank all that!
-I drank all that too!
After all that, when I picked this up,
I saw something on the inside!
[Why did it have to be the last one?]
Why did it have to be the last one?
I put it here for you to drink, Ki Jin!
I left it here for you to drink!
[Something can be seen on the inside]
Hurry up and drink it.
Jong Kook.  Don't suck it all down.
Make sure you don't gulp it down!
-It won't be good to drink it in?
-Then we have to wait until you poop it out.
I really...
I really didn't think I'd go this far.
To make us drink all this?
[Looks like a piece of paper inside...]
Let's see.
[Number... 1307?]
[Just what could this number represent?]
Just think about this.
I don't think it represents a page number.
Jong Kook... Department number!
Just throw this away.
-That battery...
-There was a battery?
Jae Suk has it!
[To be precise, inside Jae Suk's shoe]
There he is.
-Oh my...
-Hello everyone.
[Confiscated the case that Jong Kook
and Ji Hyo have thrown away]
Have a seat.
Hey.  There's nothing in the case
that Jong Kook left.
[The tennis shoes which had the cell phone
inside has returned here]
You know there was a cell phone in here.
Ah... I see...
You're not seeing it?
I told you there was newspaper in here.
As soon as I saw this, I knew it.
This is not the size of a newspaper.
[He should've at least pretended never
to have seen the running shoes]
Do you see how his face is getting red?
Did you see?  Everyone was curious as
I was taking this out,
but there was just one person
that wasn't curious at all.
Therefore,
it means that you have the cell phone.
You hid it somewhere, right?
[He's sharp... At this rate, the cell phone
may even become Jae Suk's]
Grab him!  Hurry up and grab him!
[Ha Ha starts an attack on Jae Suk!]
[Give me my battery!]
Where is it?
[The cold relationship between the
Running Men members]
[Ha Ha knows Jae Suk too well...]
[Running off with the battery!]
[Ha Ha runs off with the battery!]
[Suk Jin with the cell phone chasing after
Ha Ha as if his life depends on it]
Let's get that from Ha Ha!
-Who tickled me?
-I did.
Hey, where did he go?
[This is what he's up to]
-Hey... Let go!
-Over here.  He has it here.
I got it!
[The giraffe runs off with the battery!]
[With this the Easy Brothers get their hands
on both the phone and the battery!]
Jong Kook!  Hurry up and catch these guys!
[They don't even know about the cell phone
and the battery.  Only the number 1307]
That team is in total uproar right now.
What is it that they have
that they're in such uproar?
There must be an uproar with
quite the betrayal going on there?
I see quite the chaos over there.
What are you doing with Ji Hyo?
-What are you doing?
-What do you mean, what are we doing?
[Since he's in this situation,
Jae Suk looking for help from these 2]
Ji Hyo...
Suk Jin has the cell phone, right?
[Huh?  A cell phone?]
-Yes.
-Right?
[Mr. Capable and Ace now know
that there's a cell phone...
[Announcing it to everyone...]
It's a long story...
But I had the battery for the cell phone...
But I had it stolen from me.
[Who knew getting free information
would be so easy?]
-The battery?
-Yeah.  And Suk Jin has the cell phone.
And Ha Ha has the battery right now.
The battery...!
You didn't know that there was a cell phone?
[Now they have a faint idea as to what
1307 means...]
-I thought as much...
-Right?
-I thought as much?
[You naive man...]
Did I just tell you everything?
What are you saying?
[Mr. Capable and Ace that's finally
learned all the puzzle pieces]
Give it to me.
[Give me the battery]
Trust me.
We're seriously going to do this together.
Once we turn this on,
I'm sure something will pop up.
[Kwang Soo's phone]
-You got something.
-It's a text from Jong Kook.
[Kwang Soo.  Once you turn the phone on,
you're going to need a pass code]
It's asking for a pass code.
[Jong Kook has the pass code
for the locked phone]
Seriously...
Jong Kook is calling...
Answer it.
Yes, Jong Kook?
Did you turn the phone on?
Yes.
Why didn't you tell me then?
I just turned it on.
Shall we meet up?
Let me talk to him.
Just a minute.  Suk Jin wants to talk to you.
-Hey Jong Kook.
-Yes, Suk Jin?
Let's forget about everyone...
and just you and I...
No, with Kwang Soo too.
6th floor?
[Agreeing to meet on the 6th floor]
Okay.  Yeah.
He said they shared the phone and the battery.
He wants just me to come right now.
You just stand in front of the door.
I'll go and check first.
[Mr. Capable to handle the Easy Brothers,
and to help Ace Ji Hyo]
[Mr. Capable and Ace on the move!]
[Since the strongest 2 of Running Man
are working together...]
Have you ever seen the animal farm?
The one where the lion and the tiger fight,
and they end up falling in love...
Are you sure you got that right?
-And the baby born was a lion...
-Do you know what you're talking about?
Liger, liger...
[Lion is just a lion...]
A lion and tiger somehow got married...
-Tiger, tiger...
-Liger.
[Easy Brothers and Mr. Capable meet]
Jong Kook.  Come here.
You sit down here.
He's making me nervous.
The winning is between us 3 here.
What's the pass code?
Give it to me.  I won't run.
How can I run with the door shut?
-Hurry up and give it to me.
-Just tell us.
-I'll press it.
-Let's just set it here then.
Okay, fine.
Why are you hiding it?
[Hiding it which is unfitting to his size]
[Enters the pass code, 1307]
Why are you being like this, unlike a man?
Stop it.  Leave it in the middle.
Leave it in the middle.  Take your hand off!
[Finally, the phone is unlocked]
Let's see the phone number!
Let's check the phone number!
[2nd floor auditorium!]
Shut it now so no one else can see it.
[However Ace Song Ji Hyo...
Overheard everything!]
[The first person to arrive at the
2nd floor auditorium wins!]
-It was so we can learn this...
-That's right.
-Are you sending a text to someone?
-No, I'm not.
-It looks like you're sending a text.
[Ji Hyo... 2nd floor auditorium.  Hurry!]
[Kind friend, Mr. Capable that's even
sending her the text!]
[Easy Brothers hurrying up their walk]
-It's Ji Hyo!
-You texted her, didn't you!
-Ji Hyo!
-You texted her, didn't you?!
I'm first!  I'm first!!
[Ace Ji Hyo! First to the auditorium!]
Wait!!
No!
[The top agent to meet the 11th Running Man?]
[Secure Password:
The one that transcends time and place]
The one that transcends time and place!
[By transcending time and place...]
[the 11th Running Man is here...?]
[This place that's beyond
time and place...?]
[Location:??
May 20th.  9:00 A.M.]
[Easy Brothers and Mr. Capable
follow in her footsteps]
How could you have done this?
How could you have taken it?
Hey... I solved it all!
Only the winner, Song Ji Hyo can enter.
-Hey!  Only Ji Hyo can enter.
-Why not us?
We have to enter too!
[Only 1 agent can meet the 11th Running Man]
Jong Kook.  I'm sorry!
-Hey!  Why can't we enter?
-Ji Hyo won?
[Soccer field?
This is where the 11th Running Man is?]
[An image on the big screen up front...]
Manchester!
Park Ji Sung!
Hello, everyone.  Great job.
Once you meet the 11th Running Man,
your mission will be complete.
[Finally!]
[You'll now meet the 11th Running Man]
[11th Running Man's entrance]
Running Man's entering!
[As the ball is kicked out from the screen,
the real ball appears!]
-What's that?
-That's no joke!
[No way...!]
[The balls flying out for real like this...?]
I think Park Ji Sung is coming out!
[11th Running Man... Is it really...?]
[The final Running Man...]
[Park Ji Sung!]
[He's really here!]
[The two hearts!  The eternal captain!
Park Ji Sung in front of their eyes!]
This is awesome!
[The final Running Man's identity is
Park Ji Sung!]
You're not an imposter?
You're the real Park Ji Sung?
Are you really the real Park Ji Sung?
No!  You can't!
[Acting too friendly is prohibited]
Just shake his hand!
[Jae Suk acting as Ji Sung's bodyguard]
What are you doing, Jae Suk?
[A total chaos in a flash]
-Wait...
-Get out of the way!
Park Ji Sung!  Park Ji Sung!  Park Ji Sung!
-Park Ji Sung!
-I have a gift for the winner...
I could have seriously won this!
[Handing out a signed ball and
a winning prize to Ace]
And this is... Gold that you like...
How did you know that Ji Hyo liked gold?
Ji Hyo really loves gold!
-I'll pin this on you.
-You're pinning it yourself?
[A gold star badge]
It's the Monday couple!
If it's you, I can pass her over to you!
I can't believe Park Ji Sung is really here!
-Know that it's an honor!
-This totally is an honor!
-You really... You really came!
-This is the best!
First...
Can you say a greeting to our viewers?
Be quiet.  Park Ji Sung is about to speak.
-Let's all be quiet!
-Quiet!
Yes, hello.
I heard his voice in person!
I thought you were coming on our show...!
Are you really doing a Running Man with us?
-Yes, I am.
-Have you really watched Running Man?
I watch it often.
You must be so busy from soccer season,
how were you able to come?
I've had a lot of requests.
-It must be nice.
-We like your honesty.
Will you really be okay when we tear off
the name tag and everything?
Yes, it's okay.
You could have some uneasiness though...
I'm confident not to get caught.
I have a favor to ask...
Please tear it off of Jong Kook's back.
-It's really the impossible.
-It's all of our wish!
[Mr. Capable vs. Park Ji Sung]
Will he be doing a race with us?
Yes.
We'll be starting with the psychic soccer.
[Psychic soccer?]
-[The one that rips through the air!]
-[The one that dominates the balls!]
[The game of heroes has started]
[The one who controls the space!]
[Park Ji Sung vs. Running Man]
[The match to separate the true hero!]
[The dream game
that no one could have imagines!]
[Next week]
[Psychic soccer with Park Ji Sung]
[And...]
[Who will be become closest to?]
Because I like him!