[Running Man gets married]
This is the type of man I married!
[Marriage is...for crazy people?]
-You should save yourself!
-No!  Don't say things like that!
[Dowry. Wedding photo shoot. Housewives]
[Marriage life race that gives you
happiness and misery]
[Wedding race Start!]
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Running Man Non-stop Survivor]
[The Next Day]
[While dreaming of an enjoyable race
with the young ladies]
[Peacefully asleep Running Man]
[Giraffe...Ha Ha]
[The envelopes in front of their rooms]
[A little while later]
[Wary eyes?]
[Somehow Ha Ha is the first to wake up]
[He found the envelope in front of his door]
Suzy?
[Ha Ha... my brother]
I think Jong Kook gave me this letter.
The one who won the race today will be
able to choose partners for everyone.
-Ruined!  I'm ruined!
-You know who I want, right?
I'll just going to make one request...
seriously.
You can make the decision however you want.
Please... grant me my request.
Ha Ha...you have to be good to me.
I'm the only one who thinks of you.
You have to know that I love you.
Okay...Ha Ha!
Jong Kook... seriously...
Don't keep us apart.
[Praying earnestly for Suzy]
Jong Kook, please... Please, Jong Kook!
Please... Please.
[Could it be?]
What's this?
Me? It's me?
[No way... Ha Ha alone?]
[It's really Suzy!]
[Suzy's name that he wanted so badly!]
[My brother... Thank you]
Jong Kook, Jong Kook...
I'll be good to you...
I'll love you 'til I die...
I will always love you for doing this.
[The tiger that wakes up
upon hearing his name]
[I love you, my brother]
-I'm your brother...
-I love you, bother...
I love you, Jong Kook.
I'll be good.
If you don't bring your partner in front of
the house within 100 seconds from now,
your partner will have to
drink the flower tea.
If you don't bring your partner in front of
the house within 100 seconds from now,
your partner will have to
drink the flower tea.
[The beautiful young ladies will turn
into a scary looking older ladies]
[Same scary scenario as the last time...?]
[that can't be...!]
You think I'm crazy!
She can't drink the tea!
She can't drink the flower tea.
-Within 100 seconds...
-100 seconds?
[News that wakes them up from their sleep]
[Who knows what will happen when they
drink the flower tea?]
[Find the young ladies within 100 seconds]
Where is she?
[Young ladies that are awaiting their partners
at various spots on the hill]
[You can't drink the flower tea]
[Wait...Suzy?]
Are you my partner by any chance?
-You're my partner? Seriously?
-Don't drink it! Don't! Why?!
You can't drink that tea.
-Don't drink it.
-I can't drink it?
-See?  We're partners.
-Oh... I guess you're right.
-Suzy... You want to come with me?
-No.
I'm going to turn you down.
I'm going to turn you down...
[...Huh?]
-I'm just kidding... Let's go.
-You almost made me cry!
-We have to hurry.
-Yes, we have to hurry.
-You're spilling it all...
-Throw it away!
-Suk Jin... What are you wearing?
-Hello.
Suk Jin...
[Suk Jin's too busy looking for his partner]
Suk Jin, who is it?
Hey Ji Hyo... Ji Hyo!
Just looking at your face, it's me!
-Ji Hyo!
-I wonder who it is?
[Suk Jin... Ji Hyo]
Seeing how happy you are, it must be me!
-Hey... Hey... Let's go.
-Seeing how happy you are, it must be me.
Don't drink that tea.
[Who's Mr. Capable's partner?]
There's another one over there.
[F(x)'s Krystal?]
-Sorry... It's not you.
-It's not me?
Wait... Where is she?
Wait... Who is she?
Wait... Hyun Ah?
[Is Hyun Ah the Tiger's partner?]
Hyun Ah!
Hyun Ah.  Hyun Ah!
-Hello...
-Hi.
-I almost drank my tea.
-Really?
[Couple Jong Kook and Hyun Ah are
racing to the front of the house]
Hi Krystal... You look so pretty!
It feels like he is waiting with me.
[Where are the partners
for the remaining ladies?]
[Huh?]
[2nd handsomest man, Gary is up]
Gary!  It's written on here... Gary!
Is it a letter from her?
Gary.
[No. It's from the Tiger couple manager]
Gary... I'm doing some big things today.
[Still thinks the letter is from her]
I'm nervous... Can you please take this?
I wonder what's written on here...
Something is on here.
[Gary.  Krystal]
Oh!  Krystal!
Krystal...
-Did Jong Kook write this?
-Yes.
Why did he put a heart here then?
It confused me.
I thought a girl wrote this...
(The Tiger's hand writing]
If you don't bring them to the front of
the house within 100 seconds,
your partner will have to
drink the flower tea.
-Flower tea?
-Yes.  You have to start now.
-The clock is ticking right now.
-Please give me a little time.
[Where is he going when he's told
he doesn't have much time?]
It's going on 10 seconds now.
Which hat should I wear?
When I'm going to see Krystal...
[Gary's bury prettying himself]
20 seconds have now passed.
20 seconds...
[Not a huge change...]
[Giraffe who can barely open his eyes.]
[Kwang Soo and Gyu Ri]
[Isn't your brother the best?]
You need to put your shoes on.
-Where is Gyu Ri?
-Hurry up and put your shoes on.
[Taking all day to put his shoes on]
No!  She can't drink the tea!
When did you get here?
When did you get here? Seriously?
Krystal!
Krys...!
Soo Jung! (Krystal's korean name)
[Krystal... Where are you?]
Wife!!  Oh!  There she is!
Wife!
Krystal.
-What are you doing up there?
-Excuse me?
What are you doing up there?
I have to bring you down there quickly.
We have to get down there.
Throw this crap away!
...Throw this crap away!
Will you excuse me right now?
Of all times, we met at a time when
I look my worst.
-Did you sleep too much?
-Yeah... And had ramen before I went to bed.
[Gary and Krystal couple]
Let's go.  Should we go holding hands?
Krystal!  So early in the morning...
-To walk with a beautiful bride...
-Shouldn't we walk faster?
Things can't get better than this.
-First thing in the morning...
-Hey!  Hey!
[Jae Suk feeling the urgency]
Seung Yeon!
Where is she?  Up there?
Hello.
[Finally...he sees Seung Yeon]
-Excuse me?  It's me?  Really?
-Yeah.  Let's go.
-Come this way.
-Should I take this?
-You've got 15 seconds.
-What did you say?
-There's only 15 seconds left?
-15 seconds...
[More urgent than ever]
Gyu Ri!  Gyu Ri!!
Gyu Ri!
-Gyu Ri!  Where is she?
-Here, Kwang Soo.
How do I get up there?
What the heck?!
Don't drink it!
Don't drink the flower tea!
What do I do?
Come down here!
[I said, hurry up and come down...]
[Finally Giraffe found Gyu Ri]
Come on...
You can get down now.
[First, throw away the flower tea]
Is it you? You?
-What took you so long?
-I... I just got up.
[Giraffe runs well
even though he just woke up]
They're here... They're here.
Running Man stresses me out!
What's this first thing in the morning?
Gyu Ri was alone in the woods.
I thought I was going to freeze to death.
Gyu Ri says she was about to
freeze to death.
I thought I was going to pass out.
I'll tell you your today's mission.
-Yes, tell us.
-Today's mission...
A wedding race.
[Today's mission-Wedding Race]
Through a race...
You have to get ready for a wedding.
You have to get to your final destination
to complete your wedding.
I've been waiting to get married...
[Have to be frugal with the wedding.
But the winning couple gets a gold tiara]
Since compared to the ladies,
the men's attire isn't very good,
The men have to change into attire
that's appropriate for a wedding race.
-There's not much that's going to change.
-How do we have to dress?
You're right from the way I look at it.
Given how Kwang Soo looks.
What are you saying so early in the morning?
It's making me upset.
I'm sorry.
[Giraffe is full of advice this morning]
He's ticked off...
Kwang Soo isn't feeling well,
so he's been taking medication.
I'm sorry.
Men can change their clothes,
and we'll get started.
[After changing their attire,
the wedding race will start]
[Like beautiful Bride Groom today]
We're off!
Please put your seat belt on.
What's the first mission?
Go to an appliance store
and find the Running Man's mark.
-I want some ice cream.
-What? Ice cream?
You want some?
-I want...a nice cold...
-Shaved Ice!
-No, that's not it.
-That's what I meant... It's not what you want.
[Ha Ha forcefully trying to match their taste]
-1, 2, 3!
-Ice!
-What is that?
-I lost again.
[Towards a beautiful scenic drive
that fits their setting]
-Just look at these trees.
-It's so pretty!
[Instead of misery, today's full of laughter]
It's so very nice today.
[Enjoy it.]
[It won't always be like today]
-There it is.
-We're here?
-That's the mark?
-Are we the first ones here?
I think we're the first ones here.
-Let's get out.
-Let's hurry, hurry.
[Wedding race- 1st stop]
[Appliance store]
[What could be the wedding mission here?]
Hello.
We're the quickest.
[Jaw dropping appliances]
-This is so hard.
-We're the first ones here.
We're the first ones here.
[Gary and Krystal]
[Suk Jin and Ji Hyo also arrives]
What took you guys so long?
Come on in.
-What are we doing here?
-I'll explain it to you.
This is a quiz for your wedding dowry.
[We like dowry quizzes]
I'm going to choose the expensive ones first.
[All the good appliances will be mine]
Shall we go for the TV?
-When I say start, you guys run...
-Do we just need to press the button?
You run here...
And the couple that arrives first...
-... Can pick up your prize.
-Hey. You have to step back here.
-Do we just need to guess?
-If you get it, you can pick your prize.
Now...
Go!
[Overly eager newlyweds]
Be careful!
[Bride Gyu Ri that got injured while trying
to get her dowry prepared]
-What did you do?!  Gyu Ri!
-Gyu Ri... Are you okay?
Why are you hitting her pressure point
with your foot?
-That's not what I meant...
-You pushed me out like this!
[Gary and Krystal go up
to the front during the confusion]
Gary is first.
They're all already here.
[Jong Kook and Hyun Ah. Ha Ha and Suzy]
When did they all get here already?
-The order...
-What took you so long?
-We're the last ones here.
-Go to the back.
[The prize that Gary and Krystal choose
is a smart TV]
If by any chance this team gets it wrong,
and I say start again,
you just need to run up and
push the button.
If I say start again, just come up here.
[Are they listening?]
Stand in front of these flowers...
Right here.
I feel like it's going to happen again.
Since the females guests are here,
I can't do anything about it.
All they do is just talk non-stop...
-I will tell you the rules one last time.
-This is the 6th time telling us the rules.
-I just can't get used to it...
-We already know all the rules.
-Just give out the question.
-Okay.  I will ask the question.
This is a question for the smart TV.
What do you call a blanket and a pillow
that a married couple shares together?
-I'll give you 3 seconds.  1, 2...
-Wait...
What do you call a blanket and a pillow
that a married couple shares together?
-Can you give us a hint?
-There are no hints.  1...
-Hone-Bool...
-Wrong.
[Passionate run towards the dowry table]
[Possibly getting admitted to the hospital
on the first day of marriage]
Are you okay?
-Do it carefully and be careful!
-You're not going to do it carefully?!
What have I done wrong?  What?
[This is awesome]
He is not of the right mind right now.
[Such a loud scene.]
-Seriously...
-My wife almost got hurt!
My wife almost got hurt!
[Should the insurance be called?]
I... I stopped.
But I got pushed from behind.
What are you doing right now?
You even abandoned Hyun Ah back there.
-Where's Hyun Ah right now?
-I stopped.
If you keep this up,
there will be no more female guests.
[Automatically quiets down]
Let's step back.
-We'll concede.
-The camera will confirm, that I stepped...
-Just go back... We'll do it again.
-What do you mean, do it again?
-What do you mean?
-Just come this way... Just come.
Say something!
[Calming down the fiery atmosphere
and starting over]
Go!
[Ha Ha and Suzy the first to arrive]
Yay!!
Suzy knows it without a doubt!
-I'll give you 3 seconds for the answer.
-Suzy knows the answer!
-1... 2...
-Boo Dup Boo Gae.
Boo Dup Boo Gae.
[Boo Dup Boo Gae?]
-What did she say?
-What was it?
-Boo Dup Boo Gae.
-Ah...
Since the couple uses the blanket,
and lays their head on the pillow...?
Do you know what Ul-dong-ju is?
It's juice that has ice floating in it.
Meaning she wants an icy juice.
[19 year old bride Suzy's fascinating words]
-Someone using the blanket...
-If you take a step back, I'll give you a hint.
It's 4 letters.
[A 4 letter word is the right answer]
-4 letters?  What could it be?  I got it!
-What could it be?
I got it! I know the answer!
[Jae Suk and Seung Yeon knows the answer?]
-Shall I give you another word?  Go!
-No!  I know it!  Let us go!
[However Gary and Krystal gets the buzzer]
I know it.  I remembered it.
You really know what it is?
-Now... What is the answer?
-Uh...
Won-Ahng...
[If they get this question right,
they get a free smart TV!]
[And the right answer is?]
Won-Ahng-Shim-Shim... Won-Ahng-Shim-Shim.
[Jae Suk and Seung Yeon
who have their motor running]
-Did you all hear what he just said?
-No.  What did he say?
It was very close.
-There's no reason for another hint.
-I didn't think it through carefully.
You can't answer it.
[Gary and Krystal who are
investigating on the side]
Song Ji Hyo, you've been warned.
You can't look it up on the internet!
It's not just me!  Gary's doing it too!
-What are you doing over there?
-I'm looking up Krystal.
Please turn in all your cell phones.
[Thus their cell phones were taken]
[Not enough time to look up
the right answer on the internet]
-You really did?
-Won-Ahng-So-Ri!
[Jae Suk and Seung Yeon who's at last
pressed the buzzer]
-I finally thought of it.
-Please step back.
-You can't do it...!
-Won-Ahng-Geum-Chim!  Won-Ahng-Geum-Chim!
[Correct answer]
-Smart TV!  We got smart TV!
-TV!!  Yay!!
Won-Ahng-Geum-Chim!  That's right!
[Jae Suk and Seung Yeon win the smart TV]
-Won-Ahng-Geum-Chim?
-Seung Yeon... You did well.
You can take it.  Good job.
Now... If you go later,
there's a chance prize.
If you put that up as a bet...
You can bet it for your opponent's prize.
[If you put up the chance prize,
you can bet it up against opponents prize]
You can take your opponents items.
-That's better than anything else.
-Chance is the best one.
-Why?
-You did a good job getting the right answer.
But if I guess 2 questions correctly,
we're done here?
If you get 2 answers correctly,
you can leave here?
Why didn't you tell us that sooner?
-Hyun Ah... You're not joking around.
-Why didn't you tell us that sooner?
The 2 of you have
the exact same personalities.
Be quiet!
-Seriously...
-You guys are all being too loud.
If you put up the chance prize and take
the TV that Yoo Jae Suk won...
-Why do you keep saying that?
-Why are you upsetting us like that?
-You can't be doing that.
-I'm going to take the chance.
[All the couple are
fueled by the chance prize]
-Seriously...
-You just hit me in the face.
-This really isn't working...
-He got it again.
-I'll take the chance...
-Jong Kook... It's still early on...
If you get the air conditioner or something
to Hyun Ah over the chance gift...
-Should we get the coffee machine then?
-Yes.  A coffee maker for trouble makers.
We'll go for the coffee machine then.
[Jong Kook and Hyun Ah chooses coffee machine]
I bet that's going to be an easy problem.
-I'll read out the coffee maker question.
-Okay.
Within 3 seconds,
say 'I love you' in 5 languages.
-Wo ai ni... I love you.
-1, 2, 3...
[Manner-less Jae Suk]
Seung Yeon... Seung Yeon...
[Just why is that dowry so important...?]
What do you mean, I'm done?
[What's so important about the dowry
to get this rowdy over it?]
Go!
We got it!
[This time Gyu Ri gets it]
You've got 3 seconds for the coffee maker
questions.  Rest of you please step back.  Go.
Wo ai ni... I love you!
Wo ai ni... Um... I love you!
[I see?]
[Jae Suk who's shoved Gyu Ri's body aside
to get to the dowry gifts]
Why did you throw this down?
They're really mad right now!
[Kwang Soo and Gyu Ri already having a
lover's quarrel over the dowry]
-It's me.
-This time, it's Ha Ha.
-I don't think they're going to get it anyways.
-Okay, okay.
[With one word from the bride,
he gives up immediately]
3 seconds.  You can't stop.  Start.
Je t'aime (French), Iri dee beri (German),
Wo ai ni (Chinese), Aishiteru (Japanese)
I love you (English)
Correct Answer.
They didn't say the German one right!
-No we didn't!
-What did you say then?
-I said it the right way.
-Then say it again.
-Say it clearly.
-You have to re-say it clearly.
If he says the German one right,
then you all have to acknowledge that.
-Hurry up and say it.
-If he's wrong, then we'll cancel it.
I was born in Germany...
[So try saying it]
[Ich Liebe Dich]
See? Iri dee beri.
Iri dee beri...
[He may have been born in Germany...]
Ha Ha was born in Germany.
Go!
It's me, it's me.
[Fast Groom Ha Ha who got the buzzer again]
How many times has it been for you now?
You have 3 seconds.
It's not Iri dee beri?
If you don't know, get away!
Go!
Je t'aime (French), Rak Rak (Thai).
I love you (English), Aishiteru (Japanese),
Wo ai ni (Chinese).
[Correct answer]
It's really not Iri dee beri??
Rak Rak is I love you in Thai.
[Ha Ha still can't say it right in the
language which country he was born in]
Iri dee beri....
-It's okay. We can get the buzzer next time.
-It's okay. We can do it.
Ha Ha and Suzy have won
the coffee maker.
Let's all Iri dee beri together.
Whoever gets there this time make sure
to use the chance box!
Go!
[The Tiger couple]
I'm scared to go any closer...
-We'll take the chance.  We'll do it.
-Chance?
I can't let it go, so I'll use the chance.
-Who are you going to use your chance against?
-You're going after our smart TV?
Go after Jae Suk's.
-We should just go for it.
-Let's go!
-Then... We'll go after the TV.
-Of course!
Smart TV... Chance!
[Jong Kook and Hyun Ah smart TV chance]
[Going after Jae Suk and Seung Yeon's
smart TV]
I'll give you the 2nd question that was
attached to the smart TV.
Jae Suk's real brother Ha Ha has married
Suzy and had a son named Jong Kook...
How are Jae Suk and Jong Kook related?
I got it.
Second cousins!
[Wrong]
They did what?
Who had whom?
Please go back.  If you are the first to
arrive again, I'll say the question again.
So in one word,
you're saying real brother's son?
Go!
-The correct answer please, Gary.
-Uncle.
[Correct answer]
-That was too easy!
-No, no...
[Gary and Krystal wins the smart TV]
Why did you use the chance?
Now... As of this point on,
everyone get in a line.
[Everyone in a line to answer the question]
Go!
[Everyone ran slowly...
but Suk Jin pressed the buzzer first]
First, pick your prize.
-We will...
-The air conditioner.
Not the medicine brewer?
[Suk Jin wants a medicine brewer?]
We really can't relate!
We need to make our
own medicine when we're sick.
[Chooses the medicine brewer]
I'll give you the question
for the medicine brewer.
Then we're all getting the
question for the medicine brewer?
-It's good to make your own medicine.
-Why would you pick a medicine brewer?
-It's good for you.
-Ji Hyo, you should've stopped him!
He says his health isn't very good...
This is a consonant question.
You've got 3 seconds.
Go.
-1, 2, 3, go.
-What's that?
What is that?
Kang-Ha-Ha-Ja-Gong.
It's a sentence.
What is it that you're all doing today?
What are we doing?
I know, I know.  I'm saying, I know.
-Is it...?
-I know.
1, 2, 3!
Before... Marriage?
Before marriage?
You know it?
[A few couples seem to know?]
-We know it!
-Please go back to your place.
Seung Yeon!  Come out here!
Go back.  Go back.
You yourself asked to stand in a line.
-But... Seung Yeon says she knows.
-I understand.  Please go back to your place.
-Let's move, quickly.
-You've got 3 seconds.
Marriage... Let us marry.
[Let us marry?]
Return to the back.
What's with 'Let us marry?'
You've got 3 seconds... 1...
-1, 2, 3.
-Are you going to say it?
Ugh, that hurt my ears.
-He said, let us marry.
-1, 2, 3.
Wedding march!
-Wedding march!
-Suk Jin, you're awesome!
-We got it?
-We got it?!
-It's a medicine brewer!
[Suk Jin and Ji Hyo win a Medicine Brewer]
I really wanted to get that medicine brewer.
[Currently 3 couples each took 1]
Go.
It's us, right?
Air conditioner.
-We'll take the air conditioner.
-Air conditioner.
In a traditional wedding...
What is the animal that represents
the couple growing old together?
-That's too easy!
-Mandarin.
-You've got 3 seconds...
-Yes.
The answer is... Mallards.
-Is he right?
-Yes, I think he is.
I wonder if it's Gary then?
[The animal that represents a couple getting
old together in a traditional wedding]
-should I have said ducks?
-You've got 3 seconds.
-Parrots.
-What the heck?  No, that's not it.
[The middle-aged groom that just
throws out random answers]
What are you doing after winning the
Medicine brewer?
-I think you need to make him some medicine.
-What was that answer?
[The correct answer is this!]
Is it a chicken?
-Nutcracker.
-Stop!
Deer.
Ducks!  Ducks!
[Is duck the right answer...?]
Duck!
-Is it just a regular duck?
-It's not?
Isn't that the right answer?
With the long bill like that?
-Just get back.
-Donald Duck!
Beijing Duck... Beijing Duck.
-Beijing Duck?  What the heck?
-DJ Duck!
DJ D.O.C?
[They're saying
every duck they can think of...]
-Here is your hint.
-Yes.
Hint is... Bird.
-1, 2, 3.
-Crane?
Crane?
[Crane is also the wrong answer]
Of course, it's not it!
-Of course, it's not the crane!
-...Does that animal live long?
-They look like they know the answer.
-Your correct answer?
Turtles?
We told you, it's a bird.
-Turtles?
-I told you, it's a bird.
We really didn't hear you
saying it was a bird.
We really didn't hear the bird part.
We really didn't hear it!
[Jae Suk and Seung Yeon gets another chance]
I know the answer!  Let me answer it now!
-Come on... I know!
-I really couldn't hear.
I know!
1, 2, 3. Wild goose!
Wild goose!
[Correct answer]
We did it!!
-Air conditioner! Wild goose!
-It wasn't ducks, but wild goose!
[Jae Suk and Seung Yeon wins
the air conditioner]
It wasn't ducks... But Wild goose!
We got it!
See?  What would you have done
if I hadn't used the chance?
With the exception of Kim Jong Kook couple,
everyone else can use their chance.
Go!
-Chance! You say it.
-Chance for the medicine brewer.
Chance for the medicine brewer.
[What? Going for the medicine brewer?]
Seriously?
Yes. The medicine brewer.
You're using your chance
on the medicine brewer?
-Yes.
-You need to use it on something else!
-Are you serious, Suzy?
-Yes.
Hey Suzy... Why are you going after
the medicine brewer?
[I guess she can give it to her parents]
I'm sorry.
Jae Suk says he's not in good health!
We're not very good either...
Suk Jin is going to be 60 soon.
Here's your question.
The day that celebrates the prime of life
of young people coming into their 20's...
Has been set for next year's
3rd Monday in May.
What are the 3 gifts that are used
to commemorate this day?
You've got 3 seconds.
She is your main lady.
Rose, perfume... Kiss!
Kiss!
[Correct answer]
-Suzy's got the it.
-Medicine brewer is what I most wanted!
-It's mine now!
-Why are you taking my medicine brewer?
You two can start off first.
Nice. We got first place out of there.
Medicine brewer was nice.
What is that? Is it a mission?
Go to Banpo Department Store,
and find Running Man's landmark.
Go.
-Let's go for the fan.
-An iron?
-Hair dryer.
-Go for the fan.
Just go for the fan!
-We'll go for the fan.
-Here's the question for the fan.
For this question, only the grooms
can guess the right answer.
I can't wait to see what the grooms up front
have got to say.
[Poor grooms standing up front]
I'm ready.
If you add up the numbers of the girl groups
that are in attendance today?
-You've got 3 seconds.
-How can I do it within 3 seconds?
38.
14.
You said that there are 14!
-Hurry up and say it.  1, 2, 3.
-15 girls.
-Next up, please. 1, 2...
-19 girls.
[KARA+4 Minute+F(x)+Miss A=19 Girls]
19 girls!  19 girls!
How is it 19?  It's not 14?
-19. 3 teams of 5 girls, and 1 team of 4.
-That's right!
Ah... There's Suzy.
[They forget about Suzy, who's already left]
Miss A!  19 girls!
-Great, great... See you later!
-See you later.
Can we just go?
You have to wait until the
3rd team comes out.
But the first couple has already left.
2nd and 3rd place team have to
leave together.
-How can there be such a thing?
-We got screwed.
Then we should've gone for something else
rather than the fan!
I feel really anxious...
Who knows when they'll get here?
[Ha Ha and Suzy with plenty of margin]
Cheers.
Now... Pick your prize and as soon as you
guess the right answer, you can leave.
Go!
[Buzzer pressing Tiger]
Iron...
[Chooses the iron]
What is the headdress that the bride
wears in a traditional wedding?
-You've got 3 seconds.  1, 2, 3.
-What is it?
Do we really have to get this?
Do we have to take the iron?
Can't we take something else?
Then get it wrong and pick something else.
There's no need for that.
What is the correct answer?
Iron... I mean, no...
[The bride wears an iron
during the traditional wedding?]
[Stuttering Suk Jin]
I was muttering... Muttering!
-And the correct answer is?  1, 2, 3...
-Jokduri!
Kwang Soo and Gyu Ri...
Congratulations.
-There's the landmark.  Over there.
-Where?  Where?
Running Man landmark is over there.
No one else is here yet.
We're the first ones here.
[Seoul, Kangnam]
Let's go.  Right behind first place.
[Wedding Race second mission]
Look at all these people!
-1st place winners.
It's a mission!
[Wedding Photos]
[Grab a bouquet and shoot wedding photos]
[But... The couple has to be in the hearts...]
[The goal is found behind them]
What do we do?  I don't know.
[Jae Suk and Seung Yeon]
[Gary and Krystal arrives]
-When we say 1, 2, 3, we'll take a photo...
-Yes?
-The couple has to hold the bouquet...
-Hold it together?
Yes.  Hold it together and your face
has to appear together in the heart.
[If their faces do not show up together in
the heart, it's a failed mission]
-Not jump on 3...
-You have to make sure to hold it together.
Hold the bouquet together.
Hey you taller young ones...
can you not hide me?
The thing is... I'm short.
I'm sorry.
I'll take the picture now.
-The face is important, okay?
-1, 2, 3!
[Suk Jin and Ji Hyo that got in the way]
Song Ji Hyo!  Get out!
What the heck, Song Ji Hyo?
-The couple without the bouquet.
-If you don't have a bouquet, you can't!
-What the heck is this?  Song Ji Hyo!
-This is a big problem!
Song Ji Hyo, you keep showing up here.
[All pictures of Ji Hyo]
If it wasn't for Song Ji Hyo,
we'd be done!
[Me! Me!  Just Ji Hyo!]
-I see we have to be in the heart?
-Did you get the medicine brewer?
I had the medicine brewer stolen from me.
Ha Ha's wife took it.
I'll take the picture again.
1... 2... 3!
[Jumping with all their might in the back]
[Jumping high while grabbing his shoulder]
[Suk Jin and Ji Hyo all the way
in the front this time too]
Hey!  Song Ji Hyo!
-Let's take a look.
-We're right there!
[Even though it's clear,
they're outside the heart]
You have to be in the heart.
[Jae Suk succeeds on his own]
It's here, Jong Kook.
[Jong Kook and Hyun Ah. Kwang Soo and Gyu Ri]
What is this?
Two of you, grab a bouquet.
Then... Let's take turns doing this.
1, 2, 3.
[Everyone to cease fire and take turns?]
-1, 2, 3.
-Stand behind us.
-You have to get in the heart.
-Hey the giraffe just shows up in there.
What the heck is that?
[The giraffe that doesn't need to jump]
His height is like cheating.
The white tape line you see is where
you show up easiest on camera.
Why are you telling us that now?
We're all standing in a line!
They're all crowding up here again!
-Move away from me some.
-Lean like this.
I said, move.
[Everyone's pushing their way to the spot
where they can be seen easily]
-Move you head a little.
-You have no manners.
-Jong Kook! Why are you being like this?
-Shield him with your hand.
Let's do this!
[Photo session is starting]
1, 2, 3!
[The giraffe jumping earnestly on his own]
[Stop...]
[I'm sure there's at least one]
There's got to be at least one.
[Checking the photos]
[Giraffe that sticks out on his own]
[Everyone fails at getting in the heart]
[I get it now]
Hurry up Suk Jin.  I got us a spot.
Seung Yeon, this picture looks good.
[Everyone fighting for their spot in front]
Why do you keep coming out front?
[The wedding photos may take all night]
Why are you getting angry?
Step back a little bit.
-Look here... Seriously!
-Why?
[Let's do rock-paper-scissors]
There's are a lot of people gathered here,
let's show them how nice we can be.
-Let's everyone take 5 steps back.
-1, 2, 3, 4, 5.
[Everyone marching in their place?]
There's are so many people watching!
Come on.  Let's be orderly.
[Everyone marching in their own place]
1, 2, 3, 4, 5.
-Let's give it a rest and go.
-Let's hurry up and do this.
1, 2, 3.
[Photo shoot starts]
[Suk Jin and Ji Hyo up front again]
[Giraffe lift]
[Giraffe husband using his height]
[Vertigo from the height?]
She hit her chin on my head!
Are you okay?
[the new bride who hits her chin on the
new groom's head on their first day ]
This is crazy... Gyu Ri hit her chin on her
groom's head and almost lost her chin!
I'm so dizzy...!
[Occupying the front row]
[The danger of the giraffe lift!]
-Let's not cross this line.
-Yes.  Let's make this our line.
Let's all stick by this line here.
-Let's all abide this line then.
-Let's keep this line!
-Let's all keep to the line.
-The line...
Keep the line.
-The duck says...!
-Quack quack.
I'll be taking the pictures again.
[Whenever the picture starts,
everyone races to the front]
[Once again, the giraffe lift]
[Ha Ha and Suzy,
getting the timing in the back]
There's one couple that succeeded.
[Just who is the successful couple
from the distressful photo shoot?]
Gary and Krystal succeeded.
[Succeeds with a smile on their face]
Sorry for making this look
too easy for you guys.
[Look for the Running Man landmark
at the Suh River Bridge]
[Gary and Krystal off to the next location]
[Bride and Groom races off]
-Fighting.
-Fighting!
-Say 'Ho!'
-Ho...!
Thank you!
-Ready, set, go.
-Jong Kook, fighting!
[Giraffe lift is off to ride the wave]
Hurry, hurry, hurry!
-Take the picture!
-I'm taking the picture!
[Emergency return of the giraffe lift]
[For a cut of one good picture...
Bride Grooms working hard]
[Angry Tiger Groom]
[Jae Suk lift]
If it doesn't work this time, get on my back.
My bouquet...
[What has the bouquet done wrong?]
-There's another couple that succeeded.
-What?
-There is?  Who?
-I'll tell you who it is.
Lee Kwang Soo and Gyu Ri succeeded.
[Is it thanks to the giraffe lift?]
-Let's all stand in a zig zag formation.
-Let's do that.
-Everyone takes turns jumping.
-Okay.  We'll jump first.
Jump on 3, okay?  Let's practice it once.
Wait a second...
[Jae Suk giving his bride a piggy back ride]
Try it... here we go.
1, 2, 3!
That's not something just anyone can do!
Should I just get back down?
[The nervous bride]
Let's give it a try Seung Yeon...
[Under the coaching of the Tiger]
Jump on 3, and we'll be right behind you.
-Let's do this.
-Get ready.
1, 2, 3!
Jump... Jump... Jump!
[The groom who's about to pass out
from a photo session]
-1, 2, 3!
-Stop.
-Someone must have done it.
-1 couple has succeeded.
-Who is it?  Please...!
-I'll tell you who it is.
Ha Ha and Suzy succeeded.
Didn't I tell you?
[My first love... Are you watching?]
Since that's the spot that shows up best...
Jump and move over to the side.
Shall we do it that way?
[Calmly taking turns jumping?]
-1, 2...3!
-Get out!
-That feels nice!
-2 jumps for us.
Hurry up, hurry!
Stop!
How can you do this?!
-We didn't get to jump.
-We've been counting the time.
-You have to do it quicker.
-What do we do?
-You want to play a game on the way?
-Yes.  Let's play a game.
The day that a monkey falls from the tree!
[The strange game
being heard of for the first time]
Everyone grab their ears like this.
Everyone look at their camera.
[Everyone's looking at their camera
while holding onto their ears]
And make your lips look like
a monkey like this.
The one that looks most like a money
is the winner.
[Game Rule: The one that looks most
like a money is the winner]
The day that a monkey falls from the tree!
What kind of a game is this?!
Suzy gets the first place!
-Gyu Ri, 2nd place!
-Thank you.
-Kwang Soo last place!
-The loser, get out!
[A fun game where the
loser may have to get out...]
Get out!
-I'm sure it worked this time...
-I'm stressed!
-It's us... This time, it's us.
-Please!
Ji Hyo and Suk Jin couple succeeded.
[We're looking for the medicine brewer]
[The time passes on like that...]
-Both the couples succeeded.
-Really?
[Wedding photo shoot is over]
[Han River full of sunshine
on a crisp May Day]
Found it! Running Man!
Go!  Go!
[The Running Man flag on the bridge]
this is my first time on the bridge!
Hurry up and move it.
This is no time to enjoy the scenery!
It's so cool.
[Bride Krystal with spring fever]
Let's walk on then.
[What's the wedding mission that
the couples have to pass here?]
-Why did you set it up here?
-Stand over here please.
What's this?
[Bridge wedding march]
[You have to run to the first flag with the
bride on your back within 10 seconds to pass]
-10 seconds?!
-It's not too bad.
-Do you see the pink flag over there?
-Yes.
You have to put her
on your back up to there...
and if you get there within 10 seconds,
you'll be done right away.
If you fail, you see that other flag?
[However, if you fail,
there's another mission]
[If not succeed in the first round...]
[In the worst case scenario,
may even have to go 1.3km!]
-Let's end this in one shot.
-You think you'll be okay?
It's fine. Don't worry about me.
I have food inside...
[Krystal using food as her excuse...]
Food is still in there?!
I'm digesting it right now!  Seriously...!
[If wedding march is succeeded with the bride
on the back, then it's off to the next spot!]
It's okay!  It's okay!  It's me!
-Are you okay? I'm really heavy.
-It's okay!
Come on...
I have a duckling butt, so be understanding.
-I have a duckling butt...
-1, 2, 3.
Ready!
[With the goal of succeeding in one shot
no matter what]
[The sprinting wedding march]
[Arrive within 10 seconds...
Otherwise, who knows how far...?]
[The long and arduous wedding march run!!]
[Finish line at last!]
[First round-Fail!]
You've failed the first round.
What did you say? 14 seconds?
I ran while counting...!
Why did you eat so much?!
Are you pissed at me?
[Even if I eat a lot,
just how much do you think I can eat?]
Don't hold a grudge.  I was just joking.
-Hurry!
-What are you doing?
[Mission from the 2nd round?]
[If you can stand up and down 7 times while
holding the bride in 10 seconds, you pass]
Wait...If you can stand up and down 7 times
while holding the bride in 10 seconds...
Yes. I understand.
Let's try it!  Whatever!
You can't tighten up your limbs.
Who is that?  Someone's here.
We have to finish before Jong Kook gets here.
He'll get it done no matter what it is.
Hurry.
-You can leave me behind.
-What are you talking about?
I can't abandon you.
[Already melodramatic newlyweds]
-You can leave me...
-No!  Don't say things like that!
-You can't do this, you fool!
-At least you need to survive!
Hurry!  Hurry!
-Just sit down.
-Start!
[That kind of a destruction
while holding a girl...]
[Just how heavy can I be...?]
Let's just hurry up and go.
It's not because you're heavy,
but I lost my balance.
[2nd round also fail...]
[At this rate,
he may really have to cross the bridge]
I'm sorry, but I've
given Suzy a piggy back ride before.
-I'll give you a piggy back ride.
-I thought I was pretty weak...
I was just weak.
You really are a beautiful pair.
Hi!!!
[Mr. Ha Ha and Mr. Giraffe]
[Kwang Soo and Gyu Ri taking on the 10 second
wedding march challenge]
[With the long giraffe legs,
off to a fast start]
[Quickly diminishing speed]
[Will it be possible within 10 seconds?]
We're here!  We're here!
[The time?]
13 seconds.
[Kwang Soo and Gyu Ri fail the 1st round]
What do we do?  This is crazy!
[Ha Ha and Suzy taking on the 10 second
wedding march challenge]
-Your position doesn't look good.
-Wait... What have you been eating?
[That same feeling as from a year ago...]
[A slow heavy start]
Suzy!  What did you eat?!
[The speed that can't be found]
Hey!  What did you eat?!
[Even from a glance, no chance of success]
I can't do it anymore after this.
I think my legs are going to give out
after that one run.
[17.3 seconds... A total failure]
Don't even drink a sip of water now.
[Gary and Krystal taking on 3rd round.
Wedding march within 11 seconds]
Wait... I said, wait!
[Krystal... A mistake or revenge?]
Be gentle!  Your mike scraped me!
I'm anxious!
[If complete the wedding march in 11 seconds,
then 3rd round is a success]
[Hm... Has he gotten any faster?]
[If he's lucky, he may even succeed...?]
-We did it!!
-You passed.
[Gary and Krystal succeeds their 3rd mission!]
If you go back to the start line,
you'll find out your next location.
-Let's go.
-Krystal... I lost my balance earlier.
-What's this? You succeeded? Already?
-Succeeding isn't easy.
-It's not easy!
-You're already done here?
What the heck?
When did he get it done?
[Time time as well, the first couple
rides in comfort in their own car]
Find a wedding hall with Running Man
landmark in Mok-Dong.
Let's go.
I think... Without a doubt, that there will
be a good advantage for us.
-That's the way I see it.
-Because we got first place twice.
[What could be waiting for them at
the final destination?]
[Kwang Soo and Gyu Ri's second round
mission challenge]
[Queen of Housewives, Gyu Ri,
looking after her husband]
It's okay.  I can do this.
I can do 7 of them.
I've already been to the army too.
[Why bring up the army in front of the wife?]
- I can do this!
-You can do it!  You can do it!
That's why I told you to leave me behind.
[Standing up and sitting 7 times
within 10 seconds]
1...2...3...4...!
[Not sure if he's sitting or not...]
[But it still is torturous like death]
... 6 ... 7!
[He did complete 7!  But what's the time?]
We did it!
[10.75 seconds...!!]
[fails the mission by .75 seconds]
-I'm sorry, Kwang Soo.
-No... Seriously. You're not heavy.
-What do we do?
-No. Seriously, you're not heavy.
[The bride's weight that you can only
know once you're married]
-You want to sit and rest for a bit? Sit...
-I'm going to lay down for a moment.
Go ahead, and lay down...
-Giraffe groom stretching out his legs.
Gyu Ri, I had no idea how light you'd be.
You're like a newborn, a newborn.
[Newborn baby, Gyu Ri]
What to do?
[Time time, Ha Ha and Suzy's second round
mission challenge]
Wait, wait... Hold tight.
Otherwise, you'll fall.
Wait... Let's do this.
[Safely grabbing onto his bride]
7 counts just like that.  Start.
-1... 2...!
-What are you doing with that?
What is that?
[Giving up as soon as he starts]
Sorry, Suzy.  All the Miss A's fans...
This is not because of Suzy whatsoever.
It's because I... have no strength.
I'll try this again the right way.
[Ha Ha and Suzy fail their 2nd round mission]
[Now the 3rd round mission
with 11 second wedding march]
-Fighting!
-Don't worry.
[Giraffe groom who's regained his strength
after resting on the ground... This time...?]
Is this the right spot?
[Power sprinting while gritting his teeth]
[With the face turning beet red...]
Please...!  Please...!
-Are you okay?
-I'm okay.  Are you okay?
[Kwang Soo and Gyu Ri.  9.22 Seconds
Mission succeeded!]
[Giraffe groom and the Queen of Housewives
succeeds the wedding march mission]
Good job, Kwang Soo!
-Good job, Kwang Soo.
-9 seconds?  Thank you!
[Can return without having to
cross the bridge anymore!]
You're the best!
I've never seen
a feather weight girl like you!
[Ha Ha and Suzy's 11 second
wedding march challenge!]
[Faster than the last time...
but success within 11 seconds?]
[The last spurt]
-Did we do it?
-9.78 seconds.
[9.78 second success]
Suzy is light!
-I think he is lying... He's lying.
-No.  Not at all.
If you go back to the start line,
you'll find your next location.
It looks like we're shooting a movie!!
[45h, 5th, and 6th team finally arrives]
[Meeting up Ha Ha's team that succeeded]
Seriously?
I'm out of breath already!  This is crazy!
The weather is so nice!
What are you doing with having the girls
dress up in a dress?
[Queen of Housewives helping her hard
working husband's muscles relax]
Your shoulders are very tense.
It's because I've used muscles
I haven't used in a long time.
It's up to the red flag. Please get ready.
[Not just anyone, but if it's Mr. Capable...]
Wait, wait...
[Nice...]
[Just trust me, Hyun Ah]
I think he can do it.
[The bullet like start]
[Top speed we haven't seen until now]
[Without a doubt was fast, but time?]
Are you okay?
Has it been 10 seconds?
Under 10 seconds. Success.
[Mr. Capable is definitely different]
[Jae Suk and Seung Yeon's
10 second wedding march challenge]
This makes no sense! This is so hard!
Lower... Lower! You have to get lower!
[Barely 7]
-Did we do it?!
-Yes!!
[9.75 seconds.  Mission success]
We did it!!
[Last couple. Suk Jin and Ji Hyo]
[A stroll like speed]
[2nd round too...]
1... 2... 3...!
[3rd round too...]
Just a little bit more!
[4th round... Also a failure]
Let's go!
[Wedding march is an arduous road]
7....!
-9.35 seconds.  Success.
-You've worked hard.
You're not as heavy as I thought.
[Wedding Race's final destination]
[Wedding Hall]
[Who will be the one couple
left standing here?]
We're going to get first place today.
Okay?
What did you just do?
Was it because of a bug?
You can't do that over a bug when
we have to rip name tags off now.
[The final mission of this place?]
[Stealing other couple's gloves]
[Steal the other couple's gloves and oust them]
We have to rip off their gloves to oust them.
This is the couple glove that
the 2 of you will be wearing.
Just do it... We can hold it like this.
-If this falls off, then we lose.
-So we'll have to make sure it doesn't.
Since you guys are here first...
This is your benefit.
Reflective bracelet.
[The bracelet that outs the couple who
rips off their glove]
[The ultimate item that will act as the
decisive piece in winning!]
[Just how... Will this turn out?]
We can't use this bracelet on just anyone.
There's no use using it on Suk Jin.
-Jong Kook?
-That's right.
The best thing would be to remain to the end
and use it on the other final team.
Finish listening to what I have to say
before you get out.
In a case of emergency,
it'll be good to hide under the tables here.
[The plan to wait in hiding as to
not to use their ultimate weapon]
[A little while later...]
[Ha Ha-Suzy and Kwang Soo-Gyu Ri arrive]
Stealing couple's gloves?
Steal the other couple's gloves and oust them.
Ah... It's not pulling off the back?
Please put on the couple gloves.
[Only the strongest couple
will remain standing]
[Suddenly nervous giraffe groom]
If we get caught by Jong Kook...
First, let's beg to be kept alive.
He scares me the most.
You know how this is about ripping off
the couple's gloves?
Let's get another couple...
and we'll grab from each end and pull.
We have to form a partnership with someone.
[Gyu Ri... The ultimate Queen of Housewives]
-That way... One by one...
-Okay, okay.
-We'll pick them off that way.
-That's right.
-See you later (Jae Suk)
-Yeah, see you later (Jong Kook)
-Let's see this race through.
-What do you mean? Let's hide for now.
Shall we hide?
You scared me!
[All of a sudden, they're surrounded]
We just got here!
You know we have to do this...
-Let's not do this, and...
-Jong Kook?
-We really have to become a team.
-Team up and oust Jong Kook first.
Let me go for now...
Hey. Come here.
You're not going to corner us here...
-Let's get our revenge now...
-We could get you if we wanted now.
Are you going to work with us or not?
Of course, we'll work with you.
Of course, we will.
[If no cooperation, most likely to be ousted]
-Let's get rid of Jong Kook first... Seriously.
-Seriously... No disbandment.
Commit to something if you betray the team.
If I betray the team,
I'll get the eyelid surgery.
You should get that right away.
You should've done that sooner.
[Do that whether you betray or not]
-I'm about to go crazy.
-Just why... Haven't you done it yet?
Let's seriously start after we get Jong Kook.
For Jong Kook... You have to do it.
[Jong Kook's weak point is female Idols]
-As soon as Jong Kook gets here...
-Grab onto each of his arms...
-And pull it apart.
-Yes!  Let's do that!  Nice!
-Let's get Jong Kook!  Fighting!
-Fighting!
All the ladies here just need to team up
and get Jong Kook.
As soon as our ladies here are out there...
we can get Jong Kook.
-Let's do it!  Seriously!
-Let's do this!
If we fail this, the result is obvious.
When our plan goes into motion,
someone can become sacrificed.
I'm sorry to say, whomever that couple may be
needs to accept it coolly.
[If the plan fails, the sacrificial couple
needs to be cool about it...]
[At last, the coalition heads out to
find Jong Kook and Hyun Ah]
I think he's downstairs.
I'll go down this way.
[Off in pairs of 2 couples to search]
Suk Jin... We have to turn the tables around!
[The firm resolve that brought the
giraffe and Suk Jin together]
Just how long...
He's here!  Here!
[Mr. Capable couple]
[Eyes have locked]
[The good momentum is quickly fading]
He's here!
[Entering dramatically like this is
really fascinating too]
-I can't how scary you are!
-Wow... You really are scary.
Why are you all acting like that?
Why are you so scared?
What are you doing?
Did you all join forces again?
[The hunting has started]
[It's now]
[How will Mr. Capable handle this...?]
[The capable couple is escaping!]
[The coalition hot on his tail!]
Calm down!  Calm down!
[How can this be?]
[Mr. Capable runs away?]
He ran away!  He ran!
[Feeling as though they've already caught him]
Everyone!  We can do it!
Even though we may be weak on our own,
if we all gather together, we can live!
Kim Jong Kook has shows us his back
and ran away from us.
-Seriously... Nothing is impossible.
-This is cool.
[Gary and Krystal are taking in what's
going on while staying hidden]
[A little more breathing room due
to the reflective bracelet]
Doesn't it feel a little bit better
knowing we have 2 lives?
In my opinion, I think someone would
be out by now.
Let's wait just a little bit longer.
We'll go out there when there are
only 2 teams left,
If there are 2 teams left then there will
be 3 teams total including us...
then we can automatically oust one team
since we have the reflective bracelet. Right?
So we just need to get rid of 2 teams.
[But Bride Krystal still seems nervous]
Don't be scared.
Get some sleep.
[Capable couple that ran away earlier]
It's Kim Jong Kook!
[The coalition races on]
[Mr. capable runs away again
to protect Hyun Ah]
Catch Kim Jong Kook!
[Flying down 2 flights of stairs
to make their getaway]
[Hyun Ah's legs giving out]
Hyun Ah's about to die... Hyun Ah's dying.
-Just a minute...
-That's good... It's enough.
-This is the best!
-I'm satisfied with this.
-This is what it's like.
-I'm going to keep doing this!
This is what it's like!
-If we see Gary on the way too, let's get him.
- Yes! Let's do that!
-I'm all for it!!
-Let's go!
This is the most exciting race!
[It's not time yet...]
Doesn't your neck hurt?
[Head hurting from their sleeping position]
[The right time will get here... Sometime]
Stay here like this... Yes, like that.
They can't come if we're like this.
I think it's tough work to date Mr. Capable.
[It's tough to be the wife of a super hero]
[Where did everyone go?]
There are only 2 of us.
It's okay... We can run away.
We can keep running away to the end.
Trust me.  Put your trust in me.
-So this is what it's like to chase.
-This really is exciting.
-It's Kim Jong Kook!
-Wait!
-What are you doing?
-Why isn't he running away?
-He's hoping that one of us gets close.
They're waiting in the doorway so that
a lot of people can't rush to them.
-We can't back down at times likes this!
-Let's go!
-Come!  I said, come!
-It's Kim Jong Kook!
Why don't you go in first?
-We have a plan...
-Jong Kook...
Jong Kook... Jong Kook...
[The attack of the Idol brides]
[Hyun Ah's aggressive supportive defense]
[Mr. Capable is flustered]
-Our ladies are doing so well!
[Take a look at the men...]
[Even though Mr. Capable looks fierce,
he can't use his strength...]
-This is not fair...
-Jong Kook is too strong.
-It feels like I'm hitting a wall of bricks.
-His strength is no joke!
-There's another door.
-Where?  Back there?
[They're scattering looking for another way]
[That's right... This is the time]
You can't go! You can't!
[Scattering means death]
-We can't separate no matter what!
-We can't do that!  It's not safe!
-Just hear me out... Hear me out...!
-Okay... Let's hear it!
-Why are you doing this?
-Are you saying you don't know why?!
You're the most lethal in this game,
so we have to take you out.
What do you mean?
I didn't know he was this kind of a man
when I got together with him!
[Didn't know he was
Mr. Capable until she married him]
When he's like this...
We're all trying to be considerate of you.
[Mr. Capable has grabbed Jae Suk
and Seung Yeon's glove!]
[To attack in such a situation?!]
Everyone hold on!
[With just one attack, everyone's in a frenzy]
This is the type of a person he is!
[Using this moment to make a getaway]
This is too hard!  Elevator!
Let's take the elevator!
[Ultimately, the capable couple
succeeds in making a getaway]
I feel like if our plan works,
we can win first place.
The best scenario would be if one of them
tears off Jong Kook's name.
Right?  I wish Jong Kook gets taken out.
And Ha Ha too.
Wait...
[The coalition that's been after Capable Team
is coming in the room...]
-There they are! They're over there!
-They were hiding.
-They're over there. Everyone get them.
-Where?
-Behind the piano.
-They're behind the piano!
-Everyone gather as one team.
-Over there.  Get over there.
-Over there? No one's there.
-No. They're over there.
-They're over there.
-Are you sure?
They're behind the air conditioner.
Get away!
Come out here first and let's talk about
whether we're going to work together or not.
Okay.  We'll talk out there.
[Giving up on hiding further]
-Come out and let's talk.
-Okay... First...
I think we're going to have to
join them for now.
-After we join them...
-Why are there so many of them?
I would like to join you guys too.
What do we have to do for you to accept us?
-Gary...
-Yes?
[Krystal bride gets scared while
trying to escape]
[It looks as though Gary and Krystal
are going to be refused]
We would like to join your coalition too.
Let's grab Gary's arm first.
[If they do that...!]
-Come on...
-Let's not be like this.
[Not even in their wildest dream does the
coalition team know about the bracelet]
-I'm sorry... But Gary...
-How can they do this?
-Wait...
-Let's grab their arm first.
[This isn't going to work...!]
[The bracelet can't be wasted like this!]
-It's off!
-What the heck?!
[Attack while being corralled]
[Suk Jin and Ji Hyo out!]
[Gary and Krystal still hide the truth
of their reflective bracelet]
How did you do that?
[This time... Your turn]
[Gary outs Kwang Soo and Gyu Ri this way too]
[Kwang Soo and Gyu Ri Out!]
[The coalition is falling apart]
This is why he can't!
You can't do this!
-Hey!  Gary!
-How can he do this?!
[Really doesn't understand Gary's actions]
How many teams are there now?
4 teams are left now.
We're done if we go up against
Jae Suk and Jong Kook.
Definitely... Today you have to definitely...
For sure... To the end.
What did I tell you yesterday?
[Ha Ha and Gary unite for now...]
-Even if someone wins, it has to be one of us.
-Jae Suk ran away on his own.
Let's go up against Jae Suk together.
[Naive Ha Ha and Suzy]
I wonder if there's another way?
I want to find Jae Suk.
If we run into Jong Kook right now,
we're over.
-It'll really be over for us.
-Let's go around together as one.
[For now the game is progressing
according to Gary's plan]
How can 2 teams be ousted
in a blink of an eye?
Maybe we should hide...
I hear something!
[Jong Kook and Hyun Ah end up here
while running away from others]
-They're over there.
-It's just the 2 of them?
-Yes. Just them. Let's go.
-Are you sure? Wait...
[Making sure it's just
Jae Suk and Seung Yeon]
-Where are you going?
-Come here!
I said, come here!!
[Since they broke away from the coalition,
of course, this is how it ends]
They're calling for others.
Come here... Over there.
This is the best spot.
Can you understand now that
we've been chased?
[Seung Yeon out of her mind]
He's scary...
Jae Suk!  Let's gather around...
[Coalition team meeting up again]
If we don't gather together,
we're all dead.
Kim Jong Kook is walking around
on the first floor right now.
-We have to go down there together.
-Okay, okay.
[For now, going up against
the capable couple together]
We should have gotten Jae Suk earlier.
-I was afraid others were hiding...
-I was afraid of that too.
I saw you...
You're planning on attacking from both sides?
[Gary and Krystal going in the elevator?]
[What are you doing?]
We'll just keep the door shut.
-This is not good...
-Hey! You cowards.
Let's do this!  Why are you all hiding?
[Mr. Capable feels he can take on 3 teams]
You cowards...
Live the rest of your life as cowards.
[No matter how they're goaded,
they're not budging out of fear]
[Gary and Krystal out of elevators again?]
[Just then...!]
[Jae Suk and Seung Yeon couple glove
is right in front!]
[Huh?  Now?]
[Ha Ha is signing to him to tear it off]
[He was afraid of being suspected if
he attacked Jae Suk's glove...]
[But only grateful since
Ha Ha is helping out like that...]
[Then with a light heart...]
[Jae Suk and Seung Yeon out!]
What the heck?
Seung Yeon... Calm down.
[Seung Yeon bride loses her mind]
-We got fooled...
-How...?
Let's just talk later.
Seung Yeon... We were fooled. Calm down.
I didn't want to waste the opportunity...
[Everything is going according to plan...]
[If they can only get rid of Mr. Capable
with the reflective bracelet...]
[Little couple... It's your turn]
Ha Ha...
Ha Ha... Let's get this show on the road.
[Mr. Capable throwing down the gauntlet]
Ha Ha, come on out.
[Walking out with the 2 ladies...]
[Finally, the last fight]
Long time no see.
Us with Kang Gary couple...
[Who will the winner be?]
It's been awhile, you guys.
Where have you been running off to?
We weren't doing that.
[Come here... Come here]
Jong Kook is calling you first.
-I will let you go first.
-In that case, why don't you go first?
[When Mr. Capable is calling,
both teams conceding]
-You go first.
-No. I don't want to do that.
-Come here... Come here.
-We have to go together.
-Okay... Fine.
-So serious. 'We have to go together'
Why did you guys get so serious?
[Capable couple vs. Kiddie couple]
Seriously...
-Jong Kook, I love you!
-Should I just end this quickly?
I just want to oust them right now.
[Get on him... No other options]
I... 2... 3...!
-What are you doing?  You stopped!
-You stopped too!
1... 2... 3...!
[This time is for real]
Hey!  Hey!
[Capable's good housewife]
[Pushing their way in is the pressing matter]
[But it's not easy as it was last time]
You're through...
[If they're careful,
they may even breakthrough!]
[Ha Ha and Suzy succeed in breaking through]
[Isn't it hard to survive, Mrs. Capable?]
[The Kiddie Couple keeping their stance]
[The real fight in a wider space]
[Gary grabs Jong Kook and Hyun Ah's glove!]
[Now if they pull from both sides!]
[It's off!]
We did it!!
[Right then,
Gary slightly extends out his glove]
[Naive Ha Ha sees that...]
[How can it go just as they planned?]
[Reflective!]
[When they thought they had won...
How can this be?]
[With the power of reflection...]
[Ha Ha and Suzy out!]
Pil-Sok-Cross!
[Kang Gary with some skills]
[Everything went according to his plan...]
[Gary's perfect win!]
[Gary and Krystal]
[The ultimate winners]
The winners today...
[Winning gift to the winning couple!]
-No way!
-How can this be?
[Solid gold tiara to the winning bride]
Miss Korea... It's Miss Korea's tiara.
You worked hard today.
[Groom Gary for his Bride Krystal]
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Manchester, England]
[Mission:]
[Find the 2 hearts]
[5. 20. 2012]
[The everlasting Captain, oxygen tank...]
[Park Ji Song]
[He will make an appearance in Running Man]
Hello.  My name is Park Ji Song.
[Recent History...]
[The hottest showdown!]
I'm also an audience that always
enjoys watching Running Man...
I'll be in Thailand to meet my Soccer Fans.
If all of the Running Man
takes care of the mission,
you will attend he Asian cup with me
in Thailand.
Are you ready, Mr. Capable?
[The 2 hearts running towards Running Man]
[He is coming to you next week]
Running Man... Out.
[Dreams do come true]