[War of the Gods]
[To become the ultimate God]
[An unavoidable competition in order
to become the ultimate God]
[The myth!]
[Running Man's war of the God's starts]
[The ultimate fierce battle]
[The God of immortality]
[The War of the Gods]
[Running Man]
[June 18th, 2012]
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Running Man's 100th episode]
[100th episode party in the city?]
[Mr. Capable arriving in the midst
of all the camera flashes]
[Prepared on a small scale]
What the heck...
[But smiling nonetheless]
[Citizens of Chacheondong congratulating
the 100th episode]
What the... This is our 100th episode...!
There's not much that I can eat here.
[100th celebratory buffet]
[Arrival of the giraffe]
[Big nosed brother in shades]
[Gary's turn in the spotlight]
[Next is...]
[Black Ha Ha]
Ha Ha, it's Ha Ha!
[Stretching?]
[Utmost popularity from the neighborhood kids]
There's been a lot of
female guests in the past...
[The ultimate female guest
that fast Ha Ha picks?]
I don't know...
Wouldn't it be faster to ask those ladies?
Who misses me the most...
[That would without a doubt be
the neighborhood kids]
[Wow... Miss Blank]
[Her strong red carpet fashion that turns
any walkway into red carpet walkway]
I guess Yoo Jae Suk's here.
[So...]
[...Pretty]
Hi!
[Normally would greet her with chatter,
but now can't even meet her glances]
[A loud cheer]
[Jae Suk in all green]
[He said he didn't like green!]
[He's addicted... He's totally addicted]
[Disappointed?]
Grasshopper... Grasshopper!
Because of Ha Ha...
I don't really like green that much.
Grasshopper... Grasshopper!
How do you feel about the 100th episode?
First of all...
100th episode is something that I
couldn't even have fathomed on the first day.
Everything is thanks to all the viewers
out there that cheered us on...
And because of their support,
this was all made possible.
I thank you again from the bottom of my heart.
-A reception has been prepared inside.
-Thank you.
Yes... Thank you!
You're really ruining my appetite...
This suit was sent to me this morning...
Hey!
-This is all because of you!
-No, it isn't.
-You're the green man.
-I'm seriously about to go crazy.
I had thought there was some concept
after seeing this suit today...
But I'm the only one in green!
I'm the only one in green!
-We all know that he likes green...
-Why don't you pull this down further?
[Taking his vengeance on Ha Ha]
[Exposing Ha Ha's baby skin]
Stop that.  Look at your shoes!
-Pull this down a little bit more.
-Yeah, pull it down.
[The conversation has instantly
been turned to their party attire]
[His shirt has been turned into a sexy
black off-the-shoulder attire]
Now it finally seems like a party!
Hey, that's sexy!
-Now it's a party!
[The big nosed brother exposes his naked eye]
I heard that... Kim Hee Sun will be on today?
[Unfortunately, the big surprise guest
has already been revealed]
-She'll be here this afternoon.
-She's really coming then?
-But... Hee Sun...
-You know her too?
[Pretending again to be
friends with the guest...]
-I'm about to go crazy...
-Just let it go.
-Suk Jin... I know Hee Sun!
-What do you mean, you know her?
What is that... Her book pads.
[The woman that was always in the top for
selling the most amount of book pads]
-Stop calling her Hee Sun!
-You should call her Miss Kim Hee Sun.
-Hee Sun and I...
-Who was it the last time...
[Inside the refrigerator in the corner...]
[The Goddess... Kim Hee Sun]
[The Goddess of Korea... Kim Hee Sun]
[The ultimate top star that boasts
an unchanging beauty]
[She is here]
Why did you put a guest inside
the refrigerator?
What are you thinking?
[The special hideout, refrigerator]
[100th episode's special guest,
the goddess of beauty, Kim Hee Sun]
I have been your biggest fan all my life!
It's me!  I'm Lee Kang To!
[Automatically shouting out lines from 'Mister Q]
Sue me!  Go ahead and sue me!
Give me my book pad money back!
-That's a line from Mister Q!
-Wow... How do you know that?
-Seriously...
-But, hey...
-Kim Hee Sun is...
-She really is a goddess!
[He was just talking about
how close they were...]
I think it's been a little over 10 years
since I've first made an appearance.
I saw it last night too.
It was so funny!
My hair was a mess yesterday...
[Of all the episodes, it was the episode
where big nosed brother was made a fool]
We've decided to become more filial
towards you starting today!
What will be doing today with Hee Sun?
-I don't know if she'll be okay...
-This is a very abrasive program...
I'm even more abrasive.
[Her provocation still remains alive]
[Wait and see... Her abrasive attraction
will be seen soon...]
Kim Hee Sun has graced us with her presence
today as a special guest for 100th episode.
Yes... But she's not just a guest.
Since a goddess has joined us...
Our theme today is the 'War of the Gods.'
[War of the Gods]
[The war of a different scale]
[The desperate battle
to become the ultimate God]
[That time is approaching]
A war of the Gods?
You all know of Aphrodite,
the goddess of love?
She looks good from the front and back!
(Aphrodite's name in Korean insinuates that)
[Hee Sun is none other than that
Goddess of love, Aphrodite]
Oh... Hee Sun is Aphrodite?
Hee Sun is already a Goddess...
The rest of you aren't yet Gods.
[The rest of the members are not yet Gods]
You all have to challenge as humans...
[In order to earn the rights to become a God,
You have to overcome the limits of human]
[In the case that you fail...]
[Through voting,
2 members will remain human]
Aphrodite!
We now start out 100th episode with
our Aphrodite, Kim Hee Sun!
[The War of the God starts now with
Aphrodite, Kim Hee Sun!]
[Will everyone be able to earn
their right to be a God?]
[Move to Yeoido district at Han River Park!]
[The gateway to become a God]
[Yeoido district at Han River Park]
Hee Sun... I think we need to come
to a more familiar terms...
Jae Suk is the grasshopper...
Ji Hyo is Miss Blank...
Jong Kook is Kkeuk...
[Everyone has a nickname...]
There's Haroro, Giraffe, Impala...
There's a nickname for all of us.
Is there anything you want to be called as?
Princess is overused...?
[Self anointed princess?]
-What's wrong with it? It's not overused.
-Okay. Your nickname is Princess!
-Princess.
-Calling her that would be weird!
-Princess...
-Yes, Princess.
Or you can call me Ggong-Ju.
(Princess pronounced differently)
- Ggong-Ju...!
- Ggong-Ju.
-Then...
-She can be Mong-Ju.
Mong Ju...
-Gary is the funniest.  Gae-Ju...
-Gae Ju...!
-Our  Ggong-Ju...?
-Yes?
[ Ggong-Ju's surprising affinity]
-There's the flag!
-Is that it?
[The God's gateway]
There it is!  There's a God!
[A God... At this place?]
[God of disguise, Dong Wan FD]
-He's a God!
-What the heck is this?
[It's a good thing this is being taped]
-That's Dong Wan.
-This really seems like a variety.
[Mission.  The gateway to become a God]
[Defy the limits of
a human in strength and speed]
[The chariots of the Gods through the gateway]
That does look like a chariot.
[Stand one person
in front of each of the flags]
The first person has to
cross this finish line...
[In a relay race, pass through the goal line]
The person that can pull the chariot...
[Have to beat the God of disguise, Dong Wan
in order to win the race]
-We have to have the girls go first.
-Yes, we should do that.
The last person has to have 7 people
on the chariot...
-You have to be the last person.
-He has to be the last person.
-Preparation is complete!
-Fighting, fighting!
Hee Sun, fighting!
-Fighting!
-Kim Hee Sun, fighting!
[Challenging the gateway to become a God]
[Overcome the human limits
of speed and strength...]
[Earn the rights to become a God]
Set... Go!
Fighting!  Kim Hee Sun, fighting!
[ Ggong-Ju's significant speed]
Stopping is the problem.  That's the problem!
-Hurry, hurry, hurry!
-Getting on is taking too much time!
Go!
[2nd runner, Ji Hyo is off!]
This is actually really hard!
Nice!  More!  Fighting!
[Not easy with it being a child's bicycle]
-Ji Hyo, hurry!  Fighting!
-Ji Hyo's quick!
If she's good, she can win!
Ji Hyo's quick!  She may be able to win!
Stop, stop.  Careful.
[Ji Hyo arrives at the 3rd course
with her quick speed]
Get in, get on!
[Now it's the men's turn!]
Suk Jin, hurry!
-Hurry, hurry!  We can catch him!
-Dong Wan's talking a really long time too!
[4th runner, Ha Ha]
We can do it!  Get in quickly!
-Hurry up and get on!
-Hurry!  Faster!
[Starting to become physically taxing
for Dong Wan FD]
If we're good, we may win this!
He's out of strength already.
-Hurry, hurry!  Come on!
-He's out of strength.
[5th runner, Gary]
[His speed is slowing down more and more...]
He's sapped of strength!  We can do this!
[Now only 3 courses left]
We can do this.
Move!  Kwang Soo!
Gather up your strength!
Dong Wan is exhausted!
-Hurry up and go!
-Let's go!
-Hurry up and get in.  Let's go!
-Hurry up and go!
Let's go!
[The win is possible if they can only shorten
the time of switching off the runners!]
[7th runner, Jae Suk]
Don't stop, and just get on!
[Chaos]
[The last runner, Jong Kook]
[Only a few meter's difference!]
-Just go!
-Go!  Go!
[Now to the finish line]
[Please...]
[Mr. Capable full power]
[Depletion of power]
-Hurry!
-Go!  Go!
[Full charge?]
[If they can't overcome the limits
of human here...]
[2 of them cannot become Gods]
Please...!
[Indeed...]
[The victor of the God's chariot race...]
[Running Man's defeat...]
[Total discharge]
All the men should have just got on...
But you all came all the way back here.
Hee Sun's is mad...
[The goddess' start of annoyance]
-This is...
-All the beauties have that tendency.
Jong Kook to do it alone...
With all of us on it.
Right, right... Let's do that.
[Re-challenge with Jong Kook alone?]
Dong Wan says he can't do it.
[Refusal from the God of disguise]
Now... Please choose the 2 members that
cannot become a God.
[2 people cannot become Gods]
Kwang Soo, you can start the voting.
[2 people are chosen through voting]
-Go up to the front of the camera, Kwang Soo.
-Go on up there.
[An awkward...]
[And difficult decision]
Kim Jong Kook.
[Jong Kook=1 vote]
-You're in trouble.
-You just wait and see.
-Why are you getting seriously mad?
-Why are you getting mad?
-My spot is the best one.
Kim Jong Kook!
[Jong Kook=2 votes]
Suk Jin... Don't get flustered.
You can't break down now.  Not now.
Kim Jong Kook.
[Jong Kook=3 votes]
Pil-Chok-Cross!
-Your decision can be different from theirs.
-Really?
[Who will Hee Sun's selection be?]
Feel comfortable about it.
Kim Jong Kook...!
[Is it possible to have a unanimous vote
for one person?]
He always votes for himself when
we're picking captains.
Kim Jong Kook!
[Cooley voting for himself]
[Mr. Capable choosing the path of
a human being on his own]
Jong Kook is a human...
This is better for Jong Kook.
[I guess... He already is a superman]
Lee Kwang Soo.
[Kwang Soo=1 vote]
I pick Lee Kwang Soo too.
-Kwang Soo...
-Why?
[This is how...
Jong Kook and Kwang Soo couldn't become Gods]
If Gods are such good things to be,
why are there so many Gods?
And they allow for us to become Gods
this easily?
-You're not Gods yet...
-It's that you can become Gods.
[The secret of the Gods will be revealed
in a bit at the final destination]
Hey... Kwang Soo...
You really are being too much.
What have I done that's too much?
You think Running Man is a joke?
[The 8th member,  Ggong-Ju, realizing
the order of the food chain]
You are back.
How old were you when you became
so pretty like this, Gong Ju...?
Again, again... Ggong-Ju.
Ggong-Ju...! How old were you when
you became so pretty as you are?
[Just how old was Ggong-Ju when she started
to become so pretty?]
[The sudden laughter?]
She must find it so funny even
just at the thought of it.
-She's liking it too much.
-The answer is?
When the girls come on the show...
All of you flatter them...
But we don't ever do that on purpose.
But you are pretty...
It is true that you're pretty.
[They're not being snarky...
It's the truth]
There's no way you're not pretty,  Ggong-Ju.
-Okay.  Fine!
-See? You are pretty, just admit it.
So when did you start becoming this pretty?
I've always been!
Then how long are you going to remain pretty?
How long?
-Always.
-There you go!
Where do you place
in the pretty chart in our country?
The first!
[I'm the prettiest!]
[Ggong-Ju, Hee Sun... Nice and cool]
Seeing how you all flatter all the female
celebrities when I watch the show...
I used to think it was tacky
and gave me the chills...
-But in reality, it feels really...
-It feels good, doesn't it?
Shall we go grab a drink when we're done?
I think this is the place.
[An enjoyable time
full of chatter and laughter]
[However, all of this
is the calm before the storm...]
[100th special episode]
[The final location of the epic battle]
[Just what is the meaning of this location?]
Just what is...
[Jae Suk enters by himself first]
What's this?
Is that something scary?
[Elementals of darkness guarding the temple]
What is this?
[The scenery that's opening up
in front of his eyes...]
[Temple]
[Inside the temple is full of people]
[Running Man's myth
that is about to take place here]
Where did all these...
Wow... How come there are so many of them?
Where did they all come from?
[The human beings
that have filled up this place]
Huh?  What's this?
[A fully decorated room...]
What's this? Why am I here?
[Grasshopper Jae Suk?]
You're not by any chance
telling me to wear this?
What is this that you're doing today?
[The God of water guns Poseidon,
your weakness is water!]
[Become the ultimate God by
reaming alive in the battle]
I'm Poseidon? Poseidon?
Ultimately...
[Jae Suk!  Poseidon, the God of water guns!]
I'm a God, right?
[Switching off to gold name tag of the Gods]
[On the verge of War of the Gods!]
[Jae Suk is Poseidon!]
[Poseidon.  Weakness: Water]
I mean... What kind of an atmosphere is this?
Why are you calling me in here
and giving me this?
[God of the sun and music, Apollo]
[Your weakness is the mark!]
[Become the ultimate God by
remaining alive to the end]
[Gary is Apollo, the God of the sun and music]
[Apollo.  Weakness: Mark]
[The goddess of war, Athena]
[Your weakness is your ankle]
[Become the ultimate God by
remaining alive to the end]
[Athena.  Weakness: Ankle]
[God of love, Eros]
[Your weakness is a kiss]
[Become the ultimate God by
remaining alive to the end]
Eros...
[Eros.  Weakness: Kiss]
The God of love...!
Eros...!
[That's not quite it...]
[God of the underworld, Hermes]
[Your weakness is your alter ego]
[Become the ultimate God by
remaining alive to the end]
The God of the underworld...
I'm Hermes?
[Hermes.  Weakness: Alter ego]
[The goddess from the womb,
Aphrodite's entrance]
[The goddess of beauty, Aphrodite]
[Your weakness is exposure]
[Become the ultimate God by
remaining alive to the end]
[Aphrodite.  Weakness: Exposure]
[Thus enters the 6 Gods of Running Man]
Why can't be a God?
You and I got dropped...
What's this?
[The 2 humans also arrive at the gate
to the temple]
-Is it blocked so we can't get in?
-So we can't go in?
Why are they all gathered up there?
[Unlike when the Gods were entering,
they're not even budging]
We'd like to get through.  Excuse us.
What's this?
Why are there so many people?
[Looks like they need to shimmy their way in]
Can't we go in there?
-But how...
-We can go in?
What is this?
[Demons or not,
Jong Kook is pushing his way through]
Take me with you, Jong Kook!
[The human being is...
To the pillar of the temple?]
Why are you smashing down the temple?!
-I accidentally pushed it.
-Take me with you!
-Why is the temple...
-Jong Kook!
[Recovering it right away...]
Why did this fall down?
It's Hercules!
-Come in!
-Come take me!
How do I get in?
Kwang Soo... Come in.
[Kwang Soo may end up going home at this rate]
-How did you get in there?
-Kwang Soo...
-Help me out.
[The 2 humans barely make it in
to the inside of the temple]
I think this must be their Kingdom.
[This is the location where the
War of the Gods will soon take place]
Just what in the world are we?
[Jong Kook and Kwang Soo who weren't
able to become Gods and remain human]
Then everyone else has become Gods?
Everyone else are gods.
[Become the last man standing by surviving
the War of the Gods]
Remain alive?
Since they're all gods,
I'm sure they all have powers.
So what do we do?
We're in trouble.
But the gods...
You think they're all the same gods?
What is this?
[Will they be able to survive
in the battlefield of the Gods?]
This is seriously...
I have no idea what's going on.
Why are these people walking around with
the sashes around their shoulder...?
I wonder if there's
an incantation or something?
Are we supposed to work together with
these people and do something?
Is that not it?
They don't have any missions?
Just what... Just what is all this?
What is... What is all this?
[There's no use asking the humans...]
I see the green sash.
What are you guys doing?
What... What is it that you're doing?
This is seriously driving me crazy.
[Wait?  That's...?]
[Poseidon discovers
the room full of water guns]
Wow... Now whenever there's a water gun around,
I can't just casually pass them by.
Nice.
Whatever may happen...
[Can't seem to leave the water gun room]
Wow... This one is really tiny.
This is like a water gun ring.
[The endless interest when it comes to
water guns and the color green]
Just what the heck is this?
[Aphrodite in the room full of dolls]
I doubt the dolls are here
for no reason, right?
I'm not wasting my time right now, am I?
[Athena playing the piano]
[There are a plethora of decorated rooms.
What is the secret behind these rooms?]
These are all the guests that we've had.
Oh my... Yong Hwa.
I've completely forgotten about Yong Hwa.
Wow... Min Jung... And Ji Sung.
[Saying hello to each and everyone that has
cast their light on the past 100 shows]
Oh my... Yeon In, and Su Ro..
Oh, and Min Soo!
Min Soo... Even just his board is scary.
Why did you use a picture like this
for Min Soo?
[It's Jae Suk...]
What is this?
What is all this?
[Slowly going around to find out
which God the others are]
-I don't know if you're a God or human...
-Gary's a God too!
-You're a God?
-Yes.  I'm Apollo.
You are?  Apollo?
-You're Apollo?
-The God of sun and music, Apollo.
Which one are you?
-Why did you tell us that?
-I'm not supposed to?
[Gary, revealing his identity...]
[God of stupidity]
Why did you tell us that you're Apollo?
-Are we supposed to get him then?
-Pretend that you didn't hear it.
-You're Apollo?
-Jae Suk, pretend that you didn't hear it!
-How can I pretend to do that?
-Keep it to yourself.
-But I already heard it, so how can I?
-Just keep it to yourself then.
Okay, I got it.  Talk to Hee Sun too.
Hee Sun, pretend that you didn't hear it,
and keep the Apollo thing a secret.
He's Apollo...
I think I know what it is...
We're all supposed to get someone...
Supposed to get someone.
All the thing in each rooms
are like shields and weapons.
[All the items in the rooms are
shields and weapons?]
In my case...
[Why going in the umbrella room?]
[Ah... Since water is his weakness,
he's going to use them as shields?]
Since I'm...weak to the water,
I have to carry something like this around.
[Will Poseidon Jae Suk's
deduction be correct?]
I wonder what all this is, Kwang Soo?
[Humans Jong Kook and Kwang Soo,
busy figuring out a way to survive]
-This is a war of the gods...
-They want us to survive to the end.
Remain alive to the end,
and become the last man standing.
What else could there be?
I'm sure there's something to Gods' name tags.
In the war of the gods...
There's Suk Jin.
[What does it matter if he's become a God?
He's still on even keel with the humans]
-What are you doing?
-Huh?
-Which God are you?
-I don't think I can tell you.
-Why?
-You're not going to tell us?
-Is it okay for me to tell you?
-Sure.  We have nothing.
I think I'm supposed to keep it to myself.
-But...
-Ah!  You're human!
Wait... Wait...
-What about us being human?
-You're both human!
Is it a war between the Gods and humans?
-Is there something like that?
-No, there isn't.  But...
-But first...
-His name tag is a gold color!
The Gods are more powerful than us.
-But our situation is different.
-We don't know what's going on.
-I really don't know.
-Then let me tear off your name tag.
Come on... It's just beginning...
That's being too fast.
[Even though he's become a God,
Suk Jin is as always, the first target]
But we don't know what's going on...
Jong Kook, I'll get his arms.  Tear it off.
-Hey...!
-No... You tear it off.
You tear it off, Jong Kook.
This is 100th special episode!
What if something happens to me
after I tear it off?
-Jong Kook...
-Kwang Soo, tear it off!
[The 2 human beings pushing it off to one
another, afraid something will happen to them]
-It's been a long time since you've done it!
-What do you mean, it has?!
What are you guys doing?!
-You tear it off!
-Jong Kook!
-Let's just see what happens...
-You should be the one to do it.
[Jong Kook wants to tear the name tag off
no matter what happens]
Of course...
-Hey, Kwang Soo...
-Kwang Soo...!
I'll see you around!
Jong Kook, just let me go.
You think I'll see your wrath
if I tore your name tag off?
Not just see my wrath...
I'm sure you'll be struck down by lightning.
Just like in the comic books...
The zig zags of the lightning on your head.
Suk Jin... Let's see what happens.
You're a God... You won't die just because
a human tears it off real quick.
-There are many kinds of gods.
-But you wouldn't die...
There are many types of gods...
I'm the kind of god that can die.
-But you're a god!
-I'm the type of god that'll die!
-Let's see what happens...
-You think I'll give up my life so easily?
[The problem is that it's too easy]
Why do you have thighs for arms?
-Suk Jin!
-I'm a god!  Hey!
[At this rate, he really is about to
get his name ripped off by a human]
-Jae Suk, Suk Jin is about to be ousted.
-Why?
Why is Suk Jin about to get ousted?
-What the heck?
-Hey!
[Hermes Suk Jin's crisis]
[The human undertaking a God?]
Seriously!  The lightning!
The lightning is going to strike!
[The name tag is about to get ripped off!]
Sun!  Sun!
-What the heck is this?
-Am I out?
-His got ripped off.
-His got ripped off?
[Ousted if the name tag is ripped off
even if you're a god?]
[Uh Oh... In that case...]
[Locking on target]
[To become the ultimate God...]
[Gets rid of him!]
What the heck?
[Aphrodite Hee Sun gets rid off
Poseidon's name tag!]
Hee Sun...
Why did you tear that off...?
Hey!  How can you... Hey!
-Mine just got torn off!
-Who did it?
I tore it off without knowing...
I thought there would be something if I did...
-What do I do?
-You did good...
-Hey!  You... Apollo...!
-Jae Suk is out then...
What does this all mean then?
Am I out?
Now one of you that knows my secret is out.
[Seriously... Are 2 of the gods already
out just like this?]
[Then the Gods are
no different than the humans...?]
[No matter how many times the name tag
is torn off, Gods do not die]
Tear it off!  Go ahead and tear it off!
Let's see you do it!
Put it back on my back...
I'm not dead!
This is great!
You were trying not to do it?
You're making me do it
putting my life on the line?
This is great... Nice...!
[This is the basic power of the Gods]
[Suk Jin, who has nothing to fear now]
-They don't even get paused for a moment?
-Hurry up and put it back on.
He saw it.
What the heck?  Why did you tear it off?
-Which God are you, Suk Jin?
-Me?
Rubber shoe.
(Shin=God. GomuShin=Rubber shoes)
Just tell us.
Hey... Did you know this?
With the Gods...
The name tag...
-You can't tell him that.
-Let's go.
[Humans fleeing away for now]
What the heck?
Hey... Even if your name tag gets ripped off,
you don't die of you're a god.
Really?!
[Enlightened Gods hunting down the humans!]
-We're in trouble.  Let's go this way!
-Get them!
Get them...!
[Just what is the future
of these weak humans?]
[Even if a god gets their name tag torn off,
they do not die]
-See?
-What do you mean, see?
-You tore it off trying to oust me!
-Didn't you know about that?
-You knew about that?
-Of course.
-Gary doesn't know... Let's tear his off.
-Why don't you tear mine off?
-Really?
-No.
What the heck?  We don't get ousted?
Really?
We can't be ousted?
So Gods don't die...
Then should I tear it off again?
[The humans to whom the solution to go up
against the gods is unknown]
We were told to remain alive during
the war of the gods...
It means that by whatever means,
we have to survive the battle to the end.
This is a war among the Gods.
So using whatever means necessary...
We just need to remain alive.
We just have to remain alive.
The reason is it's a war between the gods...
-So why would we get involved in it?
-It should stay between the gods.
[Why would we step out of our place
and get involve between the gods?]
[This is a battle amongst the gods...
It's no place for us to get involved in]
Han Hae Won!
I'm Lee Kang To!
I have something to tell you!
What is it?!
Hae Won!
[Possessing the main character of the
drama, 'Mister Q' again]
Hae Won...!  Hae Won...!
-I have something to tell you.
-You do?
-Today's 100th special episode...
-Yeah?
Oh my... I'm dizzy.
You guys can spin around.
Spin.
-I have something to tell you.
-What is it?
I'm your guardian angel.
Is it okay for you to be saying that
so that everyone can hear you?
[Huh?  Hee Sun and Ha Ha...?]
[Before they can even start
their secret conversation...]
Look at him peeking in...
[The party crasher, Poseidon]
-To use such a lowly method...
-What do you mean, lowly?
-Why are you wearing the bag?
-Because I'm the God of backpacks.
I will...introduce my wife, Hera.
I'm Zeus!
Help me, Hera!
[Knee... Knee kick?]
Hera?
You do it all by yourself.
[Even the Goddess' wit is perfect!]
Jae Suk... Be careful.
[All the Gods are still cautious,
keeping their weaknesses hidden]
[Since ripping the name tag is pointless,
there's no point in doing that...]
You tore it off,
but he didn't die because he's a god.
Every person...has a weakness.
[The weaknesses about themselves
only they themselves know about]
You have a weakness too...
Do you know what your weakness is?
Yeah.
The goddess of beauty Aphrodite,
your weakness is exposure.
[Honesty]
Exposure...
-Exposure.
-Huh?  Exposure?
[Honestly confessing exposure as her weakness]
Come on... That's such a lie.
What do you mean, exposure?
I'm not that stupid!
-But it is...
-Exposure?
-But it's the truth...
-Exposure, you say?
You should at least say something
that even makes sense...
Hee Sun...
[Hee Sun told him honestly...]
You disappoint me...
Was I too honest?
Then...
The exposure that we're both thinking of?
That's too strange... That makes no sense.
[Aphrodite's weakness is indeed, exposure.
Just what is its secret?]
If I'm weak to exposure...
Then I should wear something!
[Aphrodite, who came to the clothing room
to escape exposure]
Does it suit me?
I'm weak to exposure...
But this one is short sleeved.
[Eliminated because the arms are exposed
with it being short sleeved]
It's a child's costume... A child's costume.
[This time, a tracksuit that an Italian
craftsman has sewn stitch by stitch]
[Exposure blockade!]
[But is that really what exposure means?]
Guest... This is a guest room.
In the past 100 episodes...
It's all the gusts that
appeared on our program!
All of them here...
Who's this?
Isn't this Eun Hye?  Yoon Eun Hye?
[The 2 humans also happen to find the room...]
-Suk Jin...
-Why is Eun Hye here?
This is all about the past 100 episodes...
Everything that we've done so far.
Why's her face on there?
[Huh?  Did Kwang Soo see something?]
Kwang Soo!  What is it?
[There's definitely something there]
Kwang Soo...
Let's do this together.
-Kwang Soo, let's do this together.
-Hurry up and get in here.
[Seems like something important is
in their hands]
Let me see it quickly.
[Shutting the door tight so that
the God can't see..]
[Description of usage]
[If you shout out 'Of course' while covering
their ears with the mask on, they're ousted]
[It seems like this is a weapon they
can use against the gods...]
Hey, I'll help you.
Try it.  Since you already have the mask.
-Just come in.  Don't say anything and come in.
-I'll help you.
-I'll help you.  I'll seriously help you.
-Okay, okay.
[This is the weapon to oust Hermes?]
Of course!
[Is this Hermes weakness, the alter ego?]
What the heck is that?
-Of course!
-What is that?
[Nothing is happening]
What the heck?
Are we supposed to put it on him?
I bet that's meant for someone!
Are you supposed to do it by putting it on him?
-What the heck?
-Of course!
I think it has something
to do with Jong Kook...
[The incident where Jong Kook covered
Eun Hye's ears and shouted out 'Of course!']
Of course!
[This is how today goes on by...]
This has nothing to do with me?
-There's someone that this is meant...
-Of course!
-I don't know why you...
-This has nothing to do with you.
[The truth is this is a weapon that works
for Jong Kook had he become a God]
Let's look around once more.
I got it.  That's it...
The Gods' weaknesses are all over the place...
And when you use it correctly on the right God,
then that God is ousted.
[Only when you use the weapons regarding the
Gods' weaknesses, can you oust them]
[Poseidon discovers the blacksmith's room]
[Searching to see if there's anything...]
[The 'R' sticker means...?]
Just what the heck is this now?
[Description of usage]
[If you hit the target's heart zone
with the arrow, they're ousted]
Wait... The heart zone...
[If I shot one of the Gods with this,
it will be effective...]
[In that case, who do I shoot?]
It's not Gary...
[An encounter with Aphrodite that's
prepared to block exposure]
All of a sudden,
I thought of Hyun Bin in his drama.
-That's really festive.
-Isn't it?
It's really the same thing.
What is this?
I just saw it in one of the rooms...
That's nice.
-This is...
-I got it.
It's something that I can't give to others.
Do you know anything?
Let's talk honestly among the gods.
What are you doing after asking me
to come on here as a guest?
Why are you getting mad all of a sudden?
Is this a Running Man's prank?
Tell me something...
[Huh?  This is...?]
Hee Sun... What are you doing?
-What are you doing?
-Do you have to hide?
-No.  Where's Jae Suk?
[Hermes Suk Jin,
transformed into a grasshopper]
-Will you grab Jae Suk so I can oust him?
-Sure, sure. I've already ousted him.
-Jae Suk...
-How?
I have to wear this and tear it off.
[Is that really the right weapon?]
Jae Suk...
Why are you wearing that?
I'm a grasshopper.
Out!
[No effect whatsoever]
Stick it back on for me.
[Ah... So there are weapons that'll work]
-Was there something to that?
-This?
[Just then!]
[Poseidon Jae Suk pointing the arrow
to Hermes Suk Jin!]
[Is this the weapon that'll eliminate
Hermes Suk Jin?]
[It just bounces off?]
[Jae Suk gets flustered seeing that
there's no effect]
-For the time being...
-I just shot it for the fun of it.
[A weapon that has no effect on Hermes]
No matter what you do...
We don't die.
There's a way that this works somehow...
This doesn't work against him...
This has no effect on him...
[Hee Sun, who's found out about the weapons
are now actively searching for weapons]
[Room of bags]
[Now searching each room carefully]
[There's something!]
[Aphrodite Hee Sun discovers something!]
[Dolls...?]
[The usage of these?]
[Description of usage]
[If you tear off the name tag off the
target's doll, they're ousted]
[However, you have to make sure to tear it off
in front of them]
[Where the target is watching?]
[Anyways, Aphrodite also gains a weapon!]
[Who is the God that
this weapon will work against?]
Shall we go out hunting?
[Eros searching the beverage room]
Something could be in here.
[A weapon inside a beverage?]
There could be something.
[Now all the Gods are really searching
all the rooms in detail]
[A small box with the 'R' sticker!]
[The weapons of the Gods that's being
discovered through careful searching]
[It appears to be lipstick...]
[Description of usage]
[If you make a kiss mark on the target's cheek
with the lipstick on, the target's ousted]
[Wait...]
[Eros... Your weakness is a kiss]
The information in here...
It's me, it's describing me.
[He finds the weapon that could be used
against him himself!]
I can't ever have this taken from me!
[Eros Ha Ha silently closing in on Poseidon]
Then Ha Ha...
[Lipstick on bright...]
Ji Hyo...
I love you!  I will always love you!
[To hide that it's his own weakness,
he's going around doing it to others!]
-It's not you... What to do?
-What are you trying to do?
Sorry... I'm sorry.
-This is a little awkward.
-Why do you have lipstick on?
I just wanted to put some on.
Since it's a little awkward on just one side.
Always be healthy.  I love you.
-Okay.  Thank you.
-Me too.
-Jae Suk, I love you.
-Yes, I love you too.
[Look at what he's doing to hide his weakness]
Always be happy.
-Always be healthy...
-Thank you.
-Congratulations on the 100 episodes.
-Goodbye.
[Using extreme irony to pass
this awkward and uncomfortable moment]
-Goodbye...
-Yes, goodbye.
[Wait...]
[Since we're already both here...
Try shooting the arrow?]
[Do I have to shoot them on their name tag?]
-Oh my... Goodbye...
-Goodbye...
[Since the weapon doesn't seem to work...]
Goodbye...
-Goodbye...
-Yes...
-I'll see you again sometime...
-Yes, we'll have a meal together.
[Ending with a polite goodbye from both]
To Jae Suk's VJ too, goodbye...
What was that?
As long as I don't get this taken from me,
there's no way I'll get ousted.
There's no way I could die
as long as I don't get this taken from me.
What do we do?
How in the world did we become
weak human beings like this?
[The 2 weak humans heading into
the blacksmith shop]
Hey.  These could be the weapons
that we can use to kill the gods!
You really think that
they would be knives like these?
Hey... But this is where the weapons are made.
One of these weapons could be used
to kill the gods!
Why is there an umbrella here?
[This is where Jae Suk found the arrows!]
[He couldn't possibly...]
Let's go.  This is the only way for us to
stand up to the Gods.
-Jong Kook... This is Running Man.
-I can't calm down.
-Jong Kook... Come back to your senses.
-This is the only way we can beat the Gods.
-Kwang Soo!  This is our only way!
-Enough!
Jong Kook, don't do it... Please...
Put that down.
-I seriously...!
-Enough!  Enough!
-Calm down...
-I seriously...
-Let's get out of here.
-Remember where this room is.
[Wanting to be Mr. Capable]
[Upset at having to be a normal human being]
[Uh!  It's Ji Hyo]
What is that, Jae Suk?
-That's Cupid's bow?
-Yeah.
Love...
[After his run in with Eros...]
Why's your face like that?
-I see that Ha Ha got you...!
-Yeah, I did.
-Ji Hyo... You got something?
-I don't have anything.
-I think you do.
-No, I don't have anything.
[Water gun?]
[Why is Ji Hyo hiding the water gun...?]
What the heck?
Why's this here?
Jae Suk...
[Wait... This is...!]
[God of the water guns Poseidon,
your weakness is water]
[I, Poseidon Jae Suk's weakness is water...]
-You watch yourself...
-Why did this have to fall out now?
-I wonder why that fell down?
-No kidding...
Maybe for me to shoot you?
No...
[Athena Ji Hyo,
attacking Poseidon Jae Suk!]
[Ace Ji Hyo, ready in thinking that water gun-loving
Jae Suk's weakness may be water!
[An unforgiving sprint!]
I almost died...
Wow... Song Ji Hyo in the back...
I never knew her laughter could be so scary.
I have to avoid Song Ji Hyo now...
I have to avoid her.
[Ji Hyo knows what my weakness is!
Escape her by any means...]
Ji Hyo...
[Secretly calling Ji Hyo off to the side...]
Are you a goddess?
Me?
-I wanted to give you a tip...
-I'm the goddess of war.
-Goddess of war?
-Athena.
Is it okay for me to give this to her?
[Hee Sun...
The weapon that she found earlier...!]
[If you tear off the target dolls'
name tag off, they're out]
[However, you have to make sure to
do it while they're watching]
[Ji Hyo's name tag is gotten rid of...
What is the effect of this?]
[Huh?  There are no effects...!]
-This is...
-It's a gift.
[Hee Sun, seeing there are no effects,
trying to end things in a rush]
-I think you're my life's benefactor.
-Keep this a secret, okay?
I understand...
[It doesn't work for Ji Hyo...
Then who?]
[What is that?]
There's...something there?
What is that?
[A suspicious looking box!]
[Huh?  A loofah?]
[Direction of usage]
[If you erase the carved signs on your
target's body, they're out]
[Which God's weakness is the mark?]
-What is that?
[The target of the previous God's
weapon discovered]
-What are you doing, we're on the same side?
-Yeah, we're on the same side.
-Let's not do things amongst us.
-Okay.
-Truce... This is truce?
-Okay, truce.
You're not going to die even
if we tear it off anyways.
[But the truth that
Hermes doesn't know about...!]
-Gary... Gary, are you Poseidon?
-No. I told you earlier.
Are you Athena then?
Do you see that water over there?
I think someone dies if they get in the water.
Do you want to dunk Suk Jin in there?
-Ah, the weakness?
-Yeah.
[There's something in the water pool...!
First, Suk Jin..]
[Hermes Suk Jin's weakness is alter ego...
Will this...?]
-It totally gave me the chills...
-So Jong Kook is Hercules?
[Moving towards the water pool]
[Grabbing him...and moving to the water!]
[Dunking Hermes Suk Jin in the water!]
Why isn't he dying?
[The 2 Gods who had thought Suk Jin's
weakness is water get flustered]
How can you guys do this?
-Hey!
-Why isn't he dying?
So he's not Poseidon?  He's not Poseidon...
[Just then!]
[Just in time carrying her doll weapon!]
Suk Jin... This is yours!
Suk Jin...!
[A doll?  That couldn't possibly...!]
Suk Jin... This is yours...!
[Gets rid of Suk Jin doll's name tag!]
[God of the underworld Suk Jin,
your weakness is alter ego!]
This is yours...!
[Hermes Suk Jin's weakness is alter ego!]
[The doll was none other than his alter ego!]
What the heck?!
[Ji Suk Jin, out.  Ji Suk Jin, out]
[Hermes Suk Jin-out!]
-Ji Suk Jin... Out.
-We were right!  He was Poseidon!
[The two thinking Suk Jin is out because
he's been dunked in the water!]
-I just nailed it... I just nailed it!
-How did you know that?
Suk Jin's Poseidon!
Death in the water, my butt...
What a joke...
-Jae Suk.
-Yeah?
Without even knowing myself...
I just dunked Suk Jin in the water...
-I just thought that maybe...
-You ousted him?
-Gary and I pushed him into the water...
-Yeah?
And he's out. He was Poseidon.
Suk Jin is Poseidon?
[The real Poseidon pretending not to know]
See that over there?
If 3 Gods gather around and ring that bell...
-Then the human world comes to a stop.
-Really?
[If 3 Gods gather and ring the bell,
then the human world stops]
[Bell of times]
[If 3 Gods gather and ring the bell,
then the human world shall come to a stop]
If 3 Gods gather and ring the bell,
then the human world stops.
-Really?
-Yeah.
If we were to rip it off of Jong Kook...
-How else are we going to get Jong Kook?
-We can't.
Then we all gather and ring that bell to stop
the human time, and rip it off of Jong Kook.
-Then let's just ring the bell.
-Who is that?  We need to get one more God.
[On the other hand, the 2 humans
oblivious to the Gods' conspiracy]
[Discovering something in the bushes!]
Come here, come here...
This is dangerous but open it.
-What does the seal say?
-Out!
[Discovered the out weapon of the Gods.
-This is how we can oust the Gods?
[Direction of usage]
[If you imprint the seal on the target's
bare foot, then that target is ousted]
Who's the target?
-Is someone designated for this?
-Ultimately, it's all up to you and I.
And if something happens to the humans...
You hold on to this.
So once I grab the person,
you can do the imprinting.
[Just which God's barefoot does the
seal have to be imprinted on...?]
I think the seal is for Gary,
no matter how I think about it.
[Pandora's box has just been released]
Pandora's box?
[If the Pandora's box is opened,
the world will be thrown into chaos!]
[The Pandora's box containing all the Gods'
weakness has now been released]
[If the Pandora's box is opened]
[All the Gods' weakness's are revealed!]
Let's find the box quickly!
We have to get rid of it.
Bu that's something that
we can know about each other.
[The weaknesses that should be kept a secret
can become point of target!]
If the Pandora' box gets opened up,
then there's going to be chaos.
[The Pandora's box containing all the Gods'
weakness has now been opened]
The box has all their weaknesses in it.
[If the humans open up the Pandora's box,
they can find out about the Gods' weaknesses]
Then we can find out who's weak to the seal.
Even if we don't have to try it
with every God that we come across...
The same thing with that.
-We have to find the Pandora's box!
-I know.
Pandora's box...
We have to find the Pandora's box.
[Hee Sun holding onto the weapons that
Hermes Suk Jin had found]
What is that now?
If you wrap this around your ankle,
you can have one more life.
Such a lie.
Come on... What are you talking about?
Have another life with this shackled?
-Hee Sun... It's already obvious...
-No, no...!
-No...
-Come on, I'm not lying...!
-No... That's not it...!
-Okay, okay...
-You're trying to kill me.
-No, I'm not.  Why don't you trust me?
What is this?
[No effects!]
-Jae Suk, you're all done.
-What is that?
Hee Sun, how are you carrying this around
when it's so heavy?
What's that?
I'm sure something was written on it.
Something's written on there?
-Why are you being like this?
-Are you okay?
I'm okay.
-I feel like Dumb and Dumber.
-You tried both of these on me.
I got scared when I saw my face.
Pandora's box is open?
Over there...
There are humans over there... Humans.
There are people over there.
[Eros finally discovers the humans!]
[Discovering each other!]
[The 2 humans locking the door]
These humans are trying to find
the Pandora's box...
-Are you searching for the Pandora's box?
-What?
-Pandora's box?
-No.
What do you mean no, I see that you are!
[The 2 humans looking like they're not
going to budge from where they are]
-We won't touch you.
-Jae Suk... Jae Suk...
-At a time like this... Let's ring the bell.
-Should we ring the bell?
[If 3 Gods together ring the bell,
the human world comes to a stop!]
-At a time like this... Let's ring the bell.
-Should we ring the bell?
[If they do this now,
they may be able to get Jong Kook!]
-You go...
-Just stay here then.
-Hurry, hurry!
-Hurry up and ring the bell! Ring the bell!
-Ggong Ju!
-Where are you going?
-Hurry up and come... The bell!
-Really?  Gong to ring the bell?
-Hee Sun!
-You're going to ring the bell?
[If the Aphrodite joins them,
that's exactly 3 people!]
Bell!  Bell!  Bell!
After getting him to come out...
Jae Suk, are you ready?
Ring it now, now!  Now!  Now!
[Getting ready to run once the
atmosphere has gotten strange]
[The 2 humans escape!]
[If they don't stop the time now,
they may never be able to catch them!]
Ring it!!
Hey!  Hurry!  Hurry!  Hurry!
Ji Hyo!  Hurry!
[The 3 Gods in a panic]
[This is the chance to stop the time!]
[The bell of the Gods, it's ringing!]
We did it, we rang the bell!
I think they'll be able to get them...
[As the bell rings...
The human world's time stops...]
[Human Kwang Soo also in his place...]
This...
[Handing over the seal weapon...]
[First taking the seal weapon...]
I'm not going to move.  Wait, wait!
Wait, wait!
[Getting rid of human Kwang Soo tag!]
I even gave these to you...
-How could you do this to me?
-Kwang Soo...
This is 100th special episode...
100th special episode...
All my relatives are gathered watching....
-Kwang Soo... I have no other choice.
-Why me...?
I have to stay alive...
Kwang Soo...
Great job with all the past episodes.
[But still not forgetting the friendship]
[Jae Suk... Don't be like this...
Just let me slap you once when we're done]
[Not that...
Just let me slap you once after recording]
I'm so annoyed with you right now,
I feel like I'm going to go crazy.
-Please...
-Fine.
[Anyways... Human Kwang Soo-Out!]
I give you permission.
[Once a human being has been captured,
the human world starts to move again]
What's going on?
[Eros loses Human Jong Kook]
I don't know about this...
This is just becoming a baggage carrying it.
[The truth is this is the weapon that could've
worked on Kwang Soo had he been a God]
God or not...
How is this being a God?
All I do is walk around!
Isn't this a water room?
A room of beverages or something?
[Heading to the beverage room out of thirst]
What kind of God is thirsty like this...
And feels so hungry from just running...
How is this being a God?
Getting tired and sleepy from walking...
Here it is...
[Finally discovers the beverage room!]
[Something among the boxes...?]
Be quiet... Quiet.
Is there anyone around?
Come here, come here.
[Athena is nearby...]
[Thirsty Eros also to the beverage room...]
Ugh.. So thirsty.
Let's find the Pandora's box first.
[As if nothing's going on...]
We have to fight amongst ourselves too.
Okay, I got it.
Okay I got it...
From all the running... I'm too tired.
You found something, didn't you?
I haven't found anything.
I really haven't found anything.
-Ah... I know you just found something.
-No, I didn't.  I'm serious.
[Discovered the Pandora's box!]
[Inside the box is everyone's weakness...!]
Let's look at it together!
You just stay right there for now.
[Song Ji Hyo's weakness revealed!]
[Athena... Song Ji Hyo's weakness is ankles]
What did he say?
[With the Pandora's box being opened,
weaknesses are revealed!]
Aphrodite... Aphrodite has it.
[The shackles Aphrodite has is the weapon!]
Aphro... Aphrodite!
[You're saying Athena Ji Hyo's weakness
is her ankles?]
[Soon thereafter,
Apollo discovers another Pandora's box!]
[What if it's my weakness being announced?]
[Ha Ha's weakness revealed!]
[As if they've made an appointment...
Here of all places...]
Why don't you show it to me?
[Eros Ha Ha's weakness is kiss]
You come here!
[At last, the real battle between the Gods]
You can't do it to me now!
We have to kill the human! The human!
The human! Kill the human!
[Everyone trying to find the Pandora's box]
[Also here!]
[Gary's weakness revealed!]
[Apollo Gary's weakness is the mark]
I'm here.
-We can't kill each other for now.
-Why?
-Where is it Aphrodite?  Where is it?
-What?
-The shackles... The shackles.
-I'll take care of Ji Hyo.
But right now... How can you hide that?
No... I just left it for a moment
because it was heavy.
-How did you know it was Ji Hyo?
-I just did..
I've already got it all down.
Let's get rid of Jong Kook first...
Then take care of Ji Hyo and Ha Ha...
-Then as for us...
-What's Ha Ha's?
-Kiss?
-They said kiss.
I kissed him earlier.
Did you just kiss him?
Lipstick!
Ha Ha has it!
You have to kiss him with the lipstick on!
-Does that mean a girl has to do it?
-That's not it...
[Huh???]
[Your personality is hot...
but that's not what it means]
-I just licked my lips...
-That's not what I meant!
It doesn't mean that a girl has to do it,
but there's a special lipstick for it.
Several of us has to work together.
I'll be going for now.
Wait... Aphrodite...
-Ji Hyo... What are you doing?
-What?
[Athena Ji Hyo getting ready for
the battle with her water gun]
[Just in case... I'm getting the water gun
ammunition ready for the battle]
But Ji Hyo... What is Hee Sun's weakness?
I told Gary this...
But is it the mirror?  The mirror maybe?
Hee Sun was carrying
the mirror around earlier...
[It's now!]
Could it be she has to look at her own face?
[Left unprotected]
What do you mean, look at her own face?
Jae Suk...
[Athena's weakness is... Ankles!]
[The shackle around Athena's ankles...!]
Jae Suk... Unbelievable.
Song Ji Hyo, Out.
[Athena Ji Hyo-Perfect plan succeeds!]
Jae Suk... Jae Suk, thank you!
Ji Hyo... I love you!
-Hee Sun!
Ji Hyo... You're so pretty!
You really look amazing in person!
I love you!
-Jae Suk...
-Yeah?
What did you get after you killed Kwang Soo?
Well... I got this seal.
-This seal...
-But I don't know what it is.
Did Kwang Soo tell me to imprint Gary's foot?
What was it that he said?
You have to imprint it on a bare foot...
-But that's not how you kill them.
-Then what?
-I have to rub it off with this for him to die.
-What did you say?
So there's some kind of a mark on Gary?
Where is he right now?
Then this isn't meant for Gary's foot?
Right?  This isn't Gary's foot.
You can't be looking at me like that.
His is a kiss...
[The more he thinks about it,
the target for the seal is Aphrodite]
-Wait Jae Suk...
-Hee Sun... Is it you?
No way...
Then where am I supposed to use this?
Gary's foot!
[You just said it wasn't just a bit ago...]
But how is this exposure?
[Big trouble...
I have to be cautious now...]
[Human Jong Kook who escaped earlier
when the time came to a stop]
[Meeting with Poseidon Jae Suk?]
-Jae Suk!
-What?
[Why are they so glad?]
Use me...!
-You can't win this by yourself...
-Jong Kook...
How are you going to do this alone?
I will dedicate myself to you as a human.
-Are you being serious?
-I'm being real.
[Human Jong Kook dedicating himself
to Poseidon Jae Suk?]
Anyways, tell me quickly.  Quickly.
[Everyone gathering
before they can even make a pact]
We have to shut the door first...
We have to shut the door.
-What's Ha Ha's?
-It's a kiss.
[When did they join forces?]
[Shall I join forces with human Jong Kook?]
[Convincing him to join forces
with his human self]
I will join hands with you.
Ha Ha... You can't.
Wake up!
[A God mesmerized by a human?]
Wake up... You can't, Ha Ha.
I will suppress
the other Gods with my strength.
I understand...
Then why don't we kill this one first?
-Shall we?
-Why don't we throw him in the pool first?
-Shall I?
-Yes.
Then he is... Poseidon?
Yes, I think he is.
Ha Ha, you can't!
[The awful Eros sticking right by
human Jong Kook's side]
-Are you going to betray me like this?
-I'm going to shut the door for now.
Shut the door? Seriously...
[Starting to negotiate with human Jong Kook]
-He has the lipstick...
-He has the lipstick?
Me?
-But the winning...
-You think about it carefully.
After hearing the announcement,
I know his weakness...
And I know very well what effect
the lipstick has on him.
But I won't die even if I get
thrown into the pool.  Jong Kook...
Let's easily oust a person.
Search him.
Jong Kook... Come here.
[Ha Ha doing his best
to convince Jong Kook too]
[Searching for the lipstick
starting with the pocket]
Wait... Just wait a second...
-What are you doing?
-Jae Suk!  Here it is!
Here it is!
[Discovered the lipstick weapon!]
Come on now... That's not going to work.
[Once Eros is kissed by someone with the
lipstick on then he is ousted!]
[Violent rebellion]
Look at you go!
For you in a very long time...!
I will put my pink lipstick on...!
Wait... Just wait a minute...
Just wait...
Oh my... Seriously!
[Eros weakness, lipstick kiss-A success!]
Nice going!
He's out?
[Eros-Out!]
[And... A homework that hasn't been solved]
Wait... Be honest with me.
Tell me.  Hurry.
[Others don't know Jae Suk's a Poseidon yet]
Hurry... Be honest with me.  What are you?
-Be honest with me... Hurry!
-I'm... Cupid.
-You're not!
-How is Cupid a God?
-I'm Cupid... I'm Cupid...
-Is Cupid a God?
He's not a fairy?  A fairy?
Ah... That's Tinkerbelle?
Seriously... I don't get it.
[Cupid=Eros]
[Jae Suk in trouble trying to
keep his identity hidden]
Fine... Then... You're saying you'll
believe me if I'm dunked in water?
-Yes, show us.
-Fine.
[You're telling me to go in the water...]
You have to go all the way in it.
[My weakness is water...
What do I do about this?]
I'm not Poseidon.
If I were, then I'd be ousted once
I dip my foot in there.
-What are you doing?
-Do it.
I told you, I'm Cupid!
[It's either death, or bluffing!]
None of you seem to believe me...
[He's in the water!]
[He's okay even though he's in the water?]
This isn't going to get me ousted!
Try sitting down.
Do it just once!
-Try it once...
-There!
[Even kneeling, he's okay?]
I told you, I won't get ousted!
Try laying down.
Do it just once.
-You're being too much...
-You're not Poseidon?
-You're really not?
-I told you that I'm not.
I've done all this and I'm still not ousted!
You just saw for yourself!
[Jae Suk is Poseidon, and his weakness water.
But still nothing...?]
-There!
-Sit down in there completely!
Sit down in there completely!
[Huh?  All of a sudden, that's...!]
What's that?
[Jong Kook is all of a sudden adding
something to the water!]
[Just what could that be?]
[Before everyone met up, human Jong Kook
doggedly searching for the weapons!]
[Inside it...
Is this God's weapon, the water elixir!]
[Direction of usage]
[After adding this to the pool water,
if the target gets dumped, he's ousted]
[However, the name tag has to get wet
for it to be acknowledged]
[Jong Kook is using the elixir
that he had kept hidden away]
-What is that?
-What's that?
[Human Jong Kook pretending to go for Jae Suk
but attacking Gary!]
-What is that?
-What the heck is that?
[Hee Sun getting ready
to get rid of the mark!]
[The temporary tattoo is the mark!]
[If it gets erased with the loofah,
Apollo is out!]
What did you say?
-You're not out.
-Why?
[Poseidon isn't out?]
[Well... In that case...]
What the heck?
[Poseidon gets rid of
human Jong kook's name tag]
-He says I'm not out.
-You're not out?
He says I'm not out...
What did you add in here?
-That's the elixir!
-What are you doing right now?
I got tired...
-What have you been doing then?
-Jae Suk isn't out!
He says I'm not out...
Gary, he says I'm not out!
-Really?
-What is this elixir?
[After adding this to the pool water,
if the target gets dumped, he's ousted]
[However, the name tag has to get wet
for it to be acknowledged]
for it to be acknowledged...]
[It didn't get wet!]
[Oh yeah...!]
What is this elixir then?
[Kim Jong Kook, Out]
I'm out?
[At last... The human Jong Kook meets his end]
-What about Gary?
-I still have some left on here.
-This can't mean that I'm out.
-Grab him Jae Suk... Go grab him.
Grab him.  I haven't gotten it all off.
-Come on, hurry...
-That's not it...
Wait... Wait!
[Huh!  Poseidon fell in the water!]
[Wow... But the name tag still didn't get wet!]
-Gary!  Grab Aphrodite!  Grab her!
-Aphrodite!
-Aphrodite...
-Grab her...!
Where did the seal go?!
[The out seal is missing!]
The seal!  Where did the seal go?!
[He did find the lettering portion...]
The red stamping ink!
Where did the red stamping ink go?
[Huh?  That is...?  Lipstick!]
[Instead of red stamping ink, lipstick!]
[Aphrodite's weakness is exposure!
The out seal on her bare foot!]
[Can't even see the lettering...]
[Stamping chaos... A success!]
If I didn't have this,
it would've been big trouble.
[With Ha Ha's weapon, the lipstick...]
Aphrodite, I'm sorry.
[Aphrodite-Out!]
I'm sorry... I thought I was out...
-But I'm told that I'm not out.
-So this is what it feels like to be taken.
[Tough Goddess of Beauty]
But I got Gary's mark all off!
-Aphrodite...
-I got it all off!
There's some left... There's some left.
[There's some left!]
If you're going to take this off,
you're going to need water.
This isn't just going to get off easily.
What are you doing?!
[The final showdown!]
See if it's been rubbed off!  Look!
There's still some left!
[Taking Poseidon Jae Suk to the water!]
[Utter chaos]
[Battle of the Gods...
Just how will it end?]
-Look!  Look here... Come look at this!
-I got his name wet!
You're going to take my skin off!
[Gary, out.  Gary, out]
[Right before the utter chaos]
[Already... Clean!]
[Poseidon Yoo Jae Suk, the ultimate winner]
[Apollo's fierce protest]
Aphrodite!
[The appearance of the winning God]
What is this?  Just what is this?!
I have never imagined that I would win
until the game was actually over.
Luck just follows you around.
It follows you around.
The Gods were on my side.
Everyone, thank you!
[The Battle of the Gods,
The winner is Poseidon Jae Suk!]
[A prize worthy of his winning...]
[The golden Holy Grail]
I want it!
You always take all the prizes!
[Winner of 100th Running Man,
Yoo Jae Suk]
Yes... Today's win...
Our 100th guest...
The one who did her best...
-I watched her from the side.
-Just stand still!
-Just wait a minute!
-Just stand still until he gives it to you.
My winning trophy today...
I will give it to Aphrodite!
[A sign of appreciation to Aphrodite!]
Congratulations!
And more than anything else...
Aphrodite Hee Sun that came out today
to help us celebrate our 100th episode...
And to everyone else who did
the past 100 episodes with us sincerely...
We thank you once again!
Thank you!
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Running Man's gold theft!]
[CSI investigation team,
gathered to help solve the case]
[Using the state of the art investigation,
solve the case!]
The person we have to find is Ji Hyo!
Where did she go?!
[The desperate chase of the armed forces!]
[What is the big meaning behind the incident?]
[CSI: Gold theft incident]