Spy mission.  You're the spy.
You have to oust the members
of Running Man.
And there's one other thing that
will help you on your spy mission.
That is... You can scout someone.
[With the money you win during the missions,
you can recruit one member as fellow spy]
[Park Ji Sung Spy Mission-Start!]
[Ji Sung still hasn't decided
who is going to recruit as his fellow spy]
Hey IU.  Are any of these guys an oppa?
(An affectionate way to call an older boy/man)
-Ha Ha oppa.
-Ha Ha is an oppa? What about Kwang Soo?
-Kwang Soo is an oppa too.
-What about Jong Kook?  And me?
-I'm not bad too, right?
-What about Ji Sung?
Park Ji Sung is a 'Sir'.
Park Ji Sung...
Do you have a tattoo on your arm?
No.  It's a marker.
[The reality of what the other's were
talking about... Magic marker]
[It got on the arm while he was signing
autographs at the market]
-Kim Jong Kook, please come out here.
-What?
Kim Jong Kook, please come on out.
Excuse me? You want me to come out?
Why are you doing this?
[It's finally starting...]
It's personal... It's because Kim Jong Kook and
Park Ji Sung have to go up against each other.
That's no good.
Ji Sung...
Please make sure to rip his name off.
That's our wish.
The race will start now.
What? You're saying it's starting now?!
What about our clothes?
You mean dressed like this?
Honestly, the only person who can tear the
name off Ji Sung's back is Lee Kwang Soo.
I won't tear yours off,
so please don't tear mine off.
Seriously, Lee Kwang Soo...
Lee Kwang Soo and Ha Ha...
[Who should I pick as my fellow spy
among this group...?]
Where is this place?
You want me to go in here?
[Huh? The head PD is inside?]
Ah.. Seriously...
[What's the memorable mission that he has
in store for Running Men?]
[Current mission... Huh?]
Huh? This is a question mark?
What is this?
It means that the mission information is
written on the inside of someone's name tag.
Then what?
The mission itself is written on the inside of
someone's name tag..
And you have to tear off that someone's
name tag to find out today's mission.
[If you look at the various hints hidden,
you can find out the identity of that person]
Find the hints... And find out who...
So that's how we find out...?
So it could be on my back too?
[Even the person who has it doesn't know
if it's on their back or not]
But, Park Ji Sung...
If you get to tear off that
person's name tag and find out...
Inside that tag...
It says 'Find out who the spy is'.
And your spy mission is...
[Oust the members of Running Men!]
Spy Mission.  You're the spy.
Oust the members of Running Man.
['Spy' Park Ji Sung vs.
Running Man 'Oblivious to the mission']
-Who's the spy?
-Me.
It's you, right?  The ultimate winner is
the one that finds you out and ousts you.
-You understand, right?
-Yes.
Therefore, before you get found out,
you have to find a partner and oust the others.
You have earned a total of 3,500 Baht
during the psychic soccer yesterday.
And from the other morning missions,
you have earned 15,000 Baht.
So in total, you have earned a total
of 18,500 Baht.
Seriously... There's no way I can afford
Kim Jong Kook and Song Ji Hyo.
[The fee for big timers are expensive]
Just like you said earlier...
-In that case...
-Yes.
['Spy Ji Sung...]
[Has scouted someone as his fellow spy]
[Along with the fellow spy...]
[oust all the members of Running Man
before his identity is compromised]
I'll do my best to oust the other members
of Running Man. Fighting!
[Spy]
['Spy' Ji Sung exits after scouting
his fellow spy]
[Just who did he scout...]
This is a big problem.
Where do I find the person?
[Get rid of the person with the mission
statement on their backs first!]
I wonder they have it hidden?
[Lee Kwang Soo... 5,000 Baht]
-Did you find anything?
-No, I haven't found anything.
-What?
-If I find the hint, I'll come to you first.
Okay.
[Did Ji Sung scout this person?]
Maybe I'll check out this way.  Huh?!
Park Ji sung!
[Gary-8,000 Baht]
-By any chance... Did you find anything?
-Me?  The hint?
-I think Jae Suk found it.
-Really? I think you're lying.
[Gary acting like his price tag...]
Always watch your back.
-Don't trust anyone!
-Okay.
I'm going to be an angel!
[Could Gary be the fellow spy that's
been scouted by Ji Sung?]
[The fellow spy doesn't even know yet
that they've been recruited]
[By any chance... Is it one of those?]
-It'll probably have the 'R' marker on it?
-Let's look inside.
[Took a hundred years off of Ha Ha's life]
[These Running Men have no clue
that Ji sung is a spy yet]
[Anyways... Just who out of these
is Ji Sung's fellow spy...?]
[And a little bit later...]
[Ji Sung's secret fellow spy...]
[After finding out the truth that they've been
scouted, slowly starting the approach...]
[The two finally meets!]
[Why me? Why did you make me a spy?!]
[I recruited you because you looked
like you'd make a good spy]
[Just what is going on? Hurry up and tell me.
I'm so nervous right now!]
[I have no idea what to do right now,
that's why we're meeting!]
[Do we have to find something in this
situation right now?  Or...]
[Should we tear someone's name off?]
[I don't think we should tear anything
off yet... For now...]
[I think we need to find out for sure
who it is first]
[Let's gather up the hints and find out
who that person is for sure...]
[And we can oust that person]
[A momentary relief will be our downfall.
Please don't let your guard down]
[If the mission statement on
someone's back is revealed,
then their spy identities will be compromised!]
[Find out who has the mission on their back
and oust the person without others knowing!]
[On the other hand... The members that have
no idea that a spy exists...]
What is it?  I wonder what it looks like?
[Huh? A strange piece of paper]
[The hint!]
[This hint will reveal who has the mission
hidden underneath their name tag!]
Is it me?
[Running Man member with the
mission hidden on their back!]
[Find the spy]
Thank you.
[The one with the mission on their back...
Song Ji Hyo!]
Is it me?
It could be Song...
Or it could be 'Song' as in singing.
[It's 'Song' as in Song Ji Hyo...]
These days...
We really have to be thorough.
[Now masters at looking for things
in every nook and cranny]
Before someone else gets here...
I have to find it.
[The hint!]
[Just what could be on this hint paper?]
[Single]
['Song' and 'Single'. These are
all hints pointing out Song Ji Hyo]
Did you find it or not?
-No, I haven't.
-Come here, Suk Jin.
-Suk Jin. You found it, right?
-What?
He hasn't found it yet.
He said we should tear your name off.
[Kwang Soo setting up a trap
for the first time in awhile]
-Suk Jin said we should tear your name off.
-Mine?
-Is there even a hint?
-I seriously don't have it.
-You really haven't found it?
-Really... I'm being serious.
-I told you, I seriously don't have it.
-Where do you keep your mike?
-[He really wants to take me out?]
-[Yes, Jong Kook]
[Tiger and Giraffe ousts Suk Jin]
Jong Kook, there's something on the back!
-What the heck?
-I heard you wanted to take me out...!
Who did?
[But it looks like there's something on back?]
-Race can start!
[The back of Suk Jin's back...]
Is that really written on the back?
[It was stuck on the back just in case,
and ultimately...]
Race... Start!
[The race starter that alerts everyone]
-But seriously... Why did you say that?
-Suk Jin...
He seriously is...
[Kwang Soo getting an early start]
[Is he starting to oust them because
he's Ji Sung's partner?]
Ji Suk Jin... Out.
Suk Jin being ousted means
that the real game has now started.
[For some reason, IU seems very nervous]
Why are you being so nervous?
Don't be surprised by this.
[IU starts to attack Jae Suk!]
[Why did IU attack Jae Suk
all of a sudden like that?]
[By any chance, is she Ji Sung's partner?]
I wonder who and why someone tore
the name off of Suk Jin's back?
I wonder if he was had without
any reason again?
[It's welcome since Ji Sung has
to oust everyone anyways]
[A gathering of people in front of Ji Sung...]
[Among those... Ace Ji Hyo!]
[Ji Hyo, who was too expensive to recruit...
Should he oust her at this chance?]
[Wait...! Mr. Capable...!]
[The one who was too expensive to recruit...!]
[The one he has to make sure
to oust sometime...!]
[Now... If it's now...]
I just wanted to touch it once.
-I just wanted to touch it once.
-Just where did you come from?!
-I just wanted to touch it...
-You really scared me!
This is seriously...!
-Did you find the hint?
-Is it a piece of paper?
[Let's find the hint together for now]
-Ji Hyo.
-You scared me!
Ji Hyo, come over here.
Ji Hyo, we have to work together.
I found it.
[You found it?]
You have the hint?
Inside. Let's go inside.
[Going somewhere where others can't see]
-Everyone has found one so far.
-Really?
[What if Mr. Capable and Ace finds out
the mission before me like this?]
[The hint that Ji Hyo found... 'Song']
[Actually, it's 'Song' of Song Ji Hyo,
but what is Jong Kook's take?]
-It's a song...
-It is, right?
It's a song, right?
I thought it meant 'Song', as in my name.
[It is you...]
But I don't it's that simple.  Right?
It's a song.  When we were all gathered
downstairs earlier... And I saw Gary...
And I got a strange feeling.
[Now she's suspecting Gary?]
I think it's Gary.
But I think if we found one more,
we'll be able to figure it out.
-Be honest... Did you find anything?
-I haven't found anything! I promise.
-You seriously haven't found anything?
-No, I haven't.
I'm being serious. Here, I'll show you.
[He's even flipping his pockets inside out]
No, that's okay.
-Take off your shoes.
-Okay.
[I need to go find something
on my own quickly too...]
How do I find it?
This isn't it, right?
It has 'R' stuck on it...
I'm sure it's stuck on something.
[He really is searching everywhere]
[The personality of always
seeing things through]
How did they find it so easily?
I wonder if I'm searching
in all the wrong places?
Hello.
They always hide it in the most
unlikeliest places...
I wonder if they're watching me
and laughing right now?
Wondering why I'm doing this...
Airport... This looks like an airport.
How do they expect us to find it
in such a big place like this?
This is really...
None of the other members are here.
There's IU.
Where's IU? Hey, be careful of IU.
[The girl who's face may change at
any moment and lunge after you]
Why are you looking at Ha Ha's back?
-You said we were on the same team.
-We are on the same team.
IU, where are you going?
[Fiery glint in her eye]
Does she have something?
Did you purposely act like you're tired?
No... I don't have anything like that.
I think you were purposely acting
like you were tired this morning...
[IU is definitely acting strange...?]
I know you found it.  Show us.
-I didn't find anything.
-Let's join forces.
You found it? Really? You did?
-Let me see it.
-I had mine taken away by Jong Kook.
-Really?
-What was it?
I'm sure you know what it is...
Come on now... Hey!
Look at that.  I knew it.
-Let's work together.
-I see everyone found something.
[The exhausted Ji Sung also joins
after all his searching]
Come on, let me see it!
[IU's hint... At least 160 cm]
-Then Ha Ha... And IU are out...
-I'm 161!
Then it doesn't narrow anything down!
[The gathering of hints could get dangerous]
[I think we need to oust them one by one
where no one can see first]
[Everyone is all huddled together...]
[You have to make sure to do it well
where there's no one around]
-Nothing here.
-Ji Hyo!
-Have you found anything else?
-No.
Really?  Then maybe Ha Ha found it?
-Earlier, Ha Ha...
-Ha Ha was hanging out earlier.
maybe he was just pretending
that he didn't have it earlier.
I think you guys are suspicious of me.
Oh my gosh! You scared me!
[Captain Park, scaring a lot of people today]
I thought it was one of the staff members
next to me... You scared me!
-That's crazy!
-What are you doing up there?
-You seriously haven't found anything?
-Yes. I can't find it.
The hint IU found is this.
But the hint makes no sense...
Come here, Ji Sung.
Please don't run! You scared me!
This... That it's at least 160 cm.
That makes no sense!
Is Ha Ha 160 cm?
It definitely could be Ha Ha...
['Song' 'Single' '160 cm'
Everyone thinks it's Ha Ha]
[Tsk tsk... Actually, it's this person...]
-Kwang Soo!
-It really isn't me!
-Ha Ha... Ha Ha...
-Hurry up and come over here.
[Ha Ha chooses this moment to show]
-I told you I really don't have it!
-Hand it over and work with us!
-I don't have it.
-Hurry up and hand it over.
What do you me to give you
when I don't have anything?
-Here. Search me.
-You could've thrown it out somewhere.
You could have hidden it somewhere too.
[Now everyone suspects that Ha Ha is the
one with the mission attached to his back]
-I'm telling you, I really don't have it!
-Look, IU's hand it already back there.
Look at IU... Her hand is already on the tag!
[If anything, Ha Ha is suspecting
Jong Kook who's approaching him]
When you were the spy,
none of us had any idea of it!
IU's staring at your back now.
[IU eyeing Jong Kook's back this time]
-She is really funny!
-When someone approaches her, she screams...!
But if someone turns their back,
she attacks like this.
She really is scary!
Anyways,
I don't think 'Song' means Song Ji Hyo.
That's just way too simple!
[It really is 'song'...]
I really don't have it!  Don't have it!
I'm sure there's something here...
[Gary looking for a hint
far away from everyone...]
Wait!
There it is!
[A hint!]
Hurry!  Did you get it?
You want down?
[Just what is in this piece of paper...?]
[Member hint... 'H'!]
[That's also 'Song Ji Hyo!']
Ji Sung!
-I found a hint!
-Where?
It's decisive!
-It's decisive!
-What is it?
H!!
H, H, H!  H!!
[The hint Gary found... H!]
Really?
[The person they all think of when
the alphabet 'H' is mentioned...?]
-Really?  H?
-Yes!
Hurry!  Hurry!
[IU the first to attack Ha Ha!]
[No one is thinking of Song Ji Hyo's
'H' for her 'Hyo...!']
[Maybe it really is Ha Ha?]
He can't be caught!
[Everyone cornering Ha Ha!]
No, it's not me!
It may not be me!  Bring that hint to me!
Bring the hint to me.
-H... it really is H!
[If that's revealed, he could be in trouble!]
-Hey, who found it?
-I just found it!
-Show us.  Let us see it.
-I can't.
-H... It really was H.
-Let us see it!
How can that be me?  Song Ji Hyo!
Song Ji Hyo.  Song Ji Hyo, 'H'.
[Even with the 'Song' and 'H'...]
No, it's not.
Why are you looking at me?
Why are you looking at me?!
Why does 'H' have to be me?
Then who else can 'H' be?  and 160 cm?
-And a singer too...
-But...
[Ha Ha takes this moment to escape
since he's in danger]
Hey!  I'll go upstairs.
[And Ji Hyo gets away with it again...]
Ah.  It's nice and cool up here.
-Jong Kook.
-Let's not do this, Ha Ha.
[Abandonment?]
Jong Kook...
By any chance...
'H' wouldn't mean one man, right?
[What the heck is this about now?]
I wasn't going to say this...
-What are you talking about, Jong Kook?
-Nothing.  Come over here.
Come on and let's get started.
What's going on there?
Hey, it's total chaos down there.
Get him!  Get Kwang Soo!
[On Ji Sung's persistence,
they're getting rid of Kwang Soo]
[Ji Sung gets rid of Kwang Soo's name tag]
There's something here.
Kwang Soo, you've got something.
[What do you mean, there's something?]
[Anyways, Ji Sung's starting to get rid of
members one by one]
Kwang Soo, I'm sorry.
Seriously... I'm really sorry.
[Now partner... Let's seriously start
getting them ousted!]
[Lee Kwang Soo, out]
Kwang Soo's out!
Why did they rip of Kwang Soo's?
It's not him!
Then what about you?!
-You're the thorn on my side!
-It's not like that.
Bro... Everything's pointing to you right now,
so what do I do?  I can't trust you.
Jae Suk. Why did you get rid of Kwang Soo?
Don't just tear anyone's off,
and cause problems.
Let's just go about it nicely...
What's with you, IU?
[They've come to get Ha Ha,
but IU approaches the first person she sees]
-And stop approaching me.
-Do you see what IU's doing?
[But IU's behavior definitely
has been weird since earlier]
[Is she... Ji Sung's partner?]
-Let's just rip it off now.
-No!  You can't do it!
[IU runs and latches on to Ha Ha's name tag!]
Wait... Come on, just wait.
[Ji Sung's on pins and needles worried that
'Find the spy' note is on Ha Ha's back]
Why don't you tell us first, Ha Ha.
[IU... Gets rid of Gary's nametag?!]
[Why not Ha Ha's, but Gary's?]
[Ha Ha takes this opportunity to run again!]
Get him!  Hey!
-What are you doing?!
-I thought it was Gary!
I thought for sure the 'H' stood
for Hee Gun! (Gary's given name).
I'm sorry.
[Gary is out!]
-But IU does make sense.
-I really thought he could be the one!
-I thought just in case...
-Yeah, his name is Hee Gun.
IU... How did you think to
rip off Gary's name back there?
Because... He was so insistent about the 'H'.
Why didn't you rip of Ha Ha's
when we were holding on to him?
I kept thinking the whole time
that it was Gary.
Don't you really think you're being too much?
Do we really have to go chasing after him
every time he runs away like this?
But she ripped off Gary's name.
She's here again.  There she is again.
-I!
-I'm holding onto him.
For last time...
so I can be Park Ji Sung's fan...
-Let's have Park Ji Sung catch me.
-Okay.  I'll catch you.
[Park Ji Sung vs. Ha Ha]
[Really?]
-You can catch him and tear it off too.
-Okay.
-Yes, I'll catch him.
-But you can't catch me, then that's it.
You can just do whatever you want with him.
Give me 2 seconds.
[Ha Ha gets a 2 second head start]
[Ha Ha... Do you really think
you can run away from Ji Sung?]
[The count seems awfully fast...]
[Full speed from the beginning!]
[Exactly... In 5 seconds, he's caught]
[Whew!
His spy identity hasn't been revealed!]
[There's nothing there!]
-There's nothing.  There's nothing.
-What?!
[Everyone was fully convinced that
it would be on Ha Ha's back]
[Is it... Me?]
He says there's nothing.
[All of a sudden, IU's suddenly...!]
There's nothing?
[IU finally realizes that it's Song Ji Hyo!]
[Finally!]
[The mission that was hidden on the back!]
[Find the spy!]
What is it?
-Find the spy.
-Find the spy!
-Who's the spy?
-It's not me, it's not me!
[The sudden chaos after
the mission is revealed!]
IU, you have to be careful.
[Only 4 left to the mission now]
Is this the rest now?
Hey!  It was Ji Hyo?
Why the 'H' then?
There's 'H' in Song Ji Hyo, you stupids!
How many times have I told you, you stupids?!
[One spy... And one partner of the spy!]
[And 2 innocent people...]
[Just who will be the ultimate winner?]
-This is really hard...
-Isn't it?
Because on the one side,
there's a big possibility that it's Ji Sung.
-But if you look at the behavior, it's her.
-No, it's not!
-It's totally IU!
-Who, me?  No, it's not!
Looking at the behavior... It's her!
[IU is suspicious of how she was
so eager to oust everyone...]
No, it's not me.
Just the feeling that I have...
-But... If he is the s... Spy...
-S...S... Spy?!
[Innocent Captain Park...
Stutters when lying?]
-Ji Sung... Don't be so nervous!
-I know.
No, it's because I'm afraid of him.
If Kim Jong Kook isn't the spy,
then it's no problem.
But if he is the spy,
it'll be hard for 2 people to oust him.
-But it's a relief there are 3 of us.
-What he said is right.
That's so true!
[Nice leading!]
It's just that...
If you hadn't said that,
she may have gone to you to rip yours off.
Why are you coming this way again?
[As soon as she hears,
IU locks in on her target]
Why are you coming again? Seriously!
IU is always 2 steps ahead
of what we're thinking.
She really is scary.  She's a scary kid!
She really is no joke!
[Anyways, the tension escalates]
[Jong Kook and Jae Suk leaves the room]
Why are you two leaving together?
[Spy Ji Sung...
Your partner is... IU?]
[Jae Suk and Jong Kook meeting in a room]
Let's think about this, Jae Suk.
If by any chance... If by any chance,
Park Ji Sung is the spy...
-I'm so tired.
-Of course, it's exhausting!
I'm really scared of IU right now.
There could be 2 spies...
[Now Mr. Capable nails it on the head!]
There's no rule that it has to be one person.
[Then the spies are IU... And Captain Park?]
If it's those two,
then we're really in trouble.
Let's be honest... It really isn't you?
It's not you, right?
Look at how I'm sitting with you right now.
I did the water gun recently too...
Yeah, you've done enough.
-Jae Suk. Our t-shirts are the same color.
-That's right.
[For once they're working together!]
[Spy confirmed! Let's go get Park Ji Sung!]
-We're doing this. Okay?
-Park Ji Sung is not your average guy.
[All of a sudden, out their door!]
-Just a minute...
-Park Ji Sung!
[Park Ji Sung is finally used
to the role as the spy]
[Suspicious IU is also with him outside...]
-Just a minute...
-Park Ji Sung!
-Park Ji Sung.
-What do we have to press?
[Jae Suk's hand on Jong Kook's back...]
[Could he... Could he?]
You've gathered 18,500 Baht.
[The person with the best spy record lately]
Then...
Yoo Jae Suk with his good luck...
[Ji Sung recruits Jae Suk as his partner!]
[The two that met up without anyone
knowing earlier...]
Park Ji Sung.
Why me...
Why did you pick me as the spy?
Everyone is suspicious of me because I
played Yoo-ames Bond not too long ago.
I don't think they'll suspect you
because you were a spy recently.
-That's why you picked me?
-Yes, that's right.
-You have to search every corner.
-Yes, I understand.
I found one hint.
Single. The person is single.
[When everyone thought that the mission
was stuck on Ha Ha's back...]
We have to stop them.  Stop them.
[The two in constant state of anxiety
afraid their spy identities will be revealed]
On Ha Ha's back...
Is a hint that'll lead to us.
It's not me.
[Let's rip it off]
[By convincing people,
they oust members one by one]
[The spy comrades' that were
so in sync together like this...]
[Now... If... We got rid of you...]
-I'm sorry... I'll tell you everything later.
-What?
Why aren't you coming out?
[Kim Jong Kook, out]
Really?
[Ji Sung... I took care of him]
[Now IU suspects Jae Suk is the spy!]
[He pretends to grab Ji Sung...
Then suddenly attacks!]
[Then we realize that all IU has done
is to work very hard up to this point...]
[Ji Sung purposely tears off his partner,
Jae Suk's name tag]
[Ji Sung pretends he saw the spy tag]
Are you the spy?
That's right!  I knew it!
-The spy...
-I'm sorry.
What the heck?  You're both spies?
[Spy's partner]
[The tag that was on Jae Suk's back]
You're the spy?
[IU explodes!]
What the heck is this?!
[Ji Sung and Jae Suk.
Scout mission success!]
We did it.
-Seriously... That was not an easy win!
-This makes no sense...
Then the two of you were acting?
Ugh!  I'm so mad!
-IU, you're no joke...
-If only I hadn't sat down here...
You thought it was all over...
Because you thought it was over.
I'm so mad!  I worked so hard today!
[Captain Park...
Dashingly clears the mission!]
-Good job, Hi Sung.
-Great job.
They rip off so easily.
I wonder if it needs a fixing?
[To the bus where everyone being held captive]
Why are you all wearing sunglasses?
We're curious about how it ended.
What happened?
-What happened?
-Are you really going to be like this to me?
Tell us.
Ji Sung, why don't you have a seat?
Just how did it all happen?
Because I won... All of you...
All of you are invited to Asiana Dreamcup.
[Ji Sung's surprise.
Everyone's invited to Asiana Dream Cup!]
[IU takes her leave due to her schedule]
IU... You really worked hard.
[A warm round of applause to IU
who participated in the race]
[From Captain Park's invite
who won the spy mission,
all of the Running Men head to Thailand]
[Bangkok, Thailand.  11:45 p.m]
[The late hour...]
[...But the numerous number of fans!]
[Captain Park's unbelievable
popularity even in Thailand!]
[Thailand after a year's absence...
The warm welcome...]
[Early next morning]
[With the dream of attending Asiana Dream Cup,
they all arrive in Thailand...]
[Everyone's feeling energized]
The weather is so great!
-Why is she running?
-Why are you running?
[Running Man's flag is...]
First place!
What the heck... Hey!
[But then... Jae Suk is nowhere to be seen?]
Ha Ha's Running Man!
[Without Jae Suk,
everyone vying for the center]
Yes, we've finally arrived!
Running Man in Thailand!
-Good morning, everyone.
-You're frightening everyone.
Jae Suk!  Where are you?
[His empty spot that is missed
even if he's gone for 5 seconds]
Jae Suk!  Where are you?
Things are starting to get frustrating!
Why don't we go on as if Jae Suk is here?
-Let's stand like this.
-Why don't you put one in here?
[Even through a CG effect,
they're filing his empty space]
[The reliable green color]
What are we doing so early in
the morning when we're in Thailand?
-There's something we haven't told you.
-What is it?
There are only 2 people that can
participate in the Asiana Dream Cup.
Are you for real?
The 2 people that will be participating...
Will be chosen through a Survival Mission.
2 of you can sit on the bench
and participate in the game...
And the rest of the 4 will sit in a very
far away bleachers and watch the game.
[The participating 2 will be by Park Ji Sung]
[The honor of running
the grounds with the world stars!]
-This really is an honor!
-That really is a dream come true!
Even just watching the game...
Everyone be careful today.
You may end up breaking your leg.
Who wants to proceed?
-Why are you stepping up?
-Why not?
Why don't you move?
Who was second place in looks contest?
Gary, why don't you do it?
-I can't do things like that.
-Who made you the boss?
It's good if lots of good looking
people can come on screen.
Why does he have to be the one?
Come on... Seriously.
Then I will proceed.
I will proceed.
From today,
we will restart the Monday Couple...
[Gae-MC who's main goal is to
reinstate his love line]
Is everyone ready
to have a good time in Thailand?
-What the heck is this?
-That's really tacky.
Jae Suk afraid of this happening...
So he has appointed his replacement MC.
[Today's MC that Jae Suk has appointed?]
No way...!
[He is today's MC?]
[Today's MC that the nation's MC has chosen]
[Confidently takes the center stage]
[Today's MC, Park Ji Sung!]
[Park Ji Sung immediately take the center]
I'll give you that he's a good soccer player.
-But we are better at...
-Hello. I'm your MC host for the day...
Hello. I'm your today's host
for Running Man...
-Look at him go!
-I'm not Captain Park Ji Sung today.
I'm MC Park, Park Ji Sung.
We've all been ready for this!
Yoo Jae Suk had to return
today due to his schedule...
-Yes, he returned.
-Your expression is very surprising.
Yes, he left after he has asked me to
take his MC spot today.
[A few hours earlier]
-I thank you so much for your invitation.
No, please don't mention it.
But tomorrow... Ugh...
Even though we arrived at midnight in Thailand
I have to take the 7:30 flight back.
If I knew it would be so short,
I wouldn't have invited you.
I had no idea it would be so short.
Things just didn't work out
with my schedule...
[The precious hours that he has left
with Captain Park...]
I'll invite you over to my home soon.
[Mission handoff]
[Today's mission]
[Be the MC for the day]
Are you joking right now?
No, this is for real.
This is a big job.
-Since you're so good with the process...
-You're saying I'm good?
On his own, he figured out Kwang Soo,
and he said he wanted to play jokes on him.
-Kwang Soo, he's an easy target...
-Yes, he is fun.
He instigates the pranks.
He likes doing it.
Well since... He has to get some rest...
Please take care of it...
And do well with your performance...
I think you fit in really well with the cast.
-Really?
-Yes. You totally fit in.
-I really hate to leave.
-Why don't you give him a hug?
Well, hugging Park Ji Sung
is really natural to me now.
[Wraps up the saddened heart with a hug...]
I'm really sad that I can't hold on to you.
-Bye.  Please take care of yourself.
-Bye.
[Taking their time for their goodbyes
in the hallway...]
[Ji Suk, who flew in to Thailand with the
grateful heart to Ji Sung for the invite...]
[That's how he leaves after handing off
the MC mission to Ji Sung]
[And he was burdened by the mission
late into the night...]
[The first-time MC, Park Ji Sung's debut]
-Then why don't you show us how it's done?
-Have you ever done this before?
This is my first time MC'ing today.
I have never MC'd before
outside of this experience.
Then you have to do really well today.
[He passes the first test?]
Stress!
[Even the second one with flying colors!]
-Pil!
-...I'm not doing that.
[The 3rd one an A+ pass!]
I got goosebumps!
-Park Ji Sung, settled!
-Settled, settled...
So what do we have to do today, Mr. MC?
Yes, 2012 Asiana Dream Cup...
(Yes, 2012 Asiana Dream Cup...)
[He even has the moves down]
I'll introduce your Survival Game.
The first Survival Game is...
An arm wrestling match.
That makes no sense... Come on.
Look at this guy's arms.
[Without even seeing, Jong Kook's win]
This time,
you guys won't be doing it yourselves.
If you do it yourselves,
I'm sure it'll be unfair, right?
It's not you doing it directly,
but your personal camera men will be
doing it for you in your place instead.
Yoo Suk!  Start doing pushups, Yoo Suk.
-My camera man is very strong.
-You can do it, right?
[Thailand Survival Mission arm wrestling]
This is my camera man.
[The camera men that will decide their fate]
My camera man, fighting!
-Fighting!
Fighting!
Make sure to get this right.
We can't miss this.
He and I suit each other well.
I think you guys are starting to
resemble each other.  Look.
[Since they're together,
they're starting to look alike]
Then we'll start the competition.
-Please get ready.
-Wow... This is...
[Kwang Soo's camera man, Yoo Sang]
[Ha Ha's camera man, Song Yong]
A little bit more!  More!
[With the underbelly cheer, Kwang Soo's
camera man wins!]
[Thanks to his camera man,
Kwang Soo moves on to the 2nd round!]
Song Yong, come here.
-What do we do?!
-He's really strong.
[Mr. Capable's camera man, Ki Jin]
-Look at how they look alike.
-Why is everyone starting to look alike?
[The camera man that are starting to look
like their celebrity they are in charge of]
-You can do it, right?  You have to do well.
-I think he can win.
Please get ready.
Ready, set, go!
[In one fell swoop!]
You did good.  You did well.
[Satisfaction]
[Jong Kook moves on to the 2nd round]
No, you did great!
This is the last round now, the last one.
Fighting!
The ones that have lost here,
can just get some rest at the hotel.
How easy have I made your life
during all the races, huh?
How easy have I made things for you?
You got this, right?
Please get ready.
Ready...
[Suk Jin's camera man, Yoo Suk]
[Ha Ha's camera Man, Song Yong]
-Go!
-Yes! That's right!
[Just who... Will the winner be?]
Yoo Suk!
[Ha Ha's camera Man wins!]
[thanks to his camera Man, Suk Jin eliminated]
What the heck was that?!
What happens to Running Man now?
Now... The race may begin.
[The fans that came out to cheer on
early in the morning]
We're getting on a boat?
Cheers to Park Ji Sung's MC debut!
There's no alcohol in this whatsoever.
I was planning on getting drunk today.
Please... Speak comfortably to us now.
-If you'd lower your speech first, then I'll...
-Nice to meet you, Ji Sung!
-Nice to meet you, Ji Sung.
-Ha Ha!
Ji Sung!  Good to see you!
I really like you , Ji Sung!
-Come on...
-I like you better than women.
Will you be my forever love?
Jong Kook...
Thanks, Ji Suk...
Who knew a day like this would come?
-Hey Gary.
-Nice to see you, Sung.
He spoke down to him!
No, I didn't.
[Powerfully tackled down]
-Ji Sung, please take care of me.
-Nice to see you, Ji Hyo.
How jealous Jae Suk must be!
Jae Suk left before he could lower
even one syllable with you.
[Remembering the day when the nation's MC,
and the nation's Captain twisted their words]
[Bangkok's Chao Phraya River]
[The boat is heading to the location
of their second round for the mission]
There are so many female celebrities
that really likes Park Ji Sung.
-Which girl group do you like?
-Girl group that I like?
-There are so many...
-If you had to pick one.
-If I had to pick one...
Ugh.  This is hard.
How about your ideal girl world cup?
[Captain Park's ideal girl group world cup]
-Pick 4 girl groups.
-Yes. Just pick 4 for now.
-One would be Girl's Generation.
-Girl's generation!
-And second would be... Miss A.
-Miss A!
-Then Wonder Girls.
-Wonder Girls!
-KARA.
-KARA!
Captain Park's ideal girl group world cup...
-Girl's generation vs...
-Wonder Girls!
Please count down from 5!
5, 4, 3, 2, 1!
Girl's generation.
Park Ji Sung is someone that both
moms and dads would like...
This time, it would be Miss A vs. KARA.
5, 4, 3, 2, 1!
Miss A.
[Even the people watching are nervous]
Why am I the one worrying?
Now the final round...
Miss A...vs. Girl's Generation!
5, 4, 3, 2, 1!
Girl's Generation!
Now to find out who he likes the most
out of Girl's Generation.
This is way too hard!
[The most difficult time of
Park Ji Sung's life?]
-I really can't pick one!
-5, 4, 3, 2, 1!
This is really way too hard.
Ji Sung... We're not telling you to date them.
We must be dating in my heart.
[Captain Park being corralled]
5, 4, 3, 2, 1. Decide!
Yoon Ah!
Park Ji Sung... Should write a
video love letter to Yoon Ah today...
Why don't you tell her what you want
your heart to tell her?
Start off casually.
Because we're all close to Yoon Ah.
More than that, since she's younger...
Comfortably?  Okay.
Yoon Ah...
Yoon Ah...!
I'm more nervous than him!
Yoon Ah, do you have any time off
during my vacation?
[That's right! He is a man!]
[His vacation is only until June, Yoon Ah]
When things are this fun,
Suk Jin is missing out again.
There's a rumor that it's raining
at the hotel right now.
[To pick 2 people to participate
in the Asiana Dream Cup...]
-Where is it?
-There's the Running Man landmark!
-Over there.
-There it is!
Over there.
There's the Running Man Landmark.
[Wang Lang Market]
[An open market with many vendors.
This market sells a variety of items]
[What is the mission here?]
[What are these bags?]
What's this?
I'll now explain
your second step in the mission.
Listen carefully to the Thai phrase
that I'm about to tell you.
And you have to go buy that item.
That's too hard!
[Out of the countless items that
the Wang Lang market sells...]
[There's only one answer!]
One person will be eliminated from this round.
-Then what happens to that person?
-That person has to return to the hotel.
I'll tell you the mission item.
Please listen carefully to my words.
-Eung Uh.
-Huh?
-Goldfish?
-You mumbled.
Eung Uh.  Now, off you go!
Now, off you go!
[Mission, start!]
What the heck is that?
Hurry.  Let's go quickly, okay?
[If you want to run in the dream cup...]
[Find... Eung Uh...?]
That wouldn't be carp, right?
(Carp=Ying Uh)
[Because of the inflection in the speech,
the Thai language is more difficult]
Eung Uh? Eung Uh...
[She shakes his hand in response to Eung Uh]
Eung Uh!
-Orange...
-Moo Ung!
-Moo Uh...!
-Moo Uh!
[Is she just imitating for fun?]
Thank you.
Sir... Eung Uh.
You know Eung Uh?  Eung Uh!
Eung Uh.
[Whether it's food or an item...
No idea what Eung Uh is]
[Baby babble that's coming 30 years too late]
[The various renditions of Eung Uh
that Gary's trying out]
[Understanding failed]
-What is Eung Uh?
-Eung Uh?
-Eung Uh.
Eung Uh.  Thailand's language.  Eung Uh.
[They seem to know after being told
that it's a Thai word!]
-It's a fruit.
-Fruit?!
-Rambutan, rambutan.(Correct answer!)
-Rambutan?
-Lemon? Melon?
-No, it's not.
-Red one.  Small.
-What color?
[They still don't know when
everyone's telling them]
[She's showing him a picture on the internet]
[Thailand's native fruit that's
both sweet and tart]
[Find Rambutan!]
Thank you!
[Someone hands the Giraffe a giraffe doll]
[Finally discovered Rambutan!]
[Last one to arrive is eliminated!]
-I found it! I found it first!
-No! We did it together!
I was first, right?  Me?
-No, I was.
-You give it to me first. Thank you!
-No, me!
Thank you, thank you!
[The penguin bites the giraffe!]
[The crowd fires up at that scene!]
[Ha Ha first to acquire Rambutan!]
Sorry, sorry, sorry.
Excuse me, excuse me.
Thank you, thank you!
[Kwang Soo also succeeds in acquiring it!]
I got bitten!
I got bitten in Thailand!
Ji Sung!
Ji Sung!  Ji Sung... Ji Sung!
I came before I could even get my change.
-I was in such a rush!
-Ha Ha...!
You succeeded!
[Ha Ha passes the 2nd round]
How did he come back so quickly?
That was purely skill!
Hello.  You know Eung Uh?
-What?
-Eung Uh.
Eung Uh?
-Listen!
-Okay.
What?
Is it fruit?
[They're both getting frustrated]
In Thailand.  Eung Uh.
-Huh?  Where?
-Over there.  There.
[He find Eung Uh!]
Thank you.  Good luck selling.
It's who comes first between
Song Ji Hyo and Kim Jong Kook!
There it is!
[Ji Hyo also discovers Eung Uh]
How much is it?  25?
Okay.  See you later.
[Both paying for it at the same time]
[Only one of these 2 will go
on to the 3rd round!]
Thank you!
I have to go quickly!
[the first to arrive wins!]
I wonder who it's going to be.
Who's going to come first.
Will it be Jong Kook or Ji Hyo?
Someone's here!  Who is it?!
[The tiger arrives!]
It's Jong Kook!
Kim Jong Kook...
[Kim Jong Kook passes!]
It almost could've been big trouble!
[Ji Hyo with the final spurt of speed!]
[However, unfortunately...]
[Congratulations?]
Congratulations, Ji Hyo.
-Song Ji Hyo... Eliminated!
-Really?
Why are you tearing off my name tag?
-Why are you getting mad?
-Who are you to tear off the name tag?!
-I lost?
-Yes.
You lost the second round.
I don't know why, but I keep smiling.
You know what I thought of this morning?
I wonder how Ji Sung slept?
You know what I worried about?
I worried that Ji Sung may have
drank the flower tea.
I was afraid he drank the flower tea,
and turned into Kim Hong Kook!
[Frightening, but a funny thought]
That would be so funny!
What's the last one?
The last one is about your level
of concentration regarding a ball.
[Ha Ha full of jokes]
[Captain Park gets this too
without hesitation]
I can see it through this.
[A busy Bangkok City]
[Out of the blue,
coming through the tree shades]
What's this place?
Are we playing soccer?
-There's the Running Man landmark!
-Where?
There it is.
[A park filled with trees in Bangkok]
[A lily pond that looks cool even by sight]
[This place full of big trees and green grass]
-This is a nice park.
-This is nice.
No matter how nice the park is,
the best park is, Ji Sung Park!!
-There is the landmark!
-We are going to play soccer.
[3 balls?]
Let's go, let's go!
TO the 4 of you left remaining,
I heartily congratulate you.
Why can't you give me one warm hug?!
The 3rd mission here...
I'm going to sign
the balls that are right here.
You have to and bring back the balls
that I have signed.
[The one to return with the ball
in the bag wins]
Wait a minute.
[Fooling all of the Running Man]
Something fell.
What the heck?
[A strong kick!]
[Run!!]
[Ha Ha and the Giraffe in the lead!]
[A tight race]
[Ha Ha gets the signed ball]
[During that time, another ball...]
[Mr. Capable on the lookout]
[Everyone out for themselves]
[Easily gets a signed ball]
[the last ball which would decide
who will be eliminated]
[The ball that's going out even further]
That's really far out there.
[At this rate, it'll even go to Vietnam]
[Sorry]
[The ball is in Gary's arms]
[Kwang Soo, who's not giving up to the end]
[Stealing the bag?]
He took his bag.
What are you doing?
[Only counts if the ball is in the bag]
This is my bag.
Hurry up and take it back.
[The last fight]
[Takes the bag that's wound around the neck]
Roll, roll.  Thai's right.  Roll over.
[The winning is in front of his eyes]
[3rd round... Gary passes!]
The last winner is... Gary.
[Next day]
[Empty FC Muotong Stadium]
[The 3 remaining survivors and MC Park,
that arrives at the last mission destination]
[Automatically starts humming]
Today's mission is no joke.
The last mission.
-What is it?
-I can't tell you yet.
[The final mission to the Asiana Dream Cup!]
-Even Mr. Capable should be nervous.
-Really?!
[The final mission to pick the final winners]
-What's this? Someone's in there!
-Who is it?
[The fierce pose]
[The final mission's opponent is...]
['R. Rooney']
[Jung Dae Sae]
Who is that?!
[And he is the final opponent
that they will be facing]
[North Korean representative player,
with the nickname, 'R. Rooney']
[And here he is?!]
Hello.  Nice to meet you.
[Doppelganger?]
[Finally Gae Dae Sae and Jung Dae Sae meets!]
I've really been wanting to meet you!
[Indeed a doppelganger!]
I'm so glad to meet you!  I'm a huge fan!
Gary!  Gary is here!
[They're all shocked at what they're seeing!]
It's nice to meet you.
[Rendered speechless]
[Does Jung Dae Sae know about Gary?]
My mother told me that she has 2
real brothers in South Korea.
[Real brothers his mother spoke of...]
Actually, my name is Jung Gary!
-Do you know who Song Ji Hyo is?
-Yes.
-What is your first impression?
-She's very pretty.
I'm sorry. But she and I haven't been
broken up for long...
Since only 2 of you can go on,
today's mission will decide
the last to be eliminated.
And I've invited Jung Dae Sae
to help out with that mission.
-You really seem like an MC now!
-You speak so well!
You have to at least be bad at jokes,
for me to be able to say something...
Then will Jung Dae Sae will be participating
in what we'll be doing today?
Jung Dae Sae...
Will be tearing off your name tags.
Ugh, seriously!
How can you do that?!  What the heck?!
If you tear off Jong Kook's name tag,
you'll hear a huge round of applause!
There's not just one name tag.
-There's not just one name tag.
-Then what?
Similar to a soccer game,
there are 2 name tags.
One is a red card.
A small red card will be attached.
And on top of that will be
a large yellow name tag.
-Then they have 2 lives.
-They'll have 2 lives.
And once both of the tags are ripped off,
then that person is eliminated.
[A way to eliminate Mr. Capable?
Ha Ha in great spirits]
-Then what do we do?
-Is there something we can do?
You can't participate.
(You can't participate)
[How spiteful]
They're all going to run from you,
and throw your arm off and stuff...
Ah... It's not going to be easy.
So you can just throw them down...
(So you can just throw them down...)
[Throw them down?]
What do you mean, throw them down?!
-What do you mean, throw them down, huh?
-He is just going all out.
-You can push them down and rip it off.
-Is hitting their face not allowed?
Why would you hit our face?!
Seriously...
[The ad makes it seem like it's going
to be a very arduous journey...]
[A little rest period]
How old are you, Jung Dae Sae?
-28.
-28?
We switched over to casual speech with Ji Sung
so should we do the same with you?
-How can you speak casually already?!
-He's younger than us!
He's a younger person I've been
wanting to meet for so long!
-Dae Sae... Will you call me Bro once?
-Brother!
[An emotional reunion of the brothers']
I've missed you too!
[Dae Sae brothers sitting side by side]
[Younger brother leaning into the
shoulder of his older brother]
[A picture to prove they're brothers]
What did you say?
The uglier one is the older brother.
[The Dae Sae brothers finally meets!]
[Hiding MC Park's face with his big arm]
Bro, please get this out of my face.
Even though his face looks like that,
Even though he looks like that,
he's the most popular hip hop artist
in South Korea.  Seriously.
[It is flattering...
But 'Even though he looks like that?']
What do you mean,
'Even though he looks like that?'
I wanted to say something about that too.
[Talk about Gary's face that doesn't seem
like talk about a stranger...]
[Dae Sae's heart hurts from
the talk about his brother's face]
Dae Sae... You really are the only one
that looks out for me.
[The final mission starts]
Please come on back just a little bit more.
You just say 'Here we go with the slate'
and say 1, 2, 3, and clap your hands.
Here we go with the slate.
1, 2, 3.
Jung Dae Sae, Gae Dae Sae.
Here we go with the slate.  1, 2, 3.
[The Dae Sae brothers slate shoutout]
[Perfectly in sync]
He is so strong!
-Now this is the last mission.
-Yes.
And the last 2 survivors will be in the game
with me tonight in this arena.
[Running Man vs. Jung Dae Sae]
[The boundary they can run away from him in]
-Everyone ready?
-Yes!
Ready, set, go!
[Jung Dae Sae's leisurely walk]
What do I do?
[Even Mr. Capable is nervous]
Hey!  We can't all gather in one place!
[The warning that they're going out of bounds]
This is too tight of a space.
-The space is too tight.
-You'll be warned if you step out of line.
[Tight space... The opponent is Jung Dae Sae]
[Heading off to Mr. Capable!]
[He shoes his back!]
He is way too quick!
He ripped it off so fast!
[The strength and speed that
he's never felt before until now]
[The next attack that comes without a break]
Jung Dae Sae, fighting!!
I'm your brother!!
[Gary barely escapes!]
It's your brother! Dae Sae, it's me!
[He attacks Mr. Capable again?]
Jong Kook is totally nervous!
[If Mr. Capable gets his name torn again,
then the game ends here]
[Gary again?]
Hey!  Dae Sae...!
It's your brother!  Me!  Your brother!
-Go after Jong Kook.
-I'm going out of breath here.
You can't go outside the line!
Target this time is Ha Ha]
[His name tag is caught]
[Ha Ha definitely knows how to escape]
[Chasing after him to the end]
Now the person that Dae Sae rips
off the name tag from will be eliminated.
Dae Sa!  I'm your brother!  Remember that!
[Just who will be eliminated?]
It's Jong Kook... I think it'll be him!
[Towards Mr. Capable...?]
[Desperate escape]
[His own brother, Gary?]
I'm your brother!  Dae Sa!
Remember that!
You know me... The rapper!
[Just how does Jung Dae Sae fell...?]
[Slowly picking up speed to attack]
[His target ultimately is Gary?]
[Huh?!  Ha Ha?!]
He's caught... He's caught!
[Ha Ha caught tightly without room to escape]
[Mission over]
[Ha Ha eliminated]
He is so fast!
With this, Gary and Jong Kook will run on the
field in Asiana Dream Cup with me.
With the two of you here like this,
how about a ceremonial kickoff party?
-Our Park Ji Sung...
-Hey, Ji!
[Rio Ferdinand]
[Manchester United's sector]
[Top defender of England]
[The bulldozer]
[A world class soccer player, Rio Ferdinand!]
There are so many doppelgangers today!
[Only the giraffe
and Rio's height are similar]
Thank you, thank you.
You don't know us, right?
You've never watched us before?
Do you know Running Man?
-Running Man?
-Yeah, yeah, yeah.  I know.
He's never seen it.
But he's heard me talk about it.
-Do the game.
-Are they doing the game with you?  Good.
-Yeah.
-Do you remember me?
-He sent you the choco pie.
[Ha Ha personally sent a package of
Korean snacks upon finding out Rio likes them]
The big box?  I remember.
But you don't say... You never said anything.
No, I said thank you
to whomever sent it on twitter.
I said, thank you.
He said he sent a tweet on twitter
saying thank you.
He doesn't follow me on twitter.
He's saying that you don't
follow him on twitter.
Why aren't you following me?
[Follow one another and become
good friends...]
With the last mission here,
Gary and King Jong Kook of Running Man,
will be running alongside Rio Ferdinand,
Jung Dae Sae and myself.
And the rest of you that's been eliminated
can watch the match in the bleacher stands.
[At last, about to make an appearance]
[Alongside the world-class players,
Jong Kook and Gary heads to the arena]
[This is what a dream is!]
This is really a dream come true!
[Thailand]
[SCG Muotong United Field]
[In this place...
To help the soccer dreamers in Asia...]
[Park Ji Sung and his friends will
participate in a charity soccer game!]
[The area full of spectators even
on a cloudy day like this]
How did we get here?
I've wanted to come,
but now that I'm here, I feel strange.
His expression is not as good
as when he's performing.
[Gary's also nervous]
[Once we're out there,
for 20 minutes, we each will warm up.
We can just do it at our own pace, right?
[Even Lee Chung Young who was
recently injured also attended]
[Even Joong Ki who was also separately
invited to the charity game moves to the field]
[At last...]
[2nd Asiana Dream Cup!]
[Ha Ha, Kwang Soo, Ji Hyo and Suk Jin
who found their spot in the bleachers]
[Jung Dae Sae, fighting!!]
[Captain Park Ji Sung!]
We're right here!!
[Among them, the principle stars of
2002 World Cup's honor]
[Amongst them...]
[Human ice blocks?]
[Is that the field...
and is that the stands?]
I'm so nervous!  Oh my goodness!
[Ji Hyo's more nervous than the boys
that's participating in the event]
[First half kickoff]
[Today's match is Park Ji Sung and friends
vs. Thailand's All Star Team]
[The 2 that's more nervous than ever before]
[Rio Ferdinand taking up
center midfielder for the day]
[In the spot where all the best of the
world-class soccer players are gathered...]
[Fighting with each other over
their friendship with Captain Park]
[Jung Dae Sae showing
unbelievable strength and speed]
[Park Ji Sung said
he's like to score a goal today]
[Right then, a shot!]
[Captain Park's shoot!]
[Park Ji Sung and friends
who were being led 1-0]
[With a smart pass play... Goal!]
[Soo Ho Shin and Lee Chung Yong's common goal]
[Athletes showing their class]
1, 2, 3, hooray!
[Riding the members' wave]
-It's going, going!
-Look at it go!
[Looks as if it'll go around the stadium]
There it is!  It's a wave we started!
Keep the wave going!  Go!
-Make it come back here!  Just a little more!
-You can do it!
[Back to the members...]
Here it comes!
Thailand and Korea has become one!
[A cheer meant for the players who are
playing in this hot weather]
Lee Kwang Soo!  Lee Kwang Soo!
[The act in from of 10000 people]
[The dance he says only the brave ones can do]
Sit down.  We have to cheer on the players.
-You have to look up front.
-I was just so grateful, I didn't realize...
[In this enjoyable atmosphere...]
[The only two people that are watching
the game with trepidation...]
[Without turning their head once...
Without smiling even once...]
[Only watching the scene out on the field]
[The end of first half!]
-Kang Gary!!!  Jong Kook!!
-Oppa!
[Cheering on Jong Kook and Gary on the field]
Ah.  So nervous.
It would be nice if Kim Jong Kook
could score a goal tonight.
The players from Thailand currently don't
know that Jong Kook and Gary are singers.
[The walk makes them look like army soldiers]
[Starting of second half]
[Park Ji Sung and friends are
winning the game 2-1]
-Joong Ki.  Please go warm up.
-Excuse me?
[Joong Ki, getting ready to go in]
Our Joong Ki is going out...
What do we do?
Joong Ki, fighting.
I think he's going.  He's going.
I think Joong Ki is going out.
Joong Ki is going out.  Joong Ki!
[Joong Ki going in as replacement]
Joong Ki, fighting!!
Song Joong Ki, fighting!!
He's my friend!
Song Joong Ki, fighting!
[Just then!]
-Go warm up.
Me?
Fighting, fighting.  Fighting!
[Jong Kook starting his warm up]
Jung Dae Sae!!  Great job!!
[Thoroughly ran out Jung Dae Sae replaced]
[Gary going out to greet his brother]
[Joong Ki is replacing him on the field]
[Even more nervous Gary]
Jong Kook!  Jong Kook!  Good luck!
Jong Kook!
[At last, Jong Kook going in as replacement]
Please do a good job, Kim Jong Kook.
[Substituting 2002's Man of Glory,
Ahn Chung Hwan]
[At last,
Jong Kook steps onto the field of dreams]
Kim Jong Kook, fighting!!
[Greeting Captain Park with his eyes]
[Jong Kook.  He's in the center]
[Joong Ki and Jong Kook
showing us their energetic moves]
I don't think I can watch this!
[Joong Ki's surprising pass!]
[Wow... 2 people in one moment?]
[With glaring footwork,
the tiger evades 2 players?]
[A perfect play even
Park Ji Sung is applauding]
[Shocked even from the bench]
[An even more nervous Gary]
[The tiger that keeps
showing off his smart plays]
[The unbelievable attack of the oxygen tank,
Park Ji Sung]
[The decisive pass he makes to the tiger
in front of the goal...]
Please!!
[In a dream game... Even a goal?]
[He misses the goal!]
[The tiger unfortunately misses
the pass Captain Park hands him]
It's okay, it's okay...
[Huh?]
[Captain who chastises him right away]
He's throttling him asking why
he couldn't make that goal.
[The frustrated younger brothers]
[Joong Ki who did is best is traded out]
Joong Ki, great job!
Kang Gary is finally going in!
We will wait in anticipation!
[Trading in with none other than Gary]
[Almost as if Jung Dae Sae is coming back in]
[Is it that guy again?]
1, 2, 3. Fighting!
It's Gary!
[Park Ji Sung's pass!]
[So embarrassing...]
How embarrassing!
[Even Captain Park is embarrassed]
Hey, stupid!
-You dummy!
-If you're going to play like that, stay out!
[Going to the backside to finish off
the opponent's attack, Captain Park!]
Kim Jong Kook.
[The foul that happens
after he misses the pass]
[Gary calming down the referee?]
[Nervous tiger in front of the pro players...
Already sapped of his energy]
I'm sorry.  I'll apologize in his place.
I'm sorry.
[Apologizing to Thai fans in place]
[The unbelievable speed!]
[The glaring talent]
[The chance given to Gary]
[Center ring?!]
[Who are you giving it to, Gary?]
You stupid!!
What the heck was that?!
What are you doing?!
Gary... Gary's got it.  Come on, Gary.
[Misses an easy pass]
It's okay... It's okay...!
[Who is that guy...?  Gae Dae Sae]
[Weedy life...]
[A man without means...]
[Cool center ring!]
[Not losing his confidence
in the midst of world-class players]
[His name... Kang Gary!]
It's Gary!
[Another chance at the center ring!]
It's Gary!  Gary...!!!
[It really is hard...]
You stupid!!!
[Game over]
[Even though they lost the game...
Just the chance to watch them...]
[A beautiful game]
[Refusing to be filmed?]
I have no right as a player...
[Disappointment of losing...]
[Even more disappointing because
it's an unforgettable experience]
[Only their mistakes keeps resurfacing...]
You did well...
You did well playing against
the all star players.
-I thought I was going to...
-Everyone did well except for Gary.
I hope I don't see Gary again
in a sports arena.
I thought he was a pro soccer player today.
Even I've never done that move.
[Captain Park's entrance]
I'm really sorry.
I really got cussed out on the ground earlier.
'There's not much time left!!'
I was really honored to have ran on the
same field with them even if we lost.
Well... We're family now.
Rather than calling him a guest,
since we're all family now...
Am I a fixed setting on Running Man?
The world's star soccer player,
Park Ji Sung!
I had such a great time shooting Running Man,
And with Running Man members
coming to Asiana Dream Cup,
I was so happy to have shown them a great
time and to have made such great memories.
[3 nights and 4 days spent as family...]
I'm very happy to have made such
great memories shooting Running Man.
And I will return as a good soccer player
during the next season to show you all.
Thank you.
Can I take one commemorative photo?
1, 2, 3.
1, 2, 3!
[Prize money from Park Ji Sung spy game
has been donated to Asiana Dream Cup]
-Do you rap often?
-Yes, I do.
I go to karaoke bars and do it.
I'm even trying to write a song.
-Want to rap together sometime?
-Yes.
I'll have a song ready for us.
-For a dream...
-Like kids with a dream.
-My life.  It's my life.
-The tiele, My life.  Okay.
Oh... Not bad.  Wow.
If there's revenue from it,
how many percent...
Let's talk where there are no cameras.