[Do you remember?]
[Park Nam Jung]
[Kang Soo Ji]
[Kim Wan Sun]
[Firetruck]
[The legends are coming]
[From the late 80's to early 90's...
The legends of K-pop...]
[Those that ruled a generation are coming.]
[The nobles of a legend
we've been waiting for...]
[8090 Legend Special Episode starts now!]
[This is the Running Man Ballroom]
[DJ Dong Wan]
[Harlem Desire (1987) - London Boys]
[A lively group dance.]
[Members in their own costumes
and dancing with enthusiasm.]
[To the beat of the songs that dominated the
roller skating rinks in 80's and the 90's.]
[This is how it's always been...
Individual dance time.]
[Starting with Kwang Soo, the Giraffe.]
[Kang Gary,
the former dance King of stadiums.]
[No matter what she does,
always pretty, Blank Ji.]
[Kkuk]
[National gymnast? Big-nosed Brother.]
[New Groom,
Haroro's serious dance moves.]
[Married Man's out of control dancing.]
[And the legendary dancer, Jae Suk.]
[Stealing the dance floor.]
[A white hot atmosphere.]
[Starting off with an enthusiastic dance.]
[We are Running Man]
[A satisfied round of applause for
the dance?]
- This was back from our days.
- That was so much fun.
- I'm getting so hot now.
- Where are the Firetruck members?
They have to put the fire out.
[The MC Hammer pants that used to be
the rage back in the 90's.]
- Gary, you look so cool.
- It looks like something out of your closet.
Why are you playing these songs today?
[The reason for bringing out the old hits...]
I'd like to introduce myself to you
as your DJ for the day.
Then... our first song of the day...
The ultimate dance singer of this generation,
the Madonna of Korea...
[Madonna of Korea?]
- Can you guess who it is?
- Of course, we know.
Isn't it Wan Sun?
Wouldn't that be Wan Sun?
[A silhouette striking a pose.]
[Could it really be her?]
[It is her! Kim Wan Sun!]
[The legendary Dancing Queen,
Kim Wan Sun is here!]
[Kim Wan Sun- 1986 Debut.
Made a splash as the Rookie of the year.]
[And followed up with another hit album.
She is the legendary Queen of dance songs.]
Is it Wan Sun? I can't see!
[Is this a dream or a reality?]
[Sweeping all the music award shows
between 1988-1992.]
[Grabbing all the attention of Running Man
with the appearance of this legend.]
[Pierro is laughing at us- 1990.
Kim Wan Sun]
[Running Man's ballroom full of enthusiasm.]
[Hi, Ji Hyo!]
[Wow! No changes to her performance!]
[A fantastic performance
befitting a legend.]
- She still looks the same!
- She hasn't changed a bit!
[The Dancing Queen with
unchanging beauty.]
- You look so pretty!
- You're not 30 yet, right?
No, I'm not.
- Then call me honey!
- Honey!
What are you doing right now?
[A kind-hearted Wan Sun
going along with the flow.]
[Show continuing on]
[The dancer whom all the little kids,
and the grandmothers are familiar with.]
- That dance?
- Who is it?
- Park Nam Jung!
- Park Nam Jung?
Seriously?
[An amazing dancing ability.]
[Dazzling footwork and handwork.]
[The legendary dancing skills
that haven't changed with the years.]
[A magical entrance.]
[He's here.]
[The same pose from back in the day.]
[The legend of dance, Park Nam Jung!]
[Park Nam Jung - 1988 Debut.
Conquered 1989 with 'Missing you'.]
[This is the dance that
swept through the nation.]
[The dance one more time!]
[The legendary dance that all members
of Running Man still remember.]
[Ever impressive foot working skills.]
[Dazzling moonwalk dance]
[Missing you - 1988. Park Nam Sung]
[Working the nose]
Did you just see Wan Sun?
[Wan Sun's teenage girl reaction.]
- He was awesome.
- He's just so cool.
[Ever amazing dancing machine,
Park Nam Jung.]
[What is this smell?
Smell of Kwang Soo's feet?]
Or could it be the scent of
Ji Hyo's perfume?
The scent of that woman who can
stir any man's heart...
[That woman's tantalizing scent?]
[Goddess of innocence, Kang Soo Ji.]
[The scent of purple, 1990. Kang Soo Ji.]
Kang Soo Ji!
[Kang Soo Ji- 1990 Debut.
The singer that took '91 and '92 by storm.]
[The original Goddess of Innocence
that stirred up the hearts of all men.]
[An enduring masterpiece that
still gets the crowd going.]
[A retro backup dancer]
[A dazzling shuffle dance]
[Even the other legends are
moving to the beat.]
[It's already over?]
This is just legendary.
Hello? What? There's a fire?
[Could it be?]
Firetruck?
[They're here!]
[Just hearing the opening beat
gets them moving on their feet!]
[Firetruck- 1987 Debut.
The original Idols that swept the nation!]
[Please relay it to her - 1987]
[Jung Won Kwan]
[Kim Tae Hyung]
[Lee Sang Won]
[An Idol to Jae Suk who was only a
high school student back in those days.]
[The moves that used to make the their
teenage fan girls faint.]
[An enthused teenage girl fan.]
[The performance, and presence...
just as it used to be.]
[This was it... oh yeah!]
[A powerful performance!]
[The dance everyone used to
try to imitate.]
[Firetruck is here!]
[Stage assistant removing the
mike stands.]
[All the legends are in one place.]
I really wish I could go back
to that time.
How is it that none of you have aged?
- You all still look the same!
- Suk Jin is the only one who aged.
What the heck?
[They all still look the same...]
- This is amazing.
- I haven't met you before.
[Shaking hands with their juniors
whom they've never met before.]
I'm a personal fan of yours.
[Sang Won, a personal fan of Blank Ji?]
[Monday boyfriend, Kang Gary
blocking him from touching her?]
- This is her boyfriend.
- She has a boyfriend.
- Sang Won is still a bachelor.
- Ah...
Our show today is
80-90's legends special.
All our guests today really are legends.
[Welcome]
The fact that they're even here
is really amazing.
That's why today's games will be
Running Man Team vs. Legends Team
and you'll be competing against
one another.
But as you know it's six against seven,
and it's not an even match.
So there is one more guest.
- Really? Another guest?
- Is it Jo Yong Pil?
[It's not him...]
[But he's already here.]
[The stage costume from that time.]
[He's here]
[1995 - Turbo]
[1995- Turbo Kkuk vs. 2012 Running Man Kkuk.]
[Haroro transformed into a
Turbo maniac.]
[A burdensome costume
that's not easy to get into.]
[Transformation complete!]
[Black Cat Naero, 1995 - Turbo]
[A vote performance in front of
legends of dance.]
[Seriously!]
[He's good.]
[Thus, Team Legends gains
Kim Jong Kook on their side.]
You should've given me a hint
or something!
He's totally the youngest in that group.
He's the Kwang Soo on that team.
- What year did he make his debut?
- I debuted in 1995.
- Do something with him, please.
- He really is the youngest then.
He's like a little kid.
Make him get down on his knees once.
I can't make him do that
when he's on our team.
- Come here.
- Thank you.
[Little Big-nose falling behind.]
- Why are you asking us to do that?
- Why don't you kneel down?
I'm sorry, but I'm older!
Suk Jin is getting down on his knees!
- You're older than him?
- Yes.
Then are the seven of them a team,
and the rest of us are one team?
That's why we have invited one person
who will be joining your team.
- You have?
- There's another person?
Why are there so many guests?
[This music is?]
[What? Is this a red ostrich?]
[Goo Hara of KARA.]
[Mister - 2010. KARA]
- It's KARA!
- KARA!
[Hara will be joining the
Running Man Team.]
Seriously, we like her better than
Jong Kook!
- Well, seriously...
- What?
Since we're here too,
why don't we mix up our team?
- You want us to leave?
- Why don't we switch up a member?
Is this how the teams are going
to be set up?
Your mission today...
is the time machine marble race.
[Today's mission,
Time machine marble race.]
Team Running Man and Team 8090 will
be taking the time machine
to take a trip to the past.
You really are coming up with
a variety of things for us to do.
[Now we even have to travel
through time.]
You will take a trip to each of your time in
the past, and will have to win the marble.
You will have a marble competition with
the marbles you have gained
at the final location and the team
that wins will be the final winners.
Everyone change into your team outfits first,
and your time machines await you outside.
- Sir, you have to change your outfits.
- Is this what Running Man is about now?
Hey! We're not 'Sirs' here!
We're all just
older brothers and sisters here!
- How should we address you then?
- Just call us by our names.
- Older brothers and sisters.
- Not sirs?
[The legend singers wanting to be
addressed casually.]
I think these older sisters...
both have a bit of an attitude.
[Anticipate today's events...
original beauties with attitudes.]
We have to be careful.
I know them and they have attitudes.
Please change into your team clothing and
gather outside in front of your time machines.
[Off they go to the time machines!]
Nice to see you!
[Time machine awaits you!]
Okay, everyone... let's all gather out front.
Is this what we're riding?
Wow... it's a time machine!
[Now, back to the past...]
[And they're off!]
[Back to the 8090's.]
Everyone... are you
all ready to go back to the past?
- Yes, we are!
- What year are we going back to?
- I'm nervous!
- Are we going back to the 80's or the 90's?
We're going back to 1982!
Jae Suk, then Hara wouldn't even
have been born yet.
Hara, what year were you born in?
- In 1991.
- So it's before you were born?
Hara, do you want to go to 1982?
Yes!
I bet the gravitational pull
is going to be mighty.
[The power of the gravitation pull!]
[Let's go back to the past!]
[Heading back to 1982!]
[Heading back to the past.]
[Wan Kwan disappointed at having lost
Hara to the other team.]
Let's just switch then.
I like the other team better too.
- Who is it that you like on the other team?
- Kwang Soo seems so nice and sweet.
He may be nice and sweet,
but we're much better looking than him.
We're all singers on this team
with looks to show for it.
- Of course!
- We're all better looking.
- Jong Kook...
- Yes?
- I think you got lucky coming to our team.
- Why do you say that?
The reason being is that the other team
can't be too brash towards us.
[About to utilize the advantage of the
other team not being able to act brash?]
Back in the day, I couldn't even breathe
when I was in the same dressing room with you.
I found you scarier.
[Ah... I see...]
[Believe...]
[Arriving in 1982!]
- We're in 1982?
- Of course! Believe in it.
To truly be back in 1982,
you have to walk like this.
It's Myungrang Field!
[Myungrang Field]
[1982- The program that used to start off
Sunday mornings back in that year.]
[Show host: Byun Woong Jeon]
Wow! It's 1982!
- Are we really back in 1982?
- Hara, this is 1982.
- This is 1982?
- This is Myungrang Field.
Myungrang Field!
[Show host: Kim Hwan]
[Huh? That song is
National Singing show's tune?]
- What are you doing here?
- Hey, it's Byun Woong Jeon!
Hwan, are you supposed to be
Byun Woong Jeon?
Iron stamina and a wise mind...
The time at Myungrang Field
has made its return.
The game we will be playing is the
best known game here at Myungrang Field.
It's an obstacle relay race.
That was what they did at the very end.
[The game that used to be played at the
end of each show at Myungrang Field.]
You have to wear the big person suit
and as you all can see,
there are four obstacles in front of you.
Your first obstacle is the downhill obstacle.
Second course is the
water puddle jump post.
Third course is the
rubber pass through obstacle.
And finally,
you have the cookie eating obstacle.
Just leave it to us,
we're confident we can win this.
- You've done this a lot, right?
- Of course, I have.
- Leave it to us.
- Jong Kook, give us some tips.
I'm sure there's one of here
who may be a bit too old for all this.
What we need here since we're not
able to compete with them physically...
We're going to have to cheat.
[Team Legend's plan is to cheat!]
Hey, look at them from behind.
Wan Sun is like his girlfriend right now.
[1982's Monday Couple?]
Wan Sun... you look like you're his
girlfriend from the back.
Why are you overreacting?
I'm okay with it. I like it.
It's so weird.
- Hara... go rip off his name tag.
- Okay.
Out!
[A sudden prank pulled by Hara.]
[Wan Sun about to explode?]
[What... did you just do?]
Put it back on him right now!
- Wan Sun, what's wrong?
- That's cheating!
- That's not right.
- Stop it, all of you!
[Acting as if he's really been ousted...]
So this is why men like to date
older women?
[Praising the validity of dating
older women.]
Wan Sun is jumping up and down
in joy beside him right now.
[Wan Sun overjoyed from his comment.]
Myungrang Field!
Here's the first team...
It will be Yoo Jae Suk and Ha Ha
vs. Jung Won Kwan and Park Nam Jung.
[First game: Jae Suk and Ha Ha vs.
Won Kwan and Nam Jung.]
The rest of the teammates can stay
in the back and cheer on their teams.
Are we the red?
At least we're in the inner corner.
[Third and fourth obstacle will be
Jae Suk vs. Won Kwan.]
[First and second obstacle will be
Ha Ha vs. Nam Jung.]
Park Nam Jung, fighting!
Is everyone ready?
- We'll get started right away then.
- Fair play, Nam Jung. Okay?
Fighting!
Nam Jung, fighting!
- Dong Hoon, fighting!
- Yeah!
Nam Jung, high five!
Wait! Come on!
Nam Jung!
[Nam Jung having lost his footing
from having started off too fast.]
What is Nam Jung doing?
You blew your whistle.
No, you have to start over.
You can't stand up all the way.
[If the knees can be seen, it's cheating!]
[Now doing it the right way...]
[Fighting from the start!]
- You have to get started!
- What are they doing right now?
This is what you call a variety show!
[A fierce competition right from the get go!]
You have to sit lower!
[Teenage girl reactions.]
[These two taking so long to get
through their first obstacle.]
[Passes the first obstacle!]
[Getting tangled up every few steps.]
This game is going to take over
10 hours at this rate.
[We can't have that!]
[Finally arriving at the second obstacle,
the water puddle jump deck.]
There's water in the middle.
[Water?]
[Taking flight... and kerplunk?]
[Haroro jumping right into the water.]
[Teenage girl reaction]
The water is warm!
You can step over me to get to
the other side.
I won't have you getting wet too.
- You used to be my hero!
- Don't make me talk right now.
- Come on, Nam Jung!
- No!
[This is the affection between
a senior and junior.]
[A joint immersion?]
You fell in the water, didn't you?
Come on, let's go!
[Rolling over once again...]
[Park Nam Jung, you're doing great!]
[Nam Jung getting his final spurt of energy!]
[Passing the batons along to
the second runners, Jae Suk and Won Kwan.]
Run!
[Nam Jung passes the baton off
to Won Kwan!]
[Huh?]
Move it faster!
[Jae Suk gets his baton too!]
[He's surpassed within moments...]
Move it faster!
[Third obstacle, rubber pass through.]
Won Kwon, roll!
[Jae Suk passes the third obstacle!]
Jae Suk, I have to talk to you.
- Jae Suk! I said, I have to talk to you!
- What?
Wait... wait right there.
Wait... I think I have a cramp.
I think I have a cramp.
[I don't doubt it with what you're doing...]
Won Kwan, just start rolling. Okay!
[Won Kwan,
ultimately moving forward by rolling.]
Won Kwan, just keep rolling and
push him over!
[Finally arriving at the final obstacle.]
- You can't reach by sitting down.
- You have to jump!
Seriously...
[But after just having stared at
the cookie for a while...]
Won Kwan, here...
Okay... I understand.
[What is he doing...]
Listen to his ragged breathing.
I think he's praying that the cookie
will just fall into his mouth.
[Studying the cookie?]
[Eh?]
[A mere 2mm jump]
- I can't get to it!
- Won Kwan, jump!
Won Kwan, jump!
[Cheering in her native language
to give him more strength!]
Jump!
Listen to her say jump!
- Jump!
- Jump...
- Won Kwan, jump!
Jump, Won Kwan, jump!
[Can't even think about jumping
from sheer exhaustion.]
I think we need to call a fire truck
and an ambulance for him.
[Trying to work in unison
with the breeze.]
The wind...
Are you playing with me?
- Are you playing with me!
- The cookie is teasing him.
How can you have the wind blowing!
[Our fault that the wind is blowing?]
You have to sit... sit.
Please sit. That's just a nature at play.
It's just nature at play.
[Over 10 minutes of Won Kwan
breathing raggedly...]
How are we supposed to eat this
when the wind keeps blowing it away?
[Wait... the wind is momentarily...]
[Teasing him with man-made wind.]
Come on!
[Finally succeeds at eating the cookie!]
- Hurry!
- Jae Suk, hurry up and eat it!
[Just then,
Jae Suk gets his cookie too!]
[Off to the finish line]
- Jae Suk, hurry!
- Nice!
Won Kwan, roll!
[Jae Suk's final spurt of energy!]
[Easily surpassing him...]
Hey!
- Roll! Come on, just roll!
- Wow, Jae Suk is really good!
[First round- Team Running Man wins!]
Even though you're on my team,
you're still a little hateful!
[Yes, I won!]
- Won Kwon, you should've jumped!
- No, I can't jump.
Okay... we will now start the second round
of the obstacle course relay.
For the second round,
it's going to be Song Ji Hyo and Gary.
And they'll be going up against
Kim Wan Sun and Kim Jong Kook.
[Ji Hyo and Gary vs.
Wan Sun and Jong Kook]
- Fighting!
Honey, jump!
Ju-mp!
[Ju-mp decided as the new popular slang term.]
- Kim Wan Sun, fighting!
- Yeah!
[Ji Hyo vs. Wan Sun at the starting line.]
Okay, ready...
Obstacle relay...
[His lips having frozen over in
the cold weather.]
Obstacle relay... ready!
[Start!]
[Crawling off to a start?]
- Look at Ji Hyo!
- She's good!
Wan Sun... is this 'The Ring'?
[The classic horror film]
[First course, the hill obstacle]
Wan Sun, fighting!
Wan Sun, you have to roll!
[This is the scream of the Dancing Queen.]
- Kim Wan Sun, fighting!
- Get up!
Which one is Kim Wan Sun?
[What? What did you say?]
Take off your sunglasses!
[Sang Won not able to differentiate the
colors due to his sunglasses.]
Sang Won can't tell the color difference
because of his sunglasses right now.
He just asked which one is
Kim Wan Sun.
[Wan Sun is over here...]
- What do I do?
- What do we about her?
If you're going to roll, then roll sideways.
Hey... it's not easy, is it?
- Wan Sun, you saw how I did it, right?
- You're doing good!
[Finally getting it...]
[Reverting back to her crawling mode.]
[Another horror film in the making.]
[Wan Sun having trouble controlling
her body.]
[Her only wish is to be able to
move forward on her feet.]
Oh my... my shoelace became undone.
My shoelace is undone.
Oh, yeah... oh, yeah!
[While Ji Hyo is retying her shoelace...]
[Wan Sun moving up the ramp to
the water puddle obstacle.]
Get a little rest. Rest for a second.
[Are you sleeping?]
Do something!
[The distress of having to stay upright.]
[Dancing Queen's will not to give up.]
One more time, one more time...
One, two, three!
[Barely managing to get back
into a sitting position.]
[Just a little help
to get her balance back...]
Wan Sun, just dunk yourself.
Dunk yourself and pull yourself out.
I'll give you a little break.
You can stand up to jump over the puddle.
- Help me stand up!
- Can I stand up too?
- My legs... my legs.
- Her legs are about to give out.
I have no strength left in my legs.
[Slowly about to make her jump...]
Ready... set... go!
[Wan Sun's performance.
Everyone's attention is riveted.]
Okay, come on!
[Ji Hyo also succeeds in jumping over!]
[Blank Ji catching up to her in moments!]
Ji Hyo, you have to come this way!
Ji Hyo! Good job!
[Kang Gary is on his way!]
[Wan Sun succeeds at passing off
her baton in her horror mode!]
[Third obstacle, Gary vs. Mr. Capable!]
[Pretty speedy Kang Gary!]
[Passing through the third obstacle
is right in front of his nose!]
[Moving on ahead with his eyes
set straight on his path!]
Wow... look at how fast he is.
[With the baton straight in front of him,
and walking upright.]
I'm losing strength! I'm losing strength!
[Finally arriving at the last obstacle.]
[Now off to the finish line.]
[Mr. Capable also succeeds
at eating his cookie.]
[The final spurt of energy to win the battle.]
[Just which team will be
the second round winner?]
Gary!
[Turbo Kkuk throwing
his body down to the ground.]
[Goal in!]
[Turbo Kkuk crosses the finish line!]
[How can this be?]
[The youngest of Team Legend
who forged ahead with gritted teeth.]
[Wan Sun with her aching legs
rushes over.]
Because our Wan Sun
suffered through so much...
So I had to make sure that I won.
What the heck, Wan Sun?
- I thought that you said your legs hurt?
- They do hurt. They hurt, but...
[Thus the second round goes to
Team Legend!]
You almost had it.
It's one to one for the
obstacle course relay.
And for the third course,
it'll be three on three.
- Three participants?
- Yes.
Please decide the order of the players
and gather at the starting line.
[First one up, Suk Jin and Sang Won.]
I heard that you work out a lot.
You kept saying over there that
you were confidant you could win.
[Sang Won having felt frustrated over
other people struggling with the game.]
I don't get why they can't do this.
It's easy.
[Highly anticipated first players.
Suk Jin vs. Sang Won.]
[With his sunglasses and leather gloves...]
The final obstacle relay.
[The first generation of Idol starting off
confidently just as he spoke of.]
[However...]
[Exhausted right away...]
[Depleted of energy not long
after starting out.]
It's because he didn't get any
exercise this morning.
I feel like my thighs are going to
start ripping to shreds.
[The two seniors finally reach
the second obstacle.]
- Sang Won, are you okay?
- Don't talk to me right now.
I went up to Sang Won and asked if he was
okay and he says to me, 'Don't talk to me...'.
[His reply is, 'Don't talk to me'.]
[They still have the puddle left...]
Hurry! Use this moment to jump!
Sang Won, hurry up and jump!
Jump!
Sang Won, Soo Ji just told you!
[Oh?]
[He's jumping?]
[Succeeds in jumping with style!]
He did it?
[And Big-nosed Brother...]
[Jum...]
[Kerplunk]
[Jumps right into the water.]
- Suk Jin, hurry! Hurry!
- Wait...
[Huh?]
[Sang Won, who can't differentiate colors
passes his baton off to Hara?]
[You have to give it to me!]
[Round three's second player,
Soo Ji is off on her way!]
Soo Ji, wait for me!
[A much heavier costume.]
It's really heavy!
[Sang Won sprawled out in exhaustion.]
[Finally took off his sunglasses?]
[Team Running Man barely gets
the baton handed off.]
[Soo Ji, not having passed through
the rubber rope obstacle yet.]
It won't open up!
You have to push your body through!
[Hara, having caught up to her.]
You can't open it up for her!
[A much too difficult game for
the original Goddess of Innocence.]
What do I do?
[Total chaos at the rubber rope obstacle.]
Soo Ji...
Wait! Let's go together.
[What? You want to go together?]
[When is she coming?]
[Goodness... this is hard.]
Soo Ji, jump!
Nice!
[Finally arrives at the fourth obstacle!]
Sit down, you have to sit down.
[Hara succeeds at eating the cookie!]
Hurry! Hurry!
[Soo Ji also...]
[Succeeds by using a tool?]
Kwang Soo, sit down. You have
to be seated for the baton handoff.
- You have to tuck in your knees.
- They won't go in.
Wait! They won't go in!
[In the meantime,
Team Legend passes off their baton.]
[Team Legend's final player,
Tae Hyung gets on his way.]
- You have to tuck your knees in!
- They won't go inside the costume!
- You can't do that!
- But they won't go in!
[A sad Giraffe with the long legs...]
I'm telling you,
my knees won't go in!
[All his team members are trying to
help Kwang Soo tuck his knees in.]
[Tae Hyung forging on all by his lonesome
to finish the race.]
That hurts so bad!
Just roll!
One of his knees is still sticking out.
His knees are tucked in now.
[Finally getting both his knees
barely tucked inside the costume.]
[Finally climbing up onto the first obstacle.]
[Kwang Soo experiences life of a shorty
for the first time.]
[Tae Hyung not having made
much progress.]
[Feeling like death warmed over.]
[Compressed Giraffe struggling through.]
[Tae Hyung also getting a spurt
of energy?]
There's a marble riding on this race!
- Kwang Soo, you can win this!
- Losing the race would be absurd!
[The final obstacle, the water puddle.]
- You have to jump over it.
- This is the end of it!
Tae Hyung, get it done in one try.
I don't have the strength to jump.
[Compressed Giraffe's jump?]
[Compressed Giraffe's attempt
at submersion?]
Save me!
Roll over Kwang Soo!
Roll over! Hurry up and roll!
[Just then...]
[Rolling over Kwang Soo,
who's submerged in water?]
Save me!
[Passes the water puddle obstacle!]
[Nice!]
Are you okay?
Just one person can help him.
Just one of you.
[The victor has been pretty
much decided...]
What are you doing?
What are you doing? Hey!
[Tae Hyung crosses the finish line!]
[Battered up.]
Wan Sun, you were laughing
so hard earlier.
This completes the race,
and Team Legend wins the game!
[Obstacle relay race goes to Team Legend!]
The winning team can choose
three of the items that are in front of you.
[Victors advantage:
Able to choose three marble boxes!]
I think there are marbles in there.
He said to choose three boxes,
but five of you are standing up here.
- Why are you doing that?
- We can choose them together!
He said three of you can go up and choose,
but why were there five of you up here?
That's how we used to do it
back in the '90s!
I want this one.
You just need to grab which ever
one you want.
[Selection of three boxes complete.]
Okay, you can take the other two.
[Team Running Man gets the
remaining two.]
You may open them now.
[Just what kind of marbles will there be
inside the box?]
[A gigantic marble]
Do you have one like this?
- Do you want to see ours?
- Let's see.
Take a look!
[It's... big...]
Just like the Ddak-ji,
how does he always get...
[Kkuk always gets the larger size
no matter what they are...]
We had a method for choosing
the boxes.
Why don't you guys do something
about Sang Won?
[What are you doing in the corner...]
Are you okay?
He's vomiting.
[And he was bragging about
being physically fit...]
1998.
We're taking the time machine
back to 1998.
[Back to 1998]
- We won.
- Yes, we did! We won!
And we even won three marbles.
- They can't beat the veterans.
- We have to win today.
- If we lose, then it means we're just old.
- We can't lose. We can't lose.
- We have to show them the strength of 8090.
- I know.
We're going to 1998 this time.
[Team Running Man's time machine
is also heading back to 1998]
- That was my first year in college.
- I was seven years old!
That was my third year in college.
- I was 13 years old at the time.
- I was 18 years old.
Let's go!
Back to 1998!
[Back to 1998]
[Arriving at 1998!]
- Let's get out!
- Let's all get out.
- You can't lose it, okay?
- Put it in your pocket.
I'll help you out.
[Sang Won having a difficult time...]
[What awaits them in 1998?]
Okay, come on.
We all have to go in together.
['I've got a girlfriend'- Turbo.]
[Arcade?]
[All the popular games
from that time in one room.]
- We're all up here.
- Soo Ji, you look so pretty!
[All the pictures of Team Legend members
back in their hay day on the walls.]
You really were very beautiful.
I didn't even have much makeup on
back then either.
- It's an arcade!
- It really is an arcade.
- Tetris!
- Tetris.
[Glad to see the games from their past.]
[Jumping into the games right away.]
[Working out his rage from
when he fell in the water.]
Everyone, please stop playing the games
and gather around.
Just one hour.
- What is this?
- Everyone listen to me and gather around!
[Closing off their listening ears,
and fixing their gaze on the screens.]
[Getting torn away from the arcade games
by the youngest Hara's tugging.]
That's disappointing...
Little kid, Kim Jong Kook,
come on and gather up here.
Sang Won has finally taken off
his sunglasses.
[Finally will be able to
differentiate the colors!]
In commemoration of having to come
1998 arcade room...
-The representative arcade game is...
- The punch!
We will determine who the winner is
by playing the punch game.
I thought Nam Jung was about
to fly away!
- I really thought he was going to fly away!
- I thought a gust of wind blew through.
[Flying fist that's as fast as the wind.]
I can't even see your fist!
I can't even see it.
[Four representatives per team.
One on one, all kill game.]
- All kill?
- That's absurd!
The other team has Jong Kook.
Jong Kook is the one who just
put this new record high up here.
Nam Jung is an all kill too.
- Okay then, let's do this.
- I really couldn't even see your hand.
Nam Jung is going to go first.
[First player for Team Legend is,
Park Nam Jung.]
[Team Running Man is Yoo Jae Suk]
[Nam Jung to start off the game.]
[A warm up?]
[Loosening up his body
with a little moonwalk.]
[Here I go!]
You're really funny right now.
Fighting!
[A fierce punch!]
[851 points!]
Jae Suk's no lightweight either.
Using two hands will definitely
get you more points.
I haven't really played this much...
Challenge!
[Jae Suk's punch]
[Direct hit]
[A pretty loud sound!]
[Next up is Sang Won who's appearance is
enough to make others break out in laughter.]
[Keeping his parka on.]
Stop telling him what to do!
Don't tell him what to do!
It's because he gets cold easily.
Does he draw strength from it?
[Sang Won's parka and leather gloves
which aren't ready to come off yet.]
He barely just took off his sunglasses,
but he's refusing to take off the gloves.
[100 points for his sense of individuality.]
Challenge!
[Jae Suk goes first]
[A fierce sound!]
[882 points!]
- His points keep climbing up higher.
- That was really strong.
[Wow, that's amazing.]
- His points keep climbing higher.
- I've never played this game before.
I've never played games like
this one before.
[Bratty Jae Suk slyly trying to
break down his opponent.]
He seems pretty confident right now.
- Your stance has gotten weird.
- It wasn't Ddak-ji and punching!
- Yeah, punching is it for me.
- Yeah, punching is the one for you.
It's okay. I have faith you can do it.
Why don't you rest for
about five minutes then?
You have to cut off his energy.
Okay, challenge. Fighting.
[Leather glove clad Sang Won
taking the challenge.]
- Fighting!
[Oh! Pretty fierce!]
[Will he...]
- Challenge!
- Fighting!
- Punch out an all kill!
You have an iron fist!
- Nice, that's nice!
- Your fists are made out of metal!
But your stance doesn't look very good.
Nice, nice!
[King of punches,
Jae Suk looking very relaxed.]
- Don't keep practicing too much.
- Hurry up and do it! You're taking too long.
That's right!
I think his punches are just getting
stronger with each throw.
[876 points]
[Only two players left for Team Legend.
It is Won Kwan's turn.]
- Finish it.
- You never know about Won Kwan.
- Just look at his stance.
- I think he may be able to pull it off.
Challenge.
- Just watch him.
- Here it comes.
Look at how big his build is.
You really are huffing and
puffing a lot.
[Won Kwan's punch]
[Mighty powerful!]
There it is!
[Will he be able to beat Jae Suk's 876 points,
who's won two games in a row?]
[Jung Won Kwan wins!]
- Who's going to take the next turn?
- Kwang Soo.
Let's fighting! Fighting!
You have to rest in between.
Relax and rest.
I never knew I'd get this nervous
over the punch game.
[Previous winner,
Won Kwan takes the first turn.]
[So strong!]
[His score is... 882 points!]
- You're like on Jong Kook's level.
- Kwang Soo, don't be nervous. Don't be.
[Giraffe's turn]
Show us what you used to be like
back in the day!
Go back to the days
when you used to play around!
[Transforming back to himself
when he used to play around?]
- That's right!
- Kwang Soo...
Think of this as Jong Kook's face.
[If that's the Tiger...]
I've been standing behind you.
Kwang Soo, he's been behind you.
- Just do it, just do it.
- Kwang Soo, you're looking good.
- Kwang Soo, looking good.
- Just go and do it.
[ I can see the Tiger's face!]
[Take it!]
[Not getting it quite right...]
He didn't hit it right...
he didn't hit it right.
[What?]
[Kwang Soo wins...]
[887 vs. 882. Wins by five points.]
[But the Giraffe's rage
still hasn't gone away.]
[Tiger, you!]
Good job, good job!
- That's absurd!
- You still have three people left?
But the three people left are nothing
to be worried about...
- Who do we have left still?
- We've got Jong Kook.
[If the Team Legend's Jong Kook is beaten,
then it's an all kill!]
[The power of the leather gloves?]
[Once playful Giraffe takes his turn first.]
- He picks on you all the time!
- He's always ripping off your name tag!
He disrespects you!
[Punch]
[887 points!]
If Jong Kook doesn't get 887 points,
then we win the game, right?
I think the machine is broken.
- I never knew he was that strong.
- Fighting!
Challenge.
- Kim Jong Kook, fighting!
- Jong Kook, don't break the machine.
[Team Legend's hope,
their youngest teammate, Kkuk!]
[A powerful punch!]
[What will his score come out to be?]
[889 points vs. 887 points.
Jong Kook wins by two points!]
[Bitter remaining players]
775!
Me, I'll do it.
[Team Running Man, Ha Ha up to bat.]
Okay, here I go.
I'm scared. Let's get out of his way.
- Fighting!
Fighting!
I'm scared.
[A powerful punch]
[893 points!]
- Why are you getting so angry?
- When did I get angry?
[Will Kkuk win the game like this?]
Ha Ha, you can do it!
[I can do this...]
Don't make that face though.
Your wife is watching.
Think of your wife watching the show.
- Ha Ha...
- Challenge!
[A powerful sound?]
[Just what...]
[As predicted, Jong Kook's win.]
- That's so disappointing.
- I threw it as hard as I could.
[Now even Ha Ha's been eliminated...
Only one left for Team Running Man.]
- Gary, good luck.
- Gary's really strong too.
- Let's boo him, boo!
- Kim Jong Kook, fighting!
[Will it be Kkuk's all kill...]
[The last punch]
[Using his elbow this time!]
[886 points!]
- We're in big trouble.
- 886. You can do this.
- Gary, you can do this!
- Gary, he only got 886 points.
Think about all the things I've been through.
This is nothing compared to that.
Gary, boo!
- You can't do that!
- Don't pay any attention to them.
- Pretend they're not even here!
- Stop bothering me!
- No, no...
- Gary...
Why do you keep calling my name?
So that you'll do a bad job.
[The mental attack by Soo Ji.]
She's saying all sorts of things to him.
- Let's go! Let's go!
- You can't do it.
[Hanging his life on his one punch?]
[The sound was mighty powerful...]
[Just what will the results say?]
[Gary wins!]
[The power of Gary's one punch with
his life hanging from it!]
That's so disappointing...
[I'm so angry...]
[Punch all kill, Team Running Man wins!]
We won because Jong Kook
made a mistake.
[Now heading into year 2000 after
each team gets their marbles.]
- Everyone, off.
- We're in year 2002.
[What mission awaits them
in year 2002?]
- What is this place?
- This is a karaoke bar.
We really used to come here a lot.
[A place they're glad to see again.]
A variety show of this kind was
very popular back in the 2000's.
Yes, you're right.
And the game that got the most love
out of them all was none other than...
Tray karaoke bar.
- We all used to watch it on TV.
- Why are you mentioning that?
And the writer that used to do
all the cues is still here.
And I see that camera PD is
still here too!
- And the main writer...
- Yes, he is still here too.
Since this is the last game before we go to
the final location, five marbles are at stake.
And the losing team only gets
two marbles.
[Team Running Man is first
to take their turn.]
- It can't be anything too easy.
- I'm not going to pick anything.
[Will be Team Running Man's song
for tray karaoke?]
[Team Running Man's song:
On the phone by Firetruck.]
The lyrics are way too easy.
Okay, it said, always on the phone...
Jae Suk knows it all...
he knows all the lyrics.
- I think I can get all the lyrics.
- I think you've made it way too easy.
The lyrics can be heard way too easily.
- No, we can't hear it too well here.
- But if you pay attention, you can hear it.
But our pronunciation
of the words are better.
[Self praises?]
Our pronunciation of the English words
are totally natural.
I think that is way too easy for them.
I haven't played this in so long.
Kwang Soo, that's not how you do it.
[In front of the Master...]
And you have to hold it like this
so that the numbers can't be seen.
Pick one.
- What number did you pick?
- Number one.
- Number three.
I don't know the lyrics.
And I picked number seven.
Let's all switch up our seats.
- We can't talk things over now, right?
- No, you can't talk to each other.
Ugh, I seriously don't know about this.
We're going to get the trays
put in place.
Try dropping it on us once.
[People who have never been hit by it
before are shocked by the force.]
It hurts more than they did
in the past.
I have no idea how it goes.
Which part do I have? Who did four?
You can't talk about it now.
- You have to get hit before you can talk.
- We have to get hit first.
- You have to sing it loud, okay?
- I only love you...
[Team Running Man's first try]
Please give us the music!
What the heck?
[Not having listened well before,
he misses the beat to go in.]
- What are you doing, Suk Jin?
- What the heck?
What the heck?
[Off right from the get go.]
You start on beat three, right?
If you don't know,
there's nothing you can do about it.
No, no... I didn't know either.
I didn't know either.
The music is off, right?
No, it's perfect.
Tell him. Tell him how it goes.
[Launching into lesson mode.]
You have to match it to the beat.
Even when we were recording the song,
it took us about 10 hours to get the beat.
- That's actually really hard.
- Let us give it one more try.
I'm telling you, it took us about 10 hours to
get the beat the first time around too.
- Give us the music...
- Tae Hyung is trying to get it too.
Jae Suk, it's really hard to get the beat.
We had a really tough time with it too
when we were recording it.
I think that's the third time
you've said that.
You may have heard it three times,
but I've heard it six times sitting here.
Hey, Jae Suk... I'm telling you.
It's really hard to get the beat.
That's enough!
[Team Running Man, second attempt.]
[Misses the opening beat again!]
How can you not get that?
[The team is about to disband after
only two attempts at the song!]
[Now they found out
that he's not very musical?]
[It's not like they can use their chance
card they only have one of...]
[After a team makes two attempts,
it's the other team's chance.]
- Everyone ready?
- Please give us the song.
[What will be Team Legend's song?]
[Team Legend's song:
Pretty Girl by KARA.]
I know this song.
What is this?
- This is...
- What is this?
I don't think I can get this.
So it's going back that way?
No way... I don't know this at all.
Hara may not know this part either.
- Right?
- Yes.
If it's not their own part...
- Beautiful girl... that's what they're saying.
- Wait...
I still don't get what they're saying.
We lost.
[After hearing the lyrics,
he's predicting they'll lose the game?]
[Anyways, it's time to determine
the order of their seating.]
- Do we decide by picking the spoons?
- Which number did you get?
Everyone get up and find their seats.
Why don't you try singing
the song first?
[Singing the song first to make sure
they can get the melody right.]
[Truly legends... Gets the
melody after hearing the song once.]
- It's not about the pronunciation...
- Wait... who sings my part originally?
It's not my part.
[Advice from Hara,
the original singer of the song.]
- Only one word so far has been wrong.
- Really?
But my part of saying,
no, no, no was right?
But isn't getting it wrong once okay?
I'm just letting you know
about a mistake.
[Team Legend's first attempt]
[Tray drops at second verse.]
[It's so funny to watch others getting hit.]
You got it right up to the part,
'Saying no is'...]
- What did you say?
- I said, 'Saying it's not okay'.
- Isn't that right?
- You got parts of it right.
Let's do it in a little bit.
My head hurts too much.
[Team Legend members being hit for the first
time are flustered at the force of the hit.]
Then 'Saying no to it' is wrong,
it's 'The word telling me it's wrong'?
Telling me that it's not okay?
- Your actions telling me that it's no?
- You be quiet.
What you're doing is not an
acceptable action.
[Could he possibly be searching
on the internet?]
Park Nam Jung,
are you searching for the lyrics?
I'm trying, but I can't find it.
[Not able to search correctly,
since he doesn't know the song title.]
Your heart telling me it's not okay!
Your heart telling you no!
- It's not 'words telling me no'.
- The word telling me no?
It's not heart, but the word?
Then we'll go with what Wan Sun says,
and go with 'That word'.
[Team Legend's second attempt.]
Okay, this is your second attempt.
This is our second attempt
at the challenge.
Challenge!
[The tray drops at the words, 'Word no'.]
Ugh... hurry up and pull this back up!
I can't believe we got hit again
at the same part.
[Team Legend fails at both attempts.
It's now Team Running Man's turn again.]
[Sang Won trying to get a hold of Hara,
and ask her what the correct word is.]
We have to finish this now.
[After a brief rest, they're
now confused about the lyrics.]
[English is so hard...]
[Team Running Man's third attempt]
We're doing it already?
[Again! Again!]
[It has been confirmed that Big-nosed Brother
has no musical bone in his body.]
This is really hard! I can't get the beat!
[It sounds as though as long as they can get
past the first verse, it'll be smooth sailing]
I wanna hold you,
why do you need any more than that?
What is, 'ba-baby, let's go'?
[Anyway, their biggest hurdle is to
get past the first verse.]
[Team Running Man's fourth attempt.]
- Okay, wait a beat?
- 'I love you...'
[Gary completely disregards the notes.]
[I know I did well...]
Did he get the lyrics wrong?
Or the notes wrong?
- He wasn't singing in tune.
- How can you do that?
- You can't do that!
- That's how I sing my songs!
It sounded like a completely
different song.
Soo Ji...
[Spouting off venomous words
in her elegant ways.]
Are you just trying to hog the camera?
Please don't take the camera away from us!
I don't care!
- You're really being...
- Let's switch spots.
[Team Running Man's two chances are up!
It's back to Team Legend!]
You know that you don't normally
count the tone of the songs.
[This is nice...]
[A helmet?]
[Attempting to protect his head
from the force of the tray blows.]
[Feeling reassured.]
It doesn't hurt a bit.
It doesn't hurt one bit!
Can I have it?
Here, try it.
[This is 8090 slapstick comedy.]
[Team Legend's third attempt.]
- Why didn't you start singing?
- What are you doing?
[Tae Hyung being too relaxed
about it and...]
[He does remember the lyrics...]
Hurry up and practice that 10 times.
[Practicing again now that they see
their opportunity to win.]
Ready, set, go!
[Continuing on right on cue.]
[No clue after that verse.]
Wan Sun, you don't know the lyrics?
- No, I don't know...
- Then want to take the chance card?
Then want to take the chance card?
[Suggesting it so elegantly...]
[Not able to speak in a normal way.]
Too funny...
- Then let's use our chance.
- Why don't you go pick one?
[Team Legend uses their chance!]
I hope you get a dud!
[Just what is the chance that
she chooses?]
Our own original song!
[Original song]
[Have to listen very carefully now...]
I don't know...
I don't think I can get it.
Come on, beautiful girl. Okay...
[Sensible pose doesn't come easily...]
[Taking care of other people's parts too.]
[Team Legend's fourth attempt.]
Sang Won!
[He definitely said 'Walk very healthy'...]
Wherever you are,
walk very healthy...
Hara... I think Sang Won's lyrics
are better.
Don't you think it's better?
It's because I'm getting tired...
I'm getting tired.
[A healthy walk motto song.]
[Team Running Man's turn once again.
Determined to win this time.]
[What was my part again?]
Why does his expression look
so worried?
[Extremely worried from having
forgotten the lyrics.]
He looks like he's about to start crying.
Do you want me to do it
for you instead?
[Tone deaf and beat deaf combination.]
[Everyone working together
to teach one another.]
[Team Running Man's fifth attempt.]
[Giraffe ultimately missing the beat.]
Is it that hard?
[What do I do about him...]
[Have to include all the sounds they
hear in the chorus line.]
[There's a chorus?]
You know that line...
- The line is...
- Yeah, I get it.
We've never once had anyone else
take care of our chorus lines.
We did it all ourselves.
We even did all the girls' voices.
I'm being serious.
I think we need to use our chance.
I have no idea what the chorus is.
[In order to check the chorus,
they have to use their chance card.]
[They have to get either 'Hear a verse',
or 'hear the original song again'.]
- Replace the seats!
- What did you say?
Why would we change our seats now?
[When they've finally learned their parts,
they have to switch seats...]
[We're ruined...]
- But you still kept your seat.
- Why do I still have number one?
Please give us the music!
- I wanna hold you?
- It's 'I want you baby'...
You got it all right except for
the chorus.
You got the main lyrics all correct.
[The chorus is definitely the problem.]
- Let's end it now.
- Let's not drag it out anymore and end it.
[Team Legend with another chance
may be able to get it done this time.]
The thing we have to do...
Let's listen carefully to the person singing
in our own order and pick out the mistakes.
I'll just focus on Sang Won.
You don't know that Sang Won wakes up
as the night approaches, right?
[Sang Won coming to life at night?]
You guys are all over now.
He's all warmed up and ready to go now.
[If they do a night relay race,
Sang Won could win on his own?]
Put a cape on him right now.
I bet you he'll start flying.
[Sang Won, the night creature?]
[Team Legend's fifth attempt.]
What? What did I get wrong?
- Why?
- Wan Sun got it wrong?
A sensible pose is just...
[A sensible pose is okay?
A sensible pose is just done?]
Let's just get it done and go.
- I got it!
- What is it?
[Did Jae Suk figure out the chorus?]
- The line is busy...
- No, there's no 'the' in that.
The line is busy...
Isn't that what you said earlier?
You're right. I think you're right.
Let's make a trade.
Is it 'okay' or 'done'?
- What's the lyric?
- Don't tell him what it is!
You have to let us know first.
You have to tell us first.
- The line is busy.
- Really?
- I'm right? You said it earlier.
- Yeah, you're right.
- The line is busy... okay, your turn.
- Wait!
You just need to tell him whether
he got it right or not.
What the heck are you saying?
[Giraffe not wanting to reciprocate
after getting what they needed.]
- It's just not done...
- Ah, not done!
It's not done, not done.
It's just not done.
If you don't get it third time,
we're going to win it.
[Team Legend's sixth attempt.]
Let's go it. Let's finish it.
Let's go!
Let's be calm about it,
and not be too eager.
Why is he singing so softly?
- They might get it done this time.
- No, they can't...
[With the gentle voice... wrong!]
[What a lucky break!]
'While thinking about the day, I think
back to the words you say', isn't it?
- Why did we get it wrong?
- Why did we just get hit?
How much of it did we get right?
I thought Sang Won was
a female singer for a moment.
Why are you singing so softly
all of a sudden?
[Owner of a feminine voice.]
Can we hear how much of it we got right
so we know what we got wrong?
You got the 'starting the day' part right.
'As I start the day, I can't forget'...
[And the ending it with,
'Walking in a healthy way'...]
It's not an easy song.
It's okay.
[Team Running Man with the
opportunity to win.]
The way I see it,
I think they're going to get it this time.
- Hey, let's finish this.
- Cue the music!
[Team Running Man's seventh attempt.]
[Team Running Man succeeds!]
[A victory based on their teamwork!]
[Speechless...]
[Such a relief having figured out
the chorus line!]
[I shouldn't have told them...]
Don't touch all of them,
and just pick one.
[Winning team gets five marbles,
and the loser team gets three marbles.]
[Now finally going to the present!]
[Marble competition at the final location!]
- There's red carpet.
- What is this?
What is this?
[Huh? What is this?]
Wow... this is going back in the day.
I used to play this when I was really little.
You have to knock the other
ones out, right?
[This is the marble competition ground,
bringing back good memories!]
[Each team throws in eight marbles and the
team with most marbles in the circle wins!]
- Let's all try it.
- Fighting!
[Team Legend's Wan Sun is first.]
[What a loss!]
[Team Running Man to choose eight
marbles out of the 10 that they have.]
[Team Running Man's Hara to go first.]
I think she'll get it in.
[Bouncing out from within the white line.]
[Team Legend's Soo Ji.]
I'm getting a good feeling.
I'm getting a good feeling about Soo Ji.
[Kang Soo Ji's marble, hole in!]
[Team Running Man's Ace, Ji Hyo.]
- Ji Hyo, throw it to the line in front.
- Just go with your gut instinct.
[Wow! Ace Ji Hyo also gets a hole in!]
- You're our Ace! You're crazy good!
- She's amazing!
- You're the best!
- Yes, I'm the Ace.
[Both teams with one marble in each.]
Gentle...
[Team Legend's Nam Jung fails.]
[How about Jae Suk
who's good at playing catch up?]
Looks good!
[Team Legend's Sang Won.]
[Without putting in much effort,
he gets a hole in!]
We can't lose our momentum.
[Team Running Man Kwang Soo's
counterattack!]
[Team Running Man's 2 vs. Team Legend's 2.]
- It's a right game!
- Why am I getting so nervous over this?
[Even Mr. Capable from Team Legend
misses the mark.]
You have to get it in.
Don't feel burdened and just throw it.
- Don't feel burdened.
- I think he's going to miss it.
I have to see how even it is.
[Taking a look at the evenness of the dirt]
- Which way?
- It's going to roll down this way.
[It's not like they're playing golf...]
- You can actually see something?
- Throw it to the right.
Wait...
- Okay, there's no wind.
- We're indoors.
Just throw it in comfortably.
[What a loss! Almost made it in!]
[I should've gotten it in...]
It's going to go in!
[Team Legend is already down to
their last marble with Jung Won Kwan.]
I have to make sure to get it in.
- Take your time... take your time.
- He's putting too much force behind it.
I can't bear to watch!
Even if you can't get it in,
don't feel burdened by it.
You should've given me that marble!
[It's still Team Running Man's 2 vs.
Team Legend's 2.]
[Where will Suk Jin's marble end up?]
[Ultimately down to the last marble
from both teams...]
[Team Legend's final player,
Kim Tae Hyung.]
Do a long toss.
[Will he get it within the lines,
or knock one of the marbles out?]
That one is going in this time.
[Wow! Team Legend's last marble
is a hole in!]
[The last marble miraculously
makes it in!]
[Team Running Man 2 vs. Team Legend 3]
- That was amazing!
- If I don't make it in, it's over?
- That's right.
- You have to make it in.
[Jae Suk needs to make it in to go
to the playoff round...]
[Or he needs to knock out one of the
marbles that's already inside the lines.]
Jae Suk, don't feel burdened.
Think of this as your first throw.
[The marble is green! Drawing
in the strength of the color green!]
The one who controls the marbles!
[Will Jae Suk be able to
have a dramatic ending?]
I can't bear to watch this...
[Let's do this!]
[What the heck...]
[Team Legend breaking out in
a celebration!]
[A fate that's been decided
by the last marble.]
[8090 time machine race goes
to Team Legend!]
Sang Won put his sunglasses back on!
[Lee Sang Won is back!]
It's 11 o'clock at night right now.
To all of you who's been with us from early
this morning to late in the evening...
We'd like to thank all of you once again.
Thank you!
Subtitles by DramaFever
Who is it?
I can tell it's a woman.
- Is my face breaking out into a smile?
- It's a huge smile.
[The icon of melodramas that sets all
the hearts in Korea on fire.]
Hello.
[Goddess of Innocence, Han Hyo Joo.]
[And Go Soo]
Think about this carefully.
If you take the Napa cabbage now...
[Love and betrayal between men and women
surrounded by Napa cabbages...]
I'm trying to protect you, you fool!
[But he ultimately chooses
Napa cabbages over love...]
[Goodbye to melo for today...
All prudes are buried deep away for the day.]
[Go Soo and Han Hyo Joo's
dazzling actions starts now!]
[Make the ultimate kimchi!
Kimchi making war!]
[Kimchi making race to get their
hands on the finest tools and ingredients!]
[Comedic action human drama
surrounding the art of making kimchi.]
[Kimchi making race]