Running Man
[Gangnam, Seoul- 'R' Art Center.]
[October, in the midst of crisp fall air.]
[The most beautiful bride in the world.]
[And... the man waiting for his bride.]
Are you here for a gang fight
or something?
Can't you sit more elegantly?
Can't you tell that we're here for
a wedding just from a single glance?
[Family of the Bride- Family of the Groom.]
- Intimidation is a given in this meeting.
- This is why I oppose this marriage.
Who sits like this at a first family meeting?
You were lucky enough to be accepted,
so you need to bow down to us!
You're making a big mistake. You're
being too rough at our first meeting.
You look like you're
the elder of the family.
He's our great grandfather.
[There's an empty seat
on the groom's side.]
- Don't you have any manners?
- Can't your family be more punctual?
This is the first time
I've opposed a marriage
from disliking
the groom's family so much.
He talks so much!
[Just then...]
[One man walks into the meeting room.]
This is the first meeting
of the two families.
It's Jung Suk!
[Warm and caring, Jo Jung Suk is here!]
[Unbelievable charisma
on the musical stage.]
[Showing off his amazing acting talent
in the movie, 'Architecture 101.']
[Man on fire, Jo Jung Suk, who's captured
both the stage and silver screen.]
[Welcome!]
[The groom's family's confidence level
goes up with Jo Jung Suk's appearance.]
- Come here, Kwang Soo.
- Jung Suk!
[The look of a happy groom-to-be.]
- I've always wanted to meet you.
- Don't you know what his name is?
[Jung Suk sits down in the empty seat
on the groom's side.]
Then who's seat is that?
Isn't that supposed to be the groom's seat?
[The groom and the bride's chair
still remains empty.]
- Isn't the groom supposed to sit there?
- Are you not the groom?
[Jung Suk isn't the groom?]
[In the meantime, the October bride...]
[She starts to make her way
down to the room.]
- I wonder who the bride is.
- You're not the groom?
- Here she comes!
- Who is she?
[The bride is seen walking over
behind the filmy white curtain.]
[Everyone in the room breaks out
in an excited chatter.]
She's pretty even from a quick glance.
[The beautiful silhouette of the bride...]
[It's time to meet the bride.]
- Is she pretty?
- She's a member of our family.
[The October bride is... Shin Min Ah.]
[This isn't a dream, is it?]
- She's our family member.
- The youngest member of our family.
[Shin Min Ah is standing in front
of my own very two eyes.]
Wow, it's Shin Min Ah!
[Giraffe can't even manage to
look Min Ah in the eyes.]
[Today is this blushing bride's
wedding day.]
- Come here, what are you doing over there?
- Come back here.
[Can't even come near her presence.]
- She's a member of our family?
- She looks like a porcelain doll.
- Min Ah is so pretty!
- You look like a doll just sitting there.
- Say something.
- There you go wagging your tail again.
- Can you please say something?
- I feel so awkward.
I feel so awkward.
[Everyone's so excited at
hearing Min Ah's first words.]
- Jae Suk, you go first.
- What is this?
[Find out your relation to the bride and the
groom by peeling back the name plague.]
I'm the bride's older brother, too.
- First and second oldest brother?
- I'm the bride's older sister.
I wonder if I'm the bride's little brother.
I'm her fraternal twin brother!
[Min Ah bursts out in laughter.]
That's just absurd!
- I'm her twin brother!
- How can that be? That's just absurd!
That's just ridiculous.
- I'm the groom's older brother.
- What a relief! He's not the groom!
- Ugh, what a relief.
- Groom's distant cousin-in-law.
What the heck is that?
[I guess he's not the groom.]
- One of you must be the groom.
- I want to be the groom!
[Then could that mean that either
Ha Ha or Gary is the groom?]
- I can't believe this.
- Can it please be me?
[Tear off the name simultaneously.]
[Gary- Groom.]
[Min Ah's love is Husband Gae.]
- Can he even handle that?
- Is it really me?
- You're the groom getting married?
- I'm so jealous!
- Are you throwing Ji Hyo aside?
- Who's Ji Hyo?
Ji Ho?
- I don't really remember that name.
- He's marrying Ji Hyo's younger sister.
[We're going to be married soon!]
I'm sorry to say this...
but we oppose this marriage.
- I'm sorry to hear that.
- You're opposing their marriage?
- We're sorry!
- We don't like being forced into a marriage.
What do you mean, forced?
We're not being forced into anything!
- I don't like it either.
- Excuse me?
- I just don't like it either.
- What is it that you don't like?
Why are you in love with the woman
that I'm about to marry?
- I'm not sure why, but...
- How can you do this to your own family?
Jo Sung...
Jo Jung Suk...
[It's understandable that he doesn't know
his name with it being the first meeting...]
Jung Suk can read people's faces, right?
Why don't you read her face?
- I don't think she likes our family.
- No, that's not true. I do like you.
Gary's blushing for real right now.
It would be the end for Kang Gary
if I were to open my mouth right now.
No, stop!
I don't want to see my sister getting hurt,
and that's why I oppose this marriage.
I'm sure you all know why
we oppose this marriage.
Even though she is my own twin sister...
I'm still in love with her.
- What are you saying?
- I'm in love with my own twin sister.
He needs to have some sense
beaten into him.
Do you think it's possible to be marrying
her instead of marrying her older sister?
He's marrying her because her
older sister won't marry him.
[Will they be able to marry?]
This is all because our family
is just too darned attractive.
- What is that? A menu?
- Thank you.
Listen very carefully.
- You've seen that from foreign films, right?
- What is he doing?
[Wedding consent name tag elimination.]
The bride and the groom must eliminate
everyone's name tags from both families
in order to gain consent from everyone
of their marriage within given time limit.
They need to eliminate any opposition.
Once all name tags are eliminated, shout out,
'We're getting married' in front of
the officiant in order to
successfully marry each other.
Are they getting married for real?
If they fail to eliminate all name tags and
are unable to get married
then the groom can be swapped out for
someone else from the surviving family.
- I vow to remain alive in this game.
- I'm going to run away to Namyang district.
The game will start at the count of ten
by the bride and the groom.
- We're starting already?
- Right from here?
- We're getting started from here?
- I have to eliminate those guys?
- They can't eliminate us, can they?
- One, two...
['Please allow us to get married.'-
Family name tag elimination game- Start.]
Get out of my way!
[Min Ah's twin brother, Giraffe,
takes off in a flash.]
Seven, eight, nine, ten!
[Min Ah and Gary also get on their way.]
Get out of my way!
[Min Ah's oldest brother, Big-nose,
hides under the table.]
- Do you have a lighter?
- No, I don't.
You don't have a lighter? Then the
camera can't capture me right now?
I can marry Shin Min Ah if
I can survive the next thirty minutes.
[Haroro hides out by lying down on
the second floor balcony.]
[Jung Suk hides out in the parking garage.]
I didn't finish what I was saying earlier,
but I definitely oppose this marriage.
I feel like I'm the one that the bride
is meant to marry.
'Face reading to know how women feel.
Face reading to know her virtue.'
You can look up the meaning of
that phrase yourself.
I want to get married, too.
[I want to get married, too...]
How should we do this?
What's that around your neck?
- It's a fan.
- You are so darn cute!
- I think we need to come up with a plan.
- A plan?
You can hold them down,
and I'll rip off their name tags.
Okay, I'll turn their backs towards you,
or even if I'm in front of you like this
just reach around with your arm, and do it.
Here, let's practice how we'll do it.
[Yes, Min Ah... that's how you do it.]
No, they can't rip off our name tags.
No one will be able to resist you.
Can't the two of us just run away
and live happily on our own?
- I see someone!
- Where?
[There's someone!]
[Could it be Kwang Soo?]
Where?
It was just the wind.
Min Ah... are you starting to see things?
[Could someone be outside?]
There's no one out here.
I feel like you're purposely going outside
because it feels cooler out there.
Min Ah, I really want to go through
with this wedding.
Min Ah, have you ever seen us playing
the name tag elimination game?
[Min Ah and Gary are coming!]
Get him!
- Jae Suk, who did they eliminate?
- I don't know, but Gary's coming.
I see Ji Hyo and Jae Suk over there.
[Jae Suk and Ji Hyo are cornered.]
- You go that way, and I go this way?
- Okay, on the count of three.
[Min Ah to the left and Gary to the right.]
Fighting!
[Let's go and eliminate their name tags!]
Jae Suk, you can't go that way!
Gary will be coming from that way.
- Min Ah!
- Jae Suk, wait.
- Min Ah's coming.
- Min Ah!
[Let's make our escape!]
[Jae Suk escapes the moment of danger
by the split of a hair.]
- I can't consent to this marriage!
- You have no choice!
- I can't allow for this wedding to happen.
- I'm sorry, Ji Hyo.
I'm really sorry, Ji Hyo,
but I really want to marry her.
[Song Ji Hyo- Out!]
You're going to regret this, Min Ah.
- You're going to regret this!
- I'm sorry for stealing your man away.
- He's not a good man like you think he is!
- I'm sorry, Ji Hyo!
[Sorry, but I have to get going.]
- Stop poisoning her with your words!
- This will be for the rest of your life!
[The Monday Couple if shattered
with Min Ah in the picture.]
She has no idea what kind of a man
Kang Gary really is.
I'm in big trouble.
Ugh, you startled me.
- You really startled me.
- I had a feeling I'd find you here.
[The meeting of the two enemies.]
Gary!
Jong Kook is over there.
- Where?
- He's in that room over there.
Hurry up and get him.
Jong Kook is over there.
[Since I'm already here,
let's eliminate you first.]
[Yoo Jae Suk- Out!]
- I have to eliminate everyone right now.
- You are so frustrating!
Just be patient. I have to
go through with this wedding.
[With Jae Suk's help, Min Ah heads out
to catch Mr. Capable...]
- Who's back there?
- I have to go through with this wedding.
- It's a boy.
- A boy?
- There are two back there.
- Two? We've hit the jackpot!
[Wait, that silhouette is...]
Let's go, let's just go.
We can't eliminate this one.
- No, I want to eliminate him.
- You got someone?
- I got someone here.
- that's his VJ.
That's his personal VJ.
- Min Ah, let's just come back later.
- I'm not letting go of the groom.
- I can't let your groom go.
- Min Ah!
[But Kkuk isn't able to remain
so strong in front of Min Ah...]
Rip it off, Min Ah.
[I'll take care of Kkuk myself.]
[Gary leaves the scene,
and it's a match of Min Ah vs Kkuk.]
- I don't know what to do.
- I'm actually doing this for you.
You're going to regret marrying him.
I'm his older brother.
- Big brother...
- I'd be your brother in law.
- Why don't you go get someone else first?
- No, I can't.
- Why not?
- Because you're the strongest opponent.
It's too hot.
[It's so hot in here...]
[She says she's getting too hot...]
[Kim Jong Kook- Out!]
[After having held out for a while...]
The reason why I oppose
this marriage...
First of all, I just don't like the idea of
marriage between those two people.
I just feel like I'm the one
that she should be marrying.
I did a project where I married
my very first love.
Ugh, you startled me.
Hello.
[Successful team play!
Already ousted three members.]
Does that fan feel good?
- Yes, would you like to try it?
- No, it's okay.
I feel a little awkward.
- It's only been...
- A day since we started dating.
It only took me a day to decide
that I wanted to marry her.
[Big-nose is hiding under this table.]
[Big-nose shines the light on himself
with the flashlight under the table.]
This is the perfect hiding spot.
[Min Ah and Gary start their search
through the reception hall.]
There aren't any hiding places in here.
Who is that?
[Where is everyone?]
[Wait, that is...]
[The wrong table.]
I'm starting to regret hiding under here.
I should get out of here. I don't
think I can stay under here anymore.
[You should just stay there...]
Are they gone?
That was the best hiding spot.
This is the best hiding spot.
[The way you look from behind...]
[Gary has been watching him
from behind the door!]
[You're the one who came out
from under the table.]
[Even Ha Ha is surprised from
up in the balcony!]
I was looking the other way!
[Ji Suk Jin- Out!]
How did you know that
I was in here?
[Good job, Gary!]
- You guys are all here already?
- Did you get ousted?
What's Jong Kook doing here?
[Still filled with his regrets.]
Just as I predicted, Gary's doing
a good job of ousting people.
Kwang Soo!
- Did you all get ousted?
- Yeah.
Why don't you come and sit down?
Sit down and just look natural.
Knowing Gary,
you might succeed in fooling him.
Yeah, you should put my jacket on.
[Puts on Jong Kook's jacket in
an attempt to deceive Gary.]
- Did you all get eliminated?
- What?
- Yeah, we all got eliminated.
- Kwang Soo, too?
No, not Kwang Soo.
- Jong Suk, where did everyone go?
- I don't know.
[Where did Gary and Min Ah go?]
Look behind you!
[Gary's too distracted with Jong Suk
to notice Kwang Soo sitting at the table.]
Gary can't eliminate our team.
He can't eliminate his own team.
[Even Min Ah just breezes past Kwang Soo.]
That's a great idea.
Gary really is clueless sometimes.
Min Ah, let's talk for a minute.
Wait!
[Full on attack!]
Grab him.
- Gary, go that way.
- Wait.
- Let's talk.
- Min Ah!
- Hurry!
- Wait, let's talk for a minute.
Now's the chance!
Eliminate him!
How can you do this to me!
[Jo Jung Suk- Out!]
[Then... next up is Kwang Soo?]
Who do I still have left?
- Ha Ha?
- Yeah, Ha Ha.
- Dong Hoon's still out there.
- Is Ha Ha the only one left?
- I have to go through with this wedding.
- Dong Hoon's the last of us left?
[Even pat's Kwang Soo on the shoulder
before he walks away.]
- Is Dong Hoon the only one left?
- Fighting!
- Dong Hoon, hide!
[Something doesn't feel right...]
[Min Ah and Gary leave Kwang Soo
sitting at the table...]
- I don't even know what to say.
- He really must be stupid.
[Can't believe Gary was actually fooled...]
He even patted me on the shoulder.
I feel bad, but he patted me before leaving.
Maybe you're invisible to them.
I feel kind of offended by that.
[The only ones still left
are Kwang Soo and Ha Ha.]
- I can't find him anywhere.
- I'll try to look for him.
Gary, do you know what I think?
I think he's hiding under
one of those tables in there.
I thought we already looked in there.
[Wait, that's...]
I found him.
He's up there on the balcony.
[Ha Ha is discovered.]
I found him.
I think he saw me.
My arms are too short.
[Lying down on the floor?]
[A perfect fit.]
[I will do everything I can to endure this
and become the groom myself.]
[My short limbs... stay strong!]
[But the door opens too easily.]
Min Ah, you've lost your mind.
This isn't right!
Wait, this isn't right, Min Ah.
[Haroro's last desperate attempts.]
No, I oppose this marriage!
I oppose!
[Ha Ha- Out!]
- We got everyone.
- What do we do now?
We have to get married now.
[Everyone's gathered together
at the wedding ceremony site.]
Let's go get married.
Really?
[They can't possibly...]
[Kwang Soo... it's over!]
No, wait!
[Lee Kwang Soo- Out!]
- You just realized it now, didn't you?
- No, I've known about it!
[When they realized
the truth about Kwang Soo.]
- We got everyone, right?
- Did we get everyone?
- Did we get Kwang Soo?
- Did we not get him? He was sitting there.
Did we get him?
No, I didn't get him.
- I didn't get him either.
- He's my twin brother.
Then he deceived us
and is just sitting there?
[Slow Gary finally realizes the truth.]
You have to lure him.
- You have to trick him.
- Okay, I will. We got everyone.
[Thus, their plan was to trick Kwang Soo.]
[Opposing family name tag elimination-
Mission clear!]
Everyone now consents to their marriage.
[Min Ah and Gary's wedding
finally gets underway.]
- Please allow for us to get married.
- What a joke!
[Wedding photo.]
That's just absolutely absurd.
[The newlywed's kiss is omitted.]
Even though you're now a part of our family,
and you two should live happily together
you never know what life
may have in store for you.
- No, we're going to love each other forever.
- My most sincerest congratulations.
- What is this? Is this for real?
- Are they really getting married?
Is the show over?
Are we going on our honeymoon now?
You have successfully gotten married after
the sweet, yet brief courtship.
I congratulate you wholeheartedly,
and it's now time for the honeymoon.
Are we going to Maldives?
The newlyweds can go together in
their wedding car.
As for the remaining family members, you
will go in one car since you're now in-laws.
In one car?
No, I'd rather take the bus!
[The deep rooted resentment
between the two families.]
We want to go separately.
We'll see everyone in a little bit.
Sorry, excuse us.
[The newlyweds head out hand in hand.]
This is the worst wedding I've
even been to.
- They didn't feed us anything.
- Out of my way!
[Chapter one-
Courtship, then the wedding.]
Let's go.
[Off to ride away in their wedding car.]
I'm going to brag out loud
for everyone to hear.
Min Ah!
[Gary's consideration for Min Ah.]
- Let's go.
- So many cameras.
- There are a lot of cameras, aren't there?
- Yes.
[The appearance of the two families.]
- You're really going to regret this.
- We're so happy right now!
- No, you can't be happy about this.
- You really have to think about this.
Min Ah, you're happy, aren't you?
What are you doing?
[Min Ah's twin brother, Giraffe,
uninvited gets into the car.]
- Come on, let me ride with you guys.
- No, leave! I don't want you to.
- Pretend I'm not even here.
- No, leave!
Min Ah, here's my phone number.
What are you doing?
Don't be that kind of an in-law.
Ugh, I'm sorry.
They're a rowdy bunch, aren't they?
- Congratulations on your wedding.
- Okay.
This is a list of most desirable items
by recently married couples.
With the exception of these two spots
write down the items that you'd most
like to have in these empty circles.
A list of most desirable items
by newlyweds.
- TV.
- TV?
- What else?
- The air conditioner.
- And the bidet?
- Bidet? That could come in handy.
You're choosing very rationally.
Okay, bidet.
- Bedding?
Yes, we'd need some bedding.
How about some bathrobes?
- A pair of bathrobes?
- Sure.
Even these small moments
bring me so much happiness.
Okay, let's go.
[Off they go in their lone car ride.]
- What about pet names for each other?
- Pet names?
What do you think about,
'Goldie' and 'Jade'?
- Who's the Goldie?
- I'd be the Goldie.
- Then I'd be the Jade?
- Yeah.
- No, I don't want to do that.
- Why not?
I'm sick of those names.
I just want both our families
to disappear.
Are we going to get fed soon?
Kimchi stew or soybean stew.
On the count of three.
- Soybean stew.
- How about kimchi soybean stew?
- Okay.
- Let's never break up, okay?
- Yes, Ri.
- We are...
- Pretty-Ri!
- I think we're getting used to it.
- Yes.
- Jung Suk, are you a good singer?
- Jung Suk is a musical actor.
- Seriously?
- Do you even know anything about Jung Suk?
Jung Suk made a name for himself
on the musical stage.
Don't you know the song,
'Right at this moment...'
Right at this moment...
Like a total fool! (Got the lyrics wrong.)
[Our fool of a big brother...]
- Let's hear Jung Suk sing.
- Yes, let's hear him sing for us.
[Jung Suk's rendition of
'Right at this moment' from his musical.]
Yes, I want to hear him sing.
[An explosive reaction.]
- Stop reacting like that.
- Stop, we just want to hear him sing!
[These in-laws have a long way to go.]
Sorry about that.
Seriously...
This moment,
that I have so desperately longed for.
[A forced mute button.]
My own dream, and my own wish...
I don't know if they'll ever come true...
at least right at this moment.
[Jung Suk's singing hits
all the right emotional notes.]
Be quiet!
We're still reeling from
the emotions of his singing.
Right at this moment,
like a spell of magic...
I throw away the chains that
kept me tethered down.
All I have at this moment,
is my own conviction...
that the only thing that's left
for me is my own victory!
[Right at this moment,
it feels like we are the world...]
['E' Cafe in Gyunggi-do.]
- What are we doing here?
- What is all this?
[The sweet feel of a newlywed's home
can be felt throughout the space.]
Wow, look at the pictures of Min Ah.
She looks so pretty in her pictures.
What's taking them so long?
Why aren't they even here yet?
I know from my experience of being
with Gary for the past four years
but he's a really awful driver.
- You sound jealous.
- He's a really bad driver.
She sounds really jealous right now.
- That's pretty tacky.
- She's the obsessive type.
I'm not being obsessive.
I just don't want to see my sister suffer.
[Is that all?]
- She really must've liked Gary.
- Here they come.
[The newlyweds finally arrive.]
- The homeowners are here.
- You're grinning from ear to ear.
- What the heck?
- Why are you holding her hand?
- Hey, don't hold her hand!
- What? I'm just holding my wife's hand.
- Don't hold her hand!
- You saw how Min Ah held on, right?
I'm sorry to ask this, but what were you
doing that took you two so long to get here?
- I just really need to know the answer.
- What did we do?
- I'm sure they were talking about...
- Please don't do that.
Why are you two whispering?
- We were talking about a trip.
- A trip we're going to go on together.
- You're going on a trip together?
- No, we were talking about our past trips.
You two must've had a lot
to talk about.
- Yes, we talked about things like that.
- You two must've shared a lot of stories.
You have all now become one family with
the marriage of Gary and Min Ah.
- Yes.
- Wow, it feels like a real marriage.
It feels like the in-laws have
yet to become very close.
We have prepared a group mission that
you all will do together as one unit
to help bring everyone closer
as family.
Every time you successfully complete
each of these missions
you will be given a lottery ticket that
is worth quite a sum of money.
- You will be given a lottery ticket.
- Really?
We're not going to have a choice
but to work together.
Only one of these five lottery tickets
is the actual winning ticket.
Only when you succeed the mission,
will you be able to scratch off the ticket.
- First...
- Pretty... how about you do it?
Did someone say, Pretty?
[Automatically responds to the name, Pretty.]
- How are you 'Pretty'?
- You two seem closer to each other.
- We have a pet name for each other.
- Seriously?
- Min Ah, what do you call Gary?
- Ri.
- Ri?
- What's that?
I guess she couldn't think of
anything else to call him by.
Your first mission is...
'As long as it's with you.'
Each person will take one end of
a noodle strand and meet in the middle.
Look at Gary.
The total length from all the couples must be
less than 5cm combined in order to win.
- 5cm?
- Less than 5cm?
- I think that's too long.
- How about 4cm for four boy-girl couples?
No, we'll go with three couples with
a total combined length of 3cm.
Okay, we'll go with the 3cm!
- Okay, we're just going to watch.
- Why don't you watch from here?
I'm going to watch Shin Min Ah.
[Everyone else seems to be doing well,
but how am I going to do this?]
[Whatever the case, let's just bite down.]
- Song Ji Hyo, you're being really forward.
- Jung Suk, I'm keeping my eyes on you.
Ready.
- Hurry up!
- Who's not ready yet?
- It's Gary.
- Is this how I do it?
- Ugh, seriously.
- Wow, this is awesome.
- Jong Suk, just touch her lips.
- This is awesome.
- It's a nice picture, except for those two.
[Automatically cringes back
just from watching these two.]
[Second team- Jong Suk and Ji Hyo.]
[Here I go.]
[Okay, come.]
[We're both actors.]
- Go in further!
- You can touch her lips!
- Song Ji Hyo, work harder.
- It has to be 1cm.
[Audience is really getting into it.]
[The noodle strand is getting shorter
and shorter without any hesitation.]
- With your teeth!
- Go in further!
[We'll see about that, Song Ji Hyo.]
- It should've been shorter!
- No, I think we got it.
You two need to finish it up.
It's up to you guys now.
This is what we've got,
so you two need to get it done.
[The bride doesn't seem to show
any sign of nervousness.]
[The groom doesn't seem to be sure
whether this is a dream or reality...]
[It's not going to be easy.]
- You need to get it down to 0.2cm.
- No need to be nervous about it.
[Both players approaches each other's lips
without any show of hesitation.]
[But this person doesn't seem to be
happy about it.]
[We can't lose to the other couple!]
[Screams out loud in response.]
[It's no big deal to an actress like me.]
- It's almost gone.
- Did you see Min Ah?
Did you see how Min Ah was
just doing this?
[Min Ah shows just how comfortable she
is with what she had just done.]
She looked completely at ease.
[Showing off her talent
as a skilled actress.]
She was just standing there
and slurping it down like this.
[That was no big deal.]
- How can you not even be blushing?
- Gary's face is so red.
Shin Min Ah's really forward.
She's really good at this game.
How are you so good at that?
You have to just think of your lips touching
and get it as short as you can.
You had an ulterior motive, didn't you?
She didn't feel shy about it at all.
- Ji Hyo, your hands were up by his face.
- Gary...
Are you getting jealous right now?
Ji Hyo and Jung Suk's noodle length
is 1.1cm.
- We got this.
- We should be good, right?
Jae Suk and Kwang Soo's length is 0.6cm.
- That's amazing.
- Their length is less than 1cm.
Gary and Min Ah's length is 0.4cm.
That's because Min Ah slurped down
the last bit of it.
[They got to see first-hand how skilled
Min Ah can be at this game.]
Thus, Min Ah and Gary just earned the
chance to choose a lottery ticket.
[Time to check their lottery ticket.]
- Try scratching one.
- What if this is the winning ticket?
If it turns out to be the winning ticket,
then it's the end of the race.
Will they get actual real money?
[It's a dud!
Perhaps next time.]
They're not all duds, are they?
- You may now choose the next one.
- Choose a good one, Jung Suk.
[Second lottery ticket selection.]
[Must pass the next mission in order
to check to see if it's the winning ticket.]
Here's your next mission.
It's a game that can't be left out at
a newlywed's housewarming party.
It's time to hear
the bride's singing talents.
[Bride's singing talents.]
- Me?
- Yes, of course.
The second mission, 'Bride's love song.'
Choose your favorite song to sing.
Min Ah never seems nervous
about anything.
- What do you mean?
- Girls always squirm and protest it.
But all she said was, 'Me?'
[Remaining so cool
in all types of situations.]
- She shows her agitation in the back.
- Really?
When people are looking elsewhere,
she shows her nervousness like this.
- She doesn't seem nervous whatsoever.
- She seems so composed.
It's fun to do things like this
at a housewarming party.
[Must score 90 points or above to win.]
- I'd like to sing, 'Please stop the wind.'
- Nice choice!
[If the bride fails to score 90 points,
then the other members will be punished.]
Don't worry, I'd never cheat on you.
If you can't sing, then you can't marry.
Ugh, what a hateful person.
['Please stop the wind' by Lee Ji Yeon.]
I'm so nervous!
[At least for this one moment,
they are as one family and one heart.]
[The love song sang by
the beautiful October bride.]
[Such a clear voice.]
[Singing confidently without
any sign of nervousness.]
[Gets into the groove of the song,
and moves out of his designated spot.]
[The groom dances along to
his bride's singing.]
[Get out of here!]
[Pushes the Giraffe out so that
he could have more dance space.]
[The party guests are getting into the feel
of the party with the bride's singing.]
[Min Ah's talent from her many participation
of previous OST singing shines through.]
He's dancing along as if
he's doing a musical right now.
[Plays the tambourine as if
he's in a musical.]
[The newlywed's wave.]
[Everybody... stop.]
[Singing together as
one heart, and one family.]
Extra points for enthusiasm is...
five points!
- We just need 85 points.
- We only need 85 points!
[85 points or above,
then it's mission clear!]
[What will be the score?]
[87 points plus five is...
A total of 92 points!]
[Succeeds the mission on the
first attempt!]
[Once again, the success is all thanks
to the enthusiastic new bride!]
Want to sing one more song with
another lottery ticket on the line?
There's no stopping you.
There's nothing that Min Ah
isn't good at.
- Let's go for one more lottery ticket.
- One more song.
[An encore song with
one more lottery ticket on the line.]
- We'll sing another song.
- As promised, this mission is a success.
[With the success of the mission,
it's a chance to check another ticket.]
- We need to sing another song.
- 87 points is a great score.
Since we already succeeded this mission,
let's really crank it up this time.
- Jong Suk, it's your turn to sing.
- She's the goddess of these games.
- That's awesome.
- She really is amazing.
I don't know what to sing.
[It's musical star,
Jung Suk's time to shine.]
- Should I sing something upbeat?
- Yes, do that.
[Choosing the lottery ticket
for the encore mission.]
I feel so comfortable
with these two already.
They both like to sing old
people's songs.
[What will this musical star choose to sing?]
[Jung Suk chooses to sing, 'Sorrow.']
Party time!
[Sorrow- 1998.]
[A dance show right off the bat.]
[I told you to get out of here!]
[Jung Suk's musical version
of the song, 'Sorrow'.]
[Perfectly in sync.]
[His stellar singing talent can be heard
with the opening lyrics.]
[Matching dance moves to the song
from another era.]
No, that's not it...
[It's your tune that isn't it.]
[Jung Suk and Blank Ji's
duet performance.]
[Jung Suk's musical version of the song!]
[A very enthusiastic
housewarming party guests.]
[The newlyweds are immersed
in their dance moves.]
[This housewarming party
will go down in history.]
[What kind of a score
will they receive this time?]
[Wow!]
[98 points!
Succeeds another mission!]
[Succeeds two missions in a row!]
[A perfect harmony made possible
by these two families.]
You have earned two lottery tickets.
We can't give you any more than that.
- You have the two tickets, don't you?
- Why are you stuttering your speech?
[You didn't know we'd be this
good, did you?]
Even if you're to go to karaoke bars,
it's impossible to get these kinds of scores.
[These housewarming party guests are taking
a long trip down the singing memory lane.]
[Another encore song without even
a lottery ticket on the line.]
- How about 'From the bus'?
- Ji Hyo's really excited.
[Everyone's in very high spirits as if
they're on a fun outing.]
How about the song, '3!4!'
[Once wildly popular, '3!4!' is chosen.]
- 3!4!
- We have to start it off right.
[The start of the song is the
most important part of the song.]
[Director Haroro is taking the song
very seriously.]
- Just sit around comfortably.
- How are we doing this?
['3!4!'- 1996.]
[The lone contemporary dancer.]
- What are you doing?
- You're not the star of the song!
- When do we stand up?
- Starting from the right.
When she says, '3!4!.'
[Drops down two octaves.]
[Now is the time!]
[In an orderly fashion.]
[The two families become
one with the music.]
[MC Memi-Nem's freestyle rap.]
Your footsteps are so fast!
[Impressive footwork.]
[Make way for the new King of Dance!]
Me?
Okay, I like that!
[A dance battle with Ha Ha.]
[I can't let you beat me!]
[Jung Suk has another trick up his sleeve.]
[Come on!]
[Sees Ha Ha's moves, and Jung Suk
immediately copies the moves.]
[Turbo's dancing Tiger.]
[Dream concert housewarming party.]
[The perfect impromptu performance.]
[I can't get tired out now.]
[A musical performance.]
[One move... and one heart.]
[Really getting into it!]
Where will this breathing
moment take me?
From where all these moments are
starting to jumble together...
[Wishing the newlyweds
a lifetime of happiness...]
Bend over.
[A perfect reenactment of
the song's original dance moves.]
[A very enthusiastic and
passionate housewarming party.]
There's no stopping us!
[Top score with everything
that they sing!]
- That was good.
- Did everyone have fun?
All the songs we sang were
from the nineties.
[A time traced back to the nineties
with their singing.]
I'm sure one of those two has
to be the winning ticket.
[Time to check the lottery ticket.]
- I see something.
- Really?
- Dud.
- It's another dud.
[A dud!
Maybe the next ticket.]
- Can it be?
- No, it's another dud.
[Another dud for the second ticket.]
I'm sorry, but can you give me a shot
of air? I'm really hot right now.
Okay, here's a shot of air.
[I've never felt anything quite like it...]
Why was it shooting out water?
That was shooting out water.
- Why was it shooting out water?
- Why was it shooting water?
I don't know.
But that was a shot of water.
[Is it supposed to be a shot of water?]
It's his water bottle!
Seriously!
What are you doing!
- What's wrong with you lately?
- You didn't know?
You're acting like a kid!
[I really didn't know...]
One of these last two is
the winning ticket.
- It's either number two or three.
- Why don't you pick one, Ji Hyo?
- She's lucky with things like that.
- Do you have a feel for which one it is?
- There she goes.
- She doesn't even hesitate.
[Running Man's goddess of luck-
Will luck be on her side this time, too?]
Here's your next mission.
Your next mission is,
'Perfect pair telepathic quiz.'
[Succeed the mission by correctly
answering three questions in a row.]
[The goddess of games-
Will she succeed again on the first try?]
- Okay, they're good to go.
- I have a good feeling about this.
[The two must correctly answer the questions
simultaneously in order to win the mission.]
Okay, here's your first question.
Ready.
What is the first thing you look at
when you look at your opponent?
- Eyes.
[Their close friendship shows through
their perfect compatibility.]
We just have two more questions to go!
What is the gift that is most often bought
for any anniversary event?
- Flowers!
[Quickly succeeds in answering
two questions correctly.]
The most desired location
to out on a date is?
[If we get this question right,
then we can clear the mission...]
One, two, three!
[Fail]
[Jung Suk and Min Ah fails the mission
so close to succeeding.]
We were so close.
[Second couple- Jae Suk and Kwang Soo.]
The first thought that pops into your head
when you think of Yoo Jae Suk?
- Grasshopper!
The best looking member
of Running Man cast is?
- Yoo Jae Suk!
[Giraffe is feeling enraged after
having shouted out his answer.]
Here's your third question.
Favorite movie genre is?
- Thriller!
- Something like a thriller?
[Giraffe's attempt to scheme
the answer.]
Just give us one more chance.
- Give us just one more chance.
- You know what I was trying to say, right?
- Give us one more chance.
- They're so cute.
Favorite Hong Kong actress is?
- I...
- Well...
You should've said, Joo Yoon Bal.
- Was I supposed to name just one person?
- One specific person?
One, two, three!
[We will end this mission.]
- I...
- Joo... something?
- Joo Yoon Bal.
- That's right, Joo Yoon Bal.
- Yes, Joo Yoon Bal.
- Joo Yoon Bal.
[Jae Suk and Kwang Soo fail.]
Get out of there!
[Fails at the final question.]
You failed to answer
the last question correctly.
[Third attempt-
Back to Jung Suk and Min Ah.]
- Min Ah, be careful.
- Take it easy.
- Ready.
- Go!
Dog or a cat?
One, two, three!
- Dog!
- Wow, that was so spot on.
- There wasn't even any hesitation.
- I thought that was just one voice.
- Such a precise answer.
Here's the next one.
Spice or fried?
- Spice!
That was right.
They're good.
[Just one more question left to go.]
Here's your next question.
Spicy or mild nanygmyun?
[The victory of this mission
rides on this one question.]
- Spicy!
[Successfully clears the third mission!]
- That's unbelievable.
- I can't believe they got that.
[Time to check the lottery ticket.]
Before you check the ticket,
know that it could be another dud.
- Sit down and check the ticket.
- I see something red!
- I see something.
- It's the winning ticket, isn't it?
[The winning ticket.]
[Blank Ji definitely is
Running Man's goddess of luck.]
- Check the amount.
- Three million Won?
[Jackpot amount is Three Million Won!]
[They're really giving it to us!]
Are you really giving this to us?
- It's for real.
- Why are they giving this to us?
- Count the money.
- It really is three million Won.
Yes, it's correct.
[What is the secret hidden behind
the winning lottery ticket?]
[Off to the final location with
the lottery jackpot in hand.]
- My family picked the winning ticket.
- Yes, that's correct.
It's only because we pointed you
towards the right direction.
[Back to bickering over who brought
home the winning lottery ticket.]
- Are you disrespecting my family?
- Jong Kook.
- Jong Kook?
- Wait.
[Why are they acting like this again?]
- What a disrespectful family.
- I just called you by your name.
[The two families are set on edge with
the lottery jackpot balanced on the line.]
How did we get stuck with
a family like this?
If it wasn't for Min Ah...
You should be honored to have
become in-laws with our family.
If you want to get fed,
you'd be wise to keep your mouths shut.
My nickname is 'Lightning.'
Maybe it's because you have lightning
fast family meetings all the time.
[Our in-law is
the 'Lightning of Apgujeong.']
My fist is lightning fast.
[The conflict between these two families-
What fate lies ahead for this couple?]
[Chapter two-
Marriage, and the never-ending battle.]
[Gyunggi Sungnam-si's Job World.]
- That's a cake.
- Wow, it's a cake.
[Is that a wedding cake?]
It's time to give out the jackpot money.
- But I do have an unfortunate bit of news.
- What is it?
Only one person can take
the jackpot money home.
Then I'll take care of managing
the money.
- Yes, the man should take care of that.
- Listen to him, Min Ah.
No, I want it.
- No, I want it.
- She's suddenly being so aggressive.
- She wasn't even saying anything...
- That's the loudest she's spoken all day.
- She's suddenly being so aggressive.
- How are we going to do this?
The man brings home the money, and the
woman is supposed to manage the money.
- The woman is supposed to manage it.
- This family just doesn't get it.
- You guys all have such nasty tempers.
- What an ignorant bunch of people.
- What? Ignorant bunch of people?
- I'll teach all of you a lesson.
- This wedding is nullified!
- I chose the winning ticket!
[The family battle ensues.]
We shouldn't even associate
ourselves with this family.
- What an ignorant bunch of people.
- Can you help us do something about this?
Since the two families and the couple
themselves can't come to an agreement
the couple should split up and go to
their own respective families for now.
[Everyone is to go back to
their own families.]
Just take the money, Min Ah.
I don't want us to split up.
- Really?
- No.
- I'm going back to my own family.
- Come on, don't bother with them.
[After their first quarrel over the money,
they each go back to their own family.]
Ugh, Min Ah picked the wrong guy
from a very unsuitable family.
What is it that you liked so
much about him?
Our Min Ah was so focused on her work that
she never even got to experience dating.
I took her back and forth to school
when she was a little girl.
That's why I never even got to
go to school.
- He's telling the truth.
- So that's what's wrong with you.
[The sad truth behind the two twins.]
We will now tell you how the jackpot
money should be distributed.
Please take a look at the monitor
that's placed in front of you.
- Do you all see the board?
- Yes.
A variety of household items that belong in
those empty slots on the board are hidden
throughout this building.
You must find the hidden household
items that are hidden in this building
and place it on top of the platform.
Once the household items are
placed on top of the platform
then the slot the item belongs in will light
up in the color of the team that found it.
From the slot on the very bottom to
the heart that's on top of the cake
the team that gets to that heart first
will get to keep the jackpot money.
- Okay, I get it.
- It's like filling up their hope chest.
Neither teams will know which item
will belong in which slot on the board.
But the bride and the groom possess
the clue to that answer.
- Do you remember anything?
- No, I don't.
Did they give you guys anything?
But the bride and the groom possess
the clue to that answer.
Didn't you say that you wrote
something down earlier?
Did they give you anything?
[The reason being...]
[The newlyweds themselves wrote down what
they'd like to have for their new house.]
What they wrote down earlier matches
the placement of the items on the board.
- Do you remember what you wrote down?
- Gary's the one who wrote all that down.
We're totally ruined!
I know I wrote them down,
but I don't remember a single thing.
But I can guarantee that Gary
doesn't remember what he wrote down.
We didn't write anything down
in the top two slots.
[But they weren't allowed to write
anything down in the top two slots.]
[Meaning that these two slots are random
items that the newlyweds didn't choose.]
- We chose a TV.
- This isn't about love.
Of course it's not about love.
It's about money right now.
I'm positive that Min Ah is only
thinking about money right now.
[Money distribution-
Household item search race- Start.]
I'll remember once I hear it.
Tell me what it is, and I'll remember it.
One, two, three, fighting!
[Who will be the one to take home
the lottery jackpot?]
I know what items we picked,
but I don't remember where I placed them.
Why did I allow myself to
be entranced by my bride?
Vacuum, air conditioner, wall decor...
[Groom Gary is trying to jog his memory.]
And...
- Bedding?
Bedding.
There was bedding on that list, too.
There's bedding on that list as well.
Okay, I got it.
Have you found anything yet?
[Everyone's scattering off to find items
with the 'R' sticker on it.]
Jong Kook, Kwang Soo has something!
[Ha Ha discovers Kwang Soo with
something hidden under his jacket.]
Kwang Soo's heading up to the second floor!
[Ha Ha notifies his teammates
and takes off after Kwang Soo.]
What is it?
Someone found something.
- Someone found something.
- Jae Suk!
- Jung Suk!
- What is it?
- Jong Kook! Come and help!
[The in-laws are all flocking
towards Kwang Soo.]
[Attempts to hand off the
item to Min Ah.]
- Stop Jung Suk.
- Hurry up and go.
[Big-nose gives Jung Suk a big bear hug.]
[Min Ah is handed something
in the midst of all the chaos.]
[Huh? What is this?]
- What is that?
- What the heck is that?
[Min Ah loses the strength in her legs
from the shock of seeing what it is.]
- Why did you deceive Min Ah?
- You deceived Min Ah?
Why are you deceiving your own
team member?
[Giraffe tried to trick the opposing team,
but ended up deceiving Min Ah instead.]
[Even Jung Suk fell for the trick
and sped over to Kwang Soo.]
- Why did you trick Min Ah?
- What was that?
- Can you actually do that?
- What were you thinking?
- Sorry, Min Ah.
- Seriously.
She was taking such care with it, too.
[So... this is how you play the game?]
Min Ah.
Do you remember what
you wrote down earlier?
- No.
- You don't remember anything?
- No, Gary wrote things down.
- He wrote everything down?
[Jung Suk attempts to pry information out of
her by pretending to get her some water.]
- I remember there was a washer.
- A washer?
[Immediately resorts to trickery after
witnessing Kwang Soo's attempt.]
A clothes' hangar?
You wrote down clothes hangar?
- Why would you write down clothing hangar?
- We also wrote down a cat and a dog.
Really?
What else?
- A crab, and a lion.
- A crab and a lion?
[Randomly spews things out,
and he naively accepts them.]
Lee Kwang Soo, out.
[An announcement of Kwang Soo's elimination
is broadcasted out of nowhere.]
[What? I'm eliminated?]
Lee Kwang Soo, out.
- Why? What happened?
- What do you mean, why?
- It's because I wanted him out.
- What's wrong with him?
[Kiddo Ha plays a prank
with the loudspeaker in his hand.]
[Searching through every nook and cranny
for items with the 'R' sticker on it.]
[Discovers the bidet.]
[Races off towards the platform.]
[Successfully evades the opposing team
to arrive at the platform.]
Okay.
[The Groom's family acquires the bidet.]
[Which slot on the board
does the bidet belong in?]
Okay, we found one!
[Groom's family takes the first slot.]
We've got one.
- Let's check this one out.
- No Way.
Do you really need a horse mask
for a newlywed's home?
[Did I not hear her right?]
Is there an 'R' sticker on it?
[Naive Jung Suk brought the horse mask
after fully trusting what Min Ah told him.]
- It needs the 'R' sticker on it.
- What are you doing?
- Did Min Ah lie to me?
What's wrong with you?
Why are you so naive?
The horse mask is not one of
the household items.
[That Shin Min Ah...]
I wonder if there's something in here.
[Blank Ji is searching everywhere
for the needed household item.]
The pumpkin?
[Discovers the air conditioner
by pure chance.]
It's the air conditioner.
What do I do?
[Kkuk is watching what's going on
from hiding.]
Guys, come to the kid's center
for a minute.
Come to the kid's center.
- Guys, come to the kid's center.
- Jae Suk, come to the kid's center quick.
- The kid's center.
- Jae Suk, I found the air conditioner.
- That big thing over there?
- Jae Suk, come to the kid's center now!
Wow, that big thing?
Is there an 'R' sticker on it?
- It's mine.
- Let me just see what it looks like.
- I bought it and left it here.
- Let me just take a look at it.
I just need one of you guys
to come to the kid's center.
- Where's the kid's center?
- Is that on the first floor?
- I need one of my people to come here.
- Over here, Jae Suk.
- Why did so many of you come?
- Where is it?
Why is there an army of you?
[The key point of the weaker team
is that they travel in a pack.]
We need to get this out of here
before the other team arrives.
Is it the air conditioner?
How are we going to get this out of here?
- They just found an air conditioner.
- I found something else that's really good.
[While Ha Ha brags to Jong Kook and
tries to elicit a compliment from him...]
- Stay down here, Ji Hyo.
- Come, hurry!
- We need to go now!
- Now's our chance!
[But why is Ji Hyo carrying the heavy
item with the three men around?]
Put it up there.
- There you go.
- Come here.
Ugh, it's right there?
No, never mind.
They already got it.
[Where does the air conditioner
belong on the board?]
- Nice, it's right in the middle.
- That's a good spot.
Okay, let's go.
Good job.
[Both the Groom and the Bride's side
of the family each got one item.]
[Hello, my husband.]
Hi, I feel myself melting
at your smile again.
- Do you remember anything?
- No, I don't.
[Still remaining sweet even though they're
split up by their family's bitter feud.]
- You wrote everything down.
- But I don't remember anything either.
Even though we're split up now,
we're getting back together, aren't we?
- Of course, we're getting back together.
- Then if you could tell me where...
But Min Ah, I really don't remember anything.
I didn't even remember the items.
- What did we write down again?
- Clothes hangers.
Clothes hangers?
No, there wasn't.
- Are you trying to deceive me right now?
- No, I'm not.
You told naive Jung Suk that
the horse mask was on the list.
Do you know how much he ran around
with that horse mask in hand?
- I really don't remember anything.
- Why did you tell him that?
- What would you need a horse mask for?
- I don't remember writing that down.
- I'm sure that there were clothes hangers.
- No, we didn't choose any clothes hangers.
- You're a very strange one.
- Knife and cutting board...
Knife and cutting board?
Jong Kook, we didn't pick those items.
- She's very strange.
- She's actually lying to me now.
I didn't take her to be like that.
I don't remember.
Knife?
I don't even remember what I chose.
[Min Ah wasn't lying,
she really just doesn't remember.]
[In her search for
the knife and the cutting board...]
[She finds the toaster by pure luck.]
I need someone to
come down to the restaurant.
[Just then...]
[Groom Gary finds the coffee pot.]
I found the coffee pot.
I don't see anyone.
Hurry!
[Off towards the platform!]
[Groom's family- Coffee pot.]
[Bride's family- Toaster.]
Please, let it be this one or that one.
I need one of those slots.
[Groom's family- The bidet and
the coffeepot are a direct link!]
- Okay, that's a nice line.
- Okay, we're good.
[The Bride's family is also
heading in the right direction.]
- Let's go, party time.
- You did good.
- We've got two now.
- I still haven't even seen anything.
I see another lit up slot.
Gary, there's another pink light.
- Which direction is their line headed?
- Over here at the end.
- So they're not in a good spot?
- The two slots aren't connected.
We need one of the two slots
up at the top.
Let's just face it head on.
- Suk Jin.
- Yeah?
Come here, Ha Ha.
[The 'R' sticker...]
[Attempted to go head on with the sticker
stuck to the front of the bathrobe.]
[Run and escape.]
- Come up to the top, Kwang Soo!
- Where?
Where?
- Suk Jin, where are you?
Are you looking for me?
This is really important, but no one's...
Come down here!
The Blue Team only needs two more
in order to win!
[It's a total war up on the second floor.]
[The bathrobe model is surrounded
by a band of opponents.]
Hurry up and get here!
- Stop tickling me.
- Excuse me, In-law.
- What?
- What you're doing now...
They just need to find two more
before they win!
Everyone come down to the first floor!
- No, you can't take it!
- Let's try to talk this out.
[Jung Suk and Gary each take
one person to block off.]
[Kkuk is busy spinning Big-nose around.]
[Kkuk succeeds in stealing
the bathrobe away.]
Jong Kook!
[After catching the robe,
Jung Suk sprints for the platform.]
It's off to the left!
[Succeeds in planting the robe
on top of the platform.]
[If one of these two slots lights up,
then they are almost to their victory!]
[But unfortunately lands in
a disadvantageous spot.]
If it had been one of these spots...
We just need one of those two slots.
What the heck?
We have to find the middle one.
You're all dead if you don't answer this.
- Hey.
- Jae Suk.
- What are you doing instead of searching.
- Listen to me.
I've been wanting you to come down here.
We have to find the middle one.
You have to remember this
and we need to find the one in the middle.
Are you going to keep staying down here
or are you going to start searching?
I'm telling you a very important
piece of information right now.
I placed a flower basket
on top of the platform.
We have to find the rest.
[The Groom's family successfully finds
the flower pot and the rice cooker.]
- Have you found anything?
- No, I don't remember anything.
- Kwang Soo, have you found anything?
- No, nothing.
- What's the last thing we wrote down?
- The bathrobe.
- Kwang Soo?
- But the bathrobe's already been found.
- No, I don't see anything.
- Come on, Gary.
[Meanwhile, Kwang Soo starts searching
through one of the stores.]
[That's a mini-fridge!]
Why? Why are you
suddenly looking at me like that?
- We need to talk.
- What do you want to talk about?
We...
[Even though you've lied to me,
you're still so pretty...]
[Gary's body and heart are being
pulled by Min Ah's lure.]
[Kwang Soo takes advantage of the
moment and runs away with the fridge.]
Lee Kwang Soo!
It's the fridge!
[While Gary was entranced by Min Ah...
Kwang Soo makes a touchdown.]
[Speechless...]
That's why it's so crucial for
a man to meet a good woman.
We need to just follow the line.
[The Bride's family fortunately found an item
that's directly connected to their slot.]
- This would be three.
- We don't have time for this right now.
Why do they always tell me that
whenever I try to do something?
- What's wrong?
- I fell for a girl's spell again.
- What did you do that for?
- I really may have lovesickness.
What's wrong with you?
[The undeniable pull of the bride, Min Ah.]
You try approaching her and
see if you can resist her charms.
- Don't even stand close to her.
- I keep melting around her.
I become a melted puddle
of chocolate.
She's like a chocolate factory.
[You're my very own chocolate factory.]
[Bride's family still needs three,
and the Groom's family needs two slots.]
[That's a mini-car!]
[Kwang Soo makes a run for it after making
sure that the 'R' sticker is on it.]
Lee Kwang Soo!
[Household items hunters barrage in.]
- Where?
- Over here!
- Go, Kwang Soo!
- Jae Suk!
[Passes it off to Jae Suk.]
[The bride tosses out some action moves.]
- Hurry!
- Where is it?
[Yoo Hyuk is blocked off by the Groom's
family in front of the platform.]
- Min Ah.
- Min Ah! Don't lose it to them!
Where is it?
[Min Ah stays on her path.]
Jong Kook.
[Jae Suk immobilizes Jung Suk.]
Hurry while I've got Jung Suk.
[Min Ah succeeds in making her touchdown.]
[The unlisted min-car belongs to
one of the top two slots!]
What do we still have left to find?
[Both the families only has two more
slots left to find.]
Where did you find that?
[Bride's family soon thereafter
finds the old TV.]
[Groom's family finds the plunger.]
- When did you write this down?
- Are you angry?
I didn't write the mini-car down either.
We just need one more, right?
[Where does the recently found TV belong?]
[Just where they need it to be!]
- We just need to find one more.
- Tell everyone that we already found it.
[Where does the Groom's plunger belong?]
[At the very top spot!]
But the other team just needs to find
one more in order to win.
[It's down to one last item
for both the teams!]
Ji Hyo and Min Ah...
we only have one more left to find.
Tell them that I found the last one.
Breaking news.
The searching time will soon
come to a close
and we will now reveal the items needed
for the still missing slots on the board.
They're going to tell us.
[The items needed for the empty slots
on the board will now be revealed.]
Please check and find the
items needed.
[All they have left to do now is to find
the items still needed on the board!]
We need to find the bedding.
- Bedding?
- We just need to find the bedding.
[Bride's family- Bedding.
Groom's family- Vacuum.]
[Must find their item before
the opposing team finds theirs!]
Where am I going to find the bedding?
Bedding, bedding, bedding...
I just need someone to respond.
Is anyone even listening to me?
Bedding.
Rip up the bedding to shreds.
[It all comes down to this one moment.]
What do you want to do, Jung Suk?
Want to split up the money in half?
[Anxious Bride's desperate offer.]
- Are you being serious?
- But you have to help me find the bedding.
- But you can't betray me.
- I'd never betray you.
Bedding... where's the bedding?
[Bedding... and vacuum...
Where are you guys?]
I really want to find it.
[Is that a vacuum in Jung Suk's hand?]
- The Blue Team's found it.
- The Blue Team's found it!
- Where, Ji Hyo?
- Where are they?
Jung Suk, run!
No, not that way!
[A full on chase.]
- Run!
- We have to stop him.
[Jung Suk gets caught by
the Yoo-Lee brothers.]
I have to take it from you
no matter what.
Come on, let me just take it.
I really want to do it!
I want to get it up on the platform.
[Blank Ji snatches the vacuum away.]
- Ji Hyo, get it on the platform.
- Get it up there!
Hurry up and get it up there.
- Did you get it?
- I got it!
Ugh, we lost.
[But...]
That vacuum doesn't have
the 'R' sticker on it.
[What?]
- I totally faked them.
- You faked them?
[Naive Jung Suk's
completely unexpected trickery!]
How could you have lied to me?
You must be really tired
with all my running around.
- I feel like I'm running too fast.
- Thanks to you, we're getting a workout.
Really?
In that case...
I'm just kidding.
Kwang Soo, I'm so tired.
[Unable to recover after the trickery
that Jung Suk played on them.]
- I'm so tired.
- The bedding...
The bedding...
The vacuum has to be
around here somewhere.
[Will it be the vacuum or
the bedding first?]
[The final search is on
for the jackpot cash.]
[It's the real vacuum!]
[Must lure the opposing team's attention
away to another direction.]
- We need to find Dong Hoon.
- There he is over there.
- No, it's a fake.
- We've already been fooled once.
[We're not going to be fooled again.]
[But the Giraffe is fooled once again,
and the Bride runs over to join in.]
- Kwang Soo, you need to...
- Take his walkie-talkie.
[While Ha Ha's busy keeping Kwang Soo
distracted with the twin story...]
[Gary also discovers the vacuum.]
- What's going on with Dong Hoon?
- Hurry, Dong Hoon!
[After directing everyone over
to Ha Ha for distraction...]
Jong Kook, I found it.
- I just saw it.
- Do you have it?
[The Groom's team must carefully devise
a plan to get the item.]
I think the other team has
found something.
They would've taken it already
if they had found something.
- I think that was a lie.
- He could be faking it.
[Can't be...]
[It looks like bedding of some sort...]
[Gary seizes his chance and
grabs the vacuum.]
- Gary has something behind his back.
- Hurry, Jong Kook!
[Takes off full speed ahead.]
[It's their bedding!]
[Jae Suk also takes off for the platform.]
[Both team's final sprint.]
[Who will be the first
to get to the platform?]
[Who will be the one to take
the winning jackpot home?]
[Household Item Race-
The board game is now over.]
It's now time for the final reveal.
The team that lights up
the heart is the winner?
Please...
[Which team's line
will reach the heart first?]
[The Groom's vacuum was first to light up.]
[Succeeds in connecting all the slots!]
[Groom's family wins the race!]
- But the heart is cracked in half.
- It's okay.
- Your love is shattered.
- Our families are now sworn enemies.
[The in-law's relationship is
worsened even more by this debacle.]
That's Gary's win.
[Groom Gary to take the jackpot cash.]
- I feel so bad for our Min Ah.
- Just give me 30,000 Won.
- Just be patient.
- What are you going to do with 30,000 Won?
We need some cab fare.
Gary, do you want to share the winning cash
with the members of your family?
Of course, he does.
Don't try to make us feel nervous about it.
- The decision is up to you.
- It's real money, isn't it?
- With your family members...
- Say your closing remarks right now.
You can split the money
with your family...
- Or you can even keep it all to yourself.
- Seriously?
- Also, with the woman you once loved...
- Ji Hyo?
[Gary also has the option of sharing it with
Min Ah, and reconciling with her.]
Even if you do reconcile with her,
it's all over once the cameras are off.
- Wait, I need to think.
- Min Ah won't be back next week.
Get yourself together!
- You have to think about this.
- We're ready to welcome Husband Gae.
Don't put on the cutesy act
right now!
[The Groom's resolve is shaking with
the Bride's cute little show.]
She's putting on her cute act.
[The Bride's family is trying to convince
Gary by singing him a song of sweet love.]
- No, don't do this to me.
- Get yourself together!
[Honey...]
- Get away!
- Min Ah.
One...
[What will Gary choose?]
[Will it be family, money, or love?]
I'm going to share this money with my bride.
[Groom Gary, chooses his bride, Min Ah.]
We sweated and toiled
for you all day!
[His beautiful bride takes priority
over his own brothers.]
[A ring to symbolize their reconciliation
for the bride and the groom.]
Look at how shameless she is to stick
out her hand for that ring.
Wow, look at this girl.
- Min Ah's very shameless.
- You're something else.
[Gary and Min Ah are back to being newlyweds
with well wishes from their families.]
- Families must mean nothing to them.
- Obviously not.
This is why they say that
raising children is useless.
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Chapter three- War and Peace.]
- Let's go back to earth!
- I'm Superman.
- I'm Wonder woman.
- I'm a hero.
[The superheroes that saved the world
lie in slumber in these chambers.]
[But our heroes awaken from
their slumber in the fall of 2014.]
[To find that they've lost
their super powers.]
[The only way for them to
regain their powers...]
[Is to run and help out
all the innocent citizens.]
[Heroes to the rescue to
these unsuspecting citizens.]
[We can be found anywhere,
so don't be shocked!]
[If you want to become a true superhero,
then conquer your own fear!]
[Running Heroes- Heroes' Resurrection.]