Subtitles by DramaFever
[Running Man's Cooking Battle]
What is your name?
- Please state your name for the competition.
- I'm contestant, Yoo Jae Suk.
What kind of a dish will you be
cooking today?
We caught the fish we'll be cooking ourselves.
Park Soo Hong caught it himself.
Extremely fresh rockfish.
Not just any rockfish, but
a 50cm rockfish.
It's a giant-sized rockfish.
We'll be making spicy rockfish stew,
and sweet and sour rockfish.
- Do you have a name for your dish?
- Excuse me?
A name for your dish?
Didn't I just tell you that it was spicy
rockfish stew and sweet and sour rockfish?
[First weekend dinner menu of the new year.]
[Dinner made with love for the ones we love.]
[Are you ready to taste it?]
The year of the horse has risen on us.
This is Running Man Cooking Battle
for year 2014.
Dinner menu for
the first weekend of the new year.
[Contestant Couple One- Ji Hyo and Dong Wook.
Fresh ocean king crab.]
[Contestant Couple Two- Jae Suk and Soo Hong.
Taste the freshness of the rockfish.]
[Contestant Couple Three- Suk Jin, Kyung Ho.
Harmonious dish of eel, oysters, and teot.]
[Contestant Couple Four- Ha Ha and Sung Kyu.
Pride of Jeonju, Jeonju bibimbap.]
[Contestant Couple Five- Gary and Jae Kyung.
Naju's infamous Sanjeok.]
[Contestant Couple Six- Jong Kook, Kyung Ah.
Healthy Chicken Stew.]
[Contestant Couple 7- Kwang Soo, John Park.
Special noodle soup.]
[Which dish would you choose
to be on your dinner menu?]
[Real cooking battle to determine
the best of the best starts now.]
[Running Man Cooking Battle]
[2014 Running Man Cooking Arena-
Jae Suk and Soo Hong are the first to arrive.]
Soo Hong...
I can put all my faith in you, right?
Just put your faith in me, and trust me.
- Why isn't anyone here?
- What do you mean, no one's here?
[Jong Kook and Kyung Ah are the
second team to arrive.]
[First time they are greeting each other
after being apart all day long.]
- Good to see you.
- How did you get paired up with Kyung Ah?
[Jae Suk is shocked to see who
Jong Kook's partner is.]
You look so short next to Kyung Ah.
- You look totally short.
- You think I'm the only one?
- Try standing next to her yourself.
- Wow, she's so tall.
[Certified 'Chef' is already busy prepping
in the midst of all this.]
- I'm just opening everything up.
- You can't open anything up yet.
- Hello!
- Hey, Sung Kyu!
- Good to see you, Sung Kyu.
- I didn't know you'd all be here already.
I saw you clubbing with all the
younger guys the other night.
Did I look cool?
[Happy because he may have looked
cool amongst all the younger guys?]
- Are you a pretty good cook, Sung Kyu?
- I've been living on my own since I was 20.
So I've been cooking for myself
for almost five years now.
I had a brief glimpse at his cooking skills,
and the way he handles his knife is no joke.
- Someone else is here.
- Right in here.
It's Dong Wook!
[Ji Hyo and Dong Wook returning
from Ji Hyo's own hometown.]
- Who's Suk Jin's partner?
- Do you think that it's Sam Hye?
[Who could Big-nose's mysterious partner be?]
[It's Kyung Ho, the homemaker.]
- Where have you two been?
- We went and got some teot and oysters.
[This team went all the way to the seaside to
get fresh teot and oysters.]
- There they are.
- Who is it?
[Kwang Soo, John Park and Gary and Jae Kyung
are the last two teams to arrive.]
[Thus all the experts in each field of
expertise have now gathered in one spot.]
- It's the clubber brother.
- Why is he the clubber brother?
[The two infamous clubbers are
giving each other a high five.]
[Awkward seeing each other in
a brightly lit place...]
You all know what
the final mission is all about.
This is 2014 Running Man Cooking Battle,
'First weekend dinner menu of the new year.'
You will be utilizing the menu items and
cooking techniques you've gathered yourselves
to cook your own special dishes that could be
served on the first weekend dinner table.
You will have exactly 100 minutes
to complete cooking your dish.
We will stop the time exactly at
100 minutes.
We will stop the clock exactly at that time.
And in order to ensure a fair judging...
We will now welcome a panel of judges
that we have very carefully selected.
[Time for the panel of judges
to make their entrance.]
- They're coming out already?
- I wonder who they could be?
- Welcome your panel of judges.
- I wonder who they are.
[Who could they be?]
[Celebrity Chef- Raymond Kim.]
[Shocked at the appearance
of a top celebrity chef.]
[Expert in traditional Korean cooking-
Shim Young Soon.]
It's Shim Young Soon.
[Webtoon author- Jung Da Jung.]
[Made her debut and a huge success
with a webtoon focused on cooking.]
[Amazed]
[Chocolatier Louis Kang.]
I can't believe that they're all here!
[All the top experts in Korea have gathered!]
How are we ever to live up
to their expectations?
[Their level of nervousness is heightened
by the appearance of such experts.]
We're not good enough to have
a panel of judges like this.
- This is no joke.
- No, this is no joke.
[Today's competition is no joke!]
Selection of your ingredients,
your cooking process
and how unique you are with how you
cook up your dish and present it
will determine how I judge you today.
- Yes, I understand.
- She's so well spoken.
[Automatic respect mode.]
Since none of you are professional
chefs here
I'm going to be basing my judging
on how much fun you have while cooking.
If you do it like that...
I don't think it'll work out too well for you.
- I think that's going overboard.
- You have to have respect for the food.
I don't think they know Raymond Kim.
I remained very quiet during the whole thing.
Since I'm not a professional chef myself
I think I'm going to focus on
how much fun you have
and how clean you keep everything
during the competition.
As everyone else has already said...
I'm going to be judging to see
how much care you put into your cooking.
He has such a nice voice.
[Is Jae Kyung's plan to suck up to him?]
And how well you present your dishes,
and the look of your end results
such as color and
the presentation of the dish.
- Are you married?
- No.
[Queen of flattery chiming in
at every chance that she gets.]
- Jae Kyung is trying to butter him up.
- What is she doing?
If any of you have anything to ask the judges,
then now is your only chance to do so.
In that case...
would it be okay if I called you 'Mother'?
[Chastised for his comment.]
What's wrong with what I just said?
Her sweet smile was just so maternal.
Sis... do you remember me?
She doesn't go clubbing like you do.
- We just want to get closer to her.
- We've done a show together before.
Whether you call me 'mother', or 'sis'...
It's not going to have any effect
on my judging.
[Extremely fair and just panel of judges.]
Kwang Soo says he wants to ask
Sis Da Jung a question.
- Sis Da Jung?
- She looks much younger than you.
- I was born in '85.
- I was born in '91.
[He's calling a woman who's six years
younger than him an 'older sister'?]
[A mistake that he can't take back...]
How could he have said that to her when
she looks young enough to be a student?
- What's your ideal type?
- My ideal type?
You're not it, Kwang Soo.
She really told you on that one.
I have something I'd like to ask.
What's the criteria on how you judge
the presentation of the dish?
That's a very good question.
As far as how the presentation goes...
I think I'd be okay with it as long as there's
a good explanation for your presentation.
Even if it's not presented in the best way
if you have a reason for presenting it a
certain way, such as the order of dish to eat.
What is your opinion on being
a little extravagant with the presentation?
I oppose anything that's
inedible being presented.
[Opposed to anything inedible...]
[I guess they have something
extravagant on their minds?]
Then the panel of judges may
take their place.
- Thank you and take good care of us.
- Thank you.
[And we will see the panel of judges
in a little bit!]
- You will have exactly 100 minutes.
- We understand.
- Let's all play a fair and honest game.
- Yes, I agree.
Don't pull out a secret sauce and ingredient
and try to sneak that into your dish.
[No use of any premade mixes, broths,
or spices of any kind.]
- No secret ingredients.
- Don't use any noodle spices.
- Let's all play fairly.
- Ready, set, go!
[Cooking competition- Start.]
[Whose dish will take the honorary place
as the winning dish of this competition?]
To be honest...
I'm a really horrible cook.
That's why I went into this
without any expectations
when I heard it was a cooking competition.
And since all the other teams are using
such fancy ingredients for their dishes
and since our ingredients are so simple,
I really don't have any high expectations.
I can't really guarantee how it'll taste
but I can vouch for the care we'll put into it
with the freshest of ingredients.
My partner and I vow to win
this competition
and show you how sincere we are about
starting off 2014, the new year the right way.
Fighting!
Yes, I'm confident.
I know that other teams are really good too
but even just from a quick glance
I can't help but think that our
ingredient is most superior of them all.
It's also the perfect season for it,
so I'm pretty confident that we'll win.
That sounds great.
Then we wish you the best of luck.
[Who will become the winner to take home
this golden horse trophy?]
Hey!
Let's do this!
[It's time for the real competition to begin!]
[All the teams shouting out their own
special battle cry to win the competition.]
- He looks like a girl.
- What?
- Right? Doesn't he look like a girl?
[The apron looks so well suited...
for the domesticated rocker.]
- This is war!
- This is real war!
You're all going to be shocked!
- The victory...
- Is ours!
This is amazing!
I can smell the deliciousness
of our dish already!
A clubber in his mid-forties...
He's going to shock all of you
with his cooking skills!
- Knock it off!
- My partner is a domesticated rocker!
We're going to win this thing!
- If we don't win today...
- I'm going to be angry!
- Let's win this thing!
- Be quiet!
[We knew you'd get in trouble...]
Can you stop with all the talking?
Let's use this as the trash can, okay?
[Today's chef- Soo Hong.
Kitchen assistant- Yoo Hyuk.]
- You're really fast.
- Of course, I am.
[Assistant Yoo getting praised
for his quick work.]
[Assistant Yoo is in charge of
washing all the vegetables.]
Jae Suk is a really fast worker.
He washed and organized everything,
and helped when I asked him for his help.
I don't think I could've done what I did today
if it hadn't been for Jae Suk's help.
I wish that I could use him as
my assistant for life.
- You know what, Soo Hong?
- What?
Don't worry too much since I'm going to do
my best to be a good assistant today.
You're doing a great job.
[Wait... that is?]
[His own personal knives that have
his name engraved on them?]
Hey! Soo Hong just
pulled out his personal knives!
- What?
- He has his own personal knives?
[Protests from other teams
could be heard from all around the room.]
Had I known we could do that,
I would've brought my own knives too.
Who in this world doesn't have
their own kitchen knives?
[Too much envy can become
your demise...]
[This is the power of a certified chef!]
[Clean and precise-
Impressive knife skills.]
Talking to each other while cooking will
help us be more in sync with one another.
So then why aren't you talking?
I'm the one doing all the talking over here.
- Right? I'm not being talkative enough.
- Yeah.
- It's because I'm feeling the pressure.
- Can I put the bean sprouts here?
[Chef Hong is feeling
the pressure in the kitchen.]
This completes all the prepping
for our spicy fish stew.
[Jae Suk and Soo Hong's dish
is a spicy fish stew?]
We went out fishing earlier and Soo Hong
caught the rockfish we'll be using himself.
Not just any rockfish either,
but a 50cm rockfish.
It's a giant-sized rockfish.
Let me catch just one fish.
Please, just one fish.
[Earlier this morning on a fishing boat.]
Oh!
I think I got something.
I got something!
Wow, I got something!
[Soo Hong catches his first fish
within first 20 minutes!]
I got something!
Wow!
[It's a fish!]
Jae Suk!
I can't believe this!
- I can't believe this!
- He caught a fish!
[A huge fish!]
I'm totally shocked myself!
[And not too long after...]
[Another fish!]
It's even bigger!
[It's an even bigger rockfish!
A 50cm catch!]
[And thus, with the rockfish that
Soo Hong caught himself...]
[What kind of a dish will they cook up?]
A nice and refreshing rockfish stew
that the whole family can enjoy.
And also, a savory
sweet and sour rockfish.
I see those two dishes as a
heavenly pair.
[Chef Hong is busy cleaning the rockfish
that he himself caught earlier.]
I have to make sure that all the insides
are really clean.
[Even manages to make a simple
work out of cleaning the fish.]
There's no way I can do this.
I don't think I could do this even if
my life depended on it.
I can't even watch you do this.
I'm going to go wait outside.
- Do you like your partner?
- Park Soo Hong?
Yes, I do like him.
And especially when it comes to cooking,
Soo Hong is very detail-oriented.
- He's very good at what he does.
- If you could change your partner...
- Who would you pick?
- Jae Kyung.
- Is that king crab?
- This is our king crab.
[Ji Hyo and Dong Wook's main ingredient is,
king crab.]
What is that?
Wow... this is pretty much cheating.
We went all the way to Pohang
to get this ourselves.
[These king crabs are delicious enough
even if they're just steamed...]
[Earlier this morning-
King crab auction market in Pohang.]
[Ji Hyo and Dong Wook participating
in the king crab auction.]
[Blank Ji wins the auction.]
[But...]
[The problem is, she bought all 800 crabs!]
I can't eat all these!
We're planning on making
steamed king crabs, king crab porridge,
and king crab stew.
We even came up with a name for our menu.
King crab...
A king crab delicious dinner table.
[Steamed king crabs-
Steam the crabs for 25 minutes.]
We went out to Ji Hyo's hometown
in Pohang.
That's a pretty famous place in our country
for its sunrise.
That's the place where a lot of people gather
to greet the first sunrise of the new year.
King crabs with the energy of that place,
and something that's in season right now...
Since we were able to get those crabs,
which are also of such high quality...
We thought that it would be the most ideal
thing to serve on a dinner table.
I bet this would be good
even if we just ate it raw right now.
- It's really good raw too.
- It's really sweet.
[These fresh king crabs are sweet
even when eaten raw.]
[Dong Wook gets his finger
pinched in the claw.]
I'm sorry, but just let go of me.
[Wow... enough to make our mouths water.]
I just want to eat it now.
[Are the viewers' mouths watering too?]
[Ji Hyo and Dong Wook complete prepping
all the ingredients for their dishes.]
Wow, theirs is chicken.
Their ingredient really is chicken.
It's chicken!
And it still has its head attached!
Can you really prep that chicken?
- Yes.
- Of course. We have to.
- You're making the broth, right?
- Yes.
[Meanwhile, Kyung Ah is prepping the broth
which they're going to cook the chicken in.]
I kind of thought that the dish
may be a little too ordinary at first.
But we couldn't think of any other dish.
This is supposed to be first dinner
of the new year with the family.
And what does a new year mean?
It's time to be healthy.
It's not money, but it's health.
I thought something healthy
would be the most important thing.
So I think that this is the perfect menu
for a theme like that.
[Earlier this morning-
Chicken farm in Namyang.]
[Off to catch their chicken at a farm
recommended to them by the chicken doctor.]
- It just hit me.
- Catch it.
Don't you think that you're too good
at catching the chicken?
[Fearless Kyung Ah catches her chicken
within moments.]
[They also went to pay a visit to a master of
chicken stew that chicken doctor recommended.]
I've heard that chickens have
a lot of fat in the rear.
I was told that we have to clean it out
very carefully, so how do we do that?
The most important part is right here.
You have to make sure to really clean out
the neck and the rear part of the chicken.
- You can just cut all these parts off.
- Okay, those parts?
We can take pictures of all this
to help us remember.
[Kyung Ah asks the questions,
and Jong Kook takes the pictures.]
- Good idea, right?
- Yes, it's good.
We have to take pictures of all this.
Look at this.
See how the rear is all cut like this?
[Confirming with pictures.]
- I'm going to put this in right now.
- Okay.
You're putting that in already?
Yes, so that we can cook off
all the odor from the chicken first.
[Boil it in a pot of boiling water with garlic
and ginger first to eliminate the odor.]
[They even stopped by the market earlier to
buy their abalone and octopus for the stew.]
Clean it until all the black stuff is off.
[Put the once boiled chicken into a
pressure cooker with rest of the ingredients.]
We can tell them what we're putting
in the pot later, but not now.
[Ginseng, mushrooms, tree barks, jujube,
and astragulus also go into the pot.]
Is this all set then?
I just have to shut the lid like this?
- Should the thing be standing up?
- Yes, stand it up.
- Like this, right?
- Yes.
- Right?
- We're all set then, right?
- Yes.
- High flames?
What should I do now?
[His chatter won't stop even during cooking.]
Seriously!
You ask way too many questions!
I'm asking because I don't know.
I had no idea that Jong Kook
talked so much.
I had absolutely no idea.
He's built like a mountain...
but he's so full of suspicions
about everything.
And he's timid on top off all that.
Asking me all those nonstop questions.
I thought I was going to blow up at him!
Is the dish you're cooking causing
troubles with your partner?
Yes, very much so.
Here's how I feel about it.
We did have quite a few
difference of opinions.
I know that she's a much better cook than I am
so I decided to put my faith in her.
So I just did as I was told by her, and
didn't make any comments about anything.
No, let me take that back.
I did make a comment or two.
I did make a lot of comments.
But in the end...
- How well would you say you cook together?
- I don't think you can even say that.
I pretty much did all the work myself.
But when I struggled from time to time,
Jong Kook gave me a lot of support.
He told me how good I'm doing.
I think his faith in me
was what kept me going.
Carefully and with love.
[Carefully wash the rice...]
I have never put so much effort into
cooking in my life before.
I'm going to soak the rice in the broth.
[Soak the rice in broth?]
[Soak the rice in milky colored broth
instead of plain water?]
Take good care of us, broth from Jeonju!
[The fate of Ha Ha and Sung Kyu
rides in this pit of rice...]
- This is beef bone broth, isn't it?
- You cook it with beef bone broth?
Yes, this is how the rice used to get made
back in the day.
- Rice cooked in this broth alone is amazing.
- It's really good.
[Authentic Jeonju bibimbap is made by soaking
the rice in beef bone broth first.]
All our beloved viewers and our staff members
who makes Running Man possible...
All these people, and even our own members
are who I had in mind as I was making this.
I felt like they all were part of this dish.
Viewers were the rice, staff crew was doraji.
The mushroom... represented Ji Hyo.
The carrots represented myself,
and the cucumber was Suk Jin.
I thought that's how the ingredients were
blended together harmoniously like we are.
So this is... everyone's bibimbap.
- Do you think this is enough carrots?
- Yes, that's plenty.
Didn't she put something in here
when she was panfrying this?
Zucchini is cooked in cooking oil only,
and the rest are cooked in sesame oil.
Let's have fun with this, Sung Kyu.
[Putting all their love and care
into each and every bit of the dish.]
The way you have it plated is so pretty.
[It seems as though the rice is almost
finished cooking already.]
I turned it off.
Should I open it to take a peek?
I know it still needs to finish steaming.
We're finished if the rice is ruined.
- It's a success!
- It's not a success!
- The rice has to be a bit chewy in bibimbap.
- That's right.
The rice can't be soggy.
Until it becomes transparent.
Keep cooking until the doraji is transparent.
I'm the king of cooking.
Are we sure that the rice cooked well?
We're cooking a dish that's really
good for your stamina.
That's why we're using fresh sea eel
right out of the ocean.
[Freshly caught that morning by
a local sea diver.]
[Fresh sea eel!]
Look at this eel.
Is this really a sea eel?
A true taste of Korean cuisine.
So we're cooking stir-fried eel soup.
And we're also preparing spicy red pepper,
and soybean paste teot muchim.
- Let's do this right, okay?
- You're much better than I am at that.
- You're so relaxed about it, and you're good.
- Not bad, right?
- You cut that up perfectly.
- Right?
[Big-nose and the Domesticated Rocker's dish-
How will it turn out?]
- Jae Kyung.
- Yes?
- I'm nervous.
- You'll do well because you're handsome.
- My mind has gone completely blank.
- Already?
- I'm not sure what I'm doing.
- What you're doing is perfect.
- It's perfect?
- It's perfect.
Gary looks like he's still having fun
even if he doesn't win this competition.
- Cooking is all about love.
- Seriously.
Sanjeok... that's all about love.
Why are you laughing!
Why are you all laughing?
Sanjeok is all about love, everyone.
Combination of their infamous beef,
and the naju pear.
We'll be serving that up with a pear tea,
and a special dessert made of the pears.
Year 2014...
In the new year... Korea, the world,
you and I... we all have to become one.
In order to unify all of us as one...
we all need to eat sanjeok.
Because sanjeok is...
love.
[This is sanjeok of love that will
unify the whole world as one.]
[Following orders...
exactly as given to him by Jae Kyung.]
Look at how good Jae Kyung is
with that knife.
[Jae Kyung's natural knife skills,
all thanks to her chef mother...]
[If you could switch up for a new partner,
then who would you pick?]
I don't want to say this because I don't
want anyone to misunderstand my meaning.
I really don't have the slightest desire
to switch... but, Jae Kyung.
I noticed that she's a really good cook.
Aside from everything else,
she was really good at what she was doing.
I was totally shocked when I saw that.
[These are the knife skills
that Ha Ha totally fell for.]
A part of me really wishes that
I had been paired up with Jae Kyung.
[Even Big-nose is talking about his wish
to have been partnered up with Jae Kyung.]
- You want me to dump the onions in here?
- Yes, just add the onions in there.
Let's look at the amount and see how much
of the pear and the onion we should add.
- You don't want to add the ginger?
- No ginger yet.
[Following the recipe exactly as she had
written down while they were in Naju.]
- Two.
Who would you want as your partner
if you could switch?
Jae Kyung.
- Why?
- Huh? I just want Jae Kyung.
- That's your reason?
- What reason would I need? It's Jae Kyung.
Who else is there?
There's only Jae Kyung.
Which team would you say has
absolutely zero chance of winning?
From what I've seen so far...
I would say that's Kwang Soo's team.
I don't think they have a chance.
Why did you team those two up together?
I feel so bad watching those two
struggling together.
I'm not very worried about Kwang Soo's team.
- Kwang Soo's team.
- Kwang Soo.
- That would be Team Kwang Soo.
- I'm sorry to say that Kwang Soo's team...
I'm having trouble with the dough.
I was able to make it earlier.
[Oh my...]
[What happened?
Even the expert gave you a compliment...]
I think you should be in charge
of making the dough.
[Could it be that he's nervous?
The dough is just a mess...]
[Meanwhile, Kwang Soo is busy making
the sauce for the noodle.]
Do you think this is enough of
the grated pear?
[The special spicy noodle sauce
with the pear zest.]
- Just a little bit.
- Okay.
- I think that's going to make it too sweet.
- There's a lot of the sauce.
There's a lot of the spicy sauce.
[Huh?]
[Is that patbingsoo?]
[These two guys- They weren't
such a mess in the beginning...]
[Their visit to Chuncheon to learn the real
secret behind a delicious bowl of noodles.]
[Learned the secret behind making
a special bowl of noodles.]
Wrap the noodles around your fingers.
What is this?
Dongchimi?
How am I supposed to eat this?
Just like it is?
Ah, add it to the dongchimi?
- Do I add in the broth?
- Yes, add in the broth.
[Succeeds in getting the dongchimi broth
which is crucial to their chance of winning.]
[This is what real pork is all about!]
[Even gained the real secret behind the real
broth and the pork for their noodle dish.]
Can you give us some?
[They even earned themselves some
of her top secret topping sauce.]
[Even after learning all the secrets,
and gathering all the secret ingredients...]
[these are the guys responsible
for putting it all together.]
What's that?
What's wrong with the dough?
I'm doing the best that I can.
- Don't you think you need to add more water?
- You think?
A little bit more?
It's the end for us if we ruin the dough.
I know that too.
[Is it dough or clay?]
- It's been 25 minutes now.
- Already?
[Kwang Soo and John Park have spent
the past 25 minutes making their dough.]
We have to hurry!
We don't have time to be doing this!
- Move away!
- Let me do this!
- We're not going to win at this rate!
- I can finish this!
Is laughter what those two
are aiming for?
Is that what you have those two for?
They have no idea what they're doing.
I feel so bad watching those two work.
Even though I know they're trying...
I can't help but feel sorry for them.
[This is the type of empathetic stares
they're getting from other teams.]
Hey guys.
You guys should take some time to eat
while you two work.
Why would we be taking the time out to eat?
- I just feel so bad for you guys.
- Why?
And don't have your mouths gaped open
like that while you're cooking.
Did I already add in the sesame seeds?
I forgot to add the sesame seeds!
No, he did add it in.
Okay, whew!
[It seems as though Sung Kyu already
added in the sesame seeds.]
You saute the mushrooms separately
without any cooking oil.
- You have to saute that.
- We have to saute this?
Yes, we need to saute it.
- We have to saute this too?
- You're not going to saute it?
- Did I already saute it?
- You didn't saute it?
[Both of them seem to have an
awful memory.]
- We could've been in big trouble.
- That's why we don't add the cooking oil.
Thank goodness for you.
[Luckily remembers to saute the mushrooms.]
[Tasting the vegetables
to test for the seasoning.]
Jong Kook is angry.
Jong Kook is angry!
[Sautes it one more time...]
[How does the sauteed
seasoned mushrooms taste?]
[Tastes extremely salty...]
Ugh, that's salty.
No way.
[They did as they were taught...
but can't figure out the mushroom mystery...]
The way I see it right now,
I think our dish is going to be delicious.
[Jae Suk and Soo Hong are busy
preparing their rockfish.]
Look at that fish.
- I think this is all ready.
- Don't you think we need to soak it more?
[Sweet and sour rockfish-
Baste it with curry powder.]
[A light sprinkling of curry powder before
frying it eliminates the fishy odor.]
Just sprinkle it with however much
you want.
[Jae Suk is infamous for his inability to
touch raw fish...]
- You startled me.
- The fish just snapped its mouth.
- What are you doing?
- It just moved its tail.
Stop going clubbing so much.
Even the fish is flipping its tail!
What are you talking about?
What does my clubbing have to do with this?
You're being absurd right now!
[Did the fish knowingly flip its tail
in front of the 40 year old clubber?]
- I'm telling you that it moved its tail.
- Why are you so scared of a dead fish?
Wow, that scared me to death.
[Coating it with the frying batter.]
That's good.
Is the oil hot enough?
- Is it not hot enough yet?
- No.
See? The batter is sinking to the bottom.
It needs to float right up to the top.
[The batter has to float immediately to
the top in order for it to be the right temp.]
Wow, you really are a cooking expert.
[Making sure there's plenty of
the frying batter on the fish...]
Try some.
Is the batter floating to the top?
Is it floating back to the top?
Okay, then that's hot enough.
- Do you want me to put it in?
- Yeah, put the fish in there.
[Time to start frying the rockfish!]
[Meanwhile, Ji Hyo and Dong Wook's
steamed king crabs are...]
[Even just the sight of them is enough
to make our mouths water.]
Should I start the soup broth first,
or make the rice first?
- Start the soup first, right?
- Yes, the soup.
[Ji Hyo and Dong Wook's crab stew-
They've already learned the secrets.]
[King crab stew that Blank Ji's older cousin
taught them earlier.]
Try it, Dong Wook.
It's so delicious.
It's so good.
It still needs to simmer a bit more.
Isn't it good?
Doesn't it go well with the porridge?
We're going to win this.
The broth is just so refreshing.
This would be perfect with a drink.
[Using the right soybean paste
is the real key to a great stew!]
- We need to take some back with us.
- We need to take this.
- This is my family's recipe.
- This is our secret recipe.
This is going to be our secret sauce.
[The secret to the stew...
the soybean paste is going in!]
- How's it going?
- I lowered the heat a little bit.
- Did you add the garlic?
- No, I'm about to do that now.
[Add the crab when
the seasoning is just right.]
- It's okay, this is going to be delicious.
- I think we added too much of the paste.
[Enough to make our mouths water.]
- We have to add the pepper, right?
- Yes.
[Add in all the vegetables,
and bring it to a roaring boil.]
We have to bring it to a boil first.
[Jong Kook and Kyung Ah are making fresh
kimchi to accompany their chicken stew.]
[Infuse the kimchi with sweetness by
adding in ripe persimmon.]
[These two are still
wrestling with their dough.]
We're finished if we don't
get the noodles right.
Are you finished prepping everything else?
I'm doing my best right now.
[Not allowed to change
their menu at this point!]
[John Park... Putting every ounce of
his energy into the dough!]
[The dough is finally starting to take
its shape thanks to all his hard work.]
[Looking good!]
You look like a real chef.
Your really do look like a real chef.
[Time to cut the rolled out dough
into noodle strands.]
- Try this sauce and see how it tastes.
- I don't think this is a good noodle.
I think I rolled it out too thin.
I think it's too thin.
[The noodle is too thin
and not doughy enough.]
Do you think that it needs more water?
I'll redo it real quick.
- Okay.
- I know I can do it.
[The four members of the judging panel
come around to take a look!]
She's here.
I see her walking around.
She's coming.
I have a question for you, Mrs. Shim.
There's something that
I'm a little unclear on.
What's the difference between
thick soy sauce and soup soy sauce?
I'm not sure of the difference.
Soup soy sauce is naturally brewed
and fermented.
The beans are naturally fermented
to turn it into the soy sauce form.
I can't believe how much fun
I'm having.
[Going overboard with his pretenses about
having fun with the judges around.]
- Hello.
I never knew just how much fun
cooking could really be.
I think you're spitting on your food.
- What is this?
- I'm boiling some bean sprouts.
I'm boiling some sprouts to be used for
the bean sprout soup and the bibimbap.
Boiling it for too long
will make it too chewy.
Yes, I understand!
We should stop boiling it now.
[Listening to her advice and
pulls it out of the pot immediately.]
- This is our rockfish.
- We caught it ourselves this morning.
I'm grating the onion myself right now
to add it to our sauce.
- This was caught fresh this morning.
- Why are you standing over here?
- I'm here to talk to the judges real quick.
- Go back to having fun with your cooking.
Yes, I will.
Kwang Soo.
We heard of the famous noodle shops in
Chuncheon known for their amazing noodles.
We went to all three of them to learn
of their secrets behind their noodles
and we've combined the secrets
of all three of those noodle dishes.
This is buckwheat noodle dough.
80% buckwheat, and 20% flour.
[John Park is doing a great job of explaining
unlike his partner.]
- Keep turning the dough while you roll it.
- Keep it turning?
So that it's evenly rolled out?
I told you to do that earlier!
Don't you ever listen to me?
Thank you for your advice.
We have the utmost respect for you.
[Giraffe is busier kissing butt
than he is with the actual cooking process.]
I think I'm just tuning you out.
[Raymond Kim and Jung Da Jung stop by
Jong Kook and Kyung Ah's station.]
What are you doing?
What is the dish that you're cooking?
We're making chicken stew right now.
We're focusing on making it really healthy.
So we're adding abalone and
octopus to our stew.
So we're attempting to add more complex
flavors by adding in these ingredients.
We wanted to see some creativity,
but it seems to be a pretty common dish.
[Lack of creativity is some cause for concern
since it's a pretty common dish.]
But we do like the addition of the abalone.
But we do have a small hidden surprise
inside the chicken.
- We have a small surprise in there.
- Did you add something in there?
You didn't add any eggs
inside the chicken, did you?
[Totally caught?]
- What do you think about this?
- About what?
Most people put something inside
the chicken's cavity...
- How about adding eggs?
- Eggs?
[Their plan was to add hard boiled eggs
inside the chicken's cavity!]
[These eggs will bring about
a surprise in a little bit.]
We're barely going to add
any bit of seasoning in our dish.
[No use of any seasoning.
Smallest bit of salt to keep it healthy.]
[What's going on there?]
[Not a single peaceful moment
in this competition.]
- What do we do?
- Turn off the heat.
We're in trouble!
There's a big problem!
[Must've forgotten that they already
added the cooking oil in the frying pan.]
I don't want to sound rude,
but can we be a bit more cautious?
Let the taste of our dish
do the talking.
Having you...
Having you watch me made me nervous.
- Yes, I understand.
- You'll never get it done with one knife.
Yes, Ma'am!
[Discovers Yoo Hyuk in the process
of slicing his garlic.]
- Are you slicing that?
- Yes, I am.
- The knife can't be angled inward.
- Like this then?
- Angle it outward.
- Yes, I understand.
[Instructing him to be careful
to eliminate chances of an injury.]
You have to change your grip.
You're holding it all wrong!
- When you hold something, flex your wrist.
- Like this?
Yes, that's right.
I just told you not to do that!
- No, angle it up.
- Oh, I see.
[Her mini lesson is enough to
make Yoo Hyuk sweat bullets.]
- That's more natural.
- Yes, I understand.
Keep practicing, and the slices will come out
looking so pretty.
Look at this finger.
Why is that finger sticking out?
- This finger needs to go back.
- Like this?
[This is finally the correct
positioning of the hand.]
- Are you making a mix?
- Yes, I'm preparing it.
- How are you making the mix?
- I'm using even water to powder ratio.
- And I'm going to add it to the fish...
- Looks like you know what you're doing.
[So envious...]
Happy new year everyone.
[Even early this morning...]
[Soo Hong didn't even get to chance to get
a word in edgewise around Jae Suk.]
You caught something?
[But with his catching
of the three rockfish...]
[The tables have been totally
turned around.]
Why don't you say something now?
You were going on and on talking about
this and that to all the audience
members earlier this morning.
Tell them how you're still empty-handed.
[The moment that marked
the shifting of power...]
[Complete shift in power
once the cooking started.]
[Even she's giving
all her praises to Soo Hong...]
[Ah... how heartbreaking...]
Let's just put this one in.
[Sneaking a hardboiled egg
inside the chicken cavity.]
[If they're not careful,
they could ruin the look of the chicken...]
I'll push it in there.
[How to... put this in there?]
What am I doing here?
To put so much effort into this?
- Can you move this part a little?
- I'm afraid it'll ruin the chicken.
[Afraid of ruining the egg and the chicken.]
[Attempt to decorate with the egg
is giving them an unnecessary quandary.]
Did you get it in there?
It won't be cooked if we don't put it in now.
[We will get this egg in there
to surprise everyone!]
[Doctor Kkuk will make this happen.]
[Operation 'Input the hardboiled egg.']
Good luck, Jong Kook.
I know you can do it.
I cracked the egg.
You have to be more careful!
[Emergency operation!
Must eliminate the cracked egg!]
You have to get that out of there quickly.
[Recruits Dr. Song.]
You have to keep the leg up
so that it doesn't fall back down.
You don't think you can get it in there?
There's no chance of that happening?
[Really sounds like
they're in the operation room.]
Wait a minute.
Should we just forget about it?
[Total concentration.]
We have to get this egg out.
[Hardboiled egg... please come out of there.]
Are you trying to bring
the dead chicken back to life?
They're trying to bring the dead chicken
back to life.
[Jong Kook and Kyung Ah in danger?]
- It's too deep in there.
- We should've put it in there earlier on.
You must've felt really bad
for the chicken.
You think you can get it out?
The only way we can do this is
if we can lift up the chicken.
- I think that's going to break the chicken.
- We have to lift it up slightly.
It did go in there.
The tongs!
I need the tongs!
Grab it!
Use the tongs to grab the egg!
[An extremely dangerous situation.]
- Wait!
- Grab the egg!
- Grab it and pull it out!
- Hang on!
[Dr. Kkuk and Dr. Song's operation succeeds!]
[Ten years shaved off their lives.]
- Did you operate successfully?
- We got it.
[The hardboiled egg is given
a new lease on life?]
We don't have any more time.
We have to do it now if we're going to do it.
I think I have a solution.
Put your hand in really cold water first.
[Numb the hand in icy cold water first?]
[I will succeed this time!]
[Second attempt with the chicken.]
- You can't pull it part.
- I'm holding it together.
[Their second attempt isn't proving
to be any easier either.]
- You're not cautious enough.
- Come on, Jong Kook.
- You're too wild with that.
- Hang on a minute.
[The two doctors are arguing with one another
to leave each other to do the work.]
- We don't have time for this, Jong Kook.
- This is no simple matter.
You're so frustrating!
Where did you go?
Come back here and grab it.
- You're so frustrating!
- Come grab it.
Grab it.
You have to lift this up.
Don't pull it apart too much
because you don't want to tear it.
I always seem to get sucked in
whenever Jong Kook tells me to do something.
So I was annoyed for about an hour,
but felt better for about ten minutes after.
It was like a nonstop rollercoaster.
Close it.
Close it up for right now.
This has to go under there.
We should've used a quail egg.
We should've put it in at the beginning.
How many times have I told you that?
Grab this leg.
[The operation is starting to drag on...]
[At last...]
- You got it.
- It's in there.
We got it.
[The surgery is a success.]
Good job, Jong Kook.
I have no idea what's going on.
The leeks and the onion.
Leeks and the onion.
[Suk Jin and Kyung Ho are making
their eel stir-fry.]
I wonder if this is right.
[Adding the vegetables already?]
What are you doing?
[Darn... they should've cooked the eel
in the sauce first...]
What's wrong with you?
[The domesticated Rocker has fallen
into a state of panic.]
- Hang on.
- What did she tell us to do again?
- Pour the broth in here.
- In there?
Okay!
That's good.
That's too much!
[Too much broth!]
- Why did you put so much in here?
- We can just add in more sauce.
We can boil it down.
- You're an accident waiting to happen!
- Just boil it down.
[Now that they take a closer look...
the Rocker isn't so domesticated after all?]
- We can just taste it as we go along.
- What have you done?
[Overflowing with broth.]
I think we picked the wrong dish to make.
[He's stating that they've picked the wrong
dish to cook at this point in the game?]
[No confidence in their presentation
of their dish?]
The way I see it, they got the presentation.
Jae Suk's team has got the presentation down.
[Sweet and sour rockfish and
Spicy rockfish stew got the presentation down]
I don't want the tail to break off.
It broke off.
[It broke...]
[The rockfish is ultimately in two pieces...]
[Who could've guessed that the trusted
Chef Hong would make such a mistake?]
[The whole fish's shape is ruined...]
I think that since Soo Hong does a lot of
cooking shows...
people make the mistake of thinking
that he's a professional chef or something.
But he usually orders in a lot,
and he doesn't cook all that often.
The tail should still be attached.
[Too bad for the poor rockfish...]
I remember that the exact same thing happened
to me once during a cooking competition.
- You know how I fixed it?
- How?
I just poured a lot of sauce on top.
Then you can't tell that it's in two pieces.
We're going to disguise it with
the sauce topping.
[The separated rockfish...
Will they be able to disguise it?]
[Gary and Jae Kyung are starting to
grill their sanjeok.]
I think we need to add in some more pear.
[Deciding to add in more of the grated pear
after doing a quick taste test.]
- Pick just a few pieces.
- The best looking ones?
- Let's do two a piece, not three.
- Two a piece?
[Ha Ha and Sung Kyu are finished cooking
their side menu item, dduk galbi.]
I think we need to taste one
to see how it turned out.
[Ha Ha and Sung Kyu also taste one
of their pieces to test for seasoning.]
[Huh?]
You guys just made this?
[Feeding a bite to their neighbor, Kyung Ho.]
- It's undercooked.
- It's undercooked, right?
It's completely raw in the middle.
No, I'm serious.
It's still raw in the middle.
And... it's really bland.
- It's bland?
- Yeah.
Hey.
It's bland?
We're in danger.
This one is about to burn.
It's starting to burn.
I can't control the heat temperature.
Then let's just make one.
[In the end, they ultimately decide to grill
only one piece of the dduk galbi...]
[After a whole hour...
John Park is still working on the noodles.]
[He finally managed to make noodles resembling
strands after all his hard work...]
[The boiling water is overflowing...]
What do I do?
[I hope no one saw that.]
It should still be okay, right?
[The noodles are finally starting to cook.]
We just need the noodles to
finish cooking.
But we've been cooking the noodles
for 40 minutes now.
[The noodles have been cooking
for 40 minutes already...]
- Is it never going to finish cooking?
- I think it's better to have it soggy.
Having it soggy is better than
having it be undercooked.
[Will they be able to save their dish?]
[Hm... that looks a bit...]
Can we even present our dish
when it looks like this?
What if they cuss us out?
[In a few moments...]
[Getting ready to cuss them out?]
[Serious panel of judges.]
[Cold and cruel judging.]
You ruined it right from the beginning.
[Honest and raw judging that
no one can escape from will soon start.]
- Okay, I'm putting it in.
- Okay.
- It's time.
- It's time?
- Put it all in there.
- It's time to put it in.
We're good.
This is it.
What's that?
We're going to shock you with our dish.
Look at how beautiful that looks.
[The crab porridge alone is enough
to make our mouths water.]
- Doesn't it look good?
- Are you two operating a restaurant?
- It's bitter.
- Bitter?
[Huh? It's bitter?]
- What are you doing?
- It's still undercooked.
- Let's try it.
- I'll taste it for seasoning.
- Okay, try it.
- Let me try it.
[The eel stir-fry that has been boiled down
from too much broth added to it...]
[How would it taste?]
How is it?
- It's good.
- Seriously?
Really?
But... is it okay for the eel
to be this tender?
[The eel lost its signature chewiness
from having been cooked for too long.]
We can just tell them that it's tender
because it's all natural.
[Ten minutes before the time is up.]
[Time for all the teams to start
wrapping things up.]
- Lets leave it up to fate.
- Should we?
I'll start cleaning up.
[Detailed assistant starts
the cleanup process.]
[Ji Hyo and Dong Wook's delicious
looking king crab stew.]
We just need to simmer a bit longer.
This is perfect.
Cooking seriously is no joke.
- This is too hard.
- I think bungee jumping in Macao was easier.
[Would rather jump from the tower
in Macau over doing this?]
[Oyster and teot muchim is complete!]
Don't forget the pepper.
Two pieces.
- There you go.
- Not bad, right?
Just top it off.
There you go. Great job!
[Domesticated Rocker's softer image.]
No, that's too much.
It doesn't look pretty.
[Everyone is finalizing
their finishing touches to their dishes.]
This is our highlight of the day.
I will not top it off
with the spicy pepper paste.
[Time to add in the pepper sauce topping-
The bibimbap's main highlight.]
[Secret spicy pepper paste
brought all the way back from Jeonju.]
[Beautiful and vibrantly red
pepper paste.]
This is it.
We're going to have to move it around a bit
so that the edges don't burn.
[Gary and Jae Kyung's dish
is grilling up beautifully.]
[Jae Suk and Soo Hong's sweet and sour
sauce is nearing completion.]
[Lastly... disguising the crumbled fish tail.]
Three minutes!
Three minutes until time is up!
No!
- Do you think it needs more sauce?
- No.
[Even some fancy decoration
to complete the dish.]
[Following her chef mother's advice and
decorating it with slivered scallions.]
[Everyone's starting to
hurry their movements.]
30 seconds!
Put more crab in there.
- That looks really pretty.
- You think?
[Kyung Ah uses flowers to put
her final finishing touch.]
I think putting it together
like that is better.
Seriously!
[The bickering chicken couple.]
Put it on there in a round mound.
- How does it look, Jong Kook?
- That looks so pretty.
Not bad, right?
Unbelievably beautiful.
Ten seconds!
[Ten minutes left on the clock!]
- Okay!
- Almost done!
- Wait!
- Right now! Hurry!
[Secret edible decor- Gold flakes!]
[Everyone heads to the judging table
with their completed dishes in hand.]
[Time's up!]
We did finish it.
Make sure my path is clear.
This is dangerous.
Be careful and don't come close.
[Just which of these dishes...]
[Will become the main star
of the dinner table?]
We will now start the final judging of
your 2014 Running Man Cooking Battle.
Each team will present their dish to the panel
of judges and wait for their results.
[The cooking competition that's
kept them on their toes all day...]
[It's time to determine the ultimate winner.]
[Jae Suk and Soo Hong
are the first to present their dish.]
We got up early this morning to go fishing
for the main ingredient of our dish.
Caught fresh from the ocean this morning...
It's spicy rockfish stew and sweet and sour
rockfish with the fish we caught ourselves.
[Soo Hong, who caught three rockfish
early this morning...]
This is unbelievable!
This is bigger than my face!
[Dishes made up of the fresh rockfish
they themselves caught early this morning.]
I actually heard that it's pretty difficult
to catch rockfish in the middle of winter.
Just like how fresh fish can be caught with
some patience and dedication even in winter...
it's the same belief that we can overcome
anything during times of our trial.
When everyone else told us
that it's impossible...
we were still able to make it happen.
Even though the captain himself told us
that it was difficult to catch rockfish...
- When no one had any faith in us...
- To be honest, we didn't have faith either.
But as you can see, these rockfish...
they came to be with us here today...
by sacrificing their own lives.
They wanted to sacrifice their lives
to offer you their flesh.
- That's what the rockfish decided.
- Yes, that's correct.
That's why they sacrificed their lives
to hang themselves on our fishhooks.
Our food is getting cold!
[That's right...]
- We'll just give you a little to taste.
- I want a big serving of it.
Give her more.
[Serving the panel of judges himself.]
Please enjoy it with the fish.
I'll give you more fish in yours.
The fish is really fresh and delicious.
[Time for the real taste test.]
If you stand right there,
then the judges won't show up on camera.
- What are you doing?
- Can you get out of the way?
- You're blocking the judges.
- You guys are so disappointing.
I just want to win the gold and go home.
It's a little fishy.
- Too fishy?
- Too fishy.
[The rockfish is too fishy?]
[It's still fishy?
Even after sprinkling it with the curry?]
[How can that be?]
[Time to start the judging
after tasting the dishes.]
It's not presented very well.
This is really nerve wrecking.
[Four professionals' fair judging.]
To be objective, the sweet and sour rockfish
didn't look anything like it should've looked.
Didn't look anything like it
should've looked.
It just looked like chunks of fish with
some sweet and sour sauce drizzled on top.
- That to me was pretty unappealing.
- I'm sorry to hear that.
[The studio has all of a sudden
become silent as a tomb.]
The seasoning of the fish stew
was just right.
However...
The stew was too overcooked.
Overcooked to a point where I wasn't sure
if I was chewing the broth or the fish.
[Her slam leaves them speechless.]
I'd like to say though that the stew
was seasoned very well.
- Thank you.
[This really... is no joke.]
[Second team- Jong Kook and Kyung Ah.]
The reason why we chose
to cook this dish was because...
I was never even able to make ramen for
my parents from my inability to cook at all.
But with the new year, I really wanted
to be able to cook this dish for my parents.
- Did you have any say in cooking this dish?
- No. Never.
I didn't even fathom making this dish.
I thought we were going to make something
more grand and fancier than this.
I wanted to cook something fancier
than this.
But Jong Kook said he wanted to cook something
reminiscent of a mom's home cooked meal.
Something homey and healthy.
Cooking something healthy was our main focus
and that's why we've prepared this dish.
We've also added some mushrooms
in the dish.
We went to a mushroom farm
to bring them back ourselves to add it.
Even though this may seem plain
to professionals like yourselves
but it was still a shocking process to me.
I really didn't add any additives at all.
- It's amazing how well it turned out.
- Stop talking so much.
You're really going overboard.
[His explanation may take all night.]
All our dishes are going to get cold.
[Domesticated Rocker's protest.]
I was really surprised myself.
[Kudos for the great presentation
and the beautiful plating.]
- You only used salt?
- We used the smallest bit of salt.
[Least bit of salt possible was used.]
We added just enough to give it
a bit of seasoning.
[Taste the fresh kimchi too.]
[Slowly approaching...]
[Other contestants are
wildly protesting his move.]
There's also a hardboiled egg
inside the chicken.
[Boasting about the hardboiled egg that
they worked so hard to get in the chicken.]
There are countless breastless
chickens that are waiting for you in hell.
All the chickens are mad at you.
I was shocked by the beauty
of the whole cooking process.
- We're being very sincere about that.
- This is seasoned perfectly.
This is seasoned perfectly.
[First compliment of the day!]
Both the dishes are seasoned
perfectly well.
- Thank you for the compliment.
- You two better start dating.
Pork and chicken are known for
having a high fat content.
It's really difficult to dissolve the amount
of fat that's in those types of meat.
But when you eat the fatty meat and
the fresh kimchi together like this...
it really helps with the digestion process.
It really is a perfect pairing.
[Perfect pairing made in heaven.]
Adding in the mushrooms like you did really
brought up the healthy factor
and the abalone that you added in there
is really good for elderly people's eyes.
You two did a great job with
your ingredient selection
and did a great job with
cooking the dishes as well.
[Great ingredients and great cooking.]
[Unexpected level of compliments.]
[Still full of compliments even after
the judging is over.]
[Unexpected level of compliments-
Possible first place contenders?]
I feel bad for our rockfish.
I amazed even myself with how
delicious the dishes turned out.
- Are you talking about your dish right now?
- Yes.
I don't want to hear it.
[Soo Hong is upset from the comments
that he heard from the judges.]
How is it my fault
that the rockfish was fishy?
I should've had a better partner.
Seriously.
The name of our menu is,
crab-a-licious dinner menu.
[Crab-a-licious dinner menu.]
We went to Pohang to get these crabs.
The reason why we went there is because
Pohang is very famous for the hand sculpture
that is seen sticking out of the water.
So from the location where so many people
go to see the first sunrise of the new year
we wanted to make our dish with
the iconic ingredient of that area.
So we figured that it may be the most ideal
dish to make for the new year dinner
so that's why we chose to make
what we did.
The porridge is a little bland, so we
recommend that you eat it with the stew.
It's more like a rice ball
rather than porridge.
I've never had porridge like this
in all my life.
[Other's misfortune... is my own happiness?]
Porridge is all about formula.
It's always five cups of water for
every cup of rice used.
[Five cups of water for one cup of rice
is the perfect ratio.]
- I understand.
- So this was ruined from the beginning.
- Yes.
- Thank you.
It's such a waste of this
beautiful crab.
This dish is totally ruined.
This is a very new approach to me.
I've never had porridge with stew before.
They're really twisting in the knife.
[Angry clubber is taking pleasure
in their misery?]
Do I need to twist your arm back?
You did a good job of
steaming the crab though.
- Thank you.
- Steaming the crabs are not easy to do.
[They still got some compliments
on the steamed crabs.]
[A round of applause for Ji Hyo and Dong Wook
for their full day of hard work.]
[Slamming comments even though ultimate
ingredients were used. Their result?]
[Next up- Ha Ha and Sung Kyu.]
[Jeonju bibimbap and dduk galbi.]
The name of our menu is...
'Miss Mixy lost her rib bones.'
They're making a joke of their
sacred food.
[Lovingly mixing the dish with
a pair of chopsticks.]
Thank you.
I know that the dduk galbi may be overkill,
but the bibimbap is undoubtedly our star.
And we also made some bean sprout soup
that is totally unexpected by anyone.
We made it cold.
I made with my own two hands.
[Time to test out Ha Ha's secret weapon-
The bean sprout soup.]
Is it good?
[How does his secret weapon soup taste?]
- Is it good?
- It tastes like water.
I purposely made it bland to balance
the saltiness of bibimbap.
Eating too salty makes you gain weight.
Did you just diss the judge?
[A huge mistake of insulting the judge?]
- I'm sorry! I'll lose some weight!
- No! That's not what I meant!
I'll lose weight.
This is a very healthy meal because
bibimbap is really good for your health.
You can't just let him off the hook
after that kind of insult.
But...
[What is the scary judge's opinion?]
- You did a good job.
- Thank you.
It's difficult to make it this good
when neither one of you are experts in it.
- You two did a very good job.
- I think it was planned out very well.
The soup, bibimbap and even the meat...
It's actually a very good combination.
But just work on getting the seasoning right.
Did you just poach the bean sprouts
and bring it out as soup?
In the water that you poached it in?
In the poaching water?
No, we cooked it again.
I think it would've been really nice
had you put some salt in it.
But the bibimbap was very delicious.
I don't know if I'm having a growth spurt,
but everything is quite delicious.
[Unexpected contender for the first place
position with their harmonious menu?]
[Next Team- Suk Jin and Kyung Ho.]
The dish that you see on the right
is the highlight of our menu.
I feel that we need to introduce
the world to the beauty of teot.
Kyung Ho and I went out to the ocean
this morning and climbed the rocks ourselves
to get the teot that you see
in front of you.
We went and got it ourselves...
It doesn't look like any of
the judges really care.
Kyung Ho and I went out to the ocean this
morning and climbed the rocks ourselves...
[So?]
The first thought that entered my mind
when I saw your menu...
You said you went out to get all these
ingredients yourselves, right?
But I don't get the feeling
that the ingredients are all that fresh.
If anything, it makes me wonder if
the ingredients may have gone bad.
We went out to get
the ingredients ourselves.
You don't have to try eating it
if you don't want to.
Kyung Ho and Suk Jin really do look like
a married couple from behind.
The head daughter-in-law.
A daughter-in-law who's disliked
by the mother-in-law.
[Time for the taste test.]
Not many people know what teot is
because it's not very widely known.
I think you added too much garlic in it,
so it's overly spicy.
- I apologize for the spiciness.
- I told you we should've switched it out.
It's a really good idea,
but it's not seasoned very well.
How about you just give them a swift smack
in the rear and call it a day?
I think it's good.
[Totally unexpected]
Do you like to drink?
Yes, I go crazy for it.
- Yes, I do like it.
- In all my life...
I have never met anyone who cooks
eel to quite this extent.
Since the eel is the star of this dish,
it shouldn't crumble down like this.
So I'm a little disappointed with the eel,
but the taste is really authentic.
You did a good job of bringing out
the spicy savoriness of the dish.
- Thank you.
- A bit more study...
and I think you may be able to
make a living with this dish.
[Another totally unexpected surprise.]
This dish would've been really delicious if
the eel had been grilled or fried separately.
[Suk Jin and Kyung Ho are shocked and
delighted by their unexpected complements.]
[The panel of judges' warm reception-
Will it result in their favor?]
[Next up- Gary and Jae Kyung.]
- Tea too?
- The name of our menu is...
Sanjeok...
is love.
[Sanjeok is love.]
- I'm going to love through this sanjeok.
- How are you always talking about love?
What's the first thing you think of
when you hear of Naju?
- Pears.
- Yes, pears.
Each one of our dishes was made
with the pear being part of the ingredients.
[Naju pear is in each and
every one of these dishes.]
The sanjeok is what brings everything
and everyone together.
Father minces the meat,
mother makes the seasoning sauce
and older brother grates the pear
to make pear extract...
All the love from each of these
family members are combined together
to complete the circle of love that
makes up our sanjeok.
I know that everyone is struggling
with cold and flu lately too.
So we made some tea with the pear that is
known to be a natural cough suppressant
and along with the meat on the menu,
which will keep you fuller for longer
we thought it would be a great compliment to
each other with digestive and overall health.
No matter what they're spewing,
taste is what matters the most.
- Jae Kyung is a ham.
- Yeah, she's really good.
- She's smart.
- She really is something else.
[The judges continue to eat
without uttering a word.]
[Even the onlookers are watching
with baited breath.]
Did you cook the sanjeok medium
on purpose?
Yes, the beef that was used was so fresh
so we didn't want the meat to lose its flavor
by overcooking the meat too much.
[Easily answers the judge's question
without getting flustered by it.]
[Time to taste the dessert.]
[The only team out of all the contestants
to have prepared a dessert dish.]
I know you said that pear was used,
and the pear...
[What will she say?]
was a delight in the dish,
and it's good for digestion as well.
It's a perfect complement to
this meat dish.
I really liked that the dish is representative
of authentic Korean cuisine.
I also liked the fact that you used jujube,
which is iconic of our country's cuisine.
Also, I know that you used honey
and lemon in the tea?
The taste of the two wasn't overpowering,
but it was very light and complimentary.
I believe that it was balanced out perfectly.
- I really enjoyed it.
- Thank you.
[Dessert expert,
Louie Kang's compliments.]
[Sanjeok of love-
Could the victory be theirs?]
[Time for the final dish.]
[Kwang Soo and John Park's dish.]
It's a bowl of noodles and boiled pork belly.
[Buckwheat noodles and pork belly.]
Panel of judges... Happy New Year.
[A grand bow out of nowhere.]
The dish that we've prepared
is buckwheat noodles with pork belly.
Back in our poorer days...
when we had valuable guests come to our
house, we'd slaughter a pig from our stock.
I was told that along with the pig,
we'd prepare a bowl of noodles to serve.
So along those same lines...
with our utmost love and respect
for our panel of judges...
we couldn't think of anything better
than this menu to serve you.
I'm sorry, but can you explain the meaning
of 'Hwa-Jeon-Min' to us?
[Does he even know what he's saying?]
Does it mean, 'flower'?
Is that why...
you sprinkled gold flakes on your dish?
Running Man always gives out
a gold prize to the winner.
The gold flakes are to symbolize how
we're all winners in the new year.
That's why we used the gold flakes
to decorate our dish.
How can he say such a thing without
any sense of embarrassment?
Please enjoy the dish.
- Did you make the spicy muchim yourself?
- We were told that it needed to ferment...
- So you brought it already made?
- Yes.
- That was the only thing.
- No, we actually made it ourselves.
You really shouldn't lie.
Kwang Soo...
Let's not be partnered up
together from now on.
You did good.
There's nothing else we can do now.
[Only way to get the noodles
is to use a spoon.]
- Isn't the meat a little smelly?
- The meat still has hair on it.
I'm going to tell them that.
John Park said he'd like to sing you a song
to make your dining experience more enjoyable.
- But...
- Let's do whatever we can.
We need to do everything that we can.
Would you like to hear a song?
After we make our judgment.
Yes, of course.
No, I really want to hear you sing.
- But after I finish my judging.
- Yes, of course.
I know how difficult it must be to keep
the viewers laughing with your antics.
Since you're so funny to begin with,
to be good at cooking on top of that...
then people who cook for a living
would be out of jobs.
But I feel that it's a relief that
this is the limit of your cooking talents.
[It didn't sound like a compliment...]
[But Kwang Soo and John Park are
taking that comment as a compliment?]
I don't think we have to sing anymore.
- Are you not going to sing anymore?
- We'll sing it for you right now.
[Time for John Park to
showcase his singing skills.]
[The judge's 'compliment' heard
like a ray of sunshine?]
[Automatically breaking out into a dance.]
[John Park's voice is
as buttery as the pork belly.]
[The final judging is now over!]
[Hm...]
[2014 Running Man Cooking Battle.]
Thank you everyone for all
your hard work.
We will now choose the top three.
Please lift up the name tags of
the top three winners.
Once your name tags are lifted into the air,
come stand on top of the platforms.
We were pretty surprised.
Some of you were creative enough
for me to want to ask
if they thought about opening
a restaurant.
The love and the care you all put into
making your dishes
were evident,
and I was very touched to see that.
I was very touched to see how seriously you
all took this battle, which was unexpected.
[The amount of effort they all put into
this battle deserves to be recognized.]
It is now time for three of
the four judges
to hold up the name tag of the winner
of your judging into the air.
[Who will be the first team to take
place up on the platform?]
[Everyone's waiting for the results
with baited breath...]
[Kim Jong Kook and Kyung Ah.]
[Their complimenting pairing of the
chicken stew and fresh kimchi makes it!]
Please take my reputation into
consideration.
[Time to announce the second team.]
[Gary and Jae Kyung.]
[Sanjeok made with love,
and the traditional dessert combination.]
Okay, there's still one spot left.
[Which team... will take the last spot?]
[Ha Ha and Sung Kyu!]
No, I'm sorry.
[Is she getting revenge
for Ha Ha's earlier insult?]
[The final team is,
Jae Suk and Soo Hong!]
[A total celebration.]
Why did you make us sing
if you were going to do this?
[The top three finalists.]
Rather than the food dishes themselves,
the love that I felt while cooking...
[Insult to the ones who didn't make it.]
I feel like I'm really going to regret it
if I don't share what I'm feeling.
So I want to make sure to
say this to all of you.
Mother.
Mom.
I felt it the moment I saw you.
[Time to choose the ultimate winners.]
First family weekend dinner menu
of the new year...
It is now time to choose the
final winner.
[Who will be the final winner
of the cooking competition?]
[Automatically breaking out in excitement
as she grazes her hand over their names?]
[The ultimate winning team is...]
[Jong Kook and Kyung Ah!]
[Utter shock!]
[Congratulating them wholeheartedly.]
I have never even made ramen for my parents
because I didn't know how to cook anything.
But I would really like to be able to cook
this for them with the new year upon us.
So we focused on making a healthy dish,
and that's why we chose this menu.
[Healthy chicken stew is chosen to be
the star of the new year dinner table.]
[The golden horse winning trophy.]
- This is an unexpected win thanks to him.
- No, you worked so hard for this.
[The well-being couple showed us
what real teamwork is all about.]
- Date her!
- Thank you for the great memories!
- Happy New Year!
- Happy New Year! Thank you!
I don't think you have
a chance anymore, Eun Hye.
- Stop it.
- You've lost your chance, Eun Hye.
[Thank you to all those who participated
in making this episode possible.]
[A rural school...]
[Lee Jong Suk, dreamboat.]
[Park Bo Young, and Lee Sae Young.]
[A group of male and female students.]
[Kwang Ja, who receives special love
from all those around her.]
[And Jong Sook.]
Don't I look prettier
than all the other girls?
[Bloody everyday battle.]
[But...]
[A secret affair is discovered!]
[Must continue their secret affair
by avoiding everyone's suspicions.]
[The young dangerous love affair.]
[Next Week's Running Man-
Romeo and Juliet.]
Subtitles by DramaFever