[If you could turn back time...]
[Which time frame would you
like to go back to?]
At that time, I was
ousted very early on in the game.
[Gary- 'At that time, I was ousted
very early on in the game.']
Just like a person without a future.
But I learned that in life...
there are always unexpected events.
I wish I could turn back time,
and somehow survive that game.
And also, at that moment...
that's when the story of my
victory began.
[The moment in time that they
desperately want to go back to...]
Yoo-ames Bond.
I don't know what would happen if I were
able to go back to that moment in time.
[If you were able to
go back to that moment...]
[Ji Suk Jin- I'd like to go back to
the Sherlock Holmes episode.]
No!
[However...]
[The further they go back in time,
the more twisted their history becomes.]
- January 29th, 2012.
- But I'm the star of this episode!
[Would you still choose to go back?]
Subtitles by DramaFever
[May, 2014- Sinchon, Seoul.]
Hello?
Is there anyone around?
My name tag.
My name tag is gone!
[His name tag is gone!]
[At the same time, other members of RM
start to come to at various locations.]
Wait...
I can't help but laugh right now.
[No need to laugh.
Look at this guy over here...]
My name tag!
Where did my name tag go?
[Running Man members awake to find
their name tags missing from their backs.]
[Just what could've happened
to their name tags?]
Wait... what happened to my name tag?
Why is it missing?
What happened?
What's this?
[Discovers a mysterious note in his pocket.]
[If you're missing your name tag,
it means that you've been ousted.]
[If you want to find your name tag and
come back to life, then go to this place.]
You're saying that I'm out right now?
[Already out of the game
as soon as the game starts?]
If you want to come back to life,
then you must go to this place.
What are all these symbols?
What do all these symbols mean?
What does this mean?
Is it a riddle that needs to be solved?
What the heck is this?
Are they kidding me right now?
- Why are they making it so difficult?
- How are we supposed to solve this?
- Are these alien symbols or something?
- My name tag!
Could these be...
some Greek...
No, I don't know what these are.
They're like...
hieroglyphics.
They're like hieroglyphics.
Ugh, I can't even ask anyone for help.
I think anyone I ask for help
is going to tell me that I'm crazy.
Grill?
Am I supposed to find a grill?
Oh? I see EWHA Woman's University.
We must be in Sinchon somewhere.
So I'm in Sinchon right now.
Wait a minute.
EWHA Woman's University.
This could stand for 'E'.
So these symbols could mean
EWHA Woman's University.
So I have to meet 12 students from
EWHA Woman's University...
and do 12 counts of sit-ups?
This is the front gate of
EWHA Woman's University.
Do you by any chance know
where this is pointing to?
- Is it a place within EWHA Woman's University?
- I'm not sure.
- Here?
Here?
Here.
- Here.
- Enough!
What am I supposed to do here?
I really don't know!
But... it still feels good to be here.
[Seems as though
he just wants to stay 'here'?]
- Hello.
- Jong Kook!
- You're so handsome!
Can you come here for a minute?
Can you help me out with something?
We're trying to solve a riddle
right now.
It's a riddle.
I need to figure out this location.
[Jae Suk has been trying to figure it out
on his own for quite a while now.]
Okay, there's one 'o'.
And there's either this or that character.
And there are two 'K'.
Could it be a pharmacy?
There's one 'o', and two 'k'.
See?
There are two of these characters.
[What is the location that the riddle
is indicating to?]
'Yook'?
Yook-Gyo.
(A bridge or an overpass.)
A bridge.
Could it be that bridge over there?
- A bridge?
- I don't know. That does go down though.
- See? That would use up all the characters.
- Oh, you're right.
[The female students provide
a very likely answer.]
Maybe it really is the bridge.
- That's amazing.
- Look at this.
That's something that could be used
on top or on the bottom.
One of the 'o' and two of the 'k'.
That is it!
It's a bridge!
['Yook-Gyo' - Bridge.]
But do you know how many bridges
there are around here?
Yook... Yook-gyo!
[Even Big-nosed Brother solves the riddle
with the help of others.]
Where is there a bridge?
That one? That bridge?
I think I got it.
Thanks so much.
[A bridge is spotted near the university.]
[Mr. Capable heads over
to the closest bridge.]
What are you doing?
Isn't that Dong Hwan?
[Shaman Dong Hwan.]
- Long time no see, Dong Hwan.
- You made it. Have a seat.
[PD Dong Hwan makes a long awaited return
as the mysterious shaman.]
Seeing how eager you're looking...
you must want to live again?
- Yes, I want to live.
- Come closer.
You must go back to the past.
You want me to go back to the past?
Here.
If you want to go back to the past to
reclaim your name tag and come back to life
you must go to the 'S' cancer hospital
in Sinchon and find the magical pill.
[Magical pill...]
Okay, I understand.
- Am I the first one to have come here?
- That's a secret.
['S' Hospital in Sinchon.]
[Time travel... back to the past?]
Seeing the expression on your face, it looks
as though you want to come back to life?
Yes, I do.
In that case,
I'll tell you how you can do that.
How would I do that?
You must go back to the past.
[This wasn't how it was supposed to go...]
What do you mean, go back to the past?
Here.
Huh?
Where's the magical pill?
Go to that hospital over there,
and you can find your magical pill.
- Yes, I understand. But tell me honestly...
- Take the pill and go back to the past.
- How many others came before me?
- That's a secret.
I can tell by seeing how many
mission cards you have left.
- I can find out for myself.
- Go and find out for yourself.
You know what I feel whenever I see you
doing something like this?
I haven't been on the show in a while.
Please listen and just do as I say.
Okay, I understand.
Okay, then I'll be on my way.
- Then...
- Fighting.
Is there a hint or a clue that
you can share with me?
[Instead of being on his way,
he's requesting for another hint.]
Oh, this must be the place.
[This scene... looks all too familiar...]
Wait a minute.
Isn't this from the Yoo-ames Bond episode?
[Hospital, white hospital gowns,
and all these people...]
[Could this be...
the first Yoo-ames Bond episode?]
- What do you mean, Yoo-ames Bond episode?
- It's the Yoo-ames Bond episode.
What are you talking about?
What makes you even think that?
[Starting to bicker
as soon as they see each other.]
- Don't you remember this scene?
- Yes, of course I remember.
How did you figure out the riddle?
- That was no big deal.
- What a joke!
Seriously... even a six year old
could've figured it out.
- What did you say?
- Seriously.
I'll see you once I find
and take my magical pill.
[Their six year old level
conversation comes to a close.]
Ugh, Kim Jong Kook.
He beat me here.
[Must find the magical pill before he does.]
It's not like they have name tags on them.
But some of them are carrying a bag?
Excuse me.
Excuse me, but can I take a look at
what's inside that bag?
Why are you avoiding me?
Wait a minute.
[The way she's avoiding him
definitely makes her seem suspicious.]
Wait, I need to look at what's inside the bag.
Please show me what you have in there.
[Kkuk finally manages to stop her.]
- Show me what you have in there. Please?
- It's my gift to you.
Thank you.
What's in here?
It's just a case?
[The pill that he's searching for
isn't in the case.]
I think it's in one of the cases
that they're carrying around.
[All of the members enter the hospital
one by one after having solved the riddle.]
I wonder if the pill
is in one of those cases?
[Jae Suk also suspects the case.]
Excuse me.
[Chasing them down to check
the contents inside the case.]
[Oh? A medicine bottle?]
[If it's a medicine bottle,
then could the pill be inside the bottle?]
Stop him!
[Giraffe chases down his prey
to the end of the hallway.]
It's the pill, isn't it?
- Wrestling for it won't do any good.
- Yes, you're right.
Let's play for it.
Rock, paper, scissors.
[Huh? A nail?]
- Will it work if I were to eat this?
- You can't eat that.
I said, you can't eat that.
You can't eat that, Kwang Soo.
- What word game are you playing right now?
- You can't eat it. (But also, 'Eat the nail')
The nail... eat it.
(A word play on the word, nail.)
- What?
- You can't eat it, or eat the nail.
- What are you saying?
- You either can't eat it, or eat the nail.
- Eat the nail.
- You can't eat it, or eat the nail.
You really are a master of words.
[We'll say that you will not be
eating the nail then...]
- There's Gary.
- I couldn't find the bridge right away.
So you solved the riddle,
but you couldn't find the bridge?
No, I wasn't able to solve the riddle.
- Wait.
- Why?
[Something... is about to change.]
- What did you just do?
- I didn't do anything!
[One by one... the members suddenly
start to disappear.]
I'm seriously about to go crazy.
[Just what is happening to
these members?]
[Time is starting to flow backwards.]
If you were given the chance to travel
back in time on Running Man...
Then which point in time
would you like to go back to?
[The time that Blank Ji would like to
go back to is?]
In my history of Running Man...
the most fun I ever had was...
The psychic power episode was one episode
that I will never be able to forget.
It's the Yoo-ames Bond episode.
- Which of those episodes?
- Excuse me?
All those Yoo-ames Bond episodes
were a masterpiece.
I felt so good in those episodes.
[Yoo-ames Bond showed a beautiful twist
to a story with a simple water gun.]
I almost had Jae Suk in that episode.
But unfortunately, right at the end...
I even had everything opened up too.
[If he could've starred in any episode?]
The Yoo-ames Bond episode with the water gun.
[Time travel... back into the past.]
[Wait...]
[This place is...]
What the heck is this?
Why are we starting off like this?
We're doing this again?
Seriously!
Where are my roasted dumplings?
[Someone took the magical pill.]
[And...]
[They're all locked up behind bars again
just like the last time.]
We have to find it again?
The secret number code?
Wait, this is...
This is... Yoo-ames...
[April 22, 2012.]
[Their race for the day starts off
behind locked bars.]
[Their moments of disparate running
in order to escape their prison.]
[They all became ousted by
Yoo-ames Bond's water gun.]
[The Yoo-ames Bond episode that threw
everyone into a state of panic.]
So Jae Suk ousted everyone?
[The events that transpired during that
episode are still clear in their memories.]
[Yoo-ames Bond walks away in ease
after having ousted all the members.]
What's going on here?
Even the clothes?
Then is there a water gun?
Why are we doing this all of a sudden?
Are you out of your mind or something?
But... we've already done this
so they already know what happens.
So you're asking me to go around
with the water gun again?
[Is it the return of Yoo-ames Bond?]
We had to find our way out of here
and find the key.
There were so many
security guards back then.
[Just like the last time, security guards
are seen guarding the premises.]
It's the sequel?
It was like the Yoo-ames Bond
sequel episode.
We had to find the hidden clues
to escape out of here.
I have to find the hidden number code.
[And there's one person who's more confused
than anyone else at that exact moment.]
- We've gone back to that night.
- We have?
[First time travel-
It's currently April 22, 2012.]
What are you trying to do
right now?
[How will Yoo-ames Bond's second experience
with the events of April 22nd turn out?]
Seriously, I'm going to lose my mind.
[First thing he must do is to solve the code,
and escape from behind bars.]
[Oh?]
[His padlock... is unlocked?]
Huh?
Wait, what is this?
It's unlocked.
[The events of the past are different.
Could it be the effects of time travel?]
What is this?
Find the layout of the building,
and escape within the next hour.
Isn't this what happened the
last time too?
Do I have a name tag on my back or not?
[The name tag that didn't exist in the past
is now on his back.]
What in the world?
What in the world is going on here?
[Carefully steps out from his jail cell...]
[Yoo-ames Bond...]
[Has his day returned once again?]
Where am I supposed to find
the layout of this building?
[Jae Suk searches for the blueprints
of the building as the note has instructed.]
I need to get out here within
the next hour.
Get him!
[Extreme state of nervousness.]
Wait.
I just got out here.
[Dragged back to the cell
if captured by the security guards.]
Why are you putting me back
in there already?
Did he get caught?
Hey!
It isn't you?
What's happening to you?
- I have no idea.
- Did you run into anyone?
- I think this is the Yoo-ames Bond episode.
- This is the Yoo-ames Bond episode.
Suk Jin!
This is Yoo-ames Bond sequel episode.
Yeah, this is the sequel.
You remember what happened, right?
- Suk Jin.
- You haven't made it out yet?
- How did you get out?
- You haven't made it out then?
But I remember...
[The padlock is already unlocked...]
- Did you take the pill or not?
- No, I didn't take it.
- Suk Jin, how did you get out?
- Huh?
Yeah, the padlock was already unlocked.
Why didn't you tell me about this?
- Seriously.
- Why would I have to tell you?
[Easy Brothers' loyalty always has
been a pretty thin line.]
Watch your back.
- Watch your back.
- Get him!
[Discovered by the security guards
the moment he escapes from his cell.]
I was actually in here.
I didn't step foot outside my cell.
He's the one who was out walking around.
I never left my cell.
I need to find the blueprint.
[Kkuk is on the search for the blueprint
after having escaped his cell.]
I have to find the blueprint.
Which floor am I on right now?
[The security guards.]
[He'll be dragged back to his cell
once he's captured.]
[The open jail cell is already filling up
with prisoners.]
- You were the culprit the last time, right?
- Not the culprit, but the star of the show.
I still can't forget
the sound of your whistling to this day.
Ugh, you're right.
I'm starting to remember everything.
[Yoo-ames Bond-
His betrayal that they're not able to forget.]
Even though you can tie up my body,
you can't tie up my freedom.
[Gary's infamous line.]
The blueprint is nowhere to be found.
So what are we doing in here?
Why?
But that's not your goal, is it?
But I don't have a water gun.
You think I'd be here if I had it?
I'm sure you'll be
getting one soon though, right?
- Or he'll drink his pill.
- I told you that I'm not.
- I don't even know what the pill is.
- I don't either.
- What is that?
- I don't know either. I haven't even seen it.
[Is that right?]
What did you have, Gary?
I... had a caramel macchiato earlier.
- No, you were talking about some pill.
- Did you take the pill?
No, I don't know what you're
talking about.
- Did you take it or not?
- Didn't you meet Shaman Dong Hwan?
Dong Hwan told us to take the pill.
- Did you see him?
- Yes, I saw Dong Hwan.
- But you didn't solve your mission earlier.
- You didn't solve the riddle?
- You couldn't solve it?
- You didn't solve the mission?
- Seriously.
- You couldn't even solve a simple problem?
- You went to the bridge?
- Of course I did.
- Did you take the pill?
- No, I didn't.
- Then you're the only one who took it?
- No, I didn't take it either.
- Yes, you did!
- No, I didn't!
- You just said you solved the mission!
- Give it to me and I'll take it right now.
[They're becoming more and more
suspicious of each other.]
- You're the most suspicious one here.
- Why me?
It makes no sense that you made it here when
you didn't even solve the riddle.
How did you even make it here
without having solved that?
Can a student even get into a university
without having passed the exam?
Yes, all the time!
Oh, all the time?
In the variety world?
[No matter what the case...]
[These two are acting a bit suspicious.]
Just where in the world is it?
[Yoo-ames Bond was the star
of this episode...]
[Is the blueprint what he's
searching for right now?]
[Or could it be the water gun?]
It's nothing.
Wow, I thought that was it.
[What is it that Gary is searching for?]
[That's...]
[Blank Ji discovers the blueprint!]
Awesome.
[If the memory serves right, then the location
of the key is indicated on the blueprint!]
It's on the second floor.
Department of Nuclear Medicine.
[Just like the last time...]
[Must find the key to escape from these
suspiciously similar events to the past.]
[Just then, Kkuk and Haroro meet up.]
Jong Kook.
Gary...
- Gary... it's Gary.
- What are you doing?
Why?
Tell me your reasoning for it.
- Earlier...
- Yeah?
- You're not trying to lure me in, are you?
No, not at all.
Listen... Jae Suk, Gary and I were
help captive together a little bit ago.
Without there being a reason to,
Gary started asking me weird questions.
He started talking about some pill.
So I asked him what the pill was.
Then Jae Suk started covering up for Gary
instead of questioning him with me.
- What was he trying to do?
- I kept thinking about it...
- I'm sure that Jae Suk is up to something.
- I've been thinking about it...
I want some water.
[Oh?]
[That is...]
[A water gun?]
I don't think an opportunity like this
is ever going to come around again.
What are you doing!
[Mr. Capable attacks!]
[How can this be!]
You actually brought me
into the room with you.
[But why is he...]
[Panic]
[What could have happened
to Jong Kook?]
[May 18, 2014- Present day.]
[The members went on a search for
the pill during the current day and time.]
This is the type of place
where the pill is usually found.
See?
This is where the pills are usually found.
These are the type of places where
the pills are found in the movies... Oh!
[Mr. Capable discovers the magical pill!]
[Just what is the hidden power behind
the mysterious magical pill?]
April 22, 2012.
This is way past the expiration date.
Is it okay for me to be taking this?
If I take this...
are we going to go back to
April 22, 2012?
Should I take it?
[Cautiously takes the pill
with trepidation.]
Once I took the pill,
we went back to April 22, 2012.
[Nurse Dong Hwan comes to
visit Kkuk in his cell.]
- What is all that?
- Follow me.
What?
You want me to follow you?
[An empty room.]
What is this?
[Opens up the closet in the room.]
There's a door?
[Just like the door that Yoo-ames Bond
discovered back on April 22, 2012...]
There's a door?
[Then behind that door...]
Wait, wait a minute.
What is this?
Then am I...
Could it be because I took the pill?
[It's the same room where Yoo-ames Bond
received his secret mission!]
So this is what Yoo Jae Suk must've felt.
So this is how Jae Suk must've felt like.
What is this?
- You know what this is about, right?
- Yes, I think I know.
Mr. Kim Jong Kook.
You took the magical pill.
Today is April 22, 2012.
You have come back as Yoo-ames Bond
in the Return of Yoo-ames Bond segment.
But... this is...
[The history of Running Man
is about to change.]
[Running Man Time Travel-
Return of Yoo-ames Bond.]
Today is April 22, 2012.
[You are the star of
The Return of Yoo-ames Bond Race.]
[The new star of The Return of
Yoo-ames Bond.]
Oust all the members of Running Man by
shooting them with the water gun to win.
[The new star of The Return of Yoo-ames
Bond- Kim Jong Kook.]
Wow, this is really amazing.
Then behind that wall is...
It's just as you've seen in the
past episode.
[Just like that moment from the past...]
[The spinning wall...]
[Behind that wall is...
various water guns.]
[Extremely happy]
[Selects the turtle water gun
which he can hide in his hand.]
I can hide it in my hand like this.
I think this will be perfect.
- For Kkuk-ames Bond...
- Yes?
Yes, I'm Kkuk-ames Bond.
You must recapture all the members
before they escape from the building
in order for you to win this race.
[Recapture all the members before
they escape to win the race!]
If even one member succeeds at escaping,
then this time travel will come to an end.
Is that right?
[Kkuk-ames Bond completes his preparation
to start his secret mission.]
[You just wait, Yoo-ames Bond...
Kkuk-ames Bond is now here.]
I will oust every one of them.
Especially... Mr. Yoo Jae Suk.
I want him to experience what
this feels like.
[Welcome to Kkuk-ames Bond's world.]
I don't think an opportunity like this
is ever going to come knocking again.
[Ha Ha unknowingly gave Kkuk-ames Bond
an easy way to oust him.]
What is this?
[Time for some action.]
[Kkuk-ames Bond's first shot-
A bulls-eye!]
[This has to be a dream.]
I thought it was going to be difficult to get
someone in a room, but you brought me in here.
[The water gun...
so this is what it feels like.]
You're guesses were way off.
[Extremely confused.]
Sorry, Dong Hoon.
[Sorry, my brother.
But I'm the star of this race.]
[Ha Ha is recaptured.]
I must've been crazy.
[Kkuk-ames Bond runs off to another floor
to avoid any suspicion.]
Hey!
Ji Hyo!
- Huh?
- Dong Hoon!
Where is he?
[Kkuk-ames Bond purposely shows Ha Ha's
recapturing to avoid any suspicion.]
Why is he being taken away?
He's being silenced
as they're taking him away.
[Just then!]
[Blank Ji starts to do
a body search on Kkuk-ames Bond!]
- Come on, seriously?
- You don't have anything?
[It'll all be over for him if she
discovers his water gun!]
No, I don't have anything!
[Where did he hide his water gun?]
I didn't think so.
I don't have anything either.
I really don't have anything, Jong Kook.
I only have my cellphone and a mirror.
You're acting strange.
[He's pretending to be
suspicious of Blank Ji.]
Why would Ha Ha get recaptured?
But Jae Suk told me that
Ha Ha was being most suspicious.
[Kkuk-ames Bond is casually avoiding
any of Blank Ji's suspicion.]
- Then could Jae Suk be something?
- He said Ha Ha was most suspicious.
Ha Ha is recaptured.
Then that means he's been shot
by the water gun.
[All the members are thrown into a fit of
anxiety upon the news of Ha Ha's recapturing.]
Why did he get recaptured?
Then someone must've ousted him.
Then someone must have a water gun.
This won't do.
I shouldn't be sitting here like this.
I have to escape out of here.
I'm not the star of this race.
[The original Yoo-ames Bond
lost his spotlight to someone else.]
Who is it?
Who's my imposter?
The original star is right here,
so who's going around...
I need to go catch my imposter.
Who's going around pretending to be me?
Jong Kook!
[Did Kwang Soo catch on to the plan?]
[No, of course not.]
[In anything else, the next victim is alerting
the culprit to what has just transpired.]
So this means that there's definitely
a Yoo-ames Bond amongst us today.
- So that means...
- If it's a water gun...
- But this game is all about the water gun.
- But I searched for it, and didn't find any.
Be careful.
There are too many guards walking around.
Let's find the blueprint first.
We must hurry.
[Convincing Kwang Soo to find
the blueprint first in order to escape.]
Since the blueprint indicated where
the key is located...
- I'll be in the next room.
- Okay.
[Kwang Soo walks away
to search the next room.]
[The real reason why
Kkuk-ames Bond came here is...]
[It was to retrieve his water gun!]
[Having hid the water gun elsewhere in case
of someone doing a body search on him.]
[Shall we get back in the game?]
- Ji Hyo, have you seen anyone?
- Jong Kook.
- Why isn't anyone even around?
Do you remember why Ha Ha has been
recaptured from the past episode?
Kwang Soo just told me that he saw
a water gun mark on his back.
- When you get shot by the water gun...
- Get them!
You'll be recaptured if you get
shot by the water gun.
[The two tries to flee together as they're
spotted by the security guards.]
- When?
- Don't you remember?
[Just then!]
[He drops... the water gun on the floor!]
[But fortunately for him, she's
too busy hiding to see the water gun.]
[But just then...
Kwang Soo comes up from behind!]
[Kkuk-ames Bond picks up the water gun
in a blink of an eye!]
[The idiot!
Kwang Soo didn't see it!]
[An extremely dangerous situation
that could've ruined everything!]
[Kkuk-ames Bond shaves ten years
off of his life!]
What do you have under your shirt?
[Kwang Soo found the blueprint.]
Let's see that.
[This isn't good...]
Wow, this is exhausting.
So it's not on the second floor.
- Third floor?
- What about the fourth floor?
[I think it's time... for you to go.]
[Time to hunt down the Giraffe.]
I think it's on the fourth floor.
What?
- What?
- What did you just do?
No, nothing.
Come on, Kwang Soo. Second floor?
Where did you find this?
- Jong Kook.
- Yeah?
It's really a relief...
because I really needed this blueprint.
Okay, then I'll let others believe
that I found this myself.
I don't think they'll suspect me as long as
I let them think that I'm working really hard.
Why are you such an awful person?
Did you just oust me?
[Kkuk-ames Bond is proving to be even more
of a nightmare than Yoo-ames Bond.]
Target, Lee Kwang Soo.
[Let go of me!]
[Giraffe is lashing out
from his sense betrayal.]
- Sorry, Kwang Soo.
- Hey!
Did you just say, 'Hey'?
[Lee Kwang Soo is recaptured.]
Lee Kwang Soo has been recaptured.
So the key is on the fourth floor.
[Gary is feeling the pressure to find the key
and make his escape.]
This is it.
[Carefully searching through
the entire room.]
No way they would've hidden it here.
[Curiosity... killed the cat.]
They actually hid it in there?
[Gary finds the key!]
[Now he just has to find the exit...]
So Gary hasn't been caught.
[Just then... Jong Kook uses the blueprint
as bait to approach Jae Suk.]
- Where did you find it?
- On the third floor.
- What did you find?
- The key is on the fourth floor.
[Kkuk-ames Bond tries to avoid any suspicion
by sharing his information with Jae Suk.]
[The new star, Kkuk-ames Bond...
faces off with the original Yoo-ames Bond.]
You don't have a water gun, do you?
[The original isn't proving to be
a very easy opponent...]
[And the formidable new player
on the scene.]
[The water gun is hidden in his waistline...]
[The undeniable nervous energy...
and these two formidable opponents.]
- So the key is on the fourth floor?
- Let's go up to the fourth floor.
[Leaving the room with wariness
towards one another.]
- Let's go up there separately.
- Why?
I think it would be better for us
to go up there separately.
I just shared a very crucial
bit of information with you.
- This isn't an individual victory.
- I know.
- This is a group victory.
- Yes, you're right.
Wake up, and throw away your greed.
I'm not being greedy right now,
but I think that you're dangerous.
How can I even oust you
without a water gun?
You're good at spouting off water
at times, aren't you?
You can't think that I have some watercolor
swishing around in my mouth?
What if you're up to something?
I'm sure there's a solution to this.
- Are you sure that it isn't you?
- No, it's not me.
- Why isn't it you?
- I was just with Ji Hyo and Suk Jin.
[You're saying that the three of you
were just together?]
[So that's why you're being
suspicious of me?]
I'm just going to back away right now.
- You're a little suspicious.
- Okay, fine.
[I need to find another way.]
What could it be?
Is it not him?
Just what in the world is going on today?
[Kkuk-ames Bond's ambush attack!]
[If words aren't going to do it...
then I have no other choice but to attack!]
[April 22, 2012...
the moment of ultimate insult!]
[I will rewrite the history of that moment!]
[Bulls-eye!]
[Original Yoo-ames Bond is defeated
by the new Kkuk-ames Bond!]
[The one who used to wield
the water gun...]
[is thrown back in time to become
the victim of the water gun himself.]
[Goodbye, Yoo-ames.]
That is not the way
the water gun is supposed to be used.
- How did he get you?
- What are you going to do now?
How could you have ruined the
Yoo-ames Bond episode like this?
You know how the right way to do it
is to do it secretly?
He just attacked me with the water gun
pointed at my face like this.
[Frontal attack is Kkuk-ames Bond's style.]
- That's what he did to me too.
- This is not how it's supposed to be done!
I know that everyone has
their own style.
What are you going to do about all the viewers
who love the Yoo-ames Bond episodes?
The way he's doing it is the
Terminator style!
What's even the point of him
using a water gun in this case?
Seriously.
[Kkuk-ames Bond's water gun is starting to
close in on the remaining members.]
[Blank Ji is busy searching for the exit.]
So I need to find the exit
out of this building.
[Big-nose Brother has been recaptured
without anyone even knowing!]
It's Jong Kook.
[Since it's already come to this...
I'll now just do it my way.]
[Kkuk-minator]
[Compared to Yoo-ames' annoying whistles,
Kkuk-ames' whistles are downright terrifying.]
It's been Kim Jong Kook all along.
[A terrifying sight to behold.]
- Where in the world is Kang Gary right now?
- Guys, where are you?
[Gary quickly hid himself in a hiding spot
as soon as he heard the whistling sound.]
Gary?
I'm really starting to miss you.
No!
You're going to get me caught.
Guys!
Guys, where are you?
[Barely manages to pull himself together
to move from his hiding spot.]
- You scared me!
- Did you see him?
- See what?
- Jong Kook is carrying around a water rifle.
- Jong Kook is the culprit.
- Really?
- Who was the one whistling?
- How far have you searched for the exit?
I have the key right here.
[Gary has become as blank minded
as he was back in 2012.]
I found the keys.
How many are there?
[Monday Couple are the last ones left alive,
and they each pull out their set of keys.]
Have you found the way out yet?
The exit door?
[They just need to find the exit.]
- Over there?
- Come here.
- I was thinking that it was over there too.
- See how it's wider over there?
Remember how we used to race around
the skywalk a lot back in the day?
[Just as they're predicting,
the exit is at the end of the skywalk!]
- Let's go right now.
- Even if we don't run into him...
Why?
Is it not opening?
[If one of the keys are the right one,
then they can make their escape right now!]
Guys, where are you?
Come out while I'm still being nice.
[Just then, Kkuk-ames Bond starts to
head over in their direction!]
Let's go.
Let's go quickly!
[Now that everything is out in the open,
speed is the key to their survival!]
We don't have much time!
Where could you guys have gone?
[Oh?
He catches the Monday Couple running away.]
We don't have much time!
Here it is!
Try the keys quickly!
[Gary and Blank Ji arrive at
the exit door.]
[Only one out of these is the right one.]
[He's coming!]
[Please...]
[Quickly!]
[Will they escape first...]
[Or get caught?]
[It opened!]
[Gary and Blank Ji succeed
at making their escape!]
What the heck!
It's over?
[May 18, 2014- Present Day.]
Who do you think it is?
I'm going to get Kim Jong Kook for this.
[Hi!]
- I can't even stand the sight of him.
- You've just totally ruined Yoo-ames Bond.
What are you supposed to be?
Rambo?
I was going to do it shirtless,
and I barely held myself back.
The beauty of Yoo-ames Bond is
doing it covertly.
What do you mean, that's the beauty of it?
You should just be upfront with it.
- You just totally ruined Yoo-ames Bond.
- Just shoot everyone down.
- Just shoot them all down!
- Seriously.
I'm going to make myself very clear
about this right now.
But my Yoo-ames Bond series
is a totally different thing from him.
[The Senior Bond isn't acknowledging
the validity of the Junior Bond.]
- He's totally different.
- Yoo Jae Suk, can you step forward?
Why?
- What's that?
- What is that?
What is it now?
Why is it bigger?
Seriously!
What the heck is this!
[The name tags of those who were eliminated
during the time travel are enlarged.]
So only those who succeeded keep
the smaller name tags.
I didn't know that this was
going to happen.
- You too, Mr. Kim Jong Kook.
- Yes, Kook-Bo.
[Kkuk-ames Bond unfortunately also gets
a name tag enlargement.]
You two will keep your current size.
These two always win together
whenever we do something like this.
I allowed her to step out of
the exit first.
- I'm just telling him what happened.
- You'd better pull yourself together.
You must find the next pill.
Kim Jong Kook can never become Yoo-ames
Bond in a Yoo-ames Bond episode.
He needs to play the evil character.
No, the evil character suits him better.
That way, the star can shine even brighter.
That's why Kim Jong Kook should
never play Bond.
He needs to play the evil character.
I would...
like to go back to
the Sherlock Holmes episode.
I don't think anyone other than
myself can do that one.
I'm the only one who can do it.
Why, you ask?
Because to be perfectly blunt,
the episode was written specifically for me.
If I was Lupin,
I wouldn't have done it that way.
[Kwang Soo takes the pill?]
What is it now?
Who took the pill this time?
[What happened to Running Man members
on January 29, 2012?]
I should've found the pill again.
[The start of another time travel.]
Is it the Lupin episode?
Ah, that Lupin?
The battle between Lupin and Holmes?
[That's right... it was a
battle between Holmes and Lupin.]
Wait, this is...
Sherlock Holmes!
When Jae Dong and Dong Hyun came on
in the Busan episode...
Suk Jin had done it!
I remember Suk Jin taking me down.
I still can't believe that happened.
[The painful memory of having been
ousted by Suk Jin.]
Is it the Sherlock episode?
Is it?
My ultimate masterpiece, Sherlock?
[The first time he became the star...
His unforgettable role as Lupin.]
Yes, that was a great episode.
I captured Lupin at the end.
I remember the unbelievable clue
that I found in the book.
[Brilliantly figured out the true identity
of Lupin at the end!]
[Jong Kook and Ji Hyo duo
thus captures Lupin Suk Jin!]
A rare treasure by the name of 'Blue Water',
which is a giant sized sapphire is hidden
and clues to the treasure's location
are hidden throughout this building.
[Find the clues to claim the sapphire
to win the mission!]
This is a mission tailored just for me.
Rather than the treasure hunting mission,
it's all about Lupin having returned.
Just what Lupin is all about.
This is about Suk Jin, isn't it?
Just who took the pill this time?
Right now...
it's January 29, 2012.
[Time travel back to January 29, 2012.]
You are the star of the
Sherlock Holmes Race.
You are Lupin, The Phantom Thief.
[Lupin, The Phantom Thief- Kwang Soo.]
Since you took the magical pill
you became the star of
the Sherlock Holmes Race.
You have to oust the other members of RM
while pretending to be ousted yourself to win.
I understand,
and I will do my best.
Due to the butterfly effect that took place
during the time travel back into the past
the mission for Lupin has
slightly changed.
You have to let others believe that
you've been ousted out of the race
you have to find the briefcases which
contain the name tags of the other members
and you have to oust those members by
ripping off those name tags.
[Find the briefcases which contain the
name tags of the other members to oust them.]
So I don't have to rip it off
their backs directly?
That's not too bad.
[Time travel back into the past has changed
the role of Lupin.]
[Will he be able to change the outcome
of the race as well?]
This is too hard.
It's too hard to be doing this alone.
- Hi!
- Long time no see!
[Lupin's helpers- Team Hao and Chao.]
Thank you.
Yes, thank you!
Wow, it's been so long!
That's right, I had forgotten.
[Team Hao and Chao had lured and
confused the Sherlock  Holmes characters.]
I'm the new Lupin.
- You?
- Yes, I'm Lupin.
- We're ruined.
- Why are we ruined?
- No, we're not.
- I think we can do it.
- Thank you so much.
- Fighting.
[Lupin Kwang Soo with his team
of dependable helpers.]
One, two, three... Fighting!
[Celebrating as if
they've already won the race.]
- I won't disappoint you.
- We're ruined.
You have to remain quiet.
Seriously... I'm not good at finding things,
and I have to find things all day.
I'm not good at doing
detailed things like this.
What's all that noise?
What's that?
Where are you going?
- Where are you going?
- Huh?
[I'm in big trouble!]
[Caught in a difficult position
right from the start of the race.]
Isn't it the Hao Chao guys?
Where are you going?
- Isn't it the Hao Chao guys?
- Yes.
[Caught walking together
with Hao Chao Team...]
Jae Suk.
Isn't it the Hao Chao guys?
[This would mean that he could suspect
my true identity...]
- This is the same as the last time.
- Hi!
This is the same as the last time.
They're all here?
[Lupin Kwang Soo is in danger!]
- I think they're here for a reason.
- It's the same as the last time.
[No way...]
- I think they're here for a reason.
- It's the same as the same time.
I know, they were here
the last time too.
Lee Kwang Soo, out.
The events of the past have changed.
So we will be announcing that you've been
ousted the moment you start your mission.
- Wait...
- We never announced Ji Suk Jin being ousted.
But we're going to announce that
you've been ousted.
Why would I be ousted?
[Time travel will change
the events of the past.]
Yes, the events of the past have changed.
I remember that the last time
you guys were here...
[Lupin Kwang Soo's quick decision.]
Lee Kwang Soo, out.
[The announcement of you being ousted...
tells me that you're Lupin.]
What just happened?
It's you?
Yoo Jae Suk, out.
I took the pill.
[Detective Jae Suk is eliminated
the moment the race starts.]
- Lee Kwang Soo, out.
- What?
- Yoo Jae Suk, out.
- What? The race just started!
Seriously? Or is this a lie?
They're seriously ousted?
[No one can believe that Jae Suk
is already ousted out of the race.]
What did he do?
Who's the culprit?
Then who's Lupin?
I guarantee... that the first person
ousted is the real culprit.
Because that's the way I wrote this race.
[Hmm...]
Remember what happened the last time
even though Suk Jin wasn't ousted?
So wouldn't it be either Kwang Soo
or Jae Suk this time around too?
Ugh, seriously.
I can't believe that I've been ousted
the moment the race started.
This is the first time since being on the show
that I've been ousted the moment I started.
[Rewriting history of Running Man.]
[A mysterious card that appears after
a member is ousted just like the last time.]
[Could it be?]
I have to come up with a plan.
[Kwang Soo orders Hao Chao to observe
others and to search for the briefcases.]
Hi, Song Ji Hyo.
[Greeting the other members loudly to let
Kwang Soo know of their whereabouts.]
[Lupin Kwang Soo is flustered
and doesn't know what to do.]
- Hello.
- Where's Chao Chao?
It's just the three of us.
No Chao Chao.
Oh, he's not here?
[They lie to Ji Hyo and
tell her that Chao Chao isn't with them.]
Have you seen the other members?
No, you haven't seen them?
- Okay, I'll see you later.
- Bye.
[Detective Blank Ji doesn't suspect anything
and is just happy to have seen them.]
[Tightly holding onto the door
to keep it shut.]
I didn't know that I'd be this nervous.
So Suk Jin actually did a good job
when he did it.
Take a look and see if there's
anyone out there.
I'll just stay back here.
I'm not going to move at all from here.
[Lupin Kwang Soo doesn't even budge
from the room that he's hiding in.]
[Lupin Kwang Soo's special characteristic-
Bravery of a bird.]
[Regardless of the matter, it looks as though
he's seriously about to start the search.]
[Following Chao Chao's signal...
Lupin dashes out of his hiding spot.]
[Huh?]
[Instead of searching for
the detectives...]
[Lupin Kwang Soo hides himself away
in a darkened room?]
When you knock on the door,
knock on the door like this.
I was just wondering...
I can't squeeze into that dog costume
with Chao Chao, can I?
[Wanting to hide himself away in a place
where no one could ever find him.]
- Hey, Jong Kook.
- How are they ousted the moment we start?
- Just like when you did it...
- It's the first person that gets ousted.
- I agree.
- The first person ousted is the culprit.
- Yes, it was like that with you too.
- I was the first person ousted.
But the difference is, they never
announced that you were ousted.
- We just saw you getting dragged away.
- Yes, you're right.
- Do you remember that?
- Yeah, I remember that.
But I think the situation changes a little
like the butterfly effect.
I'm telling you that it really isn't me.
- But I think...
- Just trust me, Jong Kook.
[Suspecting the original Lupin, Suk Jin,
of being the culprit.]
Whether I win the race or not...
Look, those two are together.
- That's weird.
- Who?
Come here.
- Guys.
- Kwang Soo and Jae Suk...
- Have you two been together this whole time?
- No, we just ran into each other.
- You two just ran into each other, right?
- Yeah, we only just saw each other now.
[Still unsure of
each other's true intentions.]
Having ousted two members so quickly like that
requires more than just one person.
- It doesn't make any sense.
- I had some help back then too.
- Yes, you had helpers.
- I'm sure that the culprit has helpers.
- To oust two people so quickly like that?
- The culprit must have helpers.
- But how can they both be ousted already?
- Have you two been together all this time?
We just ran into each other
a little bit ago.
[While everyone else is busy suspecting
each other, Ace Ji Hyo springs into action.]
[She's focused on finding the treasure.]
[Oh?]
[But they told me that
Chao Chao wasn't here...]
We have to find the briefcases.
[Something doesn't feel right!]
[Kwang Soo?]
[But the announcement said
that he's been ousted...]
[I must hurry!]
[I have to let the others know
of this truth!]
[Hao Chao are busy searching for the
briefcases that contains the name tags.]
[Discovers a briefcase!]
[Chao Chao pulls his weight!]
How is this being the star of the show?
You found a briefcase?
[Chao Chao can only search for the briefcase,
but only Lupin can move or open it.]
Which drawer?
Where?
Where is it?
Over there?
[Lupin Kwang Soo finds his
first briefcase!]
[Ji Hyo is still rushing
to find the other members.]
[Kwang Soo, with the briefcase in hand...]
[Rushes back into his darkened room!]
[The moment he tears off the name tag,
that member is eliminated from the race!]
[Ji Suk Jin]
I'm sure Suk Jin is being suspected
by the other members right now.
I'm so curious right now.
I'm so curious because this person is
going to get the chance to live out my dream.
- It's you though, isn't it?
- I'm telling you that it isn't me.
It doesn't make any sense otherwise.
[Suk Jin is still the only one being suspected
by all the detectives.]
- Yes, I know I was upset when I didn't win.
- So this is another chance for you to do it.
[Still unable to escape their suspicion.]
[Just then, Ji Hyo makes her appearance
on the scene.]
I've missed you guys!
Chao Chao...
Chao Chao's gotten even bigger.
- Jong Kook.
- What took you so long to find us?
- Kwang Soo's still alive.
- He's still alive?
- Then it has to be Kwang Soo.
[The jig is up!]
- Kwang Soo is still alive?
- He's still alive and I just saw him.
- Is he out walking around?
- Yes, I just saw him walking around.
I know that Suk Jin has high hopes
for this race.
- But these guys were once my helpers.
- Wait, be quiet.
- Ji Suk Jin, out.
- Why am I ousted?
Why am I ousted?
- Suk Jin, this isn't a name tag elimination.
- No, it's not the name tag elimination.
[Shock]
- Who are these guys?
- But why am I ousted?
[Completely flustered as to why he's ousted
when he was only just standing there.]
Sorry, Suk Jin.
But your name was the first one I found.
Hey, hurry up!
- Hurry up and come here, Gary!
- Were you two guys together?
Suk Jin just got ousted
right in front of our eyes.
He just got ousted when his name tag
wasn't even ripped off.
[Figured out that the members can be ousted
without the name tag even being ripped off.]
He was just standing along the wall like this,
and then we heard that he's been ousted.
- That's what just happened.
- He just got ousted.
Just what is going on?
What were you guys doing?
Were you two together this whole time?
We were together this whole time.
[In an extreme state of nervousness with
all the detectives right outside the door.]
- I saw Kwang Soo still walking around.
- She said she saw him.
I really don't think I could ever do
anything like this ever again.
I feel like I'm going to throw up right now.
Do you remember what happened the last time?
Suk Jin was the first one ousted too, right?
- No, they never announced that Suk Jin...
- Don't go near Chao Chao.
I touched all those guys earlier.
I even touched Chao Chao.
Maybe it's that we can't touch Chao Chao when
there are a certain number of us together.
[What a deduction...
Eliminated from petting Chao Chao?]
Don't touch Chao Chao.
- Don't touch Chao Chao.
- He's so cute and I just want to touch him.
- He's so cute.
- No, you can't.
I wonder how cute it'll be
to pet him on his tummy.
But look at how aged Chao Chao's skin looks.
[Could Chao Chao's sign of aging be
one of the butterfly effects?]
But it wasn't like this earlier.
Earlier when we were there...
[The star of the show is
relegated to staying in this dark room.]
Please just go away!
[Along with having figured out
the identity of who Lupin is...]
I'm getting a weird feeling about this place.
[Jong Kook and Ji Hyo arrive on the outdoor
area of 7th floor in search of the treasure.]
I'm sure there has to be a clue
around here somewhere.
[A card?]
[A hint regarding the treasure is dropped
every time a member gets eliminated.]
- What is it?
- I just found this.
[The detectives find their first hint card.]
Olympic Opening Ceremony.
- When was the Beijing Olympics?
- Month, date and time.
In 2008.
- Yes, it was in 2008.
- 2008.
- Since it was in 2008...
Then could it be on the eighth floor?
[Could it be a hint regarding which floor
the treasure is kept hidden?]
I'm starting to feel dehydrated.
[Lupin Kwang Soo's lonely existence.]
I shouldn't have taken the pill.
Lupin is...
- Suk Jin was caught when he was Lupin.
- That wouldn't have happened if it was me.
And I wouldn't stay in hiding
or anything like that either.
I would be very brazen about it.
I don't think that a person can be the big
dish if he or she constantly stays in hiding.
[The small dish...]
Is no one out there?
Where are the other briefcases?
[Lupin gets to see the light for
the first time in thirty whole minutes.]
[It seems as though Hao Chao
has discovered another briefcase!]
Chao Chao.
Hi Gary!
[Danger!
Detective Gary is seen in the area!]
- Are you speaking in English?
- I'm busy.
[Hao Chao keeps their eyes on Gary.]
[Lupin Kwang Soo uses that time
to go in search of the briefcase.]
Where is it?
[Second briefcase is discovered.]
[Breaks out in a dead run!]
I really shouldn't have taken that pill.
Please let it be Kim Jong Kook.
Can you stop shooting me
and be on the lookout?
[Lupin assigns a task to his own personal VJ.]
Yell out 'Hao Chao' if you see anyone
coming near this room.
[Films with the left hand,
and opens up the case with his right.]
Song Ji Hyo!
I will now eliminate her.
Song Ji Hyo is out.
Now that we've got this...
Song Ji Hyo, Out.
[Second member to be eliminated
in plain sight.]
- Ji Hyo!
- Hurry up and find the treasure!
- Song Ji Hyo, out.
- What are we going to do, Gary? I'm scared.
Song Ji Hyo, out.
[Yes!]
Everyone... the Lupin that you've seen so far
hasn't been the real Lupin.
What you just saw is the real original Lupin.
It's Lupin Kwang, The Phantom Thief.
I'm going to eliminate
every single one of them.
[His simulation may make others think
that he may be an actual phantom thief.]
[Lupin Kwang, The Phantom Thief, in action.]
What you just saw...
is the real Lupin Kwang, The Phantom Thief.
The dream Suk Jin never got to live out...
I vow that I will live it out for him.
What I told you earlier about me not having
become the big dish...
I take those words back right now.
I've already grown above that.
I'm the real spy in town.
Where in the world in Lupin?
- I still haven't even seen him.
- We need to search everywhere.
Let's go search all the places that
we wouldn't normally search around in.
I bet there's something in a place where
it wouldn't be easy for us to get to.
[Lupin Kwang Soo has changed!]
[Maybe he really will be able to
eliminate everyone!]
[Lupin Kwang Soo has become braver
and more proactive!]
Where?
Where is it?
[Discovers the third briefcase!]
[Oh!
Gary is observing the CCTV cameras!]
I see someone moving.
I just saw someone running by.
[Lupin Kwang Soo is caught on CCTV!]
[Once this person is eliminated,
then only two detectives will remain.]
Please let it be Kim Jong Kook.
Please let it be Kim Jong Kook!
Kim Jong Kook, Kim Jong Kook!
[But unfortunately,
the briefcase contains Ha Ha's name.]
We can't just sit back and
do nothing, Ha Ha.
We have to keep moving,
and make something happen.
- We have to make things happen.
- We have to keep him on his toes.
- What is it?
- Come towards the elevator.
- Why?
- I just saw something suspicious over there.
If you were him, where would you go
if you didn't want to get caught?
[Above the lockers.]
What is it?
We have to stay together.
You know what he is like.
[Walks into the room
that Kwang Soo is hiding out in.]
[If they walk into the room any further,
then Kwang Soo is sure to get caught!]
- I just saw something!
- Where?
[He's caught.]
- Don't come any closer!
- Who is it?
Don't come any closer!
[Threatening them with Ha Ha's name tag
which he has yet to rip off.]
You want me to rip this off?
[Lupin vs Sherlock Holmes.
The imminent moment of truth!]
- I will rip this off!
- Wait, Lupin.
[Rips off the name tag, and huh?]
No one is eliminated!
The tag hasn't been ripped off!
[The amateur thief drops the briefcase
before the name tag is completely ripped off.]
See?
The tag hasn't been completely ripped off!
[Lupin Kwang Soo gets his name tag
ripped off instead!]
[Sherlock Holmes wins!]
No!
You're such an idiot!
This is all he managed to rip off.
[Lupin Kwang's newly rewritten history.]
- Anyway, Lupin fails his mission.
- No!
The psychic power episode.
I wasn't able to rip off Gary's name tag
because of the Roll-Roll spell he used.
The victory was right in front of my eyes.
That was seriously so disappointing.
I think the psychic power episode was one
episode which I'll never be able to forget.
That's the second most episode
that I would like to go back to.
I also remember the episode when
I had the power to manipulate time.
The second psychic power episode.
I think that's the only episode in which
Jong Kook was the first to be taken to jail.
In all four years of the show.
[The magical potion that was
given to the members.]
[Through these potions...
they are once again given psychic powers.]
- Just what kind of a power is it?
- Kim Jong Kook, come out!
[The fiercest battle in the history
of the show.]
[That historical moment...
will get rewritten today.]
[The psychic battle starts again.]
[But the star of the psychic battle
gets swapped out.]
[The same battle cannot exist.]
[Just who will be the new star
of the rewritten history?]
[Ten minutes before the start of
the psychic battle.]
It's the time for my favorite episode.
December 25th, right?
The one who controls time!
[The one man who wanted the power to
control the time again with his powers.]
[The original time controller, Ha Ha.]
Ever since I was given the power
to control time
I was stuck in that role in my head
for like a year after.
[Stuck in the role of being
able to control time...]
The one who controls the time!
[He at times would bring on the power
all on his own.]
The one who controls the time!
[Would chant the spell
whenever he got the chance.]
[He even chanted the spell with
his herbal tonics.]
[Today is his chance to relive that moment.]
Running Man time travel.
The second psychic power episode.
The last person left remaining through
the name tag elimination game wins the race.
You have the power to assign the power to
other members for being the star of the show.
[Assign specific powers to others for being
the star of this specific mission.]
Just give me all the powers.
I still may not win even with all the powers.
Who's the strongest player we have?
[Importance of distributing the powers...
What will Ha Ha do?]
Time controller, Lee Kwang Soo.
[Space controller- Jae Suk,
Death Note- Suk Jin.]
[Alter ego- Song Ji Hyo, Phoenix- Gary,
Master of sixth sense- Kim Jong Kook.]
As for the power of deflection...
I will take that for myself.
[Ha Ha takes the power of deflection
for himself.]
You've just ousted yourself.
[The power of deflection to oust the person
who eliminates your name tag.]
[The power that becomes more powerful
as the number of players narrows down.]
This will be my hidden ace card.
[Ha Ha is aware of everyone's power,
and also has the power of deflection.]
[Will he be able to rewrite history
and become the new star?]
[Phoenix has three lives, and
only one person has the ability to oust him.]
The one who controls time!
[Has the power to turn back time
only once during the race.]
[The power to oust any member,
at any given time, from any place.]
[The power to move all members to one
specific place only once during the race.]
[Has the power to sense what's about
to happen before crucial moments.]
[The power to create up to
four duplicates of herself.]
[The power to be aware of
all other members' specific powers.]
- You're the one with the Roll-Roll power?
- I have the Roll-Roll power.
Wow, seriously... Ji Hyo.
Jong Kook.
I told them so many times
that I don't need this power.
I've told them over and over
[The Wi-Fi brother is disappointed
with the same power he previously had.]
Song Ji Hyo is the duplicator?
[Song Ji Hyo is feeling confident
with all her Roll-Rolls.]
- Song Ji Hyo's the duplicator?
- Song Ji Hyo is the duplicator.
[All the psychic power holders are
starting to gather in one place.]
We all look the same.
- You're all so pretty.
- You girls are like a girl group.
- So cute.
- You're all so pretty!
- We are, Roll-Roll!
- They seriously are all so pretty.
[The rest of the Roll-Rolls are
pretty as Ji Hyo is herself.]
[An immediate fan club.]
Stay away.
You can't come near us.
Can I love all four of you?
I'm going to think of all four of you
as Song Ji Hyo today.
Then I'm a part of four
Monday Couples today.
Song Ji Hyo one, Song Ji Hyo two,
Song Ji Hyo three, Song Ji Hyo four.
Why are you holding her hand right now?
I'm a part of all these couples today.
- They're all so cute.
- There are so many of them.
But seriously, Ji Hyo.
You look like you're in a girl group.
[Another super power of Roll-Roll
is their level of beauty?]
- So we don't know each other's powers?
- No, we don't know.
But the person who took the pill would know
which power everyone else has, right?
Yes, that's right.
[Only Ha Ha, who took the pill
knows which powers the others now has.]
There's the power of deflection too, right?
[This is getting dangerous.
I have to divert their attention.]
Suk Jin!
I think Suk Jin is death note.
- Why do you say that?
- Because he's not here right now.
- Suk Jin isn't here.
- Maybe he's in hiding.
Let's go find Suk Jin first!
[Succeeds in diverting
their attention to Suk Jin.]
- Let's go!
- Roll Roll!
I love you, I love you, and I love you too!
They're so cute.
Wow, they're so cute.
I have to find it quickly.
Seriously...
[Death Note- Big nosed Brother.]
[Must find the death note first in order
to be able to use his power.]
I'll be done for if I don't find the card.
I'll be done for if I can't find it.
Suk Jin.
[Just as Ha Ha intended,
Suk Jin becomes everyone's first target.]
We have to find the death note first
and destroy it before Suk Jin finds it.
Use your Roll-Roll power and tell them to
separate and find the death note.
Maybe I can use my Wi-Fi power to
find out where the card is hidden.
- Use your power to find out where he is.
- My Wi-Fi?
[Kkuk uses his sixth sense to figure out
where Suk Jin is at the moment.]
- We have to find the death note.
- Do you know what the death note looks like?
Ji Suk Jin is on the fifth floor.
The Wi-Fi range has gotten broader.
- That's nice.
- It's now 3G.
[The sixth sense has been upgraded
to be more fitting of the time.]
Since Roll-Roll one knows what it looks like,
you can go start searching for it.
If you find the card, signal to me by
yelling out, 'Roll-Roll', okay?
- You too, okay?
- Kwang Soo, are you the Time Controller?
Are you?
[Bluntly asking him about his power.]
It's similar to that.
What do you mean, it's similar?
Are you the Time Controller?
Show me what you have.
[Searching his body for any telltale items.]
- It's not like I'm asking to have it.
- You can't do this.
So you really are the Time Controller.
What are you doing?
[Information on Giraffe's psychic power
is forced out of him.]
- You can control time.
- Which power do you have?
[You receive what you put out.]
Seeing how there's paper crinkling in there,
you must be the Space Controller.
- Where is he?
- Fifth floor.
[Big-nose still hasn't found
his death note.]
[Searching through every nook
and cranny of the building.]
[The death note is right behind him!]
I'm so worried that I'll get caught.
[One of the Roll-Roll's spots Big-nose!]
[Big-nose discovers the death note.]
I'm going to write it in right now.
[Ji Hyo moves in upon receiving
the tip from her Roll-Roll.]
Yoo Ja- Suk.
[This power... is a power that was wielded
by the original death note holder, Kwang Soo.]
[The names are written down with the
exception of one character of their names.]
[Then complete the writing of their name in
a moment of danger to oust them.]
[That's the power of the death note.]
Who are you going to use the death note for?
[Ji Hyo verifies that the death note is
in Suk Jin's hands with her own two eyes.]
I know who you're writing down.
Suk Jin, tell me who's name
you're going to write down.
[Ji Hyo can't be hasty about attacking him
with the death note in his hands.]
- Are you going to tell the others or not?
- I'm not sure if I will or not.
- I'm going to write down your name.
- Okay, go ahead and write it.
The time will get turned back anyway.
It's all over.
[Preparations to oust
the members are complete.]
[Who dares to call me a weakling?]
Who knew that I could ever
feel this much at ease?
Who knew that I'd ever feel
this much at ease?
[I'm not afraid of anyone.]
Phoenix should just sacrifice his power.
I'm going to write down the name of the person
who offends me the most and leave the game.
[Danger is imminent!]
I'm going to complete writing down the name
of the person who steps any closer to me.
Then I can be ousted from the game.
[All the members are now
gathered in one place.]
- Suk Jin has the death note?
- No one better step any closer to me.
[Big-nose's death note is proving to be
much more lethal than Ha Ha had imagined.]
- You're name is Kang G-ry right now.
- Who's the phoenix?
Would you be announcing it
if it were you?
- This is so frustrating.
- One of you guys is the phoenix.
- Me?
One of you is the phoenix,
and the other is the deflector.
If I'm the phoenix,
then you can eliminate me right now.
You can eliminate the deflector.
- Why would I?
- You took the pill, didn't you?
- Why would I tell you what my power is?
- What are you going to do about it if I did?
- You took the pill, didn't you?
- What are you going to do about it?
- Rip it off!
Rip off his name tag right now.
- He's the phoenix, so rip off his name tag.
- What if he's the deflector?
- I'm telling you that he's the phoenix!
- I haven't even used my power yet.
I really want to use my power!
Get Gary.
[Gary is the phoenix!]
Gary?
[Target locked.]
[Gary's name tag is eliminated.]
[Gary's power is revealed!]
- So you took the pill, didn't you?
- I really didn't take the pill.
It really wasn't me!
- I didn't take the pill.
- Then Ha Ha is the deflector.
I really didn't take the pill.
Ha Ha is the deflector.
[This psychic battle is being carried out
completely different than the past battle.]
[Who will be the ultimate victor
of this new battle?]
We have to convince Gary to
rip off Ha Ha's name tag.
I know where Gary is right now.
Don't forget the power that I have, you guys.
[Jong Kook's sixth sense kicks in again.]
I'll find out where Gary is.
If Suk Jin uses his death note on Ha Ha,
then we can oust him by ripping off the name.
- We can just do an ambush attack on Suk Jin.
- Gary is on the third floor.
Gary is on the third floor.
Let's go up there right now.
Let's go meet up with Gary,
and I'll talk him into doing it.
- Who should I oust?
- Oust Kim Jong Kook.
- Why do you want me to do it right now?
- Just write it down right now.
- Stop hesitating and do it right now.
- Seriously.
[Even though he's the death note holder,
elimination of his name means that he's out.]
Okay, fine.
I'll write Jae Suk down and be eliminated.
Write it, write it.
I was holding onto it.
[Almost got eliminated before he even
got to write down anyone's name.]
- You're seriously angering me.
- Hurry up and write it down.
Hurry up and write it.
You're almost there.
Write down Kim Jong Kook's name.
We need to oust Dong Hoon first.
[Kkuk, Blank Ji, Gary and Kwang Soo
are now working together.]
- We need to find Dong Hoon.
- There he is right now.
Here he comes.
Hurry up and write it down.
Here he comes right now.
[Big-nose is still hesitating about his
decision up to the very last minute.]
Here he comes right now.
Hurry up and write it.
[The fate of Kkuk's life is left in
the hands of Big-nosed Brother.]
It's over for Kim Jong Kook now.
[Just one more swipe of the pen...
and Jong Kook will be ousted.]
Kim Jong Kook, out.
[Jong Kook was the first one to get ousted
the first time around from Kwang Soo's note.]
[The power of the death note
just made history repeat itself.]
[Goodbye, Sixth Sense.]
[Impala is eliminated immediately
after having used up his death note power.]
[Dragged off to jail after doing a
good deed for the other members.]
[Ha Ha's power of deflection is activated!]
[The person who tries to oust the deflector
is immediately ousted himself!]
Yoo Jae Suk, out.
I got your number now.
[Without even having used his power...
the Space Controller is eliminated!]
I told you that he's the deflector.
- Come on, what are you waiting for?
- Are you trying to eliminate me?
[Gary is the new target!]
[Just as Ha Ha had intended,
everyone is now targeting Gary.]
Roll-Roll!
[Gary has the distinct advantage
for being the only one with two name tags.]
We won't be able to oust Gary otherwise.
[This is their one and only chance
to oust Gary!]
Grab onto the name tag now.
Grab onto the name tag.
Yeah, I got it.
[Gary's defensive moves.]
[A fierce battle of six against one.]
[One of Gary's name tags are eliminated.]
[Second name tag is also eliminated.]
[Gary and Ha Ha both are almost
simultaneously ousted.]
[Ji Hyo and Roll-Roll immediately
turn their attack on Kwang Soo.]
[I must... turn back the hands of time.]
[Just need to pull out the watch and
recite the spell.]
No!
[The Roll-Rolls locks up both of
Kwang Soo's arms in a tight vise-like grip.]
Please let me go!
Let me go just this once!
[Please let me turn back the hands of time
just this once!]
I got it!
[Time Controller, Lee Kwang Soo- Out!]
[Sharing this joy with her Roll-Roll's.]
- I told you that Roll Roll is the best.
- Roll Roll definitely is the best!
[The ultimate winner of the time travel race-
Song Ji Hyo!]
[The key to Ji Hyo's win- Roll Roll.]
- Roll Roll is the best.
- Roll Roll is definitely the best.
Can you make a double for me too?
Someone who's 190cm tall?
I don't think they're going to find
anyone as tall as you are.
[The power of Roll-Roll is as powerful
as the strength of their beauty.]
- Who took the pill?
- I took it!
I knew that it was you.
That's why I ripped off your name.
[Bickering to the end.]
Thus, the winner of today is,
Song Ji Hyo and Roll-Roll!
[The ultimate victor of the race-
Song Ji Hyo and her Roll-Rolls!]
Roll-Roll!
Subtitles by DramaFever