Subtitles by DramaFever
['Chi' Theme park in Samchuk.]
[A train comes down the tracks
as if a piece of the past.]
[The train's destination is...]
[A fog covered station
at the foot of the hills.]
- What a scenic view.
- Such grandeur.
- Pretty as a picture.
- What is that? Is that a train?
There's a working train?
- It's a real working train.
- Wow, that's so awesome.
[Everyone's impressed by the sight
of the antique looking train.]
I think there's someone on the train.
[Could today's guests be on the train?]
- The train is stopping to let someone out.
- Is it our guest?
[Guests who are as elegant
as the train itself.]
[A woman whose beauty can be seen
even from her faint silhouette.]
- I see someone!
- There they are.
- Who is it?
- She's really pretty with beautiful eyes!
She has really big eyes.
[The train comes to a stop.]
[A man is seen getting off the train.]
[A man who turns the train platform
into a red carpeted runway.]
[An actor of perfection, Jung Gyu Woon.]
[The perfect model pose.]
- Wow, he's so handsome.
- Hello!
[Friendly greetings on the platform.]
- Hello.
- You didn't come alone, did you?
- I see a woman.
- Who is it?
It's a woman.
[Someone whom Kwang Soo
recognizes at a single glance.]
- It's Wang Ji Hye!
[The definition of elegance,
Wang Ji Hye.]
- Wow, she's so beautiful.
- She's a good friend of mine!
Wang Ji Hye's wearing a
revealing dress!
- What are you doing?
- She made a fist at him.
[Inner toughness cloaked behind
an exterior of elegance.]
- Her face is so tiny!
- How do you and Kwang Soo know each other?
- We're not really that close.
- What? You know we're good friends!
[Stay tuned for her antics with
her buddy, the Giraffe.]
Someone else is getting off the train!
There he is!
It's Sang Jin!
[Variety world's late blooming
gentleman, Han Sang Jin.]
[This one's Ji Hyo's good buddy- Friends
ever since filming a movie together.]
- Wow, he looks so handsome.
- Hello.
- I'm a big fan of your wife.
- This is for Jin Hye.
- Stop being like that!
- I just didn't want her to be cold.
It's because she's cold!
I just don't want her to be cold.
Kwang Soo's doing it!
[Having lost their chance to Kwang Soo
from all their bickering.]
Kwang Soo did it.
Who is it?
[Who does that familiar laughter
belong to?]
It's Sang Wook!
[The undeniably good looking actor,
Joo Sang Wook.]
- It's so great to see you!
- Everyone seem so happy to see one another.
[Multiple appearances on Running Man-
Already good friends with the members.]
He always comes on during the
post season.
[Always makes an appearance
during the annual fall baseball episodes.]
It's so great to see you!
[Just then...]
[The birth of a beauty-
Enough to shock all the members.]
[Is this a dream?
Or a reality?]
- It's Han Ye Seul!
Seriously?
- Wow, look at her!
- It's Han Ye Seul!
- Seriously?
- It really is Han Ye Seul.
[The return of the goddess,
Han Ye Seul.]
[Most excited they've been in all of 2014.]
[It really is Han Ye Seul!]
[An overwhelming welcome.]
Gary's already in love.
[She's really pretty.]
[Han Ye Seul's return to the variety world
after seven years of absence.]
- She's such a huge star!
- She's so beautiful.
[Takes his coat off Ji Hye to put
it around the goddess' shoulders.]
- What are you doing?
- She looked like she was cold.
[What a piece of work.]
Sorry to say this, but
why don't you stand with us?
[The actress is taking the sole spotlight?]
I thought you wanted me to
stand there. I'm sorry.
Sang Wook's looking smaller than usual.
[Sudden act of masculinity
in front of Ye Seul.]
What are you doing?
Please welcome the five stars of the
new upcoming drama, Birth of a Beauty.
[Team Birth of a Beauty.]
[The new weekend drama,
Birth of a Beauty.]
[Stay tuned for the fantastic
chemistry between these five.]
I want to show off my dress.
Thank you, Kwang Soo.
[I'm so glad I gave her my coat!]
Why are you trying to
cover up her beautiful dress?
- They took care to dress for the show.
- Knock it off!
Why are you acting like such
a brat today?
[This air of excitement is the
effect Ye Seul has on the members.]
I'm in such a great mood
right now.
Today's race is the
White Knight vs Black Knight Race.
I will announce the two teams
before we start the mission.
The Red Team is Han Ye Seul, Han Sang Jin,
Yoo Jae Suk, Ha Ha, and Lee Kwang Soo.
The remaining members will
make up the other team.
The Blue Team is Sang Wook, Gyu Woon,
Ji Hye, Jong Kook, Suk Jin, Gary and Ji Hyo.
[Blue Team- Sang Wook, Gyu Woon, Ji Hye,
Suk Jin, Jong Kook, Gary and Ji Hyo.]
I need each of you to come up and choose
a card from the table in front of you.
[They cannot share the identity of
their card with anyone else.]
[Members of both teams complete
making their card selection.]
- Have you checked your cards?
- Yes.
The cards showed a picture of either
a white knight or a black knight.
[The cards contained a picture of
either a black or a white knight.]
Of the twelve cards, there were five
white knights and seven black knights.
But the numbers of each of those knights
are divided up between the two teams.
They're all mixed between the two teams.
- Then one of us could be a black knight?
- Yes, that's correct.
There could be some black knights
on White Knight Team as well.
- I'm not sure what mine is.
- Don't act like that.
Han Ye Seul is the white knight's queen.
The representative of the team
that wins the mission
will get to find out how many black and
white knights there are on their team
and they'll get the chance to swap out one of
their team members with an opposing member.
The goal of your mission is this.
There will be a total of five exchanges
made throughout the race today.
If everyone on the White Knight Team
ends up being white knights in the end
then her team wins the race.
Those with the black knight
card in their hand
must try to stand with the White Knight Team
at the end to deter them from winning.
- That's how Team Black Knight can win.
- Okay, let's win this race!
Go away.
- Can I get an umbrella?
- I think he's a black knight.
[Only they know whether
they're a black or white knight.]
[Will Ye Seul be able to gather all
of her five white knights together?]
How are we going to differentiate the
white knights from the black knights?
Sang Wook, if you're a black knight,
then just get away from us.
- Black knight?
- Then are you a white knight?
- Are you a white knight?
- I'm just walking right now.
- Fold up your umbrella.
- Fold up your umbrella, Sang Wook.
[Flustered Actor Joo?]
There has to be at least one
white knight on our team, right?
[The Blue Team is also trying to
determine who each of them are.]
- Are you white or black?
- She looks like a white knight.
Can't you just tell by her porcelain skin
that she's a white knight?
- You do have very porcelain skin.
- I don't trust actors.
[Will they be able to tell the white
knights apart from the black knights?]
Wow, you really are so pretty.
How can you be that pretty?
Ye Seul, isn't this practically your
first time on a variety show?
- I think it's been seven years.
- Seven years?
[First variety show
appearance in seven years.]
I don't think I've ever done
a show with Ye Seul before.
Then why are you talking
so casually with her?
She's like a sister to me!
- It's nice to meet you.
- What the heck!
[Or someone whom he wants to
be as close as a brother to.]
- What's wrong with you these days?
- Did you just see what Ye Seul did?
[Pretending to hit Jae Suk?]
[But Ye Seul did this to me earlier.]
Ye Seul is the best!
I brought a hot heating pack.
- She uses casual speech with everyone.
- Really?
See?
She's the casual speaking type, too!
- I love people like that.
- Ye Seul, let's just talk comfortably.
- Ye Seul, let's speak in casually.
- Okay!
[Let's all become good friends
with one another.]
- I didn't know Ye Seul was like this.
- She's so laid back.
- Ye Seul.
- What?
[Nothing but laughter with Ye Seul around.]
- Did you get to chat on the way?
- We talked the whole way here.
- We're on casual terms with Ye Seul already.
- We're good friends already.
- Sang Jin also told us...
- She lowers her speech with everyone.
Director, did you already eat?
[Wow, what a feeling...]
[The birth of Running Man's cutie.]
The Director's face has turned beet red.
[Time for Ji Hye to give it a try?]
Did ya eat?
- 'Did ya eat!'
- That's so cute, don't you know!
[Short and sweet country
dialect greeting.]
In keeping up with the theme of this park,
your first mission is train related.
Everyone will start to dance until
the sound of the horn is heard.
- Then we have to get on the train?
- Sit in this thing?
Two people per train are allowed, but
your butts have to be touching the seat.
It's possible that you could fit
even more per seat.
Only those who are seated will be passed
through to the snack tent over there.
[Find a seat and win the chance to enjoy
a hearty snack under the tent.]
I love dancing outside in the rain.
[Dancing fool, Yoo Hyuk, is excited at
the chance to dance with Ye Seul.]
If I were a black knight and I worked
really hard to win at these missions
then I'd have the chance to
swap out whomever I wanted, right?
Then can I swap myself out
knowing that I'm a black knight?
- What do you mean by that?
- If I were to be a black knight.
He must be a black knight.
[Everyone's convinced
that Kkuk is a black knight.]
[Could Kkuk really be a black knight?]
Isn't this game to
the black knight's advantage?
Even though we're teamed up this way,
there may be many white knights on our team.
Which means that Ha Ha could also be
a black knight. That remains a secret.
- Are you a black knight?
- Are you really a black knight?
No, I'm not! Ye Seul,
you have to believe me!
This is so unfair!
I won't stand for it.
- I'll believe you.
- You know what'll happen?
People who talk like you
are the real black knights.
[Could Yoo Hyuk be a black knight?]
Not saying anything is the
best thing to do.
- You're being suspicious.
- I don't trust you.
- How am I acting suspicious?
- Because you look like this right now.
[The look of betrayal on
Kwang Soo's face?]
- Since there are women...
- Then I'll play it rough.
- Really rough.
- Let's do this!
[Do they not go easy
on their guests on this show?]
I've mentioned something to
the writers in the past
about always playing such old
songs like songs from Turbo...
- What? Songs from Turbo?
- Those old songs...
[Getting a rise out of
the Twist King of the past.]
I want to see Ji Hye's
dance moves.
- Wang Ji Hye even does tumbling moves.
- Seriously?
[Country girl's tumbling moves?]
Wang Ji Hye!
What's tumbling?
[Ji Hye's slapstick comedy moves.]
[Always doing what's asked of her-
Birth of the new variety beauty, Ji Hye.]
[Board the train game- Start.]
[Party starters, Ha Ha and Gary.]
[Ye Seul is slowly getting
into the groove.]
[We're singers by day!]
[Shall we dance, Ye Seul?]
[Matching the theme of the dance-
Ye Seul and Ha Ha.]
[This beauty knows how to party!]
[Actor Joo is getting into it.]
[Wang Ji Hye, come on!]
[Han Sang Jin is on the move!]
[That's Yoo Hyuk's grasshopper dance!]
[Next up- Jung Gyu Woon.]
[Fancy footwork.]
[Jung Gyu Woon's retro dance moves.]
[Everybody say, Han Ye Seul!]
[Han Ye Seul, let's go!]
[Ye Seul's got the moves.]
[A fun dance party in the rain.]
[Let's go board the train!]
[Only those sitting on the seat when
the horn sounds, pass the round!]
[First ones in the left seat-
Han Ye Seul and Ji Suk Jin.]
No!
Go away!
[I'm not getting out of my seat!]
[Nine members' train battle.]
[Big-nose is forcibly
removed from his seat.]
[Chaos over the left seat.]
[On the other hand,
Ace and Kkuk's right seat...]
[Totally peaceful on
the icy side of the train.]
They're not even attempting
to come on our side.
[The left side is bursting with people.]
[Train boarding game-
End of the first round.]
[Everyone on the left side is disqualified,
and Ji Hyo and Jong Kook passes.]
- Why didn't anyone come over to us?
- You just want me out of the game.
- They're all trying to send me out.
- Just send him out of the game.
Only Kim Jong Kook and Song Ji Hyo
of the Blue Team pass.
Why didn't anyone even come over to us?
We were waiting for people to come.
- You can't succeed!
- You can't leave us!
- I didn't want to pass.
- We can officially get started now!
We're at a disadvantage
all of a sudden.
It's more advantageous for us to
send Jong Kook out first.
- We can officially get started now.
- That was no fun at all.
- Let's start over.
- No, you already passed.
- But that wasn't any fun at all.
- Having you in the game is even less fun.
[The battlefield is a cruel place to be.]
- That's not right.
- No, that's not right.
[Not wanting to step off the platform.]
- Start the music!
- Let's start the next round!
Dancing in the rain is...
[Sang Jin's pre-game slapstick humor.]
What's Sang Jin's deal?
We should be over there helping.
- My butt's all wet.
- You're a white knight, aren't you?
No, I'm a black knight.
- I know you're a white knight.
- No, I'm a black knight.
- You totally look like a white knight.
You said something earlier
that you shouldn't have said.
'We should be over there helping.'
Why else would you have said that?
You need to be there to help our
other teammates pass.
[We can talk later.
It's time to dance!]
- Grab onto each other's shoulders.
- Let's go!
Grab onto my shoulders.
[Time for a train ride!]
[Yoo Hyuk whips his wet hair around.]
[Shake it!]
[This rain isn't going to stop
our dancing fever.]
Ugh, what the heck?
[Couple of uninvited guests
on the train ride.]
I feel so dizzy!
- I feel so dizzy!
- This is great!
Wang Ji Hye, take off your hat!
Let's enjoy the party!
[Giraffe!]
[Just have fun today, my friend.]
[Let's take off Ye Seul's hat, too!]
[Just enjoy the rain, Ye Seul.]
[Both Ji Hye and Ye Seul are onboard.]
[The two rivals,
Ye Seul and Big-nose, meet again.]
[Actor Joo onboard.]
[Sang Jin's thrown off to the side.]
I need to get onboard!
[Kwang Soo's interference is deterred.]
[Big-nose shows strong desire
to board the train.]
[Ten seconds left on the clock.]
[I'm getting on this train!]
We have to get him out.
[Get out here, Wang Ji Hye.]
[Joo Sang Wook and Wang Ji Hye
are onboard.]
[Han Ye Seul- Onboard.
Ji Suk Jin- Fails.]
He doesn't count, right?
Only Han Ye Seul, Joo Sang Wook,
and Wang Ji Hye pass.
[Round Two- Han Ye Seul,
Joo Sang Wook, Wang Ji Hye.]
Ye Seul, you really look
sexy right now.
[Her wet hair is appealing
to all the males.]
Thank you.
[Befuddled]
- Is this how it normally is?
- This is how it normally is.
It's okay.
- Ji Hye's been hurt!
- What happened, Ji Hye?
- I thought my legs were being ripped off.
- I was doing it the other way.
- Ugh, seriously!
- Ji Hye's hurt.
- Ji Hye, are you okay?
- This is my first variety experience.
- No, I'm not okay.
- Why are you asking her that now?
- Are you okay?
- Ye Seul, are you okay?
- Wang Ji Hye, are you okay?
Wang Ji Hye, tell me that
you're okay!
[A rough initiation into the variety world.]
- Come here, Ji Hye.
- Okay.
- Did Ji Hye pass?
- There are only three of us left?
- You look so ugly right now.
- Should I put my hat back on?
Should I put my hat back on?
Is that better?
[Take a look in the mirror, Kwang Soo.]
[Perfectly in sync-
New variety duo- Giraffe and Ji Hye.]
[Meanwhile, in the snack tent...]
Five guests came on the show
today, right?
Since there are five guests,
the five guests are the white knights.
But I don't think they would've
grouped the guests together like that.
Because Ji Hyo...
I know that you're a white knight.
- No, I'm not!
- I know you are.
You're seriously so annoying!
No, I'm not!
- You're definitely a white knight.
- I'm a white knight.
- Jong Kook has to be white.
- I'm white.
I know he's white and he's just trying
to thwart the suspicion off of him.
[The debate over the identity of
the black and white knight continues on.]
[Gary passes the third round of the game.]
[Let's get into the groove!]
[Proposes belly butt pumping dance moves.]
[Sounds good!]
[Round four of the train game- Start.]
One, two, three, four!
[This is a real man's dance!]
[Giraffe's enthusiastic bounce.]
Stop it, that's enough!
[Addicting bounce moves.]
[Yoo Hyuk and Giraffe are in the midst
of formulating a plan.]
Move up to the front!
You have to move up!
[Yoo Hyuk marks Big-nose
as his target.]
[Even in the midst of all that,
'Yeah baby!']
[The Red Team's goal-
Stop Big-nose from boarding the train.]
[Big-nose can go to the back.]
[Or just lay down and get some rest.]
[Sang Jin takes another clumsy fall.]
[Red Team's plan-
Let Gyu Woon board the train first.]
[Yoo Hyuk isn't strong enough
to make it happen on his own.]
[Three men lift Gyu Woon up
to force him on the train.]
[The man's heated refusal.]
Oh no!
[Big-nose is held captive,
and Gyu Woon is forced.]
[Jung Gyu Woon is forced
aboard the train.]
[I can't let it end this way...]
Gyu Woon, you have to get out of there.
Hurry!
[Train game- Round four.
Jung Gyu Woon is forcibly passed.]
[If the strong Gyu Woon is
also out of the game, then...]
Congratulation to the Blue Team for
taking such a huge lead in the game.
What did you say?
- Did you say that we're now in the lead?
- Fighting, Suk Jin!
- You can do this!
- We're at a disadvantage, but we'll try.
We won't know until we try.
- White knights!
- Yes, that's me!
- Ye Seul, can you cheer us on?
- Cheer us on, Ye Seul.
- Stay strong!
- Say it in casual speech!
Ye Seul, say it in casual speech.
Stay strong.
[Enough to make us melt.]
[I can do this!]
I believe in you!
[Give me the strength!]
Wang Ji Hye!
Give me a cheer!
Suk Jin, think of your health,
and don't push yourself too hard!
- 'Think of your health!'
- Was that even a cheer?
Don't push yourself too hard!
You'll have other chances.
- What kind of a cheer is that?
- She says he'll have other chances.
[Two very different charms. Funny
beauty, Ji Hye and Cutie pie, Ye Seul.]
[Winners of the fifth round-
Yoo Jae Suk and Ha Ha.]
- Let's throw him off.
- Sang Jin, you're looking really pale.
[The perfect pale skin of
a white knight.]
- Get him a piece of chocolate.
- My hands are freezing.
[Piece of chocolate for
a little spurt of energy.]
[Train game- Round six.]
It's Song Ji Hyo's song!
It's Ji Hyo's song!
[Blank Ji on the move!]
Back in the day, we couldn't even
force Ji Hyo to go out there.
Why are you running out here?
What's wrong with you?
[Blank Ji- Let's go!]
Wow, you're so shameless.
Go!
From the top of my head to
the tips of my toes, I'm a hot issue!
[Pale-faced Sang Jin on the
other hand...]
That's the only long standing
dance move she has.
[Moving over to Sang Jin-
A sudden couple dance time.]
- Do you know what you're doing?
- No!
[Everyone's following Blank Ji's moves.]
[Blue Team's Suk Jin vs
Red Team's Sang Jin and Kwang Soo.]
[Knocks him down to the ground.]
- Sang Jin!
- Let go of him.
Kwang Soo, just get on the train.
Sang Jin!
- Just get onboard, Kwang Soo.
- Are you sure?
[Why isn't he able to throw Suk Jin off?]
- Sang Jin's acting weird.
- I agree, he is acting weird.
- He's acting really weird.
- Three, two, one!
[Round six of the train game-
Lee Kwang Soo passes.]
- Sang Jin's much weaker than he looks.
- This game is never ending!
- This game is never ending.
- He's really strong.
- What are you talking about?
- No, he really is strong.
[He really is acting very suspicious...]
Everyone in the world knows
how weak Suk Jin is.
No, he really is very strong.
[Could this be because
Sang Jin is a black knight?]
Since it's now down to the two of you,
first one aboard the train wins the round.
Sang Jin!
If you don't make it this time, then
I'll know that you're a black knight.
[You can trust me.]
Ji Hye, give me a cheer.
Your health is what's most important.
[I shouldn't have asked...]
He's really worrying me.
[A neck to neck competition-
A battle amidst the fog...]
[Time for a little warm up.]
[Middle aged men's dance battle.]
[But in their hearts, they're
still hot and fiery young men.]
[Final train dance with the whole group.]
You two look like you're not even
interested in the game anymore.
[Fiercely competitive Jin-Jin couple.]
[I vow to win this round!]
[I can't let you beat me!]
[Who will be the winner of this final round?]
[Sang Jin is first to board the train.]
[Han Sang Jin wins the final round.]
You were already in front of me
when they blew the horn.
Thus, the Red Team wins the first game.
[Red Team wins the Board the Train game.]
[Teammate swap is still left to do.]
Only the Queen will be notified of
how many black knights are on the team
and how many white knights
she has on her team.
You must deliberate very carefully and
choose which member you'd like to swap out.
[Ye Seul must choose one member of the Blue
Team whom she thinks is a white knight.]
[Time to check how many black and white
knights she currently has on the team.]
The number of white knights
you currently have on the team...
including yourself is...
Including yourself is... three.
[Total of three white knights
on the team.]
There are a total of three white knights
on your team including yourself
and the other two are black knights.
[Only three of the current
five members are white knights.]
[Members who chose the
white knight cards...]
[Just who could they be?]
Were you shocked by the results?
You have to be smart about this, Ye Seul.
[Have to bring the white knights
over from the Blue Team.]
[And kick the black knights
off the team.]
[Just who will Ye Seul choose?]
- Hey, Ye Seul.
- Stop it!
- Seriously.
- He would've been more helpful.
[The black knight is right over here.]
Wow, these guys are awful.
- They're so hateful.
- Who are we going to bring over?
Raise your hand if you weren't sure
who had which card when we first chose it.
- Anyone who felt confused.
- I was a bit confused.
- I was confused.
- You weren't sure who had which?
Why are you asking this question when
every one of us is confused about it.
Isn't there a higher chance that you're
a white knight if you felt confused by it?
Ye Seul's speech pattern
starts off at a higher octave.
- Happier she gets, higher her pitch becomes.
- She's like a soprano singer.
- Seriously.
- Jong Kook's songs would be a good pitch.
My songs would be the
perfect pitch for her.
[Even Actor Joo is getting
a laugh out of this one.]
I really like Ye Seul.
For this first round, I'm going to swap out
two people who gave the best argument.
[Trade off two people
who gave the best argument?]
[Who will Ye Seul choose?]
Good job, Ye Seul.
Red Team's Ha Ha for
Blue Team's Kim Jong Kook.
[Ha Ha for Kim Jong Kook.]
[Queen's selection-
Ha Ha for Jong Kook.]
[Did Ye Seul succeed in trading out a
black knight for a white knight?]
[Off to the second game location.]
Ye Seul, how many white knights
did he tell you are on the team?
- There aren't very many white knights.
- Right?
Didn't I tell you that there were only two?
That was surprising, wasn't it?
I told you that there were
only two, didn't I?
I'm sure that must've been
very surprising to hear.
- Look, there are mics.
- There are ten mics.
Is this where you want us?
- It must be a quiz battle.
- Be quiet, he's about to tell us.
Your second mission is,
Black and White Competition.
[Black and White Competition.]
We have prepared a variety of games
and once we reveal the game, you
must choose one member from the team
to step forward to play the game.
All the members from the losing team
must come stand in front of the wind mic
and will be blown with a shot of air
if their representative loses.
- This could be disadvantageous for us.
- You're right.
I've heard from good sources that
Wang Ji Hye used to be quite the partier.
I also heard from someone else
that if someone confesses their feelings for
Ji Hye in the winter, she always accepts.
[Buddy Kwang Soo's ambush attack.]
She always accepts love confessions
if they're made in the winter?
There's not much time left
until the end of the year.
Ugh, he's driving me crazy.
- Is her temper starting to flare up?
- I like this.
- I know one of Kwang Soo's secrets, too.
- What is it?
- Should I tell them?
- Sorry, I won't do it again.
- What is it?
- No, tell us!
I know one of your secrets, too.
- What is it? Tell us.
- Why are you getting so nervous?
[Stay tuned.]
[A battle of revelation is
headed your way.]
[These two best friends seem to know
all there is to know about each other.]
First category is- Butt wrestling.
The first person to push the opponent off
with their butt and pick up the radish
on the ground wins the game.
- Who should go first? Me?
- Yeah, you go first.
I'll go first.
I'll take the first round.
[Jae Suk for the Red Team.]
[Gyu Woon for the Blue Team.]
[A formidable opponent from
the start.]
The loser team will get the shot of air
before sending out the next player.
We're at a disadvantage for having
a lesser number of players.
- Gyu Woon's a strong player.
- Don't be nervous!
[An enthusiastic cheer from
the two teams.]
You're known for your butt moves!
- Ready!
- Shove him with your butt!
[Butt Wrestling- Round one.
Jae Suk vs Gyu Woon.]
[Abnormal activity of his sphincter
from extreme state of anxiety.]
- You know, right!
- I totally know!
[Know what?]
[Yes, we know.]
You know what it is, right?
I totally know what it is.
- I know what you're feeling.
- You know what I'm feeling?
[Energy from all his concentration is
flowing down to that part of his body.]
- We all know what you're feeling.
- Get ready.
Set...
- Grab it!
- Put it over your head!
Put it over your head!
You did it!
[Startled by the shot of air.]
[So close...]
He tumbled around on the ground.
[Butt wrestling-
Red Team: 1 vs Blue Team: 0.]
- That was fun.
- Okay, send out the next player.
Wang Ji Hye!
[Jae Suk chooses Ji Hye
as his next opponent.]
We have fewer players on our team,
so we have to win this round.
[Selected a female opponent to
give his team an upper hand.]
- Ji Hye has some skills.
- Eyes forward and get ready.
[Butt Wrestling- Round Two.
Jae Suk vs Ji Hye.]
[Jae Suk makes the initial attack, but...]
[Ji Hye uses the force
to make her counterattack.]
[Ji Hye's plan succeeds!]
[Bravo, Wang Ji Hye!]
How did she do that?
- How did you do that?
- She did it after him.
What were you doing?
[Timed her attack to use
Jae Suk's strength.]
Pick Jong Kook.
- He's weak when it comes to women.
- Then... I choose Jong Kook.
- Why are you choosing me?
- I've always been a fan of yours.
- Why are you telling me that?
- She's lying!
[Signs herself up as his fan club member
in order to win the game.]
- That's a lie.
- What am I going to do?
Jong Kook, just smack her
and send her flying off in the air.
[Butt Wrestling- Round Three.
Jong Kook vs Ji Hye.]
- Ji Hye, you can do this.
- I can only use my butt, right?
[Then what else would you use
to push him off?]
You weren't thinking of this,
were you?
- Not this, right?
- Please don't do that.
- Wang Ji Hye's no joke.
- Wow, how did she beat Jae Suk?
- Was it on purpose?
- No, I swear it wasn't.
- Did you lose on purpose?
- What are you talking about?
- You're acting suspicious.
- Did you lose on purpose?
[A black knight's scheme to
destroy the queen's plans?]
- No, I doubt that.
- It's possible if you're a black knight.
Let's keep an eye on him, Ye Seul.
- You can only use your butts.
- Okay.
No, wait.
[Losing gets you suspected of being a
black knight, so must win the game.]
What's wrong?
Seriously? I didn't push very hard.
- Yes, that's the way to do it!
- I'm sorry.
[Butt Wrestling-
Red Team: 2 vs Blue Team: 1.]
We would've lost all the rounds if Ye Seul
hadn't traded Ha Ha for Jong Kook.
[Blue Team's next player-
Sang Wook.]
How should I do this?
Make it quick and make
Sang Wook get some rest.
- Ready.
- Wait.
[Butt Wrestling-
Red Team: 3 vs Blue Team: 1.]
What the heck?
The Red Team wins the first game.
[Red Team wins the first game of
Butt Wrestling.]
Jong Kook really must be a
white knight.
- Of course, I am.
- I think so too.
If Ye Seul gets to make another trade,
it would've been obvious
but seeing how hard Jong Kook's working,
I really do think he's a white knight.
Yes, he's working very hard.
But a black knight could
work just as hard.
- Yes, to remain on the team.
- That's right.
[Black knight or a white knight?
Just which of the two could Jong Kook be?]
Here's your next category.
It's Corn Kernel Odd or Even.
Guess whether the number of corn kernels
the opponent has is odd or even.
Guess correctly to win the round.
Choose a member from each team.
- Wang Ji Hye!
- They're at it again.
I noticed that you're a
real dirty player.
- Kwang Soo, go face off with your friend.
- Should I go?
- Go play off with your friend.
- Send Wang Ji Hye out of the game.
[Lee Kwang Soo for the Red Team.]
[They're finally getting to face off.]
[Come on, my friend.]
Should we play a round of
'Of Course' first?
- What are you talking about?
- That sounds like fun.
- Why do you want to play that?
- That sounds like real fun.
[Everyone else except for the actual
players seem excited by the idea.]
- That sounds like fun.
- Let's have a go.
It's been a while since we've played.
So it's Wang Ji Hye vs Lee Kwang Soo.
- Doesn't it sound fun!
- That sounds fun!
- Okay, a round of 'Of Course.'
- So many things I'm curious about.
You just reply 'Of Course' to
everything. Okay?
Yes, I understand.
- I'm not familiar with this game.
- Just answer 'Of Course' to everything.
If you don't, then you lose.
Are you both ready?
- Would you like to go first?
- Is this how we'll decide who goes first?
What? Yes, this is how
we'll decide who goes first.
Yes, are you both ready?
We'll start with Kwang Soo.
Set, go.
Don't do it.
Please don't do it.
- By any chance...
- Don't do it.
You've dated a celebrity before,
haven't you?
- One, two, three.
- That wasn't a bad question.
Of course.
[Seriously?]
Ji Hye's angry right now.
Ji Hye's getting angry.
This isn't how you play it!
You can't start off so strong!
You have to start off lightly.
[Is that... how you play it?]
Ji Hye's turn.
Look at the expression on her face.
- You can ask him the same question.
- You've dated a celebrity before, right?
- What did she say?
- I doubt he has.
- Can't hear you. What did you say?
[Same question, different weight.
Could be a knockout question.]
Pull yourself together, Kwang Soo.
- Of course!
- There you go. Next question.
- Ask her something strong.
- While filming...
have you ever felt attracted to any
of the actors that you've worked with?
- If she's ever felt attracted or not?
- Have you ever felt attracted to a co-star?
Can I just say 'Of course'
to win the game?
- Sure, that's fine.
- Yes, just think of it like that.
- Of course.
- Good.
You've had a co-star go from being
a 'sister' to a 'honey', haven't you?
[You've had a co-star go from being
a 'sister' to a 'honey', haven't you?]
From a 'sister' to a 'honey'?
[She's... tough.]
Hey!
I haven't played many roles
where I had a sister!
She's going too far.
[Giraffe explodes.]
[Kwang Soo's knocked down,
and Wang Ji Hye wins.]
[The power of being best friends-
Knocks him out with two simple blows.]
Wang Ji Hye's good.
Okay, Ji Hye can choose.
[Kwang Soo must correctly guess whether
the number of kernels are odd or even.]
I don't know how I'm ever going to
watch you on dramas anymore.
Wow, she really is different.
I'll never be able to
take her seriously again.
Odd!
I sincerely want you to win.
What is that all about?
She's giving him a chance
to change his mind.
I've never seen anything like this.
Just how many games are
they showing us?
They're so entertaining to watch.
You said odd, and she just told you
that she wants you to win.
- Change your answer.
- It's a mental game.
[Can I really trust you?]
[Don't you trust me, my friend?]
[I trust you.]
Even!
- What is it?
- Three.
[Three - Odd.]
[You, come here!]
[Don't try to stop me!]
[This beauty's never before seen
4D personality.]
[Wang Ji Hye single handedly wins
the second game of Odd-Even.]
Wang Ji Hye totally fooled us.
[This is just the beginning.]
Here's your next game.
- Your next game is...
- Yes?
- It's the Hand slap Game.
- Ah, this?
You've all probably played
the game when you were younger.
- Should I go? I'll go.
- Kwang Soo has big hands.
[Kwang Soo for the Red Team.]
He's pretty slow though.
[Ha Ha for the Blue Team.]
- Okay.
- You have to do the attack.
[Being on the attack is more
advantageous in the hand slapping game.]
[Ha Ha on the attack.]
- You have to keep it on the mark.
- Don't put your hand any lower yet.
You have to leave it here.
Stick your hand on the mark.
I'm so scared!
- Kwang Soo.
- Why is his hand shaking?
I'm going to smack it as soon
as the whistle blows.
- You have to leave it on the mark.
- Just go with your gut.
Don't you think that his hand is
positioned too close?
Then do you think I should
have it up this high?
[Pulls his hand away at lightning speed.]
His hand has to be on it for me to
do it. Just leave it on the mark.
Kwang Soo, it's only for 30 seconds.
[Giraffe can't keep his hand still
as if the table is a hot grill.]
[Nonstop high speed movement.]
I'm going to wait until he exhausts
himself. Good going.
Yes, you're doing great.
You're doing great.
Okay.
[Spectators and the players alike
are feeling the same nervous energy.]
Five, four...
[Hand slap- Round one.
Kwang Soo wins.]
- Good job, Kwang Soo.
- He's really good.
[Feels like he's lost his arm
in order to win this round.]
Do it right now while he's
already exhausted.
- You have to attack this time.
- You'd better be the attacker this time.
- It's hard to play two rounds in a row.
- Kwang Soo's going to get it.
What if he collapses after this round?
[Playing mind games as soon as
he joins the game.]
Attack!
[Please give me a break.]
You can do this, Kwang Soo.
- You can do this, Kwang Soo.
- You can do this.
- What if he gets too exhausted?
- It's okay.
[The high speed movement starts again.]
Just let me know when there's
only five seconds left on the clock.
Kwang Soo, you're starting
to slow down.
- Hey, you're slowing down too much.
- Kwang Soo.
[Hand slap- Round Two.
Joo Sang Wook wins.]
Good job.
[Hand slap game-
Red Team: 1 vs Blue Team: 1.]
Rock, paper, scissors.
Attack!
[High-speed defense move
that's good for one round.]
- Show them what you've got.
- You can win this round.
[Very high speed.]
Wow, he's so quick!
- Wait like 20 seconds.
- Go from one end to the other.
- Not just in that small area.
- From one end of the table to the other?
[Total concentration.]
Let me know when there are
only five seconds left on the clock.
[The final round of the second game.]
- No, not yet.
- You have to make him feel on edge!
You have to make him feel nervous
to make his hand move faster.
- That's right! He's moving fast now.
- That's pretty fast.
[The end all to the game.]
- Faster, you're moving too slow.
- Faster!
Faster!
[Five seconds left.]
[Right on the mark.]
[Hand slap game- Round Three.
Yoo Jae Suk wins.]
[Second mission- Red Team wins.]
[Red Team wins another Queen's
chance with another win.]
We may have the queen here, but
the other team has the king (Wang).
[The birth of a 4D Beauty,
Wang Ji Hye.]
The current number of knights
you have on the team are...
a total of three white knights,
and two black knights.
[Huh?]
You currently have a total of
three white knights on your team.
[He clearly said there were three white
knights and two black knights earlier.]
[Even after having swapped
Ha Ha out for Jong Kook...]
[The number of white knights on her team
still remains unchanged?]
[In that case...]
I have no idea what
the answer is!
She should've gotten the answer,
but I guess she didn't.
What's the hint you were given?
Tell us what he told you.
The hint he gave was very confusing.
This is a bad situation.
First, it's easier to try to figure this out
since we have a fewer number of players.
Because there are fewer of us.
Then I want someone from my team to
tell me if they're not one of my people.
Can't you tell just by looking?
Your Highness.
[We're all your people!]
- Did you not see how hard I worked?
- Think about the games we just played.
[They're all arguing
that they're a white knight.]
Black knights are going to keep
arguing that they're white knights, right?
Look at how white my face is, Ye Seul.
- But you were really bad at the games.
- I can't help the fact that I'm bad at it.
- I'm just bad at playing games.
- I'm a white knight.
- I'm just naturally bad at games.
- Okay, in that case...
I'm sorry that you're bad
at playing games.
I only want strong players
on my team.
[Han Sang Jin is kicked out
for being a bad game player.]
- I knew it!
- We're good.
- We have to win, don't we?
- You made the right decision.
Ye Seul.
- This is so frustrating.
- Choose a member of the Blue Team.
I'm going to swap Han Sang Jin out
and bring Ha Ha back in.
I'm going to swap these two out
because then I'll be able to tell
one way or the other from the trade.
[Han Sang Jin out,
and Ha Ha back in.]
[Did Ye Seul succeed in swapping out
a black knight for a white knight?]
[Off to the next mission location.]
You look really pretty under
the lighting in this car.
Really?
- I don't look funny?
- No way.
Seeing how Ye Seul brought Ha Ha back in,
it really must've been very confusing.
- There's something I'm curious about.
- Yeah?
Do you think Song Ji Hyo
is white or black?
- Ji Hyo?
- She's definitely black.
- It's more probable that she's black.
- She's been too quiet to be a white knight.
Wow, this is really hard.
To be honest, I'm a black knight.
I have to get on the other team.
Then we're all black knights?
No matter what the case,
we can't lose Sang Wook
- because that would be too confusing.
- No, I need to get to the other team.
If Sang Wook goes, then we're in trouble.
You can't go.
Anyone else but you can go.
- No, I'll just go. Let's just win this.
- No, we can't let you leave.
- We can't let you leave.
- We need to win.
[Sang Wook keeps trying to leave this
team. What is his true identity?]
This is the place.
[The last game site before
the final selection round.]
There's a restaurant.
[A traditional market full of
warmth and delicious foods.]
I wonder if we'll get to eat at
one of these restaurants in here.
- I see 'R' stickers everywhere.
- I see it.
Why are there 'R' stickers
everywhere?
[Now that they take a closer look,
'R' stickers are seen everywhere.]
And all the doors have been papered up
so we can't look inside.
- Hello.
- Wow, it's vegetable pancakes.
- Can we have a pancake?
- Sure, help yourselves.
- We can really eat some?
- Yes, go ahead.
Thank you so much. Freshly made
vegetable pancakes are so delicious.
- We really can eat some?
- Wow, that looks so delicious.
They came just to make you these
in case you were hungry.
[They've been waiting for them to arrive so
that they could make pancakes for them.]
Thank you for coming to
visit us in Gangwondo.
- Thank you, Ma'am.
- We really can eat some?
[Gangwondo's warm hospitality that can
be felt straight through to their hearts.]
- Thank you for the food.
- These are the best on rainy days.
Wow, it's still hot.
[Chive pancakes hot and
fresh off the pan.]
Eat plenty before you go.
It's perfect with the rain outside.
[Chive pancakes on a rainy day.]
- Thank you so much.
- Sure.
[Blue Team also smells the delicious
scent of the food.]
It's so delicious.
Wow, it's so good.
[Even more delicious with the warmth
and love of the ladies added in.]
It's a hand warmer.
[Kwang Soo quietly slips a
hand warmer in the lady's hand.]
[What a warm hearted kid.]
Thank you for such a delicious treat.
Thank you for a delicious treat.
Please always be healthy.
- Thank you, Ma'am.
- Come back again.
[Thank you to the ladies who warmed up
not only our bellies, but our hearts as well.]
[Off to the mission site with
their bellies full of pancakes.]
Wow, that was unbelievable.
No matter who wins the final mission, you'll
get the chance to swap out two people.
[A chance to swap out two people
no matter who wins the final mission.]
[I have to win this no matter what.]
We're all black knights,
so it doesn't matter who goes.
- So you've decided you're a black knight?
- Me? No, I haven't.
[Sang Jin's suddenly decided
that he's also a black knight?]
- I really am a white knight.
- Don't lie when the cameras aren't rolling.
[Sang Jin kept chatting Ye Seul up
even when the cameras weren't rolling.]
No, I really am a white knight.
You're really starting to
resemble Joo Young Hoon.
What are you talking about?
Don't say things like that!
What's wrong with that guy?
- He's really starting to resemble him.
- I thought he was English for a minute.
- A nice English man.
- No, I'm a nice white knight.
Your next mission is,
Market Memory Mission.
You are in the center of the market.
You came in from the far end.
It's equal distance to
the other side of the market.
There are storefronts with
an 'R' sticker on the door.
We've also papered up the doors
to these lovely storefronts.
The reason being, behind
the doors of those storefronts
your opponents will be posed in different
positions which you'll have to memorize
and reenact the pose
once you get back.
Even though the seven of you will only
need to remember five different poses
the five of you must memorize the poses
assumed by these seven people.
Even if one person fails to reenact,
then the whole team fails the mission.
I'm going to take off my pants.
The Red Team can go out
into the market.
- We should split up.
- I don't know what pose to make.
[Red Team to be the first
to assume positions.]
[They must first choose an 'R'
marked store to hide in.]
Hello.
May I come in for a minute?
What's a pose that only I can assume?
[It's crucial to assume a position
that their opponents can't imitate.]
- Can you help me out for a second?
- With what?
- Can you pull my leg up over my head?
- You think you can do that?
That's going to be really tough.
You're going to hurt yourself.
Kwang Soo, you're going to
pull off your leg.
What am I going to do?
[Jae Suk steps into
an 'R' marked blanket store.]
I'm sorry, but may I
impose on you for a moment?
Yes, of course.
Ugh, that hurts.
[How can I pose
so that they can't imitate it?]
I don't think I can do this.
This is my last chance, isn't it?
I really have to win this.
By any chance, do you know
who the black knights are?
- You have no idea?
- No, I wouldn't know.
You're no help.
[Had he known, he would've folded
under Ye Seul's charm.]
I'm in a really bad situation right now,
so I need to win this mission.
There is one thing that I've
thought of.
One, two, three, fighting!
[Market Memory Mission-
Blue Team on the move!]
We'll go to the right.
Where are the 'R' marked doors?
[They must find the stores that the
Red Team members are hiding behind.]
[The Red Team members are behind only
five of these numerous marked doors.]
Where are they?
[The clock is ticking...]
[You came?]
[Try your best to imitate me.]
What the heck is this!
I don't want to!
[A finger up his nose,
and a sock in his mouth.]
[Twisted Ha Ha confusing his opponent
with only one sock off his foot.]
[Must return to the cafe
after memorizing the pose.]
Why isn't this opening?
[What is the pose that Ji Hye
walked in on?]
No way!
- How am I supposed to do that?
- This was meant for a guy, not a girl.
[Can't even figure out
what pose he's assuming.]
- Suk Jin!
- What?
[Of all people, the man she calls
over is... Big-nose.]
- You take it.
- Why?
- What is that?
- A girl shouldn't be doing this.
Wait, what is this pose?
You're all twisted...
Why did you do this?
- What's this?
- Hi, Sang Wook.
What are you doing?
Why is she doing this?
You have an image to uphold.
[Queen Ye Seul is contorting her body
to find all her white knights.]
How is that even possible?
She's lost her mind.
Stop laughing.
- I have to win this.
- It's okay to lose.
Are you black or white?
Don't know about that,
but how did you do this?
[Black or white?
Sang Wook's still mysterious identity.]
[What did Gyu Woon discover?]
[Crumpled up Kwang Soo.]
[A pose that he just wants to ignore.]
[But... Gyu Woon's doing it.]
You have to look at my fingers too.
You know that a lot of people can't do
what I'm doing with my finger.
[Blank Ji discovers, Thinking Yoo Hyuk.]
[Trying hard to hide his laughter.]
Okay!
Why did you have to assume
such a difficult pose?
[It's difficult for me, too.]
Ugh, my legs!
- Like this.
- Time's almost up!
- He can't do it.
- You need to head back.
[Time's up.
Must go back to the meeting site.]
- I didn't see anyone.
- I don't know, but my legs hurt so bad.
Ugh, my legs.
Okay, Gary was here first,
so we'll start with him.
In the market, Ha Ha can be found...
There you go.
[A deep sigh of breath.]
[A sock in his mouth...
and a finger right up his nose.]
In the market,
Yoo Jae Suk can be found...
[Next up is- Blank Ji.
In the market, Yoo Jae Suk can be found.]
That looked really difficult.
[Oh? That looks pretty close...]
- No, she got it wrong.
- In the market, Kwang Soo can be found...
[Gyu Woon's turn.]
[He can't possibly...]
[He's actually doing it!]
He can actually do this?
[Amazing, Jung Gyu Woon.]
In the market, Kim Jong Kook can be found...
I don't know if I can imitate it.
What are you doing?
Gyu Woon can't hold that pose for
too long.
[Hurry, Suk Jin.]
In the market, Han Ye Seul
can be found too.
- But I had no idea she'd do that.
- Hurry up.
She's so weird, and I can't do it.
It's not a pose meant for a man.
- Hurry.
- But I can't do it like that.
Just hurry up and do it!
[While Sang Wook wastes time...
Gyu Woon starts to falter.]
Gyu Woon's hooking his finger
in his mouth because he's struggling.
You're going to rip your mouth.
A man's hips can't spread out like that.
[Sang Wook explains the pose to Ji Hye.]
No, not like that.
Just lay flat on your back.
No, a man can't do that.
- Wang Ji Hye's flexible.
- She's so flexible.
[Ji Hye's just as flexible as Ye Seul is.]
Yes, do it just like that.
Okay, all five members are in position.
Their poses are...
[Did everyone get it perfectly?]
[Ha Ha-Gary.
A perfect match.]
[Ye Seul- Ji Hye.
[Kwang Soo- Gyu Woon.
A perfect match.]
[Jae Suk- Ji Hyo. Arms on the
wrong side. Not a match.]
[Jong Kook- Suk Jin.
Mismatched in every way.]
[Blue Team fails the first attempt.]
Ji Hyo posed in the opposite direction.
Wow, Gyu Woon imitated it perfectly.
[Kwang Soo's doppelganger, Gyu Woon.]
It's time for the Blue Team to go out
and assume their positions.
Okay, you may go and get started.
If I find a woman posing,
then I'll call out for Ye Seul.
If any one of us finds a girl,
then call out for Ye Seul.
[Blue Team on the move.]
I don't think I can do this move.
What difficult pose can I assume?
[Contorting their bodies in
every which direction.]
- Three, two, one. Start!
- Let's go.
[Market memory mission- Red Team.]
[With fewer members on their team, they
must move faster to find their opponents.]
Is no one here?
There's no one here.
I found Gary.
What the heck!
[I'm the dance King of Jamsil,
Kang Gary!]
What the heck!
Do you think you can do this?
[Try and imitate me.
Gary showing off his skills.]
- That's too hard.
- Jong Kook!
- Hey, Jong Kook!
- Only Jong Kook can do this.
[Immediately gives up.]
[Meanwhile...]
[Face-off with a boneless mollusk.]
[Namaste]
[Ji Hye assumes the twisted
doughnut position.]
Ye Seul!
Come over here right now!
Hurry!
You have to look very closely.
- Seriously.
- What are you doing!
Cover the face with the left hand,
and the right hand is bent like this.
Ye Seul, this is really painful.
[Jae Suk already gave up on Gary,
what will he find this time?]
It's Sang Wook.
I think I can do this one.
[Sang Wook, the Samson.]
I think I can do Sang Wook's pose.
Okay, three fingers.
[Sang Wook holds the tough pose
on only three fingers.]
I just saw Sang Wook.
[Ha Ha discovers Sang Jin.]
Okay, left foot, right foot and hat.
Left foot, right foot, and hat.
Left foot...
The socks are in the shoes,
and the hat is placed...
[Nice English man's difficult pose.]
- You can do this, right?
- No, I can't do this.
[Ji Hyo's yoga pose.]
- I can't do this.
- You have to do it!
The left hand is...
Wow, this is really confusing.
I have to put this where?
[Big-nose puts his nose to a good use.]
Okay, the right foot.
- Did you get it?
- The right foot...
Did he memorize it already?
[Time's up.
Back to the meeting site.]
- How are we going to get seven poses?
- I heard Wang Ji Hye's pose was tough?
[Ji Hye's shocking body twist.]
Ji Hye, have you studied yoga?
I took one class.
[Ye Seul's addicting melodic speech.]
'Hey, have you studied yoga?'
We'll get started with Yoo Jae Suk.
[Time to start imitating.]
In the market, Joo Sang Wook
can be found...
No one other than Jong Kook
can do it.
You have to move fast
as not to make it tough for others.
[On three fingers only.
Will Jae Suk succeed?]
[Oh!]
[Jae Suk succeeds.]
In the market,
Song Ji Hyo can be found...
[Time to imitate Blank Ji's pose.]
[Kwang Soo also succeeds.]
In the market, Ji Suk Jin can be found...
[Jong Kook easily succeeds.]
[Also succeeds in imitating
Sang Jin's confusing set up.]
In the market,
Wang Ji Hye can be found...
[The problem is, Ji Hye's twisted pose.]
She can't do it.
No, you can do it.
[Wow, Ye Seul succeeds!]
[Five poses are successfully imitated.]
[Still left are Gary and
Gyu Woon's poses.]
In the market, Gary can be found...
Ugh, Gary's pose...
- Gary's pose.
- I've never done it before.
You know that move...
'Freeze' or whatever.
[Kkuk steps in to give it a try.]
[Wow, succeeds on first try.]
Okay, we have one more.
[One pose still remains.]
[After all they've done,
no one saw Gyu Woon's pose!]
[Even though he waited and waited
until his tongue started cramping up...]
[Still no one came.]
- No one came.
- You did well.
[Recovers from his cramps with
Grandpa's comforting words.]
Red Team fails.
[Until one of the team succeeds!
Red Team steps back out for more posing.]
We're at a definite disadvantage.
Thank you.
[A standing tree position with
the help of these ladies.]
Okay, that's good.
Yes, thank you.
That looks so difficult.
I feel bad for him.
[Blue Team starts their search.]
[Queen Ye Seul lets go of all her
inhibitions for the sake of victory.]
Ye Seul.
Must you go this far?
Wait a minute.
[Even she herself can't stop laughing.]
Your mouth needs to twist that way.
- Eyes.
- I can't cross my eyes.
I really can't cross my eyes.
Why don't you give it a try?
Wait a minute.
Ye Seul, there's something...
No, that's not it!
I really am a white knight, and
you need to trust me on that, okay?
I'm going to fail this mission for you,
so you have to trust me.
[Could Gary really be a white knight to
sacrifice winning this mission for me?]
I'm telling you the truth.
I'm just not a very good talker.
- I'm not lying about it.
- You're not failing because this is too hard?
- Why wouldn't I be able to do it?
- Then twist your lips around like this.
I'm telling you that I can do it.
I'll tell my team members that I can
do it and just send them away, okay?
Show me the pose again.
Are we done?
Do I need to go back?
[Keeps it a secret from other members.]
[Gary asks for her trust.
Could he really be a white knight?]
[Time to imitate the poses.]
[Will he get it?]
Ye Seul actually made that pose?
- Seriously?
- Ye Seul, did you do that?
Ye Seul, that's what you did?
[Did Gary get the pose
purposely wrong as promised?]
Why?
I had it right!
[The mouth is twisted in
the wrong direction- Fail.]
- I can't cross my eyes.
- If Gary had only succeeded.
[Had Gary succeeded, the Blue
Team would've won the mission.]
Wang Ji Hye should've found
Ye Seul.
[Ye Seul, do you trust me now?]
[Time for the Blue Team to pose,
and the Red Team to imitate.]
How am I going to do this?
I have zero flexibility!
[Red Team goes off on their search.]
There's no one here.
Oh my goodness!
[Who is that frightening monster!]
[What monstrosity...]
Oh my goodness!
[A scene right out of a horror movie.]
[Frightening everyone.]
- What are you doing!
- You scared me!
- Ye Seul...
You're grabbing onto your legs...
and you're sticking out your tongue.
Ji Hye, I'm going to stay for a bit longer
to make you feel the agony some more.
Do it again.
No, I'm just joking.
I'll be back.
I have to find the others.
Where's Sang Jin?
Where is everyone?
- He's here!
- Where's Sang Jin?
[What is this pose now?]
With the hat pulled over his head...
Is he sucking on his toe?
- He's sucking on his toe.
- He must've lost his mind.
What's wrong with him!
[Doppelganger Gyu Woon's
upgraded pose.]
Why are these people taking it so far?
I think I can do this.
[Young doppelganger starts to imitate.]
There you are.
- That's nothing.
- That's too easy.
- I'll do this one.
- Okay.
I'll do this one.
[Everyone rushes back to
the meeting site.]
Did you get it, Kwang Soo?
You and Gyu Woon are battling it out.
I vow to win this time!
What am I going to do!
Did you know that I play the role
of a news announcer in the drama?
An extremely intelligent newscaster.
[Having an identity crisis.]
What am I going to do?
I play a very intelligent newscaster.
What if the viewers at home
get confused about my role?
[Ye Seul runs into Gary again on
her way back to the meeting site.]
You trust me now, right?
- Yes, I really do trust you.
- I failed on purpose.
[Gary purposely got the pose wrong
as he promised to Ye Seul.]
[Earning the trust of
Queen Ye Seul with a single swipe.]
- Trust no one!
- You can't trust anyone in this world.
- Unless it's you.
- Yes.
[Could Gary really be a white knight?]
- Okay, we'll get started.
- In the market, Gary can be found...
[Gary's pose... was too easy?]
Are you done?
In the market, Ji Suk Jin can be found...
[Next up is Suk Jin's pose.]
- What are you doing?
- Not easy, is it?
[Have to bite down on the toe...]
- I can't reach my mouth.
- Have someone else do it.
[Jae Suk bites down and succeeds!]
In the market,
Jung Gyu Woon can be found...
[Kwang Soo starts to imitate his
doppelganger, Gyu Woon- Match.]
In the market,
Joo Sang Wook can be found...
[A perfect match to Sang Wook's pose.]
He was really struggling with this pose.
[Time to imitate Ji Hye's monstrous pose.]
I almost kicked her with my foot.
[Oh? How is she doing that?]
In the market,
Song Ji Hyo can be found...
[Ji Hyo's pose- Match.]
What was Sang Jin's pose?
- Why did he do this?
- No, can't be...
[Unbelievable!]
[Red Team wins the
Market Memory mission.]
Red Team wins another game.
Why does the other team
lose at everything?
- With all the members they have, too.
- Seriously.
As mentioned earlier, you can swap out
two of your teammates this time.
[Queen Ye Seul now is given the chance
to swap out two of her teammates.]
[While setting up the scene
during a brief intermission.]
- Do you have any idea?
- No, I don't.
[Ji Hyo quietly approaches Ye Seul.]
[Tries to help Ye Seul
make up her decision...]
But who do you think I should
trade out?
[Could Ji Hyo...
also be a white knight?]
If the Queen will step forward, we'll let you
know how many white knights there are.
- Maybe there are already four.
- I wish I could know, too.
The current number of white knights
on the team including yourself...
Other than yourself, there's one more.
So there are a total of two white knights.
[A current count of two
white knights on the team.]
[In that case... three of
those men are black knights!]
- I'm so confused right now.
- Tell us what he told you.
But shouldn't she have a definite
idea of what Ha Ha is?
[She should be sure of Ha Ha by now
after the two exchanges he's made.]
[Wait...]
I made the first swap with Ha Ha and
Jong Kook but still had the same results.
Which means that I either swapped out
a black knight for another black knight
or a white knight for
another white knight.
So they're the same thing, but in order to
find out whether they're friend or foe...
[What is their identity?]
[That's why she put both Ha Ha
and Jong Kook back on her team.]
[But the number of white knights
diminished down to two.]
[Which means...]
[Jong Kook and Ha Ha...]
Get out!
[Jong Kook and Ha Ha- Get out!]
[Very high chance of Jong Kook
and Ha Ha being black knights.]
Ye Seul, you have to think
very carefully about this.
- This is no joke.
- Shut that mouth of yours!
- Shut that mouth of yours.
- I can do this on my own.
[Sense of betrayal.]
Fine, since we're already in this state,
want us tell you what we are?
[Black knight duo revealing
their true identities?]
- Want me to tell you what I am?
- Didn't I tell you from the beginning?
- Do you not see what we are?
- Don't you remember what I told you?
- I already told you from the beginning.
- This really is something.
Wow, unbelievable.
You have no room to talk either!
Us, too?
Why?
[It means that either Jae Suk
or Kwang Soo is also a black knight!]
Be quiet!
[Queen Ye Seul is upset at the
sense of betrayal she's feeling.]
- No, can't be.
- You've chosen your two.
[Only one of these two is a white knight.]
[And three of these seven
are the other white knights.]
I can bite down on all
ten of my toes.
Why do you keep talking about
your toes?
Gyu Woon, what are you?
How can he not answer that when
she's looking at him with those eyes?
- I thought she was mesmerizing him.
- Why are you trying to coerce him?
I lost every single mission.
I haven't won a single thing yet.
That's because you're
just bad at playing games.
It's possible that he's purposely
failing his mission.
[Did Gyu Woon purposely lose his missions
in order to gain Ye Seul's trust?]
I'm normally very good at these games.
Watch all my previous episodes on this show.
But I purposely failed
at all my missions today.
[Game expert, Sang Wook,
purposely lost on today's missions?]
- Sorry, I'm a white knight.
- I think it's Ji Hyo and Sang Wook.
- He's a white knight.
- He told me earlier that he's white.
[Or could Ji Hyo be a white knight,
and that's why she tried to help?]
[Everyone else is convinced
that she isn't...]
- She definitely isn't.
- You have to know this.
There's something that I've been doing
in secret during the whole race.
[Did she actually get this
wrong on purpose?]
[And purposely chose an easy
pose for the opponents?]
- I really am a white knight.
- I also have a secret to share.
- Look at me, Ji Hyo. I really am white.
- I'm really a white knight, too.
I swear that I'm a white knight.
[And Gary purposely failed at his mission to
prove to Ye Seul that he's a white knight.]
Okay, I've made my decision.
- I really am a white knight.
- I could've totally ended this game.
[Selects Ji Hyo...]
[and Gary to recruit into her team.]
Song Ji Hyo and Gary, please
move over to the other team.
[Did she make the right decision?]
That's your decision?
The final decision has now been made.
You can now head over to
the final judging platform.
[Which between Jae Suk and Kwang Soo
is the black knight?]
I'm lying with an enemy
in this car right now.
There's a black knight amongst us.
We're fine as long as we win.
That team is a total mess right now.
Gary and Ji Hyo both gave out
really easy poses.
Maybe Gary really is a white knight.
We just have to hope that
one of us in on that team.
- I think it's Kwang Soo.
- It is Kwang Soo.
Then it doesn't matter. Let's
use Gyu Woon to confuse Ye Seul.
Good plan.
Just blurt out that you think
I'm a black knight.
One serious statement from you,
and everyone will believe you.
Sang Wook, just stay out of this.
[What is the truth behind
Sang Wook's mysterious identity?]
[Finally arrives at the final location
where all the secrets will be revealed.]
If you're telling me the truth,
then we'll continue to be friends
but if you're lying to me, then
I'm never going to see you again!
Tell me right now who
you're going to choose.
Ye Seul, I think we should talk
just amongst ourselves
and leave those two out of it.
[The three are suddenly united as one.]
[Jae Suk and Kwang Soo are the first
ones to walk into the final location.]
[Could one of these two
really be a black knight?]
I've made my final decision.
- Someone's identity is black as dirt.
- I regret the life that I've led.
I'm sorry to everyone
for the way I've been.
- I'm going to correct my ways.
- I can never trust this kid.
Please trust me!
I really am not lying right now!
If you had been more honest in your life,
you wouldn't be the boy who cried wolf.
[Blue Team also arrives onsite.]
What's Wang Ji Hye's deal?
She never once said she's a white knight.
- I really think that Ji Hye's a white knight.
- No, Ji Hye isn't a white knight.
Ji Suk Jin is definitely a black knight
from the way he's talking.
- But I'm telling you the truth.
- You should think about this again.
- I think you've got the right team.
- Lee Kwang Soo is black.
No, Jae Suk is a black knight.
Welcome to Black Knight Race's
final mission.
The Queen of White Knights must gather up
all the information she's been given thus far
and use the one final chance
she'll be given to make her trade.
Thank you.
If all the members on your team end up
being white knights, then you win the race.
But if even one black knight is on the team,
then the other team wins the race.
If the Black Knight Team wins, then
the balloon above your heads will pop open.
[Giant flour filled balloons!]
We win the race if one of our
black knights is on her team, right?
Then what happens to that black
knight with all that flour?
They'll get doused as well.
It's just part of the mission.
Point to the member on your team that
you'd like to kick off the team.
[Time to choose the member
whom she wants to trade out.]
Ye Seul has that look in her eyes.
- One of us is a black knight.
- I know.
- It's him.
- I'm not going to say anymore.
- I'll accept whatever decision you make.
- Don't be swayed.
- Don't hesitate on your decision.
- Go with the one whom you already chose.
Okay, I'm going to announce my decision.
I'm going to announce my decision.
[Just which of the two is a black knight?]
Yoo Jae Suk, get out!
There was nothing else we could do.
[Swaps out Yoo Jae Suk.]
- It has to be Kwang Soo.
- How frustrating.
- I'm so sure that it's Kwang Soo.
- You have to make the right selection.
[I don't know what to do either!]
[Instead of hardworking Jae Suk,
Ye Seul chooses traitorous Kwang Soo.]
- Seriously?
- Why?
You must recruit one member
to fill up your now empty spot.
[Must recruit one opposing member
to fill in Jae Suk's now empty space.]
- I think I'll bring Ha Ha back in...
- That can't be an easy decision to make.
[Verified that Ha Ha and Jong Kook are
black knights with the first two swaps made.]
[That's why I'm sure that
it's not you two.]
[And the two hard to identify members...]
[Sang Wook and Sang Jin.]
[Sang Wook strongly offered himself up
during every trading session.]
I really am a white knight.
You frighten me the most.
I've been a white knight from
the start. I'm a white knight.
I'm telling you that I'm the one!
[Sang Jin even looked desperate.]
[It's decision time.]
Sang Jin, come here!
[Han Sang Jin is recruited in.]
That's just absurd!
- Are you serious?
- I thought Sang Jin was for sure black.
Kwang Soo should've been
swapped out for me.
I really hope that he's a white knight.
[Did Ye Seul make the smart choice?]
- It's all over now.
- The dice has been thrown.
[Time to verify the answer.]
[Checking Ye Seul's monitor.]
The Queen of White Knights.
[Sign of the white knight for being
the Queen of White Knights.]
Okay, next.
One, two, three!
[Next up- Gary.]
[Ye Seul felt sure of Gary and
recruited him after the last round.]
[Gary is a white knight.]
- Just wait to see hers.
- Okay, Ji Hyo.
[Ji Hyo's turn.]
[Ji Hyo showed her trust in Ye Seul
and leaned on her throughout the day.]
[Ji Hyo- White Knight.]
[Proceeding as predicted so far.]
Kwang Soo is next.
This is the highlight of the day.
Please stand directly below
your balloons.
- It's Kwang Soo, isn't it?
- Kwang Soo?
- It was between Kwang Soo and I.
- Let's see this.
[Could Kwang Soo be a white knight?]
[Lee Kwang Soo- White Knight.]
- You're a black knight?
- Yes, I am.
- I had no idea.
- Jae Suk is a black knight!
[Jae Suk had everyone fooled.]
- I told you that I'm a white knight.
- I had no idea.
- It's still up in the air right now.
- Sang Jin is the last to go!
[Time to verify Sang Jin's identity.]
One, two... this is the final one.
[White Knights vs Black Knights.]
[If Sang Jin turns out to be a white knight,
then Team White Knights wins.]
[If Sang Jin turns out to be a black knight,
then victory goes to Black Knights.]
[Just what is Sang Jin's true identity?]
[Team White Knights wins!]
[Sang Jin has been
a white knight all along.]
[Ye Seul's completely miraculous win.]
He had me completely fooled.
[Black knights are still
left feeling befuddled.]
Why?
What did I ever say?
[Starting to turn the blame
on each other.]
- You said you were white at first.
- That was just a joke.
Team White Knights wins!
[White Knights win the race.]
Did you never once think that
I could be a white knight?
- Of course, I have.
- See? I knew it.
- He really is a piece of work.
- I should've tried harder.
You really can't go
about your life alone.
- Ye Seul, you know what it is?
- She learned a new lesson.
- Can you say it just once?
- I'm never running away again.
I'm never running away again.
[Ye Seul will always remain here with us.]
[Birth of a Beauty- Joo Sang Wook, Ye Seul,
Gyu Woon, Wang Ji Hye, and Han Sang Jin.]
Subtitles by DramaFever
Someone help me!
[The lone male survivors after
complete destruction of earth.]
[And the women who come out
to greet these men.]
[The fate of earth rests in the hands
of these six couples.]
[And the passion of their love.]
Even if you're ugly, I still love you!
[Only one of these couples can survive.
Who will share this everlasting love?]
[Next week on Running Man-
Humanity's final couple.]