Running Man
[In an instant...]
[all humanity vanished into thin air.]
[Korea's Nodeul Island.]
[In a tranquil place where only the
sounds of raindrops are heard...]
[traces of humanity are found.]
Hello!
Is anyone out there?
Is there anyone out here?
Mom!
[Six men are drawn to Nodeul Island
by some mystical force.]
What is going on here?
Am I left alone on this earth?
Is anyone out there?
Anyone?
[These are humanity's last men standing.]
[And on this island, lives
humanity's final six women.]
It's been a while.
[Jong Sook- 39 years old.
One of the final female survivors.]
Hello.
[Hana- 36 years old.
One of the final female survivors.]
It's been a while since I've made
an appearance on Running Man.
My name is Lee Kwang Ja.
[Kwang Ja- 30 years old.]
Hello.
[Gae Eun- 37 years old.]
[Ji Hyo- 34 years old.]
I'm so hungry and cold.
[Jae Soon- 43 years old.]
The thought of having to endure and
survive through this is very difficult.
Being with all these women
are very troublesome.
[What's the biggest difficulty?]
- Having to look at their ugly faces all year.
And also... they're
starting to stink like men.
I think having me around is
alleviating their worry for food.
I built these homes myself,
and everything else that you see here.
I don't know if it's because
there aren't any men around...
but I think my body is starting to develop
male hormones and testosterone.
What I need the most as a woman...
is a man!
- I would like a man.
- A nice boyfriend.
I've never once been without a boyfriend
since the minute I was born.
Even when I was in the incubator, I was
seducing the baby in the next incubator.
Where's my knight in shining armor?
Huh?
I wouldn't really know right now
since I don't see any men around
but I think if men were to come around,
I'd turn into a head turning femme fatale.
- Seriously... you look just like her.
- You look just like your mother.
- What did you say?
- You look just like your mother, too.
- You look the most like your mother.
- You take just after your mom!
[They're all looking very much
like their mothers...]
You are the final six female survivors,
and there are final six male survivors.
- I see one of the men heading this way.
- Who is it?
[On an island where it was
only populated by women...]
[A shadow of a man darkens the earth!]
I thought he was an elder
out for his early morning stroll.
- Hello.
- Wow, it's a man!
[First man on the island- Big nose.]
- It's been so long since I've seen a man!
- My goodness!
[First man they've seen in a whole year.]
- Why?
- Here comes another one! Who is it?
Ugh, Seriously.
They're all my friends.
[Nation's beloved roughneck-
Jang Dong Min.]
- He's a special guest.
- It's Dong Min.
- It's a man!
- What are you doing? Huh?
[Innocent Jong Sook feels uncomfortable with
a touch from an unfamiliar man's touch.]
- Min Gyo!
- Hello!
Show them your eyes once more.
[A man known for his expressive eyes-
Kim Min Gyo.]
- Honey!
- Who is it?
[A man of perfection- Song Jae Rim.]
- How is he so good looking?
- Give him a hug.
Wow, honey!
[Jae Rim is accosted as soon as
he arrives on the island.]
Oh my, you startled me!
[Number one rookie to the variety world-
MIB's Kang Nam.]
- Run!
- I don't know where to go.
- Why is he trying to act cool?
- Hurry up!
[Finally rushing over to the group.]
[The dignity of variety shows-
Park Soo Hong.]
[We are humanity's six final
male survivors.]
- Have you all been well?
- Yes.
I hope that you've been
saving up your energy.
It's nice seeing you all again
after this past week.
[After this past week?
What does that mean?]
[Exactly one week ago at 6am...]
[The rain pours down from the sky
on the day of Running Man shoot.]
[Raining much harder than expected.]
[Staff is having an emergency meeting
to discuss whether to film or not.]
[Ultimately wraps up filming the episode
after pre-show interview due to the rain.]
[Everyone's gathering at
the opening scene location...]
Hello.
[Even the guests are invited over
to join in on the emergency meeting.]
- You're not a girl?
- No, not me.
- Hello, Sir.
- Wow, look at you.
Soo Hong's on the show?
- Look at this guy.
- You look pretty, Gary.
He should be one of the girls,
so why isn't he playing one?
- He'd be perfect as one of the girls.
- I think he would be perfect for the role.
- What is this?
- Hello.
[Even Jae Rim seems confused by
what's going on set.]
- Wow, he's so good looking.
- Look at him.
[This actually was...
these survivors' actual first meeting.]
You are the last 12 surviving members
of earth's whole human race.
- How could these be the final survivors?
- I'm going to make him fall in love with me.
Wouldn't it be better to just
let the human race die out?
I have a wife back home.
If we really are the last
survivors of the human race
then we're going to have to find some
other ways to keep it going.
How about the men come on the island
to kill all these ugly women?
[Imminent end for the human race-
Humanity's final surviving members.]
- It's raining really hard, isn't it?
- Yes.
- I have something to ask all of you.
- What is it?
- Are you all available next Monday?
- No, what for?
- Are you available next Monday?
- Why are you talking about next Monday?
The reason being, we didn't expect the weather
to be so cold and rainy as it is today.
- We didn't expect this weather at all.
- It's raining really hard.
So we're thinking that this weather may
be difficult for you to do your missions in
and more than anything else, we're trying
to work around Jang Dong Min's schedule.
Why? Why are we
working around his schedule?
- Is it because of his work schedule?
- Why do we have to do that?
[No time to wait around for the rain to stop
due to Dong Min's afternoon schedule.]
- Just because of Dong Min?
- It's not like he's Jang Dong Geun!
- It's not like he's famous Jang Dong Geun!
- I know it's hard, but just accept it.
Just keep your mouth shut!
I just saw Soo Hong
giving Dong Min dirty looks.
Seriously, Soo Hong.
We'll work out the rest of the details
regarding everyone else's schedules.
Please go home and get plenty of rest.
- Wow, seriously?
- Okay, go home.
- Are you kidding right now?
- This isn't candid camera, is it?
I'm actually getting some time to myself
that my wife won't know about.
[Thus, filming for that day got cancelled...]
- Have you all been well?
- Yes.
I hope you all got plenty of rest.
- It's his birthday today.
- It's my birthday today!
[Okay then...]
What are you doing?
It's your birthday today?
Happy 45th birthday to Park Soo Hong!
[Park Soo Hong's 45th birthday.]
- Wow, you're older than I had thought.
- I didn't even have a celebration.
You didn't get to have one?
Did you all hear that?
He said, 'celebration',
not 'party'.
[Using terms that old people would use.]
- It's because he's older.
- He's an old man.
You will find and be coupled off
with your soul mate
and you will have to pass through
all the couple missions and final mission
to escape off of this island, thus
becoming this race's winning couple.
- Only one couple?
- Yes, just one.
- That's pretty cruel.
- We will now determine the couples.
Let's take a brief moment to introduce
ourselves to all the men here.
We don't have much time,
so we'll make our decisions quickly.
We've actually all made
our selections already.
- We're not going to change our minds.
- We can say the same about you.
- I...
- You look like an awful jerk.
- You look like a real awful jerk.
- Good eye!
I'm a real awful bastard.
- Wow, he's so attractive!
- I actually find him attractive now.
[Assumes the bad boy pose.]
- Your upper teeth are so tiny!
- They're cute.
[Unique mini upper teeth are
found to be quite charming.]
My looks are normal,
and my physique is normal too...
He's telling us that he's normal.
- He's a bluffer!
- His personality isn't what it seems.
[This man... is very unique...]
- I will do my best.
- That wasn't bad.
- Can you treat us all to a meal?
- Excuse me?
- Do you have any money?
- You're infamous for being very frugal.
We heard that you're very
stingy with your money.
Why are you suddenly asking
me about that?
- A man should be more generous than that.
- Do you go dutch in Japan?
- Do you go dutch even on dates?
- No, it's not like that...
But why are you suddenly
asking me all these questions?
- Fine, I'm not eating!
- We can take care of ourselves!
[You can just treat us next time.]
[Thus starts the final survivors'
couple selection process.]
One, two, three!
[Kwang Ja selects Jae Rim as her own.]
[Couple Jae Rim and Kwang Ja.]
[Min Gyo's cupid... is Hana.]
[Couple Min Gyo and Hana.]
[Dong Min's suspicious selection.]
[Couple Dong Min and Ji Hyo.]
[These remaining members plays a round of
rock-paper-scissors to select their mates.]
[Couple Soo Hong and Jong Sook.]
[The remaining four members.]
[Couple Big-nose and Jae Soon.]
[Last but not least,
Couple Kang Nam and Gary.]
- Is everyone happy with their partners?
- Kang Nam's the girl here, right?
- No, he's the man.
- We're going to switch on and off.
Depending on the mission.
- Are you sure we're doing this right?
- Why?
Aren't the couples supposed to
link arms together or things like that?
Had I known this,
I wouldn't have chosen her.
He picked her with an ulterior motive.
I'm going to have to train her right.
[The six couples are now complete.]
- Kwang Ja.
- Yes?
- Why are you standing apart from Jae Rim?
- No, I'm not.
- Why are you doing that?
- No, we were just talking.
- We're getting to know each other.
- Come here, honey.
[The manly man type.]
- How old are you?
- I'm 30 years old.
- We're the same age.
- You two are the same age.
[Jae Rim and Kwang Ja are
a couple both born in '85.]
- My honey friend.
- What's 'honey friend?'
[Random Jae Rim comes up with
a very unique pet name.]
- They're both the same age.
- I've never seen Kwang Soo so speechless.
- Where did Soo Hong go?
- Why are you linking our fingers?
My partner, Dong Min, is still
acting awkward around me.
Why did you pick her if you
were going to act like that?
- You're not acting like yourself!
- Look at that bashful smile.
- Why are you acting like that?
- He's acting like that on purpose.
Why is he acting like that?
Towards the end of the show,
she's going to beg and plead for me.
Let's go!
[Off to the first mission location.]
- What's all this about?
- What are they going to have us do?
This is the rice paddy where the women
were trying to cultivate food for themselves.
- Yes, I remember this.
- We were just trying to eat and survive.
Here's the first game
for Final Surviving Couple Race.
We should test the endurance and
teamwork skills for each of the couples.
Yes, that's very important for the men,
so we should test it.
That's why we've prepared this game.
This mission is called, 'The thread of fate.'
- What's it about?
- Do we have to spin around?
If you look over to the side, you'll see
the spools with the thread around it.
- The women from each team...
- Yes?
The women must get on the stand and stay
until the thread of fate finishes unraveling.
The men will run over to their women
when they hear the blow of the whistle
and run back towards the starting line with
the rope in hand until it unravels completely.
The women will then alight from their stands
and grab the food dangling from the bar.
- That's going to be hard.
- The women will have to do it?
- Why are you making the women do it?
- I really love that.
- That's too hard for us women.
- Can we grab it with our hands?
[Must jump and grab the food
with their hands.]
- Will you be able to reach it?
- Okay.
Honey, are you dissing me right now?
Any height related game will be
disadvantageous for us.
My sweetie can even get it
with his mouth.
Can you make Kwang Ja jump
from his knees?
Three rounds of the game will be played.
The couple that wins the first round
wins first place.
Really?
The couple that wins the second round
will take second place.
And the couple that wins the third round
will take third place.
- That's why three rounds will be played.
- That's a great idea.
We just need to win
one of the three rounds.
- We're playing this three times?
- Yes, one of three rounds.
We're going to play three times?
He's still acting awkward!
What do I do?
Hey, what's your deal?
Just act like yourself!
[Instead of his usual grumpy expression,
it's an expression of nervous excitement.]
He keeps acting really awkward
around me.
Do you think we all came out here at
4am just so you can act like this?
You've never been around a beautiful
woman like Ji Hyo before, have you?
She keeps wagging her tail at me.
I can't even think clearly.
I've been dealing with her
tail wagging for four years now.
I've been dealing with that tail
for four years already.
[Four years' worth of tail side effect.]
That was cute.
The three winning couples will be given
a chance to pick something that will
become extremely helpful at the final
mission of escaping off the island.
Women, off to the spool,
and men, to the other side.
[Just which couple will be the first
to unravel the thread of fate?]
Min Gyo might even be able to
pull these up to his thighs.
Hey, Min Gyo.
- These are like pants on me.
- They are like pants on you.
[The rain boots are practically
pants on Min Gyo's short legs.]
I don't want you getting cold.
Can you play some romantic
background music?
Why is Dong Min acting like that?
- What's he doing over there?
- He's being ridiculous.
Dong Min's been acting useless all day.
[I don't care what anyone says,
because I'm happy right now.]
- You're just my style.
- We're just playing a game.
So just don't hurt yourself, okay?
Seriously!
When did you become so caring?
You like that?
[Gae Eun explodes in a fit of jealousy.]
[Thread of destiny- Round one.]
Jong Sook!
It's me, your honey!
- Honey!
- You trust me, don't you?
- Of course, I trust you!
- I love you!
Honey, if you don't do this right,
then you're dead!
- What did you say? I love you, too!
- Okay!
If you don't do this right,
then you're really dead.
- What did he say? That he'll kill me?
- Yes, he'll kill you if you mess up.
- He's going to kill me if I mess up?
- Jae Soon!
- Your honey's coming for you!
- Honey, my butt!
- Hey!
- Mister, you'd better do it right!
- I'm not a 'mister'.
- Phuket boy!
- I love you!
- Phuket boy, do it right!
[It's not 'pocket boy', but 'Phuket boy.']
['Honey' Big-nose and his love for Phuket.]
- Honey, fighting!
- Ji Hyo!
- What is he doing?
- What are you doing!
[Dong Min gets criticized
whenever he opens his mouth.]
He acts like he really likes
Ji Hyo for real.
Don't worry, it's okay if we lose.
Just don't hurt yourself, okay?
- Thanks, honey!
- Knock it off, you two!
Be quiet!
[Lashes out at anyone who's
not his girl.]
Pocket boy!
You're so cute!
You're cute, pocket boy!
What happened?
Did his legs sink into the ground?
Why happened to his legs?
- Why are you even saying that?
- My legs are sinking more than others.
- Gae Eun!
- Honey, let's win this, and go to Gangnam!
No matter how ugly you are,
I still love you!
- I still love you!
- Thanks, honey!
[True love can be felt through
his shouting love confession.]
Okay!
Fighting!
[Time for random Jae Rim's
love confession.]
Honey, calm yourself down first
before you say anything!
No words are necessary!
[Shoots Kwang Ja a heart.]
- I'm coming for you!
- Honey, you're not weird!
You're just a little different.
- Jae Rim.
- The winner of the first round...
- Is the first place winner.
- Let's win this, Jae Soon!
- Fighting!
- Ready!
- This is our only chance, honey!
- Set...
- Jang Dong Min, fighting!
[Farm field newbies are struggling
to find their balance out on the field.]
[Kang Nam loses his balance and
falls as soon as the whistle sounds.]
[Other men are racing
full speed ahead...]
[Run, honey!]
[But Kang Nam is the only one
left behind.]
Kang Nam, what are you doing?
[Farm field sprint with their
manly pride hanging on the line.]
[I'm coming!]
[With the exception of Kang Nam, everyone
else arrives almost at the same time.]
[Time to start unraveling
the thread of fate.]
[High speed spinning on top of the spool.]
[Kang Nam finally arrives at the spool.]
What the heck is this!
[Great pulling and great spinning...
working better than expected.]
[Hana and Min Gyo's thread is
first to finish unraveling.]
[Ji Hyo, Dong Min and Jong Sook,
Soo Hong soon follow thereafter.]
[Grab this bread to win the round.]
[Hana is in the lead.]
[Muddy fields and rain boots-
Worst combinations for jumping.]
[And ferocious competition
on top of it all.]
[Meanwhile...]
[Three others who finally get
the chance to step off their spools.]
I don't think I can do this!
[You can do it, honey!]
Run!
[A fierce battle... with the
precious food as their prize.]
[Tall Kwang Ja, is everyone's mark.]
Let go of me!
- We can't let Kwang Soo get it.
- You can do this!
You can do this!
Run for it!
[Giraffe attempts a jump- Fails.]
[Kwang Ja's second attempt at a jump.]
[So close, but unfortunately fails.]
Just step on him!
Step on him and jump.
[Kwang Ja becomes everyone's step stool.]
[Steps on Kwang Ja stool...
and Jong Kook jumps for it.]
Jump!
[Will he get it?]
[Jong Sook knocks the bread into
the air with her powerful grab.]
Gae Eun!
[But the bread has disappeared...]
- Where did it go?
- Where is it?
Find it!
Jong Sook!
[The finder of the bread
wins the first round.]
- Jae Soon!
- Move up a little bit more.
[My precious food...
where have you gone?]
- What is this?
- Just sniff it out!
- Just sniff it out.
- I found it!
[Jae Soon discovers it!]
[Jae Soon and Suk Jin win the first round.]
We're the one who dropped it!
Why are you taking what's ours!
- Why are you taking what's ours?
- Jae Soon, you did great!
[Takes the victory and the precious food.]
- We dropped it.
- Do we have to eat this?
- We did all the work!
- They stole our food!
- I had it first.
- You're actually eating that?
I even sacrificed my sock.
Good job, Jae Soon.
The first round goes to
Yoo Jae Soon and Ji Suk Jin.
[Thread of Fate- Round one.
Jae Soon and Suk Jin win.]
- We were doing so well.
- The bread just flew off.
For the second round, the men will spin,
and the women will run and pull. Understood?
- What happened, Gary?
- Stop it, and don't say anything about it.
How is it possible for him to
be even uglier than before?
- How is that even possible?
- Be quiet!
- We're starting to get closer.
- What is Dong Min doing?
- What is he doing?
- Can you teach me your skills?
Everyone be quiet because
I'm very upset right now.
- What are you doing right now?
- She has mud all over her hands.
- Seriously!
- Her hands are muddy.
I'll take care of all that mud.
Okay, let's get started.
[Another round of couple cheer time.]
- Kim Min Gyo, fighting!
- Come to me!
Honey, since you're so tall,
gather up your energy, and do this right!
Stop nagging at me and say
something nice since you're a girl.
I said, do it right!
- He's always threatening me.
- Honey!
Don't mind the field, and
don't run so slow this time, okay?
- Gae Eun, no matter how ugly you are...
- Stop saying that I'm ugly!
No matter how ugly you are, I don't
think you should tie back your hair!
- I tied it back for you!
- You look like one of my aunts!
- Love the nape of my neck, okay?
- Fighting!
- Honey, fighting!
Dong Min!
Let's share the bread this time!
- Fighting!
- I'll get it for you!
- Ugh, just knock it off!
- Seriously!
- Just be yourself!
- Be careful, and don't trip.
- I'll run faster for you.
- What are they doing?
[His smile incites their rage.]
He must've lost his mind.
[A fascinating man who incites rage
in others for being nice.]
Honey!
Honey, you are not weird!
Let's finish this,
and go to a sauna together!
Why would we go to a sauna?
- He wants to go to a sauna.
- What's wrong with him?
[The man with a 4D personality.]
Winning this second round will
land you in second place for the game.
[The winner of this round will earn
the second place slot.]
- Ready.
- Let's win second place!
Set... go!
[Amazing speed.]
[The muddy field is like home for them.
Full speed ahead without hesitation.]
[Arrive at the spools in
the blink of an eye.]
[Even unravels the thread
at top speed.]
[The men spin around like
top spinners.]
[Kwang Ja, Jae Rim and
Gae Eun, Kang Nam are in the lead.]
[Jae Rim is the first to finish unraveling.]
[Kang Nam finishes unraveling
almost at the same time.]
[But... where are you guys going?]
- Gae Eun!
- Come on.
[Jae Rim and Kang Nam start
heading towards the food.]
Honey, you are not weird!
[Why is this guy grabbing
onto someone else's rope?]
Let go, Mister!
[Absence of sanity.]
[Min Gyo finally gets on his way.]
[Dong Min stands still to
quell his dizziness away.]
- Are you okay?
- You can step on him.
Why do I feel so dizzy?
[Everyone starts to gather
under the food.]
- You can do this!
- No!
Jae Rim...
[I'm coming!]
What are you doing!
- You're going to fall!
- Jump!
[Dong Min shoves four guys
away with one push...]
[Could this be his chance?]
[Jae Rim's forceful interference.]
You'd better start doing it right.
What's wrong with you?
Are you tired already?
One, two, three!
I seriously can't do this even if
you guys weren't interfering.
[Starting to sink deeper
and deeper into the mud.]
- Ugh, I'm so tired.
- Help me!
[Just then...]
[Soo Hong shoves four guys
out of his way.]
[And jumps into the air.]
[Will he be able get it?]
[Jong Sook and Soo Hong
win the second round.]
Wow, I can't believe what I just saw!
- Where did it go?
- The four oldest guys have won so far.
[Four oldest guys win
first and second place.]
A man should always make sure
to provide for his woman.
[Only one final round left in the game.]
[The winner of this round
will take third place.]
Why are they making us do this here?
I'm going to work even harder
for us now.
- I love you.
- You really shocked me as a man.
Ugh, seriously!
Have you lost your mind?
Stop making a fuss over it.
[Jong Sook and Soo Hong are
overflowing with love.]
Let's go start our lives as newlyweds.
[Through Soo Hong's efforts, Jong Sook
and Soo Hong wins second place]
For the final third round,
the women will get on the spool again.
- Ji Hyo!
- Ugh, what is the matter with him?
This is our last chance,
and if we lose again this time...
I don't think I'll be
able to take it anymore.
- Do a good job while I'm still smiling.
- Yes, I'll work very hard!
- If you want to live, then win this round.
- He's acting very differently.
- You should listen to your honey.
- Ready.
[Thread of fate- Round three.]
- This is our last chance!
- Fighting!
[Wow, lightning fast speed!]
[Quickly acclimated to the muddy
field in just one round.]
[Kang Nam, Min Gyo and Jae Rim-
First ones to arrive.]
Can't you run any faster?
[Even unravels the thread
at a faster speed.]
- You can go slower.
- You're going too fast!
[Dong Min's the only one taking his time.]
[Kang Nam's monstrous screams.]
[Gae Eun and Kang Nam are first
to finish unraveling the thread.]
[Hana follows Gae Eun's lead.]
Steven Segal!
[Is Gae Eun Steven Segal's
doppelganger?]
- He's right behind you.
- Steven Segal!
[Hana's dead run.]
[The two shorties fight for it.]
- Good job, Steven Segal!
- You have to jump for it.
- Ji Hyo's coming!
- Stop her!
[Ji Hyo and Kwang Ja join the group.]
You have to watch out for Kwang Ja!
[Kwang Ja succeeds!]
[Kwang Ja and Jae Rim win
the third round!]
That's too bad, Steven Segal.
You were talking to me?
I'm Steven Segal?
- You were talking to me?
- Here, you can eat it.
[Kwang Ja and Jae Rim
win third place.]
The winning couples will now come
forward in the order of their winning
and choose one of the threads of fate
that are tied to the scarecrows' wrists
and place your team's name card
in front of the dolls that you like.
- These threads must mean something.
- This one is...
Do we have to cut it off?
[Six threads of fate that are
bound to the scarecrows' wrists...]
[These threads' unexpected twist of fate!]
[The sorrowful fate that
their decision will bring...]
[What is the great hidden mystery
behind these threads?]
Do you think they're going to tie
something to our wrists later on?
- That's what I think, too.
- Do they always think out loud like this?
They do think out loud,
but they're never right about it.
- We're always wrong.
- They're just guessing.
This may actually be for the better.
[Just what is the meaning
of these scarecrows?]
Let's just go with this one.
Don't you think elastic would be better?
Why are you even asking when you're
just going to do as you want anyway?
I didn't think you'd have an opinion.
You're going to do what
you want anyway.
[Jae Soon and Suk Jin - rubber.]
Okay, the couple that
came in at second place.
- I don't know what this is about.
- My honey will decide.
That's not what you call him
because you're not going to marry him.
I can call him whatever
I want to call him.
[I'm going to call my girl
whatever I want.]
Why are you telling my man what to do?
Honey, which one would you like?
- Which one should we choose?
- Choose whichever one you'd like.
- But tell me what you're thinking.
- If you and I were to get tied up together...
- I think the metal would be the best.
- Don't you think that'd be too heavy?
You're probably right.
[Soo Hong immediately changes his mind
and agrees with Jong Sook.]
- What do you think about that one?
- I think that will be perfect.
- But why are there two similar ones?
- Just make up your mind!
Hurry up!
I'm so sick and tired of this!
- We'll take that one.
- Okay.
[Jong Sook and Soo Hong
select the hiking rope.]
- Okay, third place.
- Third place winners.
[Kwang Ja and Jae Rim's
turn to choose.]
I want my male honey to choose
whichever one you'd like.
What?
Male honey?
Do you want a beating?
I think I like this one.
Let's go with this one.
[Jae Rim selects the laundry rope
without consulting his partner.]
- That's going to snap right away.
- You can trust me on this one.
[The remaining couples can select
from the rest on their own.]
We don't know what this even means,
so this will either be the best or the worst.
Okay, then let's go with this one.
We're selecting this one.
- Let's go with this one.
- Okay.
[Gae Eun and Kang Nam select
the polypropylene rope.]
[Hana and Min Gyo select
the plastic string.]
- Where were you?
- Sorry, partner.
I had to go to the bathroom.
[Kindly attaches her name tag
onto her back.]
[With their hands tightly held...]
[Being together with Ji Hyo today...
is heaven.]
- What's wrong with him?
- Are you serious?
- Seriously, Dong Min.
- He's smiling from ear to ear.
- Are you in love with her?
- I've never seen him smiling like that.
[Together with their partners
on this crisp fall day...]
- He's too big for me.
- Who is?
[Jong Sook and her big muscles...]
The best spot to hold him by
is around his ribcage.
- His ribcage?
- His muscles provide a handle.
[My girl's unique
latissimus dorsi handle.]
I can hear your joints cracking
every time you swing your arms.
Is something wrong with your arms?
Do you hear the cracking too?
Yes, I feel it too.
I wonder what's wrong with it.
[The final 12 survivors-
Where are they being taken to?]
Your joints sound like old creaking doors.
Isn't this a huge bird cage?
This is to test the men's chivalry
and the women's loyalty.
This mission is
'Princess name tag elimination'.
Princess name tag elimination?
This is Kim Jong Kook's game!
- How is this my game?
- You're saying that it's not?
Two couples at a time will go into this
birdcage and play name tag elimination.
It's great weather for some
name tag elimination.
- For yours to be eliminated, maybe.
- Maybe you're right.
[Let's do our best, Jae Rim.]
It doesn't matter if the men's
name tag gets eliminated.
The woman's name tag must get
eliminated in order to win.
[Must eliminate the woman's name tag
in order to win the mission.]
What if I were to rip off
the woman's nose?
Why would you rip off their nose?
[This is the Dong Min
they're more used to.]
And food will be the prize to win
at each mission.
The winning couple will take the food
they won and move onto the next round.
Which means the amount of food
will keep adding up.
All the food will then be on the line for
the final round of name tag elimination.
[The final winning couple
will win all the food supplies.]
- No wonder you haven't fed us yet.
- That isn't all either.
Remember the rope that you
all had to choose?
The winning couple will also be given
the chance to swap it out
so the winning couple can earn all
the ropes and food supplies as well.
You'll see a diagram behind you,
and the final two slots in the end.
The two couples to land in those slots will
move on immediately to the final round.
You can decide amongst yourselves which two
couples will end up there on your own.
Then how about we keep it
simple like this?
The men can grab tightly onto
each other's hands like this
and the ones to scream out in pain first
will be the first to get eliminated.
- Sure, let's do that.
- How does that sound?
- Is that okay with everyone?
- Just between men?
- Get ready!
- First person to lose goes over there?
Kang Nam, you have to
win this no matter what.
- Get ready.
- Dong Jin, fighting!
- Ready!
- Is everyone ready?
I'm going to endure it even if
this game shatters my hand!
[Game to move onto the final round-
Don't scream out in pain!]
[Wicked Jang grits down on his teeth.]
- You have to endure the pain!
- I like that expression on your face.
- You look really cute.
- Endure it!
You look really cute right now.
[I shall endure through this pain.]
Even talking will get you eliminated.
- Endure it!
- Squeeze harder!
- You can do it!
- Min Gyo's almost there.
- We can't be eliminated already!
- Squeeze harder!
- I can see Suk Jin's almost there!
- I can see Suk Jin's almost there.
- You almost have him.
[Jae Soon and Suk Jin are eliminated.]
[I eliminated him.]
You can take a quick break.
Let go and take a quick break.
[Jong Sook, that hurts so bad...]
[Strength of Ji Hyo keeps me strong.]
[I will endure through
this pain for Gae Eun.]
Endure through it just a bit longer.
You're almost done.
Look at how nice my veins are.
[This man is bragging about how
good his veins are looking.]
This time, you'll grab and tug on
each other's sideburn hair.
- Hey, you can't do that.
- You have to endure the pain.
- Wow, he's really evil.
- Get ready.
I'm sorry to ask this, but what if I pull
too hard and rip off their skin?
There's no need to pull that hard.
You just have to win this round.
[With their pride on the line,
they'll sacrifice their sideburns.]
[This is for my woman...]
- Fighting, Dong Min!
- Ready... set, go!
[Round two- Sideburn tugging.]
[Jong Sook and Soo Hong are eliminated.]
[Even with Soo Hong's elimination,
the battle still continues on.]
You can't pull it out like that.
No, wait!
Why are you doing this to me!
[Ji Hyo, I endured through
the pain for your love.]
Kang Nam is eliminated.
- No, this isn't right!
- No, you're eliminated.
- This isn't even a show!
- Wait, I think you're missing hair.
- Why do you shave your sideburns?
- You're already eliminated.
You're the one who
suggested this game, right?
Come here.
Do you know how badly that hurts?
[I can endure this sort of agony...]
[I'm a man who isn't afraid of
self-sacrifice for my woman!]
- You're doing great, honey!
- This time, it'll be a tickle game.
You can do this.
How about we throw this in
the air and head butt it?
Okay, next will be a tickling game.
[Jong Sook will demonstrate how
to tickle the right way.]
[Jae Soon doesn't even last a second.]
- Soo Hong, you give it a try.
- I'm not ticklish in the least.
I'm seriously not ticklish.
Not at all.
It's a different sort of ticklish.
[I never want to do that again.]
He was literally convulsing.
It's a new dance!
[Kwang Ja's shake dance.]
[Tickling Ms. Capable-
Jong Sook's magic fingers.]
[Round three- Tickling game.
First contestant- Min Gyo.]
Wait, what is it?
[Starts giggling at the slightest touch.]
I don't know if it's because of the show
he does, but he looks so natural at this.
Min Gyo, can you do that thing you do?
[Our Min Gyo is so cute.]
[Hana and Min Gyo are a match
made in heaven.]
Ready, set, go!
[The tickling game- Start.]
[Oh!
He's enduring through it!]
[His eyes are about to
pop out of his head.]
- You're doing great.
- You're enduring it pretty well.
[He's slowly getting there.]
- How many seconds?
- 11 seconds.
[Hana and Min Gyo- 11 seconds.]
- He endured that pretty well.
- I need to get under the vest.
- Ready...
- He looks like such a grump.
[A total Mr. Grump.]
[Dong Min collapses down to the ground.]
Just laugh.
Let go and just laugh out loud.
- Dong Min, just laugh.
- Are they wrestling?
[It's okay to laugh, Dong Min.]
Just laugh!
[Grumpy Jang endures through the tickling...]
[and lashes out.]
17 seconds.
[Ji Hyo and Dong Min- 17 seconds.
Moves onto the final round.]
I think all my ribs are broken.
[Good job, honey.]
- Honey, you have to endure through it!
- He just has to last longer than 11 seconds.
[Last longer than 11 seconds
to move onto the final round.]
[Looking so at peace.]
- Keep thinking sad thoughts.
- Wow, he's handling it pretty well.
[He's even shedding fake tears.]
- Wow, I know how ticklish that is.
- He's no joke.
[What a frightening scoundrel...]
- You're doing great.
- How many seconds?
You passed 17 seconds!
That hurts!
[Kwang Ja and Jae Rim win the tickling
game and move onto the final round.]
[Round one- Jae Soon and Suk Jin
vs Jong Sook and Soo Hong.]
[Right before the start of the
princess name tag elimination game.]
I have to keep my hands moist
to help with the name tag ripping.
- You have to keep your hands moist.
- That's not true.
[Jong Sook and Soo Hong busy
themselves with their hand cream.]
Look at how at ease they are
by applying hand cream.
The first food item in the
princess name tag elimination is...
- I will now reveal the food item.
- Okay.
- That would be do good right now.
- It's perfect to eat on an empty stomach.
What is it?
[First food item-
Cup ramen and kimchi.]
- That would be perfect right now.
- That looks so good.
[Let's win and eat it!]
Which spot do you think you'd be
most comfortable lying down at?
You just worry about yourself.
But I'd prefer being in the sun.
- I feel like I'm in the UFC.
- Let's get this started.
Look at the glint in his eyes.
I'm so scared!
[Let's get warmed up a bit.]
[The final 12 survivors-
Battle over survival essential- Food.]
[Princess name tag elimination-
Jae Soon, Suk Jin vs Jong Sook, Soo Hong.]
- He's done if he steps away from Jong Kook.
- You have to step up front.
[My girl, Jong Sook, will protect me.]
[Must eliminate Jong Sook's name tag.]
[I've got you now!]
This is way too easy.
[Time to go get Jae Soon.]
[Save me!]
It's been a while since we've run
around like this together, Jae Soon.
What the heck?
[Jong Sook has Suk Jin in his clutches.]
[If Soo Hong can eliminate Jae Soon,
then they can win this round.]
[The hand on the name tag!]
[Succeeds on first try.]
[Jong Sook and Soo Hong
wins the first round.]
- You're really good.
- Ugh, I'm so mad!
I'm a man!
- I'm so mad!
- He's my man.
[Jong Sook and Soo Hong win
the ramen and kimchi.]
For round two, it's Gae Eun and
Kang Nam vs Hana and Min Gyo.
[Round two- Gae Eun and Kang Nam
vs Hana and Min Gyo.]
- Min Gyo!
- Fighting!
It's kimbap and hard boiled eggs!
[Second food item-
Hard boiled eggs and kimbap.]
- We have to win this one.
- Fighting!
Would it be better for me to stand
up front or in the back?
[Min Gyo hugs Hana from behind
to keep his name tag protected.]
Round two!
Set, go!
[Round two- Hana and Min Gyo
vs Gae Eun and Kang Nam.]
That's not a bad idea either.
Grab Gae Eun.
[Hana and Min Gyo show the perfect way
to keep the princess' name tag protected.]
We should've done it like that too.
I'm going to do it like that, too.
[On first attempt?]
[A fiery battle right from the start.]
Wow, they're really ferocious.
[A tight battle where the winner
still remains to be seen.]
- This is really entertaining to watch.
- The first round was no fun at all.
What are you talking about?
I had a lot of fun.
- You got it!
- You got it, just grab it!
[Gae Eun and Kang Nam are separated.]
[While Kang Nam's name tag
was being ripped off...]
[Hana and Min Gyo's eyes
are on Gae Eun's name tag only.]
Put the name tag back on,
and get back in the game!
- I got him!
- He's got him!
[Kang Nam gets his hand on
Ha Ha's name tag!]
[Kang Nam eliminates the name tag!]
[Eliminates Hana's name tag
in the blink of an eye!]
[Princess name tag elimination- Round two.
Gae Eun and Kang Nam wins.]
PD, are there any games
that are just all about luck?
Are there any games where we
have to crawl into small spaces?
Are there any games like that?
- Is everything based on strength?
- Anything that we can win at?
[Will kiddos Hana and Min Gyo
get their chance to shine?]
[Semi-finals: Gae Eun, Kang Nam
vs Jong Sook, Soo Hong.]
[Rule change- Must now
eliminate both the name tags.]
We have to eliminate Soo Hong first
for us to have a chance to win.
Don't take him too lightly.
We don't know how it'll end
because how name tags are so big.
Wait a minute.
Why do you keep putting on
so much hand lotion?
- I can't grab if my hands are dry.
- He's putting on Vaseline!
- That shouldn't be allowed.
- They can't be allowed to use that.
- Why do you keep putting lotion on?
- I can't grab it if my hands are dry.
You have to be smart about it.
[Semi-finals: Jong Sook, Soo Hong
vs Gae Eun, Kang Nam.]
Be careful.
- He's quick as a cat.
- We have to surround them.
Stop spinning around.
I'm getting confused.
- You told me to spin around.
- But I'm starting to get confused.
You're not walking in circles together,
but you're being chased around in circles.
- We're not walking around?
- You think you are, don't you?
[Matching hunter,
Jong Sook's footsteps.]
- Wow, he has really long arms.
- Yes, he has really long arms.
[I'm going to get all of you!]
[Wait, that's his teammate,
Kang Nam's name tag?]
[Ousts his own team member.]
[Gae Eun eliminates his own teammate,
Kang Nam's name tag!]
[Completely befuddled.]
What are you doing!
[Thank you, Gae Eun.]
Why would you eliminate my name tag!
I was just trying to help...
[First time ever on RM that someone
eliminates his own partner's name tag.]
[Thanks to that,
our workload is lessened.]
- A lover's quarrel!
- Let us do that again.
[It's a cutthroat game,
and water under the bridge.]
[Gae Eun's teammate, Kang Nam is out.]
- This isn't even right!
- Gary was really fast.
[Current score-
Jong Sook, Soo Hong:1 vs Gae Eun:1.]
- You can't do that.
- This isn't right.
Gae Eun!
- Gae Eun!
- Wait! My arm!
[A very sad ending-
His shirt gets stretched out to no end.]
[Ugh... my frustrating Gae Eun...]
I can't believe Gae Eun
eliminated his own partner.
What were you thinking, Gae Eun?
[Finals- Ji Hyo, Dong Min
vs Jong Sook, Soo Hong.]
This is the final round and all the food
that's been earned so far is in that basket.
The winner takes all the food as well as
the chance to swap out their ropes.
[The winner has the chance at a swap.]
You're mine, Grumpy.
[Grumpy Jang,
I've been waiting for this moment.]
[Muscle Jong Sook, I'm the new name in town
when it comes to name tag elimination.]
[Highly charged battlefield.]
- I wonder what'll happen.
- Ji Hyo shouldn't be taken lightly.
I'll grab Dong Min.
[Jong Sook and Soo Hong's plan-
Jong Sook vs Dong Min.]
[With Soo Hong vs. Ji Hyo.]
No need to tiptoe around Ji Hyo.
[I will protect Ji Hyo.]
- Why are you trying to act cool?
- Stay back! I'll take care of this.
- Stop that! It doesn't suit you.
- Just stay behind me!
[Ji Hyo's own personal bodyguard.]
- Hey, you're known for being grumpy!
- This is nothing like you!
[Grumpy Jang, shall we do this?]
[Jong Sook starts approaching closer.]
Where do you think you're grabbing!
I don't know what to do.
I'm so sorry.
[Eliminates each other's name tag
simultaneously?]
[While Soo Hong was taking
his sweet time...]
[Ji Hyo eliminates his name tag first!]
[Soo Hong, out!]
[Ji Hyo and Dong Min vs Jong Sook-
It's two against one!]
[If we combine our strength,
then we just may beat Jong Sook!]
[Jong Sook vs Dong Min and Ji Hyo-
The pivotal moment!]
[By the split of a hair, Jong Sook
eliminates Ji Hyo's name tag first!]
[That's our Mr. Capable!]
- It's only Dong Min now?
- Did you see how he ripped it off?
Honey, just kill him.
[The only two left now are...
Muscle Jong Sook and Grumpy Jang.]
[The last two survivors final showdown.]
- Wow, Grumpy is no joke either!
- Come here.
- You can do this!
[A fierce battle of strength.]
Teach him a stiff lesson!
- I feel so bad for him!
- The poor thing!
[Grumpy Jang is rendered helpless.]
[Stay strong, Dong Min.]
[Will this be the end for Grumpy Jang?]
Jong Sook, just finish him already!
- I'm going get you!
- Just finish him, Jong Sook.
[What...]
I'm going to rip it off!
How dare you put your hands on that!
[Immediately flustered.]
- That's the Grumpy I know!
- You're finally being yourself.
[Grumpy Jang finally shows
his wretched personality?]
- My chest...
- What about your chest?
- I don't think I can breathe.
He says he can't breathe.
Dong Min!
Just let him rip it off!
- I said, I can't breathe.
- Why can't you breathe?
I said, I can't breathe!
[Rage-filled reaction.]
[The biggest challenge Mr. Capable
has ever had to face?]
That's the Dong Min I know.
- Playing dirty is just your style.
- You're the filthiest player ever.
[Jang Dong Min- out.]
[Explosion of rage.]
Dong Min, you really are something else.
[Fits of rage and outcry.]
Show us how angry you are, Dong Min.
I'm going to rip it off!
[King of dirty tricks, Grumpy Jang.]
I've never seen such dirty plays in
all fours years of doing Running Man.
This was my favorite part.
'Ugh, I can't breathe...'
[After the show of inability to breathe...
lunges out in fit of rage.]
He undoubtedly is Mr. Capable.
- Here it comes.
- That all belongs to you guys?
[Jong Sook and Soo Hong wins
essential food supplies.]
- You can take all of it.
- We're hungry, too!
I know everyone's hungry, but
we're going to eat this by ourselves.
You can take the food for yourselves.
[Bonus round of name tag elimination
for the chance to win two cans of coffee.]
[Min Gyo vs Jae Soon vs Jae Rim
vs Kang Nam vs Dong Min.]
[Simultaneous name tag elimination-
Start.]
I'm the only girl in here.
- Get rid of the girl first.
- You should partner up.
[Partner up?]
[Everyone's target- Jae Soon.]
[Barely escapes Min Gyo,
only to be grasped by Dong Min.]
[Yoo Jae Soon successfully
escapes danger.]
[Everyone's fired up.]
Jae Rim, just stay back
and stop getting involved!
[4D Jae Rim is totally whipped
by Kwang Ja.]
[A man's fate depends on the woman-
Kwang Ja's incessant nagging.]
[Min Gyo slowly makes his way
towards Dong Min.]
[Now's the chance!]
[Min Gyo- out!]
[Dong Min and Jae Rim are still
at a standoff.]
[Both grab at the same time!]
[Dong Min- out!]
- There was a rock.
- Ouch, what the heck!
Hey, are you okay?
[Grumpy Jang is just nonstop riot.]
[It's now Kang Nam vs Jae Soon
vs Jae Rim.]
[I can't lose!
The coffee is right in front of my eyes!]
I think they're partnering up right now.
Pick the wrong partner,
and you could be on the losing end.
[Jae Soon gets cornered,
and Jae Rim attacks first.]
[Now's the chance!
Kang Nam jumps in.]
Kang Nam, you have to
get to his back!
Wow, Yoo Jae Suk!
[Spins a full round and
eliminates Jae Rim's name tag.]
[Song Jae Rim- Out!]
- Jae Suk's really fast.
- What's his deal?
[The final showdown-
Jae Soon vs Kang Nam.]
- You can't defeat a cast member.
- Use this if you need to!
[The king of dirty tricks.]
What's the rock for?
How am I going to do this?
How am I going to win?
You have to rip it off.
You have to rip off my name tag.
- You have to rip off my name tag.
- Don't retreat and just go for it!
It's just canned coffee!
Just do it already!
Wait, this is a very serious battle for us!
- This is very serious for us.
- I hate losing!
I'll buy everyone a
round of Americano coffee.
[Canned coffee is no big deal.]
You're just exhausting yourselves.
[Back to the game on hand.]
We have to end this right now.
All this over canned coffee?
[There's no more time left to waste.]
- What are you doing?
- I have to get your name tag.
[It's in his hand!]
[Canned coffee battle-
The final winner is...]
[Jae Soon.]
[Jae Soon's quick hand ousts
a total of three opponents.]
Five years' worth of skills
is on a different level.
[Jae Soon and Suk Jin win
the canned coffee challenge.]
Let's have all the winners
go up against one another.
- What are you talking about?
- He and I can duke it out now.
That's why it's important
to meet the right woman.
Ouch, that's hot.
Is this a punishment or what?
[Jae Soon and Suk Jin win? the coffee.]
We'll start with the third place winners.
Kang Nam and Gae Eun will be given
the chance to swap out their rope.
I think it'll be good
to have something stretchy.
Let's go for the rubber rope.
We're going to swap it out for this.
See?
They swapped it out for ours.
I think the rubber one
is going to be advantageous.
I'm going to follow her wishes.
- They act like they're getting married.
- We'll take this one.
[Swaps it out for Gae Eun and
Kang Nam's recently swapped rubber rope.]
Why did it have to be
the metal chain of all things?
I'm sorry, Gary.
- Let's trade it out for Hana's?
- We're so hungry.
Let's swap Hana and Min Gyo's with
Jae Soon and Suk Jin's.
[Hana and Min Gyo's plastic tie
with Jae Soon and Suk Jin's hiking rope.]
[I can't stand to see Jae Soon doing well.]
- You're such a dirty player.
- Why would you swap ours out?
You seriously are such a dirty player.
[First round selection]
[Second round selection]
[Just what is the purpose of these ropes?]
[Time to eat the cup ramen we just won.]
Are you seriously going to eat
that by yourself in front of all of us?
Why would I eat this?
I'll give it to the hard worker.
- He doesn't eat ramen.
- Seriously?
[But eats the egg in one bite.]
Can I get one of those eggs in here?
Never mind, I'll just eat it like this.
- I'm not a huge fan of eggs anyway.
- Here, you can eat this.
That looks so good.
- Wow, that's the best.
- That looks so awesome.
- Why would you get that on film?
- It's like my own cooking show.
[Park Soo Hong's cooking Korea-
Final 12 survivor's essential ramen.]
- Want some coffee in there?
- Wow, that looks so good.
- How am I going to eat all this?
I can't stand to watch it!
Watching him eat is like torture.
Is it good?
Does it taste good?
- Aren't you going to have any kimchi?
- I'm so hungry right now.
If you're not eating the kimchi,
then can we have it?
[Yeah... this is the stuff.]
[A bite of kimchi, too.]
[Eyes are transfixed.]
- Let's play for a sip of the broth.
- Okay, let's do it.
[One sip of the broth,
and a hardboiled egg.]
Rock, paper, scissors.
[Hana and Min Gyo win.]
[This is the best.]
- I really want some ramen.
- It's a perfect meal on a morning like this.
With this crisp weather...
- I can't stand this.
- I can't stand watching them eat.
[A strand of noodle in his mouth!]
[This is Hana's way of survival.]
[Final 12 survivors-
Survival mission three.]
What's this?
[What is the next survival mission
that awaits these members?]
- Thank you all for coming.
- Sure.
It's the group tug of war.
[Survival mission three-
Group tug of war.]
It's another strength based mission!
- Don't you have any luck based missions?
- Don't you think you're being too harsh?
- This is unfair.
- The world is about to end.
So it's all about
survival of the fittest.
It all comes down to strength.
- Don't you agree?
- What are you even saying?
I want all the writers on the ground
for a little beating.
[Grumpy Jang is back!]
He definitely is a grump.
The men will tie a rope around
their waists
and relay the item given to their female
partners before the opposing couples.
Do the women have to just stand still?
Then Jong Kook won't participate?
The partners receiving the items
will stand behind the table.
With the items given,
the partners will have to build a pile.
Then first person to complete the pile must
stand with their arms in the air to win.
You can relay only one item at a time.
- This looks so good.
- You can't throw it either.
[Men compete with the rope tying.]
- I'm coming, honey!
- Fighting, honey.
- Jae Rim, fighting!
- Fighting!
[Clementine for my sweetie- Start!]
[Where do you think you're going?]
You dropped your clementine!
[While everyone's busy rolling around...]
[Min Gyo alone manages to
get the job done.]
[Dong Min regains his balance right away
and makes another attempt.]
[Small but sweet couple takes the lead.]
Honey, get up!
[I wish I could get up, too.]
[While Jae Rim and Suk Jin are
still left struggling...]
[Soo Hong makes a move.]
[Successfully relays a clementine.]
[Jong Sook already gets two clementines.]
Don't give up and get up!
You're not a weird person!
- My rib cage!
- You're almost there!
Hurry, honey!
[Big-nose successfully
relays one clementine.]
- What do I do? This one is busted.
- Just give it to me.
- This clementine...
- Hurry!
[Everyone musters up their strength
to get the clementine to their girls.]
Honey!
[Current count of clementines.]
[Min Gyo and his unexpected strength.
Relays fourth clementine already.]
[Soo Hong also successfully
relays three clementines.]
[Must build a pile with four
clementines to win the mission.]
[Oh!
Now must last three seconds!]
[It topples over!]
[This is our chance!]
How did you get it over there?
[Hana hurries to put the pile
back together.]
You can do this!
[Who will win?]
[Four tiered pile is complete!]
[Must last for three seconds to win!]
[Hana and Min Gyo wins.]
[Clementine pile lasts
exactly three seconds.]
[Tiny couple's completely unexpected win!]
Yes, we won!
We won!
- Wow, Min Gyo's really strong.
- Wow, you're the best.
My shoe!
[Jae Rim's shoe is destroyed in
his efforts to win the battle.]
- Wow, what happened in the beginning?
- I was snapped back.
[Min Gyo ultimately wins for having
withstood the beginning.]
[This is really good.]
Staying low and strong... I can do that,
but I can't do anything up high.
[Sexy victory ceremony.]
Do you want to see me collapse?
[Hana and Min Gyo earn the selection
rights for coming in at first place.]
The next round will determine
who comes in at second place.
The women will take a turn
at rope pulling.
This game is purely for
Jong Sook's benefit.
- You already had your chance.
- Can I have someone stand in for me?
[Blank Ji's knight in shining armor-
Dong Min steps in.]
- Dong Min can step in for her.
- Okay, I'm going to win this time.
- Jong Kook is no joke.
- I'll beat him.
Next item for the pile is...
five tiered yogurt pile.
[Round two-
Five tiered yogurt pile.]
Fighting, honey!
[You can trust me, honey.]
- You'd better plan this right.
- I don't care who wins.
This is for the second place win.
Set, go!
[As soon as the game starts...]
[Jong Sook pulls with the strength
of three men combined.]
[Pull!]
[The plan succeeds!
Pulling over to this side.]
[Just then...]
My shoe!
[Jong Sook loses his shoe.]
[Jae Soon successfully relays one
thanks to their partnership.]
[Lucky chance!
Jong Sook gets pulled along!]
Jong Sook's down on the ground!
[What great timing!
Gae Eun successfully hands one over.]
[Hands over his second yogurt.]
[Previously confident Dong Min is...]
[Jae Soon and Suk Jin drop
one of their yogurts.]
They're no help at all!
Just forget the partnership!
- I can't do this anymore!
- Stay strong, honey!
- What's wrong with your shoe?
- It keeps coming off!
- Why are you acting unlike yourself?
- My shoe!
[Knight in shining armor, Dong Min,
is also going barefoot.]
Kwang Ja, if you'll help us,
we can help each other get four.
[Offers to help each other relay
four yogurts each.]
What do you think, Jae Soon?
We can help each other get four.
[Jae Soon and Suk Jin offers to help
Kwang Ja get four if he helps them out...]
Okay, let's go over to my table now.
[Already has four yogurts.]
[Retracts on their promise and
attempts to relay the fifth one.]
Come here!
What are you guys doing!
[Taking advantage of Kwang Ja and
Jae Soon, Jong Sook forges ahead.]
Now's your chance!
[Everyone topples to the ground
from Jong Sook's single pull.]
One at a time.
There you go, you got it!
You're like a Hercules... girl.
Hurry!
[Hercules girl?]
[Makes his delivery all at once!]
Now's your chance!
[Thanks to Jong Sook's pull,
Dong Min's also able to hand his over.]
Give it to me now.
[Gae Eun escapes the partnership and
successfully hands all five over.]
[Meanwhile...]
[Jae Soon and Kwang Ja are still
duking it out.]
You guys have to work together!
[Finally manages to get up...]
[This way!]
[Kwang Ja finally hands his first one over.]
One more!
- Just give him one!
- You've got it!
[The team to get all five tiers first and
last for three seconds wins the mission.]
How am I going to stack these?
[Yogurt pile isn't as easy as it looks.]
[Soo Hong, Kang Nam and
Ji Hyo's race to the finish line.]
They already have their five!
Bring me my last one!
[Jae Soon and Suk Jin just
need one more...]
[Successfully hands in his last one.]
- Hey! Why are you shaking it?
- Just flip the table over!
- Just flip it over.
- Can you hand me my yogurt?
- Hand me my yogurt!
- Hurry up.
[Just then, Blank Ji completes her pile!]
[But it doesn't last the three seconds.]
[With the different top and bottom ratio,
it's hard to find the balance.]
[Just who will be the first?]
Just hurry.
[Suk Jin flips every other one over to
match the size of the base!]
[Who will be the first to successfully
build the five tiered pile?]
[Chance to swap out the rope
is balanced on the line!]
[Big-nose finishes building his pile first.]
[Must last for three seconds.]
[Jae Soon and Suk Jin win!]
[So close...]
[Big-nose's flipped pile succeeds!]
- Good job, Jae Soon.
- Kwang Ja...
Thanks, Kwang Ja.
Why do we only get used
and cast aside?
- Thanks, Kwang Ja.
- We won thanks to you.
[Kwang Ja got completely used.]
Kwang Ja, we won thanks to you.
It's a very cruel world.
- I'm sorry.
- No, it's okay.
You looked really pretty while
trying to build the tier.
Ji Suk Jin and Yoo Jae Soon
win second place.
Okay, this is your final chance.
This will be the final chance for the three
winning couples to make their swap.
- We'll start with third place winners.
- I have no idea what this is for.
[What is the mystery behind these ropes?]
[A mind battle to swap out not only theirs,
but those of their opponents as well.]
[An unexpected twist from the tiny couple
who has been on the losing end all day!]
He's Korea's Tom Cruise.
[Jong Sook and Soo Hong's selection.]
[Jong Kook and Soo Hong swapped it out for
Hana and Min Gyo after the previous mission.]
[Swaps theirs out for Hana and Min Gyo's.]
[Let's help each other out.]
Okay, we're going to make our swap.
[Jae Soon and Suk Jin.]
[Swaps theirs out for Jong Sook
and Soo Hong's without even hesitating.]
- That was a good move.
- I know that they're up to something.
Remember what I did for you earlier?
Remember that.
I seriously set it up so that
you don't even have to do anything.
- You know what I mean, right?
- They helped us out earlier, didn't they?
- Just do what's right for you, not them.
- They helped out to make it easier for us.
- Yes, we helped you out on purpose.
- We gave you the best case scenario.
You saw what they just
did to us, didn't you?
This is the final game.
Helping them is going to make you lose.
- Think about our relationship.
- Ha Ha, this is the best one.
Do we have a relationship with them?
- We helped you guys out earlier!
- You're so cold hearted.
[Cold hearted Min Gyo places Jong Sook
and Soo Hong in front of the metal chain.]
Thank you!
[Completely unexpected results.]
[But just what is the meaning
of these ropes?]
[Off to the final mission site.]
- What is it?
- It's a rescue boat!
[A row of rescue boats are lined up
at the end of the dock.]
You're not expecting us to
row over to Yeouido, are you?
- The final 12 survivors.
- Yes.
I will now tell you the final mission of
how to escape this island.
I really want to escape.
Here's your final mission.
Unravel the twisted fate.
[Final mission-
Unravel the twisted fate.]
So the thinnest rope would've
been the best?
There are six different types of ropes
that are tied up to the boat in front of you.
Even though the way they're twisted up
together is similar to your fates
the team that successfully unravels
the tangle first wins the entire race.
I think our rope may be the easiest.
The rubber is going to be really hard.
Ours is the one at the end.
Which one was ours?
Is it the metal chain over there?
Ours is the metal chain.
[Just which team will be the first
to unravel the tangled mess?]
If you break the rope,
then you fail immediately.
Please be careful while unraveling it,
and you know what your mission is?
Get started!
[Final survival mission- Start.]
Tell me what to do because
I don't know what I'm doing.
We have to just unravel it.
No explanations are necessary.
We just have to unravel it.
Once you get it all untangled,
lift up your boat above your heads!
[First team to lift up the boat after
unraveling wins the race.]
[These were done by knot experts.]
How do I do this one?
[Sense of urgency...
but not unraveling as they want.]
Why did they knot it so tightly?
Wow, they went too far.
Okay, I got this one.
[Hana and Min Gyo's thick rope
seems to be the easiest.]
We got it.
We got this.
[Jae Soon and Suk Jin's rope
is on the easier side as well.]
- Let go, you can't hold onto it.
- Hold it on this side.
- Let go for a second.
- I think there's a method to this.
Someone knew what they
were doing.
[Does Jae Rim know something
about knots?]
I used to love tying knots.
Wow, Jae Rim's really good at this!
- Okay, I got this. I love you, Min Gyo.
- We're going to win this.
[Hana and Min Gyo are making progress
through the strength of their love?]
See?
They're getting it so fast.
[They can't even get a good grip
on the metal chain.]
- Wow, look at this knot.
- I can't believe they did this to us.
- I got this unraveled.
- You did?
[Dong Min says he unraveled it...
but it's not looking like it.]
- I'll give it a try.
- I need to find something sharp.
[Dong Min leaves the knot to Ji Hyo
and steps away to find something sharp.]
- How did they tie it up like this?
- A knotting expert did this.
- An expert did this.
- Let go, you can't keep holding onto it.
[Big-nose keeps holding onto the rope
without really helping anything.]
We're at an advantage with this.
We have to unravel this too.
- This is good.
- Let go, Big-nose.
They knotted this so tight!
[Who will be the first to successfully
unravel all the knots?]
They're almost done already!
[Hana and Min Gyo's knots are
coming to a complete unravel.]
Oh my goodness.
I got so lucky with my man.
[Hana throws down his wig in
his efforts to unravel the knots.]
I'd still love you even if you were bald.
- They're almost done already!
- We're almost done, too.
[Kwang Ja and Jae Rim's rope becomes
unraveled with Jae Rim's expertise.]
[Jae Soon and Suk Jin are
also getting close.]
[Meanwhile, this team is still
struggling with their knots.]
[As well as this team.]
I think we need to get this one first
before we can unravel that one.
[Hana and Min Gyo vs Jae Rim and Kwang Ja
vs Jae Soon and Suk Jin.]
[A race against time
between these three teams!]
Just pull it!
[Just who will get it first?]
Just let go and come lift this!
We got it done, right?
[Which couple will unravel their twisted fate
to be the first to escape this island?]
[Hana and Min Gyo get to their boat first!]
Lift it above your head!
[Hana and Min Gyo win!]
[We may be tiny,
but we still did it!]
[How can this be?]
[The tiny couple wins by
the split of a hair!]
We're going to be able to
have our baby after all!
I'm going to be able to
give you your baby!
We were so close.
Wow, that was really hard.
[Who cares about winning
when I can get a hug?]
- Wow, we were so close.
- Ha Ha and Min Gyo win the race.
[Hana and Min Gyo are
the final surviving couple.]
[And awaiting these escapees...
is the sweetest fate of them all.]
[Delicious cakes and baked goods with
aromatic coffee to top it off.]
- Can we really eat this?
- Yes, help yourselves.
['K' cafe in Daebangyeok.]
[Survival celebration gift to the last
remaining members of the human race.]
- We can really eat this?
- Yes, you can.
Wow, this one is really good.
- This is good.
- It's really good.
It's cheese and chocolate together.
We have a special dessert for Hana
and Min Gyo for winning the race.
Thank you!
It's just for the two of you.
Wow, that looks really good.
What's this!
[There's something inside the cake!]
It's a gold ring?
[Oh my god.]
It's a gold ring.
[Cleans it off real well
with his tongue first.]
Honey.
I'm really happy right now.
Hana's so happy right now.
Hana wants to...
[The last surviving tiny couple
lived happily ever after.]
And we also have something special
for Soo Hong's birthday today.
[A surprise birthday cake.]
It's not a happy birthday.
Happy celebration to you...
Why do you always have
to ruin my mood!
Happy birthday to you,
happy birthday, dear Soo Hong...
Happy birthday celebrations to you.
- Happy birthday.
- Hope you get married this year.
Thank you.
Want to marry me?
One, two, three.
- Thank you so much.
- Maybe there's a gold ring in there too.
- Check for a gold ring.
- Maybe there's one in there too.
[Could there be a gold ring
in there, too?]
I'm sorry, but there isn't one.
Just eat the cake.
[Thank you to our guests for
coming on the show and participating.]
Subtitles by DramaFever
- Would you like for me to sing you a song?
- Do you like music?
[They'll sing whatever you'd like.]
[From idols to rockers-
All the nation's best singers.]
[We are coming to you live!
The biggest even you've ever seen.]
- Are you a good singer?
- I sing as well as a neighborhood dog.
[Grueling training to become
the king of the event.]
[What will become of
this bloody battle?]
Wishing you lots of health,
and thank you for having us.
[Next Week's Running Man-
King of Events Race.]