Subtitles by DramaFever
- Merry Christmas!
- Wow, I can't believe it's Christmas already!
The end of the year is upon us already.
We wish everyone a great holiday season.
We have special guests that are here
to help celebrate the Christmas special.
[Special guests are waiting
inside the elevator?]
- Who could it be?
- I think they're headed down.
[Just then, the elevator starts
to head down.]
The elevator has stopped.
[Who could be their
special Christmas guests?]
Unbelievable!
[Three special guests who are taking
the members by a complete surprise.]
[The reigning queen of the TV world,
Kim Hye Ja.]
[They can hardly believe that the top actors
of the nation are standing in front of them.]
[A list actor, Lee Chun Hee.]
[The queen of charisma, Kang Hye Jung.]
She's the mother of our nation,
the epitome of all mothers everywhere!]
[Since her debut in the 1969 MBC drama,
'Frog Husband'...]
[An actress who has been a mainstay on
the small screen for over 40 years...]
[Best Actress Award for 'Manchu' in 1983,
and for 'Mother' in Asian Film Awards in 2010.]
[A top list actress, recognized all
over the world for her talent.]
[This award winning actress...]
[takes over the variety world.]
Fighting!
[The nation's mother
takes over the variety world.]
Yes, this is it.
[Yes, this is it!]
Wow, I don't remember you
ever being on a variety show before?
Look at how alert and animated
her eyes are.
[What a rude thing to say!]
[No, it's okay.]
- Can you please introduce yourself?
- Hello.
Please forgive me even if I do
something a bit weird and bizarre.
[Such elegance in her voice!]
Are you wearing tennis shoes because you
knew you were going to be on Running Man?
Yes, I wore my tennis shoes.
I don't think I've ever seen you
wear tennis shoes before.
She normally wears the
old rubber shoes.
[Huh?]
When have you ever seen me
wear rubber shoes?
In dramas and movies.
She wore shoes
even in the movie, 'Country Diary.'
[That's right.]
Hello, my name is Kang Hye Jung.
You're like my sister because
you're married to mini grasshopper.
[Mini grasshopper, Tablo's wife.]
I really wanted him to be on
the alien special you just had.
He really does look a lot like me.
And a member from the show,
Family Outing.
[A member from the Family Outing,
Lee Chun Hee.]
- He had Kwang Soo's role on that show.
- He passed his role onto Kwang Soo.
[The original goof, and the new goof.]
[Stay tuned for Chun Hee's
goofball antics.]
- Ms. Song Ji Hyo.
- Yes?
- Didn't we film 'Goong' together?
- Yes, that's right.
- Thank you for remembering.
- She was just as pretty back then.
- Yes, that's true.
- She was pretty back then.
What are you talking about?
She's still pretty!
When I say, 'just as pretty',
it means that she's still pretty.
[Kkuk is knocked out.]
[She's the best!]
I never imagined a day
like this would come.
It's truly an honor to
have you here.
I can't believe that she actually
came on our variety show.
I used to think that she and Choi Bul Ahm
were a real married couple.
- Yes, I used to think that, too.
- You've heard that before, right?
Your speech is so old fashioned.
[Old kiddo, Ha Ha is knocked out.]
[Sorry...]
[Such unique and direct approach
in her speech.]
- Are we just going to be talking on the show?
- No, we won't just be talking.
[I'm sorry to say that won't
be the case.]
- I'm not going to be made to run, am I?
- You'll have to play the name tag elimination.
- We'll have to rip off the name tags.
- Try ripping it off.
- You have to rip it off really hard.
- There you go.
- Then I'd be ousted from the game.
- Okay, then I won't rip it off.
She says she won't rip it off then.
If yours gets ripped off,
then you'll have to go to jail.
[Jail?]
- But Suk Jin and I'll be there, too.
- Okay.
She's going to pull you off to the side
after we're done filming the show.
- Rubber shoes and jail?
- I was just explaining the rules to her.
Today's race will be our Christmas special
since Christmas is just around the corner.
- It's like being with family.
- This is our Christmas special.
[These special guests are like
a Christmas gift to them.]
We have prepared a Christmas gift
that's geared more towards adults.
A prefect way to spend your Christmas,
Santa's Lottery Race.
Santa's lottery race?
For this race, all ten of you will be teamed
up together to carry out the mission.
With the completion of each round,
you'll be given a chance to win the lottery.
The lottery drawing zone
is set up over on the side
and Kim Hye Ja will pick the winning number
which will determine the prize amount.
With each mission that you win
you will be given a chance to
increase the amount of the prize
and if you fail the mission,
then you'll be given a disadvantage.
Please do your best to succeed the mission,
and take home the magic of the holidays.
- If we win, then we get a prize.
- All of us?
- Yes, everyone.
- We're all on the same team.
Think of it as a competition
against the producers.
So, those people are our enemies?
- Yes, they're the bad bastards.
- Think of them as our enemies.
- You just called them 'Bad bastards.'
- Sorry, I meant, bad guys.
I meant we're the good guys, and
they're bad. Sorry, please excuse me.
[Whether we're good and they're bad,
we're all still on the same team.]
[Gyunggido Division of 'Job World.']
The fact that Lady Kim Hye Ja is
here as a guest on Running Man
- is truly an honor.
- She seems to be leaning on you a lot.
I really want to wear one of these jackets,
but I'm afraid that I'd sweat in it.
But I see that you already have
your name tag stuck on your back.
You already have your name tag on.
[You have to chat and laugh on Christmas
because it only comes around once a year.]
- Merry Christmas!
- Santa's lottery race.
Here's your first mission.
Your first mission is, Unity Mission Relay.
You have to go and find an item that fits
within the category in the time limit given.
The mission will be carried out here.
Here's the category of the mission.
Take a selfie picture with
an animal mask.
[Animal mask?
A selfie?]
You have to spread out and
find a different animal mask
and take a selfie picture with everyone,
and all of you have to be in the shot.
- We'll start the clock now.
- Where do I have to go?
- Where do we go?
- It's all within this building.
- Ready, set...
- Wait.
- He said something about an animal mask.
- We have to take a picture with it on.
Ready, set, go!
- Find one for her first.
- Find one and give it to her first!
[All the members are making efforts
to take care of Lady Kim.]
[Gary discovers the rabbit mask.]
There's the rabbit mask.
Lady Kim can wear the rabbit mask.
[Gary tries to get the rabbit mask over
to Lady Kim as soon as he finds it.]
[But Big Sister Kim is already
in full search mode for a mask.]
Lady Kim!
Take this and go wait for us.
We'll be right there.
But I'll keep searching, too.
[She can just go and wait...]
[But she can't seem to quit her search.]
[She already seems acclimated
to the ways of Running Man.]
Here's one!
I found the cat!
[Kwang Soo discovers the cat mask.]
[Find the mask and
rush back to the mission site.]
Here it is!
[Blank Ji discovers the pig mask.]
[All the members must come back with a mask
to take the picture in order to succeed.]
Have people already searched
through here? Be honest with me.
They've already been here,
haven't they?
There's no need to search through
a place that's already been searched.
[Doing her best to find another mask when she
already has one tightly within her grasp.]
[I want to help them find one, too.]
[Hye Jung discovers a fox mask.]
- Have you found one?
- Do you have two?
[Kwang Soo hands one of his two masks
over to the original goofball.]
- Let's go! There's no time!
- Help me find one!
- Come on, hurry!
- Let's go!
- Hurry!
- Have you found one?
No, you have it on backwards.
[First time putting on the animal mask.]
[After transforming herself into a rabbit...
takes off at a dead run.]
[Everyone must return within a minute
and successfully take a selfie.]
[Christmas is off to a hot start
right from the first mission.]
[The phone is handed over,
and attempts to take a selfie picture.]
[Not easy to get all ten people in the shot
without a selfie stick.]
Where are you?
[Everyone rushes back to
the mission site.]
Hurry back!
[Still waiting on five more people.]
- Kwang Soo, you take the phone.
- We have to get everyone in the shot.
[Human Giraffe sure comes in handy
at times like this.]
[Everyone except for Gary is back.]
- Where's Lady Kim?
- She's down here.
- Gary's not here.
- We just need Gary to come back.
Come on, Gary!
[Hurry back, Gary.]
[Rushes back to the group after
finally having found a mask of his own.]
[All ten are finally back together,
and rush to take the selfie.]
[Squeezes in together
as tightly as possible.]
- Stretch out your arm some more.
- Stretch your arm out.
- Gary, you have to look up at the camera.
- Sit lower.
Gary, lift up your head some more.
[Lift up your head, Gary.]
- The chicken head is too big.
- Lower the chicken head.
- Suk Jin, lower your head even more.
- That's good.
I think we got it.
Ugh, it's hot.
[Getting steamed up after only
one mission.]
What are you asking Lady Kim
to do here?
What took you so long to
come back, Gary?
I'm sorry, Lady Kim.
I'll be better next time.
[I'm just kidding, Gary.]
[Only eight out of ten are shown.
Mission fail.]
[Ji Hyo and Kwang Soo are out
of the shot. Mission fail.]
[Where's Gary?
Mission fail.]
- That's disappointing.
- I found three masks.
- You found three masks?
- Yes, I found three masks.
- But you're really bad at finding things.
- You're awful at finding things.
But I was able to find the masks.
When it had nothing to do with winning.
[His searching skills are at its peak when
winning a mission isn't hanging on the line.]
- Lady Kim, we have to start running again.
- Yes, do not worry.
[Competitiveness is starting to peak
after only the first round.]
- You're not mad at me, are you?
- Yes, she's angry.
Why would you say that to her?
Your next mission is,
'Weigh the Item'.
You have to disperse and bring back
an item to weigh on the scale
and if the combined weight of your items are
more than 150kg, then you win the mission.
The clock starts now.
Start!
- 150kg?
- We have to bring back something?
Jong Kook, bring back
the heaviest thing you can find.
It has to be something that's
marked with an 'R' sticker.
- It has to be 15kg per item.
- They have to be heavy items.
- I'm sure they're all on the second floor.
- Right?
[Her search radar is back on
with the start of the second mission.]
I doubt they hid anything
in the trash cans.
I'd really like to find something, too.
[The Human Opener opens up
every door that she comes across.]
- Here's something!
- Is it something heavy?
It needs to be heavier than this.
This isn't going to be heavy enough.
Here's something!
- What's this? This is too light.
- Is it light?
- It's toilet paper.
- Toilet paper?
[Toilet paper is going to be
way too light.]
- Just take it back for now.
- Should I set this down?
[No matter how many items are brought back,
only one item per person are allowed.]
Here's a tire.
[Oh, that's going to carry some weight.]
I've found something!
Ugh, why is this thing so heavy?
How do I get back down?
[Chun Hee, you haven't changed one bit...]
Lady Kim, this is kind of heavy.
[Ha Ha passes the giant stuffed bear
over to Big Sister Kim.]
- Go and wait for us.
- Okay.
Does this make me a selfish brat?
I really need to find something myself.
- Lady Kim, just go! You can just go.
- Oh my goodness.
Oh my goodness, she's so strong.
How much does it weigh?
10.8kg.
Why can't I find anything?
Oh, I've found something!
I've found something!
- Jong Kook, I've found something!
- What is it? Wow!
Wait, what is it?
Okay, you can just push it.
[A giant flower pot on wheels!]
- Here's something!
- What is it?
- It's kimchi!
- That's good.
- Hey, I've got kimchi!
- Hye Jung, that's great!
- That's a sure thing!
- That's great!
[Heavy and speedy!
Hye Jung makes a great discovery.]
[Gary arrives back with his tire.]
Put in on top of it.
That's a really big item.
31.8kg!
[Jae Suk returns with the water jug in
one, and a dumbbell in the other.]
[Hye Jung arrives with her
giant flower pot.]
That's really impressive.
Oh my goodness,
I can't believe you found that.
- No, one at a time.
- 18.5kg.
[Hye Jung's giant flower pot- 18.5kg.]
- Here's a snowman!
- Where?
[He actually stops to pick up the snowman?]
[Some people just never change.]
4.36kg.
[The giant teddy bear- 4.36kg.]
- 11.88kg.
- That's pretty heavy.
- Only one item per person, Jae Suk.
- I just want to see which is heavier.
[Jae Suk is planning on choosing
the heavier item of the two.]
- Which one?
- They're both around 10.
[Water jug- 9.8kg.
Dumbbell- 9.9kg.]
[How can the two items be so similar?]
How about this one?
[Chun Hee's blanket weighs 14.8kg.]
Jong Kook is bringing back a person.
- Seriously? A person is marked with an 'R'?
- What?
Oh my goodness.
[Big Sister Kim continues to
be impressed.]
[Kkuk brings back a life sized mannequin.]
I hope that the mannequin is heavy.
The Santa can hold something.
Press down on it.
You can't press down on it.
23.
I'm just holding it steady
so that it doesn't fall over.
We already know how much it weighs.
[You already know how
much it weighs?]
- We already know the weight of it.
- Maybe he just had a nice meal.
- We already know how much it weighs.
- 18.7kg.
- Okay, Lee Kwang Soo's turn.
- You brought back toilet paper?
- It's really heavy toilet paper.
- You really are too much, Kwang Soo.
You should've just left it.
[The weight of the toilet paper can
determine the outcome of the mission.]
[Kwang Soo is practically standing
on top of the weight scale.]
- Come back down, Kwang Soo.
- It didn't work.
Oh my goodness... where are we
going to find something heavier?
Your total record is... 131.56kg.
Whose item didn't weight over 10kg?
I found your item for you.
You're really hurting my feelings.
- I found your item for you.
- I found Lady Kim's item for her.
But that item didn't even
weigh 10kg.
[I'm sorry.]
You're the one who gave her an item
that didn't weigh enough.
[Big Sister tries to uplift everyone's mood
by joking around about failing the mission.]
The size may be big,
but it's not all that heavy.
What is this? It's obvious
that it's not all that heavy.
If this is what you're going to find for her,
then don't even find her anything.
[Thanks to Big Sister Kim,
everyone's still in good spirits.]
- Are you having fun?
- Yeah, I want to become a fixed member.
I'm just talking rubbish.
Lady Kim says that she's having fun,
and she loves all the laughter.
She says she's having fun, and we
really love having you on our show.
- Really? I'm really happy right now.
- Yes, we're serious.
[A cozy scene to warm up a
wintery season.]
- I like running without having to think.
- Me, too. Seriously.
I really like running around.
I want to run around like a fool
without having to think about anything.
Your next mission is,
'Create the number with the dice'.
- This is all about luck.
- This game is about luck.
There will be five couples of two
and each member will decide who will
be the single and double digit.
For example, if the team rolls
a two and a five consecutively
then the team will end up with 25.
Then if the following couple rolls the dice
and the sum is bigger than the first couple
then you succeed the mission.
Then there will be five turns and
each will have to be bigger than the last?
- Then 66 will be the highest?
- Getting 66 in the middle will be a failure.
- Oh my.
- Don't mention failing already.
[Why would you mention that already?]
- No, we can do this.
- This has potential.
Should people with bad luck
partner up together?
Who has the worst luck
with things like this?
- Chun Hee and Kwang Soo...
- Those two, for sure.
- You, too.
- I'm pretty unlucky myself.
- You guys should partner up together,
- It'll be the four of us.
[Bad luck all-stars:
Chun Hee, Kwang Soo, Suk Jin, Jae Suk.]
- We have the worst luck.
- We're famous for being unlucky.
[Self-professed icons of bad luck.]
Would it be better for the bad luck
guys to go first?
- What if we roll 66 right away?
- You guys are unlucky no matter what.
Then how about we split up and
have one go first, and the other last?
- First bad luck, and last bad luck.
- Split you guys up?
Since these two have bad luck,
and those two have filthy bad luck...
- We don't have filthy bad luck.
- Split them half and half.
- These two are really unlucky.
- Filthy bad luck.
Why would you say that in
front of Lady Kim?
Family Outing, come over here.
This is the original bad luck,
and that is the new filthy bad luck.
He's just bad luck,
and I'm the other just bad luck.
Is everyone teamed up in pairs?
Then hold hands with your partners.
- Are you my partner?
- Yes, we have to go and find the dice.
Ready, go!
Keep your eyes open.
[The two bad luck couples
are running side by side.]
Let's go home.
We should go up.
They're going upstairs, too.
Bad luck people think alike.
All the bad luck people must think alike.
[The two couples run up
to the second floor together.]
I don't see any dice.
- I don't see any.
- Where could they be?
Let's go back to the first floor.
I don't think there are any up here.
[Are they unlucky,
or are they just impatient?]
I think we should go back downstairs
and search to our right.
Why are you taking the elevator?
We don't have time for the elevator!
[Big-nose Brother can't resist
the comforts of civilized age.]
But an elevator would be faster
than taking the stairs.
I'd like to see you in a name tag
elimination game against lady Kim Hye Ja.
Have you found something?
[Big Sister Kim has already
found something.]
- Wow, we found something!
- There's something there.
- Oh my, no one saw the one in there?
- No, they must not have.
- Should we try rolling it?
- This is just practice.
- This is just for practice.
- Double and single digit.
- We need to get the lowest number possible.
- Lower is better?
[Lower is better.]
You can't throw it like that.
[Big Sister Kim's new way
of throwing the dice.]
- You're quite the jokester.
- You just rolled it to 'one.'
- I found one.
- You did? Let's go.
[Rushes back to the mission site
with her hand in Kkuk's hand.]
- We've found ours.
- Have you found it?
[All the couples are gathered back together.]
You have to decide
which couple will go first.
Let's have Lady Kim Hye Ja go first.
Then Lady Kim will have the double digit,
and Jong Kook will have single digit.
Okay.
- I need to get 'one', right? Should I go?
- Yes.
[First couple to go,
with Lady Kim in the double digit.]
[Oh no!]
[Addition of a special rule-
Out of bounds, so doesn't count.]
That was out of bounds!
[Big Sister Kim immediately
takes another turn.]
[First couple's double digit is... one!]
That's good, right?
[Big Sister Kim gets them off
to a perfect start.]
- That's great!
- Kim Hye Ja!
- She's so cute.
- 11!
Eleven!
[The lowest number- Eleven.
The best possible start.]
[Ji Hyo and Hye Jung's turn.]
Ji Hyo's going first.
[Second couple, Ji Hyo and Hye Jung.
Single digit number.]
- Please let it be one.
- Let it be one, let it be one.
- Let it be one.
- Two!
[Second couple's number, 25.]
[Success.
25 is greater than 11.]
- My turn. I'm going for the single digit.
- Is it the single digit number?
[Third couple's single digit- Four.]
[In order for it to be greater than 25,
Gary needs to roll a three or higher.]
One, two, three!
[Third couple's double digit roll.]
[Five.]
[Success]
- Did you get 54?
- You need to roll 55.
- I need to roll 55 or higher?
- How about 61, and you roll 62?
Who should go first?
Who do you think has worse luck?
Who looks to be most unlucky?
[Points to Kwang Soo without
even a moment of hesitation.]
- She thinks you look most unlucky.
- Should I roll first?
Okay, this is the single digit.
[Fourth couple's first digit roll.]
[One.]
[The worst case scenario.
Must roll a six in order to succeed.]
Why did you roll first?
Shouldn't we have agreed on it together?
Why did you agree to go first?
- Lady Kim told me to.
- You just asked me who looked most unlucky.
[Big Sister Kim only answered
the question asked.]
- No, she wasn't indicating to him.
- We're going to go first.
[This is good!]
- That wasn't your roll?
- No, it wasn't.
I just threw it down in anger because I was
upset at her telling me that I looked unlucky.
- I'm sorry.
- Kwang Soo just threw it down in anger.
[Kwang Soo jumped the gun
from his fit of anger.]
- Current number to beat is 54.
- We need to roll 56.
[Must roll a number higher than
54 in order to succeed.]
[Fourth couple's single digit throw.]
[Four.]
You can roll either a five or a six.
You can tie it.
[Tie is accepted.
Must roll either a five or a six.]
[Rolling a six would put a great
burden on the next couple.]
[Must roll a five for the sake
of winning for all the members.]
Please be quiet.
I'm not in a good mood right now,
so just go away.
I have to get a five.
[Fourth couple's double digit toss.]
[Six.]
[Success.]
- We did it.
- We're okay.
[Must roll either 65
or 66 to win the mission.]
Lady Kim, who should roll the single digit?
The unlucky person should roll first.
Then should I go first?
- Yes, then I'll go first.
- You have two numbers you can land on.
You can roll either a five or a six.
- Lady Kim, can you cheer for us?
- Fighting!
- If you lose, you'll be stripped naked.
[Must roll either 65 or 66 to succeed.]
[The last couple's single digit toss.]
[6]
[First phase is a success.]
[No other choice but to roll
a six in order to succeed.]
I feel so pressured right now.
Why am I put in this position?
Let's just go for six, okay?
- Six!
- Roll a six.
Toss it really high into the air.
- All my new year's luck is going into this.
- If you lose, I'm stripping you naked.
- Lady Kim, give me a cheer.
- Fighting!
- One more time!
[Yes, this is a real cheer!]
[Only six will be acceptable!]
Let's go!
[What will be the last couple's
double digit number?]
[1]
[A failed mission.]
Wow, we've set it all up for you,
and you've just kicked our victory away.
[He needed a six,
but he rolls a one instead.]
No, it's okay.
He said it's with next year's good luck,
but he's just using up next year's bad luck.
[Big Sister Kim's words of comfort.]
Since this was so much fun,
how about playing it one more time?
- Really?
- Look, it's a six.
That's why you're so unlucky.
You're just really unlucky.
[Big-nose throws it again.]
- He's going to keep rolling a six.
- See?
[Another six.]
I get a one when I needed a six.
Wow, seriously.
[Fails the mission so close to winning
because of Big-nose's misfortune.]
[Maybe I'll have better luck next year.]
Please give us our next mission.
This is our last chance, isn't it?
This is your last chance.
Here's your next mission.
It's 'Spin the Hoola Hoop'.
Everyone must find and bring back
hoola hoops of various sizes
and if everyone can last for three seconds
doing the hoola hoop, then it's a win.
- Ugh, this is bad.
- You may get started.
Ugh, what are we going to do?
I can't do the hoola hoop.
- I'm really bad at this.
- There's one!
- Give that to Lady Kim.
- Give her the small one.
- Will this size be okay?
- I can't even do it. I should practice.
- Give it a try.
I've never done this before,
so I don't think I'll be able to do it.
Would it help if I held
your coat in the back?
- In case it gets caught in your coat?
- Everyone's watching.
- It's because it got caught in your coat.
- I'm not doing it. It's too embarrassing.
- Will a bigger one be better?
- I don't know.
- I've never done this before.
- I'm really bad at this, too.
No, I bet you're good at it.
Ugh, this is bad.
Lady Kim, you're really good!
Do you like that one,
or this one better?
- This one is better.
- Then you can have that one.
- Okay, thank you.
- You're good at it.
- No, I'm not good.
- This isn't working. I'm in trouble.
[Closes the door to practice by herself
out of her embarrassment.]
[Our Big Sister Kim is as sweet
and bright as a young child.]
[Everyone finds their hoola hoops
and gathers together to practice.]
I don't want to do it by myself.
Let's all do it together.
[Starts the group practice session.]
I'm too embarrassed to do this.
- I think a heavier one would be better.
- How about spinning it with your arm?
How about spinning it around my neck?
[Spinning it around the arm or
the neck will also be accepted.]
- How about spinning it around the arm?
- That's fine.
That was done on purpose, right?
[Bringing lots of laughter to everyone.]
Okay, let's get started.
You just need to spin it around.
- Okay, let's do this.
- This is your final chance.
[Santa's Lottery Race- First mission.
Final chance.]
- Wouldn't a heavier one be better for her?
- Would you like this one or that one?
I'm going to do this one.
No, give me back that one.
Why would you put me in
such a difficult spot like this?
- You're seriously too much.
- Ready... go!
[No more chances will be given!]
[Must last for three seconds!]
[Big Sister Kim gives everything
she has into spinning her hoop!]
[3.08 seconds.
Barely succeeds the mission!]
[Barely manages to clear the mission
thanks to Big Sister Kim's big efforts.]
[Big Sister Kim's leadership guides
the team into winning the mission.]
Since you've succeeded you mission,
as mentioned, the drawing zone is over there.
Getting there within 20 seconds will be
greatly advantageous for you. Get going!
We have to rush over there.
This way.
[Everyone must get there within
20 seconds for it to be a success.]
[Everyone's holding Big Sister Kim's
hand to help her along.]
Mom and dad to little kids
are always the fastest.
- Because we never know what could happen.
- Always on the move.
I'm keeping your place for you.
[All the members arrive
at the drawing zone.]
[A drawing machine sits
in the middle of the drawing zone.]
[What is the meaning of
these balls?]
I'll explain the drawing rules for you.
During the race, you will draw from
the machine at the end of each mission.
There are a total of seven figures
which you'll be drawing for.
Since it's the end of the first mission,
you'll draw for the 10,000 Won spot.
- For the 10,000 Won?
- Yes, for the 10,000 Won spot.
If you draw a zero,
then you've drawn zero Won.
But if you draw a nine,
then you've drawn 90,000 Won.
- I think they're going to give us money.
- There are numbers zero through nine.
Then the highest number possible
would be all nines?
If you were to pick all nines,
then you'd get 999 million Won.
I said that you needed to
get here within 20 seconds
but it took you 38 seconds to get here.
We lost time because we were helping
Lady Kim on the way here.
So there won't be any additional balls.
- If you had arrived within 20 seconds...
- That's okay though, isn't it?
- You could've added another nine ball.
- That's okay, Lady Kim.
[Arriving within 20 seconds would've
added another nine ball into the mix.]
[After the success of first mission,
can choose from 1-9 balls.]
[The balls are rolling around with gusto.]
[Which numbered ball
will they choose for the first slot?]
[Number eight!]
[With the draw of the first number,
80,000 Won is earned.]
80,000 Won.
You have drawn 80,000 Won so far
in the Santa's lottery drawing.
[Will this happy start continue on
until the end of the race?]
[The greatest gift is the ability to
share the joy with others.]
- I think Lady Kim really likes you.
- I'm her eldest son.
- Why are you her eldest son?
- Won Bin is her second eldest.
[Everyone is each other's siblings.]
She's just amazed to see people like you
after seeing someone as handsome as Won Bin.
- I really enjoyed watching your drama.
- You are such an amazing actress.
You played a mother who believed
in her son all the way to the end.
Even if a son were to do such a thing,
his mother would always believe in him.
Because she's his mom.
[Santa's Lottery Race- Second mission]
- It's a Bingo Quiz.
- Bingo?
- Bingo Quiz.
- Bingo quiz?
If you look behind you...
- Why are there so many numbers?
- There are so many spaces!
There are nine spaces across,
and nine spaces down.
There are a total of 81 spaces
with corresponding answers.
Why are there so many questions?
One person will ask the questions
and the remaining nine will answer
to complete at least one bingo line
in order to win the mission.
[Even one completed bingo line
would equate to winning the mission.]
[All nine members must correctly
answer the question.]
[What's with the expression
on their faces?]
The topic of this quiz is 'Popular
toy items for this year's Christmas'.
That should be easy since
this isn't about general knowledge.
This is just about things.
Since we're already on this subject,
what is it that you'd like, Gary?
Oh my, there's a Gary here?
Oh my, I'm sorry.
Gary is the name of the dog
in my movie.
[This is that Gary.]
- I'm in your movie?
- Wally's real name is Gary.
[Wally's real name is Gary.]
Whatever the case,
it's nice to make your acquaintance.
Is there anything
that you'd like for Christmas?
Me?
Well, I... I want to be loved.
[A working mom's humble wish.]
What about you, Chun Hee?
I want a laptop.
You don't have one?
- I just want a new one.
- Just buy one.
Why would you buy a laptop
if you already have one?
Lady Kim sounded like
she really pitied him when she said
'Do you not have one?'
Chun Hee, she must've
found you really pitiful.
[Maybe this mother may just buy him
his new laptop.]
- I'll ask the first question.
- Okay, Ha Ha can ask the questions.
- Then I'll answer the first question.
- I'll answer the eighth question.
- I'll go after Ji Hyo.
- Lady Kim can go last.
That way, you can see how others
are doing it in front of you.
Yes, I can do that.
Then you can see how things progress,
and you can gauge how it's done.
Okay, then you must now decide which
line you're going to go for.
- Number one!
- Let's just start from the beginning.
- Let's start with one and go diagonal.
- Yes.
- From one through nine.
- Let's get this done on first try.
- Fighting!
- I'm so nervous.
[100 seconds on the clock.
Bingo Quiz- First attempt.]
The thing that beeps from the front
and back in the newer suv's...
The front and rear sensors.
[She got that on first try?]
New front and rear sensor
equipped SUV!
[Huh?
Blank Ji is actually this smart?]
- Okay, move up.
- You knew all that?
I don't know any of that stuff.
What's your favorite tree?
An ash tree?
[Huh? What tree?]
[Ash... what?]
- He likes ash trees?
- Yes, ash trees.
- How big of a family do you want to have?
- Six.
Right?
Then combine all that together.
A six person table
made out of ash trees?
- A six person table?
- Okay!
What is it?
- The questions are so easy.
- You like six person tables?
[Have they always been this smart?]
[Just what is this situation?]
[Two hours before the opening.]
[A bakery near the opening scene.]
- There's one more guest that'll be coming.
- Really?
- There's one more guest?
- There's a reason why you all are here.
We've asked you to meet here because there's
a secret mission that you'll have to do.
- You'll be asked to play a Bingo Quiz.
- Bingo quiz?
There'll be a hidden camera mission in which
only Lady Kim Hye Ja will get a question wrong
and deter the team from getting a bingo line,
and that's how you'll succeed the mission.
If Lady Kim guesses during the mission
that there's a hidden camera
or if she correctly guesses the answer
to complete a bingo line
then you will all fail
the hidden camera mission.
And if you fail to answer the question
correctly, then you also fail the mission.
Please take a look at the bingo questions
and do you best to memorize the answers.
[These nine members will now have to
work to memorize all the answers.]
- We have to study again?
- You'll be given the time to study right now.
- Please start studying.
- These are the questions.
- And these are the questions.
- How am I supposed to know these answers?
[The questions and its corresponding
answers sound like alien language.]
- How am I supposed to know this?
- These are hard questions.
Listen to this.
The jacket that boasts its waterproof feature
as well as for being lightweight and warm?
- Is it goose down?
- No, ultralight down jacket with padding.
[How are we supposed to know this?]
- I've never met Lady Kim Hye Ja before.
- I've never met her either.
She's like a sweet young girl.
To be honest, I doubt she'll know these.
I doubt she'll know what a six cylinder
battery series engine is.
What is she knows?
'This is a six cylinder battery series engine.'
She could have a lot of interest in cars.
- She could know this.
- Maybe she likes sports cars.
- We need to come up with a good plan.
- We need to be detailed about this.
- Should we go up or down?
- It could be diagonal, too.
- There's a diagonal line.
- Let's go diagonally.
Just think about it.
- Come on.
- Do you not have a brain?
- Just do it.
- It's because you seem to lack a brain.
- You must not use your brain very much.
- Excuse me?
Do you think that my brain
is just for decoration?
[Unstable factor number one-
Members can't seem to agree on anything.]
- We just need to memorize one line.
- That's what I'm saying.
- Let's just memorize one line.
- That's what I'm saying!
[How many times must we repeat
saying the same thing?]
[There seems to be no sign
of any progress at this meeting.]
We're just going to give up
on this mission.
- Do we just need one bingo line?
- If you get a bingo line, then you fail.
We have to get a bingo?
No, we can't get a bingo line.
If we do, then we fail the mission.
[30th time explaining the rules of the game.]
What do you think, Chun Hee?
I'm not really sure what's going on yet.
You didn't know during Family Outing,
and you still don't know. When will you know?
[Unstable factor number two-
Goofy Brothers can't understand the mission.]
At this rate, we're not going to get back
in time to greet Lady Kim Hye Ja.
[They waste away all their study time...]
[And now they rush.]
[Are they studying for their SAT's?]
Isn't there a single smart person here?
This shouldn't be this difficult.
It's just because none of us like to study.
- This is too bothersome.
- Seriously!
[Unstable factor number three-
Members are too lazy to study.]
- That's not the problem.
- There are too many questions.
- How about we memorize one each?
- Let's divide the questions.
[Just then, Big-nose proposes that
they memorize one question each.]
Ha Ha can ask the questions,
and Ji Hyo can memorize the first question.
- How about Lady Kim goes second?
- Lady Kim can go second.
- Okay.
- How about we go in this order?
[Their current seating is the order.]
[Rehearsing how the quiz will go.]
- The front and rear sensor...
- New SUV's anterior sensors.
[Blank Ji's correct answer is the result
of the rehearsal they practiced earlier.]
- What is your favorite tree?
- The ash tree?
Why do you like the ash tree?
Have you even seen that tree before?
[Extremely unnatural answer to
a question- That ash tree?]
It's your favorite tree!
The tree you most like.
[Things are going along exactly
how they rehearsed it.]
- You don't think Lady Kim will notice?
- We're definitely going to fail this.
We have to do a good job
so that she doesn't catch on.
[Will this candid camera mission succeed?]
[Their studying session continues
during their drive to the opening site.]
I'm not going to study.
I'm going to go with my gut feeling.
[Even after having arrived
at the opening location.]
[Member prepares for the mission by
writing cheat notes onto their skin.]
[Even right up to the point of
the mission starting...]
[They continue to study in secret.]
[That's how they finished
preparing for their secret mission.]
[This is how the mission got underway.]
- It's made with your favorite tree.
- A six person ash tree table?
[Ash tree what?
First time ever hearing such a thing!]
[These young people are
much smarter than I had thought.]
I don't understand a single thing
that's being said.
It's my favorite!
[They don't know any of this either.]
- Burgundy... red wine?
- That's right, burgundy?
[I didn't know that Chun Hee
liked burgundy red wine.]
[Extremely excited.]
[Oh my goodness.]
[Repeating the answer to himself
in case he forgets it.]
- The really big...
- Halla Mountain!
Halla mountain's aquifer that's
500m above sea level?
That's right!
How am I supposed to know
something like that?
[We've never heard it before
today either.]
You can do this!
You gave this to your wife
as a Christmas gift last year.
[The thing Yoo Hyuk gave his wife
as a Christmas gift last year?]
- It was a bracelet of some sort.
- Oh, that one!
A 16 carat white diamond bracelet!
Wow, you're a great husband.
You told your wife that you'd take her
camping this year, right?
- The thing that you use while camping...
- Portable pots and pans!
But you know that thing...
it comes in a set!
- Stainless...
- Hurry!
[He hasn't... forgotten his answer,
has he?]
- It comes in a set!
- Stainless portable pots and pan set!
[Finally gets the correct answer.]
Oh my goodness, I have no idea
what any of you are saying.
- You know that mountain?
- Jiri mountain?
Remember the thing I said would make
me really strong if I were to eat it?
- Mountain ginseng?
- How old are the really effective ginseng?
- 25 year old Jiri mountain ginseng?
- That's right!
[What is going on here?]
- Calm down.
- This is popular these days.
[Already knows the answer before
the question is even asked.]
- It's waterproof and really warm.
- Ultralight down jacket with padding?
- That's right!
- That was right?
- It's Lady Kim's turn.
- We have faith in you!
[It's finally her turn.
Correct answer, and they fail the mission.]
How about we ask the question in such a way
that she'd never get the correct answer?
If it looks like she knows the answer,
then we can start to confuse her.
[1. Purposely make the question confusing.
2. Divert her attention in moment of danger.]
Front and the rear wheels
are shiny and bright.
The kickboards are really shiny.
You all know this one, right?
[Glow in the dark front and rear kickboard.]
- You're asking it too hard!
- Ask the question simpler.
What's the name of the board
that shines and glows?
[Time over.]
[Everyone starts to chastise Ha Ha as soon
as the game ends to avoid her catching on.]
I practically gave you the answer.
It's a glow in the dark kickboard.
- Then you should've told me that.
- I basically did.
- No, you didn't tell her.
- You need to apologize to her.
No, it's okay.
It's because I didn't know.
- He couldn't have explained it any better.
- Glow in the dark front and rear kickboard.
[They did succeed the first round...]
The final question was way too hard.
[Everyone seems to be nervous
that Lady Kim may catch on.]
- No, it's okay.
- It's okay, you did great.
- Okay, you get how it's done now?
- The question was hard.
- The answer is within the question?
- Yes, that's right.
[Thanks to Big Sister Kim
for always being so positive.]
- This is a very simple game.
- We took too long with our answers.
- How about we have Lady Kim go first?
- Okay.
[For the next round,
Lady Kim is designated to go first.]
Okay.
- Then let's move our spots around.
- Okay.
[Change of position was already
decided during the rehearsal.]
- How about we swap and have her go first?
- That's right.
- Then we'll fail right away.
Then we don't even have to
memorize this line!
[Yay, we don't have to study!]
[This is the plan they came up with
to have Hye Ja go first.]
- Okay.
- I'll explain it very slowly.
[Chun Hee to ask the questions this time.]
- We'll start with question number 21.
- Fighting.
[Do a good job, Chun Hee.]
Give me a minute.
- Are you feeling nervous?
- My mouth feels parched.
- You can take your time.
- Don't worry, we've got you.
- Explain it to her slowly.
- Fighting!
[Unstable Chun Hee-
Will he be able to do it right?]
Set, go!
Wow, this one is really hard.
[Carcharodontosauridae figure.]
[Unable to even talk.]
- Hurry up!
- Say something.
You don't know it either?
[Even the team members can't figure out
whether he's acting, or if he's serious.]
- You have to say something.
- Hurry up and explain it.
- Is it hard?
- It's a toy, Lady Kim.
Leave out the 'Lady Kim.'
- Just talk.
- She's saying there's no time.
- But...
- She's saying not to say 'Lady Kim.'
- It's a toy?
- It's an ancient dinosaur.
- Just say something.
- There's something before the dinosaur.
- This is...
- How about just the first word?
- Be quiet.
- It's a six syllable word.
It's a six syllable word?
A baby dinosaur?
[This one?]
It's blah blah blah,
and blah blah blah.
- What is that?
- What's that supposed to be?
[Just say something.]
I've never heard of it before either.
I'll explain it one at a time.
- First syllable is... 'car' in English is?
- Car.
Yes, that's the first part.
He's driving me crazy.
[Already past the one minute mark.]
- There's no time.
- We never should've had Chun Hee do it.
[Hang in there a little bit longer,
Chun Hee!]
There's a letter in the middle,
and there are double syllables.
- Cane?
- Mone?
What's he doing?
[Even his own teammates
are embarrassed for him.]
You can't even ask the question!
[If all this truly is just an act,
then it's some amazing acting.]
- Ugh, he's so frustrating.
- Lee Chun Hee, do you want to die?
[Not much time left on the clock.]
- Car...
- Yes, and then...
[Time's up!]
- It's a really tough question!
- That was just absurd!
- Carcharodontosauridae figurine.
- That is a tough question.
- That's a real tough question.
- I don't even know what that's saying.
What kind of a question was that?
That was an unreasonable question
for them to have you ask.
[It's normal for you
not to know the answer.]
- Who would even know this?
- That was disappointing.
- That was just absurd.
- That was too tough of a question.
- Let's just redo it.
- I think they want us to get it wrong.
I think they want us to get it wrong.
[Excuse me?]
[She couldn't have... noticed it?]
I think they're asking these questions
to make it funny, don't you think?
So that you can't even explain
the question and it's funnier.
- Okay, I get it now.
- Do you get it now?
[Such a close call.]
- I think she gets it now.
- Ugh, it's hot.
[Happy Big Sister Kim keeps all the
members on the edge of their seats.]
- Why don't you come over here?
- This is my new spot.
Which order should we go in?
- How about going down the eight line?
- From number 26 and down.
- Then we just need to get seven questions.
- That's right.
- We've already got two of the questions.
- Fighting!
[After a loud cheer...]
[Whew, that was a close call.]
Ready, set, go!
If there are six members in my family,
what kind of a rice cooker would I use?
Six person automatic...
Six person automatic rice pressure cooker!
Bingo!
The breed of dog I used to have
and it was at my wedding!
- Bichon frise!
- Bingo!
[Hye Jung is really good.]
The ingredient that's known to be
very good for your skin.
- Undiluted hyaluronic acid ample!
- Bingo!
[What was that?]
- It's not a manual.
- Automatic!
- And it's bad...
- Kerosene!
- And it gets rid of the moisture.
- A dehumidifier!
- Put those two together!
- Automatic ionic sterilizing dehumidifier!
- Oh my goodness.
- I've always wanted one of those.
[Shocking that Kwang Soo got it.]
It's an anti-aging face cream
that really pulls things tighter.
- Hybrid anti-aging cream?
- That's right!
- How did you know that?
- I use it at home.
- I always use it at home.
- You use it, too?
- It's harmless...
- Non-toxic?
Yes, it's like a non-toxic glue stick.
Wait, it's a non-toxic...
[He couldn't have...
forgotten the answer?]
[Non-toxic super glue stick.]
Ugh, it's at the tip of my tongue!
[Attempting to cheat
at a moment of danger.]
[If he gets caught, then it's all over!]
[But Ha Ha blocks her view with his back,
and fortunately avoids getting caught.]
Is it a non-toxic super glue stick?
- That's right!
- Yes!
[Hye Jung gives a strong reaction to
avoid Hye Ja noticing anything amiss.]
Lady Kim, this is a household appliance
that is similar to a refrigerator.
[A freestanding air conditioner.]
[We just need to last for 15 more seconds.]
- It can be on the wall, too.
- Is it a wall decor?
This is... um...
[Hye Jung suddenly starts to stutter after
having done so well up to this point.]
This is a freestanding thing.
- It's freestanding?
- Yes, it's freestanding.
- A freestanding air conditioner?
A freestanding air conditioner?
[Even with the confusing explanation,
she still gets close to the exact answer!]
[They even practiced this question!]
- I have one at my house, too, and it's...
- Time's up!
I think you're going to have to practice
how to make the question more difficult.
Since there's a time limit,
how about we take longer at the start?
- So that she doesn't have much time.
- Stall more in the beginning?
But making this difficult
is going to be the hard part.
[Even with all the confusion,
she almost gets the exact answer!]
[Ugh, we're ruined!]
[Candid camera quiz is in danger!]
- A freestanding air conditioner?
- It's not just your regular air conditioner.
It's a little...
[Time fortunately runs out
in the midst of extreme danger.]
[A little better explanation, then she
would've gotten the exact answer!]
- A heating and cooling.
- Wow, that was so close!
- It's a heating and cooling system.
- Can't this one count?
- She was so close to the answer!
- This one should count.
It's because I don't like being hot.
[Big Sister Kim doesn't like things
to make her feel hot.]
She doesn't like to feel hot,
so why would you ask this question?
- She had the answer.
- That's basically getting the question right.
- I really don't like being hot.
- You seem to like air conditioners.
- I don't like being hot.
- I really don't like heaters either.
She got that right away.
[Such a smart mother.
Almost failed their candid camera mission.]
- We're almost there!
- We've almost got it.
[Success of our mission is almost here.]
- We're almost there.
- We've got this.
- Should I go?
- What's almost there?
[Everyone freezes in their spots.]
What's almost there?
[Everyone freezes at her question.]
- Just that we almost have a bingo line.
- One more round, and we may have it.
- We're almost there to getting it right.
- We may get it at the next round.
- This is our last chance.
- This is the last round?
Let's get it done this time.
[Will they be able to successfully complete
the candid camera mission?]
[Guys, one more mistake,
and it's all over for us!]
- Who's good at explaining things?
- Who wants to ask this time?
[It's your turn.]
- Why doesn't Kwang Soo do it?
- Kwang Soo, you give it a try.
[The unlucky guy's turn?]
[Kwang Soo is tagged in.
Will their gamble succeed?]
[From question number 23 and down.]
- Wow, these are easy questions.
- Good, this is our chance.
- This is our chance, Lady Kim.
- Ready, set, go!
[Candid camera bingo quiz-
Final round.]
It's a bracelet...
[A bracelet?]
It's a bracelet.
[He's supposed to ask the
23rd question.]
[But he's asking question number five
that's already been asked earlier.]
[That's the question I answered earlier.]
The thing I found by eating baby food?
[Ready to go baby food pouches.]
- Kwang Soo...
- Isn't it baby food?
- Kwang Soo, you've got the wrong question.
- You have to start with question 23.
[Bad luck guy gets abused on.]
The baby food that my baby likes.
Jae Suk already got the 16 carat
diamond bracelet question.
[Ugh, he's so frustrating.]
My baby food.
The baby food that I like.
- What is he doing?
- What is it?
It's a really expensive baby food!
- I think I know!
- I'm going to feed this to my future baby.
- Ready to go baby food pouches!
Okay, that's the correct answer!
- What are you doing?
- You're not asking the right questions!
Just ask the next question.
[At this rate, time is going to run out
before it gets to Hye Ja's turn.]
During the Joseon era...
[Joseon era?]
- It's a keychain bed.
- What is he doing?
What is he doing?
[Buckle field cot.]
It's a bed from the Joseon era.
Are you talking about a buckle?
[A brand new quiz style where the answer
has to be tailored to the question.]
- Buckle field cot?
- Okay, that's the correct answer.
[What was that?]
- Hurry up!
- A car that spouts water.
Water that spouts from the car.
[Direct injection turbo engine
convertible.]
The engine spouts out water, too.
- It spouts out water?
- Yes, from the top and from the engine.
It spouts water when you spin it.
[It sounds like a transformer car.]
- Turbo engine convertible.
- Okay!
- How did you know that?
- What was that?
- A car that spouts water?
- You have to explain it better!
[Even Chun Hee starts to yell
at Kwang Soo.]
[Get yourself together!]
What is he doing?
[Something's very weird...]
- It's a sort of a car.
- Has he lost his mind?
[We're the idiots for
having trusted Kwang Soo.]
- What is he talking about?
- Good for the body and purification.
[He should be able to get a gauge
for what the answer is by now.]
- It's in the coffee, but not here.
- Caffeine?
Tea.
Eco-friendly and caffeine free
five variety tea set?
[But he still answers it correctly.]
[From Hye Ja's point of view,
Gary is a true genius.]
- I know what this one is!
- What is it?
It's the thing I gave you as
a Christmas gift last year!
- Timing humidifier?
- No, it's not 'timing.'
No, it's not 'timing.'
[It's not?]
[Reaches for his cheat sheet
in the sleeve.]
[Big-nose forgot the answer.]
- What are you guys doing!
- You got the humidifier part.
- Humidifier with automatic timer.
- Okay!
[Barely manages to escape the danger.]
What is this monitor called?
What do you call this monitor?
[Time fortunately runs out.]
[Barely manages to succeed
the candid camera mission.]
[Almost failed the mission no thanks
to Big-nosed Brother.]
- How could you have forgotten the timer?
- Timing and timer...
- I gave you one as a gift last year.
- What are you guys doing?
This isn't your fault, Lady Kim.
They wasted so much time.
- You did really well.
- But I didn't even do anything.
[I'm sorry, Lady Kim.]
As a team, you succeeded your mission.
[Kim Hye Ja's candid camera mission
is a success!]
[What did we succeed?]
- The truth is...
- We'll tell you down on our knees.
[Everyone gets down on their knees.]
[Me, too?]
[Our mother is so innocent
right to the very end.]
We all met about two hours before the day,
and we memorized all these answers.
We've already known all the answers.
Then why did you get it wrong?
- You were supposed to get it wrong.
- Here, have a seat.
- Have a seat here.
- Sit down here.
[It's time to fess up.]
- We already knew all the answers.
- We've studied the questions.
- That was our mission.
- Didn't you think we got the answers easily?
- Those were some hard questions.
- I thought you were all just very smart.
[We wish that was the case.]
- That was what we studied.
- We wrote cheat notes on our hands.
- They're all written on our hands.
- Oh my!
Oh my, it was a candid camera.
Our mission was to make sure
that you got all the answers wrong.
Then you succeeded.
We all succeeded together!
[Mother laughs it all off.]
But instead of getting frustrated,
you look so happy about it.
We only succeeded our mission
because it was your candid camera.
- You don't mind?
- It's fun!
[What a generous lady.]
- I had no idea.
- You didn't know?
- You didn't think it was weird?
- I didn't think it was weird at all.
I was just amazed at how good
everyone was.
But you almost got the
air conditioner question right.
Had you answered the correctly,
we would've failed the mission.
Really?
That would've been bad!
[Members are feeling worse because she's
truly happy they succeeded their mission.]
- You're making us feel even worse.
- She really is an angel.
I can't get upset over something like that.
[Angel Hye Ja.]
- This isn't something to be upset over.
- I made it more difficult on purpose.
[But...]
But I'm never going to let
you fool me again.
[So positive right up to the end.]
This is really fun.
Since you've succeeded your mission,
you can draw from one through nine.
[After wrapping up the candid mission,
it's time for another drawing.]
[Santa's lottery race-
All the numbers are added into the pool.]
[Oldest Running Man member,
Big-nose does the drawing.]
Pull it.
[Number one is chosen.]
- How could that even happen?
- Guys, the next number is most important.
Your face is beet red right now.
[Big-nose doesn't even know
what to say.]
Life can be that way.
[You can't always get what
you want in life.]
- That's what he's like.
- He just threw away 800,000 Won.
[It could've been 980,000 Won.]
We still have a chance.
- It's okay.
- Thank you.
I'll keep in touch from now on.
- Don't think about bothering her.
- Call your own parents once in a while.
- Call your own parents.
- I'll check in on you once in a while.
[Don't forget to call your own parents
once in a while.]
[Christmas is the time for
loving and caring for others.]
[Nine giant sized bells!]
It must be real flour.
- It must be real flour.
- What is it this time?
It's time for the final mission of the race.
Your final mission is,
'Yes, this is the sentence.'
I have a bad feeling about this.
Lady Kim, please step forward.
What do I have to do?
The rest of the members can take a spot
underneath the bells behind you.
Your final mission is very simple.
Lady Kim will determine the members' fates.
Can you please tell me what kind
of a cellphone you have?
- What type of a cellphone do you use?
- I use a smartphone.
- You use a smartphone?
- That's great.
- Why?
- Here's your mission.
Lady Kim must send a text message exactly
as what she is told within 30 seconds.
If she sends it accurately within that time,
then you avoid receiving the flour penalty.
But if she goes over the time limit
or if she gets the text inaccurately,
then you'll receive the flour penalty.
The thing you must remember is
you must utilize the exact spacing and
emoticons as you're instructed to.
If she gets it right on the first try,
then everyone will pass successfully.
Lady Kim's text will be shown on the screen
behind you as she writes.
[Lady Kim's text will be shown on the screen
behind them in real time.]
- Take your time, and you should be fine.
- You text often, do you not?
I'm very good at texting.
- We're all set!
- This is good.
[We'll be fine!]
This is really great.
[We have our faith in you!]
As mentioned before, she will be given
30 seconds per text message.
[Will she be able to accurately
text within those 30 seconds?]
- I have to get all the punctuations, too?
- Yes.
Comma, spacing, and everything else
has to be exactly the same.
I normally don't use things like that.
She's saying that she doesn't
like the use of emoticons.
Who out there uses all those
punctuations?
[But the rules of the game
must be followed.]
- You can just relax and take it easy.
- Please do not worry about us.
The final numerical drawing all
depends on the outcome of this mission.
- Lady Kim, fighting!
- Fighting!
Fighting!
Here's your first text message.
[Rudolph the reindeer's red nose
is a very shiny nose.]
[Spacing is very crucial!]
- Wow, she's fast.
- She's really good at it.
Is there a space between that?
There needs to be a space between
'Rudolph' and 'Reindeer.'
Lady Kim, there needs to be a space.
- I think she's going to get it.
- You left the period in there.
- You left the period.
- Hang on.
Why are there so many things?
You have to include the
smiley eyes in there.
Just be quiet!
- There she goes.
- She's very good at it.
[Round one is over in failure.]
Wow, 30 seconds goes by quick.
- She said she was good at it.
- I did do a good job.
I'd rather be under those bells.
I feel so awful about this.
It's okay, we're already covered in flour.
- Okay, I'll just do as I please.
- We don't mind being dumped on again.
We just need to succeed because
we need to draw for that money.
- Fighting!
- It's okay!
Maybe this is so that we can
experience a white Christmas.
[A special Christmas with the fall
of white flour snow.]
- It's okay.
- We're fine.
[Thank you for making me feel better.]
- We won't say anything anymore.
- Please take your time.
We're already covered in flour,
so don't worry about it.
- Don't worry.
- Okay.
- No need to be that relaxed about it though.
- Maybe stay a little bit nervous.
- Please don't forget the spacing.
- Don't feel pressured.
Maybe it'll be easier to do all that
after I finish writing it out first.
- Yes, you can do that afterward.
- No, that's even harder.
- That'll just make it harder.
- Just go in the order.
- Just do as you'd like.
- Okay.
- Do as you please.
- Here's your second text.
- Fighting!
- We're just getting started.
- Here's your text message.
[Round two.]
- I think this one is easier.
- Fighting!
[This may be easier!]
This one is easy.
[The perfect way to spend Christmas.]
- She's doing very well.
- We're going to get this one.
- She's got it!
- There's a space!
[Perfect use of spacing.]
She's got it.
- The space...
- Okay, but I need more time.
- The perfect way!
- You're almost there!
- There you go!
- Space and 'Way!'
[Now... all she has to write is, 'Way.']
[Please...]
I got it.
[Text message complete.]
[Final mission, 'This is the sentence'-
Successfully completed!]
[She did it!]
[Kim Hye Ja doesn't fail twice!]
You did such a great job.
[Mission success!
Yes, this is it.]
You did such a great job.
- Thank you, and I'm so sorry.
- No, not at all.
[Lady Kim, high-five!]
[Big-nose cuts in.]
[Left hanging.]
- Sorry.
- No, not at all.
You did such a great job.
[Kiddo Ha Ha wants to be
embraced by mommy Hye Ja.]
Can you come back on the
show every week?
Okay, then make me a
permanent member.
- Yes, wouldn't that be great?
- Congratulations on passing the mission.
[Succeeded the final mission
thanks to Big Sister Kim.]
There's a good chance that
we'll get a nine.
[Balls numbered from one and nine,
and everyone chants for a nine.]
We're all going to start screaming
if we do get a nine.
[Best case scenario would be
to get a nine.]
No thanks to Ji Suk Jin,
we only have 180,000 Won right now.
But I really want all of us
to come out winners.
Since there's a zero in there,
if you get it, you only get 180,000 Won.
Ready, it's the last ball!
[The final drawing which
Big Sister Kim will gets to draw.]
[Please... let it be a nine.]
- Anything above a five.
- Don't let it pressure you.
[Let's draw the ball!]
[Which numbered ball will it be?]
[Please let it be a nine!]
- Did you get the ball?
- Is it out yet?
- Why?
- What is it?
[Did you see the number?]
What is it?
What's the number?
- What's the number?
- What is it?
[Could that smile...
mean that it's a zero?]
- Okay... what if it's a nine?
- Is it a zero?
[Could it be a nine?]
- What is it?
- What is that smile for?
[What is the number?]
Six!
[The final number is a six!]
- That's 6.18 million Won.
- 6.18 million Won!
[Santa's lottery drawing-
Wins 6.18 million Won!]
- Wow, that's a lot of money.
- Are you really giving that money to us?
[Here's the cash.]
Really?
- Wow.
- This is for real.
- Should we take a look?
- Why don't you open one up?
- Wow, it's real.
- It's real money.
- Oh my, it's real.
- Oh my, thank you.
- 6.18 million Won!
[A truly shocking Christmas gift.]
In the name of Lady Kim Hye Ja
and our other guests
we will donate this money
to children in need!
[All of 6.18 million Won will be
donated to children in need.]
I hope you'll join us for a name tag
elimination game if you ever come back.
- I really had a wonderful time.
- Really?
I met such a wonderful group of people,
and I was so happy to be here.
It was a joyous and wonderful time,
and thank you so much for having me.
- Thank you, it was our honor.
- It truly was our honor.
Can you please say something for us?
Something that we've all wanted to hear.
- The saying, 'Yes, that's it.'
- Ah, that saying?
- As she rips off a name tag?
- Why don't you rip mine off as you say it?
[While ripping off Mr. Capable's name tag.]
- Okay.
- I can't believe this is happening!
- I feel nervous.
- But my mom's cooking isn't it.
- Here I go.
- Okay.
Yes, that's it.
['Yes, that's it.']
[Thank you to Kim Hye Ja, Lee Chun Hee, and
Kang Hye Jung for making Christmas brighter.]
[RM members and our guests donated
all the prize money to World Vision Center.]
[Merry Christmas to all our viewers.]
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Stronger than ever before...]
[The real monster.]
[2014's most exciting competition.]
[The fateful ball thrown
by the one and only.]
[Next Week-
The return of the Monster.]