Subtitles by DramaFever
[The hellish survival race starts now.]
[Do you want to stand on
the stage of dreams?]
[Then you must survive.]
[A visit from aristocratic top stars.]
[They have come to judge the audition.]
It's Ji Hoon!
[It's Rain!]
What are you doing here?
[Audition contestant number one- Rain]
Someone else is here.
Who is it?
[Audition contestant number two- Krystal]
How's your sister doing?
Didn't you have something with
Krystal's sister a while back?
- Who else is here?
- Where is he going?
[Audition contestant number three- Alex]
Is it Ki Bang?
[More and more guests
comes out to join them.]
[Audition contestant number four-
Kim Ki Bang]
[And one final contestant.]
[A visit from one of the royalties from
the world of television sitcoms.]
Hello!
[Amazed]
[Feels like a sudden and
unexpected fan meeting.]
[Audition contestant number five-
Park Young Kyu.]
[SBS Drama- Team 'My Lovable Girl'.]
[A romantic drama with a roster
of top notch actors on the cast list.]
[All the main characters of 'My Lovable Girl'
are here as today's guests.]
You will be challenged with a variety of
survival missions during this audition race.
The survivors of the missions will have
the chance to get on a final audition stage.
After each mission, one member from
the loser team will get kicked off the race.
It'll be Suk Jin from our team,
and who will it be from the other team?
That person will not move over to the
other team, but they're out of the race.
- Would they be going home?
- Do they have to go home?
- Are they eliminated for good?
- They can't participate at all?
- They're not being sent home, are they?
- They won't be on the camera at all?
It'll be completely unexpected.
Is it a working camera? They'll be
on some sort of a camera, right?
- Yes, it'll be something.
- Wait, Ki Bang really talks a lot.
- Yes, I'm the worst talker ever.
- Seriously.
Here's the prize that the winner
of the audition will be getting.
[Time to reveal the prize.]
[Audition winning prize- Golden mics.]
I grabbed a mic on my first birthday party.
Ki Bang really does talk a lot.
I don't get a lot of screen time on
the drama, so I have to get my time here.
- Just be quiet! What's wrong with you!
- Why won't you stop talking!
I was actually about to
say something myself.
It's nice that he's trying hard,
but there still should be a limit.
[This may be a very long day...]
[Both teams arrive at the first
mission location.]
Hey, it's an acupuncture mat.
Wow, I haven't seen
the acupuncture mat in a long time.
[Welcome to Health World.]
[Young Kyu is already starting
to tire himself out.]
Don't exhaust yourself out already.
- Why are you doing that to yourself?
- I'm just getting warmed up.
Are those pants from
a home shopping network?
- They're the waterproof pants, aren't they?
- Water just beads off the pants.
- No, they're not. Let's do our best.
- They're not the waterproof pants?
[Right from the warmup exercise,
he looks like a middle aged fighter.]
He wore his dress up pants
to Running Man.
- Here's your first battle.
- Okay.
- You're all familiar with the show?
- Yes.
- Each mission is a bit different.
- There's a different theme.
Your first course is a team battle.
All the members from each team
will stand in a line
and will be tied together to go through
the variety of courses in a relay form.
The team loses if the last member gets their
name tag eliminated by the other team.
- Is that understood?
- There are quite a few obstacles.
- You're the biggest obstacle!
- What did you say?
- You're an obstacle yourself!
- Seriously.
- Me?
- That's right!
- Everyone will now assume their position.
- Ugh, this is going to hurt.
It's not bad.
It's endurable.
This isn't too bad.
[An electric shock to the system.]
[This will ensure your health.]
We have to run on this.
[Running Man's first obstacle...]
[Jump horse- Rubber curtain.]
- We have to run as fast as we can.
- Rain is at the end.
We have to rip off their name tag
as soon as we get to them.
- I'll do my best not to get ripped off.
- Okay.
We'll jump under the net like this.
- We're not just going to walk over it?
- Why would they lay it out for us to do that?
It's been fun having you.
You're pretty good at the
variety show stuff.
[Krystal might have a 4-D personality.]
- Here we go with the first round.
- Okay.
Ready!
[Best out of three.]
Let's win this round.
[Team acupuncture mat spring- Start.]
[Onward to catch up to the other team.]
[Team Running Man's first obstacle-
Jump horse.]
[With everyone tied up together,
teamwork is of the essence.]
[Team MLG (My Lovable Girl) arrives
at their first obstacle.]
[Well-mannered Rain lifts up the net
to help his team members.]
[Team RM arrives at their second obstacle.]
[Must follow the lead of the person in front
so that they don't get tangled up.]
[Thanks to Rain and his manners, his
team passes through the first obstacle.]
[Team MLG has a reliable man
to bring up the rear.]
[Must run and catch up to
their opponent!]
They're almost caught up to us!
[If they get caught,
it's the end for the team!]
[Must win the battle against the
painful mat in order to win the course.]
[Team RM arrives at the net obstacle
by a very small lead.]
[Complete chaos.]
They're going to catch up to us!
[A little more speed from Team MLG,
and they can catch up to Team RM!]
We can do this!
[No obstacle will be able to stop us!]
[The teams are about to go
head to head for the very first time!]
Hurry!
[I've got you now!]
[Barely escapes the moment of danger.]
[Let's make our escape!]
[Picks up speed once again
with the help from Rain.]
- Hurry!
- Run!
[Runs as if being chased
by their loan sharks.]
[Team MLG is hot on their tail!]
Wait!
[Ha Ha gets caught from having taken
a different route from Jong Kook.]
Why aren't you coming!
[Team RM comes to a complete halt
in the rubber curtain obstacle.]
[Team RM is about to get caught!]
[Team MLG catches up to Team RM
at the rubber curtain obstacle.]
[Team MLG wins the first round of
the Acupuncture Mat Relay mission.]
- How was it, Krystal?
- That's not what I expected.
[Elder Young Kyu's battery
is about to run out.]
- My feet are getting really tired.
- It's not easy, is it?
- You did that twice!
- Whose fault was it?
- I told you to stop!
- You fell down the first time, too!
Keep your eye on the person in front
of you and just follow their lead!
[What beautiful teamwork of putting
the blame on everyone else.]
I got caught because you snapped
the rubber back in my face!
- I didn't snap anything!
- You pulled on it too hard!
[The person with the loudest voice
is the winner on this team.]
- Just admit that you made a mistake!
- You guys kept pushing too hard!
You have one vote for being
eliminated from the race.
Let's work better together.
I'm sorry, but I have to go get my hat.
I need to go get my hat
that I dropped over here.
[Tied up together as one
to pick up Jae Suk's hat.]
I need to get mine, too.
[Acupuncture mat relay- Round Two.]
I'm tired.
[Water?]
What are you doing, Young Kyu?
[Elder Young Kyu is re-hydrating himself.]
Can I try splashing some of this
water on your pants?
[Very curious about the waterproof
looking pants Young Kyu is wearing.]
Let me just do it right here.
I've seen these pants in a commercial.
- Let me try just a little.
- Go ahead.
[Completely waterproof!]
See?
I told you they're waterproof!
His pants are completely waterproof.
Look at that.
You can just shake it off.
[One shake and not a droplet
of water on his pants.]
Look at how clean his pants look!
[Not a drop of water on your pants!
Place your order now!]
I knew these were the pants.
- Okay, let's go.
- The score is, Team MLG 1: Team RM 0.
[Current score-
Team MLG 1: Team RM 0.]
- Get ready.
- Fighting!
[Starting off on the opposite ends
for the second round.]
Fighting!
[Both teams are full of energy.]
[Passing through the net obstacle.]
[Team MLG is about to enter
the rubber curtain obstacle.]
[Once again, Rain takes care of
his team from behind.]
[If we keep going at this pace,
then we can catch up to them!]
- Run!
- Hurry!
[Great plan of teamwork by lifting up
the net for one another.]
[Team RM also seems to have gotten
better at their teamwork skills.]
Who made such a wave of this mat?
[Must run before they're caught.]
[The body is caught on the net,
and is brought to a screeching halt.]
[Let's make our escape!]
[A new plan to hold up the net
for the person coming up behind them.]
- The bottoms of my feet are killing me.
- Slow down.
[Team MLG is keeping up the pace.]
[Hot on their trail!]
[Gary is caught on the net.]
[Giraffe is making sure to
check the health of his back.]
[How many laps has it been already?]
When is this ever going to end!
- There is no end to this game!
- This is a test of our endurance!
[It's all about endurance now.]
- I feel like this is never going to end.
- Let's just end this.
[Team RM is working hard
to catch up to Team MLG.]
Catch them!
[Quickly passes through the rubber curtain
thanks to Rain and his polite manners.]
[As soon as they get through the curtains...
Giraffe sticks his body through.]
[Only a three meter gap between
the two teams!]
[Let's go catch their tail!]
[Team RM finally catches up to Team MLG.]
Come on, you can't do that!
- No, you can't do this!
- Hurry up and do it!
[Giraffe raises his hands up to the sky
with some help from Rain.]
- Hurry up and do it!
- I got it!
[Team RM wins
the second round of the relay.]
Can we do the third round next week?
Let's take a little break.
I'm sorry, but let's get going.
We're not even tired yet.
- Okay, fine.
- No, we need a moment.
Young Kyu, are you crying?
- Young Kyu.
- Are you crying?
[I told you that I wanted to
take a little break...]
Why are you acting like that?
- Young Kyu, can I try it, too?
- We've already tried it.
- His pants are like a raincoat.
- They're the waterproof pants.
[His pants seems to be very popular today.]
- Are they coated with something?
- Are these pants the same?
Oh, maybe they're not.
- Sorry, I thought they were the same.
- What are you doing?
- He looks so pathetic now.
- Don't shake my pants.
No, don't do that.
Oh, I'm so sorry.
[Yoo Hyuk's simultaneous
shower of water and humiliation.]
- No, don't shake it.
- We've never seen anything like it.
- Ugh, seriously.
- Come on, I'll help you get up.
Wait, I'll do it when I'm ready.
[Can't you guys just leave me alone?]
[Final round of the acupuncture mat relay.]
It's hard to decide
who to eliminate at this point.
- No, it's not hard to decide.
- I feel like it's really tough to decide.
- It's not difficult to decide at all.
I feel like it's such a close call
that we're going to have to draw for it.
Let's just win the relay mission,
and we won't have to worry about it.
[Win the relay and there
would be nothing to worry about.]
- Okay, let's win this.
Fighting!
- I'm going to run faster this time, okay?
- Okay, run.
- Let's just get this over with.
- Let's just win this thing.
No need to draw this out any further.
This is the final round to
determine the winning team.
The loser team will have to
eliminate one member from the team
and once eliminated, that person
can no longer participate in the race.
Okay!
[Will they be the ones to catch,
or the ones to get caught?]
[Win this round...
and escape elimination!]
[Rain doesn't hesitate to sacrifice
himself for the sake of his team.]
- Grab it!
- Grab it and walk through it.
[Even though they have it figured out,
it's still very chaotic.]
Okay, open it up.
[Bodyguard Rain.]
We're almost there.
[Krystal is running hard enough to
make the bottoms of her feet sweat.]
- We're almost there.
- Grab it!
[Team MLG is very hot on Team RM's trail.]
We got this!
We have to hurry!
[Moment of imminent danger!]
[Team RM escapes danger by
the split of a hair.]
[Call us Speed Racers!]
We have to hurry!
[Must quickly pass through
the rubber curtain obstacle!]
[She's tangled up!]
[Team MLG succeeds in
catching up to Team RM.]
[IF Gary's name tag is ripped off,
then Team MLG wins!]
- We won!
- What did you guys do?
[Team MLG shows off their
great team working skills.]
- Young Kyu, we did it.
- Good job, Krystal.
Team MLG wins the first
team battle mission.
[Survival audition- Team battle.
Team MLG wins!]
- They're such an unlikely team.
- How could they have won?
- It doesn't make any sense to me.
- We shouldn't have allowed that small break.
Why are you sitting down again?
Why are you sitting down after one game?
Why don't you lay down for a bit?
- Why do you keep sitting down?
- I've seen this before in your drama.
As just mentioned, Team MLG won
the first survival audition mission.
One member from Team RM will now have
to be eliminated and kicked off the race.
Don't just automatically think
that person is going to be me.
You never know how it'll end up.
Think about this very carefully, Kwang Soo.
Why do you just assume that it'll be me?
- Can I pick for the whole team?
- Kwang Soo, you just pick.
[No need to even vote because
it's already a unanimous decision?]
- Ha Ha made a lot of mistakes.
- Okay, I'll give you that.
- We got caught because of you.
- But that was an unfair circumstance.
[Ha Ha (from his mistakes) vs
Suk Jin (for being the weakest link)]
- We got caught because of you.
- This is driving me crazy.
You need to think about this
very carefully.
[Time to cast their elimination votes.]
Okay.
- Yes, I know.
- No need to think too hard about it.
[A very precious vote to decide
who gets to stay and who gets to leave.]
We will now reveal the voting results for
the first elimination round of R-Pop race.
Let's not get mad about it because
we're all of the same team.
- No getting mad. I'll be fine with whatever.
- Let's all join our hands together.
I can sacrifice myself
for the sake of my team.
[The louder their voice is, the
more nervous they must be feeling.]
You have to know who was at fault
for our first round of defeat.
Ha Ha.
[One vote for Ha Ha's elimination.]
I think that's my handwriting.
One for Ha Ha.
[Maintaining a cool demeanor.]
- Thank you.
- Ha Ha's being cool about it.
I think we're going to have to wait and
see to find out what the results are.
Kim Jong Kook.
- Kim Jong Kook.
- Who voted him out?
- The handwriting is...
- What?
[Can guess who voted him out
without even needing to ask.]
- Just think about the race as a whole.
- This is so unfair!
As you can see from the tiny handwriting,
you can guess who wrote this, right?
- It really wasn't me.
- There better not be two votes.
- What? Is it me again?
- It really remains to be seen.
- AH AH.
- Who's 'Ah Ah?'
[No, it's Ha Ha.]
[Elimination vote result-
Ha Ha- 2; Kim Jong Kook- 1.]
[Ha Ha is in the lead with two votes.]
[Only three votes left to go.]
Okay, that's another one for Ha Ha.
I already have two votes?
Thank you.
- Wow, this is no joke.
- Who is it?
- Kim Jong Kook.
- I still don't have a vote yet!
[Elimination vote result-
Ha Ha- 2; Kim Jong Kook- 2.]
- None for me!
- This is unbelievable.
Come here!
[No matter what the vote may be for,
these two are the biggest suspects.]
[Only two more votes left to go.]
Okay, it's another one for Ha Ha.
Someone wrote that they're sorry,
but we don't need that.
- Was it you?
- Sorry, Ha Ha.
Ki Bang, you're getting into it.
It's Ha Ha, isn't it?
You have to keep going.
[Assistant MC is proving to be
quite useful.]
It's time for the last final vote.
You have to lower the noise level
when I start talking.
- You have to know when to be quiet.
- Yes, that's right.
[Elimination vote result-
Ha Ha- 3; Kim Jong Kook- 2.]
[Who will the last vote be for?]
[Ha Ha]
[Elimination vote result-
Ha Ha- 4; Kim Jong Kook- 2.]
[First person to be eliminated- Ha Ha]
- It really wasn't me! Why do you think that?
- Go away!
Is there another elimination round?
[One member will be eliminated
after each round of missions.]
- I'll be waiting for you.
- Why would you say that!
Why would you point me out?
It could be any one of us!
I thought one of you would
stand up for me.
Shall we go on to the next round
of missions?
[How does it feel to be eliminated?]
I really hope that everyone fails.
I wish I could lay down a pair
of scissors in their beds.
What are you doing?
- Why? What are you doing?
- I'm doing an interview!
- Really?
- Yes.
There's one person that I really
have a grudge against.
He's slightly heavy.
- What are you doing!
- I'm just trying to get by.
Can't you see that I'm trying
to do an interview?
I really hope that they'll come to
regret ever having eliminated me.
I really hope that they fail at
every single thing that they do.
[Korean National Athletic Center]
[Arrives at the second mission location.]
[The remaining survivors will now move onto
the second portion of the audition.]
Is this where we're going?
- Athletic center?
- That's a really nice athletic center.
- Look at the goal post.
- Are we playing volleyball?
- Are we playing basketball?
- Dong Hoon's really good at basketball.
[That's why you never should've
voted me out...]
[He's joined by Alex, who was
eliminated at the previous mission.]
If we just get sent home at the end without
getting the chance to do anything else...
- That's happened a few times.
- Seriously? That's happened before?
[What fate awaits these
eliminated contestants?]
This is the collaboration mission for
the 2014 R-Pop Star Race.
Just like the way it states,
it'll require help from other people
in order to successfully pass
the mission.
Three very special people have come
to help with this portion of the race.
Three commentators from the 2014
Incheon Asia Games are here to join us.
- Seriously?
- For real?
It's Im Oh Kyung!
[Handball- Im Oh Kyung.]
[The legendary player of
2004 Olympics in Athens.]
[From being a player to a coach-
Icon of Korean Women's Handball.]
[Badminton- Kim Dong Moon.]
[1996 and 2004-
Olympic gold medalist.]
[The pride of Korean badminton.]
- Seriously?
- It's been so long!
[Basketball- Woo Ji Won.]
[The master of three point shoots-
The founder of his moves on the court.]
[No explanations necessary for this
crowned prince of the basketball court!]
[The legends of the court sports
are here as their honorary guests!]
It's such an honor to have you all.
My name is Kim Oh Kyung, the commentator
for 2014 Incheon Asian Games.
My name is King Dong Moon, the
commentator for badminton competition.
This is my first time meeting them.
My name is Woo Ji Won, commentator
for 2014 Incheon Asian Games
as well as a commentator
for the SBS station.
- The crowned prince of the basketball court.
- He was amazing.
You're in such great shape.
- He still looks the same as ever.
- The crowned princess of the courts.
- Yes.
- And the magician of the nets.
[Magician of the nets.]
For your third mission,
it's a mix of sports and music.
Both teams will choose challenges
from these three sports.
- How do we play it?
- If you win two of the three...
then that team will win the mission
for being best out of three.
- How can we ever beat them?
- We're no longer professional players.
- But you were all professional players.
- But you're on a national league level.
When it comes to physique,
your body is a national league level.
Here's the first round
of your collaboration mission.
It's called, Dancing Goal Keeper.
While the selected members dance
in front of their goal posts
Im Oh Kyung will attempt to throw the ball
into the net once the music stops.
The team that blocks the most number
of balls wins the round.
- All five of you will be doing it.
- Then we'll be able to stop her.
- Then we'll be able to block her.
- We can block all of them, right?
- Okay, this is good.
- Your team can go first.
- Why don't you take the corner?
- Okay, I'll take the corner.
Are you sure you'll be able to
get around five goal keepers?
It would be easier if this ball was softer,
but this ball won't be easy to control.
But the goal posts are set
pretty wide apart.
- That's the only good thing.
- We have to keep dancing?
- Okay, let's start the first round!
- I have to score a lot of balls?
- You have to score as many as you can.
- Don't go easy on them.
[Dancing Goal Keeper-
Team RM- Start the music.]
- Can you stop playing Jong Kook's songs?
- Why?
His songs are so old!
[Unsatisfied]
[Perfectly in sync with one another.]
[Up the level of excitement.]
[Can't stand it.]
[This is so fun!]
Ugh, I can't stand seeing him like that!
Everybody dance!
Let's all have some fun.
[Music stop.]
[Time to start shooting!]
[Fly up like a butterfly...]
[Goal!]
[This is the signature shoot
of a legendary handball player.]
- Don't avoid the ball!
- I didn't avoid it.
[Their bodies automatically avoid the ball.]
- Why are you avoiding it?
- It's so scary!
- That's one.
- Don't avoid it, and just let it hit you.
I'm not going to avoid it.
[An ambush throw after a fake shoot.]
[Blocks it with his head?]
[No, not really...]
[Kwang Soo's black hole sucks
the ball into the goal instead.]
I didn't avoid the ball!
I didn't even move.
[Master Im Oh Kyung seems to be
enjoying herself immensely.]
I didn't avoid the ball!
I didn't even move.
You can't just stand still.
You have to block the ball!
[Third shoot]
[Smack dab into the Giraffe!]
Kwang Soo blocked that one.
[Blocked or slammed...]
[No matter,
one ball is successfully blocked.]
[No breaks between her throws.]
[Mr. Capable blocks it with his body.]
Show us your jump shot.
[Can I?]
What are you doing?
- Your goal is over there!
- There?
[Master Woo Ji Won fakes it by
pretending to throw a basketball at them.]
[Okay, no more fooling around.]
[A high speed shot.]
[His body automatically
recoils from the ball.]
- Stop avoiding the ball!
- Just don't even move from your spot.
You're starting to make her angry!
- You're getting her mad.
- Is there only one ball left to go?
One more to go.
We have to block this one.
You did good!
That's how you do it!
[That was my final gift to you.]
[Team RM successfully
blocks three shots.]
We blocked half.
[It's now Team MLG's turn.]
We should give her a shoulder massage.
[Offering shoulder massage service so
that she could make more goals?]
I only want Kwang Soo
to touch me.
- I said, I only want Kwang Soo to do it!
- Why?
- Because my daughter is a fan of his.
- Thank you!
[Dancing Goal Keeper-
Team MLG- Start the music.]
[Hot Summer- F(x)]
[Excited middle aged men dancing along
to the song by their youngest member.]
[Ki Bang's unidentifiable dance moves.]
[Huh?]
[Moving to the beat of his own drums,
and dances with the net.]
[Music stop]
[Time to start shooting.]
[Goal!]
[He thinks that he's a top spin.]
[Team MLG is off to a shaky start.]
- Nice start to the game!
- Keep your eyes on the ball.
- Seeing it from this end, it's no joke.
- How did we ever block her shots?
[Huh?]
[A gentle pass to Rain?]
Thank you.
[Her love for him as his fan weakens
even her fastest throws...]
- What was that?
- Why did you do that?
- My shoulder didn't fully rotate.
- That was so unfair.
[Explosion of envy.]
Can the opposing team
get out of here?
Thank you!
Can you throw it in
Park Young Kyu's direction?
[Clean as a sharp blade.]
- I was trying to block it in my own way.
- What were you doing?
- Just hold still.
- Hold still, and you can block it.
- How many do we have left?
- You have to block the rest to win.
[Only three balls left to go!
Block all the balls to win.]
[Ma'am... he says that
we have to block the rest...]
[You're the best!]
[In the midst of all that...]
[The ball that Ki Bang kicks away...
smacks Kwang Soo right in the face.]
I'm so sorry!
What was that?
[Giraffe definitely has the god of
the variety world looking out for him.]
- Why did you do that?
- What was that all about?
- You need better sportsmanship!
- I'm sorry.
His teammates don't even care that
he just got slammed in the face.
- His face is there for the balls to smack.
- He just got smacked in the face.
- That's what his face is there for.
- Fighting!
[Time for the mission to resume.]
You have to make the rest of the goals.
Raise your arms up like this.
[Yoo-hole is predictable as always.]
[The scaredy cat is pushed off
into the corner.]
- He needs to stand in the corner.
- We have one shot left.
Im Oh Kyung!
[If she scores, then it's Team RM's win.
Block the ball, and it's a tie.]
[Flies into the air!]
[Just then, Rain jumps out to the front.]
[Will he be able to block it?]
[Rain misses the ball,
and the ball makes it into the net!]
[So disappointing...]
Let's win in the badminton
and the basketball games.
Thus, the first round's victory
goes to Team RM.
[First round's victory in the mission with
Master Im Oh Kyung goes to Team RM.]
We will now start the second round with
Woo Ji Won's basketball game.
Time for the basketball mission.
The next mission is,
Filial Chair First Syllable Quiz.
You'll listen to the first line of the song
that Woo Ji Won will be singing
and if you correctly guess the song,
then scoot up in the chair and grab the flag.
- What does it have to do with basketball?
- If the answer is guessed correctly...
then Woo Ji Won will throw a three point
shot in place of the winning team.
Then the team with the most three point
shots thrown by Woo Jin Won wins the game.
[More questions that are correctly answered,
then more chances for a three point shot.]
I think we'll be familiar with
most of the songs.
[Correctly guess
Woo Ji Won's favorite songs!]
[First song]
First...
I know this one!
[Kwang Soo vs Jae Suk.]
[Chance for Kwang Soo of
Team RM to guess the answer.]
I've sang this song
while playing the piano.
- Yes, that's the one!
- Yoo Jae Ha's 'Because I love you!'
First, I felt the way you
gazed at me...
First...
[Could this be the same song?]
No, that's not right.
- Listen to it carefully, and try again.
- I don't think I know this song.
[What could it be?]
- First?
- I have no idea.
Okay, I'll sing it better this time.
[More accurate singing?]
First.
[Huh?]
[The chance goes to Rain.]
'The final battle.'
First, can...
- Yes, that's the one!
- I think he's right.
[The theme song from the legendary
basketball drama, 'The Final Battle'.]
First can never be predicted...
[Could it be?]
[An irrefutable singer!
Rain's accurate listening ears!]
His tone was way too flat!
[Strongly disputes it.]
'First time when we met...'
That's what it sounded like!
[Could he be tone deaf?]
- You can't tell by the way he sang it.
- That's the way I always heard it.
I'm going to have to think
outside the box.
- You have to listen very carefully.
- Please sing it accurately.
- Please get the tone correctly.
- Ready.
- Oh...
- What was that?
What was that?
- Oh...
- What was that?
Jong Kook!
[Rain succeeds in blocking Team RM.]
'Last night's story' by Fire Truck!
Last night, I really hated you.
- No, that's not it!
- 'Last night, my dad...'
['Last night's story' by Fire Truck.]
[Wrong]
Okay, listen very carefully.
[One more time.]
[Tiger on the move.]
Ugh, seriously!
[Will Kkuk have the correct answer?]
- What's your answer?
- 'Even though I loved you' by Kim Kwang Suk.
- No, that's not it.
- 'All day yesterday...'
- 'It kept raining...'
- That's a totally different tone.
- What's wrong with that?
- You can't sing it like that!
[Forcing out the tune.]
- One more time.
- 'All day yesterday...'
- 'It kept raining...'
- He really sounds like a singer!
[Could this be the same song?]
- It sounds so sweet!
- That's not the right one?
[Excuse me,
but that's the wrong song.]
Why did you make me sing it again?
I thought I had it right!
[Kkuk sang it with all the emotions
that he had... just to get it wrong.]
- Seriously.
- Are you dumb?
- You almost had me fooled.
- You were really getting into it.
- Okay, here's a good hint.
- Listen very carefully.
[A top notch hint.]
[Everyone seems to have figured it out now.]
[Too much rushing around.]
[Complete chaos.]
[Krystal totally blocks off Kwang Soo.]
[While Krystal blocks everyone off
with the use of her body...]
[Rain grabs the flag.]
I have to do this one.
- It's my Jin Young's song.
- Park Jin Young.
- 'Behind you!'
- Sing it.
- He doesn't know the song either.
- 'Did you know that it rained last night?'
He's a good singer.
['Behind you' by Park Jin Young.]
[Could this song be the correct answer?]
[Correct answer.]
[Team MLG correctly answers
another three pointer!]
- Great job, Krystal!
- You did good!
[Krystal gave them this opportunity.]
We got the answer thanks to Krystal.
[Next song...]
'One man' by Kim Jong Kook?
[Team RM correctly guesses the song.]
'I got tired from waiting...'
[Team MLG correctly guesses
another answer.]
[A total of three shots for Team MLG,
and one three pointer for Team RM.]
[One chance for Team RM.]
I love you!
- Don't say things like that!
- Woo Ji Won!
[Will the master of
three point shots make it?]
[Please...]
[Success!]
[Team RM succeeds their shot,
but Team MLG has three chances.]
How about he shoots without
jumping from his stance?
- Stop being ridiculous.
- He should be able to do that, right?
[First attempt for Team MLG.]
[Even without jumping...
he makes a clean goal.]
[That's our Woo Jin Won!]
- Okay, we're tied.
- We just need one more shot.
[If he makes this shot,
then Team MLG wins the mission.]
[Bounces off the rim,
and misses the shot.]
Why are you purposely missing
the shot?
- He was trying to make a clean shot.
- I shot it too high.
[Current score- 1:1.
Final chance at making the shot.]
[Makes this shot,
and Team MLG wins the mission.]
[Please make the shot...]
[No!]
[The fate of the two teams
lies in Woo Ji Won's hands.]
I'll make this shot.
[A perfectly clean shot.]
If you say that you'll make it,
then do you always make it?
[Woo Ji Won still has it.]
- Wow, you really are amazing.
- He willed it, so he made it in.
Wow, he and Im Oh Kyung both really
are national league champions.
Thus, Team MLG wins!
[Team MLG wins the collaboration mission.]
Okay, it's not time for the final mission,
the badminton mission.
There are four cans stacked up
together on the table.
He says that he'll be able to knock
the cans over with his shot.
- Really?
- Wow, is that even possible?
- Is that really even be possible?
- How is he going to do that?
[Smashes it... and a direct hit!]
[A direct smashing shot without
even the slightest mistake.]
- That was unbelievable!
- Amazing!
[A true legend.]
[Accuracy and power at
the speed of 200km an hour.]
[This is what brought the legendary
70 wins in a row for our country.]
Amazing!
Even I was surprised by that.
- Look , this is dented.
- He dented the can.
[The power of his shot even dents the can.]
The mission that you'll be doing with
Kim Dong Moon is, 1:5 badminton.
The team that scores the most points
wins the mission.
Okay, we will give it our best shot.
- We can do this.
- Let's give it our best effort.
One, two, three.
Fighting!
Ready!
- Are you all ready?
- Start!
[1:5 badminton-
Kim Dong Moon vs Team MLG- Start.]
[Legendary Kim Dong Moon plays
his five opponents with ease.]
[Here's my chance!]
[Rain's strong smashing is a success!]
[Team MLG- 1 vs Kim Dong Moon- 0.]
[Team MLG's ace-
All-around athlete, Rain.]
You took him by surprise.
[Not bad...]
[Second of the five serves.]
[Another smash,
and Kim Dong Moon returns it.]
[Grabs his chance.]
[Unfortunately gets caught on the net.]
Everyone always touches their racket when
they miss a shot in badminton.
People always seem to do that
when they miss their shot.
[Current score- 1:1.
Third serve.]
[Elder Young Kyu fails to
receive the serve.]
No one can even say anything
to Young Kyu.
[That's the power of being the elder.]
[[Team MLG- 1 vs Kim Dong Moon- 2.
Fourth serve.]
[Krystal successfully receives the serve.]
[Young Kyu's shuttlecock.]
Are you okay?
- You're going too far.
- You know it doesn't hurt that bad.
[Big brother loses his status
with his second mistake in a row.]
His hit to the forehead was as
precise as when he hit the cans.
I shot it directly over to you so
that it would be easier for you to hit back.
[Team MLG- 1 vs Kim Dong Moon- 3.]
[Team MLG's last serve-
Kim Dong Moon's long high serve.]
[Jae Suk returns the serve.]
[Ki Bang vs Kim Dong Moon.
A tight relay.]
[Ah...]
[The ender of Team MLG's game-
Game finisher, Elder Young Kyu.]
[Final score-
Team MLG- 1 vs Kim Dong Moon- 4.]
[Team RM's turn.]
- Who's going to stand in the back?
- Do you want to stand here, Kwang Soo?
- We just need to get two points.
- Getting even one point is tough.
[1:5 badminton-
Win against Kim Dong Moon- Start.]
Good, nice job.
[The shuttlecocks gets caught
in Jong Kook's muscle.]
- What are you doing, Jong Kook?
- I thought it was a bird.
- Don't stand there.
- What are you doing?
[Mommy muscle bird cuddles
the shuttlecock.]
- You stand in the back, Jong Kook.
- No, you go in the back, I'm staying here.
Suk Jin's starting to move forward.
He wants you to go to the back.
[Team RM- 0 vs Kim Dong Moon- 1.]
Gary!
Now, Suk Jin!
- It goes to the back more.
- Mine!
- Ji Hyo!
- Okay, good.
[Kkuk... and it's over.]
[I can relate...]
[Muscly Kkuk is pushed off to the back.]
This is the tougher spot to be!
It's more difficult here.
[Muscle black hole is born.
Team RM- 0 vs Kim Dong Moon- 2.]
I can't hit this!
I won't be able to receive it.
[Serves it towards the muscly black hole.]
[Team RM is in perfect sync
with one another.]
[Sends it back towards Kkuk...
and as always.]
- Go off to the back.
- Don't even play!
- I need to stand in the sideline.
- Just don't even do anything.
- I should stand in the sideline.
- How can you be this bad?
- I didn't know Jong Kook could be like that.
- Come stand over here, Jong Kook.
[Even Mr. Capable is a black hole
when it comes to badminton.]
[Unexpected role of the muscly black hole-
Team RM- 0 vs Kim Dong Moon- 3.]
[If it keeps going at this rate,
then it'll be another win for Team MLG.]
Okay, there you go!
[Ace Blank Ji makes her move.]
[The shuttlecock drops...]
[He receives it...]
[But it was too short!]
[That's our Ace Blank Ji!]
[Ace saves her team from danger!]
Don't get too happy about it.
[Team RM- 1 vs Kim Dong Moon- 3.]
[If Team RM scores another one,
then Team MLG loses.]
Can you tell us where you're
going to hit it?
- Yes, Kim Jong Kook is a nice choice.
- Jong Kook?
[Muscly black hole is chosen.]
[Collaboration mission-
Team RM vs Team MLG.]
[The moment that'll decide
the fate of the two teams.]
[Mr. Gary succeeds in his attack.]
[Celebrating as if he just won
the gold medal in the Asian Games.]
We won!
[Collaboration mission-
Team MLG- 1 vs Team RM- 2. Win!]
You are undoubtedly
the national representatives.
It was truly an honor.
We look forward to the amazing games
that will be played at the Asian Games
that you'll all be leading
and commentating on. Thank you!
[We pray for victory for the remaining
athletes in the 2014 Asian Games.]
You all did great.
- It's now time for another vote.
- Is there really a need for that?
There's nothing we can do about this,
so I hope that you'll understand.
[Team MLG must eliminate a member of
their own team from having been defeated.]
I didn't even have to think about it.
- Yes, I'll take the vote.
- Okay.
[Time to announce the results.]
In a woman's handwriting...
Oh my... one vote for
Park Young Kyu.
[Vote for elimination-
Park Young Kyu- 1.]
You just look so exhausted.
[Vote for elimination-
Park Young Kyu- 1.]
It's another vote for
Park Young Kyu.
[Vote for elimination-
Park Young Kyu- 2.]
[Feels bad for what's going on.]
Here's the third vote.
Wow, it's a different result this time.
- Who is it for?
- One vote for Kim Ki Bang.
[Vote for elimination-
Park Young Kyu- 2 vs Kim Ki Bang- 1.]
- Third vote.
- Who is it?
[Can't be me again, can it?]
I didn't see the name,
but I did see 'Mr.'
- It could be 'Mr. Yoo Jae Suk.'
- I think Park Young Kyu wrote down Ki Bang.
[Big brother's unexpected turn.]
- We can't argue who it is anymore.
- I'm sorry, but there's no denying.
[No more need for secrets during the voting.]
[A group apology.]
I had no idea it would turn out this way.
- I just wanted him to get some rest.
- That was my intention as well.
[Vote for elimination-
Park Young Kyu- 4 vs Kim Ki Bang- 1.]
[Young Kyu, Ha Ha and Alex-
What fate awaits these eliminated members?]
Oh my, look who it is.
We got a little too much rest.
I came on the show to show people what
I can do, but I got booted off right away.
I can't believe I got voted off right away.
[I've missed you guys!]
[One more addition to the party.]
The remaining survivors will soon be
arriving for their final audition.
The three of you have been eliminated
from the audition rounds.
But this isn't the end for you.
[But this isn't the end!]
[What secret mission awaits
eliminated contestants?]
[Final mission location-
Judo club in Gyunggi-do.]
[What is the final survival mission
that will be taking place at this location?]
- What is this?
- Isn't this the K-Pop music stage?
[Entering the brightly lit audition stage
like that of K-Pop Star.]
[Even a judging platform has
been prepared.]
The final mission for
the 2014 R-Pop Star still remains.
The final mission is...
a real audition.
[Real audition]
Is a real audition.
We have assigned a specific song
and performance to each team.
You will have to utilize the song given to
give us your most impressive performance.
[Team MLG-
Michael Jackson's 'Billy Jean']
[The King of Pop, Michael Jackson.
The legendary song from his Thriller album.]
[Team RM-
'One Night Only' from Dream Girls OST]
[The theme song with soul and rhythm
from 2007 hit film, Dream Girls.]
We will now welcome the panel of judges
who will be judging your performance.
Let's welcome our panel of judges!
[The panel of judges who will determine
the fate of these two teams...]
[The eliminated members.]
[The past eliminated contestants
will be their panel of judges.]
The surviving audition contestants will soon
be arriving here for their final mission.
- What are we going to be doing?
- Seriously?
[They will become the panel of judges.]
[This is the chance to get
their revenge.]
I will show them what it means
to be truly unscrupulous.
[You didn't know that this
was going to happen, did you?]
Hello, Sirs!
Please take good care of us.
There will be no fairness, or justice.
That's because there's a lot of sarcasm
and grudge built up inside us.
We're all hurt and disappointed
by the way you've treated us.
Even though we acted cool about it,
the rest of you up on the stage right now
I hope that you'll be understanding even if
we end up saying a few hurtful words.
[Wait in anticipation for what may come
your way from this panel of judges.]
[Will these contestants be able to
impress this panel of judges?]
[Team MLG's dressing room.]
- How about 'Lend it to us?'
- Sure, that's a good line.
[From 'Billy Jean' to 'Lend it to us'
Starting off with changing out the lyrics.]
[Ki Bang is getting into the groove of it.]
Don't give Ki Bang too many
lines to sing.
[Falling perfectly in line.]
'Lend me your heart...'
Something like that.
- 'My heart' Ow!
- You're not the lead singer.
[Lusting after being the lead singer
with every chance that he gets.]
I don't know why I keep wanting
to be the lead.
- 'Lend me your heart...'
- We have to be sexy with it.
- How?
- 'Lend me your heart...'
'As a collateral.'
Something like that.
- 'Lend me your unsecured heart...'
- 'Without any interest!'
There you go.
That's just what I mean.
[The lyrics are starting to flow along.]
Lend me your unsecured heart,
without interest as a collateral.
- 'Can't you trust me?'
- There it is!
[Satisfaction]
[Team RM.]
[Panel of judges are coming by
to check on their progress.]
- How are things going?
- Yes, it's going well.
Just because you try hard
doesn't mean that it'll work.
I'll give it my best.
Hey, Kwang Soo.
We're finally starting to
get through to them.
We're supposed to look like women.
[Gary plus a wig = Visual shock]
- This is making me feel dizzy.
- That wig looks perfect on you.
I can't find any wigs
that look good on me.
I think this one looks great on you.
[Giving us so much to anticipate for
no matter which wig he puts on.]
- That's the one.
- You look like a middle aged woman.
I wasn't too happy about it earlier,
but I like being in this position now.
- Hello.
- Hello, welcome.
Hello, judges.
This team isn't as polite.
Kwang Soo gave us a grand bow.
He gave us a grand bow and
wished us a bountiful new year.
[Immediate bow down to the ground.]
- Hello, Sir.
- Okay, that's enough.
- Okay, we heard you.
- Yes, Sir!
[Winning the favor from this panel of
judges is the key to winning the audition.]
- We will give it our best shot!
- Okay, we heard you.
[I will endure through this.]
I said, I heard you.
We will see you later.
[Completely focused on preparing for
the show even in the midst of all this.]
Ji Hoon's working so hard at it.
He's not even saying goodbye to us.
- We'll see you all later.
- Have a great day!
- Bye, see you.
- Good luck.
[The three eliminated contestants have
been reborn as the panel of judges.]
[Which team will move their hearts to
take home the golden mics?]
[Time over]
The final audition stage of
the 2014 R-Pop Star.
The panel of judges will now tell us
what they will be looking for.
I'm so happy and impressed by the fact that
they were able to do this within an hour.
I was impressed as a judge,
but that's just a feeling of emotion.
[Judging and emotions are
two completely different things.]
The important thing is that my judging will
be done fairly, accurately, and seriously.
Team RM will perform first.
Team RM, please come up
on the stage!
['One Night Only.'
How did they transform the song?]
[Team RM reveals themselves through
the mist of the beautiful lights.]
[All eyes are on Team RM
as the beautiful melody begins.]
To all our Running Man fans in the world
who constantly cheered us on...
We dedicate this song to you.
[What's going on behind Blank Ji?]
[Visual shock.]
The first time we felt the cheer
and the shouts from our fans...
It made us forget all about the pain
from our pasts.
We'll forever be the global Running Man.
- For the love...
- That we received from all our fans!
Korean sister,
Asian sister.
- We will forever remain.
- Thank you, thank you!
- Thank you!
- Asian sister, to everyone in the world!
Korean sister,
Asian sister.
- We will forever remain.
- Thank you, thank you!
- Thank you!
- Asian sister, to everyone in the world!
[Unable to get over their shock.]
- Forever...
- Forever and always...
[Rebirth of Dream Girls to Running Girls?]
[Big-nose and Gary misses their timing.]
[Dance moves that imitates
the members running.]
[To the other side. Running Girls
are keeping up with the moves.]
[Time for individual dance moves
to the beat of the music.]
[Miss Gary's scarecrow dance.]
[Miss Big-nose's swim dance.]
[Kkuk's cutesy muscle dance.]
[Running Girls miss the beat to
the chorus from all their dancing.]
[Miss Giraffe is the latest of them all.]
- Thank you!
- Asian sister, to everyone in the world!
Korean sister, Asian sister,
forever and always!
- Just like this forever!
- Forever and always!
[Their grateful hearts to the fans
to the beat of the rhythm.]
[Screaming out at the tops of their lungs.]
[Time for a big ending.]
[We are DNA.]
[A standing ovation from the judges.]
Wow!
- Thank you!
[Running Girls' amazing performance
complete with singing and dancing.]
Thank you!
- We want to make our comeback.
- Can you not flex your arms?
- Your biceps are really unnerving.
- Why?
[His biceps are the size of
other people's thighs.]
You worked so hard to get prepped with your
singing and everything for the past hour.
Kwang Soo makes for an
unexpectedly attractive woman.
Thank you.
- I have always been a huge fan of yours.
- Thank you!
I forgot what I was going to say
because I was too busy laughing.
- It was very entertaining.
- Thank you.
As for your score...
it may not have anything to do
with the entertainment factor.
- But you can't do that.
- That has to remain a factor in scoring.
- That will be all.
- Thank you!
[Time for final comments from Ha Ha.]
[Team RM eliminated Ha Ha
after their first mission.]
- Are you kidding me right now?
- Excuse me?
What do you think you're
doing right now?
- What was that?
- Why?
We worked really hard on it.
- What is it that you didn't like about it?
- Are you crying?
[Giraffe is starting to tear up.]
- He's tearing up again.
- He cries a lot.
Stop crying!
Do you admit that your performance
lacked practice?
Lee Kwang Soo even forgot his lyrics
a time or two, isn't that correct?
You ran over in a rush because
you were too busy dancing.
[Kwang Soo misses his beat from having
been too engrossed in his dancing.]
[A severe punishment.]
Even though Kwang Soo made some mistakes,
it still showed your efforts and hard work.
I was very impressed by your performance,
and I enjoyed it. Thank you.
- Thank you!
[Was Team RM able to
move the judges' hearts?]
It is now time for Team MLG's performance.
Please welcome Team MLG
onto the stage.
Jae Suk's mother is here.
Are you all ready?
Then let's get started!
Cue the music!
[Original song- 'Billy Jean'.
How did they transform the song?]
[Impressive entrance.]
[An explosion of dance moves.]
- Wow, it's a stiff competition already.
- Come on, that's cheating.
[Jae Suk and Ki Bang Duo
are dancing along to Rain's moves.]
[Dance moves that are reminiscent
of Michael Jackson's moves.]
[World star's impressive dance moves.]
I got to get some rare rest at home,
so comfortably and peacefully.
But then a sudden thought
came into my head.
[Judge Ha Ha gets into the groove
and starts dancing himself.]
That I should film a drama.
A good drama.
Kim Ki Bang!
[Kim Ki Bang, come on!]
You need a female actress?
Or is it me that you need?
[He must've gotten the lyrics wrong.]
Here she is right here!
Let's have our angel join our throng!
She is watching us!
This is our chance!
Lend us your heart!
As a collateral,
and without any interest.
[Impressive play of lyrics.]
Don't you trust me?
[Even appropriate acting
thrown into the mix!]
Don't you trust me!
I was walking down the street
when I saw him approaching.
I saw such handsome men,
and I don't know what to do.
A Grasshopper, an Ape,
and a Flower boy.
- They're too good.
- They're very good.
- They're all coming at me!
- I came because I needed you!
And I'm waiting right here for you!
She is finally here,
she is finally here!
[He forgot the lyrics again!]
Lend me your heart.
As a collateral, and without any interest.
Don't you trust me?
[The support of this duo.]
[Rain and Krystal's adorable couple dance.]
[Krystal and Rain take their leave
off the stage...]
[Only the Duo still remains on stage.]
[An extremely rare performance.]
[An explosion of impromptu ad-libbing.]
Lend it to me.
[Another standing ovation.]
Bravo!
- Bravo!
- Thank you.
[A perfectly executed performance
of dancing and singing.]
Team MLG, are you sure that you came
up with this in just an hour?
Are you sure that you didn't have this
already prepared at home?
No, we didn't.
I love how the lyrics were transformed.
I really liked the line, 'Lend me your heart
as a collateral, and free of interest.'
I was really impressed by how well everyone
just fit into the performance together.
I can't believe that you were able to
put all that together within an hour.
- I was very impressed, thank you.
- Thank you.
I highly respect you.
Even though I didn't like getting eliminated,
I'm thankful that it happened.
Because it makes me think that
had I been a part of the show
I would've broken up the perfect
harmony that the four of you had.
It was that perfect!
Don't you think that
you're being too biased?
- You're seriously being too biased!
- No, I'm not!
- You're seriously being really biased.
- I'm not finished talking yet.
[You have to let me finish
talking first.]
I'm not done yet!
Kim Ki Bang and Yoo Jae Suk's hard efforts
to be such perfect harmonious duo...
I really am extremely impressed,
and thank you for all your hard work!
- Thank you!
- Thank you.
Judge Ha Ha will start by revealing
his score for the teams.
Score for Team MLG?
My score for Team MLG is...
[What is Ha Ha's score for Team MLG?]
[A perfect score!]
Is it out of 200?
[A score to set Team RM on edge.]
- Is it out of 200?
- Did you just give us a perfect score?
[A tough to beat perfect score.]
- Thank you!
- How can this even be?
My score is...
[Score from Judge Young Kyu.]
[Impressive 95 points.]
My score for Team MLG is...
[What will Alex give them?]
[Hoping for even one extra point
in their score.]
[Team MLG- A total of 280 points.]
- Thank you.
- Is that out of 300 points?
[Time to reveal the score for Team RM.]
My score is...
[What will their former teammate,
Ha Ha give then as their score?]
[One point shy of a perfect score.]
I was very generous with my scoring.
My score is...
[Judge Young Kyu's score please...]
[Not a bad score of 92 points.]
[Team RM will win as long as
Alex's score is above 90 points.]
90 points or more, and we win.
[It all comes down to Alex's score.]
I guess it all comes down to my judging.
Thank you to both the teams.
My score is...
[What will Alex give them as their score?]
[90 points or above,
then it's Team RM's win.]
[88 points or below,
then it's Team MLG's win.]
[Who will be the ultimate winner
of the audition?]
[Team MLG- 280 points vs
Team RM- 279 points.]
[Team MLG is the final winner!]
[An unbelievably unexpected event
will soon come your way.]
[Happy as if they had just won
the real audition.]
I feel like I won a real audition.
[Crying by himself in the corner.]
[Giraffe is crying again in the corner
out of disappointment.]
The final winner of the R-Pop audition is,
Team MLG. Congratulations.
[2014 survival audition winner-
Team My Lovable Girl.]
This isn't the end.
[This isn't the end!]
Before the winner's ceremony,
the winning team must...
Select one of the judges to help train them
to become the next top musical star.
Even the judges weren't aware of this.
But once one of the judges are selected
then the remaining two will
have to face their punishment.
- What did you say?
- Please reveal the punishment!
[Giant sized flour filled balloons.]
That's not even right!
- I like this.
- Excuse me.
- Remember I just gave you a perfect score.
- Who are you again?
- I gave your team a perfect score.
- What did you say?
- At the count of three...
- We'll shout out our answer.
The two non-chosen judges will have to
face their punishment.
- Okay, one...
- Please don't do this!
Two!
- Seriously!
- Three!
[Just who... will Team MLG choose?]
- Ha Ha!
[Flour as white as freshly fallen snow.]
Alex.
The time that I've spent with you today
has been most joyous and enjoyable.
Thank you very much!
Park Young Kyu!
Subtitles by DramaFever
Please allow us to marry.
[Nation's fresh faced beauty,
Shin Min Ah is here.]
- Isn't that her husband?
- I oppose!
- I like him.
- I oppose this marriage!
[Find this beautiful bride-to-be's
husband!]
[Sweet newlywed life with this beauty.]
[When will we ever marry?]
- What are you doing?
- Are you trying to deceive me?
[Next week on Running Man-
October Bride.]